♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO THE FINAL
EPISODE OF "SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN
DEL SUR: BLOOD VS. WATER."
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
WE'RE GOING TO BE LIVE ALL
NIGHT.
FIRST WE HAVE OUR TWO-HOUR
FINALE.
THEN WE HAVE OUR LIVE REUNION
SHOW WHERE WE BRING BACK ALL THE
PLAYERS TO TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING
THAT WENT DOWN OVER THE 39 DAYS.
AND I'D LOVE FOR I TO BE A PART
OF THE SHOW TONIGHT.
YOU CAN TWEET YOUR QUESTIONS OR
YOUR COMMENTS TO
ME@JEFFPROEB.TWITTER.
HASHTAG IS SURVIVOR FINALE SO WE
CAN FIND IT IN CASE WE DECIDE TO
TIEWZ ON THE SHOW.
WE STARTED WITH 18 PLAYERS AND
WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE.
KEITH, MISSY, BAYLOR, JACLYN,
AND NATALIE.
IT IS TIME TO FIND OUT WHO WILL
TAKE HOME THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION DOLLAR
PRIZE.
I'M GOING TO BE WATCHING WITH
ALL OF MY FRIENDS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
500 OF MY CLOSEST FRIENDS.
I HOPE YOU'LL BE WATCHING WITH
YOUR FRIENDS AND YOUR FAMILY
BECAUSE WE ALL HAVE ONE THING IN
COMMON-- WE LOVE "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: 35 DAYS AGO, NINE
PAIRS OF LOVED ONES WERE DROPPED
IN THE JUNGLES OF NICARAGUA TO
BEGIN THE ADVENTURE OF A
LIFETIME AFFECT.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN
DEL SUR: BLOOD VS. WATER" SUR.
BUT THEY WERE QUICKLY PULLED
APART.
SAY YOUR GOODS.
AND IN A NEW TWIST-- YOU'RE
COMPETING AGAINST YOUR WIFE.
LOVED ONES WERE FORCED TO BATTLE
AGAINST EACH OTHER FOR REWARD,
WITH THE LOSER HEADED TO EXILE
ISLAND.
AT COYOPA, WHILE THE MAJORITY OF
THE TRIBE WAS GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER--
>> WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME.
>> WESTLAND.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> Jeff: FORMER PROFESSIONAL
BASEBALL PLAYER JON ROCKER WAS
HIDING FROM HIS PAST.
THE ONE THING COYOPA HAD IN
COMMON--
>> THIS ISN'T IT.
>> Jeff: THEY COULDN'T WIN A
CHALLENGE.
HUNAHPU WINS FOR THE THIRD
STRAIGHT TIME.
WHEN THEY THOUGHT IT COULDN'T
GET ANY WORSE.
>> WHY DON'T YOU SAY SOMETHING
HOMOPHOBIC OR RACIST LIKE YOU
DID IN YOUR PAST.
>> Jeff: THEY HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
>> IF YOU WERE A MAN I'D KNOCK
YOUR TEETH OUT.
>> Jeff: FOR HUNAHPU-- WINNING
OF THE ONLY THING THEY COULD DO
RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU DON'T
HAVE MY BACK.
>> Jeff: THEY ARGUED.
>> YOU'RE WAY TOO EMOTIONAL
ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW, JEREMY.
>> GET YOUR BOARD, MAN, GET YOUR
BOARD OUT.
>> Jeff: THEY WASTED THEIR
FOOD.
>> WE'RE DOWN TO JUST, LIKE, A
HAND FULL OF RICE.
>> Jeff: THEY LOST THEIR
FLINT.
>> OH, GREAT.
>> DO YOU NEED A FLINT TO START
A FIRE?
>> IT HELPS.
>> Jeff: AND EVENTUALLY LOST
THEIR ENTIRE CAMP.
HERE'S WHAT I WANT-- YOUR TARP,
YOUR HAMMOCK, YOUR BEDROLL, THE
PILLOWS, THE BLANKETS.
YOU ARE STARTING OVER.
FOR THIS SEASON'S CASTAWAYS WAS
THE ONLY THING MORE DIFFICULT
THAN SURVIVING--
>> DREW VOTED OIT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL--
>> OH, MY GOD GLFS PLAYING
AGAINST THEIR LOVED ONES.
>> WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE GOOD.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: THIS IS ONE OF THE
LAYERS OF THIS GAME.
IT'S YOUR WIFE, YOUR SISTER,
YOUR BROTHER.
IT IS BLOOD.
ONE BY ONE--
>> WELL PLAYED.
>> Jeff: LOVED ONES WERE
RIPPED FROM THE GAME.
>> YOU SEE COMPLETE STRANGERS
LEGISLATURE YOUR DAUGHTER BEFORE
YOUR EYES.
IT'S TOUGH.
>> Jeff: BUT WHEN THE TRIBES
MERGED--
>> WELL HOME, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MULTIPLE COUPLES HAD
SURVIVED.
NONE WERE MORE POWERFUL THAN
ALL-AMERICAN COUPLE JON AND
JACLYN.
>> WE FIND OURSELVES IN THE
MIDDLE.
SO WE'RE BEING GIVEN A LOT OF
OPPORTUNITIES TO CONTROL OUR
FATE.
>> Jeff: JOSH.
THEY LED THE CHARGE IN TAKING
OUT THE GAME'S BIGGEST THREATS.
JEREMY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
IN A VERY UNPREDICTABLE SEASON.
IDOLS DESTROYED PLANS.
>> DUDE, PLAY YOUR IDOL.
>> JEFF, I'D RATHER PLAY THIS
THAN GO HOME WITH IT IN MY
POCKET.
>> HERE YOU GO, JEFF.
>> Jeff: BIG MOVES FLIPPED THE
GAME.
>> I'M SUPPOSED TO VOTE FOR
KEITH, BUT I'M VOTING FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: ALEC.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: THERE WERE BAD
BREAKS.
>> THAT WAS MY ANKLE.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> I'M BAD.
>> THIS IS SO FRUSTRATING.
>> Jeff: BIG FIGHTS.
>> HEY, HEY.
>> DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> BAIL OYOU'RE A BRAT.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> Jeff: AND SOME VERY ODD
MOMENTS.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE EPISODE OF
"TWO AND A HALF MEN" WHEN YOU
WERE NAKED WITH PANCAKES.
THAT'S AWESOME, DUDE.
>> Jeff: AFTER 35 DAYS, SIX
PLAYERS REMAIN.
AND AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
IT APPEARED KEITH WAS ON THE
BOTTOM.
WITH THE POWER COUPLE SITTING
PRETTY.
BUT IN THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR,"
WHEN YOU GET COMFORTABLE--
>> THIS IS PAYBACK FOR JEREMY.
I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
>> Jeff: YOU GET BLINDSIDED.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JON.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JON WAS VOTED OUT WITH AN IDOL
IN HIS POCTD.
JON, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND JACLYN WAS LEFT ALL ALONE.
"SURVIVOR" IS A TRICKY GAME.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN THE BASIC PREMISE--
OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
THIS GAME IS WIDE OPEN.
FIVE ARE LEFT.
MISSY AND BAYLOR.
THEY'RE THE ONLY PAIR OF LOVED
ONES REMAINING.
NO STRANGERS TO ADVERSITY,
THEY'VE STUCK TOGETHER THROUGH
MISSY'S MULTIPLE DIVORCES AND
AND ARE FOUR DAYS FROM ACHIEVING
THEIR GOAL OF MAKING IT TO THE
END TOGETHER.
>> I FOUGHT LIKE HELL TO STAY IN
THIS GAME, KEEP MY DAUGHTER IN
THE GAME, BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP
FIGHTING.
>> THE MILLION DOLLARS AT THE
FINISH LINE.
ALL OF OUR DREAMS COULD BE
FULFILLED.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, AFTER HER
SISTER, NADIYA, WAS THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT, SHE HAD ONLY
HERSELF TO RELY ON.
GAVE HER THE COURAGE TO MAKE BIG
MOVES AND WITH AN IDOL IN HER
POCKET, SHE'S NOT DONE YET.
>> WHEN NADIYA GOT OUT, IT LIT A
FIRE UNDER ME, I'M GOING TO GET
IF FOR NADIYA, JUST TO PROVE TO
EVERYBODY ELSE THAT I'M THE BEST
ONE OUT HERE.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, SHE AND HER
BOYFRIEND, JON, DOMINATED THE
GAME, BUT AFTER JON'S BLINDSIDE,
SHE'S LEFT ALONE TO FEND FOR
HERSELF.
>> JON AND I WERE IN THE GAME
TOGETHER.
WE PLAYED AS A TEAM.
WE CARRIED EACH OTHER
ESSENTIALLY.
BUT I'M IN THIS GAME FOR MYSELF
NOW, AND I'M NOT GOING DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
>> Jeff: KEITH.
>> I BET YOU'RE SURPRISED TO SEE
ME AGAIN, AIN'T YOU?
>> Jeff: THIS 53-YEAR-OLD
FIREMAN CAME INTO THE GAME AS AN
UNDERDOG, BUT AFTER 35 DAYS,
HE'S OUTLASTED HIS SON, WON
MULTIPLE IMMUNITY CHALLENGES,
AND IS DETERMINED TO BEAT THE
ODDS.
>> I THINK I GOT THIS, BABY.
CONFIDENCE.
P.M.A.-- POSITIVE MENTAL
ATTITUDE.
>> Jeff: IT ALL CONCLUDES
TONIGHT.
WHO WILL WIN THE MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE AND THE TITLE OF "SOLE
SURVIVOR IN?
>> YOU GOTTA DO WHAT YOU GOTTA
DO, RIGHT?
>> I GUESS SO.
DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
I HAD THIS GUT FEELING THAT
MAYBE JON SHOULD PLAY HIS IDOL
JUST IN CASE, BUT WE REALLY
TRUSTED MISSY, NATALIE, AND
BAYLOR, AND WE GOT SCREWED.
BUT, DAMN, YOU GUYS, GOOD
ACTING.
>> I KNOW--
>> IT WAS ALL A BIG FAKE.
BECAUSE THAT'S CRAZY.
>> I' LOYAL TO A FAULT.
IN MY LIFE, I'M LOYAL TO A
FAULT.
>> SO IS HE.
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> YEAH.
YOU HAVE KNOWN HIM FOR 35 DAYS.
>> I'M TALKING ABOUT IN THIS
GAME, GIRL.
THIS IS NOT THE REAL LIFE.
>> SHE JUST SAID IN HER REAL
LIFE SHE SAID SHE IS LOYAL TO A
FAULT AND I SAID JON IS LOYAL TO
A FAULT IN HIS REAL LIFE.
SO DON'T ( BLEEP ) SAY YOU KNOW
JON BECAUSE YOU DON'T.
>> I KNOW JON IN THIS GAME.
>> NOT IN REAL LIFE.
>> I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT REAL
LIFE.
>> SHE WAS AND SO WAS I?
IT WAS REALLY HARD AFTER TRIBAL.
I JUST FELT LIKE SINCE THE
MERGE, EVERYBODY LOVED ME AND
JON.
I DON'T SEE PEOPLE EVER, EVER IN
REAL LIFE SAYING BAD THINGS
ABOUT JON.
IT WAS REALLY HURTFUL.
AND I JUST SNAPPED.
I WENT OFF ON NATALIE.
>> I MEAN, I JUST MAKE MY
OBSERVATION ON WHAT HAS
HAPPENED.
>> KEEP IT COYOURSELF IF IT'S
GOING TO BE TALKING ( BLEEP ) TO
MY FACE.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR.
IT ( BLEEP ).
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> IT'S BECAUSE JACLYN HAD A FIT
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
IF ANYTHING IS TRYING TO WORK
WITH HER, IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
IT DOES SCARE ME A LITTLE BIT
WHERE NOW I'M IN THE SITUATION
WHERE I HAVE TO TRUST BAYLOR AND
MISSY TO WANT TO TAKE ME TO THE
FINAL THREE FOR THEM BECAUSE AT
THIS POINT THEY COULD
TECHNICALLY VOTE ME OUT UNLESS I
WIN IMMUNITY.
THAT'S WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS.
IT'S A LOT OF WORK BUT THERE'S A
BIG PRIZE AT THE END.
YOU HAVE TO PUT IN WORK IF YOU
WANT TO WIN THIS.
♪♪
>> THE FACT WE MADE IT TO THE
FINAL FIVE AND WE COULD GO TO
THE FINAL THREE TOGETHER TO ME
IS JUST, LIKE, SO COOL.
>> BUT LET'S THINK ABOUT THE
END-ALL GOAL.
THE GOAL IS FOR US TO WIN.
>> I KNOW.
YOUR DREAM AND MY DREAM WAS FOR
US TO MAKE THE TOP THREE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING IT?
WE HAVEN'T STARTED.
>> WE HAVE FOUR DAYS LEFT.
I CAN SEE THE FINISH LINE.
I CAN SEE THE FINAL THREE.
I CAN SEE THE FINAL TRIBAL.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE THINKING
NATALIE, MY MOM, AND I FOR FINAL
THREE.
>> DO YOU FEEL TOTALLY STRONGLY
ABOUT US GOING TO THE FINAL
THREE, THEN LET'S DO IT.
>> DO YOU NOT AT ALL?
>> NO, NO, I FEEL TOTALLY
STRONGLY ABOUT IT.
HAVING BAYLOR HERE WE NOW HAVE
TWO SHOTS AT A MILLION BUCKS,
BUT I'M NOT REALLY SURE ABOUT
THESE CHALLENGES.
I FRACTURED MY FOOT, AND I HAVE
THIS HARD CAST NOW ON MY FOOT.
JUST SO FRUSTRATING.
WE CHOSE TO GO TO THE FINAL
THREE TOGETHER.
>> COOL, I LIKE IT.
>> SO THE GAME PLAN NOW IS FOR
NATALIE AND BAYLOR TO START
CRUSHING THESE CHALLENGES
OPINION THE LAST THING WE WANT
IS FOR KEITH OR JACLYN TO WIN IT
FROM HEREON OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN GUYS.
BOY, IT'S WORK JUST GETTING
HERE, ISN'T IT?
>> A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ATTACHED TO A ROPE.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE TO UNSPOOL
THE ROPE.
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE ENOUGH,
YOU'LL HEAD OUT TO ASSEMBLE A
BRIDGE.
ONCE THE BRIDGE IS COMPLETE, YOU
WILL THEN USE SANDBAGS TO KNOCK
DOWN A SERIES OF BLOCKS.
THE FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TODAY YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR SOMETHING THAT WILL HELP YOU
WIN THIS GAME.
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR AN ADVANTAGE
IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
WIN THIS CHALLENGE, USE THAT
ADVANTAGE, WIN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE IN THE FINAL
FOUR, ONE STEP AWAY FROM FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HUGE STAKES.
MISSY, GOOD NEWS/BAD NEWS FOR
YOU.
THE BAD NEWS, IS THE CHANCES OF
YOU COMPETING IN THIS CHALLENGE
ARE ZERO.
AGREE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: GOOD NEWS IS, YOU'RE
STILL IN THE GAME.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: MISSY WILL NOT
COMPETE.
GOT A SPOT ON THE BENCH FOR YOU.
EVERYBODY ELSE WILL DRAW FOR
SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'RE GATHERING ROPE THAT WILL
BE ATTACHED TO YOU THROUGHOUT
THIS CHALLENGE.
IN ADDITION, YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO MANAGE THAT ROPE.
YOU DON'T WANT IT KNOTTED.
OUT OF THE GATE, EVERYBODY
MOVING QUICKLY.
DAY 36, ONLY FOUR PEOPLE IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
YOUR ODDS INCREASE THE MINUTE
MISSY SHOWED UP.
KEITH IT HEADING OUT.
NATALIE GOING TO HEAD OUT NOW.
SHE'S NOT LETTING KEITH GO
ANYWHERE WITHOUT HER.
KEITH STARTING TO WORK ON HIS
BRIDGE.
JACLYN THINKS SHE HAS ENOUGH
ROPE.
SHE'S HEADING OUT.
BAYLOR HEADING OUT NOW.
REMEMBER, YOU CAN'T WALK AROUND
THE STRUCTURE NATALIE STARTING
TO BUILD HER BRIDGE.
BAYLOR'S BUILDING HER BRIDGE.
JACLYN STILL WORKING ON HER
ROPE.
IT'S ALL KNOTTED UP.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
YOU WIN THIS, YOU HAVE A DECENT
SHOT AT WINNING THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
IT IS NATALIE AND KEITH SIDE BY
SIDE.
THEY'VE BEEN NECK AND NECK THIS
ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
NATALIE HEADING BACK FOR MORE.
KEITH'S HEADING BACK.
EVERY TIME YOU HAVE TO COME BACK
AND GET MORE OF THESE WOODEN
PEGS, YOU HAVE TO COME ALL THE
WAY BACK ON THAT BRIDGE, SO THE
MORE YOU CAN CARRY, THE FEWER
TRIPS YOU WILL HAVE TO MAKE.
BAYLOR NOW STRUGGLING WITH THAT
ROPE.
JACLYN WITH A BIG FALL.
THAT WILL LEAVE A MARK.
KEITH GOES DOWN.
EVERYBODY'S STARTING TO RACE.
MISTAKES STARTING TO HAPPEN.
KEITH NOW WITH A BIT OF A LEAD.
HE'S GOT TO COME BACK FOR HIS
LAST THREE PIECES.
NATALIE PLACES ANOTHER ONE.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
BAYLOR STILL DEALING WITH ROPE,
FALLING OUT OF IT.
>> DROP THE ROPE!
>> Jeff: NATALIE TAKES A FALL.
JACLYN HAS FALLEN OUT OF IT.
NATALIE NOW PICKING UP THE PACE.
NATALIE CLOSING THE GAP.
WE ARE TIED NOW, NATALIE AND
KEITH.
KEITH PLACES ANOTHER ONE.
HE'S GOT TWO LEFT.
NATALIE'S GOT TO GO BACK FOR HER
LAST THREE PIECES.
KEITH HAS HIS BRIDGE COMPLETE.
KEITH CAN START UNTYING HIS
SANDBAGS.
>> DON'T QUIT, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: KEITH HAS HIS
SANDBAGS.
KEITH WITH A BIG HIT.
KEITH KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER.
NATALIE SNAGGED ON ROPE, MISSING
A PEG, EVERYTHING FALLING APART.
KEITH KNOCKS OFF TWO MORE
BLOCKS, AND ANOTHER ONE.
NATALIE TRYING TO GET BACK IN
THIS.
SHE CAN START TOSSING SANDBAGS.
KEITH KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER.
NATALIE WITH EYE NICE HIT.
KEITH'S GOT TO COLLECT HIS
SANDBAGS.
THIS OPENS THE DOOR FOR NATALIE.
NATALIE WITH A BIG HIT.
KEITH KNOCKS OFF ANOTHER BLOCK.
HE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
NATALIE'S GOT TO PICK IT UP.
KEITH WINS REWARD!
AN ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
I'M KILLING IT.
>> Jeff: KEITH, COME ON OVER.
IF YOU CAN.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> SORE ALREADY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KEITH,
ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
THIS SAYS MUST BE READ IN
PRIVATE.
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS.
THIS IS FOR YOU, AND YOU ONLY.
>> ALL RIGHTY, I'LL TAKE THAT.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE ONE MORE
DECISION TO MAKE.
DAY 36, WHO YOU GOING TO SEND TO
EXILE ISLAND?
EVERYBODY HAS BEEN EXCEPT MISSY.
IT WOULD TAKE MISSY A WHILE TO
GET THERE, BUT YOU CAN SEND HER.
OTHERWISE, IT'S JACLYN, NATALIE,
OR BAYLOR.
GOING TO EXILE.
AND ON DAY 36, TO BE AWAY FROM
THE POLITICS OF THIS GAME GIVEN
WHAT HAS BEEN GOING ON IN TRIBAL
COULD BE A SEVERE DISADVANTAGE.
WHO YOU GOING TO SEND?
>> I CAN'T SEND MISSY.
HOW ABOUT JACLYN?
>> Jeff: JACLYN.
HEAD OUT TO EXILE.
JACLYN WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT, KEITH, YOU HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
TUT IT TO GOOD USE.
YOU COULD BE STANDING HERE AGAIN
WITH A NECKLACE AROUND YOUR
NECK.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING FOR.
>> Jeff: KEITH, NATALIE,
BAYLOR, MISSY, GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> GETTING BEAT PIE BOO A
55-YEAR-OLD MAN IS NOT EASY.
I NEED TO BE ABLE TO BEAT HIM AT
THAT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE EVEN
WITH HIS ADVANTAGE.
IT'S ANYTHING TO BE REALLY
TOUGH, BUT IF I WANT MY PLAN TO
GO THE WAY I WANT IT TO, THEN I
NEED TO GET RID OF KEITH FIRST.
>> Jeff: IT IS GETTING GOOD.
OKAY, SO WE'RE 36 DAYS INTO THE
SHOW, AND YOU CAN SEE HOW
PHYSICALLY EXHAUSTED THE
CONTESTANTS ARE.
AND STILL I GET ASKED THIS A
LOT, "HOW MUCH FOOD DO THEY
REALLY LIVE ON?"
SO I WANT TO TRY TO CLEAR THIS
UP TONIGHT.
EACH SEASON, THE SURVIVORS ARE
GIVEN A BAG OF RICE, AND THEY'RE
TOLD TO RATION IT.
THIS SEASON, ONE TRIBE ATE A
LITTLE MORE THAN THEY SHOULD,
BUT NORMALLY THEY STICK TO IT.
AND HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
THIS IS WHAT YOU GET.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS A HALF A CUP OF COOKED
RICE, ABOUT 100 CALORIES.
THIS IS WHAT THEY GET EACH DAY.
SOMETIMES THEY CATCH A FISH.
YOU'VE SEEN THEM, THEY'RE PRETTY
SMALL.
SOMETIMES THEY GET REWARDS.
IT GOES THROUGH YOU PRETTY
QUICKLY.
JUST TO GIVE YOU SOME COMPARISON
HERE.
THIS IS WHAT THEY LIVE ON EACH
DAY.
THIS IS WHAT THE AVERAGE
AMERICAN EATS EACH DAY.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
YOU HAVE YOUR BREAKFAST, SOME
EGGS MAYBE SOME TOAST.
THEN YOU HAVE MAYBE A BURGER,
YOU LOVE YOUR FRENCH FRIES,
OKAY, SOMETHING TO DRINK.
AND THEN DOWN THERE AT THE END
IS SPAGHETTIS.
THIS IS ABOUT 2500 CALORIES.
THIS IS FROM THE U.S.D.A., I'M
NOT MAKING THIS STUFF UP.
COMPARED TO THIS.
THIS SHOW IS REAL.
THIS SHOW WILL KICK YOUR ASS.
AND YOU-- GLENN, LET'S GO DOWN
THERE.
STAY THERE.
I'M COMING TO YOU.
I SAW YOU EARLIER.
YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING AT ME.
YOU'RE A "SURVIVOR" FAN,
OBVIOUSLY?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: DO YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT DOING THIS SHOW?
>> SOMETIMES.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> OLIVIA FELLEDMAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, OLIVIA, DO
YOU THINK YOU COULD DO IT?
>> MAYBE IN A LONG TIME.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: OKAY.
WELL, THERE'S NO BHRT TIME THAN
THE PRESENT TO START.
THIS IS YOUR FIRST CHALLENGE.
THIS IS ALL THE FOOD YOU GET FOR
THE REST OF THE NIGHT.
GOOD LUCK.
( APPLAUSE )
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO-- WE'RE
GOING TO SEE HER ON THE SHOW ONE
DAY AND YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE ME
EAT THAT RICE MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO SEE
NOW WHAT HAPPENS WITH KEITH.
HE JUST WON THIS ADVANTAGE.
IT'S A BIG ADVANTAGE, BUT THE
QUESTION I IS WILL IT PAY OFF.
IT'S THE "SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN DEL
SUR: BLOOD VS. WATER" FINALE
CONTINUING RIGHT AFTER THIS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
"UNDERNEATH A CAVE OF ROCKS
HIDES AN IDOL WHICH IMPROVES
YOUR CHANCES."
THE SAME CLUE EVERYBODY ELSE
GOT.
I'M ON EXILE, AND JON GOT VOTED
OUT.
I MEAN, AT THIS POINT IN THE
GAME, THE NEXT TRIBAL, IT'S
BASICALLY ME OR KEITH.
OH!
THIS GAME, MAN, IT MAKES YOU
EMOTIONAL.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT IN MY
LIFE.
YOU KNOW, BEING DIAGNOSED WITH
NOT BEING ABLE TO HAVE KIDS AND
ALL THAT, WHEN I WAS REALLY
YOUNG.
SO, THIS IS ONE NIGHT, AND IN
THE GRAND SCHEME OF THINGS, I
FEEL LIKE I'M FIGHT FOR ME AND
JON NOW, FOR MONEY TO HAVE KIDS
IN THE FUTURE.
AND IF JON WAS HERE AND HE COULD
GIVE ME A PEP TALK HE'D BE LIKE,
"YOU'RE ALMOST DONE.
YOU'VE DONE WAY HARDER THINGS IN
YOUR LIFE THAN THIS.
JUST ROCK IT OUT."
AND I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
>> GOOD JOB, KEITH, WAY TO GO.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> THAT WAS INTENSE.
>> THE REWARD CHALLENGE WAS
SUCKY.
KEITH WON.
WHICH MEANS HE GOT AN ADVANTAGE.
UN, IT'S FRUSTRATING BECAUSE HE
IS THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE THREAT.
>> OKAY, SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
THIS.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT THAT IS.
IT GIVES HIM AN ADVANTAGE
TOMORROW.
>> I HOPE IT'S AN ENDURANCE.
>> IT WILL BE TOMORROW, BECAUSE
WE HAVE TOMORROW AND THE NEXT
DAY AND THEN THAT'S IT.
>> BUT TOMORROW, IF HE DOESN'T
WIN, LET'S SEND HIM HOME
IMMEDIATELY.
>> YEAH.
>> THE LITTLE NOTE SAID READ IN
PRIVATE SO I SNUCK OFF AND READ
IT.
"YOU HAVE EARNED AN ADVANTAGE IN
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
A CHALLENGE TABLE HAS BEEN
DELIVERED TO A PRIVATE SPOT AT
YOUR CAMP.
YOU CAN PRACTICE FOR AS LONG AS
YOU WANT, BUT ONCE YOU STOP, YOU
ARE FINISHED."
GOOD GRIEF.
"THIS CHALLENGE REQUIRES
PATIENCE AND FINESSE.
YOU WILL USE A SERIES OF METAL
SPOONS TO TRANSFER BECAUSE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES
FROM ONE SIDE OF THE TABLE TO
THE OTHER."
WHEN I GOT TO THE TABLE, IT HAD
A FEW MORE CLUES, YOU KNOW,
TELLING ME HOW THE CHALLENGE
WORKS.
THERE WASN'T NOTHING TO FILL ME
IN.
OH, IT GOES LIKE THAT?
I MEAN, IT TOOK ME A LITTLE
WHILE TO FIGURE IT OUT.
START IT LIKE THAT.
THE CHALLENGE TABLE HAS GOT FOUR
HANDLES AND YOU JUST PASS A BALL
TO A PADDLE OVER AN OBSTACLE TO
ANOTHER PADDLE, COMPLETE THAT
THREE TIMES, BAM.
NECKLACE AROUND YOUR NECK.
WHOA!
I'M GOING TO STAY HERE AND
PRACTICE BECAUSE I NEED THAT
NECKLACE TOMORROW.
THIS IS A BIG ADVANTAGE, BELIEVE
ME.
THERE DOES COME A POINT IN THE
FIRE SERVICE WHERE IT'S STAY AND
DIE OR JUMP OUT THE WINDOW.
IT'S CALLED FLASH OVER.
THIS ROOM IS FIXING TO FLASH
OVER, AND YOU BETTER DO
SOMETHING QUICK LIKE.
IT'S TO THE POINT NOW I'M ON THE
HOT SEAT, BUT I THINK MAYBE I'M
NOT FLASHED OVER YET.
I'M PROBABLY GOING TO PRACTICE
UNTIL DARK.
I'M READY TO GO TACKLE THIS BABY
AND GET THAT NECKLACE.
YOUR CONCENTRATION AIN'T AS GOOD
AS IT WAS WHEN YOU FIRST
STARTED.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THAT'S SO HARD
RIGHT THERE.
GOOD GRIEF, MAN.
I'M GOING MENTALLY.
OH!
WHOA!
ALL I CAN DO RIGHT NOW IS WIN
CHALLENGES, AND GO FOR THAT
NECKLACE.
I'M LOSING FOCUS.
>> YUP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK IT'S UP TO GUYS.
I HAVE SAID-- BASICALLY, I HAVE
TWO DECISIONS AT THIS POINT.
MISSY AND BAYLOR, FEEL LIKE I'M
DEFINITELY GOING TO BE WITH
MISSY AND BAYLOR, BUT I COULD
DECIDE TO GO WITH KEITH AND
JACLYN AND SAY LET'S GET ONE OF
THESE GIRLS OUT.
LET'S TRY AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THAT'S HOW IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
>> I HAVE AN IDOL FOR MYSELF IF
I DON'T WIN IMMUNITY, BUT THE
ADVANTAGE IS BASICALLY GOING TO
HELP KEITH IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
IT TOTALLY SUCKS THAT HE GOT IS
BECAUSE HE'S GOING TO BE HARD TO
BEAT.
I KNOW IT'S A BIG DECISION ON
WHO GOES HOME TONIGHT.
>> HEY, LET'S WIN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
JACLYN, RETURNING FROM EXILE
ISLAND.
>> YEAH, JACLYN.
>> HI, GUYS!
I'M ALIVE.
>> Jeff: SO, JACLYN, HOW WAS
EXILE ALL ALONE?
>> WELL, IT DEFINITELY SUCKED
BEING AWAY FROM CAMP.
I MEAN, IT'S A TERRIBLE TIME TO
GO AWAY TO EXILE.
>> Jeff: AND, MISSY, YOU HAVE
A NEW PART OF YOUR WARDROBE.
>> WELL, THIS WAS BIG JON'S SHOE
THAT HE LEFT BEHIND, AND SO I
DECIDED THAT I COULD KIND OF CUT
IT AND SO I COULD HAVE AT LEAST
A FOOTHOLD SO I COULD AT LEAST
STAND, AND IT LOOKS LIKE TODAY I
MIGHT BE ABLE TO PARTICIPATE.
>> Jeff: YOU FEEL GOOD ENOUGH
TO COMPETE IN THIS ONE.
>> I'M GOING TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
NATALIE, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE TWO VERY SMALL
PADDLES TO MANEUVER A BALL
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
IF AT ANY POINT THE BALL DROPS,
YOU GOTTA GO BACK TO THE START.
FIRST PERSON TO TRANSFER THREE
BALLS WINS IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED
A SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR, ONE
STEP AWAY FROM FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT AND BECOME THE SEVENTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
STAKES GET BIGGER EVERY SINGLE
DAY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A GUARANTEED
SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR.
SURVIVES READY?
GO.
BIG LEARNING CURVE OUT OF THE
GATE.
TAKES A LOT OF TOUCH.
YOU ONLY GET THAT TOUCH BY
PRACTICING AGAIN AND AGAIN.
YOU'RE GOING TO DROP THAT BALL A
LOT IN THE BEGINNING.
DON'T LET THAT WORRY YOU.
DON'T GET FRUSTRATED.
JUST KEEP GOING.
MISSY DOING A NICE JOB.
BAYLOR DOING A NICE JOB.
KEITH DROPS.
JACLYN STILL AT THE FRONT,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
THAT BALL MOVING.
MISSY GETTING SOME MOMENTUM NOW.
KEITH DROPS AGAIN.
KEITH HAD AN ADVANTAGE IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
THE QUESTION IS DID IT HELP?
YOU DON'T WANT TO PAN NICK THIS
CHALLENGE BECAUSE ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN.
MISSY DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
JUST WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE IT
FIGURED OUT, YOU LOSE YOUR BALL
AND YOU GOTTA START AGAIN.
BAYLOR HALFWAY THROUGH WITH HER
FIRST BALL.
IF SHE CAN KEEP IT ALIVE.
BAYLOR DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO START OVER.
KEITH WORKING ON HIS FIRST BALL.
KEITH WITH A NICE SAVE.
KEITH NOW STARTING TO MAKE SOME
PROGRESS.
KEITH DOING A NICE JOB.
HE'S GOT HIS BALL ON THE FINAL
OBSTACLE.
KEITH VERY CLOSE.
IF HE CAN GET IT UP TOP AND
DROPPED, IT GETS VERY TRICKY AT
THE END.
KEITH HAS HIS FIRST BALL
THROUGH.
TWO TO GO.
THERE ARE THREE BALLS TOTAL YOU
HAVE TO TRANSFER.
KEITH HAS ONE.
EVERYBODY ELSE STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE IT OUT.
JACLYN TRYING TO GET A KEY.
SHE'S LOOKING OVER AT KEITH.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHAT DOES HE KNOW THAT I DON'T
KNOW?
IS THAT ADVANTAGE HELPING KEITH?
IT WOULD APPEAR SO.
JACLYN STILL WORKING AT THE
FIRST OBSTACLE.
KEITH WHIPPING THROUGH THIS
COURSE.
KEITH WORKING THAT SECOND BALL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: KEITH VERY CLOSE TO
HAVING A SECOND BALL.
KEITH HAS HIS SECOND BALL.
ONE LEFT FOR KEITH.
NATALIE STILL TRYING TO GET ONE.
BAYLOR DROPS AGAIN.
SHE'S GOT TO START OVER.
JACLYN DROPS AGAIN.
MISSY STILL WORKING ON THAT
FIRST BALL.
>> I KEEP DROPPING THEM.
>> Jeff: KEITH WORKING ON THAT
THIRD BALL.
NOBODY ELSE EVEN CLOSE YET.
NATALIE STARTING TO PANIC NOW,
RUSHING.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO HELP.
BAYLOR RUSHING NOW.
TRYING TO PUT SOME PRESSURE ON
KEITH.
KEITH GETTING VERY CLOSE TO
FINISHING THIS CHALLENGE.
HE'S GOT HIS THIRD BALL ON THE
TIME OBSTACLE.
CAN HE KEEP IT STEADY?
IT WOULD BE HIS THIRD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEEING HIM A
SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR.
KEITH WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
KEITH, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, KEITH.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: FOR THE THIRD TIME,
YOU ARE SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
KEITH CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
YOU ARE GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FOUR.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SLEF
DAYS IN THIS GAME, YOUR DREAM
WILL FALL TWO DAYS SHORT.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
YOU'LL BECOME THE SEVENTH MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
SHOULD BE A VERY INTERESTING
AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL,
CONGRATS.
>> I'M IN THE FINAL FOUR, I KNOW
LIKE THE N.C.A.A. BASKETBALL
PLAY-OFFS.
ONE MORE STEP AND I WON'T BE
SITTING BY THIS LOG.
I'LL BE JUMPING ON IT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: KEITH IS ON A ROLL.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU TO A
REALLY SPECIAL GUEST.
THIS IS ONE OF MY BEST NEW
FRIENDS, AUSTIN.
WE MET AUSTIN THROUGH OUR
FRIENDS AT MAKE A WISH.
HE HAD THIS BIG DREAM.
AUSTIN'S DREAM WAS NOT ONLY TO
COME VISIT THE LOCATION OF HIS
FAVORITE SHOW BUT TO ALSO CREATE
A CHALLENGE THAT WOULD MAKE IT
ON THE SHOW.
VERY TALL ORDER.
I'VE NEVER GOTTEN A CHALLENGE ON
THE SHOW, EVER, 29 SEASONS.
( LAUGHTER )
SO WE INVITED AUSTIN AND HIS
FAMILY AND HIS SISTER ADDISON TO
COME OUT.
EVERYBODY FLEW OUT.
THEY PRACTICED CHALLENGES.
YOU GOT BEHIND THE CAMERA A
COUPLE OF TIMES.
THEY VISITED TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND THEN CAME THE MOMENT, THE
PITCH.
AND YOU WENT IN TO SEE JOHN
KURHOFFER.
SHE ONE OF OUR SUPERVISING
PRODUCERS.
HE'S RESPONSIBLE FOR EVERY
CHALLENGE THAT'S EVER BEEN ON
THE SHOW AND YOU HAD TO PITCH
HIM.
WHAT WAS THAT MOMENT LIKE?
>> IT WAS A REALLY GREAT MOMENT
THAT I'LL ALWAYS REMEMBER.
>> Jeff: YOU KNOW WHY YOU WILL
REMEMBER IT?
YOU PITCHED LIKE YOU DID IT YOUR
WHOLE LIFE.
WE TOLD YOU WE CAN'T PROMISE IS
IT WILL GET ON THE SHOW.
YOU LEFT THE ROOM AND KURHOVER
SAID, "I THINK SO IT'S GOING TO
GET ON THE SHOW."
AND THEN YOU HAD TO WAIT ALL
THESE WEEKS.
THIS IS THE CHALLENGE AUSTIN
CREATED.
IT AIRED LAST WEEK IT WAS A
MASSIVE CHALLENGE.
AND THIS IS ALL HIM.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
AND THEN I KNOW YOU GUYS HAD A
PARTY, RIGHT?
WE SHOT SOME VIDEO, I THINK--
YEAH.
SO YOU HAD ALL YOUR FRIENDS OVER
WHILE YOU WATCHED THE EPISODE.
WERE YOU A BIG DEAL THAT NIGHT?
>> YES, IT WAS.
>> Jeff: MOM AND DAD, WHAT'S
IT BEEN LIKE FOR YOU GUYS?
BECAUSE AUSTIN REALLY HAD THIS
JUST GIGANTIC ADVENTURE?
>> IT WAS-- IT WAS SUCH A PROUD
MOMENT, WATCHING HIM IN FRONT OF
THAT WHITE BOARD WITH JOHN IS
SOMETHING WE'LL NEVER FORGET.
>> Jeff: WELL, WE ARE SO HAPPY
THAT YOU ARE HERE, AND YOU HAD A
LOT OF THINGS HAPPEN.
YOU HAD TO GET A PASSPORT, YOU
HAD TO GLIE FLYON A PLANE.
YOU WENT TO A FOREIGN COUNTRY.
IT WAS SWEAT, THERE WERE BUGS
YOU YOU ATE THE RICE WE SHOWED
EARLIER.
HOW DO YOU WRAP THIS UP?
HOW DO YOU WRAP UP THIS
EXPERIENCE JAI JUST WANTED TO
HOSPITAL SHOW.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: THAT IS WHY I LOVE
YOU!
OKAY.
BACK TO THE SHOW.
BIG TRIBAL COMING UP.
KEITH IS SAFE, AND THAT MEANS
ONE OF THE GIRLS IS GOING HOME.
SO SOMEBODY IS GOING TO TURN.
WHO IS GOING TO MAKE THE BIG
MOVE?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
RUN OVER AND WATCH YOU DO IT
ONCE, BECAUSE I THOUGHT IF I
COULD WATCH YOU DO IT ONCE.
>> DID YOU GET IT GOING DOWN?
>> I GOT IT UP TO THAT AND
THAT'S WHEN IT STOPPED.
>> YOU NEVER GOT IT GOING DOWN?
NOBODY GOT A BALL.
>> NO!
>> REALLY?
THAT'S WAS JUST A LITTLE BIT OF
PRACTICE.
>> AND YOU'RE GOOD WITH BALLS,
KEITH.
>> I'M GOOD WITH BALLS.
COMING BACK TO CAMP WASN'T TOO
BAD.
I DON'T KNOW.
UH, MAN.
YEAH, I OUGHT TO HAVE THIS BY
NOW, RIGHT?
YOUR MIND GOES ON THE 37th
OR 8th DAY OR WHATEVER.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
COMING BACK TO CAMP AFTER THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, WASN'T TOO
BAD.
YOU KNOW, TONIGHT PROBABLY WON'T
BE TOO HARD.
I MEAN, JACLYN KNOWS, SHE'S
GOING RIGHT UP THERE TO THE
JURY.
>> I MEAN--
>> BEST CAN BE EXPECTED?
>> YEAH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S GOING TO GET TO HAVE HER
NICE BOTTLE OF WINE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I THINK JABLIN IS READY TO
GO.
>> YEAH.
>> SO ARE YOU STILL VOTING WITH
THEM?
>> I AM BEING TOTALLY REAL RIGHT
NOW, IF YOU WANT TO VOTE ONE OF
THEM OUT AND DOWN, I WOULDN'T
VOTE YOU OUT TOMORROW I WOULDN'T
VOTE YOU OUT TOMORROW.
YOU GUYS WOULD PROBABLY VOTE MY
ASS OUT TOMORROW.
IT WILL BE ONE MORE DAY FOR ME.
THAT'S MY WHOLE THING, ONE MORE
DAY.
I JUST WENT THROUGH A WHIRLWIND
TWO DAYS, JON BEING VOTED OFF,
FEELING ALONE AFTER THAT.
THEN GOING TO EXILE, FEELING
MORE ISOLATED AND I'M COMING
BACK HERE AND I KNOW I'M GOING
HOME AND IT SUCKS, AND I'M LIKE,
NO, I'M NOT GOING TO LAY DOWN.
>> WHAT WOULD DO YOU TODAY?
>> I FEEL LIKE MISSY?
JUST BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE BAYLOR
DISW WHATEVER HER MOM TELLS HER.
>> I MEAN, LISTEN, I FEEL REALLY
SECURE WITH MISSY AND BAYLOR,
LIKE, I TRUST THEM 100%.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THEY'RE BLOOD.
>> ME AND MY MOM ARE NOT VOTING
FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW THAT.
>> I WAS THINKING TONIGHT,
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY YOUR IDOL,
RIGHT?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO.
>> PLAY IT FOR MY MOM.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU NEED TO
PLAY IT FOR YOU, HONESTLY.
>> THAT'S FINE.
I KNOW I'M IN THE FINAL FOUR
BECAUSE OF MY IDOL.
I ALSO KNOW THAT MISSY AND
BAYLOR PROBABLY WON'T VOTE ME
OFF BECAUSE THEY FEEL CONFIDENT.
WE'RE SO TIGHT.
WE TRUST EACH OTHER.
>> NO ONE IS VOTING FOR YOU
KEITH'S NOT GOING TO VOTE FOR
YOU.
HE'S GOING TO VOTE FOR JACLYN
WITH US EVERYONE IS ON JACLYN.
AND JACLYN WILL VOTE MISSY.
>> ONE THING IS FOR SURE BIG
MOVES DO WIN THIS GAME, AND I
FEEL LIKE I'VE DONE MOVES THAT
HAVEN'T BEEN AS IMPACTFUL AS I'D
LIKE.
BUT IT'S NOT ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE
AT THIS POINT.
I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT MYSELF.
IT'S EITHER MAKING A BIG MOVE
TODAY, GETTING RID OF BAYLOR OR
MISSY, AND RISKING LOSING ITAL
AND NOT MAKING FINAL THREE, OR
KIND OF PLAYING IT SAFE AND VOTE
OUT JACLYN.
THAT'S THE ONLY FEAR THEY HAVE
IS THAT PEOPLE WILL BE LIKE,
"LOOK AT THE MOVE NATALIE MADE.
AM PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS SCARED OF
PEOPLE WHO MAKE BIG MOVES.
IF I DID SOMETHING BIG TONIGHT,
TOMORROW, I COULD BE THE ONE
GOING HOME.
SCARY.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH.
JEREMY.
WES.
REED.
ALEC.
AND JON, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JACLYN, HOW IS YOUR GAME
DIFFERENT NOW THAT JON IS OUT?
>> PROS, OBVIOUSLY, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THE OTHER
PERSON.
CONS, YOU HAVE NO ONE YOU CAN
TRUST 100%.
SO IT'S LIKE I'M TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO NOW WHEN
THE ONLY PERSON I REALLY TRUSTED
IS GONE.
>> Jeff: KEITH, WHAT WAS THE
REACTION WHEN YOU GOT BACK TO
CAMP AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL?
>> IT GOT HEATED.
IT GOT LOUD.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE A
CAT FIGHT.
I MEAN, HAIR PULLING.
IT GOT HEATED.
BUT I NEVER HEARD MY NAME, SO --
>> SO THAT WOULD MAKE IT GOOD
NEWS FOR YOU.
>> WRONGER THAT.
YUP.
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: MISSY, FINAL FIVE,
LAST TIME YOU CAN USE AN IDOL IF
YOU HAVE IT.
WHAT'S THE SPHEELG BECAUSE VERY
FEW HAVE BEEN PLAYED, AND ALWAYS
AT SURPRISING TIMES.
>> I'M PRETTY CONFIDENT ABOUT
THE IDOL SITUATION BECAUSE I
KNOW WHO HAS IT.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, WHAT DO YOU
READ INTO THAT?
MISSY'S SAYING I'M CONFIDENT
ABOUT THE IDOL SITUATION BECAUSE
I KNOW WHO HAS IT.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THERE WAS
ANISEED ANISEED ON HERE.
>> DON'T BE WHO HAS IT.
>> SO I'M THINKING SHE OR
NATALIE OR BAYLOR MAY HAVE IT,
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: SO THAT WOULD MAKE IT
POTENTIALLY WORSE FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: MISSY, ANY CONCERN
AT NOW I, AS THE FINAL LOVED ONE
PAIR STILL IN THE GAME, NOW IT
BECOMES A LIABILITY.
IF BOTH OF YOU COULD MAKE IT TO
THE END, IT'S A PRETTY GOOD
STORY.
>> I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE WE'RE
PROBABLY IN A DANGER ZONE BUT I
DO FEEL PRETTY STRONGLY THAT I
STILL HAVE AN ALIGNMENT THAT'S
STUCK LIKE GLUE.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHAT WAS THE
VIBE AT CAMP TODAY AFTER KEITH
WON IMMUNITY AND YOU KNEW IT WAS
GOING TO BE YOU, JACLYN, MISSY,
OR BAYLOR GOING HOME TONIGHT?
>> IT TAKES ONE PERSON OFF THE
CHOPPING BLOCK AND THE REST OF
US ARE JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO.
EVERYONE ASSUMES ME, MISSY AND
BAYLOR ARE VOTING TOGETHER, BUT
THERE WERE SOME DISCUSSIONS THAT
HAPPENED, JACLYN CAME TO ME AND
PLUS KEITH WINNING IMMUNITY, YOU
KNOW, IT MAKES EVERYTHING SO
MUCH MORE COMPLICATED.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, WAS KEITH THE
NEXT TO GO IF HE DIDN'T WIN?
>> AS FAR AS I KNOW, YEAH.
SO IT WAS KIND OF A TOSS-UP
BETWEEN KEITH OR MYSELF, WHICH
SUCKS.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE IF IT'S NOT
KEITH, THEN--
>> THEN IT'S ME.
LIKE NATALIE SAID, I CAME TO
HER.
I'M LIKE, "WHAT CAN I DO?
I'M SERIOUSLY AT THE BOTTOM.
IS THERE ANY POSSIBILITY WE CAN
DO ANYTHING?"
>> Jeff: MISSY, IS THERE
ANYTHING JACLYN COULD DO IN THIS
POSITION?
>> I THINK THAT THERE COULD
ALWAYS BE CRACKS IN THIS GAME.
I THINK IN OUR PARTICULAR
SITUATION, THERE AREN'T, AND SO
I COMPLETELY RESPECT AND HONOR
HER FOR TRYING, BUT SOMETIMES I
THINK AFTER YOU SWING AS HARD AS
YOU CAN, I MEAN, YOU DO JUST
KIND OF HAVE TO SHRUG YOUR
SHOULDERS AND GO OKAY, WELL, YOU
KNOW-- I MEAN, THIS IS MY TIME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KEITH, YOU'RE UP.
>> IT WAS REALLY FUN PLAYING
WITH YOU.
I HOPE YOU DON'T TAKE THIS TOO
PERSONAL.
>> NATALIE TOLD ME TO DO THIS
AND TO JUST TRUST HER.
IF IT'S NOT YOU, IT'S GOING TO
BE ME.
SO HOPEFULLY I CAN TRUST
NATALIE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IT IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT TO
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
>> YEAH.
I GUESS IT'S TIME TO PULL THE
IDOL OUT OF THE BAG.
I WAS GOING TO PLAY THIS FOR
MYSELF TONIGHT, BUT IT'S MORE
FUN WHEN YOU PLAY THEM FOR
SOMEBODY ELSE.
JACLYN, DID YOU VOTE FOR WHO I
TOLD YOU TO VOTE FOR?
I'M PLAYING THIS FOR JAC.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
>> I KNEW I LIKED HER.
I KNEW I LIKED HER.
>> I'M GOING HOME.
LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR JACLYN WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
JACLYN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
JACLYN, DOES NOT COUNT.
BAYLOR.
THAT'S ONE VOTE BAYLOR, ONE VOTE
LEFT.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SEVENTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
BAYLOR, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
>> I LOVE YOU, MOMMY.
GIVE ME A HUG.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> HANG IN THERE.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> LOVE YOU ALL.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, JACLYN,
MISSY, KEITH, YOU'VE MADE IT TO
THE FINAL FOUR.
TOMORROW YOU WILL COMPETE IN
YOUR FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
TRY TO GET A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP
BECAUSE ARE YOU DEFINITELY GOING
TO NEED IT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> I FEEL SURPRISED.
THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD
BLINDSIDE.
I'M SUPER PROUD OF MYSELF.
I'M NOT MAD AT NATALIE.
THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD MOVE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: WELL THAT WAS ONE OF
THE BIGGEST MOVES THE SEASON.
THAT IS HOW YOU PLAY "SURVIVOR,"
AND IT IS MOVES LIKE THAT, I
THINK ARE ONE OF THE BIG REASONS
WHY I HEAR THE SAME THING OVER
AND OVER WHEN YOU GUYS STOP ME
ON THE STREET TO TALK
"SURVIVOR," WHICH I LOVE, AND
THAT IS IS.
>> NEVER MISAN EPISODE.
>> NEVER MISS AN EPISODE.
>> WATCH IT AND REWATCH IT.
>> Jeff: ALL OF YOU HAVE
WATCHED EVERY SINGLE EPISODE.
AND THIS IS NOT UNCOMMON.
WE VETERAN ON 29 SEASONS.
THAT'S 400-SOME HOURS DEDICATED
TO THIS OVER 15 YEARS.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT THE SHOW THAT
KEEPS YOU COMING BACK?
WE WERE IN A LONG-DISTANCE
RELATIONSHIP AND IT MADE
"SURVIVOR."
>> IT WAS OUR DATE NIGHT.
>> Jeff: DO YOU WATCH WITH
MOM?
>> YES.
>> WEDNESDAY NIGHT, OUR NIGHT IS
GIRL NIGHT, GIRL POWER.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE GIRL POWER
GOING ON RIGHT THERE.
ARE YOU GUYS TOGETHER?
>> WE WATCH IT AND REWATCH IT.
>> Jeff: YOU REWATCH IT?
>> ONCE A YEAR WE START AT
SEASON ONE --
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE NUTS.
>> I'VE HAD A LOT OF CHANGES,
CHANGED CAREERS, CHANGED
BOYFRIENDS, BUT "SURVIVOR" IS
THE ONE CONSTANT FOR ME.
>> I TAPED IT EVERY WEEK ON VHS,
AND ONE NIGHT I HAD A DATE IN
COLLEGE AND HAD TO CANCEL
CAUSE IT WAS THURSDAY
NIGHT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S "SURVIVOR,"
THAT'S LOVE RIGHT THERE.
NATALIE JUST PULLED OFF A BIG
MOVE AND NOW SHE HAS TO GO BACK
TO CAMP AND DEAL WITH THE
FALLOUT.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO LOOKED
FOR TO.
>> WHEN I WALKED INTO TRIBAL, I
HAD AN IMMUNITY IDOL AND MY PLAN
WAS BASICALLY DECIDING KEEPING
BAYLOR AROUND OR JACLYN AROUND.
TRUSTING TWO FAMILY MEMBERS IN A
SITUATION WHERE I COULD BE THE
OUTSIDER JUST SEEMED LIKE A
REALLY DANGEROUS THING.
SO BAYLOR WENT HOME.
>> THAT WAS PRETTY SLICK.
I MEAN, IT'S SHOWTIME NOW.
>> AT ONE POINT, YOU'VE GOT TO
REALIZE IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL'S
GAME.
MAKING THIS MOVE, I REALIZE THAT
I CAN GET RID OF A COUPLE BUT
NOT BE THE MAIN THREAT.
IF KEITH WINS TOMORROW, HE'LL
PROBABLY WANT TO VOTE OUT MISSY
OVER ME.
THIS WAY I GET TO GO TO THE
FINAL THREE AND I'M NOT JUST
PUTTING MY FATE IN MISSY'S AND
BAYLOR'S HANDS, AND MISSY'S CASE
IN FINAL THREE IS SO MUCH
STRONGER SITTING NEXT TO BAYLOR
THAN WITHOUT BAYLOR.
>> NO.
IT'S A GAME.
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
IT WOULD HAVE MADE ME NERVOUS,
TOO, TO HAVE YOU AND YOUR
SISTER.
>> YEAH.
>> AH!
IT DIDN'T GO AS PLANNED.
UM, SO, BAYLOR GOT VOTED OUT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A GAME.
AND, I MEAN, I'M OKAY WITH IT
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE TO WRITE MY
CHILD'S NAME DOWN ON A VOTING
BALLOT.
I MEAN, IT'S A RELIEF, AND IT'S
A LIFT OFF MY SHOULDERS.
>>
>> THIS IS THE ONLY THING I HAVE
EVER KEPT FROM YOU.
>> I KNOW, I UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE TOLD ME MORE THAN
ANYBODY ELSE HAS COME CLOSE TO
TELLING ME THIS THIS GAME.
I MEAN, I GUESS THE FATE OF MY
GAME IS IN THESE OTHER PEOPLE'S
HANDS BECAUSE I CAN'T COMPETE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> WELL, THANKS FOR GIVING ME
LIFE ONE MORE DAYS BECAUSE OF
YOU.
>> IF KEITH WINS IMMUNITY
TOMORROW, I WON'T HAVE ANY
CHANCE.
>> OBVIOUSLY, YOU DID THE SMART
THING.
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL I THOUGHT I
WAS GOING HOME, AND NATALIE
TOTALLY STEPPED IN AND SAVED MY
LIFE.
>> IT'S BETWEEN ME AND YOU
TOMORROW FOR THE IMMUNITY.
>> YEAH, WE GOT IT.
>> I NEED TO WIN IMMUNITY
TOMORROW.
AND IF I DON'T AND NATALIE DOES,
SHE'S TAKING ME AND MISSY TO THE
FINAL THREE.
>> KEITH IS THE NUMBER ONE
THREAT RIGHT NOW, SO THE GOAL IS
TO NOT LET KEITH WIN SO WE CAN
VOTE HIM OUT NEXT.
>> YEAH, KEITH IS SCARY.
>> KEITH IS SCARY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
KEITH, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: HATE TO GIVE THAT UP,
HUH?
>> I DO, I DO.
>> Jeff: THE LAST TIME
IMMUNITY IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE DOWN A GIANT
TOWER.
YOU'LL THEN MANEUVER THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES, COLLECTING
BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES AS YOU GO.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE FIRST THREE
BAGS, YOU'LL HEAD BACK TO THE
TOP, DROP THEM, HEAD BACK DOWN
AND GET THE OTHER TWO.
YOU WILL THEN USE THOSE PUZZLE
PIECES TO SOLVE A PUZZLE.
BUT THERE'S A TWIST.
WHEN YOUR PUZZLE'S COMPLETE,
THREE PIECES WILL BE MISSING.
THE SHAPES OF THOSE PIECES WILL
REVEAL THE THREE NUMBERS YOU
NEED TO SOLVE THE COMBINATION
LOCK.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT AND
RAISE THEIR FLAG WINS IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
THREE, A CHANCE TO PLEAD YOUR
CASE ABOUT WHY YOU DESERVE THE
TITLE OF "SOLE SURVIVOR" AND THE
MILLION DOLLARS THAT GOES WITH
IT.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE EIGHTH AND
FINAL MEMBER OF OUR JURY, NO
SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
SO, MISSY, OBVIOUS QUESTION--
LOOKING AT THE SIZE OF THIS
CHALLENGE, I DON'T SEE ANY WAY
YOU CAN PARTICIPATE GIVEN THE
SHAPE YOU'RE IN.
>> YEAH, I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MISSY
GOING TO SIT THIS ONE OUT.
WE'LL CRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A SPOT AT THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
FIREMAN'S POLE IS THE FIRST
STEP.
NATALIE DOWN, KEITH, JACLYN,
EVERYBODY DOWN.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO GO BACKWARDS.
USING THAT ROPE.
IT'S NATALIE, KEITH, JACLYN.
HEAD OUT TO YOUR FIRST STATIONS.
YOU GOTTA HIT ALL FIVE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT ORDER YOU
GO.
NATALIE THROUGH THE FIRST
OBSTACLE.
SHE'S UNTYING.
KEITH THROUGH HIS FIRST
OBSTACLE.
HE'S UNTYING.
JACLYN THROUGH HER FIRST
OBSTACLE.
NATALIE HEADING BACK.
KEITH HEADING BACK.
NATALIE HAS HER FIRST BAG.
SET IT DOWN AND HEAD OUT FOR
ANOTHER.
THE WIND IS PICKING UP.
JACLYN TAKING A LONG TIME ON
THAT FIRST OBSTACLE.
KEITH BACK WITH HIS FIRST BAG.
HERE COMES JACLYN.
JACLYN HEADING BACK OUT.
IT IS NATALIE AND KEITH RIGHT
NOW BOTH WORKING ON THEIR SECOND
BAGS.
JACLYN NOW HEADING OUT FOR HER
SECOND BAG.
NATALIE HEADING BACK.
KEITH NOW IN THE LEAD WITH HIS
SECOND BAG.
>> COME ON, NATALIE.
>> Jeff: DROP IT AND GET
NUMBER THREE.
ONCE YOU HAVE THREE, YOU GOTTA
HEAD UP AND COME BACK DOWN FOR
THE OTHER TWO.
HERE COMES JACK WIN WITH HER
SECOND.
KEITH WORKING ON THAT THIRD BAG.
NATALIE NOW LOOKING FOR HER
THIRD.
KEITH HEADING BACK.
JACLYN WITH HER SECOND BAG.
LOOKING FOR NUMBER THREE.
KEITH HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
HE CAN HEAD UP TO THE TOP.
57 STEPS YOU GOTTA CLIMB TO COME
BACK DOWN AND DO IT AGAIN.
NATALIE BACK WITH HER THIRD BAG.
SHE CAN START HEADING TO THE
TOP.
JACLYN WORKING ON THAT THIRD
BAG.
AND IT'S KEITH AND NATALIE BOTH
WITH THREE BAGS.
JACLYN STILL WORKING ON THAT
THIRD BAG.
NATALIE HEADING BACK DOWN.
KEITH HEADING BACK DOWN.
JACLYN QUICKLY FALLING BEHIND IN
THIS FINAL CHALLENGE.
IT'S NATALIE AND KEITH STILL
SIDE BY SIDE.
JACLYN HEADS UP NOW TRYING TO
PICK UP SOME TIME.
>> YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT, YOU
GOT IT!
BE CAREFUL ON THE POLE ON THE
WAY DOWN.
GRAB TIGHT.
>> Jeff: KEITH ACROSS HIS
FOURTH OBSTACLE.
NATALIE HAS HER FOURTH.
JACLYN HEADING BACK DOWN NOW.
JACLYN IS FALLING OUT OF IT.
RIGHT NOW IT IS KEITH AND
NATALIE, BOTH COMING BACK WITH
THEIR FOURTH BAGS.
NATALIE HEADING OUT FOR HIR
FIFTH AND FINAL BAG OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
KEITH HAS HIS FOURTH.
JACLYN WORKING ON HER FOURTH.
NATALIE ON THAT FIFTH BAG.
JACLYN WITH HER FOURTH BAG.
NATALIE WITH HER FIFTH AND FINAL
BAG.
SHE CAN HEAD UP, START WORKING
ON THE PUZZLE.
KEITH WORKING ON HIS FIFTH BAG.
NATALIE NOW WITH A BURST OF
ENERGY.
SHE'S SPRINTING UP THOSE STEPS.
KEITH HAS HIS FIFTH BAG.
KEITH AND JACLYN HEADING IN
DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
JACLYN WORKING ON HER FIFTH BAG.
KEITH HEADING UP.
JACLYN HAS HER FIFTH BAG.
SHE CAN HEAD UP.
NATALIE HAS A BIG HEAD START
WORKING ON THIS PUZZLE.
HERE COMES JACLYN.
PICK IT UP!
LET'S GO!
JACLYN'S LOST A LOT OF TIME IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
38 DAYS TAKING ITS TOLL.
BIG GUST OF WIND MAKING THIS
EVEN MORE DIFFICULT.
JACLYN EXHAUSTED.
CAN BARELY OPEN THE BAGS.
NATALIE ALREADY WORKING ON HER
PUZZLE.
NATALIE, KEITH, AND JACLYN
FIGHTING FOR A SPOT AT THAT
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL MISSY CAN DO IS WATCH AND
HOPE SOMEBODY TAKES HER TO THE
END.
NATALIE'S PUZZLE COMING TOGETHER
NICE LEALLY.
KEITH WORKING ON THE BORDERS.
JACLYN STRUGGLING EVEN TO GET
THE PIECES OUT OF THE BAG.
THAT'S WHAT "SURVIVOR" DOES TO
YOU.
YOU LAST LONG ENOUGH, IT WILL
KICK YOUR BUTT.
IT IS THE LOGO OF THIS SEASON.
WIND BLOWING EVERYBODY AROUND.
WE ARE ON A TOWER THAT IS FOUR
STORIES HIGH WITH A MASSIVE WIND
WHILE YOU TRY TO SOLVE WHAT
COULD BE A MILLION-DOLLAR
PUZZLE.
NATALIE STILL WITH A BIT OF A
LEAD OVER KEITH.
JACLYN RACING TO GET BACK IN
THIS.
KEITH WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
KEITH'S PUZZLE NOW STARTING TO
COME TOGETHER.
NATALIE STILL WITH A BIT OF A
LEAD, BUT NOT MUCH.
JACLYN STARTING TO PICK UP THE
PACE.
HER PUZZLE'S STARTING TO COME
TOGETHER NOW.
JACLYN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
KEITH WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
NATALIE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
EVERYBODY'S STILL FIGHTING,
STILL IN IT.
IT WOULD BE NATALIE'S SECOND
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN.
IT WOULD BE KEITH'S FOURTH.
IT WOULD BE JACLYN'S FIRST.
JACLYN PLACES ANOTHER PIECE.
JACLYN IS NOW BACK IN THIS
CHALLENGE OUT OF NOWHERE.
I'D WRITTEN HER OFF.
NATALIE GETTING VERY CLOSE TO
FINISHING.
KEITH GETTING VERY CLOSE NOW.
JACLYN DOWN TO TWO PIECES LEFT.
JACLYN HAS HER PUZZLE COMPLETE.
JACLYN HAS HER THREE SHAPES.
THEY WILL CORRESPONDENT TO THREE
NUMBERS.
SHE'S HEADING DOWN.
JACLYN WITH A BIG HIT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
JACLYN TOOK A HUGE FALL AND
SHE'S STILL FIGHTING.
KEITH STILL STUCK.
WAS SO CLOSE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: NATALIE HAS HER
PUZZLE COMPLETE.
SHE'S GOT HER THREE SHAPES.
NATALIE CAN HEAD DOWN.
IT IS JACLYN AND NATALIE.
>> COME ON, GUYS!
>> Jeff: UNTIE, THAT JACLYN.
MATCH UP THE SYMBOLS WITH THE
NUMBER, THEN RACE BACK UP!
HERE COMES NATALIE.
MAKE SURE YOUR NUMBERS ARE
RIGHT.
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE WRONG, YOU
GOTTA GO ALL THE WAY BACK.
JACLYN HEADING BACK, DOES SHE
HAVE THE RIGHT NUMBERS?
JACLYN'S COME FROM BEHIND AND
HAS A SHOT TO WIN IT.
NATALIE STILL TRYING TO UNTIE.
THIS WOULD BE IT FOR JACLYN.
JACLYN BACK.
DOES SHE HAVE IT?
NATALIE HEADING BACK.
DON'T GIVE UP.
YOU GET ONE SHOT TO BE RIGHT.
OTHERWISE YOU GOTTA HEAD BACK
DOWN.
DOES SHE HAVE IT?
YES!
JACLYN WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
THREE!
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> I COULDN'T GET THAT FOR
NOTHING.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, COME ON OVER.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: OUT OF NOWHERE.
>> CRAZY.
>> PERFECT TIMING.
>> Jeff: PROVES ONCE AGAIN,
NEVER, EVER GIVE UP IN THIS
GAME.
JACLYN, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THAT MEANS YOU ARE GUARANTEE AID
SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, 38 DAYS
IS NOT QUITE ENOUGH.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT,
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE EIGHTH
AND FINAL MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> THAT WAS A TOUGH ONE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, JACLYN WON.
NATALIE SAVED JACLYN LAST
TRIBAL, SO I SEE NO REASON WHY
JACLYN SHOULD GET RID OF
NATALIE.
THAT MEANS TROUBLE FOR ME IS
WHAT IT MEANS.
BIG TROUBLE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT WAS, LIKE, THE HARDEST.
>> HARDEST CHALLENGE EVER.
>> THAT'S THE DAY TO WIN.
>> THAT'S THE BIGGIE.
YOU ANTICIPATE KIDDING.
>> JON IS GOING TO DIE WHEN HE
SEES ME WEARING THE NECKLACE
TONIGHT.
I CAN'T WAIT.
OH!
I DIDN'T WIN ONE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE THE WHOLE GAME, AND I
WON THE FREAKING MOST IMPORTANT
ONE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M NOT TAKING THIS OFF.
>> DON'T.
I WOULD BE SPAING OUT IF I WAS
YOU.
>> TONIGHT I HAVE A HUGE
DECISION.
WHO TO TAKE TO THE FINAL THREE.
I LIKE TO TALK EVERYTHING OUT.
THAT'S HOW ME AND JON PLAYED THE
WHOLE GAME, JUST TALKING
EVERYTHING OUT, EVERY SCENARIO
WE COULD THINK OF.
AND ULTIMATELY IT COULD BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
IT COULD BE A MILLION-DOLLAR
MISTAKE.
>> CAN I PLEAD MY CASE RIGHT
NOW?
YOU'RE WHO I NEED TO BE TALKING
TO JAC.
SHE'S THE POWER, SHE'S THE MAN.
>> WHOEVER WINS THE NECKLACE HAS
THE POWER.
>> YOU TRY TO MAKE A PITCH TO
GET TO THE MILLION.
AND DAY 39, YOU'RE PITCHING WHY
YOU DESERVE THE MILLION.
I'VE GOT TO GET IN THE FINAL
THREE.
I'M THINKING YOU GOT A BETTER
CHANCE WITH ME AND NAT INSTEAD
OF MISSY AND NAT.
MISSY'S GONNA GET A LOT OF
VOTES.
SHE'S GOING TO GET THE SYMPATHY
VOTE FOR HER ANKLE-- SOME.
SHE'S GOT BAYLOR LAWYER ALREADY.
>> THAT MAKES SENSE.
>> I GIVE JACLYN MY PITCH.
IF JACLYN GETS RID OF MISSY,
SHE'S GOT A BETTER CHANCE WITH
ME IN THE THREE THAN MISSY.
HOPEFULLY, SHE'LL VISUALIZE THAT
AND SEE.
THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
IT'S IN Y'ALL'S HANDS.
THINK ABOUT IT JACLYN.
>> I WILL.
>> SO, I MEAN, IT'S OBVIOUSLY ME
AND YOU.
AND ONE OF THEM.
>> THESE TWO ARE DANGEROUS IN
DIFFERENT WAYS.
>> I KNOW.
TRYING TO OUTWEIGH THE PROS PROS
AND CONS.
WE SHOULD HAVE A CONVERSATION
ABOUT THIS.
>> THE PROBLEM WITH JACLYN IS
SHE'S WEARING THE NECKLACE, SHE
KNOWS SHE'S IN THE POWER SEAT.
I WILL KEEP GOING AND HOPE SHE
DOESN'T LET THIS POWER TRIP GO
TO HER HEAD.
OKAY, MISSY.
>> WHO WOULD VOTE FOR MISSY.
WE VOTE MISSY OUT.
>> I WOULD VOTE MISSY OUT TODAY.
BUT I THINK KEITH IS SCARER.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
I DON'T WANT JACLYN THINKING TOO
MUCH.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU WHAT TO
DO WHAT'S GOOD FOR YOU AND ME
HERE AND LISTEN TO ME.
LET'S GET RID OF KEITH.
I SHOULDN'T SPAS OUT BUT THIS IS
THE END.
I HAVE ROOM TO BE NERVOUS.
I HAVE TO TALK TO MISSY, TOO,
BUT.
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE
KEITH FOR SURE, UNLESS SOMETHING
HAPPENS IN MY HEAD IN THE NEXT
FOUR HOURS, BUT I KIND OF DOIT
IT.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
>> OKAY?
>> WOULD YOU EVER VOTE NAT?
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> JACLYN, I HAVE TO BE HONEST I
THINK IT'S A TOSS-UP.
>> I THINK OUT OF US FOUR, SHE'S
GOT THE STRONGEST GAME PLAY.
THEN I'M LIKE HOLY CRAP, SHE
GAVE ME LIFE LAST NIGHT.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT, SHE
COORDINATED THE BARELY BLINDSIDE
AND THE JON BLINDSIDE, AND
THAT'S TWO HUGE PLAYS THAT BROKE
UP THE FAB FIVE.
THAT'S A HUGE STATEMENT.
>> YEAH.
>> JACLYN COMES UP AND SAYS, HOW
WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT VOTING OUT
NATALIE?
MY HEAD I WENT-- UM.
WELL, "A," NUMBER ONE, SHE VOTED
OUT MY KID.
AND, "B," KEEP TALKING.
IF YOUR GUT IS TALKING TO YOU,
YOU NEED TO LISTEN.
WHAT'S IT SAYING?
I MEAN--
>> MY GUT IS SAYING KEITH
BECAUSE THE GUYS.
BUT MY GUT'S ALSO SAYING NATALIE
COULD BEAT ME WITH THE GAME
PLAY.
>> WHAT WOULD JON SAY?
>> VOTE HER OFF.
TOTAL ( BLEEP ).
I KNOW.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH.
JEREMY.
WES.
REED.
ALEC.
JON.
AND BAYLOR, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
TODAY.
JACLYN, BIG FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
TELL ME ABOUT THE FEELING ON DAY
38 KNOWING YOU ARE GUARANTEE TO
BE HERE TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
I MEAN, IT'S A GOOD FEELING.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IT'S HARD.
BECAUSE NOW I'M IN THE MIDDLE,
AND I'VE TALKED TO EVERYBODY
ABOUT DIFFERENT SCENARIOS, AND
IT'S TOUGH.
IT'S REALLY TOUGH.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, YOU HAD AN IMMUNITY
IDOL, YOU PLAYED IT FOR JACLYN,
AND SAVED HER.
DO YOU EXPECT A LITTLE
RECIPRICATION FROM JACLYN?
YOU SAVED HER LAST TRIBAL THAT
SHE CERTAINLY WON'T VOTE FOR YOU
TONIGHT?
>> IT'S NICE TO THINK LIKE THAT,
BUT I WASN'T EXPECTING IT BACK,
BUT IT WOULD BE, OBVIOUSLY, A
NICE GESTURE.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, DO YOU FEEL
AN OBLIGATION TO NATALIE TO KEEP
HER TONIGHT, EVEN IF YOU THINK
SHE MIGHT BEAT YOU?
>> UM, I DO AND I DON'T.
I MEAN, SHE DID BLINDSIDE JON.
THAT LEAVES A SOUR TASTE IN MY
MOUTH.
>> Jeff: KEITH, WHAT WAS THE
DAY LIKE FOR YOU?
WHAT DID YOU EXPERIENCE?
>> WELL, I WENT THROUGH THE SAME
SCENARIOS THAT EVERYBODY IS
GOING THROUGH.
YOU KNOW, NAT SAVED JAC LAST
TRIBAL, SO SHE MIGHT HAVE A
HEADS UP.
AND I'M THINKING IT'S GOT TO BE
ME AND MIS, IT'S GOT TO BE.
>> Jeff: I'M CURIOUS, MISSY,
WHY NATALIE IS NOT IN THESE
DISCUSSIONS.
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU GUYS THINK
YOU CAN BEAT NATALIE.
>> I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE THAT
NATALIE IS GOING TO THE END.
I DON'T KNOW IF KEITH HAS
INFORMATION I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
BUT THE THREE OF US CAN'T BE
COMFORTABLE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHAT'S A
REASON TO GET RID OF KEITH
TONIGHT?
>> EVERYBODY LOVES A FIREMAN,
YOU KNOW.
HE'S A REALLY CHARISMATIC GUY.
PEOPLE ARE DRAWN TO HIM, AND
EVERYBODY LOVES HIM.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> NICELY SAID.
>> Jeff: KEITH, DO YOU HAVE A
REASON IT WOULD MAKE SENSE TO
GET RID OF NATALIE TONIGHT?
>> UM, NATALIE'S GOT A BUNCH OF
VOTE OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: BASED ON WHAT?
>> WELL, BASED ON THE WAY SHE'S
PLAYED THE GAME, GOOD, REAL
GOOD.
I MEAN, SHE'S A BIG THREAT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, YOU CAN WIN
THIS GAME?
>> YEAH, I THINK I COULD WIN
THIS GAME.
I THINK I HAVE A GOOD SHOT AT
WINNING.
I REALLY DID THIS NOT ONLY FOR
ME, BUT FOR ME AND NADIYA.
I WAS WITH A BUNCH OF LOVED
ONES.
EVERYBODY WAS COUPLED UP BUT ME.
I JUST SAID EVEN IF IT'S HARD,
GO THE HARD ROUTE.
DON'T GO THE EASY ROUTE.
AND MADE SOME RISKY DECISIONS
AND KICKED ASS IN CHALLENGES AND
IT'S BROUGHT ME THIS FAR AND I'M
REALLY HAPPY WITH THE WAY I
PLAYED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
MISSY, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE.
KEITH.
MISSY.
TWO VOTES KEITH, ONE VOTE MISSY.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH AND FINAL MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: KEITH, YOU NEED TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> SEE Y'ALL.
>> BYE, KEITH.
>> Jeff: MISSY, JACLYN,
NATALIE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'VE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO
IN THIS GAME.
THE POWER SHIFTS TO THE JURY.
EIGHT PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A HAND
IN VOTING OUT, THEY WILL DECIDE
WHO THEY THINK IS MOST DESERVING
OF THE TITLE OF "SOLE SURVIVOR"
AND THE MILLION DOLLAR CHECK
THAT GOES ALONG WITH IT.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT OUT HERE
IN SAN JUAN DEL SUR.
THEN WE WILL RECONVENE AGAIN
TOMORROW NIGHT FOR YOUR FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> MISSY, WE NEED PUBLIC
SPEAKING 101.
>> OKAY.
>> SO ALL THREE OF THEM VOTED
FOR ME.
IT WASN'T A BLINDSIDE.
IT'S THREE WOMEN.
I CAN BARELY HANDLE ONE WOMAN AT
THE HOUSE, MUCH LESS THREE OF
THEM HERE.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
I LOVE THEM ALL.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: THAT RESPONSE SPEAKS
TO HOW MUCH PEOPLE I THINK
ENJOYED WATCHING KEITH, AND
WATCHING HIM LEARN THE GAME AS
HE WENT ALONG.
AFTER IT WAS OVER-- THIS IS 15
SECONDS AFTER KEITH WAS VOTED
OUT-- I CATCH UP WITH HIM IN THE
JUNGLE-- THIS IS AFTER A MONTH
OF PLAYING "SURVIVOR" AND BARELY
MISSING OUT ON A MILLION
DOLLARS, HERE'S WHAT WAS ON
KEITH'S MIND.
YOU GO BACK HOME AND YOUR
BUDDIES SAY, "TELL ME WHAT IT
WAS LIKE."
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THIS
EXPERIENCE?
>> WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT I
WOULD BE SITTING IN A SPOT IN
NICARAGUA.
IF YOU WOULD HAVE ASKED ME IS
KEITH COMING BACK FROM THE MOON
OR SITTING IN NICARAGUA?
THEY'D SAY I'D BE COMING BACK
FROM THE MOON.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: SO WE'RE WATCHING
KEITH AND WE SEE HIS SON WES OUT
THERE, IF YOU'RE LIKE ME, AT
SOME POINT YOU'RE THINKING WHO
MARRIED KEITH?
WHO CREATED THIS FAMILY?
THIS IS DANA, WELCOME.
>> HI.
THANK YOU!
>> Jeff: MOUTH HAVE YOU.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HOW LONG HAVE YOU AND KEITH BEEN
MARRIED?
>> WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER ABOUT 30
YEARS MARRIED 25.
>> Jeff: SO IS THERE
ANYTHING-- KEITH WAS REALLY FUN
TO WATCH BECAUSE HE DIDN'T
REALLY KNOW THE SHOW.
AND HE WAS LEARNING IT.
WAS THERE ANYTHING HE DID,
THOUGH, THAT EMBARRASSED YOU OUT
THERE?
>> WELL, ABOUT THE ONLY THING
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT WAS
THE WAY HE WAS TRYING TO TEACH
MISSY HOW TO RAISE HER CHILD.
YUP.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
SO DID YOU HAVE SOME WORDS ABOUT
THAT?
>> YES, WE DID, YES, WE DID.
YOU DON'T TELL ANOTHER WOMAN HOW
TO RAISE HER BABY.
>> Jeff: MISSY DOES A GOOD JOB
OF LETTING PEOPLE KNOW THAT
HERSELF.
HERE'S A QUESTION THAT CAME UP,
HERE'S A TWITTER QUESTION
@SOFTBALLSAM WANTS TO KNOW, WHAT
ABOUT THE SPITTING?
>> HE DID SPIT A LITTLE TOO MUCH
ON THE ISLAND BUT THAT'S PRETTY
TYPICAL FOR HIM.
WHAT YOU SEE IS WHAT YOU GET FOR
HIM.
>> Jeff: THAT'S WHY WE LIKE
WE ARE DOWN TO IT, JACLYN,
MISSY, AND NATALIE.
THIS IS IT, FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY'S ABOUT TO WIN A
MILLION BUCKS.
NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME, I WILL
HAVE THE VOTES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> OH, MY GOSH.
OH, MY GOSH.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WHEN WE STARTED THERE WERE 10
MEN AND EIGHT WOMEN.
FOR THREE WOMEN TO BE SITTING IN
THE FINDS IS PRETTY COOL.
>> ON THE JURY, IT'S ALL GUYS.
>> SEVEN MEN ON THE JURIES.
I'M SO NOT INTIMIDATEED BY SEVEN
MEN.
I HAVE BEEN MARRIED AND DIVORCED
THREE TIMES, SO I'M NOT FEARFUL
WHATSOEVER ABOUT SPEAKING TO
THESE GUYS.
>> I WONDER WHAT THE QUESTIONS
ARE ANYTHING TO BE?
>> I THINK TONIGHT IS GOING TO
BE SUPER IMPORTANT FOR ME TO
REALLY SWAY THEM, PRESENT MYSELF
THE BEST I CAN, AND NO MATTER
HOW IT ENDS, YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO BE POSITIVE ABOUT IT OR DIVE
YOUR HEAD IN THE STAND AND
BECOME A FAILURE.
AND THAT IS NOT WHO I AM.
( SCREAMING ).
>> OH, MY GOD!
EGGS, BREAD, CHAMPAGNE.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> PINEAPPLE, MANGO!
>> MY GOD, IS THAT CHEESE?
>> I'VE ACTUALLY LEARNED A LOT
ABOUT MYSELF, AND THE FACT THAT
I WAS ABLE TO NAVIGATE THROUGH
THIS WITHOUT THE ONE COMFORT
I'VE HAD MY ENTIRE LIFE, WHICH
WAS NAWDIO.
AND I WAS ABLE TO DO THIS ON MY
OWN MAKES ME REALLY PROUD.
AND I KNOW MY PARENTS WILL BE
PROUD, TOO, BECAUSE THEY FEEL
LIKE WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
WITHOUT EACH OTHER.
FINAL THREE, BABY.
NOW I NEED TO REALLY WORK
THROUGH WHAT I'M GOING TO SAY TO
THE JURY.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE HAVING ANY
REGRETS ABOUT THIS FINAL TRIBAL.
AMAZING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I CAN'T LEAVE ANYTHING UP TO
FATE.
I GOTTA DO THE JURY'S JOB FOR
THEM.
I GOTTA MAKE THEM SEE WHY THEY
NEED TO PICK ME AND WHY I
DESERVE TO BE THE SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> CAN'T WAIT TO RECONNECT WITH
JON AND BE LIKE, "I MADE IT TO
THE FINAL BREAKFAST, SUCKER."
( LAUGHTER )
I FEEL LIKE I WAS UNDERESTIMATED
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING IN THIS
GAME.
WINNING THE MILLION DOLLARS
MEANS A LOT MORE TO ME THAN IT
WOULD ANOTHER PERSON JUST
BECAUSE "BLOOD VERSUS WATER."
IT'S FAMILY AND RELATIONSHIPS.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT MOST, I WANT
A FAMILY WITH JON.
AND I CAN'T START A FAMILY OR
GIVE JON THE FAMILY HE WANTS
WITHOUT THE MONEY.
BUT THE TITLE OF "SOLE SURVIVOR"
WOULD MEAN MORE TO ME THAN THE
MONEY BECAUSE THE TITLE WOULD
EVEN FURTHER INSPIRE ALL OF THE
GIRLS WITH M.R.K.H.
I WANT TO PROVE TO ALL THE GIRLS
THAT HAVE MY SYNDROME THAT YOU
CAN DO IT.
THERE ARE WAYS.
NEVER GIVE UP.
THIS EXPERIENCE HAS JUST MADE ME
APPRECIATE AND REALIZE HOW
STRONG I REALLY AM.
I'VE BEEN FIGHTING FOR 39 DAYS.
TONIGHT IS THE BIG
ONE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH, JEREMY, WES, REED, ALEC,
JON, BAYLOR, AND KEITH VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU'VE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO
IN THE GAME, AND TONIGHT, IN ONE
OF THE TRULY UNIQUE ASPECTS OF
"SURVIVOR," THE GAME SHIFTS.
THE POWER MOVES FROM THIS SIDE
OF TRIBAL OVER HERE TO THE JURY.
EIGHT PEOPLE THAT YOU HAD A HAND
IN VOTING OUT WILL NOW DECIDE
WHO WINS THIS GAME.
WHO GETS THE MILLION DOLLARS.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE TO
PERSUADE THEM IT SHOULD BE YOU.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
YOU WILL EACH GET A CHANCE TO
MAKE AN OPENING STATEMENT.
THEN THE JURY WILL GET THEIR
CHANCE TO ADDRESS YOU.
AND THEN WE VOTE.
ALL RIGHT, MISSY, OPENING
STATEMENT.
( SIGHS ).
>> WELL, AS I HUMBLY SIT HERE IN
THE FINAL THREE, I REALIZE THAT
THESE ROLES COULD BE REVERSED,
AND I COULD BE SITTING THERE,
TOO, AND I KNOW YOU GUYS HAVE A
HUGE DECISION ON YOUR HANDS,
PROBABLY AS BIG AS A JURY ON A
MURDER TRIAL BECAUSE WHAT YOU
DECIDE TONIGHT IS GOING TO
AFFECT THE REST OF MY LIFE.
MY DEAL WAS LOYALTY FROM
BEGINNING TO END.
AND ANY TIME THAT SOMEONE SAID
THEY DIDN'T TRUST ME, WELL, THEY
HAD TO GO.
THE BIGGEST DECISION AND THE
BIGGEST MOVE AND THE HARDEST
DECISION I MADE THIS THIS GAME
WAS VOTING JON OUT.
I HAD TO WAKE UP AND PLAY THE
GAME, AND I HAD TO VOTE THAT
WAY.
DAY 33 WAS THE HARDEST AND THE
ROUGHEST DAY OF THIS GAME FOR
ME.
IT'S THE DAY I BROKE MY FOOT.
I FINISHED THE CHALLENGE ON ONE
LEG.
I BROUGHT MY TEAM TO THE
VICTORY, BUT IT WAS DEVASTATING.
BUT I WASN'T GOING TO QUIT.
THE FINISH LINE WAS IN SIGHT,
AND I KNEW I COULD FIGHT THROUGH
IT.
AND THAT'S WHAT I DID.
I PLAYED THIS GAME CONSISTENTLY
WITH INTEGRITY AND DIGNITY AND
MAINLY LOYALTY.
AND I THINK THAT'S WHY I DESERVE
TO BE THIS SEASON'S SOLE
SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: JACLYN.
( SIGHS ).
>> I DESERVE TO BE THE SOLE
SURVIVOR BECAUSE I WENT THROUGH
A LOT OF UPS AND DOWNS IN THIS
GAME JUST LIKE IN MY REAL LIFE.
I STARTED OUT PRETTY SLOW ON A
TRIBE WHO HAD ME ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK FROM DAY ONE.
I FELT REALLY ALONE.
AND IT DIDN'T STOP ME FROM
FIGHTING.
WHEN THE TRIBE SWAP HAPPENED, I
WAS ABLE TO ALIGN WITH SOME
REALLY GREAT PEOPLE, INCLUDING
MY LOVED ONE.
FROM THAT POINT ON, I WAS IN
THIS MIDDLE POSITION THROUGHOUT
THE MAJORITY OF THE ENTIRE GAME,
SWAICHING ALLIANCES.
AND IF IT WASN'T FOR THAT
DECISION, THESE TWO WOULDN'T BE
HERE RIGHT NEW.
JON GETS BLINDSIDED, AND I KNEW
AT THAT POINT I HAD TO TAKE THE
REINS AND STEP IT UP AND FINISH
THE GAME, AND THAT'S WHY I'M
HERE IN THE TOP THREE.
MY JOURNEY THROUGHOUT THIS GAME
IS LITERALLY LIKE A METAPHOR FOR
MY LIFE.
WHEN I WAS 15, I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH M.R.K.H. SYNDROME, WHICH
MEANS I WAS BORN WITHOUT HALF MY
REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS.
WAS DOWN AND ALONE, FEELING
REALLY TERRIBLE ABOUT WHO I WAS,
AND THEN I JUST GAINED THIS
STRENGTH THROUGHOUT MY LIFE,
TURNED A NEGATIVE INTO A
POSITIVE, AND JUST TRIUMPHED
FROM IT.
AND I FEEL LIKE I DID THAT IN
THIS GAME, TOO.
AND THAT'S WHY I WANT TO BE THE
SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: NATALIE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I DESERVE YOUR
VOTES TONIGHT AND FEEL LIKE I
DESERVE THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE OUTWIT,
OUTPLAYED, AND OUTLASTED BETTER
THAN THE TWO LADIES SITTING NEXT
TO ME.
I HAVE OUTWIT BY MAKING SMART,
RISKY, AND EVEN SCARY MOVES BY
MYSELF.
OUTPLAY EYE FEEL LIKE I
REPRESENT WELL IN EVERY
CHALLENGE OF THE GAME.
ONLY GIRL TO VOLUNTEER TO GO TO
EXILE TWICE, CARRIED MY WEIGHT
AROUND CAMP.
NEVER ONCE HAS ANYBODY CALLED ME
LAZY.
AND OUTLAST, I FEEL LIKE, YOU
KNOW, NADIYA GETTING VOTED OUT
DAY THREE, WHEN SHE GOT KICKED
OUT, I CHANGED THE WAY I PLAYED
THE GAME FROM LET'S JUST SURVIVE
ANOTHER TRIBAL TO, YOU KNOW,
WHAT?
YOU GOTTA WIN THIS GAME.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE HERE, YOU
MIGHT AS WELL WIN IT AND DO
EVERYTHING WITH A PURPOSE.
SITTING HERE ON DAY 39, MAKES ME
SO PROUD, AND FEEL SO HONORED TO
BE PLEADING MY CASE TO YOU GUYS
TONIGHT, ESPECIALLY SINCE I FEEL
HONESTLY, THAT LAST NIGHT, THE
RIGHT DECISION AND THE RIGHT
PERSON TO GO HOME SHOULD HAVE
BEEN ME, NOT KEITH, IF THEY MADE
THE RIGHT DECISION.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY, I
KNOW SOME OF YOU HAVE WAITED A
LONG TIME TO ADDRESS THESE
THREE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A MOMENT
TO COLLECT YOUR THOUGHTS.
AND THEN WE'LL GET TO IT.
THIS IS YOUR FIRST CHANCE TO
ADDRESS
MISSY, JACLYN, AND NATALIE.
YOU ARE LOOKING FOR INFORMATION
TO HELP YOU MAKE A
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
JON, GET US STARTED.
>> JACLYN.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU THE
OPPORTUNITY TO PRESENT A BIG
MOVE OR DECISION THAT YOU SOLELY
WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAKING AND
HOW DID IT AFFECT THE FINAL
THREE?
>> I THINK FOR ME, IT WOULD BE
THE FIRST VOTE, JOSH.
I THINK THAT THAT SWUNG THE
ENTIRE GAME, AND I KNEW THAT IF
I WAS WITH THE GUYS LIKE KEITH
AND WES AND JOSH, I'D BE ON THE
BOTTOM, JUST LIKE I WAS AT
COYOPA WITH THEM.
REED CAME TO ME AND ASKED ME AM
I OKAY?
AND I SAID YES.
HE THANKED ME LATER FOR BEING
HONEST BUT I WASN'T BECAUSE HIS
LOVED ONE WENT HOME, AND I KEPT
THAT FROM HIM.
BUT I GOT TO THE FINAL THREE,
AND I DON'T THINK I WOULD HAVE
IF I SWUNG THE OTHER WAY AND
WENT WITH THE JOSH AND REED
ALLIANCE.
>> SURE, SURE.
GOOD LUCK.
>> THANKS, JON.
KEITH, YOU'RE UP.
>> HI, GALS.
NAT, HOW DOES IT FEEL THE LAST
WORDS YOU EVER SPOKE TO ME WAS A
LIE?
HOW DOES THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
>> I KNEW, KEITH, IF IT WASN'T
YOU, IT WAS GOING TO BE ME.
AND AT THE END OF THE DAY, WE'RE
ALL TRYING TO GET TO THE FINAL
THREE.
I REALLY DID FEEL BAD ABOUT, YOU
KNOW, TELLING YOU ABOUT MISSY,
BUT I THINK THEY WERE ALL TRYING
TO MAKE IT TO HERE.
AND I KNEW THAT THE ONLY WAY I
COULD SURVIVE IS IF I SOLD YOU
AS THE BIGGEST THREAT, AND YOU
ARE A BIG THREAT.
BETWEEN YOU AND MISSY, I NEEDED
YOU TWO IN THE FINAL FOUR SO THE
TARGET WOULD BE OFF ME.
>> WELL, I KNOW YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO, AND I JUST
HATE-- I HATED THE CONSTANT
LYING.
I KNOW IT'S PART OF THE GAME,
BUT I WENT THROUGH HALF THIS
GAME WITHOUT AN ALLIANCE,
WITHOUT LYING, WITHOUT-- UNTIL
IT BOILS DOWN TO IT.
IT'S JUST-- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
SAY.
THAT'S THE WAY I LOOK AT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU,
KEITH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALEC, YOU'RE UP.
>> ALL RIGHT, LADIES, WELL, NAT,
WHAT'S YOUR BIGGEST ONE MOVE IN
THIS GAME?
AND HOW DID IT IMPACT THE
TURNOUT OF IT?
>> THE ONE MOVE I MADE THAT
ENDED UP CHANGING THE COURSE OF
THE GAME FOR ME AFTER WAS VOTING
YOU YOU OFF.
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD SAY THAT.
>> THAT WAS A MOVE NOBODY KNEW I
WAS GOING TO MAKE BECAUSE I HAD
THIS FEELING,UN, I COULD WORK
WITH KEITH, NO MATTER WHAT
HAPPENED.
I COULDN'T DO THAT WITH YOU.
GETTING YOU OUT, MEANT KEITH WAS
ABLE TO HELP ME AND BAYLOR AND
MISSY GET JON OUT, AND AFTER JON
WENT, GETTING OUT BAYLOR MEANT
ALL THE COUPLES IN MY BIG,
STRONG ALLIANCE WAS GONE, AND WE
WERE A BUNCH OF SINGLES.
SOAS IT WAS PROBABLY YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, MOMMA.
YOU CLAIM TO BE THE MOTHER IN
THIS GAME.
WHAT WAS SO MOTHERLY ABOUT THE
WAY YOU PLAYED THE GAME JAI
CENTERED MYSELF IN THE MOM
POSITION IN THE MIDDLE OF WHAT
WE CALLED OUR DYSFUNCTIONAL
FAMILY AND I AS THE MOM GOT TO
DIRECT PEOPLE TO VOTE FOR THE
PEOPLE I WANTED OUT WHICH WERE
THE PEOPLE THAT WOULD SAY THEY
DIDN'T TRUST ME, STARTING WITH
YOUR BROTHER, DREW.
THAT'S WHAT I DID.
I STAYED IN THE CONTROL POSITION
AND DIRECTED MY PEOPLE TO DO
WHAT THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO DO.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: THANKS, ALEC.
BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
>> OH!
OH, MY GOSH!
SO HAPPY FOR YOU GUYS.
OBVIOUSLY, I LIKE BEING A GIRL
AND LIKE SEEING THREE LADIES UP
THERE, REPRESENT.
OKAY, I JUST WANT TO TALK TO MY
MOM FOR A SEC.
SO, MOM, I'M GOING TO TRY NOT TO
CRY.
SO, OBVIOUSLY, THIS IS MUCH MORE
THAN A GAM FOR YOU AND ME JUST
BECAUSE RELATING IT TO OUR LIFE
BACK HOME, WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
THE RINGER TOGETHER.
AND WE WENT THROUGH THE RINGER
TOGETHER HERE AS WELL.
I FEEL LIKE WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN ON
ONE FOOT, HOBBLING THROUGH
MARRIAGES AND DIVORCES AND MEN
COMING INTO OUR LIFE AND OUT.
YOU KNOW, BEING BLINDSIDED, AND
I FEEL LIKE YOU MAKING IT TO THE
FINAL THREE ON ONE FOOT IS THE
MOST INCREDIBLE THING YOU'VE
EVER DONE IN OUR LIFE.
SO I'M SUPER PROUD OF YOU, JUST
SO YOU KNOW.
I LOVE YOU.
CONGRATS, YOU GUYS.
>> I LOVE YOU BACK.
THAT'S THE BEST HUG I'VE EVER
HAD, RIGHT THERE.
I'LL TAKE IT.
>> Jeff: JOSH, YOU'RE UP.
>> HEY, GUYS, WELL DONE.
I CAN'T SAY THEY DON'T WISH I
WAS RIGHT IN THOSE POSITIONS
TONIGHT, BUT YOU GUYS ARE THERE
AND NOT ME, SO GOOD JOB ON YOU.
JACLYN, I GUESS I WANT TO KNOW
DO YOU THINK THAT THE REASON WHY
YOU'RE HERE TONIGHT IS FROM,
LIKE, THE STRENGTH OF YOUR OWN
MERIT OR DO YOU THINK CHOICES
MADE BY STRONGER PLAYERS IN THIS
GAME IS THE REASON WHY YOU'RE
SITTING HERE?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
I MEAN, EVERY DECISION BETWEEN
ME AND JON WAS ARGUED AND
THOUGHT OUT AND DISCUSSED.
THAT'S WHY JON AND I WENT OFF
ALONE TOGETHER MULTIPLE TIMES
AND WEIGHED OUT PROS AND CONS OF
EVERYTHING.
IF YOU'RE SAYING STRONGER
PLAYER, MEANING JON, NO.
MY MERIT CARRIED A LOT OF THOSE
DECISIONS.
>> CAN YOU JUST GIVE US, LIKE,
ONE MOVE THAT WAS SOLELY YOUR
MOVE, AND NOT INVOLVING ANYONE
ELSE, THAT IT WAS YOUR IDEA.
>> VOTING YOU OUT WAS MY MOVE
AND MY IDEA.
>> OKAY.
COOL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Jeff: WES, YOU'RE UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> ME PLAYING WITH MY DAD WAS
AWESOME, AND I'VE BEEN WATCHING
SINCE I WAS NINE, FINALLY
GETTING TO PLAY WITH HIM WAS
LIKE, OH, CRAP.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST A GREAT
EXPERIENCE, AND MY QUESTION TO
Y'ALL IS WHAT WAS IT LIKE
GETTING TO PLAY WITH YOUR LOVED
ONE?
Y'ALL CAN DECIDE WHO GOES FIRST.
>> FOR ME IT WAS LIKE A DREAM
COME TRUE.
BAYLOR AND I HAVE TAKEN MANY
CRAZY PATHS, AND THIS ONE, BY
FAR, WAS THE BEST.
BUT I ADORE YOUR DAD.
WE PLAYED FROM THE VERY START OF
THIS GAME TOGETHER, AND HE WAS
THE SHOULDER WHO LITERALLY
CARRIED ME WHEN I BROKE MY FOOD
FOOT.
SO I LOVED THAT, TOO.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I LIKE THAT.
>> PLAYING WITH JON WAS A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, BOYFRIEND-GIRLFRIEND
SCENARIO IS DIFFERENT THAN
MOTHER-DAUGHTER, FATHER-SON,
OBVIOUSLY.
BUT IT'S BEEN A GREAT
EXPERIENCE.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S BEEN A
COMMUNICATION THING FOR US,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> NAT?
>> YOU KNOW, THE LONGEST I'VE
BEEN APART FROM NADIYA WAS
PROBABLY A WEEK AND A HALF, AND
IT'S BEEN 36 DAYS I HAVEN'T
HEARD FROM HER, TALKED TO HER--
OH, MY GOSH.
I'M GOING TO CRY-- OR SEEN HER.
AND I FEEL LIKE EVEN THOUGH I
DIDN'T GET TO PLAY WITH NAWDIO,
THE FACT THAT DITHIS ALONE MAKES
ME PROUD BECAUSE I'VE NEVER DONE
ANYTHING WITHOUT HER.
I'VE DONE THIS WHOLE THING NOT
THINKING ABOUT MAKING NAWD YEAH
PROUD AND IF SHE GOT KICKED OUT
FIRST, MY TORCH WAS GOING TO BE
THE LAST TO PUT OUT.
>> Jeff: DID YOU GET WHAT YOU
NEEDED?
>> I GOT WHAT I NEEDED.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHAT'S UP?
I'M A STUDENT OF THIS GAME.
AND WHEN YOU ALL MAKE BIG MOVES,
I LIKE THAT.
YOU MADE A BIG MOVE ON ME.
I APPLAUD THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
GOOD JOB.
I THINK IT COULD HAVE GONE BAD,
BUT THE BEST PLAYER IS GOING TO
WIN.
NO MATTER-- EVERYBODY HERE, THE
BEST PLAYER IS GOING TO WIN.
AND I THOUGHT I WAS UP THERE,
BUT Y'ALL GOT ME.
BUT, CLEARLY, NAT BALLED OUT.
LIKE YOU GOTTA JUST GIVE IT TO
HER.
SHE BALLED OUT, SHOW GIVE HER,
HER CREDIT.
DON'T BE MAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
WE ALL WISH WE WERE THERE, BUT
WE AIN'T.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
DON'T BE BAD.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
I HAVE NOTHING BAD TO SAY ANY
ANYBODY.
I DON'T EVEN NEED A
BACK-AND-FORTH.
I FEEL GOOD.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU ALL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: THANKS, JEREMY.
ALL RIGHT, REED, YOU'RE UP.
>> LADIES, JUST A FEW THINGS
BEFORE WE CLOSE TONIGHT.
NAT, I JUST HAVE TO SAY THEY
LOVED WATCHING YOUR GAME PLAY.
IT WAS DYNAMIC AT TIMES A LITTLE
SPASTIC.
I THOUGHT YOU MADE SOME REALLY
GREAT CHOICE.
SO I JUST WANTED TO SAY
CONGRATS, IT'S AWESOME.
>> OH, THANKS.
>> JACLYN, YOU'RE ANOTHER PERSON
I REALLY ENJOYED GETTING TO KNOW
OUT HERE, AND IT WAS SO FUNNY
BECAUSE I NEVER REALLY FELT LIKE
WE COULD GET OUR PLAN TO
CONVERGE TOGETHER, BUT THAT
DIDN'T STOP ME FROM TRYING WITH
YOU AND STILL HAVING A GOOD TIME
TRYING TO PLAY THE GAME.
IT WAS NICE TO GET TO PLAY WITH
YOU.
AND I DO LOOKED FOR TO, YOU
KNOW, HANGING OUT WITH YOU
AFTERWARDS.
MISSY, YOU CAST YOURSELF AS THE
MOTHERLY FIGURE.
HOWEVER, FANS OF CLASSIC
LITERARY FICTION WILL SEE
THROUGH VERY QUICKLY TO WHO YOUR
TRUE CHARACTER WAS, WHICH WAS
THE WICKED STEP-MOTHER, REALLY,
OF THE TRIBE.
IT'S THE ECCENTRIC WOMAN WHO
COMES IN AND MAKES DEMANDS OF
EVERYONE TO THE THINGS FOR WHICH
SHE FEELS SO ENTITLED.
SHE SPOILS HER CHILDRENS BY BYE
PERHAPS GIVING THEM MORE RICE AT
DINNER OR THE BEST PLACES TO
SLEEP AT NIGHT IN THE SHELTER.
SHE TAKES THINGS THAT SHE'S
EITHER NOT ENTITLED TO OR DIDN'T
EARN HERSELF WHICH WAS ALWAYS
EVIDENCED BY THE FACT YOU GOT
MORE GIMMES IN THIS GAME THAN
ANYONE AND PERFORMED THE WORST
OUT OF ANYONE AT CHALLENGES.
LASTLY, YOU MADE THE
QUINTESSENTIAL WICKED
STEP-MOTHER MOVE BY ABUSING THE
HELP, WHICH IN THIS CASE, WAS
THE MINORITY ALLIANCES
THROUGHOUT THE GAME.
YOU ALWAYS MADE SURE THEY FELT
INFERIOR.
YOU ALWAYS KEPT THEM IN THEIR
PLACE.
AND YOU ALWAYS MADE IT EMINENTLY
CLEAR, THEY WEREN'T COMING TO
THE BALL, WHICH IS THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL THIS EVENING HERE, WITH
YOU.
THAT ALWAYS FELT LIKE YOUR FATAL
FLAW IN YOUR WHOLE PLAN.
UNLIKE LIFE, IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR," THE OUTCASTS ARE THE
ONES WHO GET THE FINAL SAY.
SO IN A SWEEPING MOMENT OF
POETIC JUSTICE, THE PEOPLE TO
WHICH YOU WERE SO RUDE AND
TERRIBLE TO BEFORE RELEGATING
THEM TO THE JURY WITH THE HELP
OF YOUR ALLIANCE ARE GOING TO
DECIDE YOUR FATE THIS EVENING.
THIS IS WHY I LOVE FAIRY TALES
BECAUSE THEY ALWAYS HAVE A HAPPY
ENDING.
AND THE WICKED STEP-MOTHER,
NEVER WINS.
NAT, JACLYN, GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS A LIVELY
FINAL TRIBAL FOR SURE.
THIS IS WHAT COMES WITH MAKING
IT TO THE FINAL THREE.
A JURY WHO IS GOING TO MAKE YOU
EARN IT EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
>> BAIL ODON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> STOP!
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> I KNOW!
>> JUST LET ME BREATHE FOR A
SECOND.
GOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY, IN A
MOMENT, YOU WILL VOTE FOR THE
LAST TIME.
THIS VOTE IS A MILLION-DOLLAR
VOTE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MOMENT TO TAKE
IN EVERYTHING YOU'VE HEARD
TONIGHT, AND THEN WE WILL VOTE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JURY,
AFTER 39 DAYS IT COMES DOWN TO
THIS.
YOU'RE GOING TO CAST YOUR VOTE
FOR EITHER MISSY OR JACLYN OR
NATALIE, THE PERSON YOU THINK
MOST DESERVING OF THE TITLE OF
"SOLE SURVIVOR" AND THE
MILLION-DOLLAR CHECK THAT GOES
ALONG WITH IT.
FOR THE LAST TIME, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JOSH, YOU'RE UP.
>> I LOVE YOU.
I'M SO PROUD THAT I GET TO WRITE
YOUR NAME DOWN TONIGHT.
>> YOU DID YOUR THING, GIRL.
>> MOM, I LOVE YOU, AND I THINK
YOU PLAYED THE BEST GAME, NO
MATTER WHAT ANYBODY ELSE SAYS,
AND I'LL ALWAYS BE YOUR NUMBER
ONE FAN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: MISSY, JACLYN,
NATALIE, JURY, THANK YOU FOR
ANOTHER FUN SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
I WILL SEE YOU BACK IN THE U.S.
FOR THE READING OF THE VOTES.
GOOD NIGHT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: THANK YOU!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S BRING IT DOWN.
LET'S GET TO THIS.
IT'S BEEN A FUN NIGHT.
LOVED DOING THIS LIVE.
LOVED BEING WITH YOU GUYS AND
HAVING THIS PARTY HERE.
I WISH EVERYBODY AT HOME COULD
EXPERIENCE THIS, THE ENERGY IN
HERE.
BUT NOW IT IS TIME TO FINISH UP
THIS SEASON.
I GOTTA SAY, TO THE FINAL THREE,
MISSY, JACLYN, NATALIE, IN A
SEASON THAT STARTED OUT WITH
MORE MEN THAN WOMEN, TO END UP
WITH A FINAL THREE OF WOMEN
SPEAKS TO WHAT SOMEBODY SAID
EARLIER-- GIRL POWER, NICELY
DONE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TO THE JURY, THAT WAS-- THAT WAS
TOUGH.
REED.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
WELL-- WELL DELIVERED, BUT THAT
WAS ROUGH.
I CAN'T WAIT TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
OKAY, LET'S GET TO IT.
VOTES IN HERE FOR A WINNER
TONIGHT, AND ONLY TIME ON
"SURVIVOR" YOU WANT TO SEE YOUR
NAME ON THESE VOTES.
THESE ARE FOR THE WIN.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST VOTE.
JACLYN.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
NAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
ONE VOTE JACLYN, ONE VOTE NAT.
JACLYN.
TWO VOTES JACLYN, ONE VOTE NAT.
MISSY.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TWO VOTES JACLYN, ONE VOTE
NATALIE, ONE VOTE MISSY.
NAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES NATALIE,
TWO VOTES JACLYN, ONE VOTE
MISSY.
NAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THAT'S THREE VOTES NATALIE, TWO
VOTES JACLYN, ONE VOTE MISSY.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR: SAN
JUAN DEL SUR," NATALIE.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR WINNER, NATALIE, WHO
PLAYED WITHOUT HER LOVED ONE
LONGER THAN ANYBODY ELSE, USED
THAT TO HER ADVANTAGE.
VERY UNPREDICTABLE SEASON AND
THERE'S A LOT TO TALK ABOUT, FOR
INSTANCE, ARE JON AND JACLYN
STILL TOGETHER?
IT WAS QUITE A FIGHT.
AND THE FIGHT BETWEEN NATALIE
AND JOHN ROCKER, WAS THAT
ACTUALLY A STRATEGIC MOVE BY
NATALIE?
PLUS JOSH AND REED AN OPENLY GAY
CHRISTIAN COUPLE ARE GOING
BEYOND "SURVIVOR" AND CHANGING
LIVES.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU WHAT
WE'RE DOING FOR SEASON 30 AS
WELL.
AND IT'S AWESOME.
IT'S THE "SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN DEL
SUR: BLOOD VS. WATER" LIVE
REUNION SHOW.
THAT'S NEXT.