>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON SURVIVOR
NINE PAIRS OF LOVED ONES
WERE DROPPED IN NICARAGUA
TO BEGIN THE ADVENTURE OF A
LIFETIME TOGETHER, BUT THEY WERE
QUICKLY PULLED APART.
>> Jeff: IF YOU HAVE ORANGE
YOUR NAME IS COYOPA.
IF YOU HAVE BLUE YOUR NAME IS
HUNAHPU.
SAY YOUR GOOD-BYES.
IN A BRAND NEW TWIST-- YOU'RE
COMPETING AGAINST YOUR WIFE.
LOVED ONES WERE FORCED TO FACE
OFF FOR REWARD WITH THE LOSER
HEADED TO EXILE ISLAND.
JEREMY WINS REWARD FOR HIS
TRIBE!
AFTER GER ME WON--
>> YOU'RE GOING TO CHOOSE ONE
PERSON FROM YOUR TRIBE TO JOIN
HER.
HE SENT KEITH TO JOIN HIS WIFE
AT EXILE ISLAND.
>> IT'S MY FAULT THAT SHE'S
GONE.
>> Jeff: AT COYOP COYOPA,
RELATIONSHIPS WERE ALREADY
FORMING.
>> WES BUSTED ME.
"WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?"
>> Jeff: WHILE THE HUNAHPU
TRIBE WAS GETTING ALL THE
DETAILS THEY COULD STOMACH.
>> HE'S JUST KIND OF LIKE A
YOUNG DUMB GUY.
>> BA-DA-BING, BA-DA-BOOM.
>> Jeff: AT EXILE ISLAND VAL
CAUGHT A BREAK AND GOT THE
BIGGEST PIECE OF INFORMATION.
>> I GOT A CLUE FOR THE IDOL.
>> Jeff: AT THE FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, VAL AND KEITH
RETURNED FROM EXILE ISLAND, AND
HUNAHPU WON.
HUNAHPU WINS IMMUNITY!
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL IT LOOKED
IT WAS THE WOMEN.
>> Jeff: BUT A SECRET ALLIANCE
BETWEEN BAYLOR AND JOSH-- KEPT
THE VOTE UP IN THE AIR.
WHERE IS YOUR HEAD?
HAVE YOU TALKED TO THE GUYS?
>> THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT
NADIYA.
>> I THINK I'M KIND OF RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE BETWEEN THE GUYS'
ALLIANCE AND THE GIRLS'
ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
JOSH WENT ROGUE.
>> I AM SO SORRY.
>> Jeff: AND BAYLOR VOTED FOR
NADIYA.
>> Jeff: FIRST PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN DEL
SUR-- BLOOD VS. WATER," NADIYA.
BREAKING APART THE WOMEN'S
ALLIANCE AND LEAVING VAL AND
JACLYN ALL ALONE.
NADIYA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
17 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT.
>> LISTEN, DON'T GET UPSET WITH
ME.
THERE'S A METHOD TO MY MADNESS.
I PUT YOUR NAME DOWN.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT, I
VOTED FOR BAYLOR TO FURTHER
ADVANCE OUR ALLIANCE IN THIS
GAME.
I TONIGHT WANT THE GUYS THINKING
I WAS GETTING TOO CLOSE TO
BAYLOR, BUT I STILL WANTED TO
KEEP BAYLOR ASAB ASSET.
>> WOW.
>> DO NOT BE MAD AT ME.
>> JOSH COMES UP TO ME.
HE EXPLAINED TO ME WHAT WAS
APPARENTLY A GAME MOVE BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T WANT THE GUYS TO KNOW
THAT ME AND HIM ARE ALIGNED.
>> THAT WAS A SMART MOVE IN A
WAY BUT IT WAS ALSO SKETCHY AND
SCARY THAT HE DIDN'T TELL ME
BEFORE HE WAS GOING TO WRITE MY
NAME DOWN.
I REALLY HOPE THEY CAN TRUST
HIM.
>> I'LL PROBABLY SPLIT MY PANTS
BECAUSE THESE ARE DEMAM.
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I CAN DO THAT.
>> BENDY.
>> THAT'S GOOD, YEAH!
I'M GOING TO BE EVEN MORE PROUD
OF MYSELF.
>> I'LL DO THE PUSH-UPS.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
THAT WAS TOO INTENSE FOR ME.
>> WE HAVE JON AND WE HAVE DREW
AND THEY'RE BOTH LIKE CARTOON
CHARACTERS.
>> I WAS SECOND IN THE WORLD IN
TAE KWON DO.
>> ARE THEY LISTENING TO
THEMSELVES?
THEY'RE SO HAPPY AND IT'S, LIKE
NOT REAL, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
SAYING?
WHICH FOR ME IS GOOD BECAUSE I
KNOW ALL THE GIRLS CAN'T STAND
THEM ALREADY.
>> I CAN UNDERSTAND IF YOU'RE
LIFTING A LOG TO BRING IT OVER
HERE, BUT JUST IN THE MEAN,
THAT'S ONLY 50 POUNDS.
SO YOU'RE SQUATTING 50 POUNDS.
YOU THINK THAT'S A BIG DEAL,
BRO?
THAT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
>> I THINK WE HAVE POSSIBLY LOST
OUR FLINT.
>> GONE, YOU MEAN, LIKE YOU
CAN'T FIND IT?
>> IT'S NOT IN ANYONE'S POCKET?
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> BOYS?
>> I CANNOT BELIEVE WE LOST THE
FLINT.
LOSING THAT IS NOT GOOD.
WELL, GREAT.
>> I MEAN, I STRUCK THE FLINT IN
THE FIRE.
I MUST HAVE SET IT DOWN THERE, I
GUESS.
>> I LEARNED IF YOU'RE WRONG,
YOU ADMIT IT, AND YOU ADMIT IT
EMPHATICALLY SO PEOPLE KNOW NOT
ONLY DOES HE KNOW HE'S WRONG.
HE FEELS AWFUL ABOUT IT AND HE'S
PROBABLY GOING TO DO A LOT TO
MAKE UP FOR ME.
I'M THINKING I'M-- LIKE JON
POURED THE RICE IN THE FIRE!
JON LOST THE FLINT!
IS THAT ACCEPTED BY EVERYONE?
I HAVE NO IDEA UPON.
I MEAN, I'M VERY NERVOUS ABOUT
IT, VERY NERVOUS ABOUT IT.
>> DO YOU NEED FLINT TO START A
FIRE?
>> IT HELPS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
COYOPA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW COYOPA TRIBE.
NADIYA VOTED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NATALIE, IS THIS ONE OF THE
FIRST TIME YOU'VE TRULY BEEN
WITHOUT YOUR SISTER?
>> YEAH.
TRULY, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES THAT FEEL
LIKE?
>> UM-- I TOLD EVERYBODY I
HAVEN'T CRIED IN, LIKE, 10
YEARS.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
NOT A TEAR IN A DECADE?
>> I NEVER CRY.
>> Jeff: IS THE EMOTION MORE
FOR YOUR SISTER THAT SHE'S OUT,
OR FOR YOU THAT YOU'RE ALONE?
>> IT JUST REALLY HURTS BECAUSE
YOU KNOW THERE IS PEOPLE HERE
THAT HAVE BEEN TOGETHER YOU KNOW
FIVE YEARS, SIX YEAR.
ME AND NADIYA HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR 28 YEARS.
IT'S JUST REALLY HARD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THE GAME
MOVES ON.
YOU GOOD TO GO?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO YOUR NEXT REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TRIBE WILL BALANCE A BALL ON A
DISK ATTACHED TO A POLE AS YOU
MANEUVER THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES.
YOUR BALL TROPS, GUBACK TO THE
START.
ONE YOU FINISH, YOU MUST THEN
ROLL THREE BECAUSE LANDING THEM
IN A SERIES OF TARGETS.
THE FIRST TO FINISH WINS REWARD
FOR YOUR TRIBE.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YES.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: IT'S A GOOD ONE.
MASSIVE AMOUNT OF FISHING GEAR,
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO GET SOME
FISH AND CHANGE YOUR WORLD.
BIG REWARD.
WE'RE GOING TO ONCE AGAIN ROCK,
PAPER, SIDSOR TO SEE WHO GETS
THE ADVANTAGE OF PUTTING UP
FIRST.
JOHN VERSUS REED IN ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSOR.
PAPER COVERS ROCK.
JOHN WINS FOR HIS TRIBE.
COYOPA, WHO ARE YOU GOING TO PUT
UP?
THIS IS ANOTHER LOVED ONE
SHOWDOWN.
JOHN IS GOING TO DO IT.
THAT MEANS HE'S TAKING ON JULIE.
COME ON DOWN.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> EASY!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR
SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
BIG STAKES-- WINNER WINS FOR
THEIR TRIBE FISHING GEAR.
LOSER GOES TO EXILED.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
JOHN VERSUS JULIE.
JOHN OFF TO A GOOD START.
>> TAKE A DEEP BREATH, JOHN, YOU
CAN DO THIS.
>> SLOW AND STEADY, GIRL.
>> SLOW LIKE THAT, YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: JOHN DROPS, GOTTA GO
BACK.
THAT IS PART OF THIS CHALLENGE.
YOUR BALL IS GOING TO DROP.
DON'T DESPAIR.
JULIE GOT A LITTLE MOMENTUM NOW.
>> EASY.
NICE?
>>
>> SHHH!
SHHH!
>> WAIT FOR IT.
>> Jeff: JULIE HAS SOME NICE
MOMENTUM.
SHE'S HALFWAY THROUGH THE
COURSE.
>> SLOW DOWN, JULIE.
>> DON'T EVEN RUSH IT, JULIE,
YOU'VE GOT TIME.
>> Jeff: JOHN GOING FOR THAT
FIRST BIG OBSTACLE, AND HE HAS
CLEARED IT.
JOHN THROUGH THE TOUGHEST PART
SO FAR FOR HIM WITH HIS HEIGHT.
JULIE HAS A GOOD PACE GOING.
GLAWN RIGHT ON HER TAIL.
WE ARE VERY CLOSE.
>> STAY FOCUSED, JOHN.
>> Jeff: JOHN ONCE AGAIN HAS
TO DUCK UNDER A POLE.
>> ARGH!
>> Jeff: HE CAN'T DO IT.
JOHN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
NOW IT'S JEWEL BAEK IN THE LEAD.
JOHN GETTING FRUSTRATED.
HE WAS SO CLOSE.
JULIE NOW UNDER THAT SECOND
POST.
SHE'S GOT IT.
JULIE DOING A NICE JOB.
SHE'S ALMOST AT THE END OF THIS
FIRST PART OF THE CHALLENGE.
JULIE'S GOOD.
START ROLLING BALLS.
HAVE TO LAND THREE BALLS NOW.
JOHN COMING UP TO HIS NEMESIS,
THAT SECOND POST.
NICE SAVE.
HE IS THROUGH.
AND HE DROPS!
JOHN'S GOT TO GO ALL THE WAY
BACK AGAIN.
A HUGE TIME LOSS.
JULIE LANDS HER FIRST BALL,
WORKING ON HER SECOND.
JULIE LANDS HER SECOND BALL.
VERY CLOSE TO WINNING REWARD FOR
HER TRIBE.
JOHN VERY CLOSE TO HEADING TO
EXILED.
NOBODY WOULD PREDICT THIS.
JULIE JUST MISSES.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
YOU STILL HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS!
JULIE WINS REWARD FOR HER TRIBE,
SENDING JOHN, HER BOYFRIEND, TO
EXILED!
>> GREAT JOB.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: JULIE, IS THIS
UNUSUAL?
>> YEAH, IT'S VERY UNUSUAL.
WHEN IT'S ANYTHING LIKE
CHALLENGING OR ATHLETIC OR-- I
MEAN, HE'S GOT IT, YOU KNOW.
IT KIND OF SUCTION BECAUSE I
KNOW I'M GOOD AT SOME THINGS BUT
HE'S REALLY GOOD AT A LOT OF
THINGS.
>> Jeff: JOHN, WHAT IS THIS
LIKE FOR YOU TO NOT ONLY LOSE,
BECAUSE THAT'S TOUGH FOR
ANYBODY.
BUT YOU'RE LOSING TO YOUR
GIRLFRIEND.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO EXILE.
>> REMOVE THE "FRIEND" PART.
I'M LOSING TO A GIRL.
I JUST GOT BEAT BY A GIRL.
>> Jeff: JULIE, COME ON OVER
NEXT TO ME.
GOOD NEWS IS YOU'VE WON A
MASSIVE REWARD FOR YOUR TRIBE.
THE TOUGH PART IS YOU NOW HAVE
TO SEND SOMEBODY FROM YOUR TRIBE
TO JOIN JOHN ON EXILE.
>> OH, YOU GUYS!
THIS IS SO DIFFICULT.
>> Jeff: WHO'S IS GOING TO BE?
>> JEREMY YOU WENT THROUGH SO
MUCH, I JUST HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION, AND IT'S SO HARD.
I HOPE YOU DON'T HOLD IT AGAINST
ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SWAP
SPOTS.
JEREMY WILL COME DOWN AND JOIN
JOHN.
JULIE RETURNS TO HER TRIBE.
JEREMY AND JOHN, YOU'LL HEAD TO
EXILED.
YOU WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR YOUR
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
GO ON AND HEAD OUT.
HUNAHPU, THE WINNING STREAK
CONTINUES.
CONGRATULATIONS.
NICE BIG REWARD.
COME DOWN AND GET IT.
HEAD OUT.
>> JEFF, JEFF, WE HAVE KIND OF A
NOT-TRADITIONAL SITUATION THAT
WE'D LIKE TO PROPOSE TO YOU.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
>> OUR TRIBE SEEMS TO HAVE
MISPLACED OUR FLINT.
AND SO WE WERE WONDERING IF WE
COULD POTENTIALLY BARTER WITH
YOU AND TAKE THE FISHING
EQUIPMENT BUT TRADE YOU THE
BEANS FOR OUR FLINT.
>> Jeff: FIRST, LET ME
UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION.
SO THE TRIBE WITH TWO FIREMEN,
KEITH AND JEREMY, YOU'VE LOST
IT.
>> IT'S GONE, JEFF.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WANT TO MAKE A
TRADE BUT YOU WANT TO KEEP THE
FISHING GEAR AND YOU WANT TO
TRADE THE BEANS.
WALK ME THROUGH THIS FROM A
NEGOTIATION STANDPOINT.
YOU'RE THE ONES WHO NEED TO MAKE
THE DEAL.
MY LIFE IS FINE.
SO YOU COME IN, SURVEY THE
SCENE, SEE WHAT THE REWARD IS,
AND THEN OFFER ME THE THING OF
LEAST VALUE, POSSIBLY A HALF A
BAG OF BEANS AT THIS POINT, I'M
GUESSING.
>> A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN THAT.
>> JEFF, IF YOU DON'T ASK, YOU
DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S ALMOST FULL.
>> Jeff: A BETTER NEGOTIATION
WOULD HAVE BEEN TO WALK IN AT
THE TOP OF THE CHALLENGE SAY,
"CAN WE TRADE OUR BEANS?"
STRAIGHT UP.
YOU CAME IN TO SEE IF YOU COULD
WIN, AND THEN LEVERAGED THAT.
AND THAT DOESN'T WORK ON
"SURVIVOR."
I GOT ONE OFFER FOR YOU IF YOU
WANT TO MAKE IT, AND THAT IS YOU
GIVE UP ALL THIS FISHING GEAR
FOR A NEW FLINT.
>> NO, WE'LL JUST KEEP
COLLECTING FIREWOOD.
>> Jeff: NOW I KNOW WHEN YOU
DON'T HAVE A FLINT, WHEN IT
RAINS AND IT WILL AND YOUR FIRE
GOES OUT, AND NOW YOU NEED TO
MAKE A TRADE, THE PAIN WILL BE
MUCH TOUGHER.
THIS IS YOUR OPPORTUNITY NOW TO
SEIZE IT IF YOU WANT IT, BECAUSE
I PROMISE YOU TO GET A FLIPT
LATER WILL COST YOU MORE THAN
FISHING GEAR.
>> WE'LL KEEP THE FIRE GOING.
>> I'LL EAT RAW FISH.
>> NO, WE CAN'T SURVIVE WITHOUT
FIRE.
>> NO, WE'RE GOING TO KEEP THE
FIRE GOING.
>> YOU GUYS --
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE DECISION.
>> WE GOT DPAWRNTED--
>> WE'LL TAKE THE FLINT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE'LL
LEAVE THE FISHING GEAR BEHIND.
YOU'LL HAVE A NEW FLINT WAITING
FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
>> OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: COYOPA, I GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
HUNAHPU, GRAB YOUR STUFF AND
HEAD OUT.
>> CATCHING SOME FISH WOULD HAVE
BEEN JUST HEAVENLY.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE DIDN'T GET IT
BECAUSE ALL WE DID WAS TRADE IT
FOR FLINT.
LOSING THE FLINT WAS A PRETTY
BIG MISTAKE.
IT WAS MY FAULT WE WASTED OUR
CHANCE AT FISHING GEAR.
>> YAY!
FLINT!
>> LET'S NAIL IT TO A TREE.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> GOOD JOB, JULIE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT WAS AWESOME, AWESOME,
AWESOME.
>> I LITERALLY HAVEN'T CRIED
FOREVER.
>> IT'S PENT UP PUP NEED TO GET
IT OUT.
>> YOU KNOW ALL THE STUFF WE'VE
BEEN GOING THROUGH.
YOU CAN LET IT ALL OUT NOW.
>> I WOULD HAVE SAID I THINK
THERE'S NO OTHER BOND BESIDES A
MOM AND A DAUGHTER, BUT MAN,
TWINS.
WOO"P" AND IT'S REALLY PRETTY
TOUCHING TO SEE A TOUGH GIRL
CRY.
I WANT TO HELP HER.
SHE'S AS BIG AND BAD ASS AS YOU
ARE YOU SHE'S PERFECTLY FINE.
>> YOU CAN REMIND YOURSELF IT'S
A GAME BUT IT'S STILL YOUR
FAMILY.
IF IT WAS YOUR DUDE, YOU WOULD
PROBABLY BE ALL RIGHT.
BUT IT'S YOUR SISTER.
>> NADIYA GOT VOTED OFF, AND
SHE'S PROBABLY FINE.
IT'S JUST THAT WE'RE NOT
TOGETHER.
THAT'S THE HARD PART.
NOW IT'S REALLY GOOD MOTIVATION
FOR ME TO KEEP MY HEAD IN THE
GAME AND JUST PLAY HARD SO THAT
I CAN JUST AT LEAST GO AS FAR AS
I CAN.
>> I CAN TOTALLY REMEMBER SEEING
ROCKER, ATLANTA BRAVES, ON THE
BACK OF THEIR JERSEYS.
>> WHAT'S HIS LAST NAME?
>> ROCKER.
THAT'S MY POINT.
>> JOHN ROCKER?
>> JOHN ROCKER.
>> WAS HE THE GUY THAT GOT RAN
OUT OF THE LEAGUE?
>> THE WHAT?
>> I'M NOT SURE BUT THERE WAS A
PITCHER FOR ATLANTA THAT GAVE AN
INTERVIEW, AND HE LET EVERYBODY
KNOW WHAT HE THOUGHT ABOUT THE
ETHNIC MAKEUP OF THE PEOPLE THAT
RIDE THE SUBWAYS IN NEW YORK.
HE GOT OFSRACIZED FOR BASEBALL
JUST ABOUT FOR IT.
>> WELL, MAYBE HE'S CHANGED.
>> JUST BECAUSE JOHN DOES THINGS
I DON'T LIKE, DOESN'T MEAN I
DON'T WANT TO WORK WITH HIM
BECAUSE I THINK THAT MAKES HIM
EVEN MORE OF AN ASSET TO BE USED
BECAUSE HE'S PISSING OFF SO MANY
PEOPLE ALREADY THAT, YES, I WANT
HIM ON MY TIME TEAM!
>> JOHN AND JEREMY ON EXILE.
>> BETTER BE A BIG DAMN ISLAND.
>> EXILED IS NOT A HAPPY PLACE.
IT'S DESOLATE.
IT'S DRY.
THERE ARE NO COCONUTS.
IT IS NOT A GOOD PLACE TO BE.
PLUS THE ICING ON TOP IS NOW I'M
STUCK OUT HERE WITH JOHN ROCKY.
I KNOW WHO HE IS.
HE USED TO PITCH FOR THE BRAVES
AND EVERYTHING.
>> YOU MUST EACH CHOOSE AN URN.
HE WAS PLAGUING AGAIN THE NEW
YORK METS, AND TALKING ABOUT
BLACK PEOPLE AND HOMOSEXUALS AND
ALL THIS OTHER STUFF.
I CAN'T REMEMBER EXACTLY WHAT HE
SAID BUT I REMEMBER HE SAID
RACIST THINGS.
>> BUPKUS.
IT'S NOTHING.
>> IT IS UP TO YOU WHETHER YOU
SHARE THIS INFORMATION WITH
ANYBODY ELSE.
I'M NOT SAYING JOHN ROCK SER A
RACIST.
YOU CAN STAY STUFF LIKE THAT BUT
IT WILL FOLLOW YOU THE REST OF
YOUR LIFE.
HE COULD HAVE CHANGED BUT IT
WILL STILL FOR YOU.
NOW I NEED HIM TO PROTECT MY
WIFE SO I'M GOING TO BUDDY UP
WITH HIM A LITTLE BIT "THERE'S
AN IDOL HIDDEN BACK AT YOUR
CAMP.
YOUR WELL UPON HELP.
DIG, WATER, NORTH, SEVEN."
I'M THINKING YOU PROTECT VAL,
AND I PROTECT JULIE.
I JUST THREW OUT, YOU TAKE CARE
OF VAL, I'LL TAKE CARE OF JULIE,
AND IT WILL BE GOOD.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GIVE VAL TIME
ON HER SIDE TO WORK SOME MAGIC,
BUT IF SHE'S VOTED OUT, JULIE'S
GONE RIGHT AFTER HER.
>> I LIKE THAT.
I LIKE IT.
>> DONE AND DONE.
GET TO OUR NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, WE WILL NOW BRING
BACK JEREMY AND JOHN RETURNING
FROM EXILE ISLAND.
( APPLAUSE )
>> WELCOME BACK!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO YOUR NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT BACK, NATALIE.
>> WE'LL TAKE THAT OVER HERE.
>> Jeff: OH, REALLY?
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO SQUARE OFF ONE ON ONE
SUMO STYLE USING A PADDED BAG,
YOU WILL TRY TO KNOCK YOUR
OPPONENT OFF THE PLATFORM AND
INTO THE WATER.
FIRST TRIBE TO SCORE FIVE WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
HUNAHPU HASN'T LOST.
COYOPA HASN'T WON.
HUNAHPU, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
>> KELLEY OR JULIE, RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: WHO'S GOING TO SIT
OUT?
>> JULIE.
>> Jeff: JULIE TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
>> ALL RIGHT, JULIE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FIRST
ROUND IS TWO WOMEN.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
IT IS KELLEY FOR HUNAHPU.
JACLYN GOING TO GO UP FOR
COYOPA.
>> COME ON, JACKIE.
>> IT'S JACLYN FROM COYOPA,
TAKING ON KELLEY FROM HUNAHPU.
>> LET'S GO, JACKIE, YOU GOT
THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT, KELLEY!
>> COME ON, KELLEY!
LEAVE EVERYTHING OUT THERE.
>> Jeff: HERE WE DP GO, FIRST
ROUND.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
JACLYN COMES OUT STRONG RIGHT
AWAY.
>> YEAH, JACK!
YEAH, JACK!
>> Jeff: KELLEY FIGHTING BACK.
BUT KELLEY IS ON THE EDGE.
JACLYN KNOCKS KELLEY IN.
COYOPA SCORES.
COYOPA LEADS 1-0.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
DUDE, SHE'S BIG!
>> Jeff: OUR FIRST BLOOD
SHOWDOWN, TWO BROTHERS.
ALEC, LITTLE BROTHER TAKING ON
HIS BIG BROTHER, DREW.
HERE WE CAN, COYOPA LEADS
ONE-ZIP.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
DREW SLIPS EARLY.
ALEC HAS HIM.
>> GET HIM OFF!
GET HIM OFF!
>> Jeff: LITTLE BROTHER HAS
HIS BIG BROTHER ON THE MOVE.
DREW NOW PUSHING BACK.
THESE GUYS ARE FIGHTING HARD!
DREW HAS ALEC.
ALEC GOES IN.
HUNAHPU SCORES.
( APPLAUSE )
DREW BEFEET HIS LITTLE BROTHER,
AND TAKING A LOT OF JOY IN IT.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
NEXT MATCH-UP, JEREMY TAKING ON
WES.
SURVIVORS READY?
>> COME ON, JEREMY!
>> HERE WE GO, WES, HE'S COMING
AT YOU HARD.
>> Jeff: JEREMY WITH A BIG
HIT, BUT WES SUSTAINS IT.
WES IS BACK IN THIS.
WES KNOCKS JEREMY OFF!
COYOPA SCORES!
COYOPA LEADS 2-1.
NEXT MATCH-UP, NATALIE GOING TO
TAKE ON VAL.
>> YEAH, VAL.
>> THIS IS FOR NADIYA, NAT.
LET'S SEE IT.
>> Jeff: COYOPA LEADS 2-1.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
NATALIE COMES OUT HARD.
HAS VAL DOWN.
>> RECOVER AND PUSH HER LEGS
OUT.
>> Jeff: VAL FIGHTING BACK
NOW.
NOW IT'S VAL WHO HAS NATALIE ON
HER BACK.
VAL SLOWLY MOVING NATALIE
TOWARDS THE EDGE.
NATALIE IS NOT MOVING.
>> CHOKE HOLD!
>> LET'S GO, VAL, FIGHT!
>> Jeff: NATALIE BACK UP.
NOW SHE'S GOT VAL ON THE EDGE.
>> NATTILY, NOW, NOW, NOW.
>> Jeff: NATALIE PUSHING,
ALMOST HAS HER IN.
VAL GOES IN NATALIE SCORES, WE
ARE TIED 2-2.
>> DAMN, JEREMY'S GOT A
TOUGH-ASS WIFE.
>> Jeff: THE BATTLE OF THE
JOHNS.
THIS COULD BE UGLY.
>> COME ON, JON!
>> COME ON, BIG JOHN.
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED, 2-2,
BIGGEST BATTLE SO FAR.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: A HUGE COLLISION OUT
OF THE GATE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: BOTH GUYS HOLDING
THEIR OWN.
IT IS SLIPPERY, HARD TO STAY ON
YOUR FEET.
JON FROM HUNAHPU DOING A GREAT
JOB AGAINST A MUCH BIGGER GUY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
JON PUSHING HARD.
HE'S GOT HIM CLOSE.
JON SCORES FOR HUNAHPU!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: GOTTA FEEL GOOD WITH
THAT.
WHAT A BATTLE!
HUNAHPU LEADS 3-2!
>> YOU GOT SOME BLOOD ON YOUR
NOSE.
>> Jeff: JOHN, HOW'S YOUR
NOSE?
( BLEEP ).
>> Jeff: MOTHER-DAUGHTER
MATCH-UP.
BEEN WAITING FOR THIS.
NOW, MISSY, MOST PARENTS WOULD
SAY IT IS MUCH TOUGHER TO BE THE
PARENT IN THIS SITUATION TRYING
TO DEFEAT YOUR CHILD.
>> PRETTY TOUGH BUT ALL I GOTTA
DO IS PUT A DIFFERENT FACE ON
HER AND I'M GONNA KILL HER.
>> BAILOSH YOU HEAR THAT?
>> BETTER NOT BREAK MY NOSE.
>> WHO ARE YOU VISUALIZING, ONE
OF THE EXES.
>> AND I'M VISUALIZING ONE OF
THEEXES, TOO.
>> Jeff: WOW, A BATTLE OF THE
EXES.
HUNAHPU LEADS 3-2.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> Jeff: WHAT'S HAPPENING,
BAYLOR?
YOU NEED MEDICAL.
>> NO.
>> SORRY.
>> Jeff: TELL ME WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
IS THERE A TOOTH ISSUE, OR IS IT
BLEEDING?
>> SHE SPLIT HER LIP.
>> YOU'RE FINE.
>> DEEP BREATH, BAYLOR.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: WOW, THAT INSPIRATION
OF THE EXES IS CLEARLY QUITE
POWERFUL.
>> FIGHT THROUGH TGIRL.
PUSH THROUGH THAT PAIN.
A COUPLE OF DEEP BREATHS,
BAYLOR.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, MISSY.
SHE'S OKAY, MISSY.
PLAY THE GAME.
IT'S JUST A GAME.
SURVIVORS READY?
>> MISSY, COME ON.
>> ARE YOU OKAY.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GO!
>> Jeff: MISSY MUCH LESS
STRENGTH.
BAYLOR KNOCKS HER MOM IN THE
WATER AND CELEBRATE.
AND YOU COULD SEE THE DIFFERENCE
IN EMOTION IN MISSY.
DID NOT HAVE THE SAME ENERGY.
WE ARE TIED 3-3.
ANOTHER LOVED ONE MATCH-UP.
REED FROM HUNAHPU TAKING ON HIS
BOYFRIEND JOSH FROM COYOPA.
>> LET'S GJOSH!
>> LET'S GO, JOSH!
>> IT'S REED THAT IS ON OUR
TEAM.
>> Jeff: WE ARE TIED, 3-3,
PLAYING TO FIVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
JOSH AND REED MEET IN THE
MIDDLE.
JOSH HAS REED DOWN.
GOOD BATTLE.
A LOT OF SPINNING AROUND AND
MANEUVERING.
>> GET UP, JOSH!
>> Jeff: PUSHING HARD.
JOSH BACK UP.
REED HAS JOSH ON THE EDGE.
JOSH GOES IN.
REED SCORES FOR HUNAHPU!
>> GOOD JOB, REED.
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU LEADS 4-3.
WE'RE DOWN TO OUR LAST TWO MEN.
KEITH IS GOING TO BE TAKING ON
DALE.
>> CLASH OF THE OLD GUYS.
>> DALE, YOU HAVE THIS.
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU LEADS 4-3.
PLAYING TO 5.
KEITH COULD WIN IT FOR HUNAHPU
RIGHT HERE.
SURVIVORS READY?
>> KEITH YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: GO!
KEITH COMES OUT STRONG EARLY,
BUT DALE CAN TAKE IT.
KEITH NOW ON HIS BACK.
DALE PUSHING HARD.
HE'S GOT KEITH ON THE EDGE.
DALE STILL PUSHING.
KEITH BACK UP!
KEITH IS BACK IN THIS!
DALE KNOCKS HEATING IN.
HUNAHPU SCORES.
WE ARE TIED 4-4.
>> CRAZY, DUDE.
THAT WAS INSANE.
>> YOU TIED IT UP FOR US.
NEXT UP, WE'RE IN A REMATCH,ICLE
FROM HUNAHPU, TAKING ON JACLYN
FROM COYOPA.
IT IS A SHOWDOWN FOR IMMUNITY.
>> COME ON, JACKIE.
FIGHT HARD.
>> Jeff: JACLYN WON THIS THE
FIRST TIME.
COYOPA WOULD LOVE TO WIN A
CHALLENGE AND NOT GO TO TRIBAL.
BIG STAKES KELLEY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: DALE, WHAT'S IT LIKE
SEEING YOUR DAUGHTER OUT THERE?
>> I'M NOT WATCH GLG YOU'RE NOT
WATCHING?
>> I'M NOT WATCH GLG WHY?
>> IT'S HER BIRTHDAY TODAY.
BUT I GOTTA ROOT FOR JACLYN.
>> I'M ALL RIGHT, DAD.
>> COME ON, KELLEY!
>> BIRTHDAY GIRL IS GOING DOWN!
>> COME ON, JACKIE.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
JACLYN VERSUS KELLEY.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE, SURVIVORS
READY, GO!
JACLYN HITS HARD EARLY.
HAS KELLEY DOWN.
>> GET AWAY FROM THE EDGE,
KELLEY!
>> Jeff: KELLEY FIGHTING BACK.
JACLYN IS NOW DOWN.
ICLE YOUY NOW HAS JACLYN ON THE
EDGE.
>> PUSH HER, KELLEY!
YOU GOT IT.
PUSH HER, KELLEY!
>> Jeff: KELLEY COULD WIN IT
RIGHT HERE.
JACLYN'S GOT TO FIGHT BACK.
>> PUSH!
>> Jeff: KELLEY'S GOT HER ON
THE EDGE.
ONE MORE PUSH.
JACLYN GOES IN.
KELLEY WINS FOR HUNAHPU!
HUNAHPU WINS IMMUNITY, REMAINS
UNDEFEATED IN THIS GAME!
>> KELLEY, HAPPY BIRTHDAY, GIRL!
YOU DESERVE IT!
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB!
>> GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: HUNAHPU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS ONCE AGAIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
SWIM OUT.
COYOPA, SECOND TIME HEADING TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE SECOND PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
HEAD OUT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT APT TRIBAL.
>> SOMEBODY IN MY TRIBE IS GOING
HOME TONIGHT AND I AM IN A TIGHT
SITUATION BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
AN IDOL, AND JACLYN'S MY ONE AND
ONLY ALLIANCE.
BUT I'M PREPARED TO MAKE BIG
MOVES TO MAKE SURE THEY STAY IN
THIS GAME.
IT WAS ONE OF THE TOUGHEST
THINGS I EVER HAD TO WATCH.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN PROUDER
THAN ANYBODY IN MY LIFE THAN
KELLEY.
WELL, JACLYN?
>> I CURRENTLY HATE HERE.
BUT IT'S JUST IN THE MOAPT.
I'M SURE I'LL GET OVER IT.
>> SHE NEVER QUIT.
SHE WAS DOWN, HER TRIBE WAS
DOWN, AND SHE GAVE HER TRIBE THE
WIN.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT WAS THE WRONG
TRIBE.
>> IT WAS A PLEASURE HANGING OUT
WITH JEREMY.
>> YOU PROBABLY GOT A CLUE.
>> JEREMY DID.
>> DID HE SHARE IT WITH YOU.
>> YES.
>> I FOUND ONE ON THE ISLAND
HERE.
>> BASICALLY, I'M SAVING ME AND
JACLYN.
RIGHT NOW, I AM IN A TIGHT
SITUATION BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
AN IDOL.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
I AM JUST LYING.
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I HAVE TO PLAY BIG.
OR I'M GOING HOME.
SO SAVE YOURSELF AND FIND IT.
>> VAL'S CLAIMING TO HAVE TWO
IDOLS AND I'VE SEEN THE CLUE.
I THINK AT THIS POINT, I NEED TO
GET OFF MY ASS, AND START
LOOKING FOR IDOLS.
THE CLUE I GOT SAID, "DIG, WEL,
NORTH, 7."
I'M THINKING WELL, SEVEN PACES
NORTH, DIG.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE IT A SHOT.
SEE WHAT WE CAN FIND.
HOPE SOMETHING GOOD TURNS UP.
RIGHT NOW, ALL I'VE GOT IS ROCKS
ROCKS.
AND BINGO, BOYS.
HERE IS WHAT JOHNNY ROCK HAS
BEEN LOOKING FOR.
I FOUND AT LEAST AN EXTRA THREE
DAYS IN THE GAME.
WEAR IT WITH PRIDE.
TEND TO BE THE ATHLETE TYPES
ALWAYS MAKE IT RIGHT BEFORE THE
MERGE AND THEY'RE GONE, SO I
WOULD LOVE TO SAVE THIS ABOUT
THE FOURTH, FIFTH COUNCIL, PLAY
IT AND TAKE MYSELF TO THE MERGE
BUT THIS HAS BOUGHT ME SOME
PRATIME.
NOW I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO PROTECT VAL.
>> IF SHE DOES HAVE TWO, YEAH,
THEN ONE OF US 5 GUYS IS GOING
HOME, SO THE ONLY OTHER WAY
AROUND THAT AND NOT LETTING THEM
THAN THREE VOTES ARE GOING FOR
BAYLOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I DID MAKE A PROMISE TO
JEREMY, IF I WANT TO ENSURE
JULIE'S SAFETY, I HAVE TO ENSURE
VAL'S SAFETY.
SO SHE PLAYS HER IDOL, TONIGHT,
SHE SHOULD BE FINE.
PLAY THAT IDOL.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS LIKE AN
OSCAR-WINNING MOMENT.
I DON'T HAVE THE IDOL.
BUT IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER.
BECAUSE THREE OF THEM VOTE
BAYLOR, AND JACKIE AND I VOTE
BAYLOR, THAT'S FIVE AGAINST
BAYLOR.
I KNOW ME AND JACLYN ARE SAFE.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN JOHN AND VAL
WALKED OFF TOGETHER.
THEY'VE NEVER WALKED OFF
TOGETHER.
LIKE, THEY-- JUST THOSE TWO?
I KIND OF WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON ABOUT THAT, AND I DON'T
THINK HE'S BEING HONEST WITH ME.
SPLITTING A VOTE IS DEFINITELY
RISKY AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME
BECAUSE WE DO HAVE SOME PEOPLE
ON OUR TEAM THAT YOU WONDER
ABOUT SOMETIMES.
SO TONIGHT, WHAT ENDS UP COMING
DOWN TO IS WHAT DO I THINK IS
GOING TO GET ME TO THE TOP.
>> Jeff: DALE, YOU'RE 0 FOR 4
IN THIS GAME.
>> WELL, I THINK WE MADE
MISTAKES STRATEGIZING IF ARE THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
EXCEPT FOR BAYLOR AND HER MOM,
EVERY TIME LOVED ONE AND LOVED
ONE WENT HEAD TO HEAD, WE LOST.
I THINK IT'S A PRIDE THING.
I CAME HERE TO FIGHT MY FAMILY
MEMBER.
>> IT WAS DEFINITELY A PRIDE
THING FOR ME.
>> HE WALKED RIGHT UP AND CAME
UP ON THE SHORT END.
>> Jeff: SO THERE'S A LOT MORE
STRATEGY WITH THIS LOVED ONE
THING THAN IT APPEARED AT FIRST.
>> I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
DOING THAT WITH DREW FOR A LONG
TIME.
I DIDN'T COME OUT ON TOP.
IT WAS DEFINITELY NOT THE
SMARTEST MOVE FOR ME TO GO UP
AGAINST DREW BUT THIS ISN'T THE
FIRST TIME WE'VE FAILED TO
DECIDE BEFORE WE JUST THROW OUR
MATCH-UP OUT THERE.
>> AT SOME POINT, JEFF, IT'S
GOING TO GEL AND CLICK AND WE'LL
BE RIGHT BACK THERE MENTALLY AND
PHYSICALLY.
>> Jeff: JOSH, THAT WORKS IF
TIME IS NOT AN ISSUE.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A BROADWAY
SHOW THAT STARTS THEIR PREVIEWS
AND THEY THOUGHT THEY HAD A
GREAT SHOW AND ALL OF A SENT
AUDIENCES HATE IT.
SO WHAT THEY DO IS THEY STOP AND
REWORK THE SHOW.
THEY TAKE OUT SONGS, THEY PUT
OTHER THINGS IN AND THEN THEY DO
IT AGAIN AND HAVE AN OPENING
NIGHT WITH ALL THE CHANGES AND
COME OUT STRONG.
SO WE'VE GOT TO MAKE SOME
CHANGES TO MAKE US STRONGER
COMING OUT.
>> Jeff: SO HOW TO YOU DO
THAT, VAL?
>> WELL, JEFF, I THINK IT GOES
BACK TO JUST EVEN HOW CAMP IS.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE PEOPLE IN CAMP
THAT TRY TO PLAY BOTH SIDES OF
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: WHICH IS WHO?
>> BAYLOR.
>> Jeff: SO, BAYLOR, NOW
YOU'RE UNDER THE BUS.
>> YEAH, I FEEL LIKE VAL'S BEEN
OUT FOR ME FROM THE MOMENT SHE
WALKED ON THE ISLAND.
SHE BROUGHT THE GIRLS TOGETHER.
WE HAD A DISCUSSION.
>> AND CHOSE TO GO WITH THE GUYS
AT THAT POINT.
>> YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING WITH
US.
>> WELL...
>> Jeff: WHO IS "US" JACLYN?
>> ME, VAL, NADIYA, AND BAYLOR.
AND THEN YOU FLIPPED.
>> AND THEN YOU TOLD US TO VOTE
FOR DALE BECAUSE I HADN'T BEEN
THERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYBODY, AND THE
ONLY PEOPLE THAT WERE TALKING TO
ME WERE THE GIRLS.
>> THAT WASN'T ME SAYING, "LET'S
VOTE DALE."
>> THAT EXACTLY WAS.
YOU TOLD ME TO VOTE DALE.
STRAIGHT UP, YOU TOLD ME TO VOTE
DALE RIGHT AT CAMP.
>> WOW.
>> WOW IS RIGHT, BECAUSE YOU
DID.
OWN IT.
>> Jeff: WES, THERE IS CLEARLY
TENSION IN THIS TRIBE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: AND WHEN THERE'S
TENSION, AS VAL SAID, IT'S HARD
TO PERFORM AT YOUR BEST.
>> SHE SAYS SHE HAS AN IDOL.
THAT'S THE MAIN REASON RIGHT
THERE.
>> I HEARD TWO.
>> AND I HEARD TWO, TOO.
>> YOU HEARD TWO WHAT?
>> I HEARD SHE HAD TWO IDOLS.
>> Jeff: WES WHAT, IS THE
IMPACT OF VAL SAYING SHE HAS TWO
IDOLS?
>> VOTE FOR HER, DRAW WITHIN
OUT.
>> Jeff: VAL, WILL YOU BE
SURPRISED IF YOU GET VOTES
TONIGHT?
>> NO.
>> Jeff: BAYLOR, WOULD YOU BE
SURPRISED IF YOU GOT VOTES?
>> NOW, I'M NOT, BUT IT WOULD BE
A SHAME TO SEE A LOT OF FLIPPING
HAPPENING NOW JUST BECAUSE OF
SOME-- SOME CRAZY TALK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
ALEC, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE AS SWEET AS YOU CAN
BE, BUT YOU GOTTA GO.
>> I JUST WANT TO SEE THAT IDOL,
GIRL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ALL RIGHT, IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, VAL.
BAYLOR.
TWO VOTES VAL.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
TWO VOTES EACH.
VAL.
BAYLOR.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES EACH.
BAYLOR.
FOUR VOTES BAYLOR, THREE VOTES
VAL.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
WE'RE TIED.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A REVOTE.
HERE'S HOW IT WILL WORK.
YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR VAL OR
BAYLOR.
VAL AND BAYLOR, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
ALEC, YOU'LL COME GRAB THE URN.
>> I TOLD YOU TO PLAY YOUR IDOL,
AND I TOLD YOU WHAT WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
YOU MAKE ME LOOK LIKE A LIAR TO
YOUR HUSBAND.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, BAYLOR.
VAL.
THAT'S TWO VOTES VAL, ONE VOTE
BAYLOR.
VAL.
THREE VOTES VAL, ONE VOTE
BAYLOR.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"BLOOD VERSUS WATER."
VAL.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
VAL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, THERE'S NOTHING I CAN SAY
THAT'S GOING TO HELP YOU.
HAVEN'T WON A CHALLENGE, LOST
TWO TRIBE MEMBERS.
SOMETHING HAS TO CHANGE QUICKLY
OR ONE BY ONE YOU WILL EACH BE
OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STIFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> YOU ALL DON'T KNOW WHO JOHN
ROCKER IS.
I KNOW WHO HE IS.
>> Jeff: JOHN ROCKER'S PAST IS
FINALLY EXPOSED.
>> HE SAID A WHOLE BUNCH OF
RACIST STUFF.
>> HE'S A BIGOT.
>> Jeff: AND SO HAD HIS
TEMPER.
>> YOU'RE A BAD SPORT.
>> TAKE DOWN ALL THE STUFF AND
WE'LL FIGHT.
>> JOHN, JOHN, STOP!
>> I FEEL LIKE I PLAYED BIG,
MADE BIG MOVES, CONSIDERING THAT
I WASN'T WITH THE TRIBE FOR TWO
DAYS.
IT WORKED FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I WISH IT WOULD HAVE WORKED FOR
LONGER, BUT I'M HAPPY WITH WHAT
I DID.
AND I THINK JEREMY SEEING ME
GONE WILL BE A SHOCK TO HIM
INITIALLY, BUT I THINK IT WILL
MAKE HIM GO HARDER IN HIS GAME.
AND I THINK IT WILL INSPIRE HIM.
SO I'M HAPPY WITH THAT.