>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... EIGHTH PERSON
VOTED OUT AND THE SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, JEREMY.
AFTER JON BLIND SIDED JEREMY AND
REVEALED HE FOUND THE IMMUNITY
IDOL, NATALIE AND BAYLOR WANTED
HIM OUT.
>> I SAY JON, BUT DON'T TELL
ANYONE.
>> Jeff: BY AFTER JON WON
IMMUNITY -- JON WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY -- THE MAJORITY
ALLIANCE DECIDE TO TAKE OUT
KEITH.
>> WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
WE SHOULD VOTE KEITH AND HE'S
GOING HOME AS LONG AS HE DOESN'T
HAVE AN IDOL.
>> Jeff: BUT NATALIE HAD A
DIFFERENT IDEA.
AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, NATALIE
SECRETLY SWITCHED HER VOTE TO
RUIN JON'S PLAN.
>> KEITH, BUT I'M VOTING FOR
YOU.
>> Jeff: 11th PERSON VOTED
OUT, ALEC.
ALEC, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SIX ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> I'M COLD.
>> ME, YOU AND --
>> JUST THE WAY TRIBAL WENT, I
KNEW I HAD TO PRETEND TO MESS UP
AND ACCIDENTALLY VOTE OWL ALEC
INSTEAD OF KEITH, AND ACT MY ASS
OFF TO CONVINCE THEM IT WAS A
MISTAKE.
>> HE CAME UP TO ME.
I DIDN'T TALK TO HIM.
>> IT WAS A RISK I WAS WILLING
TO TAKE BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
JON TO HAVE MORE POWER AND
CONTROL IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW
THAN HE NEEDS.
I THINK I SOLD IT TO THEM
PROPERLY, BUT IT'S GOING TO BE
SCARY, BUT JON IS ON MY HIT
LIST.
HE'S BEEN ON MY HIT LIST SINCE
HE SENT JEREMY HOME, SO IT'S
BEEN A LONG TIME COMING.
I NEED TO MAKE SOME MOVES SOON.
>> NOBODY TALKED TO ME.
NOBODY CHECKED IN WITH ME.
>> IT'S HILARIOUS WATCHING
NATALIE BE AN ACTRESS TOWARD JON
AND JACLYN TONIGHT.
IF THEY WERE SMART, THEY WOULD
KNOW NATALIE KNEW EXACTLY WHAT
SHE WAS DOING.
>> IT'S FINE.
>> TRIBAL WAS A DEBACLE.
I GUESS WE DIDN'T TALK ENOUGH
GOING INTO IT, AND NATALIE
DIDN'T FULLY UNDERSTAND WHO SHE
WAS VOTING FOR.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE THAT IT
HAPPENED HERE, BECAUSE KEITH
REALLY IS A THREAT IN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
>> THAT'S A BIG, BIG DEAL.
THAT POTENTIALLY COULD SCREW UP
A LOT OF PLANS.
>> HOW DID THE VOTES WORK?
>> I WAS SUPPOSED TO VOTE FOR
YOU AND I VOTED FOR ALEC.
>> HAVE YOU ABOUT HAD IT WITH
ALEC?
>> YES BECAUSE ALEC WAS OBSESSED
WITH JON FOR NO REASON.
>> MAN, IT SEEMS LIKE I JUST
KEEP SQUEAKING BY, SQUEAKING BY,
SQUEAKING BY.
>> THEY ALL KNOW THAT IT WAS ME,
SO ME, YOU, MISSY AND BAYLOR, WE
HAVE TO BE TIGHT.
>> MAYBE NOW 30 DAYS INTO THIS I
HAVE SOMEBODY.
I HAVE NAT.
WHAT COULD HAPPEN AFTER THAT,
WHO KNOWS.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU SHOULD BE IN
THE GAME LONGER THAN ALEC.
>> DON'T PAY THOSE TWO ANYMORE.
>> YOU MEAN MISS PROM QUEEN OR
MISS HOMECOMING QUEEN?
>> IT'S UNPREDICTABLE, BUT I
TOLD KEITH HE WAS BASICALLY HERE
BECAUSE OF ME.
I TOLD HIM THAT ME AND BAY
ALREADY AT THE END OF THE DAY
HAD HIS BACK.
HOPEFULLY THAT WILL RESONATE
WITH HIM AND HE WILL BE A
PERFECT PERSON TO USE IN OUR
PLAN AGAINST JON.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'LL BE DIVIDED
INTO TWO TEAMS AND BELTED
TOGETHER.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL RACE THROUGH A
TUNNEL OF HAY.
YOU'LL THEN MAKE YOU WAY OVER
AND UNDER A SERIES OF HITCHING
POSTS.
YOU'LL THEN GRAB A BUCKET, FILL
WITH IT WATER AND MAKE YOU WAY
OVER A GIANT TEETER TOTTER.
YOU'LL THEN POUR THAT WATER INTO
A LARGER BUCKET.
WHEN THAT BUCKET FILLS, IT WILL
LOWER A GATE.
YOU'LL THEN RACE TO SOLVE A
PLANK PUZZLE.
FIRST TEAM TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WINNING TEAM WILL
ENJOY A "SURVIVOR"-STYLE SPA.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL START WITH A
HOT SHOWER.
AFTER 33 DAYS, KEITH...
>> YEAH, WE NEED IT.
>> Jeff: YOU NEED IT.
YOU'LL THEN ENJOY A NICE
MASSAGE, AND THEN YOU'LL EAT SPA
FOOD, SEARED STEAK, COOKIES.
>> STEAK AND BROWNIES.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
>> Jeff: GREAT DAY OF
REJUVENATION TO GET YOU THROUGH
THESE LAST SIX DAYS.
WE'LL DRAW FOR TEAMS.
LET'S GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
FOR BLUE, IT IS KEITH, MISSY AND
JON.
FOR YELLOW IT IS NATALIE, BAYLOR
AND JACLYN.
HERE WE GO, FOR REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST OBSTACLE IS THROUGH THAT
HAY.
YOU CAN GO OVER, UNDER, AROUND,
JUST GET THROUGH IT.
NATALIE, BAYLOR, JACLYN THROUGH
THE HAY FIRST.
JON, MISSY AND KEITH ARE NOW
THROUGH THE HAY.
>> OVER.
>> Jeff: GOT TO GO OVER AND
THEN UNDER.
YOU'RE ALL TETHERED TOGETHER.
IT'S VERY HARD TO MOVE.
MISSY TAKES A HARD FALL.
AND ANOTHER FALL BY MISSY.
YELLOW IS NOW THROUGH IT.
START UNTYING THAT BUCKET.
KEITH, MISSY AND JON FINALLY
THROUGH.
THEY START WORKING ON THEIR
BUCKET.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE BUCKET, YOU'RE
FILLING IT WITH WATER AND
HEADING OVER THE TEETER TOTTER.
NATALIE, BAYLOR, JACLYN, THEY
HAVE THEIR BUCKET.
FILL IT WITH WATER.
OVER THE TEETER TOTTER THEY GO.
>> COME ON.
>> GO.
>> Jeff: BIG FALL.
JON, MISSY, KEITH, THEY'VE GOT
THEIR BUCKET.
THE GOAL IS TO ADD ENOUGH WATER
TO DROP YOUR BUCKET, OPENING THE
GATE.
MISSY COMES DOWN HARD ON THAT.
MISSY MOVING SLOWLY.
NOTHING EASY ABOUT GOING OVER
THIS TEETER TOTTER TIED TO TWO
OTHER PEOPLE CARRYING A BUCKET
OF WATER.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> COME ON, JAC.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER BIG FALL BY
JACLYN.
JON, KEITH AND MISSY MOVING VERY
SLOWLY NOW.
THE TRICK IS KEEPING YOUR
BALANCE WHILE HOLDING THE WATER.
JON, MISSY, KEITH COMING BACK.
WE'RE VERY TIGHT RIGHT NOW.
WILL THIS BE ENOUGH WATER?
YOU GOT TO RAISE THAT BAG.
THAT WILL DO IT.
HEAD ACROSS.
>> BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
>> Jeff: MISSY HOBBLEING.
JON, MISSY, KEITH SPILL A LOT OF
THEIR WATER.
WILL THIS BE ENOUGH?
NO, THEY'VE GOT TO GO BACK.
YELLOW IS ALREADY WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
BLUE NEEDS TO MOVE.
KEITH AND JON HELPING MISSY
THROUGH THIS COURSE.
JON, MISSY, KEITH HOPING THIS IS
ENOUGH WATER.
YES, THAT'S ENOUGH.
GET ACROSS.
>> SIDE BY SIDE.
>> Jeff: CAN BLUE PICK IT UP?
>> ONE, TWO.
ONE, TWO.
>> THAT'S AN R RIGHT THERE.
>> WHERE'S A?
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY WORKING ON
THE PUZZLE.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
GET CLEAN, GET FED.
BLUE HAS A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
UP.
IT WILL COME DOWN TO THE PUZZLE.
WHO WORKS TOGETHER THE BEST?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
LOOK.
>> Jeff: THE GIRLS ARGUING,
SLOWING DOWN NOW.
>> THIS IS A W, GUYS.
>> Jeff: KEITH, MISSY AND JON
WORKING TOGETHER VERY WELL,
STARTING TO PICK UP THE PACE.
>> THIS GOES HERE.
THIS GOES HERE.
>> HOLE ON, GUYS.
I GOT IT HERE.
GIVE ME THAT.
>> Jeff: THE GIRLS NOW PICKING
UP THE PACE.
>> MISSY.
>> Jeff: JON, MISSY, KEITH
THINK THEY HAVE SOMETHING GOING
NOW.
GIRLS GETTING CLOSER.
ARE THEY RIGHT?
BLUE NOW GOING TO MOVE
EVERYTHING OVER.
>> THIS IS CONNECTED RIGHT HERE.
>> I GOT THE WATER.
>> Jeff: BOTH TEAMS ARE MOVING
A LOT OF PIECES QUICKLY.
BOTH THINK THEY HAVE IT.
PUT YOUR PIECES OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: THE GIRLS ARE PICKING
UP THE PACE.
THEY THINK THEY HAVE IT.
WE'RE NECK AND NECK.
>> GOT IT!
GOT IT!
KEITH, MISSY, JON WIN REWARD!
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> IT'S JUST SWOLLEN.
NO BIG DEAL.
>> Jeff: YOU ALL RIGHT, MISSY?
>> I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD,
I'M GOOD.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
>> Jeff: KEITH, MISSY, JON,
NICE REWARD.
MISSY, A SPA DAY BACK HOME IS A
GOOD DAY.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: BUT OUT HERE ON
"SURVIVOR," WHERE DOES THAT RANK
33 DAYS IN?
>> THIS IS LIKE GAME CHANGER.
I COULD LAST 16 MORE DAYS.
>> A SPA DAY FOR HER IS GOING TO
COMPLETELY REJUVENATE HER.
SHE'S GOING TO FEEL AS YOUNG AS
SHE LOOKS.
>> JON, YOU'RE ANNOYING RIGHT
NOW.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, DO YOU KIND
OF FEEL LIKE YOU DESERVE IT?
>>
NATALIE, YOU KNOW THE
WAY.
YOU WILL RETURN IN TIME FOR THE
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> LOVE YOU, NAT.
>> Jeff: MISSY, BAYLOR, KEITH,
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
>> THIS NOT WALK ON YOUR ANKLE.
>> GET ON MY BACK.
>> Jeff: MISSY, YOU'LL LET ME
KNOW IF MEDICAL NEEDS TO LOOK AT
THAT.
>> ENJOY THAT MASSAGE, KEITH.
>> LOOK HOW THIS WORKS OUT.
>> I GET TO GIVE HER, HER OWN
PERSONAL SPA DAY.
JON, JACLYN, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
BUT YOU'VE GOT EACH OTHER.
>> TRADED PLACES WITH BAYLOR WAS
AN EASY DECISION FOR ME.
IT JUST OPENED UP A WINDOW FOR
ME TO DO A GOOD DEED FOR ONE OF
MY ALLIANCE MEMBERS TO SOLIDIFY
OUR ALLIANCE AND IT MAY HAVE
EVEN STRENGTHENED MY CASE IN THE
JURY.
>> HI.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> PINEAPPLE.
>> MMM.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A SPA.
>> THIS IS GOOD.
>> OH, MAN.
>> KEITH, GIVE ME SOME OF THAT.
WE WON THAT, BABY.
>> THANK YOU, JON.
THAT WAS THE NICEST THING EVER.
MY MOM, KEITH AND JON WON THE
REWARD.
BEFORE I KNEW IT, JON WAS LIKE,
I'M SWITCHING WITH BAYLOR.
I WAS LIKE, WHAT?
>> TAKE A PEEK AT MY ANKLE AND
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
>> THAT WAS SUPER NICE OF HIM TO
DO THAT, BUT GETTING JON OUT IS
ME AND NATALIE'S NUMBER-ONE
PRIORITY.
>> OH, I CAN TELL FROM HERE.
>> OUCH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO IT THEN.
>> AT THE REWARD CHALLENGE, I
WAS TRYING SO HARD NOT TO SHOW
ANY SIGNS OF PAIN IN MY ANKLE,
BUT I COULD JUST FEEL IT
SWELLING UP.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SPRAINED?
>> I DON'T KNOW, SPRAINED OR
STRAINED.
CAN YOU PULL AGAINST ME?
>> THAT HURTS REAL BAD.
>> THAT AIN'T GOOD.
>> I'M IN A LOT OF PAIN.
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY HOW THIS
NEXT COUPLE DAYS IS GOING TO GO
DOWN AT CHALLENGES.
I'M GOING TO DO THE BEST I CAN.
I'M GOING THE CRAWL IF I HAVE
TO, BUT I'M GOING TO FINISH.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO RUIN OUR
AFTERNOON.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> I SEE SOME GOOBERS ON THE
END.
>> OH, NUTS.
>> OH, YEAH.
SLOW DOWN NOW, BAYLOR.
DON'T FILL UP ON THAT RABBIT
FOOD.
>> HE'S GOING TO DIE WHEN HE
SEES YOU'RE AT A SPA.
>> IT'S A GIRL THING, BUT AS
LONG AS THIS FOOD IS HERE, IT'S
A GUY THING.
>> YEP.
>> I'VE NEVER HAD A SPA DAY OR
SPA FOOD.
TURNED OUT NOT TOO BAD.
THAT LOOKS LIKE A PIECE OF
BACON.
>> IT'S NOT SO BAD.
>> NO.
I ATE ABOUT AS MUCH AS I COULD,
AND THEN I WENT OFF THE SHOWER.
IT KNOCKED THE FUNK OFF ME.
30-SOMETHING DAYS I HAVEN'T
BATHED.
THEN I WAS OFF TO THE MASSAGE.
SHE HIT THE RIGHT SPOT, OH, LIKE
RIGHT THERE.
OH, OH MY GOODNESS.
THAT'S MY BONEY RIB CAGE.
OH.
>> KEITH AT A SPA WAS PRETTY
DANG FUNNY.
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> I HADN'T SEEN THAT SIDE OF
KEITH BEFORE.
>> I DON'T GET TO THAT MANY OF
THESE IN LOUISIANA.
>> I HAD REALIZATION.
HE'S KIND OF COOL.
>> DO YOU FEEL THE KNOTS IN YOUR
SHOULDER?
>> I THINK SO.
IT MAY BE MY BONES.
DON'T TELL NOBODY.
I DON'T WANT THE GUYS AT THE
FIRE STATION TO KNOW I'M GOING
TO A MASSEUSE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO ROLL ME
OFF THIS BABY.
MAP, I'VE BEEN REJUVENATED.
I HAVE FOUR, FIVE, SIX DAYS
LEFT.
I CAN TAKE THIS ON OUT NO
PROBLEM NOW.
GOOD GRIEF.
>> I THINK ACTUALLY IT WORKED
OUT THE BEST IT POSSIBLY COULD
HAVE.
>> BEING AT CAMP ALONE, IT'S
NICE TO JUST BE THE TWO OF US.
>> YOU KNOW, MATT FELT REALLY
BAD ABOUT THE BOAT.
>> I TOLD HER, KEITH.
>> I KNOW YOU DID.
THAT WAS A GREAT THING TO BRING
UP.
THAT'S SOMETHING I'LL DEFINITELY
BRING UP IN THE JURY, 100%.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO SPLIT VOTES,
KNOW WHO YOU'RE VOTING FOR.
>> NATALIE MADE A BIG MISTAKE,
VOTING FOR THE WRONG PERSON, AND
NOW YOU KEPT IN KEITH, ONE OF
THE BIGGEST THREATS.
CAN'T HAVE THAT HAPPEN.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING
FOR $1 MILLION.
>> BUT THEN IN THE BECOME OF MY
HEAD, I'M LIKE, MAYBE HER AND
KEITH HAD SOMETHING GOING ON.
SHE'S REALLY, REALLY THREATENED
BY US TWO PAIRS.
>> SO IT'S TWO VERSUS FOUR, IT
WOULDN'T MAKE ANY SENSE?
>> WELL, MAYBE SHE WANTS A GOOD
PAIR.
MAYBE SHE TRUSTS KEITH MORE THAN
ALEC.
MAYBE SHE DID IT ON PURPOSE AND
LIED ABOUT IT.
KEITH IS FREAKISHLY GOOD AT
THESE CHALLENGES.
SO IF KEITH KEEPS WINNING
IMMUNITY, THEN I THINK THAT
EVERYBODY WILL GET EVEN MORE MAD
AT NATALIE FOR SCREWING UP THAT
VOTE.
THEN WE'LL HAVE TO BREAK UP THE
FIVE SOONER THAN WE THOUGHT.
>> I VOLUNTEERED TO GO TO EXILE,
BUT AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME,
WHEN YOUR BODY IS ALREADY SO
DRAINED AND IT'S SO CLOSE TO THE
END YOU CAN ALMOST TASTE IT BUT
YOU'RE NOT THERE YET, IT'S BEEN
REALLY DEPRESSING ME OUT HERE.
IT'S BEEN REALLY A ROLLER
COASTER OF EMOTION FOR ME
BECAUSE THIS IS THE LONGEST I'VE
GONE WITHOUT SEEING OR TALKING
TO MY SISTER.
I'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR 28 YEARS.
I'VE NEVER LET ANYBODY SEE HOW
MUCH I MISS HER.
AND I KIND OF ALWAYS JUST
PRETEND LIKE I'M FINE, BUT
NADIYA'S BEEN GONE FOR LIKE 30
DAYS NOW, AND I HAVE BEEN DOING
THIS WITHOUT HER, BUT I'M JUST
TRYING TO MAKE IT INTO SOMETHING
WHERE I CAN USE IT AS MOTIVATION
INSTEAD OF JUST BRINGING ME
DOWN.
TIME TO, YOU KNOW, BUCK UP AND
MAKE EVERY DECISION MOVING
FORWARD COUNT.
I HAVE ONE SHOT TO PROVE TO
MYSELF THAT I LEFT EVERYTHING ON
THE TABLE.
MAKE THESE LAST FOUR DAYS FULLY
WORTH IT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
CLEARLY WE HAVE SOMETHING TO
TALK ABOUT.
LET'S GET NATALIE IN HERE,
RETURNING FROM EXILE ISLAND.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, WHAT DID
THEY JUST HAND YOU?
>> SOME RICE, AND I'M HAPPY THAT
THEY BROUGHT IT FOR ME.
IT WAS PROBABLY ONE OF THE
HARDEST THINGS I EVER HAD TO DO.
I CRIED PROBABLY 50% OF THE DAY.
IT WAS EXHAUSTING EMOTIONALLY
AND PHYSICALLY TO ME.
>> Jeff: MISSY, LAST I SAW
YOU, BAYLOR WAS CARRYING YOU OUT
ON YOUR BACK.
CLEARLY THE ANKLE HAS GOTTEN
WORSE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY IT'S GETTING
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO QUIT.
THERE'S NO WAY.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO ABOUT THIS, BUT I'M GOING
TO TRY THE STAND ON ONE FOOT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> Jeff: I THINK WE SHOULD
HAVE MEDICAL LOOK AT IT BEFORE
THE CHALLENGE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF FAITH YOU'RE GOING TO
BE ABLE TO DO THIS GIVEN THAT
YOU'RE ON A CRUTCH RIGHT NOW.
SO WE'RE GOING TO BRING MEDICAL
IN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
MEDICAL.
WHY DON'T WE SIT YOU RIGHT HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> HI, MISSY.
SO IF WE START BY GETTING BOTH
SHOES OFF SO I CAN COMPARE YOUR
GOOD ANKLE WITH YOUR BAD ANKLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T REALLY...
>> IT'S HUGE.
>> SO BOTH THE PAIN AND THE
SWELLING IS GETTING WORSE FOR
YOU?
>> UH-HUH.
>> I JUST WANT TO EXAMINE YOU.
I WANT TO KNOW WHICH AREA IS
SORE.
IF I'M CAUSING YOU PAIN, MAKE
SURE YOU TELL ME.
SO FAR SO GOOD?
>> IT'S JUST TENDER.
IT'S SORE.
OH, RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE!
RIGHT THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> I HATE THAT.
>> OKAY, AND TRY LIKE YOUR FOOT
IS ON THE ACCELERATOR OF A CAR.
>> YEAH, THERE'S NO WAY.
>> NOTHING THERE.
>> SO GIVE THEN EXAMINATION, MY
CONCERN IS THAT AT THE VERY
LEAST WE HAVE A VERY SIGNIFICANT
SPRAIN.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT IT TO BE
BROKEN.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU CONCERNED IT
COULD BE BROKEN?
>> AFTER TWO DAYS, WHEN THINGS
ARE GETTING WORSE, I HAVE TO
CONSIDER A FRACTURE, YES.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
THE ONLY WAY TO KNOW FOR SURE
THAT THIS IS BROKEN IS TO DO AN
X-RAY, AND TO DO AN X-RAY, I'D
HAVE TO PULL MISSY FROM THE
GAME.
[SOBBING]
>> IT'S SO FRUSTRATING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO, BEN, IS THIS SEVERE ENOUGH
THAT YOU AS A DOCTOR WOULD SAY
SHE NEEDS TO BE PULLED FROM THE
GAME?
>> OF COURSE, THERE'S ONLY A FEW
DAYS LEFT IN THE GAME.
WE CAN IMMOBILIZE THE LIMB,
WHICH MEAN NO FURTHER DAMAGE
WILL OCCURS, SO, NO, I DON'T
THINK SHE NEEDS TO BE PULLED
FROM THE GAME.
JEFF JEFF CLEARLY SHE'S IN PAIN.
IT'S NOT LIFE-THREATENING.
SO AS FAR AS YOU'RE CONCERNED,
IT'S HER CALL WHAT SHE DOES IN
>> YES.
>> Jeff:, HOW ARE YOU FEELING
KNOWING BEEN SAID YOU MAY HAVE A
BREAK?
>> I'M STAYING IN THIS GAME.
I'M NOT QUITTING.
>> Jeff: WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
DO FOR THIS MOMENT?
>> I WANT YOU TO IMMOBILIZE IT,
THE SMARTEST THING TO DO.
AND I'M JUST GOING TO ROOT ON MY
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO SIT
THIS CHALLENGE OUT.
THEN YOU TAKE EACH DAY AS IT
COMES.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU CAN STAY HERE WITH BEN,
AND WE'LL GET BACK TO OUR
CHALLENGE.
BAYLOR, WHAT'S THAT LIKE FOR
YOU?
MOM IS CLEARLY IN A TON OF PAIN.
>> WELL, I MEAN, MY MOM'S A
FIGHTER.
THAT SOUNDS REALLY SIMPLE, BUT
IT'S NOT.
IN OUR LIFE SHE NEVER GIVES UP,
AND SO WE'RE GOING TO KEEP
FIGHTING AND I'LL CARRY HER TO
THE FINISH LINE IF I HAVE TO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO MISSY WILL SIT THIS ONE OUT.
SO SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
JON, FIRST THINGS FIRST, TAKE
BACK THE NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO HOLD ON TO TWO HANDLES
WITH YOUR HANDS WHILE YOUR FEET
WILL BE BALANCING ON A TEETER
TOTTER.
ATTACH TO THE TEETER TOTTER IS A
VASE.
THE LONGER THIS CHALLENGE GOES,
THE MORE DIFFICULT IT WILL BE TO
BALANCE THAT VASE.
WHEN THE VASE DROPS, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
FIVE SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON IN THE JURY, AND AS LUCK
WOULD HAVE IT, THE WIND GUSTS
ARE BIG.
THIS CHALLENGE COULD GO A LONG
TIME, OR IT COULD BE OVER VERY
QUICKLY, WHICH MEANS EVERY
SECOND THAT YOU STAY UP THERE
WILL COUNT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY IS IN PLACE AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON.
EVERYBODY VERY STEADY OUT OF THE
GATE.
IT WON'T BE THAT WAY FOR LONG.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, BAYLOR WITH
MOVEMENT.
KEITH WITH A LITTLE BIT OF A
WOBBLE AND A NICE RECOVERY.
MISSY, YOU CAN SEE YOU HAD NO
CHANCE.
>> NO WAY, NO CHANCE.
>> Jeff: 35 DAYS.
WIN THIS CHALLENGE YOU ARE IN
THE FINAL FIVE.
THAT MUCH CLOSER TO THE MILLION
BUCKS.
YOU CANNOT LOSE YOUR
CONCENTRATION.
THERE'S VERY LITTLE FORGIVENESS
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
AS YOU WOULD EXPECT ON DAY 35 IN
"SURVIVOR."
JACLYN WOBBLING.
JACLYN CAN'T RECOVER.
JACLYN THE FIRST PERSON OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, BABY.
>> Jeff: SHE'LL JOIN MISSY ON
THE BENCH.
THAT'S HOW QUICKLY IT GOES.
TAKE TINY ADJUSTMENTS ALL THE
TIME.
ESPECIALLY AS YOUR FEET BECOME
NUMB AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING ANYMORE.
KEITH WOBBLING AGAIN.
BAY ALREADY'S VASE IS ALSO
MOVING.
BAYLOR CANNOT RECOVER.
BAYLOR IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE NOW DOWN TO THREE, AND
HERE COMES A HUGE GUST OF WIND.
IT IS KEITH, NATALIE AND JON.
NICE JOB BY ALL THREE BATTLING
THAT WIND.
YOUR FEET ARE NUMB.
THE WIND IS BLOWING.
WHO CAN HANG THIS THERE THE
LONGEST?
WHO WANTS THIS THE MOST?
HERE COMES THE WIND AGAIN.
BRACE YOURSELF.
BIG WIND.
THE WIND IS TOO MUCH FOR KEITH.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS NATALIE AND JON FIGHTING
FOR IMMUNITY ON DAY 35, AND IT
GUARANTEES A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO RISK BEING
VOTED OUT TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THIS IS IT.
YOU GOT TO WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
WIND UP AGAIN.
MAKING AN ALREADY DIFFICULT
CHALLENGE EVEN MORE DIFFICULT TO
NAVIGATE.
OUT OF NOWHERE, MOTHER NATURE IS
SAYING HELLO.
AND JUST LIKE THAT JON DROPS.
NATALIE WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT IN
THE FINAL FIVE.
>> THAT WAS QUICK.
>> I DIDN'T EVEN MOVE IT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, NAT.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, COME ON
OVER.
>> IT MAKES EXILE SO WORTH IT.
>> Jeff: AFTER 35 DAYS, YOU GO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE OTHER FIVE OF YOU,
SOMEBODY IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
YOU WILL BECOME THE SIXTH MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK THE
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> NICE JOB, NAT.
>> KEITH IS AN INCREDIBLE
THREAT.
SO NATALIE WINNING TODAY DOES
KIND OF MAKE UP FOR HER MESSING
UP THE LAST VOTE.
SO THE PLAN IS TO DO WHAT WE
TRIED TO DO LAST TRIBAL AND GET
KEITH OUT.
>> THANK YOU, KEITH.
YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
>> THE FACT MISSY HAD TO SIT OUT
TODAY I'M SURE WAS EXCRUCIATING
FOR HER AND PROBABLY JUST AS BAD
AS THE PAIN SHE WAS FEELING.
HOW YOU FEELING, MISS?
>> I DON'T KNOW YET.
>> HOW THE CHALLENGE ENDED UP
WAS VERY FRUSTRATING.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> DANG WIND.
>> BUT I'VE GOT A PLAN.
I HAVE TO ACCEPT IT HOWEVER
THINGS FALL.
IT'S GOING TO BE BEST.
>> WE SHOULD KEEP AN EYE ON
KEITH.
>> HE KNOWS WHAT'S UP.
>> WHO DOES HE THINK THAT WE'RE
VOTING FOR?
>> HE KNOWS.
>> JON AND JACLYN THINK WE'RE
ALL VOTING OUT KEITH AND KEITH
IS GOING HOME, BUT MY PLAN IS TO
BASICALLY GET OUT JON.
>> SO WE'RE VOTING KEITH
TONIGHT, RIGHT?
>> BUT JON HAS AN IDOL, SO I
KNOW IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
MY ULTIMATE PLAN IS TO SPLIT THE
VOTE AND BLINDSIDE JON TONIGHT.
TONIGHT JUST VOTE JON.
I'LL TELL YOU.
THE PLAN IS TO SPLIT VOTES.
IF JON PLAYS HIS IDOL, WE VOTE
OUT JACLYN.
GETTING OUT JON WOULD BE A DREAM
COME TRUE.
>> IT'S TRIBAL TONIGHT.
IF ALL GOES AS PLANNED,
MR. ALL-AMERICAN OR MISS U.S.A.
IS GOING HOME.
AND I'LL BE SITTING HERE WITH
FIVE.
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
WE'RE PRETENDING LIKE WE'RE ALL
VOTING FOR YOU, SO AT TRIBAL
DON'T ACT CRAZY, BUT JUST ACT
DEPRESSED THAT YOU'RE GOING
HOME.
>> I THINK I CAN TRUST THIS
BUNCH.
IF I CAN'T, I'M A GONER.
>> I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED ABOUT
YOU NOT WINNING.
I'M LIKE, WHAT IF THEY ALL
BLINDSIDE JON.
>> I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
I THINK IF THEY WERE GOING FOR
KEITH LAST TIME, THEY'RE GOING
TO GO FOR KEITH AGAIN.
>> KEITH WAS SUPPOSED TO GO HOME
LAST TIME, SO IT'S LIKE, OKAY,
LET'S JUST GET IT OVER WITH, BUT
I FEEL LIKE YOUR MIND CAUSES ALL
THIS PARANOIA.
COULD I GO HOME TONIGHT?
COULD JON GO HOME TONIGHT?
YOU NEVER KNOW 100%, BUT AT
LEAST JON STILL HAS HIS IDOL.
>> I KNOW I'M BEING PARANOID,
BUT I THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
BLINDSIDE JON.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> JON IS SUPER BIG ON
VISUALIZING THE WIND, AND IT'S
ALWAYS WORKED OUT FOR HIM, SO
HOPEFULLY IT DOES THIS TIME,
TOO.
>> WE VOTE, TWO, TWO, TWO.
>> YES.
>> YOU AND KEITH VOTE JON, MY
MOM AND ME VOTE JACLYN, AND THEM
TWO, JOHN AND JACLYN VET KEITH.
IF HE PLAYS THE IDOL, WE VOTE
JACLYN OUT.
I NEED MY MOM TO GET ON BOARD,
BUT MY MOM TREATS JON LIKE HER
SON THAT SHE NEVER HAD, SO I'M
WORRIED ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
SHE'LL WRITE HIS NAME DOWN.
IT JUST REALLY DEPENDS ON MY
MOM.
>> NATALIE AND I THINK WE SHOULD
VOTE JON.
>> BAYLOR, I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> WHY?
>> I'VE GIVEN HIM MY WORD TO THE
END AND I WILL GET NO VOTES.
>> BUT CHALLENGE-WISE, YOU'RE
NEVER GOING TO WIN.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> MY, BUT GOING WITH NATALIE
AND KEITH AND ME, THAT'S A LOT
BETTER CHANCE.
>> BAYLOR, I HAVE A DEAL WITH
JON, I'M NOT BREAKING THAT DEAL.
>> IT'S VERY FRUSTRATING TO GET
MY MOM TO WAKE UP, GET WITH THE
PROGRAM, LET'S MAKE A MOVE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO BREAK THAT
LOYALTY.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE A DEAL WITH
JON.
>> YES, YOU DO.
>> NEW YORK I DON'T.
I HAVE NOTHING WITH JON.
MOM, HE'S A HUGE THREAT, AND HE
DOES HAVE AN IDOL.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> SO WHY DON'T WE GET HIM OUT
WITH HIS IDOL, GOOD-BYE.
>> BECAUSE I CAN'T BREAK THAT.
>> IN MY MOM'S LIFE, THREE
MARRIAGE, THREE DIVORCES, SHE IS
PUTTING THE MEN FIRST BEFORE
HERSELF.
THAT'S HER DOWN SIDE I THINK,
AND THAT'S WHAT I FEEL LIKE IS
HAPPENING IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW
WITH JON.
>> I DON'T THINK I CAN TRUST JON
IN ANY VOTE.
I KNOW YOU TRUST HIM, BUT I
DON'T.
I SAY WE VOTE OUT JON TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT THAT'S NOT HAPPENING.
>> IT'S TOTALLY LIKE, MOM, HEY,
I'M YOUR FIRST BORN.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW THIS GUY.
LET'S PLAY THE GAME TOGETHER.
I JUST HOPE SHE'S GOING TO SEE
IT BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
>> WHEN MY CHILD SAYS TO ME,
MOM, OUR GOAL WAS TO GO TO THE
END TOGETHER, I'VE HAD THE START
TO LISTEN, AND, YOU KNOW, HAS IT
CROSSED MY MIND THAT THIS
JON-JACLYN SHOW MAY NEED TO COME
TO AN END, ABSOLUTELY, BUT IT'S
IMPORTANT FOR ME TO FEEL LIKE I
PLAYED THIS GAME TRUTHFULLY.
I WASN'T SOME SLY DOG THAT CAME
IN, SHOOK PEOPLE'S HANDS AND
LIED IN THEIR FACES.
I HAVEN'T.
I PRIDE MYSELF ON THAT.
THAT'S WHY TONIGHT THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME I'M HAVING A TOUGH
TIME WITH IT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
JOSH, JEREMY, WES, REED, AN AN
ALEC VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, KEITH...
>> YES, SIR.
I'VE BEEN TRYING...
>> Jeff: WAIT.
I DIDN'T EVEN SAY ANYTHING.
>> COME ON.
GIVE IT TO ME.
>> Jeff: NO, GIVE IT TO ME.
>> WELL, I'VE BEEN TRYING THE
PIERCE THIS FIVE, AND THEY'RE
SOLID, BUT I'M NOT INVISIBLE.
I'VE GOT A VOTE.
USE IT.
I THINK IT WOULD BE A BIG MOVE,
AND I THINK THEY WOULD THINK IT
WOULD BE A BIG MOVE.
AND BIG MOVES MEANS YOUR PLAYING
THE GAME AND PLAYING THE GAME
GETS YOU VOTES.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN YOU'RE THE ONE ON TO
OUTSIDE?
IT MIGHT NOT HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH YOU.
>> TRUST ME, I'M TRUSTWORTHY.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE A FIREMAN.
WHO IS MORE TRUSTWORTHY THAN A
FIREMAN.
>> IT'S NOT A MATTER OF NOT
FEELING LIKE WE CAN TRUST KEITH.
IT'S THAT WE'VE BUILT THIS TRUST
WITH OUR GROUP OF FIVE.
I DON'T WANT TO LET THIS GROUP
OF FIVE DOWN.
I WOULD BE HYPOCRITICAL IF I
PEKO TO TRUST THEM IF THEY CAN'T
TRUST ME.
>> Jeff: JACLYN, IS THERE ANY
ARGUMENT THAT KEITH CAN MAKE
THAT COULD MAKE SENSE?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT'S NATURAL
FOR PEOPLE TO THINK ABOUT
DIFFERENT SCENARIOS, BUT ALL I
CAN SAY, THOUGH, IS THAT I FEEL
STRONG IN THE FIVE.
SO I DON'T THINK JON ANDRY GOING
ANYWHERE.
>> Jeff: NATALIE.
YOU'RE ON THE OUTSIDE OF THIS
FIVE IN THAT YOU DON'T HAVE A
LOVED ONE IN THE GAME.
WHICH AT A CERTAIN POINT WOULD
MAKE YOU VERY VALUABLE.
>> YEAH, BLOOD IS REALLY, REALLY
THICK.
IT'S HARDER TO PENETRATE IT AND
SAY, COME ON, LET'S DO
SOMETHING.
I HAVE BEEN GONE FOR TWO DAYS AT
EXILE.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN IN TWO DAYS,
AND SO THANK GOD I WON IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: JON, HOW MUCH TIME DO
YOU SPEND THINKING ABOUT THAT
FINAL SPEECH WHERE YOU MAKE THE
ARGUMENT THAT STICKING TOGETHER
FIVE STRONG IS A BIG MOVE?
>> UM, I THINK ABOUT THAT FINAL
SPEECH QUITE A BIT.
YOU KNOW, STICKING TOGETHER AS
FIVE IS NOT AS EASY AS ONE WOULD
THINK.
HAVING THE LOYALTY AND HAVING
THE TRUST AND BUILDING THAT
TRUST THROUGHOUT THE GAME IS
PROBABLY ONE OF THE MOST RARE
THINGS YOU CAN FIND IN
"SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: SO MISSY, AS JON
SAID, IF YOU WANT TRUST, YOU
HAVE TO GIVE TRUST, BUT THE
UMBRELLA OVER ALL THAT TRUST IS
OUTWITH IT, OUTPLAY, OUT LAST.
IF YOU WANTED TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE, THIS WOULD BE A GREAT
NIGHT TO DO IT.
>> YEAH, IT'S A LITTLE HARD FOR
ME RIGHT THIS SECOND BECAUSE
WITH A BROKEN FOOT, YOU KNOW, I
DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO BEGIN
ON THIS DAY.
YOU KNOW, WHEN SOMEBODY SAYS USE
ME I'M A VOTE, COULD THAT BE
SOMEBODY THAT COULD COME ALONG
AND POTENTIALLY BREAK UP THE
ALLIANZ?
SURE.
THAT SCENARIO COULD BE A BIG
MOVE, BUT I'M PRETTY LOYAL TO A
FAULT IN LIFE.
THAT'S MY LIFE, SO I'VE BEEN
LOYAL TO THE PEOPLE I'VE BEEN
LOYAL TO FROM THE VERY
BEGINNING, AND I DON'T WAIVER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JACLYN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMPUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ,
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE KEITH.
JACLYN.
KEITH.
THAT'S TWO VOTES KEITH, TWO
VOTES JACLYN.
JON.
THAT'S TWO VOTES KEITH, TWO
VOTES JACLYN, ONE VOTE JON.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
JON.
WE HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE.
KEITH, JON AND JACLYN EACH HAVE
TWO VOTES.
WE'RE GOING TO REVOTE.
JACLYN, JON, KEITH, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
BAYLOR, MISSY, NATALIE, YOU CAN
ONLY VOTE FOR ONE OF THOSE
THREE.
BAYLOR, YOU'RE UP.
WILL YOU COME GRAB THE URN.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCILLARY
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE JON.
THE NEXT PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
JON.
THAT'S TWO.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE.
>> NO HARD FEELINGS, GUYS.
>> OH, YEAH, TORCH.
>> Jeff: JON, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> SEE YOU GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE.
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" IS A
TRICKY GAME.
IT CAN LULL YOU INTO BELIEVING
THINGS THAT AREN'T REAL.
LIKE TRUST.
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN THE BASIC PREMISE --
OUTWITH IT, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
THIS GAME IS WIDE OPEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK THE CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON THE
TWO-HOUR SEASON FINALE OF
"SURVIVOR" --
>> IS IT REALLY FAIR BECAUSE I
CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
JEFF LARSON IT ALL COMES TO AN
END.
>> I DIDN'T COME 36 DAYS TO GET
VOTED OUT.
>> DON'T SAY JON BECAUSE YOU
DON'T.
>> I KNOW JON.
>> IN THE GAME, NOT REAL LIFE.
>> Jeff: JOIN US FOR THE FINALE
>> I THOUGHT I WAS DOING A GOOD
JOB PUTTING MY TRUST IN THE
RIGHT PEOPLE, BUT IT ENDED UP
BITING ME IN THE BUTT.
MISSY AND NATALIE DID A GOOD JOB
GAINING MY TRUST.
HONESTLY, DIDN'T FEEL THIS ONE
COMING.
I DEFINITELY REGRET NOT PLAYING
MY IDOL.
JACLYN, I HOPE YOU MAKE IT TO
THE FINAL THREE.
KICK BUTT, I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT,
BABE.
YOU KNOW YOU GOT MY VOTE.