english from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Everyone, throw away your bandanas!
We will change the tribes.
After a surprise change,
the new tribes
were completely different.
At Coyopa, we have
three close duos, and Keith.
At Hunahpu, we have
a close duo, Josh and Reed,
with a group of single people.
The new Coyopa
had a fake idol...
It's not an idol,
but it could be used one day.
...a true idol...
Oh yeah !
...and a whole new
dominating couple.
Missy and Baylor want us
and Kelley and Dale want us.
It's pretty crazy.
In the new Hunahpu,
Jeremy, Natalie and Julie
dreaded
losing their ally, Reed.
So it will be enough for Josh to
exert his influence on Reed
for Reed to switch sides.
To make matters worse,
everyone was starving.
What are we going to do
to have more to eat?
We are reduced
to a handful of rice.
Jeremy wins immunity for Hunahpu!
And after gaining immunity,
Hunahpu made
a desperate plea.
We have nothing more to eat.
We would like to trade for rice.
The bill will be salted.
I have a council to organize.
We'll see each other tomorrow
and we'll find a solution.
Coyopa to face the council...
We have to figure out
who we are close to.
...Jon and Jaclyn had to
choose between two couples.
Dale is sneaky,
and I'm sure his daughter is too.
But Baylor has already let me down
and it could do it again.
And at the council, they decided
to stay with Missy and Baylor...
- Kelly.
- It's okay, Dad.
...eliminating Kelley, Dale's daughter.
Kelley, the tribe has spoken.
There are thirteen left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What party !
At least it's over.
The advice
surely couldn't have been worse.
For me,
it was obviously upsetting.
You see complete strangers...
slaughter your daughter before your eyes.
And you can't do anything about it.
I had never seen my daughter
go through something so hard.
And no father could be
more proud of his daughter than I of Kelley.
It's rough.
But I won't give up
as long as I can talk.
Health !
How are you ?
I'm going to make breakfast.
Looking at yesterday's votes,
I know who's next.
I have to do something drastic
to make sure I stay.
I'm not dead until
I see my name four times.
What's this ?
An idol.
So know it,
since at the next vote,
I guess I'm targeted.
The idol is not real.
I took it on the well,
the first day.
They ignore it.
They will spend two sleepless nights
believing it to be true.
- So I'm not leaving next time.
- OK.
It seems like.
This morning
Dale showed me an idol.
If we lose the next immunity,
the idol could ruin our plans.
And that really scares me.
I hope he won't
raze our camp.
I think that if.
If we have to give up the roof,
we're screwed.
It would be horrible.
I don't know what I would do.
The fire goes out,
we can no longer cook...
In the mess.
After we won immunity yesterday,
Reed asked Jeff
if we could do a trade.
For rice.
If we make a trade for rice,
Jeff's gonna screw us up.
I don't want that.
Come on, collect!
We could win
a reward and celebrate tomorrow!
Why such a hunger
for a little rice?
Is beyond me.
- Oh my God !
- Oh Lord!
Hi Jeff!
Hello Jeff!
Health.
Let's get together and discuss.
Oh damn it!
I'm afraid.
What are you afraid of, Julie?
Of what will happen.
- I'm afraid.
- How much rice do you have?
- You want to see ?
- A...
- Like, a...
- A cup like this.
- A handful.
- Not even.
It's rather depressing.
- Yeah, nothing.
- Barely enough to taste.
One teaspoon each.
So you only have
a handful of rice left.
Think how many times
we've done this adventure.
On only one other occasion
was it necessary to supply rice again.
It was in Australia.
And it was due to
many other difficulties.
Reed, what can we
infer about this tribe?
Too many cooks in the kitchen,
who wanted to make too much rice.
- Too many customers, rather!
- It's true.
Dominant personalities
insisted on eating.
We don't necessarily want to
oppose and become a target,
only to regret it later.
What is happening to us now.
Josh, in your tribe,
you did the right thing.
We mix,
and here you are in a tribe
who has almost nothing left.
How do you react ?
Jeff, it's been really hard, honestly.
We arrive, and:
"Oh, by the way, we have nothing to eat."
We didn't eat much
and now nothing.
I feel so weak.
I want to say,
"Damn, guys!"
It's not like you
stopped us when we arrived.
I must say
there never was a tribe,
in the history of Survivor,
who needed help so much
after only fourteen days.
First, you lose your flint.
You are losing fire!
And must exchange the fishing kit.
And now
you're out of rice
and you need help again.
And I don't lose sight
that disproportion
in food
probably played an
important role in your dominance
so far in the tests.
So, to keep the game fair,
and in fairness to Coyopa,
who plays as you should,
the penalty must be fair.
I have enough rice
to last until the end of the game.
But the penalty will be severe.
This is what I want.
Your tarp, your hammock,
your bedding, pillows,
blankets, candles.
All the rewards
you have earned.
The hatchet, the hammer,
one of the pots,
and the second flint.
Which will leave you with a machete,
a pot and a flint.
You start from scratch.
Unhook the tarp.
Jeff took our comfort,
our tools and a pot,
and for me, it's...
It's worth it.
The infamous
second flint!
They are all happy.
I'm pissed.
You know we have nothing left?
Why are you happy?
It's really frustrating.
We made all our comfort,
it feared a max.
Not having a tarp
affects me particularly.
I don't know if it affects
others as much as me.
But I know it is for me.
I dread the rain.
Being cold will be a test for me.
- Good.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Let's hope it doesn't rain.
Over here everyone!
Hunahpu, discover
the new Coyopa tribe.
Kelley was eliminated
at the last council.
Oh my God !
Ready for a new
reward challenge?
Today, one member of each
team will be blindfolded.
You will overcome a series of obstacles
to a position
where there is a mask.
You will study it with your fingers.
Then you will untie
bags of puzzle pieces,
come back to a second position,
where you will use these parts
to recreate the mask.
To mislead you, there are decoys.
They will look similar,
but will not match.
The first person to succeed
wins the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
You should like it.
Oh my God !
Lord ! Lord !
With the grill,
what it takes to light it,
and meat. It's worth it ?
- Yes.
- Well yes !
Good. Since the change,
So today you can
field your champion.
Who is cut out for this event?
- How are you?
- Yeah.
Qui y va chez Hunahpu ?
- It'll be me, Jeff.
- Reed will go.
Coyopa, who goes and there?
Baylor versus Reed. The winner
takes home the reward for their tribe.
The loser goes to Exile Island.
Take a seat, let's get started.
Let's go. For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Reed hits the 1st hurdle hard,
but it doesn't slow him down.
Baylor really takes its time.
Reed is at the first post,
he has his first bag,
and he analyzes the puzzle.
Different strategy for Baylor.
She takes the bag and leaves.
We'll have to bring back
the three bags anyway.
The difference is the order
in which you do things.
Reed came back. Baylor has returned
to the puzzle table.
Reed returns to examine the mask.
Your companions could help you,
but they are not allowed to.
Name of...
You are on your own.
This is perhaps
the biggest reward so far.
Lots of meat.
Baylor has her second bag,
she's coming back.
Reed has his second bag, he's coming back.
Reed flies over the obstacle.
Baylor bangs his head.
Baylor is going to get its 3rd bag.
Reed studies his plays.
Two very different strategies.
Two up.
Big up.
The nose.
Reed goes to get his third bag.
Baylor has the third bag.
On the head, a blow in the bar.
Reed has his third bag.
Baylor returns with its 3rd bag.
Baylor has all the necessary parts.
She can start trying
to recreate this mask.
Reed has all the pieces now.
This is where it gets fun.
You have to remember the shapes
using only your fingers.
Seven pieces are needed,
but these bags hold much more.
This is the problem.
If you could see, you would know
that the lures are red.
If only you could see!
Huge in-game reward!
Reed placed two pieces.
One for Baylor.
Reed places a third coin
on his mask.
But that's not necessarily fair.
Reed places a 4th piece.
Baylor places another coin
on his mask.
Reed places another piece.
Baylor only placed two.
He's missing five.
Reed is only missing one piece.
- If that's right.
- If that's right, Jeff!
Baylor struggles but does not progress.
You, I'm not sure.
Reed is going to change a part,
he has doubts.
Is he right ?
Jeff, is that okay?
Reed thinks he's there.
Reed is right! Reed wins
the reward for his tribe!
- Cheer !
- Chicken and beef skewers!
- And here are the tears.
You succeeded ! You succeeded !
- You succeeded !
- You did it, honey!
- Impressive, Reed!
- That was crazy!
Reed, why the immediate tears?
It's stressful.
I'm so hungry.
How are you, Baylor?
You know, everyone is hungry.
So...
Confidence takes a hit,
"damn, I can't do it".
You feel like you've
let your tribe down.
Reed, come here.
Good, Reed!
Baylor goes to Exile Island.
Choose a member
of your tribe to accompany him.
There is a good chance
that the person you choose
will not benefit from this reward.
I thought about it a lot.
It seems to me that
Julie really rocks here,
and that would give him a chance
to show John
what she can take.
I was going to volunteer.
Interesting.
You want to send Julie,
and Natalie offers to go.
- Julie is doing her part, and...
- Yes, but...
- Everyone does their part.
- Not me.
Reed, one person you want to
send and one who wants to go.
Frankly, if Natalie wants
to go so badly, I won't stop her.
So, Natalie, gear up!
- Natalie, come down.
- Thank you, Natalie.
You're welcome.
- Well done Natalie! Well done Reed!
Make the best of it. Cheer.
Good. Natalie, Baylor,
on their way to exile. You will come back
for the next immunity.
Hope we don't get lost.
- Thank you, Natalie.
- Bye.
- I love you, Bay!
Hunahpu, your dominance
in this game
continues. Congratulation.
Take your things, on the way.
Have a good afternoon.
Coyopa, it seems
like I always say the same thing.
I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
Baylor is in very good hands.
Natalie volunteered.
I know Natalie is with me.
I think it will be very profitable.
It bites, but...
The fish must be
too small, no way to catch them.
They nibble.
And they steal my bait,
every time.
So Missy.
Natalie is always with you.
Completely. No chance
of her letting me down at this point.
OK. This morning
Dale showed me an idol.
- It's not true !
- Yeah. So...
- It really sucks.
- If we don't win immunity,
we could use Dale
to eliminate Keith.
Today Dale showed
Jon that he has an idol.
It thwarts our plans a bit.
I don't see
how Keith could stay.
I would love to,
but I don't see how.
Alright, let's find that camp.
- Where is he ?
- I do not know.
volunteered for exile,
I hope it will work in my favor.
At the merger,
it will prove to Missy and Baylor
that they will have to take care
of Natalie if necessary.
"An idol is hidden on your camp."
"Buried", "flag", "ten", "of".
"It's up to you whether you want to
share this information."
Baylor immediately showed me the clue,
without me asking him.
- Ten something...
- Buried by the flag.
Obtain information
from Baylor, in the long term,
it is far more important
than the reward.
I have to find this idol.
Jeremy and I
- we have to find her.
- Yeah.
- It would be great.
- And then we unroll.
Yeah.
Jeremy, Julie and I are in danger.
In the long term, I listen to Baylor,
because I have confidence in Missy,
and therefore in Baylor.
Reed, you tore it all up!
We're going to eat tonight!
Reed, you're a chef!
I'm very proud of Reed.
We come back with
eight skewers and a barbecue.
And me: "Yeah, that's my guy!
It's thanks to him !"
Thank you for contributing to the tribe!
I'm so excited to eat.
You did it.
I love you so much.
Josh and Reed behave
like the bosses.
And then they coo.
If Val was here,
we'd be so apart
that you would think
we don't like each other at all.
That's what you should do.
But these two
stuck together all the time, it's dangerous.
- These skewers are huge.
- In effect.
- Eight skewers!
- Who prefers chicken to beef?
- Vive Hunahpu !
- Hunahpu !
I love meat.
I eat a lot of it.
It was incredible.
I got kicked out of it.
Lord ! It's beef!
- My God !
- This is exceptional.
We feasted,
but we no longer have a tarp,
because our gifted
have decided to give it up.
If we had just waited 24 hours,
we would have had a full meal.
They are too stupid.
- It's refreshing!
- Yeah.
Give me an item of clothing
you want to keep dry.
Amazing
how the temperature has changed.
- Look at the height of the tide!
- It's freezing !
I'm already soaked.
Me too.
Of course, the day
we return the tarp, it's raining.
No lull in sight, apparently.
It might take a while.
Shit, it's falling apart.
Oh my God.
This rain sucks.
I say.
I can't stand
being wet all night.
I say.
I'm about to break down.
I am at the limit.
For sure.
Sad situation.
In tears, ready to leave.
Oh my God.
I don't know if I can do it.
Not all night.
I can't.
If Julie gives up,
I don't know what to do.
I need a majority.
But if she has to leave,
she has to go first...
Before me. You see ?
To be able to achieve fusion
and work wonders.
Don't let yourself down.
The day will be sunny.
I can't stand
another night like this.
- I can't.
- I say.
Don't let them see you like this, okay?
- Nope.
- Hold on. Hold on.
OK ? It will be fine.
This bad night is over.
No, I do not think so. It will be the same
every night for a while.
And I won't last.
Jeremy came over to check on me.
He tells me to hold on,
that he needs me,
that we will protect ourselves.
I need you, my daughter.
We are almost at the merger.
Yeah.
Last night exhausted me.
It was the hardest night of my life.
I've thought about it a million times.
"It's hard, but you can walk away."
But I'm here.
And that says it all.
It's Survivor!
You signed up for this!
Go home !
Over here everyone!
Let's welcome Natalie and Baylor
back from Exile Island.
Come on Baylor.
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yeah !
First of all, Julie, I get her back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will climb a high wall.
Then you will move a large
wooden cube from post to post.
At each post,
you will collect a bag of coins.
Once the three bags have been collected,
two team members will use
the rolls they contain
to solve
a flag puzzle.
The first tribe
to do so wins immunity,
is out of the vote. Losers,
you know the song.
Someone will be eliminated from the board.
Hunahpu, you have one more member,
who will not participate?
Julie or me.
I would say Julie, but...
Okay that's good.
Julie will not participate.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we start.
Let's go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Everyone must cross the wall.
After fifteen days,
this three meter wall
seems much higher.
The Hunahpu passed.
They start moving their cube.
- This cube is very heavy.
- 1, 2, 3, come on!
It's good, you lead!
Carry on, carry on!
The Coyopa have passed.
They move their cube.
- Go on !
- It's good, you assure!
Now you have to climb
and bring back the first bag.
- Go on !
- Jeremy climbs for Hunahpu.
Come on Jeremy!
You can't detach it,
you have to twist it.
- Throw it!
- Jon, on the 1st sack for Coyopa.
Jon picks up the pace.
Come on !
The Coyopa have the first bag.
- Go on !
- One more turn!
Jeremy has the 1st sack for Hunahpu.
Perfect equality at the start of the race.
Its good.
- Climb !
- Come on Jon!
Jon goes to get the second bag.
- Push, push!
- Go on !
Jeremy climbs again for Hunahpu.
Jon spins the bag
at a very good pace.
The Coyopa have their second bag.
They move
on to the third and final bag.
Yes, Jeremy, it's good!
Jeremy is stuck!
It's hooked!
Big setback for Hunahpu!
- Go on !
- They are used to winning,
but here they are lagging behind.
Back, Jeremy.
- Shoot it!
- So !
Go on !
Coyopa, looking for the 3rd bag.
- Attention.
- In the other direction.
Jeremy is still stuck.
Turn it down! Yes !
It's good for Jeremy.
Jeremy has
some catching up time for Hunahpu.
Caught !
The Coyopa have their 3rd bag.
Attack the puzzle!
- The Hunahpu have their 2nd bag.
- Come on !
Go on !
- Before !
- Jon and Missy
take care of the puzzle at Coyopa.
Hunahpu still doesn't have the 3rd bag.
They are exhausted.
- Climb !
- Come on Wes!
Wes is climbing now.
Jon thinks he has the first coin.
Hang it up, guys!
Good job guys ! Go Jon!
Cheer. Hook the corner.
Jon hung
the first piece for Coyopa.
Let's go!
The Hunahpu have their third bag.
Reed and Josh are going to solve
the puzzle for Hunahpu.
Yes, that's it, that's it!
Missy and Jon work well together.
- Let's go!
- He places the second piece.
There are eight rooms in all.
- Come on !
- [???]
Josh and Reed need to speed up
or it will be the end.
Third piece for Jon.
Yeah, big Jon!
Who is the big Jon now!
The tribe that has dominated since the beginning
might get in trouble
for the first time.
- This one.
- Accelerate, guys!
Come on !
Jon places a 4th piece for Coyopa.
- Nope !
- It's not the right one!
He must bring her back.
Josh places the first piece.
Yeah, that's it !
Reed places a 2nd piece for Hunahpu.
Coyopa is on the fourth.
- Do not !
It's not good either!
Coyopa's lead fades.
Josh places the 3rd piece for Hunahpu.
- Cheer.
- They have 3, it's good, continue!
Jon and Missy got it wrong again.
The Coyopa are struggling
to find the right part.
- A 4th piece for Josh.
- Yeah, good!
- Hunahpu took the lead.
- Wait, wait!
The Coyopa led all the way,
but they crumble
in the last part,
- on the jigsaw.
- Yeah !
Hunahpu is at five.
Coyopa n'en to what trois.
- Its good.
- Come on Jon!
Josh places another piece
for Hunahpu.
Hunahpu increases his lead.
Yeah, here it is!
Jon places another coin
for Coyopa.
He must hurry!
Reed places the 7th piece for Hunahpu.
- Place it!
- Hurry up, Jon!
It would be an incredible comeback
for Hunahpu.
Come on, Jon, come on!
Reed has the 7th piece.
Josh has the last piece for Hunahpu.
Hurry up, we're there!
Like that.
Is it right ?
It is !
Hunahpu wins immunity
once again!
We had it!
Shit, we had it!
It will be fine.
Cheer. I like you.
Hunahpu, once again,
immunity is yours.
Your dominance continues.
- You got it. Really.
- Nope.
Hunahpu, no advice.
No one will leave this group.
Take your things,
return to camp. Congratulation.
- Good boy.
Coyopa. Who can explain to me
what you feel?
What happens tonight will be worse.
We have all
already experienced departures,
but it will be the departure
of someone's loved one.
Coyopa, once again
you return to camp,
to try to define
what you will do tonight.
Take your things, on the way.
See you tonight at the council.
Nice team work!
It was violent.
We have no respite.
What to do ? Damn,
we were in on it today.
Our emotional fatigue
cause our rout.
It's frustrating.
But now my job
is to take out Dale
and achieve fusion,
to find Wesley there,
and then our pact will be strong.
Is it a good time
for me to take a nap?
Yes, lay down, you deserve it.
I also have a backup plan.
It's great to have this idol.
I can always take it out.
I don't want to, but I can.
It's the luxury I have.
I suck at this.
- In what ?
- In defeat.
I don't want to
play my idol tonight.
Good to have it in the merge.
I am willing to make a sacrifice
to achieve fusion.
If I'm not eliminated tonight,
as soon as the vote is finished and the torch extinguished,
I will give you my idol.
Wow.
To make sure I reach fusion.
At this point, I'm one guy
against a tribe of five.
So I sat down
with Jon to tell him
that if I didn't go out tonight,
I would give him my idol.
I'm sure
the idol isn't real.
Playing it would bring me nothing.
There, I therefore negotiate it
against votes.
And...
...another torch
than mine is extinguished,
I'll give you the idol
before we leave.
- So Missy would be leaving.
- Yeah.
On the board, I think
Jon, Jaclyn and I
let's eliminate Missy.
She's the one with the most
ties to the other side.
I guarantee it.
Dale said
if he didn't leave tonight,
he would give me his immunity idol.
Accepting this offer is tempting,
but we can't
stay focused on details,
I have to consider
the puzzle as a whole.
He said,
"I don't want to leave tonight.
If I stay,
I'll give you my idol."
We four have to move on.
This is only possible by firing them.
- OK.
- So Dale has an idol.
So, three Dale votes.
Two Keiths.
OK.
In case Dale has this idol,
three people will vote Dale,
and Baylor and I will vote Keith.
If he plays his idol,
Keith leaves. And that saddens me.
But better Keith
than Baylor or me.
The interest of following Dale...
The alliance would be you and me...
with an idol.
Do you think he has it? Frankly ?
I really believe it to be genuine.
Jaclyn and I
are again in the middle.
We could vote Dale.
We could fire Keith.
Or we could vote Missy.
The best option seems to me to
be the alliance with Dale.
Then to use the idol
in the interests of the alliance.
But what I have to do
first and foremost with this vote,
is to position myself
so that at the time of the merger,
Jaclyn and I are
in a strong position.
Dale, today, after the ordeal,
you said this vote
would be worse than defeat,
because you are eliminating
someone's loved one.
I know how it feels.
It's like taking
a wall in the face.
Since Kelley left,
I must have slept three hours.
The physical part of the game is nice.
These are the other 23 hours
of the day
which empty you.
Jon, do you feel that too?
Absolutely, yes.
I clearly agree.
Him too.
Howler monkeys agree.
Baylor, you were in exile.
How was your night?
We feel like a kid
lost in a store
when he no
longer finds his parents.
It's scary, it's rough,
and we don't know if we'll hold on.
Missy, it must be hard
to hear her daughter say:
"I felt like a little
girl lost without her mom.".
Yeah, it's rough.
This is the moment when we realize
that we are not there to help.
Baylor, what's happening to you?
When she cries, I cry.
When my father cries, I cry.
It's a family thing.
But she wasn't crying!
But it will come.
And when it starts,
I'm a fountain.
It's not fair.
What is it exactly?
Because it's so rare to have loved ones here.
And it definitely changes
the game, completely.
Yeah. I think
it's knowing
that you have someone
who will love you no matter what.
Dale, how is tonight's vote
different for you,
now that Kelley is gone?
My game went
from a long-term strategy
to a 12-hour term strategy .
Jon, did you feel that?
Did you feel that Dale was saying:
"I'm alive,
use me if you want."
Yes. Actually, Dale and I
talked,
and this is what he said:
"I am ready to do
what it takes to progress."
So yes, I felt it.
Jaclyn, if you two are
indeed in the middle again,
someone to tell you:
"Use me,
I'm a free vote!",
it must be very tempting.
Yes. It was nice
to hear another point of view.
Missy, this is not good for you.
No, neither for me nor for Baylor.
It's a bit disconcerting.
But at the same time,
Jeff, from my point of view,
I must place my faith
in those who eliminated my daughter.
It's my only choice in the game.
Basically all I have to offer,
is that I am loyal,
alone, an isolated vote,
and that I am not related to
anyone in the game.
Baylor, a single vote
can have great value.
I think
Jon and Jaclyn are very loyal,
as Dale says to be.
But I'm more loyal than him.
That's all I can say.
Dale, your eyes are gigantic!
It is very simple. I like Baylor,
but she has to assume her game.
"Go back to the first day,
if you want to talk about loyalty,
and remember who was there
and who was not.
I know, and it's hard.
There is one person
who has never wronged me,
and another that
more or less betrayed me at first.
You have to weigh the pros and cons.
Jon, this must influence
your decision,
to hear what
happened at the beginning.
Of course it influences him.
The merger is coming.
I have to know who will be with me,
who I can trust in the long term.
This is what guides tonight's vote.
Good. It's time to vote.
Keith, over to you.
More rain,
more rain, more rain.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
One Dale vote, one Missy vote,
one Keith vote.
Dale. Equality.
Two Dale votes,
two Keith votes, one Missy vote.
One vote remains.
Sixth person eliminated
from Survivor: Blood vs. water...
Dale.
Bring me your torch.
Dale, the tribe has spoken.
You are so Beautiful.
You said it was
the most important vote so far,
and that it revolved around loyalty.
The question that
time will answer is:
did you make the right decision?
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
It's fusion
in Blood vs. water.
Everyone knows
the game is on.
And no one is safe.
Thanks for helping me.
Now I have to eliminate you.
He's going to come after each one of us.
If we eliminate it, it's over.
I will fight until the end.
I did everything I could,
when I woke up this morning.
I thought I was covered.
Jon and Jaclyn did
the same thing to me as Kelley.
I did my best,
but the battle was hard.
This game was everything
I hoped for and more.
I can't wait to speak with Kelley.
We're going to talk for a long time tonight.