>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... AT THE
WHITE-COLLAR TRIBE, SHIRIN AND
MAX WERE BECOMING OUTCASTS.
>> THEY'RE RELENTLESS, BUZZING
IN YOUR EAR, AND YOU'RE JUST
LIKE, GOD.
>> Jeff: WHILE AT THE
BLUE-COLLAR TRIBE, IT WAS ALL
WORK AND NO PLAY.
>> HOW DO YOU [BLEEPED] THINK
THIS FIRE IS GOING RIGHT NOW,
MAGIC?
>> THIS BLUE-COLLAR TRIBE IS
FAILING.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, WILL STRUGGLED.
NINA WAS LEFT OUT, AND NO COLLAR
LOST THEIR SECOND CHALLENGE IN A
ROW.
WHITE COLLAR WINS IMMUNITY,
SENDING NO COLLAR BACK THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL... WILL.
WILL RECEIVED TWO VOTES, BUT IT
WAS NINA WHO JUST DIDN'T FIT
INCH NINA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
[THUNDER]
>> NINA SAW WHAT WAS COMING TO
HER, FINALLY.
SENT HER ON HOME.
BUT IT WAS PRETTY DELIGHTFUL TO
COME BACK TO CAMP AND SEE EMBERS
IN THE FIRE.
THAT WAS A SHINING HOPE, YOU
KNOW.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH DARKEST AND
NOW WE HAVE OUR EMBERS AND WE
HAVE OUR FIRE JUST BLAZING.
>> IN CASE YOU'RE WONDERING WHY
YOUR NAME CAME UP TWICE, THAT
WAS ONLY IN CASE NINA HAD THE
IDOL.
NO ONE WANTED YOU GONE.
>> NEW YORK I KNOW.
YOU GUYS STAYED TRUE TO THE
ALLIANCE, AND I TOLD YOU I WAS
LOYAL.
YOU GUYS SHOWED ME YOU'RE LOYAL.
NOW IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT GAME.
WE ARE DEFINITELY AT THE
MAKE-OR-BREAK POINT.
WE HAVE THE MENTALITY OF A
STRONG UNIT NOW.
THIS IS THE UNIT WE WANTED IN
THE BEGINNING, BUT I GOT TWO
VOTES.
IF WE LOSE THE NEXT CHALLENGE
AND GO TRIBAL COUNCIL, I'M GONE,
UNLESS I CAN CONVINCE JOE TO
VOTE ONE OF THE GIRLS, I'M GONE.
>> I AM STARVING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> GET THE MACHETE.
OH, YEAH.
>> HELL, YEAH.
>> SPREAD IT OUT SO YOU DON'T
CUT IT IN HALF.
THERE YOU GO, MIKE.
GET HIM.
THAT ABOY.
THAT ABOY, MIKE.
>> WE'RE STILL UNABLE TO GET A
FISH, WHICH IS BREAKING MY HEART
A LITTLE BIT.
WE'RE NOT GETTING CHICKEN
OBVIOUSLY.
ARE YOU GROSSED OUT EASILY?
I WANT YOU TO GRAB THIS.
BUT WE'VE BEEN SEEING A COUPLE
SNAKES THROUGHOUT CAMP, AND WE
HAVE GOT A SNAKE.
HERE WE GO.
>> IT'S STILL MOVING.
>> ANY OPPORTUNITY TO GET FOOD,
YOU KNOW, YOUR BOY FROM TEXAS IS
GOING TO EAT IT, I DON'T CARE
WHAT IT IS, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN, WHETHER BIT A SCOPEON OR A
SNAKE.
IT DON'T MATTER.
SNAKE'S READY.
>> I'M STARVING RIGHT NOW.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN TO GET
PROTEIN.
I'M A BIG TODAY.
I'M PROBABLY ONE OF THE BIGGER
DUDES OUT HERE.
I HAVE TO DO WHAT I HAVE TO DO
TO SURVIVE.
IT TASTES PRETTY GOOD.
I'LL EAT ANYTHING.
I'M EATING THINGS I NEVER
THOUGHT I'D EAT BEFORE.
>> WE'RE TURNING RODNEY INTO A
COUNTRY BOY KIND OF.
>> MIKE'S A LOYAL TEXAN.
HE GOT ME TRYING SNAKE.
WE HAD A HEATED ARGUMENT EARLIER
IN THE GAME.
BUT THAT'S MEN BEING MEN.
>> SNAKE, BRO.
>> FIRST TIME, HUH?
>> I'VE GOT SOME HAIR ON MY
CHEST, YOU KNOW.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WHITE COLLAR, BLUE COLLAR TRIBE
GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE
NEW NO-COLLAR TRIBE.
NINA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, ONE PERSON WILL BE
YOUR CALLER.
THE REST OF THE TRIBE WILL BE
BLIND FOLDED.
USING ONLY VERBAL COMMANDS, THE
CALLER WILL INSTRUCT ONE PAIR OF
BLINDFOLDED TRIBE MEMBERS TO GO
OUT AND COLLECT FOUR ITEMS.
EVERY TIME YOU GET AN ITEM, YOU
HAVE TO BRING IT BACK, HOIST IT
TO THE TOP, HEAD BACK OUT.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL ITEMS.
YOUR CALLER WILL SEND YOU BACK
OUT FOR ONE FINAL TRIBE FLAG.
THE FIRST TWO TRIBES TO RAISE
THEIR TRIBE FLAG TO THE TOP WIN
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH...
>> OH, YES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THREE EGG-LAYING
HENS, ONE ROOSTER.
THIS IS NUTRITION AND
COMPANIONSHIP.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH, TEN
EGGS.
>> WHOA.
>> Emily: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR, YOU
HAVE ONE EXTRA TRIBE MEMBER.
WHO'S GOING TO SIT THIS ONE OUT?
>> J.P., I'M OUT.
>> Jeff: J.P., YOU'RE OUT.
BLUE COLLAR, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
TRIBE MEMBERS.
RODNEY AND MIKE GOING TO SIT
THIS ONE OUT.
EVERYBODY ELSE, TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR POSITIONS.
THE WHITE-COLLAR TRIBE, CAROLYN
IS THE CALLER.
FOR BLUE COMER, SIERRA IS THE
CALLER.
FOR THE NO-COLLAR TRIBE, JOE IS
THE CALLER.
A NICE REWARD ON THE LINE.
HERE WE GO, SURVIVORS READY.
GO.
ALL ABOUT COMMUNICATION.
>> SIDE STEP RIGHT.
>> STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
>> TO THE LEFT, TO THE LEFT.
GET THROUGH FIRST ONE.
KEEP GOING.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR AND WHITE
COLLAR OUT QUICKLY.
>> STOP, STOP!
STAY WITH ME.
>> Jeff: RIGHT INTO THAT 2X4.
SHIRIN TOOK A NICE HIT TO THE
GROIN.
>> BACK, BACK.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR HAS THEIR
FIRST ITEM.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
>> BEND DOWN, BEND DOWN!
LEFT, LEFT, LEFT!
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR HAS
THEIR FIRST ITEM.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
>> STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, WATCH IN
FRONT OF YOU.
STRAIGHT!
GO AROUND IT.
YOU'RE FINE.
>> SIERRA, LOUDER!
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR BACK TO
THEIR FIRST ITEM.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET IT TO THE
TOP.
WILL PULLING ON ONE SIDE, THE
GIRLS PULLING ON THE OTHER.
NO COLLAR HAS THEIR FIRST ITEM.
>> DROP IT, DROP IT.
>> TO THE RIGHT.
UNDER THAT BAG.
YES!
>> Jeff: LINDSEY AND KELLY
COMING BACK WITH ABITEM.
SHIRIN TAKES ANOTHER HIT.
>> AT YOUR FEET.
AT YOUR FEET.
YES.
COME BACK.
>> Jeff: HALI AND JENN HAVE
THEIR FIRST ITEM.
WHITE COLLAR COMING BACK.
NO COLLAR BACK WITH THEIR SECOND
ITEM.
GETTING IT HERE IS FIRST PART.
GETTING IT TO THE TOP IS THE
SECOND PART.
>> OKAY.
NOW BOTH TOGETHER.
UP.
>> HALI, ONE MORE.
>> Jeff: A SECOND ITEM FOR THE
NO COLLARS.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK OUT LOOKING
FOR NUMBER THREE.
WILL, BE CAREFUL WHEN THAT
DROPS.
>> PULL, PULL!
>> I GOT IT.
DROP IT.
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR HAS THEIR
FIRST ITEM.
WHITE COLLAR HAS THEIR FIRST
ITEM TO THE TOP.
>> 3:00.
3:00.
>> TURN RIGHT.
>> Jeff: NO COLLARS HAVE THEIR
THIRD ITEM.
SHIRIN TAKES ANOTHER HIT.
>> THAT REALLY HIRTS.
>> A LITTLE MORE LINDSEY TO THE
RIGHT.
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR TRYING TO
GET THEIR SECOND ITEM.
WHITE COLLAR SEARCHING.
WHITE COLLAR'S GOT THEIR SECOND
ITEM.
>> NICE.
PUSH IT DOWN.
YES.
PERFECT.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR TRYING TO
GET THAT THIRD ITEM TO THE TOP.
BLUE COLLAR WORKING ON THEIR
SECOND ITEM.
>> DROP IT!
GO.
DROP IT!
>> Jeff: BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
NO COLLAR WITH THEIR THIRD.
JOE'S GOT IT.
>> LET I GOT, WILL.
WATCH YOURSELF, WILL.
>> Jeff: WILL GETS HIT AGAIN.
THAT IS ON YOU.
TAKE CARE OF THAT PLATFORM.
WHITE COLLAR HAS THEIR SECOND
ITEM.
GOT TO GET IT UP TO CAROLYN.
SHE'S GOT IT.
>> WATCH IT, JOAQUIN.
>> RIGHT THERE.
YES, THAT'S IT.
LINDSEY, YES.
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR HEADING
BACK WITH THEIR THIRD ITEM.
NO COLLAR SEARCHING FOR THEIR
FOURTH ITEM.
>> IT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
BEND OVER.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR LOOKING
FOR THAT THIRD ITEM.
WHERE IS IT?
>> YOU GOT IT.
LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR GETTING
ALL TIED UP IN AN OBSTACLE THAT
THEY REFUSE TO GO AROUND.
>> IN FRONT OF YOU.
ON THE GROUND.
YES.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR DOMINATING
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
THEY HAVE THEIR FOURTH ITEM.
>> BRING IT HOME.
BRING IT HOME!
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR TRYING TO
GET THIS THIRD ITEM TO THE TOP.
HERE COMES NO COLLAR WITH THEIR
FOURTH ITEM.
SIERRA GRABS IT BEFORE IT DROPS.
>> DROP IT, DROP IT!
>> Jeff: OH, KELLY, A MASSIVE
COLLISION.
>> KELLY, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Jeff: ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> SHE'S BLEEDING.
>> Jeff: STOP!
STOP WHERE YOU ARE.
MEDICAL, TAKE A LOOK AT KELLY.
TALK TO ME, BABE.
>> KELLY, YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE
BIT OF BLOOD.
THERE HAVE A SEAT FOR ME.
>> Jeff: BEN, SHE TOOK IT
RIGHT IN THE HEAD.
>> OKAY.
SHE'S GOT A GASH, THREE TO FOUR
CENTIMETERS.
>> Jeff: BEN, REASSURE HER
RIGHT NOW SINCE SHE'S
BLINDFOLDED.
IS SHE OKAY?
>> SHE'S FINE.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
OKAY.
SO YOU'RE NOT EMOTIONALLY...
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> SO I'M QUITE HAPPY TO JUST
BANDAGE THIS UP AND THEN
COMPLETE THE CHALLENGE.
AND THEN AFTER THE CHALLENGE IS
COMPLETE, I'LL HAVE A PROPER
LOOK AT IT.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU GOOD WITH
THAT?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP
GOING WITH A BLIND FOLD AND HEAD
INJURY KNOWING THAT IF YOU GET
AT ALL LIGHT-HEADED WE'LL STOP
THIS CHALLENGE, NO DAMAGE.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HURT ANYBODY
IF WE STOP IT AGAIN.
>> I'M GOOD.
I FEEL GOOD.
>> WAY TO GO, KEL.
>> Jeff: DO WHAT YOU NEED TO
DO.
>> GOOD JOB, KILL.
[CLAPPING]
>> GOOD JOB, KEL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
KELLY IS BANDAGED UP.
SHE'S OKAY.
GOING TO CONTINUE.
>> PEACE, GIRL.
>> Jeff: LET ME RESET WHERE
EVERYBODY IS.
BLUE COLLAR HAS THREE ITEMS.
THE WHITE COLLAR TRIBE IS BACK
WITH THEIR THIRD ITEM.
THE NO COLLAR TRIBE IS BACK WITH
THEIR FOURTH ITEM.
FIRST TWO TO FINISH WIN REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON.
>> TO THE RIGHT.
GO STRAIGHT.
YOU GOT TO GO FASTER.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR TRYING
TO GET THEIR THIRD ITEM.
CAROLYN HAS IT.
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR HAS ALL
FOUR ITEMS.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR THEIR FLAG.
THAT'S THE LAST ITEM.
>> TO THE LEFT!
TO THE LEFT!
>> TO THE RIGHT!
TO THE RIGHT!
TO THE RIGHT.
>> TO THE LEFT!
>> TO THE RIGHT!
TO THE RIGHT!
LINDSAY, TO THE RIGHT!
>> I'M GOING TO THE [BLEEPED]
RIGHT.
>> GRAB IT!
STOP AND GRAB IT!
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR LOOKING
FOR THEIR FOURTH ITEM.
MAX HAS IT.
>> REACH, REACH, LEFT, YES!
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR LOOKING
VERY GOOD RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN WHILE AND BLUE FOR
SECOND PLACE.
KELLY SUFFERED A LOT OF BLOOD
LOSS, WANTS TO WIN THIS.
>> NO, GUYS, NO, DOWN.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR CANNOT
GET THEIR ITEMS ON THEIR
PLATFORM, WHICH OPENS THE DOOR
FOR BLUE COLLAR TO GET BACK IN
IT.
BUT BLUE COLLAR'S PLATFORM IS
ASKEW.
THE ONLY TRIBE THAT HAS FIGURED
THIS CHALLENGE OUT IS THE NO
COLLAR TRIBE.
THEY HAVE THEIR LAST ITEM FOR
THE WIN.
NO COLLAR WINS REWARD!
THREE HENS AND A ROOSTER.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR SECOND PLACE.
WHITE COLLAR HAS THEIR FOURTH
ITEM UP.
BLUE COLLAR, YOU GOT TO MOVE,
BLUE COLLAR.
YOU GOT TO MOVE.
WHITE COLLAR LOOKING FOR THAT
FLAG, THEIR LAST ITEM.
SHIRIN RUNNING.
SIERRA HAS THE FOURTH ITEM FOR
BLUE COLLAR.
HEAD OUT, BLUE COLLAR, HEAD OUT.
>> MAX, FIND THE FLAG!
YOU GOT IT.
LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR HAS
THEIR FLAG.
BLUE COLLAR HEADING OUT FOR
IT MAY BE TOO LATE.
>> RUN.
YOU GUYS GOT TO GO FASTER.
>> TO THE LEFT AND GO STRAIGHT.
>> DAMMIT, SIERRA.
>> Jeff: BLUE COLLAR LOOKING
FOR THEIR FLAG.
WHITE COLLAR HAS THEIR FLAG.
THEY JUST HAVE TO GET IT TO THE
TOP.
>> OKAY.
AGAIN.
UP.
SLOWLY.
AGAIN.
UP.
>> Jeff: FOR THE FIRST TIME
THEY'RE MOVING THEIR PLATFORM
SLOWLY.
>> GO FORWARD.
>> THIS IS FORWARD.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN IS VERY
CLOSE, AND SHE HAS IT.
WHITE COLLAR WINS REWARD.
BLUE COLLAR WINS NOTHING AFTER A
BIG EFFORT.
>> I'M SO PISSED RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: NO-COLLAR TRIBE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
GREAT COMMUNICATION.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: AS A RESULT, A HUGE
REWARD, THREE EGG-LAYING HENS
AND ONE ROOSTER.
THIS WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK,
ENJOY.
WHITE COLLAR, TEN EGGS.
>> WAY TO GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ENJOY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
BLUE-COLLAR TRIBE, YOU'LL GRAB
YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ON YOUR WAY BACK THE CAMP,
KELLY, MEDICAL WILL LOOK AT THAT
AND STITCH YOU UP.
BLUE-COLLAR TRIBE, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
HEAD OUT.
>> I LIKE YOU BETTER THAN OUR
OLD TRIBE MATES.
>> YEAH, WE DO.
>> WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK
ABOUT...
>> SLAUGHTER ONE?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MY GOD, FINALLY WE GOT A
WIN, AND TODAY IS MY 42ND
BIRTHDAY.
I'M HAPPY BECAUSE BIRTHDAYS ARE
ALWAYS SPECIAL TO ME.
>> LOVE YOU, BROTHER.
>> LOVE YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> I NEVER SPENT A BIRTHDAY AWAY
FROM MY FAMILY, AND I MEAN I
KNOW IT'S A GAME, BUT THEY WENT
OUT OF THEIR WAY TO MAKE SURE I
HAD A SPECIAL 42nd BIRTHDAY.
TOP THIS BIRTHDAY OFF WITH A
LITTLE FRIED CHICKEN.
>> ARE YOU CARING FOR THEM RIGHT
NOW?
IT'S ONLY GOING TO MAKE IT
HARDER, RIGHT?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO EAT THEM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO EAT THEM.
>> BUT THEY HAVE EGGS.
>> BACK HOME I DON'T EAT MEAT.
I DON'T LIKE HURTING ANIMALS.
I DON'T SEE THE PURPOSE IN
KILLING THIS CHICKEN.
IT PROVIDES US WITH EGGS.
BUT THEY DON'T CARE.
THEY'RE DEAD SET ON EATING THIS
CHICKEN.
>> SORRY, BABY GIRL.
>> YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE?
>> NOPE.
>> I THINK JENN'S TOTALLY JUST
STARVED.
>> PROBABLY.
>> WILL YOU CUT IT?
>> EVERYONE'S AT THE CAMP
COOKING AND KILLING AND GUTTING
WHATEVER-ING THE CHICKEN.
>> WHERE'S JENN?
JENN CAN'T HANDLE IT.
>> IT REALLY BOTHERS ME TO SEE
THAT.
I'M OUT GOING FIREWOOD.
OF COURSE I'LL POKE AROUND FOR
THE IDOL, BUT MY CONFIDENCE FOR
FINDING IT IS ABOUT 10%.
ALL THESE TREES LOOK THE SAME.
WITH NO CLUE, IT'S A NEEDLE IN A
HAYSTACK-TYPE DEAL.
BUT HISTORICALLY THE IMMUNITY
IDOL IS IN THE DRY CREEK BED,
LIKE IN THE WALL OR SOMETHING,
OR IT'S GOING TO BE IN A TREE.
IT'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE IN A
TREE.
>> OH, THIS IS GOING TO BE
AWESOME.
CHICKEN.
SO EXCITED.
WILL'S BIRTHDAY, BIRTHDAY FEAST.
>> BIRTHDAY FEAST FOR WILL.
>> IT'S USUALLY A UNIQUE-LOOKING
TREE, SOMETHING THAT MAKES THEM
STAND OUT A LITTLE BIT.
>> JENN'S BEEN GONE FREAKIN'
FOREVER.
>> THIS IS SO GOOD.
>> NO, FREAKING WAY.
THIS IS LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE.
I DID IT.
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS IS AMAZING.
I THINK IF I WERE ON THE BLUE OR
WHITE-COLLAR TRIBE I WOULD BE
WORRIED BECAUSE IT'S OUR PEOPLE,
THE NO COLLARS THAT STIR THINGS
UP AND MESS UP THE GAME.
I CAN SCREW UP THE GAME SO
EASILY WITH THIS THING.
I GUESS KILLING THE CHICKEN KIND
OF WORKED OUT FOR ME.
WINNER, WINNER, CHICKEN DINNER.
>> THE GIRL, KEL, KEL, GOT
KNOCKED IN THE HEAD TODAY.
SHE ENDED UP GETTING SIX
STITCHES.
THIS IS ONE OF THE TOUGHEST
GIRLS I'VE SEEN IN A LONG TIME,
SO FITTING THE STEREOTYPE OF A
BLUE COLLAR.
I HAVE MAD RESPECT FOR THAT AND
I FEEL LIKE WE COULD GO REALLY,
REALLY FAR IN THIS GAME
TOGETHER.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WHAT?
>> GIRLS NEED TO HOLD THEMSELVES
TO A HIGHER STANDARD THAN GUYS.
>> THAT'S SUCH CRAZY LOGIC TO
ME.
>> LISTEN, HOW MANY TIMES...
>> YOU BROKE IT DOWN.
YOU BROKE IT DOWN.
>> NO, NO, NO, IF A GIRL BROKE
UP WITH A GUY, A GUY WOULD BE
LINING UP.
IF I GO TO A CLUB, I JUST BROKE
UP WITH MY GIRL, I HAVE TO PUT
IN WORK.
>> THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
>> I SAY IF YOU GO TO A CLUB,
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T MEET
PEOPLE AT THE CLUB.
>> OR THE CAR OR THE CARNIVAL OR
A MUSEUM.
>> IF YOU WERE MY SON I'D BREAK
YOUR JAW.
>> WELL, MY MOTHER'S PROUD OF
ME.
>> THERE'S SO MUCH WRONG WITH
YOU.
>> RODNEY THINKS THAT WOMEN NEED
TO HOLD THEMSELVES TO A HIGHER
STANDARD THAN MEN, WHICH IS
WHAT'S WRONG WITH SO MANY
RELATIONSHIPS, BECAUSE GUYS
THINK THEY HAVE THE RIGHT TO DO
THINGS THAT A WOMAN CAN'T, AND
IT'S HARD TO LIVE WITH SOMEONE
SO CLOSELY WHO HAS SUCH
DIFFERENT VIEWS BECAUSE I LOOK
AT SOMEONE LIKE THAT, AND I'M
LIKE, WHO RAISED YOU?
LIKE WHAT TYPE OF WOMAN WOULD
RAISE A MAN TO THINK THAT?
THE BOTTOM LINE IS EVERYONE IS
ON THE EQUAL PLAYING FEED, AND
IF YOU THINK WOMEN SHOULD HOLD
THEMSELVES TO A HIGHER STANDARD,
THEN YOU SHOULD HOLD YOURSELF TO
A HIGHER STANDARD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FIRST OF ALL, LINDSEY, SHE LOOKS
LIKE A FEMALE MIKE TYSON OUT
HERE.
WHO THE HELL GETS A TATTOO ON
THEIR DAMN FACE UNLESS YOU GOT
SOME SERIOUS PROBLEMS?
YOU CAN TELL SHE'S GOT SOME
SERIOUS PROBLEMS HAVING A MIKE
TYSON TATTOO.
>> IS THAT HOW YOUR MOM RAISED
YOU?
THAT'S HOW YOUR MOM RAISED YOU?
>> ALL I WAS TRYING TO SAY IS I
THINK GIRLS SHOULD HOLD
THEMSELVES TO A HIGHER STANDARD
THAN MEN.
MEN ARE DOGS.
WE WANT ANGELS.
THAT'S HOW ME AND MY BOYS ARE.
I MIGHT NOT BE AN ANGEL.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT WHEN I SETTLE
DOWN.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY WE'RE
FIGHTING OVER SOMETHING SO
STUPID.
>> SO I GOT TO GO BACK TO MY
THREE Cs -- COOL, CALM AND
CHECKED.
I CAN'T BE A HOTHEAD IN THIS
GAME.
THAT'S WHO I AM.
I'M A HOTHEAD.
THAT WILL SEND ME OUT, TOO.
>> EGGS.
>> THERE ARE TEN EGGS.
>> THE CHICKENS WOULD HAVE BEEN
DELICIOUS.
>> LISTEN, WE GOT EGGS.
>> I'M KIND OF THRILLED THAT WE
DIDN'T WIN THE WHOLE CHICKEN
PACKAGE JUST BECAUSE I KNEW THAT
WAS GOING TO BE YET ANOTHER
WHITE COLLAR NIGHTMARE.
I KNOW THAT NONE OF MY GUYS HAVE
EVER SLAUGHTERED ANY KIND OF AN
ANIMAL LET ALONE A CHICKEN.
I LEARNED HOW THE KILL A CHICKEN
FOR "SURVIVOR."
I WATCHED A VIDEO AND TALKED TO
A FARMER ALL ABOUT IT AND THEN I
SLAUGHTERED A RABBIT.
IT'S DIFFERENT, VERY DIFFERENT,
BUT IT DESSENSTIZES YOU.
>> SHIRIN SAYS SHE SLAUGHTERED A
BUNNY RABBIT.
REALLY?
FIRST THING THAT CAME TO MY MIND
WAS SOSA PATH.
FIRST THING THEY START DOING IS
KILLING SMALL ANIMALS.
IT PROBABLY STARTED WITH A MOUSE
AT LIKE 14.
SHE'S AT A RABBIT RIGHT NOW AT
29.
IT'S INSANE HOW SHE TRIES TO
JUSTIFY HER PSYCHOTIC WAYS.
ALL RIGHT, PSYCHO, YOU SIT OVER
THERE.
>> I PREFER TO, YOU KNOW, PUSH
SOMETHING, NOT PUNCH SOMETHING.
>> LISTEN, THE CHALLENGE WILL
DICTATE WHICH ONE, BUT I'M JUST
MORE CONCERNED IF THE FOUR OF US
COMPETE AND SHE'S IN DOUBT, IS
SHE GOING TO FEEL ALIENATED AND
WHEN WE COME BACK TO CAMP...
>> WHAT WOULD BE THE DIFFERENCE
IF I SAT OUT?
>> YOU'RE THE LOGICAL PERSON.
>> SO IS THAT THE LOGIC FOR
SITTING ME OUT?
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> IT MIGHT BE THAT I SIT OUT.
>> IT DEPENDS ON... I GUESS WE
WAIT UNTIL THEN.
>> MAX IS PITCHING I REALLY
DON'T THINK WE SHOULD SIT OUT
SHIRIN BECAUSE IT WILL UPSET
HER?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
ON THE SPECTRUM OF CRAZY, I
THINK BOTH MAX AND SHIRIN ARE
VERY CLOSE TO 10.
I'M A BETTER ATHLETE SO WE'RE
GOING TO GIVE UP THE POTENTIAL
FOR WINNING BECAUSE WE HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT WHETHER HER FEELINGS
ARE HURT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT HE BROUGHT
THAT UP.
MAX WANTS TO BE THE CULT LEADER
OF OUR TRIBE.
SHIRIN GOES NAKED BECAUSE MAX
GOES NAKED.
SHE WOULD DRINK HIS KOOL-AID.
VERY DANGEROUS.
VERY, VERY DANGEROUS.
>> WE LOSE TOMORROW, ARE WE ALL
IN AGREEMENT IT'S MAX?
>> THAT'S A SERIOUS TALK.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS ARE
FREAKING KILLING ME.
HE'S A CULT LEADER AND YOU'RE
BEING ROMANCED.
>> HE'S USING HIS SAFE BULL UM
TO MAKE MOVES?
>> NO QUESTION IN MY MIND, YOU
CUT THE HEAD OF THE SNAKE OFF.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
WILL TAKE IT BACK.
LINDSEY, GIVE IT UP.
SHIRIN.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: YOU GUYS DO NOT GIVE
THIS UP EASILY.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, EACH
TRIBE WILL BE ATTACHED TO A
ROPE.
ON MY GO, ONE AT A TIME YOU'LL
MANEUVER THROUGH A ROPE
OBSTACLE.
YOU'LL GRAB THE BAG OF BALLS,
HEAD TO THE FINISH, WHERE YOU
MUST THEN BALANCE ON A BEAM
WHILE ATTEMPTING TO MANEUVER A
BALL THROUGH A MAZE OF HOLES TO
THE TOP.
IF THE BALL FALLS THROUGH A
HOLE, YOU GOT TO START OVER.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO GET ALL
THREE BALLS TO THE TOP WINS
IMMONEYTY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
THE LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
BLUE COLLAR, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
PEOPLE, SITTING TWO PEOPLE OUT.
WHO'S GOING TO SIT OUT?
LINDSEY AND DAN, TAKE A SPOT ON
THE SIT-OUT BENCH.
WHITE COLLAR SITTING ONE PERSON
OUT.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
SHIRIN, TAKE A SPOT ON THE
SIT-OUT BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> COME ON, HALI.
>> Jeff: HALI, MIKE AND
JOAQUIN HEADING OUT FIRST FOR
EACH TRIBE.
ROPE MANAGEMENT AND YOU'RE DOING
THIS ON AN ANGLE, WHICH MAKES IT
EVEN MORE DIFFICULT.
>> COME ON, HALI.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN IS THROUGH.
HALI'S THROUGH.
MIKE IS HUNG UP.
>> YOU GOT THIS, HALI.
NIGHT.
NOW MIKE IS DOWN.
THERE GOES JOAQUIN.
>> Jeff: MIKE PICKING UP THE
PACE NOW.
GO BLUE COLLAR.
GO, NO COLLAR.
NOW SIERRA FOR BLUE COLLAR AND
CAROLYN FOR WHITE COLLAR.
HERE COMES WILL FOR NO COLLAR.
HE'S STRUGGLING WITH THIS
ELEMENT IN THE WATER, AND HE'S
NOW STRUGGLING AGAIN ON LAND.
>> GO, GO, GO.
YOU'RE FINE.
>> Jeff: SIERRA FLYING THROUGH
IT FOR BLUE COLLAR.
GO, BLUE COLLAR.
BLUE COLLAR IN THE LEAD.
NOW WILL'S STARTING TO FIGURE IT
OUT.
>> COME ON, WILL.
>> Jeff: GO, WHITE COLLAR.
GO, NO COLLAR.
GO, BLUE COLLAR.
HERE COMES MAX FOR WHITE COLLAR.
THERE'S RODNEY, THE FINAL PERSON
FOR BLUE COLLAR.
GO, WHITE COLLAR.
WHITE COLLAR ON THEIR LAST
PERSON.
GO, NO COLLAR.
JOE THE LAST PERSON FOR NO
COLLAR.
>> NO, NO, NO!
>> UNDER THE ROPE, UNDER THE
ROPE!
>> NO!
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
>> UNDER.
>> THIS WAY?
>> Jeff: IT IS RODNEY NOW
STUCK FOR BLUE COLLAR AND LOSING
A LOT OF TIME.
>> GO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: RODNEY FINALLY GETS
FREE.
RODNEY THE FOURTH AND FINAL
MEMBER FOR BLUE COLLAR.
HEAD OUT, BLUE COLLAR.
GOT TO UNTIE THAT BAG OF BALLS.
START GOING, NO COLLAR.
EVERYBODY ON DECK.
START GOING, WHITE COLLAR.
BLUE COLLAR HAS THEIR BAG OF
BALLS.
HEAD OUT TO THE MAZE.
>> GOT IT?
>> GO.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR HAS THEIR
BAG OF BALLS.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT TO THE MAZE.
IT IS MIKE FOR BLUE COLLAR
ALREADY WORKING ON THE MAZE.
JOE FOR NO COLLAR WORKING ON THE
MAZE.
WHITE COLLAR NEEDS TO PICK IT
UP.
>> GO.
>> Jeff: YOUR GOAL IS TO GET
THAT BALL TO THE TOP WITHOUT
DROPPING THROUGH ANY OF THE MANY
HOLES.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, MIKE.
>> LET'S GO, JOAQUIN.
>> Jeff: BOTH FEET HAVE TO
STAY ON THAT BEAM AT ALL TIMES.
IF YOU FALL OFF, YOU HAVE TO
START OVER.
MIKE TRYING SOME CRAZY STRATEGY.
>> THAT ABOY, MIKE.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN HAS FIRST
BALL FOR WHITE COLLAR.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
HERE COMES CAROLYN.
JOE VERY CLOSE FOR NO COLLAR.
JOE HAS FIRST BALL FOR NO
COLLAR.
JENN NOW GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
MIKE GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER
FOR BLUE COLLAR.
>> GET IN THERE.
YEAH!
>> Jeff: YES, MIKE HAS IT.
WE ARE TIED 1-1-1.
>> YOU GOT THIS, SIERRA.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN NEAR THE TOP
NOW.
CAN SHE GET IT IN THERE?
THERE IT IS.
CAROLYN HAS THE SECOND ONE FOR
WHITE COLLAR.
IT IS WHITE COLLAR NOW WORKING
ON THEIR THIRD AND FINAL BALL.
JENN'S GETTING VERY CLOSE TO
THAT SECOND BALL FOR NO COLLAR.
THERE IT IS.
JENN HAS THE SECOND FOR NO
COLLAR.
WE'RE TIED, WHITE COLLAR WITH
TWO, NO COLLAR WITH TWO, BLUE
COLLAR WITH ONLY ONE.
>> THAT'S IT, SIERRA.
TAKE YOUR TIME, BABE.
>> Jeff: SIERRA VERY CLOSE
WITH THAT SECOND BALL.
>> THAT'S IT, SIERRA.
>> Jeff: GO, BLUE COLLAR.
WE'RE NOW TIED 2-2-2.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: WE HAVE TYLER, KELLY
AND HALI ALL WORKING ON THAT
THIRD AND FINAL BALL.
>> MAX, MAX, MAX.
>> Jeff: TYLER DROPS IN AND
HE'S GOING TO DROP OUT, CALLING
MAX IN.
>> COME ON, MAX!
>> Jeff: THAT OPENS UP THE
DOOR FOR BLUE COLLAR AND NO
COLLAR.
HALI VERY CLOSE TO WINNING
IMMUNITY FOR NO COLLAR.
HERE COMES KELLY.
>> NICE MOVE, KELLY.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS.
NO COLLAR WINS IMMUNITY.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM NO
COLLAR.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
KELLY VERY CLOSE.
BLUE COLLAR COULD WIN IMMUNITY
RIGHT HERE.
KELLY DROPS HER BALL.
SHE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
BIG MISSED OPPORTUNITY FOR THE
BLUE COLLAR TRIBE.
RODNEY TAKING OVER FOR KELLY,
DIDN'T EVEN ASK, JUST FORCED HIS
WAY IN.
IT'S WHITE COLLAR NOW IN THE
LEAD.
MAX MAKES A BIG MOVE AND IT DOES
NOT WORK.
>> NEVER GOING TO WORK THAT WAY.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN WE'RE BACK
EVEN.
BLUE COLLAR HAS NOT GONE TO
TRIBAL.
MAX KNOWS WHAT TRIBAL IS LIKE
AND DOES NOT WANT TO RETURN.
MAX ONCE AGAIN MAKING BIG MOVES,
HUGE RISKS.
IT IS NOW MAX IN THE LEAD OVER
RODNEY.
RODNEY TAKING HIS TIME.
MAX PLAYING MORE AGGRESSIVE.
>> TO GET AROUND THE HOLE, JUST
PULL ONE.
>> Jeff: MAX WITH A NICE
MANEUVER.
MAX WITH THE LEAD.
>> GO, WHITE, GO, WHITE!
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: RODNEY DROPS.
THIS COULD BE IT.
>> LEFT, LEFT, LEFT.
>> Jeff: MAX VERY CLOSE.
>> YEAH!
YEAH!
>> Jeff: MAX SCORES FOR WHITE
COLLAR.
WHITE COLLAR SAFE FROM TRIBAL,
SENDING BLUE COLLAR TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL FOR THE FIRST TIME THIS
SEASON.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
>> Jeff: NO COLLAR,
CONGRATULATIONS.
WILL, YOU GET IT?
>> YES, SIR.
MY BIRTHDAY.
>> Jeff: NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM NO COLLAR AND NOBODY GOING
HOME FROM WHITE COLLAR.
IMMUNITY FOR WHITE COLLAR, AS
WELL.
NO COLLAR, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> Jeff: WHITE COLLAR GRAB
YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
BLUE COLLAR, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FOURTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
AND THE FIRST PERSON TO LEAVE
FROM YOUR TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> IN THIS CHALLENGE RODNEY WAS
THE FACTOR THAT SLOWED US DOWN.
HE GOT STUCK AND LOOKED AT ME
LIKE A LOST PUPPY.
MY HORSES ARE MUCH SMARTER THAN
RODNEY, ESPECIALLY WHEN IT'S
COMPETITION DAY.
AND FOR ME, IT'S NOT EVEN IN THE
CHALLENGES BUT IN CAMP LIFE,
RODNEY'S JUST GOT TO GO.
>> WELL, THAT SUCKED.
>> WIN, LOSE OR DRAW, YOU GUYS,
I WANT TO SAY THAT I'M REALLY
PROUD I GOT YOU ON MY MATT THAT
FIRST DAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
TONIGHT.
>> AGREED.
100%.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE'RE READY FOR.
>> I WASN'T READY TO GO SEE
PROBST, NOT EVEN.
>> THIS LOSS COULD BE EXACTLY
WHAT THE BLUE TRIBE NEEDED.
YOU DO NOT KNOW WHO YOUR TRUE
ALLIANCE IS UNTIL JEFF IS
READING THOSE NAMES.
>> SO IS IT ME?
LET'S JUST GET RIGHT TO IT?
>> ACTUALLY, I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU.
>> YEAH?
>> RODNEY HAS MY VOTE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE MORALS.
HE HAS ABSOLUTELY NO...
>> NO RESPECT FOR GIRLS.
>> FOR WOMEN.
I JUST HOPE THAT YOU'LL CONSIDER
VOTING HIM OUT.
>> THERE ARE TWO WAYS TO LISTEN,
YOU CAN LISTEN LIKE A GUY, OR
YOU LISTEN LIKE A GIRL.
WHEN YOU LISTEN LIKE A GUY, YOU
TRY SOLVE THE PROBLEM BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT WE DO, WE WANT TO
FIX THINGS.
WHEN YOU LISTEN LIKE A GIRL, YOU
EMPATHIZE, YOU JUST NOD YOUR
HEAD AND AGREE.
I CAN'T DISAGREE WITH YOU.
REALLY CAN'T.
YOU JUST SMILE AND NOD, YES,
DEAR, I UNDERSTAND, YOU'RE
RIGHT.
IF GETTING RID OF RODNEY HELPS
TO BRING THIS TRIBE TOGETHER,
I'M IN.
>> I THINK IT WILL.
>> IT WILL MAKE THE TRIBE
STRONGER IN THE END.
>> IT'S HUGE.
>> I DON'T DISAGREE WITH THAT.
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
I THINK THAT IS THE BEST WAY TO
GO.
I AM SO MUCH SMARTER THAN I
LOOK.
THIS IS A GAME OF NUMBERS, AND
YOU KNOW SOMETHING, THEY HAVE
ISOLATED THEMSELVES INTAS A
GROUP OF TWOs.
>> WHAT IT COMES DOWN TO RIGHT
HERE IS THIS FOUR RIGHT HERE.
I LOVE THIS FOUR.
I'M A LEADER.
I'M GOING TO BE THE LEADER NO
MATTER.
WHAT I'M THE TOM BRADY HERE.
IF I STEP ON THE FIELD, ALL
BUSINESS ASIDE, I'M TOM BRADY
OUT HERE.
THESE BROADS DON'T NO WHAT
THEY'RE DOING.
THEY CAME INTO THIS GAME WITH NO
STRATEGY AT ALL.
>> SO WHAT'S GOING ON IS ME,
DAN, KELLY AND MIKE, WE'RE A
STRONG FOUR.
SO BYE-BYE, LINDSEY.
ANYTHING YOU DO, YOU GOT TO BE A
SMOOTH CRIMINAL LIKE MICHAEL
JACKSON, BABY.
LINDSEY IS SAYING SO MUCH
DISRESPECTFUL STUFF AND I'VE
BEEN HOLDING BACK.
IF SHE WERE HOME I'D SPANK HER
LIKE A BAD BABY.
>> RODNEY SHOULD NOT BE SO
FLAMBOYANT ABOUT LINDSEY GOING,
HE COULD BE THE NEXT TO GO.
IT'S FUNNY TO WATCH HIM.
>> THE WINNER IS ON THE BLUE
COLLAR.
>> MIKE ANDRY DEFINITELY
TOGETHER.
AND MIKE DOES NOT TRUST RODNEY,
AND I DON'T TRUST RODNEY EITHER.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> IT'S YOU AND ME.
I AGREE.
>> OKAY.
>> I DON'T TRUST HIM.
>> HE PISSES ME OFF, LIKE BAD.
>> I'M WITH YOU, 110.
>> IT'S RODNEY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> IT'S BEST FOR TRIBE.
>> IT IS.
HE'S MADE MISTAKES IN
CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH.
NO, I KNOW.
LINDSEY AND RODNEY CLASH.
THEY BOTH HAVE ATTITUDES.
THEY BOTH WANT TO BE THE BOSS.
LINDSEY IS BITCHY HOW SHE'S
GOING ABOUT IT.
MIKE AND I ARE IN A GOOD
POSITION TONIGHT TO GO WITH
EITHER THE GIRLS OR THE GUYS.
WE COULD VOTE FOR RODNEY OR WE
COULD VOTE FOR LINDSEY.
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE HUGE.
SOMEONE'S GOING HOME AND
SOMEONE'S GOING TO BE PISSED
OFF, BUT I KNOW IT'S NOT ME.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE,
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, DAN, LET'S GET REAL.
GIVE ME THE VIBE OF THIS TRIBE.
WHO QUICKLY BONDED?
>> LINDSEY AND SIERRA BONDED
REALLY QUICKLY.
>> Jeff: RODNEY, WHO DIDN'T
GET ALONG?
UM, THE ONE I DIDN'T GET ALONG
WITH WITH IS THIS GIRL RIGHT
HERE.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT, WE
DON'T MIX, WE'RE LIKE CHICKEN
APARTMENT AND TUNA FISH.
IT JUST DON'T TASTE GOOD.
>> Jeff: SO LINDSEY, THIS
THERE IS THIS WALL WITH RODNEY.
>> RODNEY AND I JUST COME FROM
VERY, VERY DIFFERENT
BACKGROUNDS.
WE HAVE VERY DIFFERENT MORALS.
>> Jeff: SO IF RODNEY HAS
DIFFERENT MORAL, IT WOULD IMPLY
HE HAS NO MORALS.
>> NONE.
CORRECT.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, HAVE YOU SEEN
THAT SIDE OF RODNEY, AS WELL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, JUST HIS VOCABULARY,
IT'S VERY VULGAR, IT'S VERY
DEMEANING.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S DEMEANING?
>> THE WAY HE TALKS ABOUT WOMEN,
HOW HE TREATS WOMEN, I MEAN, IT
GOES ON AND ON.
I CAN SEE WHERE HE RUBS PEOPLE
WRONG, YOU KNOW?
>> Jeff: KELLY, WHAT'S YOUR
TAKE ON RODNEY?
>> AT FIRST I WAS A LITTLE UPSET
WITH RODNEY, BUT YOU HAVE TO
BITE YOUR TONGUE OUT HERE,
THAT'S WAY HE COMES OUT AND
WANTS TO PORTRAY HIMSELF, BUT I
DO GET FRUSTRATED, LIKE SHUT UP,
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR YOUR MOUTH.
>> BUT IF YOU GO BACK TO WHERE
I'M FROM, THE NUMBER-ONE LOVE OF
MY LIFE, I DON'T HAVE A
GIRLFRIEND, IT'S MY MOTHER.
MY MOTHER WILL TELL YOU I'M THE
BIGGEST SWEETHEART OUT THERE.
I'M JUST STATING FACTS OF HOW
WOMEN DISRESPECT THEMSELVES.
THAT'S THE TYPE OF STUFF I DEAL
WITH ALL THE TIME.
I'VE GOT BURNED BY WOMEN.
WOMEN SHOULD HOLD THEMSELVES TO
A HIGHER STANDARD AND RESPECT
THEMSELVES BECAUSE HE'S HOW MY
MOTHER DID IT AND NOWADAYS GIRLS
DON'T RESPECT THEMSELVES.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU ABLE TO
SEPARATE THEMSELVES AND SAY I
KNOW THAT COMMENT JUST OFFENDED
MILLIONS OF WOMEN?
>> WHAT?
THAT WOMEN SHOULD HOLD
THEMSELVES AT A HIGHER RESPECT?
>> Jeff: I GOT TO SAY, FOR
WHAT IT'S WORTH, IT'S ULTIMATELY
A SOCIAL GAME.
YOU ARE AWARE THAT YOU'RE
PLAYING WITH FIRE A LITTLE BIT
WITH THAT KIND OF ALTITUDE,
RIGHT?
>> I KNOW IT COMES FROM MY HEAD,
SO GUESS WHAT, I LOOK MY ENEMY
IN THE EYE AND I'LL ATTACK BACK.
>> Jeff: SO KELLY, YOU HAVE
LINDSEY AND SIERRA THAT ARE
PERCEIVED TO BE TIGHT, AND YOU
HAVE RODNEY WHO IS ALSO HIS OWN
LIGHTNING ROD.
THEN YOU AND DAN AND MIKE, YOU
HAVE TO DECIDE WHAT DO WE DO
TONIGHT THAT IS GOOD FOR US AS A
UNIT MOVING FORWARD IN THE GAME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LIKE SAYING WE VOTE FOR LINDSEY,
SIERRA IS HER BEST FRIEND, SO
YOU LOSE TWO PEOPLE.
WE VOTE FOR SIERRA, WE LOSE TWO
PEOPLE, IF WE VOTE FOR RODNEY
TONIGHT, WE GAIN TRUST FOR OUR
TRIBE.
>> BUT LOOK AT US, I LOVE THIS
I LOVE THIS TRIBE SINCE THE DAY
THAT WE STEPPED ON OUR MATT.
THIS TRIBE RIGHT HERE, WE WORK
FOR EACH OTHER, WE FIGHT FOR
EACH OTHER.
WE LOVE TOGETHER.
WE DO IT WITH DIRT ON OUR HAND,
WITH BLOOD ON OUR HAND, WITH
SWEAT ROLLING DOWN OUR FACE,
WITH TEARS IN OUR EYES, AND I'M
TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW, WHETHER
HE WALKS, I WALK, SHE WALKS, HE
WALKS, SOMEONE ON THIS TRIBE ON
THESE STOOLS RIGHT HERE IS GOING
TO WIN $1 MILLION.
BOTTOM LINE.
>> Jeff: MIKE, DOES IT MAKE
YOU SIT UP A LITTLE TALLER WHEN
YOU HEAR LINDSEY, BECAUSE THAT
SPEECH REALLY DOES ENCAPSULATE
ONE THING, WE ARE ALL BLUE
COLLAR, AND WE ALL KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS.
>>LY GIVE LINDSEY 100% CREDIT.
I THINK SHE UNIFIED US DAY ONE
WHEN SHE SAID THE WINNER OF THIS
GAME IS ON THIS TRIBE.
IT SPARKED BIG DREAMS IN ALL OF
OUR HEARTS, WHICH MADE US FIGHT
FOR EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW, I DO LOVE THESE
PEOPLE.
IF I WOULD HAVE BEEN ON THE
NO-COLLAR TRIBE, I PROBABLY
WOULD HAVE SLIT MY THROAT DAY
ONE, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HONEST TO GOODNESS.
AND THE WHITE-COLLAR TRIBE, THEY
JUST LIVE OFF OF THE HARD WORK
AND THE BACKS OF GOOD, SOLID,
BLUE-COLLAR AMERICANS.
BUT, YEAH, SO WE LOST A
CHALLENGE TODAY, ONE OF US IS
GOING HOME, SO I THINK WE FORMED
BONDS REGARDLESS.
FOR ME THAT'S MASSIVE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
SIERRA, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE RODNEY.
LINDSEY.
RODNEY.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES RODNEY,
TWO VOTES LINDSEY.
SIERRA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES, LINDSEY, TWO
VOTES RODNEY, ONE VOTE SIERRA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SIERRA.
WE HAVE A THREE-WAY TIE.
LINDSEY, RODNEY, SIERRA, YOU
WILL NOT VOTE.
MIKE, DAN, KELLY, YOU WILL VOTE,
AND YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR ONE OF
THOSE THREE.
MIKE, YOU'LL COME GET THE URN.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE LINDSEY.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT,
LINDSEY.
THAT'S TWO, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LINDSEY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, IT'S BEEN SAID MORE THAN
ONCE THAT THE WINNER OF THIS
GAME WILL COME FROM THIS TRIBE,
AND THAT WILL REQUIRE TRIBAL
UNITY.
WE'LL SEE IF VOTING OUT THE
PERSON WHO PREDICTED IT GIVES
YOU THAT UNITY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE A PERSONALITY
LIKE WHAT I HAVE, YOU ARE THE
EPITOME OF PLAY WITH FIRE, YOU
MIGHT GET BURNED.
SOMETIMES OTHER PEOPLE GET THE
BURN, SOMETIMES I GET THE BURN
MYSELF.
I'M WALKING OFF THIS ISLAND
BECAUSE I HURT A MAN'S EGO.
I'M NOT GOING TO APOLOGIZE, NOT
TO MYSELF, NOT TO ANYBODY ELSE,
NOT TODAY, NOT TOMORROW, NOT
EVER.
I WOULD STAND BY EVERY CHOICE
THAT I MADE AND I WOULD DO IT
AGAIN.
>> YOU VOTED FOR ME.
>> DOESN'T MATTER WHO IT WAS.
>> I MEAN, I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW.
>> THE REASON YOUR NAME GOT
WRITTEN DOWN IS BECAUSE IF THERE
WAS AN IDOL IN PLAY, IT WASN'T
GOING TO BE ONE OF THESE FOUR
THAT WENT HOME.
THAT'S NICE AND TO THE POINT AS
I CAN POSSIBLY BE.
TRIBAL WENT EXACTLY AS OUR
ALLIANCE PLANNED.
I'M 100% HAPPY WITH THE DECISION
WE MADE TONIGHT.
I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT SIERRA BEING
CUT OFF AND ALIENATED FROM THE
TRIBE.
>> SIERRA, WE DO WANT THERE TO
BE UNITY BACK IN THIS TRIBE
AGAIN, AND WE CAN'T DO THAT
UNLESS WE AIR THE GRIEVANCES,
GET 'EM OUT IN THE OPEN AND THEN
WE CAN BE DONE WITH THEM.
THE FIRST PUZZLE CHALLENGE, YOU
COULDN'T DO IT.
YOU STEPPED OUT.
THE SECOND CHALLENGE IN THE
WATER, YOU NEARLY KILLED MIKE
AND I BECAUSE YOU MISSED SO MANY
SHOTS.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT I DON'T
LIKE YOU.
WE ALL LOOK AT YOU AS AN ASSET.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO HEAR THAT
LITTLE BIT THAT I'M AN ASSET
WHEN YOU SAY REPEATEDLY
NUMBERING OUT THINGS I DID
WRONG.
NOT ONLY DID I JUST LOSE MY
CLOSEST ALLIANCE, BUT TO COME
BACK AND GET ATTACKED FOR THE
PLAYER THAT I AM, THAT'S TOUGH.
AT THIS POINT, I CAN'T TRUST
THESE PEOPLE.
I BUSTED MY ASS FOR YOU GUYS
AROUND CAMP, IN THE CHALLENGES.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME?
MY NAME GOT WRITTEN DOWN.
>> SOMEBODY'S GOING TO COME OUT
AND BLIND SIDE ME, I GOT NO
SORROW FOR TEARS COMING DOWN
YOUR EYE, NOT FROM A GUY LIKE ME
AND HOW I GREW UP.
SIERRA'S OUT THERE CRYING.
GUESS WHAT, I DON'T CARE.
YOU WROTE MY DOWN.
TIME FOR DO YOU GET OVER IT.
ONLY THE STRONG SURVIVOR.
IF YOU CAN'T DO THIS, TAKE YOUR
BAG, PACK 'EM AND TAKE YOUR ASS
HOME NOW.
>> WE CAN SIT HERE AND ALL JUMP
ON SIERRA OR START BUILDING A
BRIDGE RIGHT NOW AND MENDING
HURT AND WOUNDS TO WHENEVER WE
DO GET SPLIT UP, WE CAN COME
BACK AND WORK TOGETHER BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT THESE FIRST 11 DAYS
TO BE FOR NOTHING.
I WOULD LIKE NOTHING MORE TO
PULL SIERRA BACK IN, BUT I DON'T
THINK THAT SHE'LL EVER TRUST US.
>> I THOUGHT WE HAD SOMETHING.
>> WE STILL DO HAVE SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WHITE COLLAR, NO COLLAR GETTING
YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW BLUE
COLLAR TRIBE.
LINDSEY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU ARE ALSO GETTING YOUR LAST
LOOK AT THE BLUE COLLAR TRIBE AS
WELL AS WHITE COLLAR AND NO
COLLAR.
[APPLAUSE]
WE'RE SWITCHING THINGS UP.
>> THERE'S A SWITCH-UP, WHICH
I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT.
I'M GOING TO GO IN AND FIND NEW
ALLIANCES, BECAUSE MY TRIBE IS
ABSOLUTELY DEAD TO ME.
DEAD.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WHITE COLLAR, BLUE COLLAR, NO
COLLAR IS NO MORE.
FROM THIS POINT FORWARD THERE
WILL BE TWO TRIBES, THE BLUE
TRIBE, ESCAMECA, AND THE RED
TRIBE, NAGAROTE.
EVERYBODY WILL TAKE A BUFF.
DON'T OPEN IT YET.
WAIT FOR ME.
FATE.
RIGHT HERE.
ARE YOU GETTING RED?
ARE YOU GETTING BLUE?
WHO WILL BE ON YOUR TRIBE WITH
YOU?
ALL THESE QUESTIONS.
ABOUT TO BE ANSWERED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY OPEN UP.
IF YOU'RE BLUE, HEAD OVER TO THE
BLUE MATT.
YOU'RE A PART OF ESCAMECA.
>> YES!
>> IF YOU ARE RED, HEAD OVER TO
THE RED MAT, YOU ARE NAGAROTE.
>> I FEEL LIKE MY OLD TRIBE ARE
CRAPPY PEOPLE AND HAD TO PRETEND
I WAS EXCITED I WAS WITH THREE
OF THEM, BUT I HAVE THREE NEW
PEOPLE, AND I'M GOING TO FIND
NEW ALLIANCES.
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT BALLGAME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE HAVE, ALMOST
THE ENTIRE BLUE COLLAR TRIBE
STAYED TOGETHER, DAN, SIERRA,
MIKE AND RODNEY, AND THEY ARE
JOINED BY TWO WHITE COLLARS,
TYLER AND JOAQUIN, AND ONE NO
COLLAR, JOE.
PRETTY STRONG-LOOKING TRIBE.
NAGAROTE IN RED, THREE OF THE
FOUR NO COLLARS STAYED TOGETHER,
WILL, HALI AND JENN.
AND YOU ARE JOINED BY THREE
WHITE COLLARS, MAX, CAROLYN AND
SHIRIN AND ONE BLUE COLLAR,
KELLY.
>> NO WAY.
THIS CANNOT BE HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
I AM THE ONLY ONE FROM MY TRIBE
GOING OVER TO THE OTHER TRIBE.
WE JUST SPENT 11 DAYS BUILDING
THESE ALLIANCES AND NOW YOU'RE
STARTING OVER.
I AM DEFINITELY SCARED TO DEATH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY TO GET TO YOUR FIRST
REWARD CHALLENGE AS A NEW TRIBE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, PLAYERS FROM EACH
TRIBE WILL LAUNCH BALLS OUT ONTO
THE BEACH WHERE THEIR TRIBE
MATES WILL ATTEMPT TO CATCH
THEM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU CATCH A
RED BALL OR A BLUE BALL.
YOU CATCH A BALL, YOU SCORE A
POINT.
FIRST TO FIVE WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: KITCHEN SUPPLIES.
[APPLAUSE]
POTS, PAN, UTENSIL, OIL, SPICE,
AND WITH ALL THESE SUPPLY, YOU
NEED SOMETHING TO COOK, NICE
PLATE OF SAUSAGE.
A NICE WAY TO CELEBRATE YOUR
FIRST VICTORY AS A NEW TRIBE.
IN ADDITION, BECAUSE NOBODY IS
GOING BACK TO THE WHITE COLLAR
BEACH, ANY REWARD WON BY THE
WHITE COLLAR TRIBE IS ALSO PART
OF THIS REWARD TODAY.
IT WILL GIVE ONE TRIBE A MASSIVE
HEAD START.
SHALL WE GET TO IT?
TAKE A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND
WE'LL GET IT ON.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR MATCHUPS.
IT IS JENN UP AGAINST JOAQUIN,
MAX AGAINST JOE, MIKE SQUARING
OFF AGAINST WILL AND TYLER
TAKING ON KELLY.
LAUNCHING FOR ESCAMECA, OUT OF
THE GATE IT'S RODNEY.
FOR NAGAROTE IT IS SHIRIN.
PLAYING TO FIVE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
AND LAUNCH.
FIRST SCORE FOR NAGAROTE.
JOE SCORES FOR ESCAMECA.
WE ARE TIED OUT OF THE GATE,
1-1.
>> KEEP IT UP.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
SIERRA IS LAUNCHING AND CAROLYN
LAUNCHING.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
SIERRA IN THE AIR.
>> YOU GOT IT, JOE.
>> Jeff: JOE SCOOPS ONE UP FOR
ESCAMECA.
CAROLYN IN THE AIR.
TYLER SCOOPS ONE UP FOR
ESCAMECA.
TWO POINTS FOR ESCAMECA IN THAT
ROUND.
IT IS 3-1.
WE'RE PLAYING TO 5.
DAN NOW FIRING FOR ESCAMECA.
HALI IN FOR NAGAROTE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
LAUNCH.
DAN IN THE AIR.
>> GOT IT.
>> I GOT YOU, BABY.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN WITH A NICE
SCORE FOR ESCAMECA.
>> RIGHT AT YOU!
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: JOE JUST MISSES FOR
THE WIN.
>> ONE MORE, ONE MORE, ONE MORE.
ONE MORE.
>> Jeff: ESCAMECA DOMINATING
THIS CHALLENGE.
IT IS NOW SIERRA AND SHIRIN.
ESCAMECA ONE POINT AWAY FROM A
BIG REWARD.
NAGAROTE TRYING TO PLAY DEFENSE
OUT THERE AND MAKE SURE NOBODY
ON THE BLUE SIDE SCORES.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
LAUNCH.
BOTH BALLS IN THE AIR.
WILL SCORES, BUT IT WILL NOT
MATTER, MIKE SCORES FOR
ESCAMECA.
ESCAMECA WINS FIRST REWARD AS
THEIR NEW TRIBE.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ESCAMECA,
NICE REWARD.
COME GET IT.
ENJOY YOUR AFTERNOON.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL OF THE REWARD
FROM THE WHITE COLLAR BEACH WILL
BE WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
ALL RIGHT.
NAGAROTE, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> WHEN WE GOT THE WORD WE WERE
SWITCHING TEAMS, I WAS SO
EXCITED, AND I OPENED IT UP, AND
I'M WITH MAX AND SHIRIN.
WHAT, ARE THE SURVIVOR GODS
TRYING TO KILL ME?
>> GREAT JOB, GUYS.
[ALL SPEAKING AT ONCE]
>> SO WE'VE GOT THREE NO
COLLARS, THREE WHITE COLLARS AND
ONE BLUE COLLAR, KELLY.
SO IMMEDIATELY I'M LIKE, WE GOT
TO GET KELLY ON OUR SIDE, BUT I
WANTED THINGS TO BE SLOW AND
FEEL PEOPLE OUT, BECAUSE OUR
CAMP IS SO LAID BACK, OUR NO
COLLAR CAMP, WE CAN SIT BACK AND
WATCH, AND OUR PLAN JUST COMES
TO US.
>> JUST F.Y.I., WE USUALLY DO
BEANS IN THE MORNING AND RICE AT
NIGHT.
>> SHIRIN IS AN AMAZING SURVIVOR
COACH.
>> WELCOME TO THE KITCHEN.
>> THERE ARE TWO THINGS WE DO
WITH THE COCONUT, I DON'T KNOW
HOW BIG OF FANS YOU RUSSIA BUT
THAT'S HELPED ME BE A COOK.
>> I KNOW THIS GAME REALLY WELL,
NOT JUST HISTORICAL FACTS BUT
STRATEGY.
WE HAVE THREE NO COLLAR, THREE
WHITE COLLAR AND ONE BLUE
COLLAR.
I'M IN ONE OF THE POWER TRIOS,
SO THE SIMPLEST ROUTE IS TO
STICK WITH WHITE COLLAR AND PULL
OVER THE BLUE COLLAR.
>> I KEEP SAYING IT, BUT I'M SO
GLAD THAT YOU'RE HERE, HALI,
CAROLYN.
>> STILL ON YOUR TRIBE.
>> THEY WERE LIKE THE ONLY COOL
PEOPLE ON MY TRIBE.
>> I AM AN UNDERCOVER COP.
THIS IS LIKE GOING INTO A HOUSE
THE BUY DRUGS FROM PEOPLE YOU
TOTALLY DON'T EVEN KNOW.
YOU HAVE TO START TALKING.
YOU HAVE TO BUILD THEIR TRUST.
YOU DON'T HAVE TIME TO WAIT
BECAUSE YOUR LIFE DEPENDS ON IT,
BUT THIS ISN'T AS BAD AS I
THOUGHT.
MAYBE I'M IN A GOOD POSITION
BECAUSE I'M THE SWING VOTE.
>> YOU AND MAX, I JUST FELT,
YEAH, THIS IS AWESOME.
AND CAROLYN, TOO.
>> WE WANT THE PLAY WITH YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'M DEFINITELY IN.
>> I TALKED TO KELLY, THREW HER
A LITTLE BAIT.
SHE BIT AND THEN WE JUST
SOLIDIFIED SOMETHING.
IT WAS VERY WINK, WINK, HUSH,
HUSH, WE'LL TALK MORE LATER, BUT
YES.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WELCOME
TO CAMP ESCAMECA.
>> THIS LOOKS LIKE THE
RITZ-CARLTON COMPARED TO WHERE
WE WERE.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> OH, YEAH.
THE NEW ESSEC BASICALLY FOUR
BLUE COLLARS.
>> JOAQUIN, NICE THE MEET OWE,
BRO.
>> TWO WHITE COLLAR AND ONE NO
COLLAR.
>> WE'VE GOT THE MAJORITY, SO
THE NUMBERS COULDN'T HAVE WORKED
OUT BETTER IN OUR FAVOR.
>> NO IDEA AFTER LAST NIGHT'S
VOTE, BUT WITH DAN AND RODNEY
CUTTING INTO SIERRA LAST NIGHT,
IT DEFINITELY CAUSES CONCERN.
THESE THREE GUYS COULD WOO
SIERRA OVER.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE SURE
SHE DOESN'T GET TOO CLOSE TO
SOMEBODY AND GET SWAYED OVER TO
THE OTHER SIDE.
>> MY MOTHER IS 64, BUT IF YOU
SEE HER, YOU'D MAYBE HIT ON HER.
THAT'S HOW GOOD SHE LOOKS.
SHE LOOKS YOUNG.
>> ROB, WHAT ARE THE TATTOOS?
>> THIS ONE SAYS, EVEN THOUGH
I'LL NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN, YOU'LL
ALWAYS BE MY BIG SISTER.
TWO YEARS AGO I CAME HOME AND
FOUND MY SISTER DEAD.
IT WAS CRAZY, PROBABLY THE WORST
THING THAT EVER HAPPENED IN MY
LIFE.
>> RODNEY'S GONE THROUGH A LOT
OF STRUGGLES, BUT MIND'S
STRAIGHT.
LIKE A BUNCH OF MY FRIENDS BACK
HOME, I'LL FEEL HIM OUT, TRY
LEARN AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE AND
WORK THEM LIKE I'VE BEEN WORKING
EVERYBODY ON MY LAST TRIBE.
>> SOMEBODY WANT TO GO WITH ME
TO GRAB WATER?
>> YEP.
>> ARE ALL MY TRIBE MATES GONE?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SO GRATEFUL YOU GUYS ARE
HERE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
LIKE THE SECOND I THREW MY BUFF
ON THE GROUND, I WAS SO EXCITED
TO GET AWAY FROM THOSE PEOPLE
AND I HAPPEN TO GET STUCK WITH
THREE OF THEM AGAIN.
>> GLORY, GLORY, I'M LATCHING ON
THE ANYTHING I CAN GRAB ON TO
BECAUSE THESE PEOPLE SUCK AND
TREAT ME LIKE DIRT.
>> SIERRA SEEMS TO BE KIND OF
THE BROKEN PUPPY.
THESE THINGS ARE GOOD.
AS I'VE ALWAYS SAID, BRING ME
YOUR POOR, YOUR TIRED, YOUR
HUDDLED SURVIVORS.
LIKE I WANT THE BROKEN PEOPLE TO
COME WITH ME AND BE ON MY TRIBE.
>> THOSE PEOPLE WERE SO MEAN TO
ME.
>> I MARTIN SEEMUNGAL TALKING
WITH THE THREE GUYS, WHICH MAKES
ME A LITTLE NERVOUS BECAUSE IF
JOE, JOAQUIN AND TYLER CAN GET
SIERRA, THEN IT'S ME AND DAN AND
ROD NISM WE NEED HER AS A
NUMBER.
IN THIS GAME OF SURVIVOR, IF YOU
DO NOT HAVE THE NUMBERS, YOU GO
HOME.
O SAY CAN YOU SEE
WHAT SO PROUDLY WE HAILED
>> THE CHICK WITH THE LONG HAIR,
I DON'T KNOW HER NAME, BUT I
DON'T LIKE HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T LIKE HER.
MAYBE IT'S HER VOICE.
>> I'M A PROFESSIONAL WHISTLER.
[WHISTLING]
>> I HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN AROUND
HER FOR 12 HOURS AND I KNOW MOST
OF HER LIFE AND I KNOW THINGS
THAT I NEVER WANTED TO KNOW.
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO GO TRY
THE POOP.
IF I DON'T TRY, IT WILL NEVER
HAPPEN, RIGHT?
>> SHE HASN'T STOPPED TALKING
SINCE WE GOT HERE.
IT'S DRIVING ME INSANE.
LIKE JUST SHUT UP, MAN.
LIKE JUST SIT.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BRO?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I GOT A STINGRAY.
>> GET SOME WATER.
>> I TODAY WAS STUNG BY A STING
WAY, NOT ONCE, BUT TWICE.
SO I HOBBLED IN OFF THE BEACH,
I'VE GOT BLOOD POWRLG OUT OF MY
FEET.
>> YOU GOT TO STICK THAT IN WARM
WATER.
IT'S A LITTLE HOT.
>> FORTUNATELY FOR ME, WE HAVE A
FORMER LIFEGUARD ON THE TRIBE,
JENN IMMEDIATELY SPRUNG INTO
ACTION.
SHE TOOK A POT OF BOILING WATER
THAT WAS MEANT FOR DRINKING,
PULLED IT FROM THE FIRE AND
SAID, PUT YOUR FEET IN THERE AND
DON'T TAKE THEM OUT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED TO BE ABLE TO
SWIM.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YEAH.
>> "SURVIVOR" IS NO JOKE.
SITTING THERE WITH MY FEET IN
SCALDING WATER, I SUDDENLY
FORGOT I HAD THAT ROBBING ANIMAL
INFLICTED WOUNDS BECAUSE MY FEET
WERE ON FIRE FROM THE BOILING
WATER THEY WERE SITTING IN.
>> WHAT'S ON THE BOSTON UM OF
YOUR FOOT?
IS THAT A PLANTAR'S...
>> YES.
>> SO MAX STICKS BOTH OF HIS
FEET IN OUR DRINKING WATER POT.
IT'S BEEN LIKE AN HOUR THEY'RE
SOAKING.
THEN HE LIFTS HIS FOOT UP.
HE HAS A PLANTAR'S WART THE SIDE
OF A QUARTER IN OUR DRINKING
WATER.
I'M LIKE, MAX, WARTS ARE
CONTAGIOUS, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> WE HAVE TO BOIL MORE WATER.
>> ANYONE WHO WOULD STICK THEIR
WARTY FEET IN THE TRIBE'S
DRINKING WATER FOR HOURS WHEN
WE'RE THIRSTY HAS HIS MIND ON
ONE PERSON, HIMSELF, AND HIS
STINGRAY FEET.
IT WAS DISGUSTING.
>> HE'S BEEN ON MY NERVES.
>> MAX AND SHIRIN ARE SO
ANNOYING.
AND THEY MAY THINK IT'S 3-3, NO
COLLAR AGAINST WHITE COLLAR, NOT
HAPPENING.
SO I'M THINKING, ALL RIGHT,
CAROLYN, PATIENCE IS A VIRTUE,
DON'T GO CRAZY, BUT TO BLINDSIDE
THEM WOULD BE SO SWEET.
YOU JUST CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
>> WHAT I'M WORRIED RIGHT NOW IS
SIERRA IS NOW A SWING VOTE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I TRIED TO TELL
YOU GUYS.
LAW OFF OF HER A LITTLE BIT, BUT
YOU AND RODNEY HAD TO JUST DIG
INTO HER INSTEAD OF TAKING THE
OPPORTUNITY OF REELING HER BACK
IN, YOU ALREADY HAD IT SET IN
YOUR MIND THAT SHE WAS GONE.
>> WE HAD TO HAVE SIERRA'S VOTE,
RIGHT OR WRONG?
>> WE HAVE TO HAVE SIERRA'S
LOYALTY.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE HER LOYALTY,
YOU DON'T HAVE HER VOTE.
>> DAN, JUST LISTEN TO WHAT I'M
TELLING YOU.
SHUT YOUR MOUTH, APOLOGIZE AND
LET'S MOVE FORWARD.
>> TIME TO PLAY NICE, DAN.
>> OKAY.
I'LL TAKE SIERRA OFF, ASK HER IF
SHE'S WILLING TO GO FOR A WALK
WITH ME AND SAY, LISTEN, I WAS
UPSET AND I'M SORRY.
I DID NOT TRY TO TELL YOU THAT I
DIDN'T THINK YOU PULLED YOUR
WEIGHT.
>> DON'T EVEN DO NONE OF THAT.
>> I'M SORRY.
I JUST WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
>> THE ONLY THING SHE WOULD LOVE
TO HEAR IN MY PERSONAL
EXPERIENCE WITH WOMEN, THEY
DON'T WANT THE EXPLANATION, THEY
JUST WANT TO HEAR YOU SAY
THEY'RE SORRY SO THEY CAN BE
RIGHT.
>> DUDE, YOU'RE HALF MY AGE.
OKAY.
I HAVE TALKED TO SO MANY MORE
GIRLS THAN YOU HAVE, IT'S SILLY.
DUDE, DUDE, I GOT SIERRA.
I GOT THIS.
>> CAN WE PLEASE TALK IT OUT?
>> BUT, OF COURSE, I COME BACK
AND HAVE TO SIT AT THE FIRE AND
GET ATTACKED.
YOU JUST PICKED THE WRONG TIME.
>> I DON'T DISAGREE, AND I OWN,
THAT BUT WHAT HURT ME WAS YOU
ATTACKED ME, AND THAT WAS OKAY.
>> NO.
>> BUT WHEN I GAVE IT BACK TO
YOU, IT'S NOT.
>> IT WAS THE WRONG PLACE AND
THE WRONG TIME.
>> I'M SEEING WHAT WE DID,
ABSOLUTELY, EXACTLY THE SAME
THINGS, BUT FOR SOME REASON YOU
TAKE YOURS AS MORE OF A SLIGHT
THAN MINE, AND I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY.
>> IT'S NOT THE SAME.
YOU COME BACK FROM TRIBAL AND
YOUR NAME HAS BEEN WRITTEN DOWN
TWICE.
>> I'M ALL EXCITED TO GO INTO A
CHALLENGE TO HELP.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO GET
ANYWHERE.
IF YOU'RE SORRY, YOU DON'T GO
INTO AN APOLOGY SAYING, I'M
SORRY THAT I MADE YOU FEEL THAT
WAY, BUT YOU DID IT TO ME,
THAT'S WHY.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO BELITTLE
IT, BUT WE BOTH SAID SOME PRETTY
NOT NICE THINGS TO EACH OTHER.
>> IT WAS THE CRAPPIEST APOLOGY
I'VE EVER RECEIVED ON MY LIFE.
>> WE CAN TURN ON EACH OTHER OR
LOOK EACH OTHER IN THE EYE.
>> CAN WE JUST KEEP WALKING.
>> I HAVE TWO SEPARATE ALLIANCES
COMING AT ME SAYING, WE NEED YOU
AS OUR FOURTH.
I WANT TO GO WHERE I'M WANTED,
AND I DON'T THINK THAT'S WITH
THE BLUE COLLARS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
LET'S TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
BOTH PIECES.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, TWO
MEMBERS FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
PLACE POTS ON A SLED AND DRAG IT
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
ONCE YOU REACH THE FINISH,
REPLACE THE POTS ON STANDS AND
HEAD BACK.
ONCE ALL OF THE POTS ARE IN
PLACE, ONE TRIBE MEMBER WILL USE
A WRECKING BALL TO SMASH THE
POTS.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE
AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS JOAQUIN AND TYLER, AND
JENN AND HALI.
>> PULL, PUSH, PULL, PUSH.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN AND TYLER
OUT.
JENN AND HALI DOING A GOOD JOB.
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE A LOT OF
PHYSICAL EFFORT.
ESCAMECA IS GOING TO HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE SIMPLY BECAUSE THEY
HAVE A LOT OF MEN, A LOT MORE
STRENGTH.
JENN AND HALI ARE DIGGING IN.
>> WILL LET'S GO, GIRLS.
>> LET'S GO, LADIES.
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN AND TYLER OUT
THE AN EARLY LEAD, BUT IT IS NOT
OVER UNTIL ALL THE POTS ARE
THERE AND BROKEN.
JENN AND HALI MADE UP SOME TIME.
GET THEM ON THE STANDS.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN AND TYLER
HEADING BACK.
THERE YOU GO.
HALI AND JENN RACING BACK.
GO BACK THROUGH THE OBSTACLE
COURSE BEFORE THE NEXT PAIR CAN
GO.
JOAQUIN AND TYLER ARE BACK.
JOE AND RODNEY ARE NOW OUT.
THEY'RE MOVING QUICKLY.
HALI AND JENN REALLY SLOWING
DOWN ON THE WAY BACK, SHOWING
YOU HOW MUCH EFFORT IT TAKES TO
DRAG THIS SLED THROUGH THE MUD.
NOW CAROLYN AND KELLY GOING TO
HAVE TO DO A BIG JOB TO CATCH UP
TO JOE AND RODNEY, TWO VERY FIT
GUYS.
CAROLYN AND KELLY DIGGING, NOT
QUITTING.
YOU CAN SEE JUST BY THE AMOUNT
OF EFFORT HOW TOUGH IT IS IN
THIS HEAVY MUD.
JOE AND RODNEY HAVE THEIR SLEDS.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
KELLY AND CAROLYN STILL FIGHTING
TO STAY IN THIS.
HERE COMES SIERRA AND MIKE NOW
FOR ESCAMECA, TURNING INTO A
BLOWOUT RIGHT NOW.
KELLY AND CAROLYN WITH THEIR
NEXT TWO POTS.
PLACE THEM AND HEAD BACK.
HERE COMES MIKE AND SIERRA WITH
THE FINAL TWO POTS FOR ESCAMECA.
>> PULL THE SLED, BOTH OF YOU.
>> Jeff: NAGAROTE HAS A LOT OF
TIME TO MAKE UP.
>> BOTH PULL.
>> Jeff: BOTH WOMEN EXHAUSTED.
SIERRA AND MIKE HAVE PLACED
THEIR LOSS LAST TWO POTS.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK NOW FOR
ESCAMECA.
>> COME ON, LADIES.
>> Jeff: MIKE AND SIERRA ARE
ABOUT TO LAP CAROLYN AND KELLY,
PUTTING AN EXCLAMATION POINT ON
THE UNEVEN TRIBE.
NOW EVERYBODY FROM ESCAMECA
HEADS BACK.
>> COME ON.
PUSH, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ESCAMECA HAS ALL SIX
OF THEIR POTS.
THEY'RE ALL HEADING BACK, WHILE
SHIRIN AND MAX, THE FINAL PAIR
FOR NAGAROTE, VERY FAR BEHIND
RIGHT NOW.
>> GO, DAN.
HERE'S YOUR TIME TO SHINE.
>> Jeff: DAN GOING TO BE ON
THE WRECKING BALL FIRST FOR
ESCAMECA.
HERE COMES SHIRIN AND MAX.
THEY HAVE SOME NICE MOMENTUM.
THEY'RE PICKING UP SOME TIME.
WILL IT BE ENOUGH?
DAN SMASHES THE FIRST POT FOR
ESCAMECA.
NAGAROTE, YOU GOT TO MOVE!
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: DAN SMASHES A SECOND
POT.
DAN SMASHES A THIRD POT.
>> GOOD JOB, DAN.
>> Jeff: SHIRIN AND MAX
HEADING BACK.
THEY GOT TO GET ALL THE WAY
BACK.
>> HARD, DANNY, HARD!
>> Jeff: DAN SMASHES A FOURTH.
HE'S GOT FOUR LEFT.
>> HARD, BROTHER, HARD.
>> Jeff: THERE'S FIVE AND
NUMBER SIX.
DAN IS A HUMAN WRECKING BALL.
THERE GOES NUMBER SEVEN.
HE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
HERE COMES NAGAROTE.
IT MAY NOT EVEN MATTER.
DAN HAS ONE POT LEFT.
THIS COULD BE IT RIGHT HERE.
>> BANG.
>> Jeff: AND IT IS.
ESCAMECA WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WELL, ESCAMECA, THAT WASN'T EVEN
CLOSE, A BLOWOUT.
IMMUNITY FOR ESCAMECA.
>> I'LL HAPPILY TAKE IT.
THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: NOBODY GOING HOME FOR
ESCAMECA.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
NAGAROTE, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> THE HARDEST THING ABOUT THAT
CHALLENGE FOR ME WAS NOT SMILING
TOO BIG AFTER WE LOST IT.
I'M REALLY HAPPY TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AND CHANGE THE DYNAMIC
AROUND MY CAMP.
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING WE COULD HAVE DONE WITH
THAT ONE.
>> I THINK WE DID WHAT WE COULD.
WE PLAYED VALIANTLY, TRIED AS
HARD AS WE COULD UNTIL THE LAST
MINUTE.
NEVER GIVE UP.
>> I'M VERY EXCITED TO GET ON
WITH THE GAME "SURVIVOR."
THE BLIND SIDES, THE DOUBLE
CROSSING, THAT'S REALLY WHAT I
SIGNED ON FOR.
AND FINALLY I'M GOING TO HAVE
ANOTHER CHANCE TO GET TO DO IT
TONIGHT.
>> BEFORE WE LEFT I WENT THROUGH
ALL OF THE "SURVIVOR" WINNERS, I
THINK CAPRICORNS WON "SURVIVOR"
THE MOST.
>> REALLY?
>> THEN AFTER THIS THERE WERE A
COUPLE LEOS.
>> COOL.
THANKS.
BYE.
I'VE SEEN EVERY SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
I'M A HUGE FAN OF THE GAME, BUT
MAX KNOWS EVERY LITTLE DETAIL
ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT'S EVER
HAPPENED ON "SURVIVOR."
IT'S CRAZY.
LIKE WHY DO YOU KNOW THIS MUCH?
WHY DO YOU REMEMBER LIKE
LITTLE... IT'S LIKE PEOPLE THAT
REMEMBER LIKE THE '96 BULLS GAME
AGAINST THE HEAT ON LIKE OCTOBER
13th OR WHENEVER BASKETBALL
HAPPENS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING FOR
TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT I LIKE MAX
OR SHIRIN.
I DON'T KNOW IF THE THREE YELLOW
WILL STAY TOGETHER AND WE NEED
TO GRAB KELLY OR WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO RIGHT NOW.
>> I MEAN, I LIKE KELLY.
>> I LIKE KELLY, TOO.
IT'S JUST MATTER OF IF SHE WANTS
TO GO WITH US.
>> WILL'S GOING TO STAY WITH US?
>> OBVIOUSLY.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
WE NEED TO START THINKING ABOUT
WHAT WE WANT TO DO.
>> TRIBAL TONIGHT, IT WILL COME
DOWN TO KELLY BECAUSE SHE'S A
SWING VOTE.
BETWEEN NO COLLAR AND WHITE
COLLAR.
SO KELLY BEING THE SWING VOTE IS
IN THE POWER POSITION.
WHAT IF WE JUST GET A MAJORITY
APART FROM THEM TWO, VOTE OFF
SHIRIN AND THEN TAKE MAX IN
BECAUSE WE NEED HIM FOR
CHALLENGES?
>> I LIKE THAT.
I LIKE THAT.
>> OKAY.
SO FROM MY POINT OF VIEW,
THERE'S IN WAY WE'RE GOING TO
WIN ANY CHALLENGES BETWEEN NOW
AND THE MERGE.
>> THE ONLY THING IS THIS, I
THINK WE NEED TO BLIND SIDE...
>> WE CAME INTO THE MIX UP WITH
A CLASSIC "SURVIVOR" SPLIT.
THREE NO COLLARS, THREE WHITE
COLLARS AND KELLY FROM THE BLUE
COLLAR TRIBE IN THE MIDDLE.
WHITE COLLAR WAS MOST AGGRESSIVE
ABOUT PURSUING KELLY AT THAT
CRUCIAL SWING VOTE.
SHIRIN WAS DOING A LOT OF HARD
WORK UP FRONT.
AND I FEEL PRETTY CONFIDENT THAT
WE'RE ABLE TO SECURE HER.
>> OKAY.
YOU GOT IT.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, WE'VE
GOT ALL THE BRAINS OVER HERE,
WE'VE GOT SKINNY GIRLS WHICH ARE
GREAT FOR SO MANY CHALLENGES.
WE'VE GOT GREAT SWIMMERS OVER
HERE.
WILL CAN'T DO ANY OF THOSE
THINGS.
AND I THINK WITHOUT HIM, WE
ACTUALLY HAVE A REALLY STRONG
CHANCE OF WINNING.
>> BY THE WAY, JUST BRILLIANT,
THAT'S ALL I WANTED TO SAY TO
YOU.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE I'M IN THE
POWER SEAT TONIGHT.
I'M PRETTY SURE I'M THE ONE THAT
ORCHESTRATED EVERYTHING THAT IS
GOING DOWN.
I'M THE ONE WHO DECIDED IT'S
GOING TO BE WILL.
DOES IT IMPACT ME ALL THAT MUCH?
NOT REALLY.
>> KELLY WAS THERE AMPS WE
HASHED IT OUT WITH HER.
>> WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> GET RID OF HER?
>> ON PAPER KELLY LOOKS LIKE THE
SWING VOTE, AND MAX AND SHIRIN
THINK I'M 100% IN WITH THEM, BUT
I'M A SWING VOTE.
I CAN TAKE THAT POWER AWAY FROM
KELLY AND BE FOUR STRONG WITH
THE NO COLLARS AND WE'RE GOOD TO
GO.
SO I THINK A FABULOUS BLIND SIDE
MAY BE IN THE MAKING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
ANYTHING?
>> I'M KIND OF OBVIOUSLY NOT
LIKE MY PEOPLE.
BUT WE'VE GOT US THREE AND
THREE.
KELLY'S THE ONE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW CLOSE YOU ARE
WITH THEM.
>> I'M IN THE A PART OF THAT
THREE.
>> I WILL TELL YOU, THEY TELL
YOU I'M PART OF THE THREE.
IF YOU GUYS ARE IN, I'M 150% NOT
EVEN WITH THEM.
>> THAT MAKES OUR LIFE SO MUCH
EASIER.
>> I'M EXCITED BECAUSE IT SOUNDS
LIKE EVERYONE HATES MOST OF THE
WHITE COLLARS.
NO ONE CAN STAND MAX.
NO ONE CAN STAND SHIRIN.
AND WE HAVE CAROLYN.
SO WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
WE'LL CONTROL THE GAME.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE WITH US.
>> SO GOOD TO KNOW.
>> CAROLYN, SHE SAID GREAT.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO AVOID
ANY SORT OF POTENTIAL UNEXPECTED
EVENTS TONIGHT.
>> WHY DID THEY LET US KNOW THEY
KNOW THAT MUCH ABOUT "SURVIVOR,"
MAX AND SHIRIN?
I DON'T THINK SHE'S STOPPED
TALKING SINCE WE GOT HERE.
>> SHE WILL NEVER VOTE OUT MAX.
THEY'RE LIKE THIS.
>> SO DO YOU FEEL TOTALLY ON THE
OUTS WITH THEM?
>> TOTALLY.
THEY'RE SCHEMING.
>> I SAY GET RID OF THEM TWO.
>> THE NO-COLLAR TRIBE, THEY'RE
TIGHT.
CAROLYN'S IN THE TIGHT WITH WITH
THE WHITE COLLAR.
SO IT WOULDN'T BENEFIT ME TO
STAY WITH SHIRIN AND MAX.
>> LET'S DECIDE WHO WE'RE GOING
TO GO FOR RIGHT NOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH WE NEED
MAX IN CHALLENGES.
BUT SHIRIN TALKS SO MUCH.
>> THE DEBATE TONIGHT IS BETWEEN
MAX AND SHIRIN, WHO IS THE MOST
ANNOYING.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT NECK AND
NECK, BECAUSE NEITHER ONE OF
THEM WILL SHUT UP AND THEY WON'T
STOP STRATEGIZING.
THEY WILL JUST GO OFF BY THE
FIRE AND LEAVE US AND JUST
STRATEGIZE, STRATEGIZE,
STRATEGIZE.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW WHETHER
THEY COULD BE OVER THERE
SCHEMING ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> IT'S LIKE WHO IS MORE
ANNOYING.
I CAN'T DECIDE.
WHO IS MORE ANNOYING?
MAX OR SHIRIN?
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE A HORSE RACE?
NO, HERE COMES MAX WITH HIS FOOT
WART.
NO, HERE'S SHIRIN.
NO, HERE'S MAX AGAIN, WHO'S
GOING TO GET VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
WHO'S MOST ANNOYING?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL SEE.
WE'LL FIND OUT TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
SO AFTER THE SWITCH WE END UP
WITH THREE WHITE COLLARS, THREE
NO COLLARS AND KELLY FROM THE
BLUE COLLAR TRIBE.
SHIRIN, WHAT DID YOU NOTICE WHEN
ALL SEVEN PEOPLE GOT TOGETHER?
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, IT FELT
LIKE A BRAND-NEW HOME TO ME.
WE ALL GELLED REALLY QUICKLY IN
A WAY THAT WHITE COLLAR NEVER
DID, AND... YOU'RE MAKING A
FACE.
>> Jeff: I AM?
>> YES.
LIKE I'M DELUSIONAL.
NO.
OKAY.
SORRY.
>> Jeff: HOLD ON.
LET ME CHECK MYSELF, BECAUSE
MAYBE THE BOTOX ISN'T WORKING.
IT SEEMS WEIRD THAT I WOULD MAKE
A REACTION TO YOU SAYING IT
FEELS LIKE A NEW HOME.
THAT SEEMS LIKE AN ORDINARY
COMMENT TO MAKE.
>> YOU JUST LOOK REALLY INTENSE.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S JUST ME.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: KELLY, DID YOU FEEL
THE SAME UNITY EVEN THOUGH
YOU'RE FROM THREE DIFFERENT
TRIBES?
>> THERE'S BEEN A FEW THINGS
THAT HAVE GONE DOWN AT THE TRIBE
THAT HAVE BEEN A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> Jeff: LIKE WHAT?
>> UM...
>> Jeff: WHY IS THAT FUNNY?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE HITTING AT
SOMETHING THAT'S EMERGING FROM
THE UNIQUE SITUATION WE FIND
OURSELVES IN, THAT ON PAPERER
THIS TRIBE IS A DISASTER.
IT'S LIKE THE SWAMP FOR
"SURVIVOR" ONE WORLD.
YOU HAD ONE TIME THAT SEEMED TO
GET EVERY TALL, ATHLETIC FIT
PERSON, AND THE OTHER ENDED UP
WITH COLTON AND TARZAN AND THEY
SELF-IDENTIFIED AS MISFITS.
IF WE'RE GIVING YOU AN
INAUTHENTIC COUPLE BUY YAW,
WE'RE TRYING THE TRICK OURSELVES
INTO THINKING WE HAVE CHANCE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: WHY ARE YOU LAUGH,
JENN?
>> I'M LAUGHING AT HIS KNOWLEDGE
FROM EVERY SINGLE SEASON.
I'M LIKE, HOW DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT?
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
WHY DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> I HAVE A HARD TIME
REMEMBERING EVERYONE'S HERE
NAME.
>> GUILTY AS CHARGED.
I KNOW IT'S NOT NECESSARILY
HEALTHY.
THERE'S SOMETHING IN MY D.N.A.
I DON'T KNOW MY MOM'S CELL PHONE
NUMBER, BUT I DO KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED AT THE SWAP IN "ONE
WORLD."
THAT'S WHAT SPEED DIAL IS FOR,
RIGHT?
>> Jeff: SHIRIN, YOU WEAR THIS
LOVE OF THE GAME AS A BADGE OF
HONOR, NOT SOMETHING TO BE
EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
>> YEAH, "SURVIVOR" HAS ALWAYS
BEEN MY LIFE DREAM, SO I HAVE A
LOT OF RESPECT FOR THIS GAME AND
I'M SOUPING EVERYBODY PREACH
YAILTS MY SUPER FANDOM, BUT I
THINK EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT I'M A
LITTLE BIT OF AN OVERTHINKING
OBSESSIVE TYPE.
>> Jeff: MAX, CAN YOU RELATE
TO THAT?
>> CERTAINLY.
LISTEN, I KNOW IT'S NOT
NECESSARILY HEALTHY.
I KNOW IT'S THE SORT OF THING
THAT LANDS A LOT OF TYPE A
PERSONALITIES IN THE HOSPITAL
WITH A CORONARY AT AGE 47, AND I
CERTAINLY HOPE THAT THROUGH MY
MANDATORY RELAXATION I CAN AVOID
THAT SORT OF FATE.
>> Jeff: WAIT.
MANDATORY RELAXATION?
>> I HAVE TO MAKE MYSELF RELAX
OR ELSE I JUST WON'T.
>> Jeff: WILL, DO YOU PICK UP
ON THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND THAT FRUSTRATES ME IN THE
CAMP.
YOU GOT SHIRIN AND MAX GOING OFF
TO THE FIRE AND JUST TALK,
JUST... I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
STRATEGIZING.
THEY DO THAT CONSTANTLY EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
>> Jeff: HALI, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE VOTE, BECAUSE YOU
CAN'T CHANGE THE FACT THAT
YOU'RE OUTMATCHED PHYSICALLY BY
THE OTHER TRIBE.
SO WHAT DO YOU BASE THE VOTE ON?
>> THERE ARE STRATEGIC VOTES
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
THERE'S LOYALTY VOTES THAT COULD
HAPPEN.
AND THERE'S QUALITY OF LIFE
VOTES THAT COULD HAPPEN.
AND AFTER TONIGHT'S VOTE, I
THINK THAT IT WILL BE A MUCH
MORE PLEASANT CAMP LIFE FOR ALL
OF US.
>> Jeff: WILL, DO YOU THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE A BLIND SIDE
TONIGHT?
>> UM, YEAH.
I DO.
>> Jeff: SHIRIN, FEEL RIGHT TO
YOU THAT IT'S GOING TO BE A
BLIND SIDE, AS WELL?
>> YEAH, I DO THINK IT'S A BLIND
SIDE.
COULD BE ME AND THEN IT'S
DEFINITELY A BLIND SIDE, BUT,
YEAH, I THINK THERE ARE SOME
ADVANTAGES TO A BLIND SIDE THAT
HELP KEEP TEAM UNITY.
TYPICALLY YOU'RE BLIND SIDING
SOMEBODY BECAUSE THERE IS SOME
UNPLEASANTNESS OR SOMEONE IS NOT
FITTING IN, SO A BLIND SIDE IS A
WAY OF PUTTING AN END TO THAT
AND MOVING ON.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MAX, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> HEY, JEFF, HOLD UP, BRO.
I JUST ALWAYS WANTED TO SAY
THAT.
>> Bianca: OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, WILL.
WILL.
TWO VOTES WILL.
MAX.
TWO VOTES WILL, TWO VOTES MAX.
THAT'S THREE VOTES MAX, TWO
VOTES WILL.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT, MAX.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
MAX, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, IF BLIND SIDES DO INDEED
BRING MORE TRIBAL UNITY, THEN
YOU GUYS SHOULD BE ONE VERY
TIGHT GROUP.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning sponsored by
Survivor Productions, CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> I LIKE APPLES AND ON,
BROTHER.
>> Jeff: RODNEY FINDS A NEW
PARTNER IN CRIME.
>> I WAS LOOKING FOR A BROMANCE,
A NEW PARTNER TO CHILL WITH.
>> HIS OLD PARTNERS AREN'T IN
LOVE.
>> I THINK HE WANTS TO SCREW US.
>> RODNEY AND JOAQUIN ARE A
POWER COUPLE.
THEY HAVE TO BE SPLIT UP
IMMEDIATELY.
>> IT'S A LITTLE UNCOMFY.
I THINK THE 14 DAYS I SPENT OUT
HERE ONLY DEEPENED MY LOVE AND
APPRECIATION FOR THIS GAME.
MOST OF ALL IT DEEPENED MY
APPRECIATION FOR HOW DIFFICULT
IT IS TO PLAY IT.
I'M TRULY HUMBLED.
I'M AWED AND I'M THRILL I GOT TO
LIVE OUT MY DREAM OF PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."