>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... AFTER 17 DAYS,
NAGAROTE AND ESCAMECA FINALLY
MERGED.
[CHEERING]
>> NOW IT'S ONE TRIBE BATTLING
IT OUT FOR $1 MILLION.
>> Jeff: AND AT FIRST
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
JOE OUTLASTED ALL THE REST.
JOE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL...
>> CAN'T GET JOE, GET HIS
RIGHT-HAND WOMAN OUT.
>> Jeff: MIKE WANTED TO TEST
WILL'S ALLEGIANCE.
>> WHEN I SEE HALI'S NAME
WRITTEN DOWN, I'LL KNOW I CAN
TRUST WILL.
>> Jeff: THE REAL BATTLE WAS
BLUE COLLAR TARGETED JENN VERSUS
WHITE COLLAR TARGETING KELLY
WITH WHITE COLLAR IN THE MIDDLE
DECIDING.
>> WHEREVER WE GO, WE'LL CHANGE
THIS GAME DRAMATICALLY.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SHIRIN STUCK WITH THE NO COLLARS
WHILE CAROLYN, TYLER AND WILL
STUCK WITH THE MAJORITY.
IF ANYONE HAS THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT THE
PLAY IT...
BUT NUMBERS DON'T MATTER WHEN AN
IDOL IS PLAYED.
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT TO GO
HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: SEVENTH PERSON VOTED
OUT, KELLY.
IN THE END, KELLY WAS SENT HOME.
KELLY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR," LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN.
>> I WAS PLAYED, KID, WELL
PLAYED.
>>SEEING KELLY GO, IT BROKE MY
HEART.
I'M REALLY MAD ABOUT THAT AND I
PUT IT ON MIKE.
MIKE IS THE LEADER WHO CHANGED
UP THE VOTE.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HALI AND
AT THE LAST SECOND HE CHANGED IT
TO JENN TO TEST WILL'S TRUST.
MIKE'S AN IDIOT REDNECK STRAIGHT
UP.
>> MIKE IS RUNNING THE SHOW AND
LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENING.
SEVEN VERY US THE FOUR NOW.
LISTEN...
>> I GAVE IT TO YOU.
>> THAT WAS MIKE.
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE THAT VOTED
HALI.
>> ME, YOU, TYLER, MAMA C.
>> YOU GOT MAMA C, CAROL, ME,
WILL, TYLER, ALL OF US ON BOARD.
YOU KNOW, I DO LOVE MY BLUES,
BUT YOU COULD BE WITNESSING SOME
VERY INTERESTING STUFF WHEN IT
GETS DOWN TO SEVEN.
>> MIKE'S RUNNING THE SHOW.
BUT ONCE JOE, HALI, JENN ARE
GONE, WE'RE GOING TO RUN THE
SHOW.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> THANKS.
>> IT DEFINITELY DIDN'T GO WITH
WHAT I WANTED TO HAPPEN TONIGHT
OBVIOUSLY.
>> SORRY I'M STILL HERE TO
DISAPPOINT YOU, MIKE.
I KNEW THEY WERE GOING TO VOTE
FOR ME SO I PLAYED MY IDOL.
THEN KELLY WENT HOME.
>> I RESPECT THAT PLAY.
THAT WAS... THAT WAS SWEET.
>> THANKS.
JOE, HALI, SHIRIN AND I WERE
STOKED, JUST STOKED.
THE REST OF THE TRIBE WAS LIKE
MOUTH OPEN, LIKE SHOCKED AND
SAD, OH, POOR KELLY.
WHO GIVES A [BLEEPED].
I THOUGHT IT WAS GREAT.
APPRECIATE IT, THOUGH.
THE NO COLLARS ARE BACK IN TOWN,
AND WE'RE READY TO WIN.
I LOVE TO MESS WITH THE OTHER
ALLIANCE.
I BELIEVE THERE'S STILL FUN TO
BE HAD, LITTLE THINGS TO SCREW
UP FOR EVERYONE ELSE.
I MEAN, I WANT TO LIKE MESS WITH
THINGS WHILE I CAN BECAUSE IT
PROVIDES ME WITH ENTERTAINMENT.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> HOW MANY SCOOPS DID YOU PUT
IN?
>> THREE, WHICH I THINK
EVERYBODY WAS IN TOTAL CONSENSUS
OF.
>> DO A LITTLE MORE.
JUST A LITTLE MORE.
>> I THOUGHT WE SAID THREE.
>> SO.
EVER SINCE JOE AND HIS STOOGES
CAME OVER HERE, THEY RUN THE
FOOD.
THEY PORTION OUT THE FOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT, ANY TIME I GET
MAD, I'M JUST GOING TO WALK A
WAY, MAYBE PUNCH A TREE OR
SOMETHING AND THEN COME BACK IN
THERE WITH THE FRESH COOL, CALM
AND COLLECTED MIND.
>> WHY IS HE... I'D RATHER JUST
PEEL THE THING OFF ON MY OWN.
I LIKE TO EAT RIGHT UP UNDER THE
SKIN AND CHEW ON IT.
>> THE WAY I GIVE UP, RESPECT IS
NOT GIVEN, IT'S EARNED.
OUT HERE IT'S TOUGH.
I DON'T BE FAKE.
I GOT TO RESPECT YOU ON THE
OTHER HAND TO GIVE YOU RESPECT.
AND IF I DON'T RESPECT YOU,
YOU'RE GOING TO KNOW IT.
>> IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL TO LEAVE
IT ON.
>> IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I WANT, HOW'S
THAT?
>> IT'S SALAMI.
>> I KNOW, SO WHY ARE YOU
GETTING UP IN WHAT I'M DOING?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN, IF IT'S
JUST SALAMI, WHY DO YOU CARE I'M
TAKING THE SKIN OFF FOR ME AND
TYLER?
SO JUST SAY IT?
>> I DID SAY IT.
>> SHERRY, THE MOST POINTLESS
PERSON IN THE GAME, WHATEVER HER
NAME IS, SHE SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WE'RE
RUNNING THE GAME.
THE GAME IS PRETTY MUCH OVER FOR
THEM.
WE HAVE TO WEED OUT ALL THE
GARBAGE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE YOUR WAY
ACROSS A SERIES OF BALANCE BEAMS
COLLECTING BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES
AS YOU GO.
EVERY TIME YOU GET A BAG, YOU'LL
DROP IT OFF AND HEAD BACK.
THE FIRST THREE TO COLLECT ALL
THREE BAGS AND CROSS THE FINISH
LINE MOVE ON TO THE FINAL ROUND,
WHERE YOU WILL USE THOSE PUZZLE
PIECES TO SOLVE AN ANCHOR
PUZZLE.
THE FIRST TO FINISH THEIR PUZZLE
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF TODAY'S
CHALLENGE WILL BE TAKEN TO THE
CANOPY OF THE RAINFOREST, TO THE
TOP.
YOU'LL ZIP LINE DOWN TO THE
BOTTOM.
WAITING FOR YOU AT THE BOTTOM, A
PICNIC, A PIZZA PICNIC.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: SHOULD BE A FUN
AFTERNOON.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
DAN TAKES A HARD FALL OUT OF THE
GATE.
GOT TO HEAD BACK.
SHIRIN TAKES A FALL.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
THESE BALANCE BEAMS ARE NOT
EASY.
AND YOU'VE GOT TO BALANCE WHILE
UNTYING BAGS.
HERE COMES JOE WITH HIS FIRST
BAG.
JENN HAS HER FIRST BAG.
HERE COMES MIKE.
JOE'S ACROSS.
JENN'S ACROSS.
MIKE'S ACROSS.
HALI'S ACROSS.
HERE COMES SIERRA AND TYLER.
TYLER WITH A HUGE LEAD.
BUT HE'S ACROSS.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THREE PEOPLE
WITH ALL THREE BAGS.
DAN'S ACROSS.
THERE'S RODNEY AND HERE COMES
WILL AND HE MAKES IT.
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THEIR
SECOND BAGS EXCEPT FOR SHIRIN,
STILL BECOME ON HER FIRST.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BAG.
HERE COMES JOE WITH HIS SECOND
BAG.
JOE IS FLYING THROUGH THIS
CHALLENGE.
RIGHT ON HIS TAIL IS MIKE.
IT IS JOE AND MIKE IN THE LEAD.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THE FIRST
THREE WITH ALL THREE BAGS.
HERE COMES HALI WITH HER SECOND
BAG.
SIERRA HAS HER SECOND BAG.
CAROLYN FALLS SHORT AGAIN.
JENN WITH HER SECOND BAG.
HERE COMES TYLER.
A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THIS.
HERE COMES JOE WITH HIS FINAL
BAG.
JOE MOVING ON.
RODNEY... NO, RODNEY FALLS
SHORT.
MIKE MOVING ON.
LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
WE HAVE JOE, WE HAVE MIKE AND
HALI MOVING ON.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS HALI, JOE AND MIKE.
FIRST TO FINISH THEIR PUZZLE
WINS A NICE REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
FIRST STEP IS GETTING THE PIECES
OUT OF THE BAG.
>> COME ON, MIKE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOE.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE PUTTING
TOGETHER AN ANCHOR, A ARE RUSTY
ANCHOR.
ONE BLUE COLLAR, TWO NO COLLARS,
BATTLING IT OUT.
MIKE OFF TO FAST START.
>> GOOD JOB, MIKE.
>> Jeff: JOE TRYING TO GET
SOMETHING GOING.
HALI STARTING TO MAKE SOME
PROGRESS NOW.
SOME PIECES MAY GO IN A COUPLE
OF SPOTS, BUT IT WILL ONLY
FINISH ONE WAY.
HALI WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
HALI STARTING TO PICK UP A LOT
OF MOMENTUM NOW.
JOE GOT SOME PIECES GOING.
HE'S MOVING QUICKLY.
MIKE HAS NOT MADE MUCH PROGRESS
ON HIS PUZZLE.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: HALI WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> YEAH, HALI.
>> Jeff: JOE WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
MIKE'S FALLING OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE QUICKLY.
HALI HAS FIVE PIECES LEFT.
JOE HAS FOUR PIECES LEFT ON THIS
PUZZLE.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT, THEY'RE BOTH
VERY CLOSE.
THESE LAST FEW PIECES ARE WHERE
IT GETS VERY DIFFICULT.
HALI MOVING SOME PIECES AROUND
NOW.
SHE'S BACK THE FIVE PIECES THAT.
WILL HAPPEN WHEN YOU GET CLOSE
AND YOU REALIZE SOMETHING'S NOT
RIGHT AND YOU HAVE TO MOVE A
PIECE.
JOE NOW REMOVES AN ENTIRE
SECTION, OPENING THE DOOR FOR
MIKE TO GET BACK IN.
MIKE NOT GIVING UP.
HE'S STILL FIGHTING IN THIS.
>> THAT'S THE BOY, MIKE.
>> Jeff: MIKE WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
MIKE NOW BACK IN THIS.
JOE NOW TRYING TO FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
HALI TRYING A NEW COMBINATION.
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
MIKE DOWN TO FOUR PIECES.
JOE DOWN TO FOUR PIECES.
MAKE IT THREE.
MIKE STARTING TO PANIC NOW.
JOE MAKES IT TWO.
SUDDENLY JOE HAS FIGURED IT OUT.
MAKE IT ONE.
THERE IT IS, LAST PIECE.
JOE HAS IT!
JOE WINS REWARD.
[APPLAUSE]
JOE, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, JOE.
>> THANKS, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: UNDEFEATED SO FAR IN
THE INDIVIDUAL PORTION OF THIS
GAME.
NICE AFTERNOON ZIP LINING,
PIZZA.
ALL RIGHT, JOE, PICK THREE
PEOPLE TO JOIN YOU ON THIS
REWARD.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE TYLER.
>> TYLER, COME ON OVER.
>> WILL.
>> Jeff: WILL, COME JOIN
TYLER.
>> IN THE LAST CHALLENGE, MAMA C
DID IT RIGHT.
I THINK SHE EARNED THE REWARD.
>> COME ON OVER.
>> WE HAVE FOUR, BUT A NICE
ROUND NUMBER IS FIVE.
PICK ONE FINAL PERSON TO JOIN
YOU ON THIS REWARD.
>> I'VE BEEN THE MOST STARVING
OUT HERE MORE THAN ANYBODY.
>> YOU'VE BEEN EATING MORE THAN
EVERYBODY, TOO.
>> NO, I DON'T.
SOME PEOPLE ARE PICKING OUT
THERE.
IF YOU DON'T PICK ME, I DON'T
CARE.
I KNOW WE'RE SEVEN STRONG AND
I'M GOOD WITH IT.
SO IT IS WHAT IT IS, MAN.
>> Jeff: SO RODNEY TOOK
HIMSELF OUT.
>> I'M OUT.
I DON'T CARE.
I'M GOING TO KEEP IT REAL, JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHO IS IT GOING TO
BE, JOE, YOU GOT ONE LAST SPOT.
>> SUPER FAN.
>> Jeff: SHIRIN?
>> SHUT UP?
SHUT UP?
, OH, MY GOD.
>> AND THAT'S WHY.
RIGHT THERE.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
EXPERIENCE.
>> WE HAVE OUR FIVE HEADING FOR
A NICE AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, ENJOY
THE DAY.
GOOD WORK.
>> HAVE FUN.
HAVE SO MUCH FUN.
>> KEEPING IT REAL, MAN.
I'M HERE TO PLAY THIS GAME, BRO.
>> Jeff: GUYS, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
>> JOE WINNING THIS REWARD WAS
DEVASTATING BECAUSE PROBABLY
GETTING A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL ON THE REWARD.
THE KID'S AMAZING, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING TO
BEAT HIM, IS -- THIS IS WHERE
THE RUBBER MEETS THE ROAD.
>> I WON REWARD, AND IT FELT
FANTASTIC, FLOATING OVER THE
JUNGLE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER BEEN ZIP
LINING BEFORE.
OH, MY GOODNESS, IT WAS SO MUCH
FUN.
IT WAS MYSELF, CAROLYN.
>> YOU DID IT, CAROLYN.
YOU DID IT, BABY.
>> TYLER.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> WILL.
AND SHIRIN.
>> WHO'S NEXT?
>> ME.
OH, MY GOD.
WHOA.
>> BRAKE.
>> COMING IN WAY TOO FAST.
>> COMING IN HARD.
THAT'S A TREE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO HIT THAT.
>> I JUST COULDN'T BELIEVE MY
LUCK.
I GOT TO GO ZIP LINING WITH
CAROLYN.
I'M LIKE, I DON'T LIKE HER AND
DON'T WANT HER TO EAT PIZZA AND
HAVE A COOL ADVENTURE.
>> COME SIT, BUD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I WAS SO EXCITED.
THERE'S WATERMELON AND PIZZA AND
SODA.
>> I'M GOING TO DO AN ORANGE.
>> WHO WANTS THE RED ONE.
>> I'LL DRINK WHATEVER.
>> BUT IF YOU LOOK AT IT, YES'S
PICK WAS INTERESTING BECAUSE HE
PICKED NO BLUE COLLAR BECAUSE
OBVIOUSLY THE BLUE COLLARS ARE
OUT TO GET HIM.
>> CHEERS, YOU ALL.
>> I WAS HAPPY ABOUT IT.
SMART MOVE.
>> I LOOKED OVER AND I THOUGHT I
SAW SOMETHING IN CAROLYN'S
BOTTLE OF SODA.
>> RODNEY WAS LIKE ANGRY THAT WE
DIDN'T DO IT.
>> I GRABBED IT AND AS SOON AS I
LOOKED INSIDE, I SAW THERE WAS A
NOTE IN THE BOTTOM.
AND I TRIED TO JUST CHUG IT AND
PUT IT IN MY MOUTH.
BUT I SAW TYLER LOOK OVER AT ME.
>> WHAT'S THIS ONE?
>> DELICIOUS.
>> TYLER SAW ME.
SO I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT OUR
PLAN TO READ IT TOGETHER.
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO.
>> HAVE A LITTLE MORE.
>> HE KILLED THE REST OF THE
LAST ONE.
>> SORRY.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
>> IT WAS WARM.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LIKED IT.
>> OUT OF THE CORNER OF MY EYE I
SAW JOE ALMOST CHOKE ON AN
IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE.
I COULD HAVE OUTED HIM RIGHT
THEN AND THERE.
BUT I SAT ON IT.
I WAS SILENT.
I JUST FIGURED, THE CLUE WAS
SOMETHING THAT DEFINITELY OPENS
UP NEW OPTIONS.
IF JOE FINDS THE IMMUNITY IDOL,
THAT ALSO OPENS UP NEW OPTIONS.
>> WASN'T EVEN BARELY TWILIGHT
AND TYLER WAS WIDE AWAKE WAITING
FOR ME TO GET UP.
SO I'LL SHARE THE CLUE WITH THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND THAT'S
GOING TO MAKE HIM AND I CLOSE
AND BONDED.
>> I'M ACTUALLY SITTING IN THE
CHAIR WITH MY EYES HALF-WAY OPEN
TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON, ACTING
LIKE I'M SLEEPING.
JOE AND TYLER GET UP AND GO
AROUND THE CORNER.
THEY WRING THE DISHES LIKE
THEY'RE GOING DOWN THE RIVER.
I KNEW TODAY WAS GOING TO BE A
MAD DASH BECAUSE I FIGURED THERE
WAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL CLUE
AT THE REWARD.
THE WHOLE TIME I'M TRACKING THEM
DOWN THE BEACH FROM TREE TO
TREE.
I'M LIKE SPY VERSUS SPY.
I'M JUMPING IN BURKES.
I'M CLIMBING UP THIS TREE.
I'M PEEKING THROUGH THE LEAVES.
YOU KNOW, TRYING THE STAY
CAMOUFLAGED WHERE THEY CAN'T SEE
ME.
>> WHERE A TRIBUTARY RUNS, HOW
YOU SEE THIS, FIND GRAVITY.
>> WHY WOULD JOE BE SHOWING
TYLER A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
CLUE?
UNLESS HE'S TRYING TO WOO HIM
OVER.
>> I DIDN'T SLEEP VERY WELL AT
ALL.
>> I CAMPFIRE, ASH.
>> JOE READS THE CLUE AND WITHIN
MOMENTS MIKE IS UPON US.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT HE SAW.
HE COULD HAVE SEEN ME READING
THE CLUE WITH JOE.
I HAVE TO BE VERY, VERY CAREFUL
ABOUT ALIENATING THE GROUP THAT
I AM IN, SO WHAT DO I TELL MIKE?
SO HE'S GOT THE CLUE.
BUT NOBODY... HE HASN'T REALLY
TOLD ANYBODY.
SO IT'S NEAR THE RIVER, NEAR A
SEA OF GREEN.
FIND GRAVITY AND FOLLOW.
>> I TOLD HIM WHAT THE CLUE
READ.
THUS BEGAN A MAD DASH TRYING THE
FIND WHERE JOE IS AND MIKE WAS
LEADING THE PACK OF INSANITY.
>> I THOUGHT HE WAS WITH YOU.
>> NO.
>> HE'S GOT THE CLUE AND JOE'S
NOWHERE TO BE FOUND DOWN THERE.
WHEREVER JOE IS, THAT'S WHERE
THE CLUE HAS TAKEN HIM.
>> WELL, WE HAVE TO FIND JOE.
>> JOE JUST TAKES OFF BY
HIMSELF.
HE'S OUT LOOKING FOR THE IDOL
RIGHT NOW.
NO ONE ELSE IS WATCHING JOE.
>> DUDE, I WAS CHANGING.
HE CAME DOWN THE PATH AND HE
CAME DOWN THIS WAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE WENT.
>> I HAVE TO FIND JOE BEFORE HE
FINDS THE IDOL SO WE CAN SEND
THIS GUY HOME AND IT'S NOT ME,
BECAUSE I HONESTLY FEEL THAT
ONCE JOE IS OUT OF THE GAME, IF
I DON'T HAVE SOMETHING IN MY
BACK POCKET, I'M THE NEXT ONE TO
GO HOME, SO I'M GOING THE LOOK
FOR JOE.
>> SURE ENOUGH.
I ROLL UP AND I FIND JOE, AND IT
DAWNS ON ME THAT I WANT A BIGGER
TARGET ON YES'S BACK.
BOOM, I DIDN'T SEE HIM GRAB AN
IDOL.
I DIDN'T SEE HIM PUT AN IDOL IN
HIS POCKET.
SO I HEAD TO THE RIVER.
>> GOOD JOB, BABY BROTHER.
HE'S GOT IT.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> YOU'VE GOT IT.
>> HE FOUND IT?
>> YEAH, HE'S GOT IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT.
>> I BASICALLY SCREAMED OUT,
GOOD JOB ON FINDING THE IDOL.
HE TRIES THE PLAY IT OFF.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET HIM PLAY IT
OFF.
I'M GOING TO SAY I SAW HIM PUT
IT IN HIS POCKET.
>> YOU NOVI TO BLOW IT UP.
>> OF COURSE.
IT'S A GAME.
>MIKE COMES OVER, OH, YOU DOG, I
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GOT IT.
YOU KNOW, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
>> GOOD JOB, BROTHER.
>> YEAH, MIKE KIND OF SPOILED MY
PLAN.
SO MIKE THINKS I HAVE IT.
HE'S CONVINCED THAT I HAVE IT.
>> YOU DON'T.
>> I DON'T.
BUT EVERYONE THINKS I HAVE IT,
WHICH IS GOOD.
SO IF I JUST LAY BACK THEN IT'S
LIKE I HAVE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WORRIED ABOUT THIS IDOL
NONSENSE?
>> I'M SURPRISED AT YOU TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
I REALLY AM ACTUALLY.
YOU'RE LIKE ME.
YOU'RE A FAN.
WHY IS IT THAT FANS CAN'T DO
BASIC MATH.
>> HUH?
>> WHY WOULD YOU SIDE YOURSELF
ON THE SHORT SIDE OF THE STICK?
>> I HAVE PLANS.
>> YOU'RE JUST ONE OF JOE'S
MINIONS AND THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
SEEN AS NOW.
SERIOUSLY.
YOUR GAME IS DONE.
YOUR GAME IS OVER.
>> I THINK YOU JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND MY GAME.
>> RIGHT.
I DON'T.
YOU KNOW, WITNESS AGAIN ANOTHER
FAN WHO CAN'T DO BASIC MATH.
SHANINI OR WHATEVER HER NAME IS,
I CAN'T REMEMBER HER DAMN NAME
BECAUSE SHE ANNOYS ME SO MUCH.
SOMEBODY SLAP THIS WOMAN.
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD JUST SLAP
HER AND SHUT HER UP ALREADY.
DEAR GOD IN HEAVEN, DO US ALL A
FAVOR.
I CANNOT WAIT UNTIL HER TORCH
GOES OUT.
YOU'RE AN EASY MARK.
IF JOE WINS IMMUNITY TOMORROW,
AND HE HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, DO YOU REALLY THINK HE'S
GOING TO GIVE IT TO YOU?
SO THAT MAKES YOU A VERY EASY
TARGET.
>> DAN JUST TRIES TO RIP ME
APART.
HE JUST SLINGS INSULT AFTER
INSULT FOR ME.
I ACTUALLY FELT SORRY FOR DAN,
SO I SAT BACK AND THOUGHT, WHAT
ELSE.
>> THERE ARE ONLY TWO PEOPLE IN
THIS GAME, OKAY.
PEOPLE THAT DON'T DO ANYTHING
AND GET VOTED OUT BECAUSE OF IT
AND PEOPLE THAT DO TOO MUCH.
AND ANNOY EVERYBODY AND GET
VOTED OUT.
CASE IN POINT.
YOU DID IT TO YOURSELF.
AND THAT'S JUST THE TRUTH.
AND I'M ACTUALLY JUST TRYING TO
BE NICE, I TRULY AM.
>> I'VE BEEN RUNNING AROUND
LOOKING FOR THIS IDOL ALL DAY,
AND I'M DOWN TO A LITTLE TERMITE
NEST TRYING TO GET A LITTLE BIT
OF SUSTENANCE IN MY BELLY.
HELP ME KEEP GOING LOOKING FOR
THIS IDOL.
STILL NO LUCK FINDING THE IDOL
FOR MIKE.
THIS IS SUCH A MIND-BEATING,
EXHAUSTING GAME.
>> IT'S TOUGH.
IT'S A TOUGH PART OF THE GAME.
BUT I'VE GOT THE FIND IT.
I HAVE THE FIND IT.
SO I GOT WORK TO DO.
THIS IS NOT AN EASY TASK.
DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING TO COME
OUT HERE AND YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO FIND AN IDOL AND IT'S THAT
EASY BECAUSE YOU CAN'T.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP SEARCHING, KEEP
LOOKING IN EVERY NOOK, EVERY
CRANNY.
PEOPLE WHO FIND IDOLS IN THIS
GAME ARE THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
WORKING HARDEST IN THIS GAME.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
IT'S HAPPY DAY, BABY.
THIS IS HAPPY DAY.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE FEELING LIKE EVERYTHING'S
GOING AGAINST YOU, YOU KEEP
DIGGING WITHIN YOURSELF, WHEN
YOU HAVE NOTHING LEFT.
AND THIS, THIS RIGHT HERE, THIS
IS WHAT YOU FIND.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, NOT GOING TO
SHARE IT, BECAUSE I NEED THAT
PROTECTION FOR MYSELF AND RIGHT
NOW I HAVE A CHANCE TO GET RID
OF JOE, SO IF JOE DOESN'T WIN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY, JOE HAS TO
GO.
AND THAT'S JUST REPUBLICAN --
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, JOE, I WILL
TAKE IT BACK.
NO HELP AT ALL.
>> SHENANIGANS.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE TO MOVE A PUZZLE
PIECE THROUGH THREE SLIDE MAZES.
ONCE YOU'VE MOVED THE SAME PIECE
THROUGH THE THREE MAZES, YOU
WILL USE THAT PIECE TO COMPLETE
A SLIDE PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY
GUARANTEED TO MOVE ON IN THIS
GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WE'RE
AFTER 22 DAYS.
SOMEBODY'S QUEST FOR THE $1
MILLION AND THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR WILL FALL SHORT.
SHIRIN, HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
A PUZZLE.
NO BALANCE BEAM, NO OBSTACLES.
>> THIS IS WHAT I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR THIS WHOLE TIME,
LIKE I'M A COMPUTER SCIENTIST,
SO THIS SHOULD BE MY ARENA.
IT REALLY COMES DOWN TO HOW BIG
OF A FAN I AM.
I'M STILL JUST SO STOKED TO BE
HERE AND I WANT TO BE HERE SO
BADLY THAT I JUST...
>> Jeff: SO YOU GOT...
>> I'VE GOT SO MUCH ENERGY,
JEFF.
I HAVE TO CONTAIN IT.
LIKE THE OPPOSITE OF A BOMB, I
HAVE TO...
>> Jeff: YEAH, WHAT YOU JUST
DID.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
YOU HAVE ONE PUZZLE PIECE IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU HAVE TO GET IT THROUGH THREE
SLIDE MAZES THEN THE SLIDE
PUZZLE.
JOE OUT QUICKLY.
SIERRA WITH A BIG FALL, BUT
SHE'S THROUGH.
HALI, TYLER, DAN, CAROLYN,
SHIRIN.
HERE COMES JENN.
HERE COMES WILL.
AND DEAD LAST IT IS RODNEY.
>> MAN.
>> Jeff: JOE MOVING ON TO HIS
THIRD MAZE.
SHIRIN ON HER THIRD.
THERE'S TYLER AND MIKE.
IT'S SHIRIN, JOE, TYLER AND MIKE
IN THE EARLY LEAD.
CAROLYN NOW ON HER THIRD.
THERE'S SIERRA.
THERE'S DAN.
GOT TO GET OVER THAT OBSTACLE.
JOE THROUGH THE THIRD ONE.
JOE NOW WORKING ON HIS SLIDE
PUZZLE.
SHIRIN IS NOW THROUGH THE THIRD
ONE.
TYLER IS THROUGH THE THIRD ONE.
THERE'S SIERRA.
THERE'S MIKE.
HERE COMES CAROLYN.
EVERYBODY NOW GETTING THROUGH
IT.
THERE'S DAN.
THERE'S WILL.
JENN NOW JOINS THEM.
THE ONLY PEOPLE NOT IN THIS ARE
RODNEY AND HALI.
NOW YOU'RE LOOKING TO COMPLETE A
PUZZLE.
YOU WILL KNOW WHEN YOU HAVE IT.
SHIRIN PREDICTED SHE WOULD BE
GOOD AT THIS.
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
DAN FLYING THROUGH THIS PUZZLE.
RODNEY FINALLY AT HIS SLIDE
PUZZLE.
HALI'S AT HER SLIDE PUZZLE.
JOE WOULD LOVE TO MAKE IT THREE
IN A ROW.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: DAN THINKS HE HAS IT.
>> GOOD JOB, DANO.
>> Jeff: DAN IS WRONG!
EVERYBODY'S STILL IN IT.
YOU HAVE TO BE BOTH FAST AND
RIGHT TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
JOE HAS WON FIRST TWO INDIVIDUAL
CHALLENGES.
CAN HE MAKE IT THREE IN A ROW?
>> NOW.
>> Jeff: DAN NOW THINKS HE HAS
IT.
DAN IS WRONG AGAIN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: DAN HAS THOUGHT TWICE
HE HAD IT AND HAS BEEN WRONG
BOTH TIME, OPENING THE DOOR BACK
UP.
MIKE MAKING SOME PROGRESS.
JEFF, JEFF.
>> Jeff: JOE THINKS HE HAS IT.
JOE IS RIGHT!
JOE WINS IMMUNITY THREE STRAIGHT
INDIVIDUAL WINS.
JOE, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, JOE.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IS JOE'S.
UNDEFEATED IN THREE INDIVIDUAL
CHALLENGES.
IF YOU WEREN'T A THREAT BEFORE,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY A THREAT NOW.
JOE SAFE AGAIN TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 22
VERY TOUGH DAYS IN THIS GAME,
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> JOE WON.
ALL HE DOES IS WIN CHALLENGES.
HE'S A PROTOTYPICAL ALL-AMERICAN
WHITE BOY.
WHO WOULDN'T WANT HIM TO WIN
"SURVIVOR."
IF IT WAS MY DECISION, JOAQUIN
WOULD HAVE MADE IT.
WE WOULDN'T EVEN BE DEALING WITH
THIS DRAMA.
WE'D BE SITTING BACK EATING RICE
AND BEANS.
WE HAVE TO RUN AROUND AND HUSTLE
BECAUSE OF DECISIONS MIKE MADE.
>> TODAY I GOT HANDED AN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE ON A SILVER
PLATTER, A PUZZLE, AND JOE WINS.
JOE WINS EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, I WOULD INVOLVE TO WIN A
CHALLENGE.
THAT WOULD BE LIKE A LIVE
ACHIEVEMENT FOR ME, BUT AT THIS
POINT EVERYBODY THINKS I'M SO
NOT A THREAT, LIKE I'M SO WEAK
IN EVERY WAY, AND I HOPE THAT
BUYS ME A FEW EXTRA DAYS IN THIS
GAME.
I'M NOT TOO CONCERNED.
>> SHIRIN, RIGHT?
>> IF THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY
WANTS TO DO.
>> WE THINK SHIRIN HAS THE IDOL.
I DON'T THINK SHE WAS.
>> FROM WHERE?
>> I SAW HER SCRAMBLING UP UNTIL
THE VERY LAST DAY LOOKING UP IN
THOSE HILLS WITH JOAQUIN,
SCREAMING, BITCHING AT HIM.
IF ALL CAMPS HAVE AN IDOL, WHERE
IS WHITE COLLARS?
CAROLYN AND TYLER SEEM VERY
CONFIDENT THAT SHIRIN DOES NOT
HAVE THE IDOL.
PROBABLY BECAUSE SHE HASN'T SAID
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
AND I DON'T THINK HER GAME IS
GOOD ENOUGH TO KEEP HER MOUTH
SHUT.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT IS.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE SHE'S AN IDIOT
SAVANT.
I'M LEANING MORE TOWARD THE
IDIOT SIDE.
>> BUT SHIRIN IS NEVER GOING TO
WIN ANYTHING.
>> THE THREE OF THOSE NO COLLARS
ARE SO TIGHT.
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE OF THE
TRIPOD, THEY'LL CRUMBLE.
>> HALI.
>> SO HALI.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE THE MAJORITY OF
EVERYBODY WANTS TO GO SHIRIN.
SO I'M JUST VOICING CONCERN.
>> SO DAN CAME UP TO ME AND HE
WAS JUST LIKE, IT BLOWS MY MIND,
YOU'RE A FAN AND YOU CAN'T EVEN
DO BASIC MATH.
AND I'M LIKE...
>> WHAT?
>> I'M LIKE, WHAT.
HE SAYS EVERYBODY SEES THE THREE
OF YOU AS JOE'S PUPPETS.
>> I WOULD LEAVE MY KIDS WITH
RODNEY BEFORE DAN.
>> WHAT DID DAN SAY TO YOU?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
START.
>> GETTING RID OF DAN WOULD BE
AMAZING.
HE SAID SOME HURTFUL,
UNNECESSARY THINGS BEING A GROWN
MAN.
I HAVEN'T FORGIVEN HIM.
SO TO HEAR EVERYONE ELSE FEEL
THAT SAME WAY MAKES ME FEEL A
LOT BETTER.
IT REITERATES TO ME WE'RE NOT
CRAZY.
>> WE NEED ANOTHER VOTE.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT I WANT TO DO
GIRLS.
>> MY INITIAL BLUE COLLAR
ALLIANCE IS GOING TO GO FOR A
GIRL, BUT IS THAT WHAT I WANT TO
DO?
I WANT GIRLS IN THE END.
SO I HAVE TO DECIDE DO I WANT TO
GO WITH THE GIRLS OR DO I WANT
TO STICK TO MY BLUE-COLLAR
ALLIANCE?
>> ACTUALLY I'M JUST READY FOR
THE GIRLS.
>> WHY DON'T WE JUST DO DAN?
>> OKAY.
>> I LIKE THE DYNAMIC OF US
GIRLS JUST BANDING TOGETHER.
TOGETHER WE CAN MAKE EACH OTHER
STRONGER.
AND IF SIERRA IS GOING TO FLIP
TONIGHT, WE NEED ANOTHER VOTE TO
GET DAN OUT.
>> LET'S VOTE OUT DAN.
>> OKAY.
YOU GO MISOGYNISTIC ON THE GIRL,
GIRLS ARE GOING TO TAKE YOU OUT.
>> DAN.
>> I'M WILLING TO VOTE DAN OFF.
EVERYBODY IS WILLING TO VOTE HIM
OFF.
EVERYBODY.
>> THEN AFTER THAT WHAT HAPPENS?
>> AFTER THAT WE THEN REASSEMBLE
, BUT THERE'S NOT SOME
STRONG-ASS BLUE ALLIANZ.
WE'VE TAKEN OUT ONE OF THE KICK
PINS OF BLUE.
OTHERWISE IT'S JUST THE DAN AND
MIKE SHOW.
>> IT IS.
>> THIS MIGHT BE THE LAST
OPPORTUNITY WE GET.
LIKE WITH NUMBERS LIKE THIS, TO
TAKE ONE OF THEM OUT.
>> THEY ARE RUNNING THE SHOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
THAT CAN GO ON.
>> SOME OF THESE GUYS IN MY
ALLIANCE ARE BIG THREATS.
I WANT NOTHING MORE THAN TO
TARGET MIKE AND DAN.
>> I GOT YOUR BACK.
>> I'M HOPING JUST TO STRIKE
BEFORE BLUE COLLAR EVEN KNOWS
WHAT HITS THEM.
>> TYLER, THEY HAVE NO
ALLEGIANCE TO YOU.
YOU'RE A THREAT TO THEM.
>> Jeff: TYLER, WHAT WAS THE
REACTION AT CAMP AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL WHEN JENN PLAYED THE IDOL
AND EVERYBODY'S JAW DROPPED?
>> THERE WERE SOME BUMMED OUT
PEOPLE FOR SURE.
KELLY WAS WELL LIKED.
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, WE
TALKED ABOUT A CHAINSAW KIND OF
SPLITTING THIS GROUP, BUT PEOPLE
WERE ALREADY STARTING TO BLUR
THE LINES.
CONVERSATIONS WERE STARTING TO
BE HAD AGAIN.
IT WASN'T US VERSUS THEM, IT WAS
A BIG GROUP OF SURVIVORS.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, DO YOU FEEL
THAT, AS WELL?
>> I DON'T THINK THE LINE IS
COMPLETELY DRAWN IN THE SAND AT
THIS POINT.
I CAN GO WITH WHATEVER ALLIANZ
AWANT TO.
>>
>> Jeff: MIKE, HOW SURE ARE
YOU OF THE VOTE YOU THINK IS
GOING TO GO DOWN?
>> I KNOW I'M 155,000% KNOWING
WHAT I'M DOING TONIGHT, BUT
THESE ARE A BUNCH OF GAMERS
SITTING RIGHT HERE, AND YOU ALL
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WE ALL KNOW HOW TO TICKLE
SOMEBODY'S EAR.
SO ARE YOU GOING TO GO WITH
SOMEBODY THAT TOOK YOU MAYBE FOR
SOME PIZZA, OR SOMEBODY THAT HAS
BEEN PROVIDING FOOD THE WHOLE
TIME FOR YOU?
>> Jeff: DAN, AFTER THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, ARE YOU A LITTLE
UNEASY GIVEN THAT THINGS CAN
CHANGE LIKE THAT?
>> AS A BIG FAN OF THIS GAME,
YEAH, YOU HAVE TO EXPECT THE
BOMBS TO DROP.
AND YOU JUST HOPE IT DOESN'T
DROP ON YOU.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE IN YOUR
ALLIANCE AND STAND BY IT.
IT'S THREE MAGIC WORDS, JEFF --
QUITTERS NEVER WIN.
>> JEFF, THAT'S FLAT-OUT WRONG.
FLIPPERS DO WIN.
TONY FLIPPED A MILLION TIMES AND
WON.
IT'S LIKE A FEAR TACTIC THAT
HE'S USING AGAINST HIS ALLIANCE
SO THAT NOBODY WILL VOTE AGAINST
HIM.
>> Jeff: HALI, THREE WORDS,
FLIPPERS NEVER WIN.
DO YOU THINK HE'S STATING A
FACT, OR DO YOU THINK HE'S
SENDING A MESSAGE TO ANYBODY
THAT MIGHT BE THINKING ABOUT
FLIPPING?
>> I THINK HE'S SENDING A
MESSAGE, BUT HE NEEDS TO
REMEMBER THAT WE'RE TRIBE
MERICA, AND IF YOU LOOK AT
HISTORY, WHAT IF THE COLONISTS
NEVER FLIPPED ON THE GREATEST
EMPIRE IN THE WORLD?
HOW ABOUT THAT, SINCE WE'RE
TRIBE MERICA, I THINK FLIPPERS
HAVE A GREAT HISTORICAL RECORD
TO WIN THIS GAME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: HOW ABOUT THAT?
WOW.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
MERICA.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
WILL, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'VE GONE OFF THE RAILS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT THE PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE DAN.
HALI.
DAN.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES DAN, TWO VOTES HALI.
DAN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES DAN.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES DAN, THREE VOTES
HALI.
DAN.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES HALI.
FOUR VOTES DAN.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, HALI.
THAT'S SIX.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
HALI, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> LOVE YOU, MERICA.
>> BYE, HALI.
HAVE A BEER FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WELL, THERE WAS A LOT
OF TALK TONIGHT ABOUT LINES
BEING DRAWN IN THE SAND.
BUT WITH TEN PLAYERS LEFT, LINES
DRAWN IN THE SAND TONIGHT CAN BE
WASHED AWAY BY THE TIDES
TOMORROW.
GAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," EVERYONE TAKES A
BEATING.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: THIS IS AN AWKWARD
THING TO WATCH.
AND ONE SURVIVOR CONSIDERS
THROWING IN THE TOWEL.
>> IT'S JUST NOT FUN.
PEOPLE SUCK.
I HAVE NOTHING OUT HERE EXCEPT
FOR DESPAIR.
>> I WAS SHOCKEDMENT LIKE I
DIDN'T THINK I WAS GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
I REALLY THOUGHT WE HAD THIS
GIRLS THING GOING, BUT I'M THE
SUCKER ON THAT ONE.
HONESTLY I UNDERSTAND WHY SIERRA
AND WHOEVER ELSE VOTED FOR ME
DID.
I THINK IT'S GOOD GAME PLAY.
I'M READY TO GO TAKE MY FIRST
SHOT OF WHISKEY AND HAVE MY BIG
BOWL OF ICE CREAM.