translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
After 29 seasons and 15 years,
Survivor, TV's biggest
social experiment,
break the mold once again.
These 18 Americans were
divided into three tribes,
according to their professions
and their approaches to life.
The White Collar tribe,
made up of a Yahoo executive,
of a media consultant
and former university professor
and a retail buyer.
They are accustomed to ordering
and deciding to obtain satisfaction.
I am a buyer for
a department store. I am demanding.
I made everyone
who worked for me cry.
I'm the devil.
In college, I
taught a course on Survivor.
Few of the things I wanted
to do that I didn't accomplish.
I step on the people
I need to level up.
In the business world,
I worked in hard boxes.
Everyone wants your spot.
And it's the same in Survivor.
Everyone has the same goal.
Here we go, kids!
Work Blues. This tribe
is made up of a policewoman,
a rodeo professional
and a post office worker.
They are used
to hard, physical work
and aren't afraid to get
their hands dirty to get the job done.
I work
on an oil rig.
I'm usually the most
covered in oil and mud.
It's the same in this game.
You can't win
without getting your hands dirty.
And my hands will be gross.
I am a single mother and hairdresser.
Having a little girl is hard,
but it made me who I am.
Mentally, no one in the world
is as strong as me.
I have worked at the Post Office
for 22 years.
I am here to live my dream.
I've dreamed of being in Survivor
since season 1, episode 1.
I want to be remembered.
One way or another,
you won't forget me.
The Colorless Tribe.
This group includes
a sailing teacher,
a YouTube legend
and a coconut seller.
They use their free spirits
to get ahead in life.
I am curious, an adventurer,
I let myself be carried by the wind.
I do what I want
when I want.
But of course, I want the million.
Money makes life easier.
Ever seen someone
unhappy on a jet ski?
When people find out
that I'm studying law,
they probably see me
as a ruthless capitalist.
But this is not the case.
I do this for the poor,
the castaways of life.
I am not an anarchist.
I am for the common good.
As a coconut seller,
I seek the truth.
My eyes are open to reality.
In my life,
I am guided by my decisions.
I have no rules.
My personality
is like riding a wave.
So let me surf for a moment.
This is the ultimate challenge.
Les Cols Blancs
against the Labor Blues
against the Colorless.
I always wanted to be the boss.
And I'm here
to win the million.
Quick money, easy women, flowing
champagne. Serious?
I don't want people to think I
'm dangerous.
I want people to think I'm here
to enjoy the beaches.
No, I want to beat you at Survivor.
Which way of life will prove
most useful?
People see me
as a big pile of meat,
but in the competition, I am
a tenderloin and they are low cuts.
In the end, only one will win
the million dollars.
Let's go.
39 days,
18 people,
1 Survivor!
As a Survivor fan,
this is my life's dream.
I've wanted to be in Survivor
since I was 16.
Ten years of applications.
But I've never been so ready.
It's fate!
War of the Worlds.
You have been divided
into three groups,
based on your professions
and approaches to life.
What we will discover
in this season,
which of these divisions
is most appropriate for Survivor.
The Yellows, you are the White Collars.
Professionally, you
usually have a position of authority.
Your approach to life
is similar.
You like to decide
and be in control.
White collar workers tend
to make the rules.
Behind, in the center,
what is your name?
Does that seem like it to you?
Office environment, authority?
Typically. I like giving
goals to a team.
In general, the best way
to do this is to lead.
I work at the most ruthless talent
agency in the world.
Going from the urban jungle
to the real jungle will not be a problem.
The Blues, that's good,
you are the Blues of Work.
Professionally, your job
is usually physical.
You earn your living on a daily basis.
You don't always make the rules.
Most of the time,
you follow those of others.
- The guy in the cap, your name?
- My name is Dan.
Does this description of the Overalls
correspond to you?
For sure!
- Are you with your brothers?
- Brothers and sisters, absolutely.
We built the heart of America.
Blood, sweat
and tears, calluses on the hands,
ache everywhere at the end of the day.
But smiling, knowing that we had
a good day's work.
And Madame, in front, with the necklace?
What is your name?
- Lindsey.
- Lindsey, okay with that?
The winner of this show
is on this mat.
Good. This brings us to the Reds.
You are the Colorless,
the free spirits.
Your professions are often
determined by your passions.
You don't really make the rules,
nor do you follow them.
The Colorless tend
to break the rules.
The guy behind.
What is your name?
- You already kiss that, right?
- 100%.
As soon as I saw these people,
I knew it was my family.
How is it possible,
just by looking at a band...
The first smiles you see.
This free smile that
I live with and want to live with.
Without following anyone's rules.
The guy in front.
What is your name?
Considering your group,
do you feel like you belong?
Yes. I am a mover. I move
stuff for office people.
Hot tubs, all the stuff
lazy people don't want to move.
I work hard,
see, I'm burly.
It's my thing. Work hard,
play harder.
You think I'm a mover,
but I'm not anymore.
I use my brain
to play people.
I am a manipulator,
a seller. It's my thing.
Every day I have to sell myself
to make money.
White Collars, you seem
to be boiling over getting into the discussion.
The woman in yellow, your name?
- Carolyn.
- You shake your head.
They tarnish our image.
We work just as hard,
and we're just as free-spirited
than anyone here.
The guy behind, your name?
How
about being among the White Collars?
It's okay with me.
I wouldn't choose any other tribe.
My 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. does not define me.
Well said.
Judging by appearances
can be very expensive.
Let's talk about serious things.
White Collars,
now choose a representative.
Choose someone.
A volunteer?
Jeff asked for a volunteer
to make a heavy decision.
One thing I learned
while studying this game,
is that the worst mistake to make
is to take a leadership role.
- Joaquin?
- Yeah.
Come on, get off the mat.
There, it's good. Perfect.
The Blues, the same.
Choose a representative.
Who wants to do it?
I say... Wisdom.
The Blues, who will it be?
Dan, comfortable with this choice?
It's a double edged sword,
it can be good or bad.
Dan, take a few steps forward.
Well, the Colorless,
who will represent you?
What do you think?
- You want me to?
- It's okay with me.
- Can you get us sandwiches?
- Sandwiches?
- What's your name?
- Will.
What a surprise,
that they have trouble deciding!
Well, the Colorless,
who will it be?
They can't decide!
Jeff, send them a White Collar
to fix this!
We've made up our minds, Jeff!
We have a decision!
But we are not offended.
It passes us by.
- So who for the Colorless?
- Will.
The woman in front, your name?
- Jenn.
- Jenn, why Will?
He promised us sandwiches,
we chose him for that.
- Are you going to make sandwiches?
- Yeah!
With what?
Resources
abound there.
From the ocean,
are you going to make sandwiches?
It will be cool!
We'll have a whole display of food.
- You maintain this.
- We are like that.
Oh my God!
Will, come on.
Last year,
one of my hardcover videos,
it featured my wife dancing
and singing at a gas station.
The video liked because sometimes
people are too serious
and do not take advantage
of this kind of opportunity.
Live in the moment, lower
your guard and have fun!
Will, Dan and Joaquin,
you will choose a 2nd person,
with whom you will make a very
important decision for the tribe.
Who will join you?
Choose someone.
Anyone volunteer?
- I do.
- Yeah?
I do.
- You're the boss.
- OK.
- What's your name?
- So.
Being a chef can be
a tricky position.
- Sure.
- But you chose to be.
But there are two of us, so if I fall,
he falls with me, I guess.
- Dan, why Mike?
- He volunteered.
Without color. Will, you
picked Jenn pretty quickly.
- Yeah.
- Why Jenn?
She's a free spirit,
like everyone here.
I can trust him
to make the right decision.
Good. The cards.
White collar, your name is Masaya.
This map will take you home.
Overalls ,
your name is Escameca.
Without Color,
your name is Nagarote.
Go to your camps.
When you are settled,
each pair will make a decision.
Good luck! Go for it!
Jeff said "Go to your camps",
and I saw those of the other tribes:
"You white -collar people
who work in offices..."
"We want to kill them!"
But for me, it's not
a question of social class.
This is Survivor's War.
I love being Colorless.
I could see in their eyes
that these people were funny.
I believe that in this tribe,
the idea, for the moment,
is to play it cushy
and let it flow.
It's kind of my way of life.
My ears must intrigue you.
I am completely deaf.
I lost my hearing seven years ago.
I have cochlear implants.
That's how I hear.
They were shocked to find out
that I am deaf.
I know it will be a disadvantage.
I can only go 110%
and give it my all.
We are a team, we support you.
- Want to take a ride?
- Are we moving here?
We must act. We should decide
together, depending on what it could be.
It could be a choice
between shelter and food.
Jeff said we should
make a decision for the tribe.
So before we go,
- "Let's decide together.".
- No. 1. No. 2, tarp, food...
- We work as a team.
- That's how you win.
- We have good vibes.
- I see something!
"Honesty", "deception".
I knew
it would be like that.
Well, I read "cheating",
you read "honesty"?
"If you choose deception,
you will receive a small bag of beans.
It will only last a few days,
but you also have a clue
about the immunity idol."
"If you choose honesty,
you will receive a large beanbag.
This big advantage will also show
that you can be trusted
and that you should be favored."
If you want to be dishonest,
we can get a clue about the idol
and the little bag of beans.
Or we can be honest
with the tribe and take the big bag.
We should take the big bag
and explain it to them.
We choose for the tribe.
The choice of the large bag is obvious.
The game is not individual.
We do the best for the group.
Do you want to play nice
or play bad?
- You know...
- How do you want to start?
My heart tells me to be nice,
but the bad guys win this game.
- But it's too early for that.
- I agree.
We should have the beans.
- I think so too.
- Are you sure?
Take the beans.
We must be fair, this is the beginning.
Alright, let's get the beans!
I lean towards honesty,
simply because at this stage of the game,
cheating, for me, is stupid.
What are you doing?
Focus on
building camaraderie.
In front of us were notes
"honesty" and "deceit".
The "honesty" note read:
"If you're honest
and don't take advantage,
you will have a big bag of beans.".
- And we had the beans.
- It's true?
- Owl!
- It's too early in the game...
I don't believe
this is a complete bag.
I think they took the other.
It's not a big bag.
What was in the other,
four beans?
Trust takes time.
I hope we deserved some
If you give us reason
to believe you are liars and dishonest,
so be prepared to take it on.
They are shady.
This bag should be
four times bigger.
They fucked us.
Either they believe us
or they don't.
There's nothing we can do about it.
We made the right choice.
- Absolutely.
- You know what?
We have to deal with it.
- Yeah.
- You know? I mean...
The hardest part is not juggling.
It's not looking at
your hands when juggling.
What if I do this?
- We make the presentations?
- Yeah.
I'm Joaquin, from New York.
Marketing director
for a research center.
I am in training. We
always start with introductions.
My name is Tyler.
Until recently, I was working
at Hollywood's biggest talent agency.
Your name, how long have you been working there,
what else have you done...
That's kind of what we did.
We are not ashamed to be white collar.
I'm Max, from Southern California.
I am in research and consulting.
Everyone knew what to do.
It was settled like clockwork.
What's it gonna be, do
you think?
Jeff said we should
walk away and make a decision.
"Lying is hard. Tune
your violins before you go back to camp."
Frankly...
I know we'll take this.
But what do we tell them?
And so, we are allied, there?
I think we've been allies ever
since you stepped forward.
- Otherwise, we can be honest.
- That's stupid.
It's a stupid decision.
So is cute, really cool,
down to earth. But seriously!
Who wants to be honest?
Honest as...
Do you want to make friends
or win a million? Come on, my pretty.
If there is an advantage, I take it.
And you know you want it too.
Joaquin was really sure.
At no moment
he didn't want to be honest
or work with the tribe.
What does your instinct tell you?
OK, let's do it!
Eventually, the instinct
to take advantage prevailed.
“Near where you quench your thirst,
you will satisfy your craving for power.
It's tucked away in a corner,
no need to climb,
your time might have come."
- Where thirst is quenched.
- So near the well, wherever it is.
Yes, tucked away in a corner.
I love having an edge,
but that means relying on Joaquin.
And that's a little scary.
You're stuck with me!
I feel like I'm making
a pact with the devil.
Do you really find
my story too complicated?
No, it's fine.
If you want to say it,
that's fine.
We finally decided to cheat.
We took the clue.
- Are we hiding it?
- Yeah.
I'm mostly afraid of becoming a target
for making the wrong decision.
My life in this game could
crumble around me.
When they return,
So and Joaquin have a closed bag.
So what was it?
You have been gone for a long time.
I say.
We had a kind of dilemma.
It was what?
There were three boxes.
One said "honesty".
Another "deception".
And the third "neutral".
We chose "neutral",
because with the other two,
there was a kind of caveat.
I don't know
what would have happened.
- Is it rice?
- Beans.
We wanted to take "honest", but...
We didn't know
what would happen. To be honest.
Look, might as well be neutral...
That's what we said.
I don't really trust
So and Joaquin.
I think they have the clue
on the immunity idol.
But I would do the same.
I can't be mad at
anyone. It's a game! Hello!
This bag of beans was very small.
Yes, they lie very badly.
I don't believe it for a moment.
As a Survivor fan, I know
it's "honesty" or "cheating".
And they clearly chose
"deception". So I worry.
So I immediately
wanted to create links,
see what they thought of me.
See if anyone is ready
to start something.
I felt good about you from the start.
- I don't know about you, but...
- Exactly.
- I think we can be strong.
- Absolutely.
"I'm
so happy to be here!".
"Me too, my girlfriend!"
- Do you want to do this?
- Very well.
She was up for it.
I also have
a very good feeling with Max.
Just on looks.
Kind of a college hipster.
So and Joaquin are too close.
They clearly know where the idol is.
I spoke with Carolyn this morning...
So and Joaquin become dangerous?
I agree.
From then on, I had a strong bond
with Carolyn and with Max.
That's three people.
In a tribe of six!
As long as the three of us know we are united , we can move forward.
Crab on the menu!
Got it, got it!
We are working blues.
We saw the work to be done
and we all got into it.
It's going to work. We are like that.
They light a fire.
And here comes the fire!
We started a fire
in less than two hours.
The work blues tear everything apart.
- I like your tattoos.
- Thanks.
Is it just artistic or...?
This arm is family stuff.
And on my leg, a drawing of the ocean.
I'm really
happy with my tribe.
There's a tattooed girl,
and I like it,
because if you have so many
tattoos on your body,
it's because we want to express ourselves.
It facilitates the first contact.
- Do you want to read it?
- "Dear Natalie...
Even though I'll never see you again,
you will always be my big sister.
I like you. Bubba."
- Did you lose your sister?
- Yes, two years ago.
She lived downstairs.
I knock on his door on a Monday.
His car isn't here to go to work.
I wonder what's going on.
No way to open the door,
I broke a window.
I found her face down,
with blood all around.
I found my sister
in her blood two years ago.
When I arrived, I knew I could
touch the girls with this story.
It is reinforced by this tattoo,
which also tells it.
They know that I am telling the truth,
that I am sincere.
- Maybe we'll be your family.
- Absolutely.
My strategy, from day 1:
catch the girls.
Girls want to sit down
and let a man lead.
So I want to catch the girls,
be their leader and take them to the merge.
I pick up a piece of bamboo
and there is a scorpion.
It's not huge, but it can
surely do some damage with a sting.
- You want to eat it, you psycho?
- Oh yeah! I'm starving!
Protein!
So I cut off his tail...
Here he is harmless.
Are you going to eat
this thing full of sand?
Yeah, that's a first.
How does it taste?
Bam! Bottoms up!
It was disgusting.
T'es taré!
Did you eat a scorpion?
This is not good.
When you starve tonight,
and I'll have a scprion
in my stomach, don't blame me.
I knew from the start that any
opportunity to get protein,
I would take it.
But it turns out that
might not have been the best idea.
Oh, I will...
He vomited?
- How are you?
- Yeah.
- He vomits?
He ate a scorpion.
He pays it.
I'm having trouble there.
Maybe not the best idea.
But I am the type to seize
the opportunities that present themselves.
I'll run
as fast as I can
I'll hold
on as tight as I can
and ride that bull
as long as I can.
I saw the scorpion, seized the opportunity,
and paid the consequences.
I am like this.
It's just the weakness
leaving the body!
Our first coconut!
I wish I had a bongo there.
Too soft.
Les Sans Couleur is
a great little community.
Everything is going wonderfully.
Everything rolls, Abdul,
everything slides, Alice.
I want to kiss
everyone. I am so happy.
Jenn exudes sincerity.
It makes me feel comfortable. Completely.
Emotionally comfortable,
physically comfortable. That's great.
I also had
feathers in my hair.
Not that it creates an immediate bond,
- "my people!".
I saw your smile, your beautiful eyes,
- "instant bond".
Absolutely.
You and me, with our spirit,
our intelligence,
we could go all the way.
The feathered guy, direct,
he pulls me aside and says
that he thinks
we're kindred spirits.
"I like your smile.
I want to go all the way with you."
It is exactly as
I imagined it. And maybe more.
If you make friends
like I do,
breaking a bond is very difficult.
- It's nice to have a person...
- An anchor.
One of my biggest weaknesses
is my strong attraction to women.
Jenn brought a bit
of herself here, and so did I.
And I want to play
with someone like that.
When I want something,
I get it.
He plays a little more intensely
than his feathers would suggest.
Is it worth it
to play at being what he thinks
I am to him?
For now, it's worth
having allies, people on your side.
So smiling is my approach
with Vince, for now.
Let's raise it to that height.
At least it's not touching the ground.
Vince wanted to make the shelter
a certain way.
"As you want, man.".
Very "colorless" on my part.
But I have skills
in this area.
I worked in construction.
I built a lot of things.
We will use the long bamboos
for the main frame.
It's just the top of the canopy.
- We mount this and make the frame.
- It's a lot more work.
We put that over there,
we put three or four frames.
We put it there.
I just want to put a roof over it.
I don't really like being told
something that I know is wrong.
I know what to do
to make it safe.
So at some point,
politeness flies away.
You want to put that in,
so you have less space to fill?
Let's just put it together
and see what happens.
We're spontaneous, remember?
The spontaneous tribe.
Let's just continue.
See Joe only want to do it
his way,
it will surely cause concern.
We are the Colorless.
We have to collaborate.
Otherwise, it will be a problem.
- It's a bit high.
- What are we missing?
We need someone
to make the decisions.
Let's make decisions!
We'll need...
Three poles, that's what we said?
It's stupid, completely stupid!
- Why are you upset?
- I'm not mad.
- What are you worrying about?
- The base is going to be weak.
- I just want shelter.
- It's getting frustrating.
Dan starts to inflate me,
he climbs quickly in the towers.
He's the only one
who doesn't belong here.
Bamboo is hollow.
It won't hold.
The bamboo will break and we will fall.
I'm fat, it doesn't...
This way of speaking...
I can't stand it.
Dan, given his age, and being a man,
wants to prove to himself that he knows
what he is talking about.
But he's dealing
with people in their twenties,
and he's twice their age,
so he's going to have to listen to them.
But he doesn't have the
social skills to do that.
It's way too high.
Dan, what do you think?
- You look pensive.
- Not at all.
- Make a decision!
- No no no!
I'm the only one who wants that.
And then you change your mind.
You said below. Make a decision.
I agree, below.
So say it.
Don't stay silent.
If I say something, they
yell at me. If I shut up, the same!
- We discussed it before.
- I agree with you!
It all started with Lindsey.
Then I saw Sierra, Kelly react...
Now I'm changing tactics.
I stand aside and close it.
Do you want me to stay
or go get some wood?
As you wish.
I just want to make myself useful.
I'm going to get some wood.
I can't win.
Because whatever I do now,
they blame me.
My position in this tribe
soon became bad.
The bearded man is rather authoritarian.
We need to fire Harry Potter's grandfather .
I'm not doing well in this game.
It doesn't matter if I want to decide
or stay away from the decision.
- It's hard.
- I agree with you.
We took it out on you.
I noticed it today.
But don't feel alone.
I am your friend.
I hear you.
Mike is great. He really wants to
stay positive. It's a ray of sunshine.
He is the glue
that holds our unity together.
There's probably a million
people who wanted to be here.
- And here we are.
- It's still the best day of my life.
How do you know how to
light a fire without flint?
I saw this on YouTube,
I trained
every day before coming.
Joe says he knows how to make fire.
OK, Joe, go make a fire!
You say you can do it without flint,
I'll try to watch you.
I found some coconut shell , do you want some?
Yes, it's great.
- My sweet prince!
- My princess!
Stop that!
I really like Joe.
He has a great personality.
He is handsome.
Tall, muscular...
He should be on the cover
of romance novels.
Do you need
us to blow on the wood?
I do not think so.
- "Do you need to be blown on the wood?"
- I'll enlarge this hole.
This game means a lot to me.
I've always been a big fan.
I said I can make a fire,
I must ensure.
I see smoke.
Making a fire was
the best feeling in the world.
It was really good. I scored
points with the tribe.
- Need some water? I go.
- If you agree.
I already have a thing with Jenn,
but she seems to want
to ride Joe's wave.
It worries me,
because I don't trust him.
So I have to dig
this relationship with Jenn,
get a good idea
of ​​who she really is.
I want to ask you
a real human question.
Do you feel closer to Joe?
I don't flirt.
- He doesn't appeal to you?
- Nope.
- Not even a little?
I think Vince is jealous.
"So, do you like Joe?".
- But you love him...
- I love him as a person.
Just like you.
It's not that
I prefer him to you, not at all.
He apparently has a thing
for me and he suffers from it.
But I think I
know how to handle it.
It's you and me.
- Do you still want it?
- Yes.
And you?
Because you freak me out.
You don't seem to want it.
Yes, I really want it.
But I don't see enough evidence.
I really wish Jenn
was honest. But I don't feel it.
I feel it fake.
Are you less stressed now?
If you give me a hug.
Vince is the most paranoid here.
Dealing with him is not easy.
Calm down! He drives me crazy.
That's a hug!
And don't hug me
for ages. We stink!
OK? We stink.
Don't put that under my nose.
Our lovely home!
It doesn't look like anything.
It's not so bad. We have a roof.
We're going to work on it today.
The shelter is very ordinary.
I had probably
never slept so badly.
- What kind of shelter do you want to build?
- I would like a good mattress.
Our tribe is white collar people
giving orders.
But we're gonna have
to roll up our sleeves
and put us there with the
professional ethics of the Blues of Work.
Let's make a plan.
Repair the shelter
and focus on the fire.
Yes good idea.
- I'm going to slip in there,
- Yes.
This place lacks coverage.
- It's coming?
- Nope.
What are we doing wrong?
Go on!
Who knew it would be
so hard to make a fire?
No one knows how to make a fire.
None of us.
Why would we know?
White Collars!
We hire a blue worker
to light a fire for us.
I just need two minutes.
We won't have the fire.
But it's not big deal.
I'll go get the idol.
When So and Joaquin came back
with that bean bag,
I understood
that they had a clue.
So I watched them closely,
because if they are looking there,
she may be there.
So, it was obvious, she searched
this tree desperately.
From previous seasons, I've learned
what kind of stuff to look for.
It's bound to be something
that looks different.
I saw this funny tree,
and I thought... Good.
The perfect place
for a damn idol.
I have the idol!
Oh my God!
I open it and...
"You found the immunity idol."
What is magic,
is that everyone thinks
So and Joaquin have the clue,
and they are all still searching.
It's hilarious!
Over here, everyone!
Ready for your first
immunity test?
Fart!
Today, you will go down a ramp,
cross an obstacle,
to a large crate
containing a ladder.
You will have a choice:
open padlocks with keys
or undo knots.
Both will release the ladder.
With it, you will climb, cross
and descend from a platform
to another series of obstacles.
With the scale, you will then make
the most important decision of the test:
what a puzzle to solve.
There are three choices.
The first puzzle
has only five pieces,
but it requires
knowing how to take a step back.
If you are able,
you will solve it very quickly.
The second puzzle has ten pieces.
It asks to see things
more visually.
If that's how you think,
it'll be a piece of cake.
The last puzzle
- 50.
But it is also the most obvious.
The only problem with this puzzle
is 50 pieces.
They all require on average
the same time of realization.
By choosing the right person
and the right puzzle,
you can finish
way faster than average.
The first two tribes
to finish win immunity.
Here is the immunity idol.
If you have the idol,
you are safe from voting.
You will not go to the council
and cannot be eliminated.
The first tribe to finish wins this.
The second tribe to finish wins this.
Both have the same meaning.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be the first to be eliminated
- The War of the Worlds.
You are also playing for a reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
This will be really useful to you.
A huge fire-making kit.
Not as much,
but still effective. Flint.
Big stakes, and the right
to show off from the start.
One minute to get organized
and we'll get started.
On and go!
This is the first trial
- The War of the Worlds.
For reward and immunity!
Survivors, ready?
All attack the straw!
You have to lift your legs
on this second obstacle!
- How are you?
- Yeah.
Not as simple as it sounds!
A person on that scale
now.
The three tribes chose the keys
to unlock the padlocks.
No one took the knots.
It's Vince for the Colorless.
Lindsey for the Labor Blues.
- One turn and you change!
- And Joaquin for White Collar.
20 keys. Three work
for three different padlocks.
You can change at any time.
Joaquin hands over to So,
who attacks the knots.
First change strategy.
Lindsey pulls out
and sends Mike over the knots.
Come on, Vince, come back!
Vince waives on the keys.
He puts Joe on the knots.
Big changes right away!
The three tribes
are not afraid to change.
So is on the
white collar knots, and she's going for it.
Mike is on his fifth knot.
Joe on his sixth.
Joe made up a lot of time
for the Colorless.
Joe, you ski lifts!
Its good.
So, always in the lead.
Mike tries to catch up with her.
Joe, in second place
for the Colorless.
It's okay, Mike, don't panic!
The Blues of Work
are quickly outdistanced.
Last node for So.
Open!
Free that ladder and go!
The White Collars are in the lead.
Last knot for Joe. And There you go!
Open, the Colorless!
Grab that ladder and forward!
It's White Collar, Colorless
and Overalls.
Another five knots for Mike.
It's not over, give it your all!
There are three stages.
Climb, cross, descend.
White is now crossing.
The Colorless are mounted.
Overalls
are still on the knots.
- It's okay, Mike!
- Do not panic!
The White Collars have come down.
The Colorless fall a lot.
The White Collars are now negotiating
this new obstacle together.
You have to slide the ladder
through the gaps.
Mike finishes the last knot
for the Blues.
The Overalls
have their scale.
It's neck and neck.
The White Collars have passed
the first phase.
Come on, we can do it!
The work blues are mounted.
They must cross and come back down.
The Colorless lead.
The White Collars are second.
The Blues are trying to come back up.
The Colorless have cleared
the second hurdle.
Now the big decision.
Which puzzle will they choose?
The White Collars have passed.
They will choose their puzzle.
Come on, work blues!
5, 10 or 50 pieces. Choose!
The Colorless opt
for the middle puzzle.
The visual puzzle.
- Which?
- 50, 50!
White Collars choose
the simplest with the most coins.
Surprising, for these intellectuals!
Jenn. As expected, the Colorless
went with the visual puzzle.
No pressure, baby!
Shirin takes on the logic puzzle,
where there are no surprises.
They will never get there.
Lord, I'm sorry.
The working blues collaborate.
Jenn is already withdrawing.
Joe's turn.
Joe is on the puzzle
and he has the first piece.
Shirin works fast, tries
to figure out what this puzzle is.
When you understand that,
it will go very quickly.
The work blues have passed.
Choose your puzzle!
Third piece for Joe.
You have to go up.
The Blues don't understand
what to do with the ladder!
- Hold it!
- Their delay is increasing!
Joe skims over this difficult puzzle,
while Shirin struggles
with a seemingly simpler puzzle.
- The one in the middle!
- My fingers, my fingers!
Rodney picks up the ten-piece puzzle,
which requires a different perspective.
Another room for Joe.
- Shirin, are you okay?
- I know what it is, but...
Another room for Joe.
The Colorless
are very close to the goal.
Three pieces left for Joe.
No, more than two
for the Colorless!
A huge win right from the start.
Joe only needs one piece to
win
the first test
- The War of the Worlds.
It is done! The Colorless
gain reward and immunity!
There is still a place!
Sierra placed a first piece.
His tribe helps him a lot.
Shirin starts to panic,
she has made very little progress,
on what should be
the simplest puzzle.
Without color! Without color!
- Intervene!
- Shirin, frankly!
Shirin se retire, Max se lance.
Sierra, let me take your place!
Sierra retreats, Mike launches.
Losers go to the board.
Nobody wants that.
- Take a step back!
- Second room for Mike.
It's okay, Mike! Immunity
is ours if you get there!
It's Mike versus Max.
Return it!
Third piece for Mike.
Work Blues.
What a mouthful.
Mike is progressing well,
where Shirin was failing.
Will he have time to finish?
50 pieces
is a lot more than 10.
- Come on, baby!
- This is where we come back, baby!
The Blues were far behind, they fully returned.
809th
- We need that immunity!
- Come on, Max!
Max has done a third of the puzzle.
But will it be too little, too late?
Two pieces left for Mike.
I'm in the...
Mike is just one piece
away from winning immunity
for the Blues, protecting them
and sending the Whites to the council.
Turn it 180 degrees.
Yes like this!
And he does!
Worker's Blues gain
immunity and reward,
sending the White Collars to the council!
Holy comeback, Batman!
- It's never over before the end.
- It's clear!
Colorless, congratulations.
Immunity is yours. No
one will leave your tribe tonight.
Overalls, no
one will leave your tribe.
Without Color, come take
your reward and leave.
Good work.
Overalls,
it's not a big kit,
but it will do the job.
Here is a flint.
Take your things, return to camp.
No advice for you tonight.
White collar, one of you will be
the 1st eliminated at tonight's council.
A very interesting
afternoon awaits you.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Oh my God!
This ordeal was a disaster.
A desaster.
We led almost the whole way.
Shirin and Carolyn were
clearly the weak links.
We were leading.
We started the puzzle in 1st,
and from there, it went on a lollipop.
Shirin said from the start
that she was good at puzzles.
But we lost.
Which is not a problem,
because you have to refine yourself, right?
Want to discuss it?
We all know what to do,
but no one wants to start.
- Do we establish a schedule?
- That's so White Collar!
It will be a girl tonight,
we all know that.
I'm going to fetch water.
I need 17 glasses.
Because everyone will realize
that girls are weaker.
We all like each other,
but one of us is leaving tonight.
As simple as that.
- We seize the opportunity?
- Yes.
First of all, you tore
in your part of the test.
It was just untying knots.
What do you think, what is your...?
Who planted us? She.
Actually,
it's not my idea. Shirin?
- Are you thinking of her?
- I thought it was your idea.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm pissed at Shirin.
She speaks a lot.
But she knows how to make herself heard.
Carolyn was happy
to do nothing.
She didn't want to get involved.
As a businesswoman, I expect
people to deliver.
If you don't insure,
it's a problem.
Let's go for a walk.
Yes, Shirin was physically weak
and failed on the puzzle.
Carolyn plays it safe.
She doesn't volunteer.
So I'm leaning towards Carolyn.
If we say Carolyn,
I can convince Joaquin.
The hard part is convincing
the three guys to vote Carolyn.
Carolyn, how are you?
- Carolyn, are you okay?
- Yeah.
Shirin felt very bad
about her failure.
Yes. She did her best.
What annoys me is that Carolyn
will never put herself in danger.
She will stay in the middle.
It can work wonders
in this game.
So worries me.
She left to chat
with everyone.
To keep the tribe strong,
you have to target the weakest link.
They might want to take me out
because I'm the oldest.
So who are you voting for?
I know you are thinking
of Shirin or me.
I do not believe that.
Me, yes.
I already have someone in mind.
I've made my decision.
- I'm very...
- Your name didn't come up.
Are you saying I'm not
in danger tonight?
Not from me.
Word of New Yorkers.
- And I vouch for it.
- It's okay with me.
White collar workers tend
to know when someone is lying.
And I think So lied
about the clue about the idol.
I don't trust him.
She plays with me
like the others.
There, I do not feel calm.
Voila. Don't freak out,
but your name has come up.
But I want strength,
and you showed yours.
Lord. I knew I was targeted
and that So was involved.
I think So suggested my name.
It has to be a girl,
because guys are stronger.
So if it's not me,
it's one of those two.
- And the idols?
- I don't think any of them have it.
- I know it.
- Because?
I have the idol.
I bring it to the council.
There may be
absolutely no reason,
without even discussing it further,
so that you have to play it.
I have the hidden idol, so I know
I'm not leaving tonight.
But I don't want to
use it tonight.
I want to go there,
sure it won't be me.
So I have to get So out.
So militates for me to go out.
I say it must be her.
I think we should vote So.
Shirin, Carolyn and I have been playing
cards since day one.
Above all, I want
to be sure that I am in the majority.
She targets me, I vote against her.
The names mentioned for tonight
are Carolyn and So.
Carolyn stands out for her age.
That kind of little difference
can put you aside
in a small tribe of six.
On the other side, there is So.
She got in trouble
by lying to the tribe
about the choice made with joaquin.
What do you say?
You have to take the temperature
with the balèze. He is the unknown.
There's the three of us, there's
So and Joaquin, and there's the hefty guy.
What do you think of the situation?
On the one hand, you have people
who have lied to their teammates.
But it's complicated by the fact
that So has insured on the knots.
On the other side,
when I think of trust,
Carolyn thinks she's off to a bad start,
but I only think well of her.
My point of view,
is that we need a majority
and hard-working and loyal people.
If only the physical
were taken into account tonight,
that would be Carolyn,
because she's the oldest.
I look small,
but I'm very strong.
Moreover, if integrity takes precedence,
So will be in the sights.
But Carolyn scored points
for telling me she has the idol.
I don't think I
have to play it tonight.
Logic dictates
that Carolyn should leave first.
I know how
dangerous the idol can be.
Both outcomes
are possible tonight.
But I'm sure
someone will be shocked.
Behind you, torches.
Grab one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
Let's talk about the first dilemma.
Joaquin, you were chosen,
then you chose So.
You then had to make
a decision for the tribe.
How did it go?
There was a "deceit" box,
a "neutral" and an "honesty".
We chose "neutral".
Shirin, what did you think of all this?
Jeff, I'm a huge fan of the show.
It's season 30,
and their story is shaky.
I think there was a clue
about the immunity idol
and that they weren't honest
about what happened.
Max, you've known them
for 5 minutes,
and comes the first
confidence test.
Jeff, I'm not angry or disappointed
with them for making this decision.
I probably would have done the same.
I would have just lied better.
So, how do you react?
It hurts a little to hear that,
because yet, we four
are really strong.
- And I really hope...
- Are you four strong?
Oh, that's interesting.
Who is it?
Interesting.
So Carolyn and Shirin,
you're not in the core of 4,
which is not good
in a group of 6.
It's bad.
- "There is something going on."
- As a wise man said.
Carolyn, how do you react
to the existence of this core of 4?
I'm the oldest,
the first one thinks of:
"You will not be able to ensure
in the tests and the rest.".
And yet, Max and Shirin
have been with me since day 1.
So Max is lying to me?
- I think I'm in danger.
- In effect.
We were voting for you tonight.
- You're the weak link.
- You told me it was Shirin!
Yes, it had to.
Everyone agreed
to be told that.
I think you've been lying to me
since day one.
Yes, I didn't trust you.
OK. Good. I don't
trust you either.
You know these two women
are the weakest.
What is "weak"?
Because you undid some knots?
What a feat! We could all have
undone a few knots.
Tyler, are you okay?
If we took the lead
in the event, it's thanks to So,
thanks to her concentration,
she was able to overcome these 20 knots.
It was impressive
and it kept us in the game.
Ultimately,
we were trying to be a team,
and me to have a team spirit.
Yes, the game started, and Joaquin
and I had to make a choice.
We ended up getting caught.
But in the races,
I'm there for the team.
- I showed it today.
- Unlike me?
No. You did not offer yourself
at any time in the test.
You chose safety
and didn't take the lead.
Oh really?
'Cause I'm getting high on camp.
And by the way, I'm
as sporty as the others.
That they want to eliminate me today
plunges me into perplexity.
Tyler, with only 6 people,
you better make the right choice.
Jeff, our opponents
are the others.
If we choose badly, we will be weaker
physically, emotionally or...
In any case, weaker.
And we'll be right back here.
Max, how are you feeling
right now, before the vote?
I thank the Survivor gods
for giving me exactly what I
was hoping for for my 1st advice,
namely torrential rain
and drama galore.
So far you have both.
It's time to vote.
Joaquin, over to you.
I didn't trust you from
the start. You've been lying to me since day 1.
I hope
it's you and not me tonight.
The tribe must remain strong.
You are the lesser evil.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Carolyn.
Two votes Carolyn.
So.
Equality.
Two votes Carolyn,
two votes So.
So.
Three votes So, two votes Carolyn,
one vote left.
First person eliminated
White Collars vs Overalls
vs Colorless...
So.
Bring me your torch.
So, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Good luck!
You are players.
Do you play well?
Was it the right decision?
The future will tell.
You leave with flint.
Take your things,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
I'm going swimming, okay?
A White Collar adopts
the Colorless mentality.
Why did our camp
become a naturist camp?
What's going on?
- You mate.
- No, then really not.
And Nina goes after her whole tribe.
Do not touch me!
You would think that my tribe
would try to make me feel included.
This moment is my worst nightmare.
I would never have imagined
coming out first.
They made a mistake.
This tribe will destroy itself,
because they eliminated someone
who is an asset in the trials.
It really hurts.
I'm just trying to take the shock.