translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Well done,
you flipped Rodney.
- Who did I betray, you psycho?
- Yeah !
The game seemed simple.
It was all against Mike.
Mike is still only here
because he won immunities.
The next time he loses immunity...
See you soon !
But beneath the surface
there was much more.
We are looking for white.
- Dan gained an advantage.
- Yeah !
"You have acquired
an additional vote."
- Damn it !
- And Carolyn...
- ...just like Mike...
- God!
...had immunity idols.
I'm protected
by my immunity idol.
While, celebrating his birthday,
Rodney began to self-destruct.
I'm pissed at Mama C.
And those bastards who neglect me
on my birthday,
they won't go all the way.
Carolyn considered
teaming up with Mike.
Mike has a lot of power
in the game right now.
It may be time
to join forces.
At the last immunity test,
Carolyn won her second
consecutive immunity.
Carolyn wins individual immunity
for the 2nd time in a row!
- I'm so excited!
- Congratulations Mom!
On the advice...
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
- ...Mike played his idol,
- Thank you.
forcing the majority alliance
of the six to finally kill each other.
Twelfth person eliminated
and fifth member of the jury: Tyler.
In the end, they eliminated Tyler.
The tribe has spoken.
Now Mike has no
protection whatsoever.
There are six left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Congratulations, friends.
We are as numerous
as in our original tribes.
This advice was
very funny for me,
because I was finally able to break the six.
Four votes, huh!
Thank you friends !
'Cause I played
my idol tonight
I could be vulnerable.
So to secure my place,
I either have to find
another idol,
or gain all
remaining immunities.
Come on, baby,
what's the matter?
Do you want me to get involved?
I will do it.
Everyone wants
Mike gone.
'Cause Mike has already proven
that he is selfish and egocentric.
And you know what ?
It's to his credit.
He dropped an atomic bomb
and drew the immunity idol.
But all that Mike gets,
it's a free ride.
And that's all.
Do you want me to do it?
I have zero interest in working
with Mike at this point.
Ah! I win !
Mike must be the hero.
He's so arrogant
and condescending.
To hell
with his idol!
Once in a while,
people like to have a chance.
In the end,
I am in a position of strength,
because I have an advantage in the game,
namely an additional vote
in the council.
Besides, I'm allied
with Carolyn, Sierra,
And I really hope
that the five of us
let's get Mike out of this game.
You know I'm in, huh?
I hope.
I'm a little nervous.
I don't trust Dan,
cause he's the most dangerous
except for Mike in this game.
Because its advantage
is very dangerous.
- It's good for me.
- Good. Come here.
- I have only one word.
- OK.
I have my idol,
it can save me once.
But that won't get me to
the final quartet, the final trio.
So I need Mike
to consolidate...
God forbid, if
something happens on this side,
I want options.
The next vote will be crucial.
Dan has to go.
We have to fire Dan.
It's over, from my point of view.
- Yeah.
- He's next.
But there aren't enough of us
to take Dan out.
And it has its advantage.
It's an extra vote.
What do you mean ?
I don't understand.
- I do not follow you.
- An additional vote in council.
An additional vote.
He can just take out a vote.
He will have two votes.
I love my new
little angel, Carolyn.
Because I now know
what Dan's advantage is.
I hope she thinks she
can trust me
and that we can progress
and collaborate a little
to eliminate
greater threats.
It's huge, especially
with so few people.
- That's a massive advantage.
- And therefore deadly.
I'm right in the middle.
I got some stuff on fire around here
and stuff on fire over there.
Of course, I'll tell him
what he wants to hear.
But if Mike
doesn't win immunity,
He must go !
Bon sang!
Crucial vote. It could
be the turning point of the game.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
Today you will be divided
into two teams of three.
At my signal, you will cross
a series of obstacles,
untying knots
to open a passage.
Then, using a hatchet,
you will cut a rope,
releasing puzzle pieces.
When you have them all,
you will use them to
solve a word puzzle.
The first three to find
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
- Clearly.
The winning team
will board a helicopter
and take a helicopter tour
of that area where you live
for 33 days.
Then you will sit down and enjoy
a land-and-sea with wine.
And we'll take you back to camp
to resume the game.
In 33 days, Rodney, you're
the only one who didn't get a reward.
What inspires you?
I see stars, Jeff.
I wake up nauseous.
I've been on the same beach
for 33 days.
It's like being in jail.
I haven't experienced anything out of that.
But maybe someone
will pity me, 0 out of 5...
Wait, someone
would give you their reward?
Hey, who knows?
Maybe someone will.
I have to ask you:
do you consider it a due,
should we give you a reward
because you didn't get one?
The only one that mattered to me
was for my birthday.
And when a friend said she was going to
do something and didn't,
it hurt me a little.
Mike, something seems to be missing here:
if it's called a reward,
it's because you deserve
it and it gives you an advantage.
This is the concept of the game.
It's hard to see he's in pain,
he clearly is.
But all I can say
is win!
If you win, you are sure to go.
Alright, let's get to it. We draw
the teams and we start.
Well, we have our teams.
It's Dan, Sierra and Rodney
against Carolyn, Mike and Will.
Let's go. For the reward,
Survivors, ready?
Everyone descends quickly
the first hurdle.
We have to move forward together,
as a team.
Perfect equality, from the outset.
- Dan's having a little trouble.
- Come on !
Go on !
- Carolyn, you...
- When everyone's here, keep going!
Go, Blues!
Go, Reds!
Now the knots.
You have to undo them all.
And, Sierra et Rodney...
- Are you doing this one?
- It's good, it's good.
...are fast on these nodes.
When this is done,
the drawbridge will lower.
And There you go ! Ahead !
The Blues take the lead!
- Jump!
- The Reds, always on the knots.
And here we go!
Dan and Mike are on the hatchet.
Dan attacks with two hits.
Mike in two shots!
Puzzle pieces,
start putting them together!
Looking for letters.
If there is nothing,
you don't need it.
Here, communication is the key.
Everyone must collaborate.
- Rodney, you always gather!
- Rodney, come on!
Rodney, you always gather!
Everyone should be
on the same wavelength.
Throw the voids over there,
on the other side!
Come on !
The Blues think they have them all,
they will attack the puzzle.
Spread them!
Let's go, let's go!
The Reds think
they have all their pieces.
Let's go, let's go!
Looking for
an eight-word phrase.
"Want". "Want".
What could it be ?
Use your Survivor knowledge .
Think about how
we talk in Survivor.
The Reds guinea pig alongside,
looking for a lead.
It must be something
with "reward".
Lots of strategy
in this event
to prevent cheating.
- Good idea, actually.
- Here they are returning the letters.
Even I don't know
what progress the teams are making.
"What's needed" ?
"What's needed".
No, it doesn't fit.
After 33 days,
ELAPSED TIME: 30 Minutes
it's like it
's ELAPSED TIME: 30 Minutes
a foreign language
that you would never have encountered.
Both teams are totally dry.
Think "Survivor".
For 30 seasons, I repeat
the same 200 words,
again and again and again
and again and again.
I have to see a shrink
so much I repeat myself.
Can we buy a vowel, Jeff?
ELAPSED TIME: 45 Minutes
It's been going on for quite a while.
It is perhaps a bit
of a phrase "Blues of work".
It's not Harvard.
Don't worry too much
about your grammar grades.
"A reward
that will grant your wishes."
We've been solving this puzzle for an hour .
It kills me !
It's now officially
the longest word puzzle
in our history.
What are you playing for?
What's with it?
Did he just say it?
- Is that a clue?
- I'm not listening.
- He's giving us a hint.
- I say.
It's like those commercials.
"Order now,
and you will have this, with this, and this!"
"All-in."
"Everything necessary."
"With all..."
Oh my God ! Oh my God !
I see energy for the first
time in the event, smiles!
Dan doesn't know what to do.
They don't have it.
- Boom!
- On the ! On l'a !
- We have it !
- The Reds think they have it.
"A reward
with everything you need"!
win the reward!
- What do you say about that!
- Bou-ya!
Nice reward. Maybe
just what you need
to go to the end.
Carolyn. You stare at the Blues.
- Ready to go?
- Not yet.
It's terribly hard for me.
Are you wondering if you will
give your place to Rodney?
Yeah.
I spoke to him, I told him
that I would give it to him.
I haven't decided yet.
There are therefore
several levels to this debate.
On the one hand, it's a social game.
Give your seat to Rodney,
if you go all the way and he's sworn,
you can assume you have a vote.
On the other hand,
let Rodney go,
to fill the stomach,
to revive spiritually,
and that might be enough
for him to go all out and oust you.
Big, big decision.
Good. I will keep it.
Carolyn will keep her award.
Carolyn, Mike, Will,
get your things and go.
Enjoy your reward.
Congratulation.
I sympathize with Rodney,
who won no awards
I got them
all but one.
I hope he does
n't take it personally.
But that's also my
personal experience of Survivor.
Sierra, Dan, Rodney,
I have nothing for you. Take
your things, return to camp.
It's not every day
that we fly in a helicopter, Mama C!
No, not every day.
I had never flown
in a helicopter.
It was... epic.
It's breathtaking.
- We're approaching the volcano.
- Oh my God !
Have you ever been
this close to a volcano, Will?
Never.
It was breathtaking.
I'm really next
to a smoking volcano!
I will remember it all my life.
There is a Colorless,
a White Collar
- and a Work Overall.
- All together.
I've been lucky enough to participate
in a lot of awards.
But the helicopter ride
is the best.
There are no words
to say how fabulous it was.
Oh my God !
It's a joke!
We're going to fill our stomachs
today.
To the best reward
all time !
We land in the open field,
and on a table
there is all the food
that we may
want or need
to reach the end of the game.
Is it me, or are you feeling
your wits getting sharper too?
Yeah. My whole body
just woke up.
What do you think of
A final trio with the three of us
would be a solid trio.
- And we have all the colors!
- Yeah.
Colorless, White Collar,
Overalls.
Mike suggested that we could
form the final trio.
It was interesting,
because I could really
collaborate with him.
It would be a big blow,
but it could be
a mistake.
Will, would you
consider a final trio
with Mama C and me?
I already considered it with Mama C.
Not with you, because you're
public enemy number one.
You could win immunities
all the way to the final trio...
Yeah.
...and not have to worry.
Mike fidgets, knowing
he's next in danger.
He is the biggest threat
still in play.
And threats must be warded off.
All I can ask of you,
very sincerely,
It's: Please don't let
Rodney beat me in this game.
- Oh my God !
- That...
It would kill me.
He really needs to calm down.
It's starting to get
on my nerves.
He's the only Survivor
I remember
who tries to get rewards
by making people feel guilty.
- He wanted me to feel bad.
- Yes of course.
I thought, "Wait!
This is my reward, I won,
I go.".
Frankly, I don't know
exactly what Carolyn thinks.
I hope she is with me.
But if she is with them,
I have to win immunities
to stay in the game.
- This is exactly what we needed.
- Yeah.
Earth and sea !
Do you realize that land and sea
is my favorite menu?
Frankly,
I don't want to talk about it.
It exasperates me.
I'm just pissed, Sierra.
I can't believe
we didn't get it.
And Mama C, she goes as a reward
every other day.
Carolyn fucked me
on my birthday,
and she betrayed her word today.
I shouldn't take
it personally, but it is.
Once Mike is gone,
Mama C, you jump.
My revenge will be sweet.
It will be delicious.
Take a nap, rest.
Everyone is hungry.
Really hungry.
And since they left to
eat land and sea in a helicopter,
it would definitely be nice
to find something to eat.
That's something.
Looks like some kind of fruit.
I have no idea what it is,
but I'm going to find out, I'm
telling you!
I have good
news and bad news.
- The maid...
- What is that?
The good news:
I found fruit.
The bad:
I don't know if they are good.
What do you think it is?
I'm going to open them
so we can see inside.
All of a sudden, Dano comes back
with two large fruits.
It is really good.
It's like a reward!
It's like
an enchilada for Rodney!
What did I get?
I am in paradise !
Rodney is back.
This is what
food can do.
- I see it.
- Food brings people together.
And you brought me two watermelons.
I am ready to give everything
until the end, now.
Dan's watermelons
make Rodney feel good.
Once started again in my
manipulations, it will be piece of cake.
We agree.
Mike et Carolyn, hay?
- Absolutely.
- 100%, period, it's settled.
- Good.
We go out there and kick
that redneck out of this game.
So, Mike, do you want to face me?
Let's go, I'm ready.
I will face anyone,
in the game or in life.
I'm coming on top of you,
you better watch out.
We have mail!
Read it, girl!
"With good
hand-eye coordination,
you could take the right path.
Patience, skill and delicacy
will determine
who goes and who stays."
- Fart!
If Mike wins the next immunity,
again, the remaining five
will have to kill each other.
It is unthinkable. Mike can
not win the next immunity.
Full stop, that's it,
end of debate.
I don't know
how long I will have
to talk to Carolyn and you
today.
- Yeah.
- With the ordeal and all.
But Dan can only beat
those two.
- Yeah.
- I mean,
he won't take you or Carolyn.
This is our last chance
to get enough numbers.
'Cause if they take you out, then Carolyn,
these three guys will go all the way.
- They're the final trio.
- Yeah.
And if they all reach
the final trio...
How the hell will we choose?
Mike is not wrong.
Dan has an advantage.
He could use it against me
or to help me move forward.
You never know what Dan will do.
But if Mike
doesn't win immunity,
He must go. I don't want to
face him in the end.
That would be shooting me
in the foot.
- This is our only chance to get Dan out.
- Yeah.
He will end up losing, and then,
he will go away.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
- Yes !
- Clearly.
First of all, Carolyn,
- you have to give it back to me.
- I don't really want to.
- No more than last time.
- In effect.
- Win it again!
- OK.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will use grappling hooks
to retrieve three bags.
Each bag contains one ball.
When you have the three bags,
you will use one of the balls
to solve a maze.
The first person to finish
wins immunity,
ensures a one in five chance
of winning this game.
The losers: advice,
where after 35 days,
your dream of winning this game
will come to an end.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
- Let's go!
Alright, here we go. For immunity
and a guaranteed place
in the final quintet.
Survivors, ready?
First task:
use this grappling hook
to retrieve three bags.
You have to figure out how to
send the rope far enough.
Nice first pitch for Dan.
Dan has his first bag.
Nice throw for Will.
That will catch a bag.
Rodney has a bag, he brings it back.
Nice throw for Sierra.
Two in a row for Sierra.
Mike has his second bag.
Dan hangs up his second bag.
It's between Mike, Sierra and Dan.
Another great pitch from Mike.
Can he hang the bag?
And it's done!
Mike has his third bag!
Go to the maze!
Mike took the lead.
Go on !
Mike released his ball, he can
attack the maze. Let's go.
Meanwhile,
Rodney is struggling with his rope.
Nice throw for Carolyn.
It could be his second.
She has it.
Dan has his third bag.
Vas-y Dano !
Dan is coming now.
It's Dan versus Mike now.
Two Overalls
who started together.
Which doesn't mean
they want to finish it together.
Dan attacks the maze.
Mike and Dan are on the maze.
All the others are still in the bags.
Will has his second bag.
Sierra narrowly misses her 3rd.
Mike progresses through this maze.
Dan is progressing too.
Both are in the same place.
Dan has made up a lot of time.
He wins over Mike.
Mike falls into a hole,
he has to start over.
The difficulty
is that we hurry
to beat the other,
and when we hurry,
we make mistakes.
Mike again falls into a hole.
Sierra has her third bag.
- Sierra takes off.
- Come on Sierra!
Three Blues, Mike,
Sierra and Dan, on the maze,
while Rodney, Carolyn and Will
scramble to get
their last bag.
Dan loses his ball,
he has to start over.
Sierra gets on it.
Mike is doing a good job so far.
It is progressing very slowly.
Another nice move from Mike.
It would be a huge victory
to secure the final quintet...
I'm totally useless.
...so close to a million.
- Go Will!
- Will has his third bag.
Will can get on with it.
Mike, slowly but surely.
He knows how hard it is
to have to start over.
Dan accelerates, he tries to go up.
Sierra starts to take the hit.
Mike approaches the center circle.
But there are still pitfalls.
There is no easy path.
Another great move from Mike.
Mike is close now.
Carolyn, Rodney,
always on the bags.
Will loses his ball,
he has to start over.
Dan hangs on.
Sierra has made up a
lot of ground,
winner over Mike.
Mike is in the center circle.
All you have
to do is put it in the hole.
Can he make it, for a place
in the final quintet?
Mike goes in and out!
Sierra is now approaching
the center circle.
Mike enters and exits again!
She is in the center circle.
It's neck and neck!
Mike wins individual immunity,
- ensures a one in five chance!
- Thank you Jesus! Thank you Jesus!
Unbelievable.
Mike, come closer!
Third victory
in individual immunity.
This ensures Mike his place
in the final quintet.
As for you others,
Rodney, Dan, Carolyn,
after 35 hard days
sleepless nights,
physical and mental exhaustion,
your dream of winning this game
and the million dollars
will end.
Someone will be eliminated tonight
and join the jury.
Pack your things, get back
to camp, see you tonight at the council.
- Congratulation.
- Thanks.
In me, it was the national holiday,
right in Texas, the fireworks,
loud music,
because this little necklace, there,
means that
one of these five is leaving tonight.
And not me.
- Well done, Mike.
Lord God!
This guy is unbeatable.
It was... crazy.
Man, that was [???].
Mike gets away with it again.
Dan, start the fire again.
I'm going to fetch water.
Let's go.
The covenant always knew
the time would come
where we should kill each other.
And in my mind,
Carolyn was next.
She assured in the tests,
she has presence,
so she has to go.
Who are you voting for?
You already know it.
- Carolyn?
- Yeah.
They say it's you
- just so they get wind of it.
- No problem.
Looks like
Carolyn is going to go.
But Dan is very dangerous,
he has an advantage.
And if we play like from the beginning,
that we eliminate the threats,
maybe we should eliminate Dan.
We don't fidget,
we don't run all over the place.
One in five chance, honey.
- I'm going to get some wood.
- We're out of wood.
We're out of wood.
What do you say ?
- What ?
- Are you thinking about Dano?
It's okay with me.
He is the most dangerous at this stage.
Because he has an advantage.
Their little family
turns against Dan.
Everyone says: "vote Dan,
vote Dan, vote Dan!"
If they all want out Dan,
it makes me hesitate
and tell me:
"What if I got rid of
of one of them instead?".
Just to spoil their plans
and not follow their desire.
So this is it. I can
eliminate you tonight, easily.
Easily.
I don't even have to do anything.
Even if I vote
anything, you leave.
Your allies, YOUR allies,
are after you. What will you do ?
Because you're leaving tonight,
unless I intervene.
Mike has the audacity, the
absolute effrontery, to say to my face:
"I will save you,
I have the power to save you!".
- How would I believe you?
- OK.
- You don't give me anything.
But a part of me wonders
if there's a chance
they'll turn against me.
I have little time left
to use my advantage,
and I'd rather
go with a bang
than to let the opportunity pass.
Maybe, maybe not.
Maybe they're all lying to you.
I do not believe it.
- I do not believe it.
- OK.
You may be right, you
may be wrong.
Maybe I'll leave with an advantage
in my pocket and a great memory.
Dan was not wavering.
He was arrogant,
he doesn't think he's going to leave.
All I guess
is that Dan wants to take
Will and Rodney to the end,
because they are the only two
people he can beat.
And if I'm right,
and he doesn't leave tonight,
so it's one of the girls.
If the boys are telling the truth,
and honestly...
Honestly, I believe it.
- OK.
- That they're going to vote for Dan.
- Hey, I... Sorry.
- Oh my God !
- You fucked me up!
- Right, real quick.
Look who
's sleeping in the shelter.
- And...
- Rodney.
- Dan and Rodney.
- Yeah.
That says everything you need
to know about who's coming out.
Who feels safe or not.
This, this is Survivor's code
for "I'm not going anywhere,
I don't need to do anything".
Dan is voting for one of you tonight,
with the boys.
At 1,000,000%.
- Well...
- I think it's you tonight.
I'll let you finish talking,
I'll get my things.
I think he's delirious.
- It's paranoid.
- Yes !
That's what put him in
that position, originally.
I think so too.
I want to believe they vote Dan.
But if they don't?
What if Mike was right?
It could be a final trio
Will, Rodney and Dan.
They could bamboozle us.
And it's there
I'm
really racking my brains.
Do I trust them?
I don't want to
waste my idol.
And if I really believe
they're going to vote for Dan,
then I can keep it
for one more vote.
Now here are
the members of the jury.
Character, Joe, Jenn, Plan,
and Tyler,
eliminated at the last council.
Good. Let's talk about trust.
Mike. You return to
camp again with immunity,
which gives you the advantage
of not having to worry.
Based on what
you saw this afternoon,
would you say that there is
trust in this group?
There are clearly
one or two people
who feel less confidence,
in one way or another,
but they still have
a common enemy,
that guy.
A common enemy facilitates
rapprochements.
But tonight,
one of the five allies leaves.
So yes, it got a little hectic
today at the camp.
Rodney, where do you place
your confidence at this point?
On the 35th day, confidence...
Confidence...
Let me think.
I digress a bit here.
- Is this a sign of fatigue?
- Absolutely.
Your brain has to
strain to form a sentence,
- because you are exhausted?
- When you have very little to eat,
sometimes it can affect
your decision-making.
When you're really tired
and you go to a test,
that you cannot accomplish it
because the spirit is not there,
It can start to weigh, so...
What was the question again?
At this stage of the game,
do you trust
in the relationships
you have established?
On the 35th day, let's be honest,
we are always
with the same people.
I can't even spend
that much time with my mom
without wanting to strangle him,
and I love him.
So for a moment,
you think you can trust,
and suddenly, we could
form another alliance.
Ultimately, you have to
stay true to your allies
hoping they vote
well with you tonight.
Carolyn, are you
in a situation where you think:
"Yes, I trust
my allies.", or
"I can't afford
to trust anyone." ?
We want to trust
certain people,
but I know I am in danger tonight.
People tell you
what you want to hear,
because they are all scheming
to save their own skins.
So I'm very,
very nervous tonight.
Dan, does Carolyn have anything
to worry about, from a "threat" standpoint?
'Cause Mike's protected,
and Carolyn showed up too
rather dominating
in the tests.
Yes, Carolyn has proven
herself over and over again.
But she is not
the only one in danger.
My name came
up a lot in this game.
- Did you hear it this afternoon?
- Absolutely.
There is a time to act
and a time...
I know that answer sucks,
it's political waffle.
"You know, I can move
or not move."
Five of us are still there.
But that won't be the case
after tonight.
Will, are you alarmed
to hear Dan say that?
"I don't know what to do
and I'm afraid to act."
Absolutely, I'm very nervous.
Because the successive victories
of Mike reduce our workforce.
And Dan always has an advantage
of which we do not know
what effect it will have.
Rodney, having an advantage is a
lot of power.
But the trick
is knowing when to play it.
The advantage is
an intimidation tactic.
You can say you're going
to use it tonight, let it be known,
or keep it in your pocket
and not say a word.
And so you're at five
and you use it,
and it becomes more worrying,
because you could leave.
Sierra, have we talked a lot about
benefits and idols,
and if they would be played tonight?
Jeff, there's
tons of talk.
You don't want to leave
with something in your bag
that you could have played.
And yet, Dan, you could
play bully, as Rodney used to say,
and try to get
one more day.
Yes, tonight would be
a great night to use it.
But what about the next tip?
It could be even better,
bring me into the final quartet.
Frankly,
I'm like a metronome.
I go back and forth.
But I don't know
what is the right thing to do.
It's time to find out
what's going to happen tonight.
It's time to vote.
Dan, over to you.
I will count the votes.
Excuse me !
Jeff, I'd rather go with a bang
than to let the opportunity pass.
I'd like to play my advantage,
please.
The advantage gained
by Dan at auction.
It is an additional vote,
which has the same weight as the others.
In other words, tonight
there will be seven votes.
Dan, go vote.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
I'm not gonna
take any chances, Jeff.
I'm not leaving tonight.
This is an immunity idol.
Votes against Carolyn
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Does not count.
Carolyn. Does not count.
Dan. Un vote Dan.
Thirteenth person eliminated
and sixth member of the jury.
Dan. Bring me your torch.
Good luck.
Dan, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
This game started with three tribes.
35 days later, there are still
representatives of each of them.
Victory is within everyone's reach.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time, in
a special two-hour finale...
Why did you
hide your idol from us?
Why did everyone vote for me?
Four days from the end,
it's a clash of worlds.
Let the games begin !
Don't lower your head.
I'm afraid.
We go all the way.
It's a million dollar mistake.
Join us for the final,
Wednesday May 20!
I had three things to do here.
Number 1, have fun.
Number 2,
remember me.
Number 3,
hopefully win this game.
But having accomplished
the first two,
that's fine with me, that's how it is.
Every day here was
a dream come true.
I played well
and respectably.
I have no regrets.