>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> A GREAT JOB THAT YOU ALL
FLIPPED ON.
>> WHO DID I FLIP ON, YOU WHACK
JOB?
>> Jeff: THE GAME SEEMED
SIMPLE: IT WAS EVERYONE VERSUS
MIKE.
>> THE ONLY REASON MIKE IS STILL
HERE IS HE WON IMMUNITY.
THE NEXT IMMUNITY HE LOSES,
SMELL YOU LATER.
>> Jeff: BELOW THE SURFACE
THERE WAS SO MUCH MORE.
DAN WON AN ADVANTAGE IN THE
GAME.
>> YOU BOUGHT YOURSELF AN EXTRA
VOTE.
>> HE'S GOT THE IDOL.
>> Jeff: AND BETH CAROLYN AND
MIKE HAVE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS.
>> I'M SAFE WITH MY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> Jeff: MEANWHILE, BIRTHDAY
BOY RODNEY STARTED TO
SELF-DESTRUCT.
>> I'M REALLY PISSED ON MAMA C.
THEY'RE A BUNCH OF SCUMBAGS THAT
NEGLECTED ME ON MY BIRTHDAY.
THEY ABOUT IT GOING TO THE END.
>> Jeff: CAROLINE CONSIDERED
TEAMING UP WITH MIKE.
>> HE HAS A LOT OF POWER.
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO THINK ABOUT
TEAMING UP WITH HIM.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN WON THE
SECOND IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IN A
ROW.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL --
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
MIKE PLAYED HIS IDOL, FORCING
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE OF SIX TO
FINALLY TURN ON EACH OTHER.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, TYLER.
IN THE END THEY VOTED OUT TYLER.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NOW MIKE IS LEFT WITHOUT ANY
PROTECTION.
SIX ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> CONGRATULATIONS, GUYS.
>> WE ARE NOW WITH THE ORIGINAL
NUMBERS THAT WE ALL STARTED
WITH.
>> TRIBAL TONIGHT WAS A WHOLE
LOT OF FUN FOR ME BECAUSE I
FINALLY GOT THE BRECK APART THE
SIX.
FOUR VOTES, HEY.
THEY, GUYS.
BECAUSE I PLAYED MY IDOL
TONIGHT, I COULD BE VULNERABLE,
SO TO SECURE MY SPOT, I EITHER
NEED THE FIND ANOTHER IDOL, OR I
NEED TO WIN IMMUNITY THE REST OF
THE TIME OUT.
COME ON, BABY.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> YOU WANT ME TO GET IN THERE?
LY.
>> EVERYBODY WANTS MIKE GONE.
BECAUSE MIKE HAS ALREADY PROVEN
THAT HE'S SELFISH AND THAT HE'S
SELF-CENTERED.
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING, TO HIS
CREDIT.
HE DROPPED AN ATOMIC BOMB AND HE
WHIPPED OUT THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, BUT ALL MIKE GETS IS ONE
FREE PASS, AND THAT'S ALL HE'S
GETTING.
>> YOU WANT ME TO GET DOWN
THERE?
>> I HAVE ZERO INTEREST IN
WORKING WITH MIKE AT THIS POINT.
>> HA.
I WIN.
MIKE, HE HAS TO BE THE HERO.
IT'S THE FACT THAT HE'S SO
ARROGANT AND HE'S SO CON
DESCENDING.
TO HELL WITH MIKE.
TO HELL WITH HIS IDOL.
SOMEBODY ELSE LIKES A SHOT,
MIKE.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, I'M IN
THE POSITION OF POWER, BECAUSE I
HAVE AN ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME,
WHICH IS AN EXTRA VOTE AT THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BESIDES, I TEAMED UP WITH
CAROLYN, SIERRA, WILL AND
RODNEY, AND I GENUINELY HOPE THE
FIVE OF US CAN TAKE MIKE OUT OF
THIS GAME.
>> YOU'RE ALL IN, RIGHT?
>> I HOPE SO.
I DON'T TRUST DAN BECAUSE DAN IS
THE BIGGEST THREAT OTHER THAN
MIKE IN THIS GAME BECAUSE DAN'S
ADVANTAGE IS A VERY HUGE THREAT
IN THE GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M IN.
MY WORD IS MY BOND.
>> I HAVE MY IDOL, SO THAT SAVES
ME FOR ONE, BUT THAT DOESN'T GET
ME TO THE FINAL FOUR OR THE
FINAL THREE.
SO I NEED MIKE TO SOLIDIFY, GOD
FORBID SOMETHING HAPPENS WITH,
YOU KNOW, THAT SIDE.
I WANT OPTIONS.
THE NEXT VOTE IS GOING TO BE THE
PIVOTAL VOTE.
>> YEAH.
>> DAN HAS TO GO.
>> WE GOT TO GET DAN OUT.
>> HE'S DONE, IN MY OPINION.
HE GOES NEXT.
>> BUT WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
NUMBERS TO GET DAN OUT, AND HE
HAS HIS ADVANTAGE.
HIS ADVANTAGE IS AN EXTRA VOTE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M NOT FOLLOWING.
>> HE'S GOT AN EXTRA VOTE AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> IT GIVES HIM AN EXTRA VOTE,
SO HE CAN JUST PULL A VOTE?
>> HE GETS TWO VOTES.
>> I LOVE MY NEW LITTLE ANGEL
CAROLYN, BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT
DAN'S ADVANTAGE IS NOW.
I HOPE THAT SHE FEELS LIKE SHE
CAN TRUST ME AND THAT WE CAN
MOVE FORWARD AND WORK TOGETHER A
LITTLE BIT TO ELIMINATE SOME
BIGGER THREATS IN THIS GAME.
>> THAT'S HUGE, ESPECIALLY WHEN
NUMBERS ARE THIS LOW.
THAT'S A MASSIVE ADVANTAGE.
>> THAT'S WHY IT IS SO DEADLY.
I AM SMACK IN THE MIDDLE.
I GOT STUFF WORKING HERE AND I
GOT STUFF WORKING OVER.
THERE I'M GOING TO TELL HIM WHAT
HE WANTS THE HEAR, BUT IF MIKE
DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY, GOT TO GO.
>> MAN, OH, MAN, OH, MAN.
>> CRITICAL VOTE.
IT COULD BE THE TURNING POINT OF
THE GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES, WE ARE.
>> FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, WE'LL
DIVIDE INTO TWO TEAMS OF THREE.
>> ON MY GO, YOU WILL RACE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES,
UNTYING KNOTS TO RELEASE A
DOORWAY.
YOU'LL THEN USE A HATCHET TO
CHOP A ROPE, WHERE YOU'LL SEE
PUZZLE PIECES.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE PUZZLE
PIECE, YOU'LL USE THEM TO SOLVE
A WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST THREE TO GET IT RIGHT WIN
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: TODAY THE WINNING
TEAM WILL BE PICKED UP BY A
CHOPPER, TAKEN ON A HELICOPTER
TOUR OF THIS COUNTRY THAT YOU'VE
BEEN LIVING IN FOR THE PAST 33
DAYS.
YOU'LL THEN TOUCH DOWN AND ENJOY
A NICE SURF AND TURF WITH WINE,
BE TAKEN BACK TO CAMP THE RESUME
THE GAME.
33 DAYS IN, RODNEY, YOU'RE STILL
THE ONLY GUY WHO IS YET TO WIN A
REWARD.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT THAT?
>> I'M SEEING STARS, JEFF.
I WAKE UP NAUSEOUS.
I'VE BEEN ON THE SAME BEACH FOR
33 DAYS.
I FEEL LUKE I'VE BEEN IN JAIL
AND I HAVEN'T ABLE TO EXPERIENCE
NOTHING WITH NOBODY OUT HERE,
BUT MAYBE SOMEBODY WILL FEEL FOR
ME, 0 FOR 5.
>> Jeff: WAIT, SOMEBODY WILL
WHAT, GIVE YOU THEIR REWARD?
>> MAYBE.
>> Jeff: SO IS IT ENTITLEMENT
THAT YOU'RE FEELING THAT PEOPLE
SHOULD GIVE YOU A REWARD?
>> THE ONLY ONE I CARED ABOUT
WAS MY BIRTHDAY, AND WHEN A
FRIEND SAID THEY WERE GOING TO
DO SOMETHING FOR ME AND THEY
DIDN'T, IT KIND OF HURT ME A
LITTLE BIT.
>> Jeff: MIKE, ANOTHER BIG
ELEMENT OF THIS THAT SEEMS TO BE
MISSING IS THE REASON IT'S
CALLED A REWARD IS YOU EARNED IT
AND IT GIVES YOU AN ADVANTAGE.
THAT IS THE DESIGN OF THE GAME.
>> IT'S TOUGH TO SEE HIM
STRUGGLING.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY STRUGGLING, BUT
THE ONLY THING I CAN SAY IS WIN.
IF YOU WIN, YOU GO ON IT
GUARANTEED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO IT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR TEAMS.
LET'S GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TEAMS.
IT IS DAN, SIERRA AND RODNEY
TAKING ON CAROLYN, MIKE AND
WILL.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
EVERYBODY MAKES IT DOWN QUICKLY
THROUGH THE FIRST OBSTACLE.
GOT TO MOVE TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
DEAD EVEN RIGHT OUT OF THE
START.
DAN STRUGGLING A LITTLE WITH
THIS.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON.
>> Jeff: ONCE EVERYBODY'S
THERE YOU CAN MOVE ON.
GO, BLUE!
GO, RED!
NOW YOU'RE WORKING ON THE KNOTS.
YOU GOT TO UNTIE EVERY SINGLE
KNOT.
IT IS DAN, SIERRA AND RODNEY.
>> GOT IT, GOT IT.
>> Jeff: WORKING QUICKLY
THROUGH THE KNOTS.
ONCE YOU HAVE THEM, THAT
DRAWBRIDGE WILL DROP.
BLUE NOW IN THE LEAD.
RED STILL WORKING ON THEIR
KNOTS.
THERE YOU GO.
MOVE THROUGH.
IT IS DAN AND MIKE WORKING WITH
THE HATCHET.
DAN ATTACKS IT IN TWO CHOPS.
MIKE IN TWO CHOPS.
PUZZLE PIECES, START COLLECTING.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR LETTERS.
IF IT IS BLANK, YOU DON'T NEED
IT.
THIS IS WHERE COMMUNICATION IS
KEY.
EVERYBODY GOT TO WORK TOGETHER.
RODNEY, YOU'RE STILL COLLECTING.
EVERYBODY NEEDS TO BE ON THE
SAME PAGE.
>> THROW THE BLANK ONES THAT
WAY, THE OTHER WAY.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> BLUE THINKS THEY HAVE THEM
ALL, THEY'RE GOING TO START
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
>> JUST LAY THEM OUT.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: RED NOW THINKS THEY
HAVE ALL THEIR PIECES.
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: SIX-WORD PHRASE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
WHAT COULD IT BE?
USE YOUR "SURVIVOR" KNOWLEDGE.
THINK ABOUT HOW WE TALK ON
"SURVIVOR."
RED LOOKING NEXT DOOR TRYING TO
GET A CAN CLUE.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
ABOUT REWARD.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF STRATEGY IN
THIS CHALLENGE TO TRY TO PREVENT
CHEATING.
>> GOOD CALL ACTUALLY.
>> Jeff: NOW TRIBES ARE
TURNING LETTERS OVER.
I DON'T KNOW THE PROGRESS THAT
EITHER TEAM IS MAKING.
>> WHAT IS NEXT?
>> Jeff: 33 DAYS IN.
IT IS AS IF THIS IS A FOREIGN
LANGUAGE BEING LEARNED FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
BOTH TEAMS ABSOLUTELY STUMPED.
START THINKING "SURVIVOR."
IT'S BEEN ON FOR 30 SEASONS.
I SAY THE SAME 200 WORDS OTHER
AND OVER AND OVER AND OVER AND
OVER.
I'M IN THERAPY I SAY THE WORDS
SO OFTEN.
>> CAN WE BUY A VOWEL, JEFF?
>> Jeff: YOU'VE BEEN OUT HERE
A LONG TIME.
>> IT'S A W.
>> Jeff: MAYBE THIS IS A BIT
OF A BLUE COLLAR PHRASE.
THIS IS NOT HARVARD.
STOP BEING WORRIED ABOUT BEING
GRADED FOR YOUR GRAMMAR.
WE ARE ONE HOUR INTO SOLVING
THIS PUZZLE.
>> IT'S KILLING ME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS NOW
OFFICIALLY THE LONGEST WORD
PUZZLE IN OUR HISTORY.
WHAT IS IT YOU ARE PLAYING FOR?
WHAT DOES IT COME WITH?
>> I'M NOT EVEN LISTENING TO
HIM.
>> HE'S GIVING US HINTS.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: IT'S ONE OF THOSE
COMMERCIAL, AND IF YOU ORDER NOW
YOU GET THIS WITH THIS AND THIS.
COMPLETE SET.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED.
>> YES!
OH, MY GOD.
I SEE ENERGY FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN THIS CHALLENGE, SMILES.
DAN DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THEY DON'T HAVE IT.
>> WE GOT IT.
WE GOT IT.
WE GOT IT!
>> Jeff: RED THINGS THEY HAVE
IT.
A REWARD WITH ALL THE FIXINGS!
MIKE, CAROLYN, WILL WIN REWARD.
>> COME TALK TO ME.
>> BOO-AYE!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
CAROLYN, MIKE, WILL, NICE
REWARD.
THIS COULD BE JUST WHAT YOU NEED
TO GET TO THE END.
CAROLYN, YOU'RE STARING AT THE
BLUE TEAM.
YOU GOOD TO GO?
>> NOT YET.
THIS IS SO FRICKEN HARD FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: CONSIDERING WHETHER
OR NOT TO GIVE UP YOUR REWARD TO
RODNEY.
I TALK TO THIS GUY.
I TOLD HIM I WOULD GIVE IT TO
HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M WANTING TO
DO YET.
>> Jeff: SO YOUR DEBATE IS
LAYERED.
ON THE ONE HAND, THIS IS A
SOCIAL GAME.
YOU GIVE YOUR REWARD TO RODNEY.
YOU GET TO THE END, YOU MIGHT
GET ONE VOTE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, YOU LET
RODNEY ON THIS, FILL UP HIS
BELLY, SPIRITUALLY GET
REAWAKENED, AND IT COULD BE WHAT
HE NEEDS TO GO TO THE END AND
GET RID OF YOU.
IT'S A BIG, BIG DECISION.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO KEEP IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
CAROLYN'S GOING TO KEEP HER
REWARD.
CAROLYN, MIKE, WILL, GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
HEAD OUT, ENJOY YOUR REWARD.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> I DO FEEL BAD FOR RODNEY THAT
HE HASN'T WON A REWARD AND I'VE
BEEN ON EVERY REWARD EXCEPT FOR
ONE.
I HOPE HE DOESN'T TAKE IT
PERSONALLY, BUT THIS IS MY
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE, AS WELL.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, DAN, RODNEY,
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> IT'S NOT EVERY DAY YOU GET TO
FLY IN A HELICOPTER, MAMA C.
>> NO, NOT EVERY DAY.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN ON A
HELICOPTER BEFORE IN MY ENTIRE
LIFE, AND IT WAS EPIC.
IT'S BREATHTAKING.
I CAN SEE A CENTRAL KAY KNOW
COMING UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU EVER BEEN THIS CLOSE TO A
VOLCANO, WILL?
>> NEVER.
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY STUNNING.
I'M GOING BY A VOLCANO THAT'S
STEAMING RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU GOT A NO COLLAR YOU GOT A
WHITE COLLAR AND YOU GOT A BLUE
COLLAR.
>> WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
>> I'VE BEEN BLESSED TO BE ON A
LOT OF DIFFERENT REWARDS, BUT
THE HELICOPTER RIDE IS THE
GREATEST REWARD EVER.
THERE'S NO WORDS TO DESCRIBE HOW
FABULOUS IT REALLY IS.
OH, MY GOD.
>> WE'RE GOING TO FILL OUR
BELLIES TODAY.
ALL RIGHT.
THE BEST REWARD EVER.
>> WE LAND IN THIS OPEN FIELD,
AND THERE'S THIS TABLE AND IT'S
GOT ALL THE FOOD ON IT THAT YOU
COULD EVER WANT OR NEED TO GET
YOURSELF THROUGH THE REST OF
THIS GAME.
IS IT JUST ME OR CAN YOU ALL
ACTUALLY FEEL YOUR MIND GETTING
SHARPER?
>> MY WHOLE BODY JUST WOKE UP.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS
FINAL THREE?
>> I THINK FINAL THREE WITH THE
THREE OF US IS A STRONG FINAL
THREE.
AND WE GET EVERY COLLAR, RIGHT
IN NO COLLAR, WHITE COLLAR, BLUE
COLLAR.
MIKE BROUGHT UP THE PITCH THAT
MIKE, ME AND WILL COULD GO TO
THE FINAL THREE, WHICH WAS KIND
OF INTERESTING BECAUSE I COULD
REALLY WORK WITH HIM.
IT WOULD BE A BIG MOVE, BUT IT
MIGHT BE THE WRONG MOVE.
>> WILL, COULD YOU ENTERTAIN A
THOUGHT OF A FINAL THREE WITH ME
AND MAMA C?
>> I'VE ALREADY ENTERTAINED WITH
MAMA C.
YOU I HAVEN'T.
YOU'RE PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE.
YOU COULD IMMUNITY UP UNTIL THE
FINAL THREE AND HAVE NOTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT.
MIKE'S SCRAMBLING BECAUSE HE
KNOWS HE'S NEXT ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
HE'S THE BIGGEST THREAT STILL IN
THE GAME.
AND YOU GOT TO GET RID OF YOUR
BIGGEST THREAT.
>> THE ONLY THING I CAN ASK YOU,
MAN, HONEST TO GOD, PLEASE DO
NOT LET RODNEY BEAT ME IN THIS
GAME.
>> THAT WILL KILL ME.
>> HIS ASS GOT TO CALM DOWN.
HE'S STARTING TO GET ON MY
NERVES.
>> HE'S THE ONLY SURVIVOR THAT'S
TRIED TO GUILT EVERYONE INTO
GIVING HIM A REWARD.
>> HE WAS TRYING TO MAKE ME FEEL
BAD.
>> COURSE HE WAS.
>> BUT THEN I'M LIKE WAIT, IT'S
MY REWARD, I WON IT.
I'M GOING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHERE CAROLYN'S
HEAD IS AT.
I'M HOPING IT'S WITH ME, BUT IF
SHE'S NOT WITH ME AND SHE'S WITH
THEM, I HAVE TO WIN THE IMMUNITY
TO STAY IN THIS GAME.
>> THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT WE
NEEDED.
>> YEAH.
SURF AND TURF, MAN.
>> SURF AND TURF IS MY FAVORITE
MALE.
>> I DON'T WANT THE TALK ABOUT
IT, HONESTLY.
IT AGGRAVATES ME.
>> I'M JUST SO MAD, SIERRA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE DIDN'T GET
THAT TODAY.
MAMA C HAS WON A REWARD EVERY
OTHER DAY.
SHE SCREWED ME ON MY BIRTH DAY
AND WENT BACK ON HER WORD TODAY.
GUESS WHAT, MAMA C, MAYBE I
SHOULDN'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY,
BUT I AM.
ONCE MIKE'S OUT OF HERE, YOU'RE
OUT OF HERE.
REVENGE IS GOING TO BE SWEET.
REVENGE IS GOING TO BE VERY
SWEET.
>> EVERYBODY'S HUNGRY, REALLY
HUNGRY, AND GIVEN THE FACT THAT
THEY'RE ON A SURF AND TURF
HELICOPTER REWARD, IT SURE WOULD
BE NICE TO FIND SOME FOOD,
SOMETHING.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND OF A
FRUIT.
I DON'T HAVE THE SLIGHTEST IDEA
AS TO WHAT THESE THINGS ARE, BUT
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT IF THEY
ARE RIGHT NOW.
>> GOOD NEWS AND BAD NEWS.
THE GOOD NEWS IS I FOUND FRUIT.
THE BAD NEWS IS, I DON'T KNOW
WHETHER IT'S ANY GOOD OR NOT.
>> WHAT FRUIT DO YOU THINK THAT
IS?
>> I'M GOING TO CUT IT OPEN SO
WE CAN LOOK INSIDE OF IT.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN DANO COMES
OUTS WITH TWO BIG PIECES OF
FRUIT.
>> THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
>> I FEEL LIKE I GOT A REWARD.
THAT'S LIKE THE WHOLE ENERGY
DIDN'T ENCHILADA FOR RODNEY.
WHAT HAVE I HAD?
RODNEY IS BACK.
THIS IS WHAT FOOD CAN DO TO YOU.
FOOD BRINGS PEOPLE CLOSER
TOGETHER AND YOU JUST BROUGHT ME
TWO WATERMELONS, BRO.
THESE WATERMELONS DAN FOUND ARE
MAKING RODNEY FEELING SOME TYPE
OF WAY.
ONCE I START FEELING LIKE, THIS
IT'S A RAP OUT HIRE.
>> SO WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME
BEIGE, MIKE AND THEN CAROLYN,
RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY, 100%, PERIOD, END
OF STORY.
>> LET'S JUST GO OUT THERE AND
GET THE REDNECK OUT.
>> SO, MIKE, YOU WANT TO BATTLE
WITH ME, LET'S DO IT.
I'M READY TO BATTLE.
I'LL GO TOE TO TOE WITH ANYBODY
IN THIS GAME IN REAL LIFE.
I'M COMING AT YOU FULL FORCE.
WHEN I COME AT YOU FULL FORCE,
BABY, YOU BETTER WATCH OUT.
>> WE GOT TREE MAIL.
>> READ IT, GIRL.
>> WITH GOOD HAND-EYE
COORDINATION, YOUR PERFORMANCE
COULD AMAZE.
PATIENCE, SKILL AND A DELICATE
TOUCH DETERMINES WHO LEAVES OR
STAYS.
>> BRING IT ON, BABY.
>> BRING IT ON.
>> IF MIKE WINS THE NEXT
IMMUNITY, ONCE AGAIN THE FIVE
THAT ARE LEFT ARE GOING TO HAVE
TO THE TURN ON EACH OTHER.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT.
MIKE CANNOT WIN THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
PERIOD.
END OF STORY.
END OF DISCUSSION.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME
I'LL HAVE TO TALK TO CAROLYN AND
YOU TODAY AFTER THE CHALLENGE
AND EVERYTHING, BUT DAN CAN ONLY
BEAT THOSE TWO.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO, I MEAN, HE'S NOT TAKING
YOU AND HE'S IN THE TAKING
CAROLYN.
TODAY'S OUR LAST CHANCE TO HAVE
NUMBERS, BECAUSE IF THEY TAKE
YOU OUT, IF THEY TAKE CAROLYN
OUT, THOSE THREE GO TO THE END.
>> THEY'RE THE TOP THREE.
>> YEAH, AND IF ANY OF THEM MAKE
THE TOP THREE...
>> MAKE MAKES A GOOD POINT.
DAN DOES HAVE AN ADVANTAGE.
HE MAY USE IT TO GET ME OUT.
HE MAY USE IT TO HELP ME GET
FURTHER.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT DAN'S GOING
TO DO, BUT IF MIKE DOESN'T WIN
IMMUNITY, HE HAS TO GO.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SITTING NEXT
TO MIKE IN THE END.
THAT WOULD BE SHOOTING MYSELF IN
THE FOOT.
>> IT'S OUR ONLY SHOT TO GET
THEM OUT OF THE GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> HE'S BOUND TO LOSE, AND AT
THAT POINT, HE WILL BE GOING
HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
CAROLYN.
I GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
>> DON'T REALLY WANT YOU TO.
>> Jeff: YOU DIDN'T WANT ME TO
LAST TIME.
>> NEW YORK I DIDN'T.
>> Jeff: WIN IT AGAIN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE GRAPPLING HOOKS TO
RETRIEVE THREE BAGS.
EACH BAG CONTAINS A BALL.
WITNESS YOU HAVE ALL THREE BAG,
YOU WILL USE ONE OF THOSE BALLS
TO SOLVE A TABLE MAZE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
FIVE SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AFTER 35 DAYS, YOUR DREAM OF
WINNING THIS GAME WILL FALL
SHORT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO IT.
>> LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A GUARANTEED
SPOT IN THE FINAL FIVE,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOUR FIRST TASK, USE THAT
GRAPPLING HOOK TO RETRIEVE THREE
BAGS.
YOU GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
THE ROPE FAR ENOUGH.
DAN WITH A NICE FIRST TOSS.
DAN HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
WILL WITH A NICE TOSS.
THAT WILL GRAB A BAG.
WILL HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
MIKE HAS HIS FIRST BAG.
SIERRA HAS HER FIRST BAG.
CAROLYN WITH HER FIRST BAG.
RODNEY HAS A BAG.
HE'S DRAGGING IT BACK.
SIERRA WITH ANOTHER NICE TOSS.
SIERRA TWO IN A ROW NOW.
MIKE HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
DAN SNAGS HIS SECOND BAG.
IT'S NOW MIKE, SIERRA AND DAN.
THERE'S MIKE WITH ANOTHER GOOD
TOSS.
CAN HE HOOK IT?
AND HE DOES.
MIKE HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
START HEADING TO THE MAZE.
IT IS MIKE NOW IN THE LEAD.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MIKE NOW HAS HIS BALL
FREE.
HE CAN START ON THE TABLE MAZE.
HERE HE GOES.
RODNEY HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
WITH HIS ROPE.
CAROLYN WITH A NICE TOSS.
THIS COULD BE HER SECOND.
SHE'S GOT IT.
DAN HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
>> GOOD BOY, DANO.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES DAN NOW.
IT IS DAN AND MIKE NOW, TWO BLUE
COLLARS STARTED THIS GAME
TOGETHER.
DOES NOT NECESSARILY MEAN THEY
WANT TO FINISH TOGETHER.
DAN NOW WORKING ON THE TABLE
MAZE.
IT IS MIKE AND DAN WORKING ON
THE MAZE.
EVERYBODY ELSE STILL GATHERING
BAGS.
WILL HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
SIERRA JUST MISSES WITH HER
THIRD BAG.
MIKE MAKING SOME PROGRESS IN
THIS MAZE.
DAN MAKING SOME PROGRESS.
THEY'RE BOTH IN THE SAME SPOT
RIGHT NOW.
DAN HAS MADE UP A LOT OF TIME ON
THIS PUZZLE, NOW GAINING ON
MIKE.
MIKE DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK TO THE
START.
THE TRICKY PART IS YOU'RE TRYING
TO RUSH TO BEAT THE OTHER GUY,
AND WHEN YOU RUSH, YOU MAKE
MISTAKES.
MIKE DROPS AGAIN.
SIERRA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
SIERRA GOING TO GET IN ON THIS
NOW.
>> GOOD GOING, SIERRA.
>> Jeff: THREE BLUE COLLARS,
MIKE, SIERRA AND DAN WORKING ON
THE TABLE MAZE.
RODNEY, CAROLYN AND WILL
STRUGGLE TO GET THEIR FINAL
BAGS.
DAN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
SIERRA NOW GETTING IN ON IT.
MIKE HAS BEEN DOING A NICE JOB
THIS ROUND.
HE'S BEEN VERY GOING VERY SLOW.
ANOTHER NICE MOVE BY MIKE.
THIS WOULD BE A HUGE WIN TO
GUARANTEE YOURSELF A SPOT IN
THAT FINAL FIVE.
THAT MUCH CLOSER TO THE MONEY.
>> GO, WILL.
WILL HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
WILL NOW CAN GET IN ON IT.
MIKE SLOW AND STEADY.
KNOWS HOW PAINFUL IT IS WHEN YOU
DROP AND HAVE TO START AGAIN.
DAN RUSHING NOW, TRYING THE
CATCH UP.
SIERRA STARTING TO GET THE HANG
OF IT.
MIKE GETTING CLOSER TO THAT
INNER CIRCLE BUT STILL PITFALLS
AWAIT.
NO EASY PATH THROUGH THIS MAZE.
NIKE WITH ANOTHER MIKE MANEUVER.
MIKE GETTING VERY CLOSE NOW.
CAROLYN, RODNEY STILL LOOKING
FOR THEIR BAGS.
WILL DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
DAN HANGING IN THERE.
SIERRA HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
GROUND IN THIS CHALLENGE.
GAINING ON MIKE.
MIKE IS IN THE INNER CIRCLE.
JUST GOT TO DROP IT IN THAT
FINAL HOLE.
CAN HE DO IT FOR A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FIVE MIKE WAS IN THE HOLE.
HE'S BACK OUT.
SIERRA NOW GETTING CLOSER TO
THAT INNER CIRCLE.
MIKE IN AND OUT ONCE AGAIN.
HERE COMES SIERRA.
SHE'S IN THE INNER CIRCLE.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
MIKE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FIVE!
>> THANK YOU, JESUS.
THANK YOU, JESUS.
>> Jeff: MIKE, COME ON OVER.
THIRD INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN.
GUARANTEES MIKE A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FIVE.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, WILL,
SIERRA, RODNEY, DAN, CAROLYN,
AFTER 35 TOUGH DAYS OF SLEEPLESS
NIGHTS, PHYSICAL AND PENAL
EXHAUSTION, YOUR DREAM OF
WINNING THIS GAME AND $1 MILLION
WILL FALL SHORT.
SOMEBODY IS GOING TO BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT AND JOIN THE JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT ON TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> INSIDE OF ME IT WAS LIKE THE
FOURTH OF JULY IN THE MIDDLE OF
TEXAS, FIREWORKS GOING OFF,
MUSIC PLAYING LOUD BECAUSE THIS
LITTLE NECKLACE RIGHT HERE SAYS
ONE OF THOSE FIVE ARE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
AND IT'S NOT ME.
>> HOLD ON, MIKE.
>> GOOD LORD.
THIS GUY IS UNBEATABLE.
>> THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> MIKE LIVES ANOTHER DAY.
>> I KNOW.
YOU GET THE FIRE STOKED.
I'LL GO GET SOME WATER.
>> WORKING ON IT.
>> THE ALLIANZ ALL THE KNEW THAT
EVENTUALLY WE WERE GOING TO HAVE
TO TURN ON EACH OTHER.
AND IN MY PECKING ORDER, CAROLYN
WAS NEXT ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
SHE'S KICKED ASS IN CHALLENGES.
SHE'S BEEN PERSONABLE, SO SHE'S
GOT TO GO.
>> WE ALREADY KNOW WHO WE'RE
VOTING FOR.
>> CAROLYN?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> CAROLYN?
>> JUST DON'T LET HER GET WIND
OF IT.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S CAROLYN,
BUT DAN IS A HUGE THREAT AND HAS
AN ADVANTAGE, AND IF WE'RE
PLAYING THIS GAME LIKE WE'VE
PLAYED IT THE WHOLE TIME TO GET
RID OF THE HUGE THREATS, MAYBE
WE NEED TO GET RID OF DAN.
>> NO SCRAMBLING, NO RUNNING
AROUND.
>> ONE IN FIVE CHANCE, BABY.
>> HERE COMES MIKE.
>> WANT TO SEE IF I CAN FIND
SOME.
>> WE'RE OUT OF FIREWOOD.
>> DANO.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
>> HE'S REALLY THE BIGGEST
THREAT IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE HE HAS AN ADVANTAGE.
>> THEIR LITTLE FAMILY IS
TURNING ON DAN.
EVERYONE IS SAYING VOTE DAN,
VOTE DAN, VOTE DAN.
WELL, IF THEY ALL WANT DAN GONE,
IT MAKES ME PAUSE AND THINK,
WHAT IF I GET RID OF ONE OF THEM
INSTEAD JUST TO COMPLETELY MESS
WITH THEIR PLANS AND NOT GO
ALONG WITH WHAT THEY WANT DONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL, I CAN GET
RID OF YOU TONIGHT EASILY.
EASILY.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
I CAN THROW MY VOTE AWAY AND
YOU'RE GOING HOME.
YOUR ALLIANCE, YOUR ALLIANCE, IS
GUNNING FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO ABOUT IT
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING HOME
TONIGHT UNLESS I CHANGE
SOMETHING.
>> MIKE HAS THE AUDACITY, THE
UNMITIGATED GALL TO LOOK AT ME
AND SAY, I CAN SAVE YOU.
I HAVE THE POWER TO SAVE YOU.
>> HOW CAN I BELIEVE YOU IN
YOU'RE GIVING ME NOTHING.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT PART OF ME IS ACTUALLY
WONDERING IF THERE IS A CHANCE
THEY'LL TURN ON ME.
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME TO USE
MY ADVANTAGE, AND I'D RATHER GO
DOWN SWINGING THAN STAND THERE
AND WATCH THE THIRD STRIKE GO BY
ME.
>> MAYBE, MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE EVERYBODY'S LYING TO YOU.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> OKAY.
>> MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE I'LL GO HOME WITH AN
ADVANTAGE IN MY POCKET AND AN
AWESOME SOUVENIR.
>> DAN WAS NOT SHAKEN AT ALL.
HE WAS UPPITY.
HE DOESN'T FEEL LIKE HE'S GOING
HOME.
THE ONLY THING I CAN FIGURE OUT
IS DAN WANTS TO TAKE WILL AND
RODNEY TO THE END BECAUSE THOSE
ARE THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE HE CAN
BEAT, AND IF I'M RIGHT AND HE'S
NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT, IT'S ONE
OF THE GIRLS.
>> IF THE BOYS ARE TELLING THE
TRUTH, WHICH I HONESTLY BELIEVE
THEY ARE...
>> RIGHT.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR
DAN.
>> HEY --
>> OH, MY GOSH, YOU SCARED THE
LIVING CRAP OUT OF ME.
>> REALLY FAST.
LOOK WHO IS IN THE SHELTER
SLEEPING.
>> DAN AND RODNEY.
THAT TELLS YOU EVERYTHING YOU
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT A TRIBAL
NAME.
WHO FEELS SAFE, WHO DOESN'T?
THAT RIGHT THERE IS THE
"SURVIVOR" CODE FOR "I AIN'T
GOING NOWHERE.
I DON'T NEED TO DO NOTHING."
DAN IS VOTING ONE OF YOU TWO
TONIGHT WITH THE BOYS.
ONE MILLION PERCENT.
I THINK IT'S YOU TONIGHT.
I'M GOING TO LET YOU GUYS FINISH
TALKING.
I'M GOING TO GRAB MY STUFF.
I --
>> I MEAN, I THINK HE'S PSYCHOO.
HE'S PARANOID.
THAT'S WHAT GOT HIM IN THIS
POSITION IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> I THINK SO.
>> I WANT TO BELIEVE THEY'RE
VOTING FOR DAN, BUT WHAT IF THEY
DON'T VOTE FOR DAN?
WHAT IF MIKE IS RIGHT?
IT COULD BE WILL, RODNEY AND DAN
FINAL THREE.
THEY COULD BE SCREWING US OVER
AND THIS IS WHERE I AM REALLY
RACKING MY BRAIN IS DO I TRUST
THEM?
I DON'T WANT THE WASTE MY IDOL,
AND IF I REALLY BELIEVE THEY'RE
GOING TO VOTE FOR DAN, THEN I
CAN SAVE IT FOR ONE MORE VOTE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
HALI, JOE, JENN, SHIRIN AND
TYLER VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT TRUST.
MIKE, YOU GO BACK TO CAMP AGAIN
WITH IMMUNITY, WHICH GIVES YOU A
VANTAGE POINT OF NOT HAVING TO
WORRY AS MUCH TONIGHT.
SO BASED ON WHAT YOU SAW THIS
AFTERNOON, WOULD YOU SAY THIS IS
A GROUP OF PEOPLE FOR WHOM THERE
IS SOME TRUST?
>> I DEFINITELY THINK THERE'S A
COUPLE PEOPLE THAT PROBABLY
AREN'T FEELING AS TRUSTWORTHY OR
AS TRUSTED, BUT THEY STILL HAVE
A COMMON ENEMY, THIS GUY RIGHT
HERE.
IF YOU HAVE A COMMON ENEMY, IT'S
EASY TO BOND WITH OTHER PEOPLE,
BUT TONIGHT ONE OF FIVE OF THEIR
ALLIANCE IS GOING HOME.
SO, YEAH, THERE WAS SOME
SCRAMBLING GOING ON TODAY AT
CAMP.
>> Jeff: RODNEY, WHERE IS
TRUST FOR YOU AT THIS POINT IN
THE CAME?
>> DAY 35, TRUST IS... TRUST
IS... LET ME THINK.
I'M KIND OF LIKE OUT OF MY MIND
RIGHT NOW A LITTLE BIT.
>> Jeff: IS THIS A SIGN OF
FATIGUE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: SO YOUR BRAIN REALLY
HAS TO WORK HARD TO TRY TO FORM
A SENTENCE BECAUSE YOU'RE JUST
DEPLETED.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE VERY LIMITED
FOOD, SOMETIMES THAT CAN AFFECT
YOUR DECISION MAKING.
WHEN YOU'RE VERY FATIGUED AND
YOU GO INTO AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AND YOU CAN'T REALLY
PERFORM BECAUSE YOUR HEAD IS NOT
THERE, IT CAN GET A LITTLE HARD
ON YOU.
SO WHAT WAS THE QUESTION AGAIN?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: ARE YOU AT A POINT IN
THE GAME WHERE YOU TRUST IN THE
RELATIONSHIPS YOU'VE MADE?
>> WELL, IT'S DAY 35.
LET'S BE HONEST, YOU JUST ARE
AROUND THE SAME PEOPLE 24/7.
I CAN'T EVEN BE WITH MY MOTHER
24/7 WITHOUT WANTING TO RING HER
NECK AND I LOVE HER TO DEATH.
SO ONE MINUTE YOU THINK YOU CAN
TRUST THEM.
ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY COULD BE
FORMING ANOTHER ALLIANCE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU HAVE
TO GO WITH THE PEOPLE YOU DID
FORM YOUR ALLIANCES WITH AND
HOPEFULLY THOSE ARE THE VOTES ON
YOUR SIDE TONIGHT.
>> CAROLYN, ARE YOU IN A
SITUATION WHERE YOU THINK, YEAH,
I TRUST MY ALLIANCES OR I JUST
CAN'T AFFORD TO TRUST ANYBODY?
>> YOU WANT TO TRUST THE PEOPLE
WHO YOU WANT TO TRUST, BUT I
KNOW MY HEAD'S ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK TONIGHT, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT YOU
WANT TO HEAR BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL
SCRAMBLING TO SAVE THEMSELVES,
SO I AM VERY, VERY NERVOUS
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: DAN, DOES CAROLYN
HAVE A REASON TO BE CONCERNED
FROM A THREAT STANDPOINT BECAUSE
YOU CAN'T TAKE OUT MIKE AND
CAROLYN HAS SHOWN HERSELF TO BE
PRETTY DOMINANT IN CHALLENGES.
>> YEAH, CAROLYN HAS DEFINITELY
PROVEN HERSELF AGAIN AND AGAIN,
BUT SHE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE WITH
HER HEAD ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
MY NAME HAS COME UP A LOT IN
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: DID YOU HEAR IT THIS
AFTERNOON?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND THERE'S A TIME TO MAKE A
MOVE AND THERE'S A TIME... I
KNOW THIS ANSWER SUCKS BECAUSE
IT'S A POLITICAL WAFFLING
ANSWER, I CAN MAKE A MOVE OR I
CAN STAY WHERE I AM.
YOU KNOW, FIVE OF US ARE STILL
HERE.
BUT NOT AFTER TONIGHT WE WON'T
BE.
>> Jeff: WILL, DOES THAT ALARM
YOU WHEN YOU HEAR DAN ACTUALLY
SAY IT, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
AND I'M AFRAID TO DO ANYTHING.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'M VERY NERVOUS BECAUSE MIKE
CONTINUING TO WIN IMMUNITY IS
DIGGING INTO OUR NUMBERS AND DAN
STILL HAS AN ADVANTAGE IN THIS
GAME, BUT WE HAVE NO CLUE WHAT
IT'S GOING TO DO.
>> Jeff: AND RODNEY, HAVING AN
ADVANTAGE GIVES YOU A LOT OF
POWER, BUT THE REAL TRICK IS
WHEN DO YOU PLAY IT?
>> THE ADVANTAGE IS LIKE A
STRONG-ARM TACTIC.
YOU CAN SAY I'M GOING TO USE IT
TONIGHT AND LET IT BE KNOWN, OR
YOU CAN KEEP IT IN YOUR BACK
POCKET AND NOT SAY A WORD ABOUT
IT.
SO NOW YOU'RE AT FIVE AND YOU
USE IT AND IT GETS MORE SCARY
BECAUSE IT COULD BE YOU THAT'S
GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, HOW MUCH TALK
HAS THERE BEEN ABOUT ADVANTAGES
AND IDOLS AND WILL THEY BE
PLAYED TONIGHT?
>> JEFF, THERE WAS TONS OF TALK.
YOU DON'T WANT TO WALK OUT THE
DOOR WITH SOMETHING IN YOUR BAG
YOU COULD HAVE PLAYED.
>> Jeff: AND YET, DAN, YOU
COULD STRONG ARM, LIKE RODNEY
SAID, AND TRY TO BUY YOURSELF
ANOTHER DAY.
>> TONIGHT WOULD BE AN EXCELLENT
NIGHT TO USE IT.
BUT THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL
MIGHT BE EVEN BETTER.
IT MIGHT GET ME TO THAT FINAL
FOUR.
HONEST TO GOD, I'M LIKE A
METRONOME GOING BACK AND FORTH
UK BACK AND FORTH, BACK AND
FORTH, BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
RIGHT THING TO DO IS.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S TIME TO
FIND OUT WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
>> EXCUSE ME.
JEFF,'D RATHER GO DOWN SWINGING
THAN STAND THERE AND WATCH
STRIKE THREE GO BY.
I'D LIKE THE PLAY MY ADVANTAGE
PLEASE.
>> Jeff: THE ADVANTAGE THAT
DAN BOUGHT IN THE AUCTION WAS
ANOTHER VOTE.
THE VOTE HAS THE SAME POWER AS
ANY OTHER VOTE CAST AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHICH MEANS TONIGHT
THERE WILL BE SEVEN VOTES CAST.
DAN, GO CAST IT.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> I'M NOT TAKING A CHANCE,
JEFF.
I'M NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR CAROLYN WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE CAROLYN.
[APPLAUSE]
DOES NOT COUNT.
CAROLYN.
DOES NOT COULD.
>> WHEW!
>> Jeff: CAROLYN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DAN.
THAT'S ONE VOTE DAN.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
SIXTH MEMBER OF THE JURY, DAN.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: DAN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, WE STARTED THIS GAME WITH
THREE TRIBES, 35 DAYS LATER,
REPRESENTATIVES FROM EACH TRIBE
STILL LEFT IN THE GAME.
IT IS ANYBODY'S GAME TO WIN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FROM SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON A
SPECIAL TWO-HOUR SEASON FINALE.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US YOU
HAD THE IDOL.
>> WHY DID YOU VOTE FOR ME?
>> Jeff: WITH ONLY FOUR DAYS
LEFT, WORLDS COLLIDE.
>> LET THE GAMES BEGIN.
DO NOT PUT YOUR HEAD DOWN.
>> I'M SCARED.
>> WE'RE GOING ALL THE WAY.
>> THIS IS A $1 MILLION MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: JOIN US FOR THE
FINALE
>> I CAME OUT HERE WITH THREE
THINGS THE DO.
NUMBER ONE, HAVE FUN.
NUMBER TWO, BE REMEMBERED.
NUMBER THREE, HOPEFULLY WIN THIS
GAME.
BUT AS LONG AS I MADE THE FIRST
TWO, I'M STILL OKAY WITH THAT.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT GOES.
EVERY DAY I WAS HERE WAS A DREAM
COME TRUE FOR ME.
I PLAYED A GOOD GAME.
I PLAYED A RESPECTABLE GAME.
I GOT NO REGRETS.