>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... JOE, SHIRIN AND
JENN WERE STUCK ON THE BOTTOM.
>> WHATEVER.
>> Jeff: AGAINST THE MAJORITY
ALLIANCE OF SEVEN.
>> THE ONLY WAY I'M GOING TO GET
TO THE END IS BY TAKING BIG
RISKS.
>> Jeff: BUT SHIRIN HAD A PLAN
THE SHAKE THINGS UP.
SHE WARNED MIKE ABOUT A SECRET
ALLIANZ WITHIN THE SEVEN.
>> CAROLYN'S GOT WILL IN HER
POCKET, RODNY AND TYLER IS WITH
THEM.
>> SHIRIN'S SMART ENOUGH TO
REALIZE THERE'S A GROUP WITHIN
OUR GROUP.
I SEE IT.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT
CAME DOWN TO TWO NO COLLARS, JOE
VERSUS JENN.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JOE.
IN THE END THEY TOOK OUT JOE,
THE BIGGEST THREAT IN
CHALLENGES.
JOE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> I'VE GOT A REALLY SOLID PLAN.
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
THIS: WE GET MIKE OUT RIGHT NOW,
RIGHT AFTER THIS IMMUNITY?
WE CAN GET HIM OUT RIGHT NOW AND
HE'LL NEVER KNOW.
>> MIKE, ARE YOU CRAZY?
>> WE GOT RID OF JOE LAST NIGHT,
THE BIGGEST THREAT IN THE GAME,
AND RIGHT OFF THE BAT RODNEY
APPROACHED ME WITH A NEW TACTIC,
WHICH IS WHY DON'T WE STOMP ON
MIKE BEFORE HE PULLS HIS NUMBERS
AND HIS CHARISMA AND JUMPS ON
US, AND RODNEY'S IDEA COULD BE A
REALLY GOOD IDEA.
>> WE'LL COME BACK AND REVISIT
IT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE FINAL
FOUR.
>> I OVERHEARD RODNEY, WILL,
TYLER AND MAMA C, AND THERE'S
DEFINITELY BEEN A POWER SHIFT IN
THIS GAME.
RODNEY HAS FLIPPED ON THE BLUE
COLLARS.
HE IS NO LONGER IN MY ALLIANCE.
SO I KNOW THAT THEY ARE COMING
FOR MY HEAD.
THAT'S WHY I'VE GOT TO START
DOING A LOT OF WORK STARTING
TODAY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME TO THE "SURVIVOR"
AUCTION.
>> WHEW.
THIS MORNING IN TREE MAIL YOU
EACH RECEIVED $500.
BIDDING WILL BE IN INCREMENTS OF
$20, THERE IS NO SHARING OF
ITEMS AND THE AUCTION WILL END
WITHOUT WARNING.
IF YOU SEE SOMETHING YOU LIKE,
BID ON IT.
SHALL WE GET STARTED?
>>
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
FIRST ITEM WILL REMAIN COVERED.
>> $20.
>> Jeff: $20 TO JENN.
$60 THE WILL.
>> $80.
>> Jeff: $80 TO JENN.
>> $100.
>> Jeff: WILL AT $100.
SOLD TO WILL.
COME ON UP.
>> PROBABLY GRILLED ASS OR
SOMETHING.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: HERE'S WHAT YOU
BOUGHT, WILL.
>> WHOA.
>> Jeff: IT'S A NOTE.
YOU CAN TAKE IT BACK TO YOUR
SEAT AND OPEN IT AND READ IT.
>> IT'S A CLUE.
>> OH, YOU JUST BOUGHT YOURSELF
OUT OF THIS AUCTION.
PICK UP YOUR PERSONAL ITEMS AND
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: YOU REALLY DO NOT
KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT IN THE
AUCTION.
>> EAT UP FOR ME, GUYS, PLEASE.
>> Jeff: WILL, TAKE THE NOTE
WITH YOU.
HEAD BACK DOWN THE BEACH.
>> BYE, WILL.
>> SEE YA.
>> HOLY COW.
ARE YOU GOING TO KICK ANY OF US
ELSE OUT?
>> Jeff: YOU NEVER KNOW.
>> I WILL NOT FORGIVE YOU.
>> Jeff: LET'S MAKE THIS A
LITTLE MORE FUN AND SHOW YOU
WHAT IT IS.
FRIED CHICKEN AND WAFFLES.
>> $300.
>> WOW.
OUT OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: $300?
YOU WANT THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO SHIRIN.
$300.
>> I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: THE MOST EXPENSIVE
FRIED CHICKEN YOU HAVE EVER
BOUGHT.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO BID FOR AN
ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME.
FOR ME IT WAS MATTER OF GO FOR
IT.
>> Jeff: ENJOY.
SHIRIN SAID, I DIDN'T WANT TO
WAIT AND TRY TO GO FOR AN
ADVANTAGE.
SIERRA, YOU'RE NODDING YOUR
HEAD.
>> A LOT OF US FEEL LIKE WE'RE
IN DANGER, SO I THINK A COUPLE
PEOPLE WILL HOLD OFF.
>> Jeff: ANYBODY HERE WANT TO
SAY STRAIGHT UP, I'M NOT BIDDING
ON FOOD?
SO, DAN, CAROLYN, MIKE, YOU ARE
NOT INTERESTED IN FOOD.
YOU'RE WAITING FOR AN ADVANTAGE.
>> I CAME INTO THIS GAME KNOWING
THAT WHENEVER IT WAS "SURVIVOR"
AUCTION TIME THAT I'LL STARVE TO
DEATH.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
>> OH, MY GOD, $100, $100.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO JENN.
>> SOME IF NOT ALL OF MY
ALLIANCE HAVE FLIPPED ON ME.
>> $100.
>> Jeff: SOLD TO SIERRA.
RODNEY, THIS IS WHAT YOU HAVE.
>> I HAVE STEAK, BABY.
>> NO FOOD IN THIS WORLD IS
WORTH WHAT AN ADVANTAGE IS WORTH
IN THIS GAME TO ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, SINCE IT SEEMS THAT
EVERYBODY WHO WANTED FOOD HAS
SOME FOOD, LET'S GET TO WHAT YOU
GUESS ARE WAITING FOR, THE
ADVANTAGE.
BUT BEFORE WE PUT THE ADVANTAGE
UP, LET ME TEMPT YOU WITH
SOMETHING ELSE, LOVE FROM HOME.
♪ YEAH ♪
LOVE NOTES FROM HOME WRITTEN FOR
YOU AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME TO
HELP YOU GET TO THE END.
MORE VALUABLE THAN AN ADVANTAGE?
>> YOU GUYS, IN THE PAST,
WHATEVER THE HIGHEST BID ENDED
UP BEING, JEFF LET EVERYBODY
ELSE BUY IT FOR THAT HIGH BID.
I'M SERIOUS.
>> SOMEONE JUST DO $20.
>> $20.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, GOING TO BID
FOR $20?
GOING ONCE, GOING TWICE, SOLD TO
SIERRA.
COME UP, $20.
WE SET THE PRICE AT $20, WHICH
MEANS ANYBODY ELSE WHO WANTS TO
BUY THEIR LOVED ONE LETTERS FROM
HOME FOR $20 CAN DO SO, WHICH
PUTS DAN, CAROLYN AND MIKE IN AN
INTERESTING POSITION.
>> LET'S ALL DO IT FOR $20, AND
THEN WE FIGHT FOR THE ADVANTAGE
FAIR AND SQUARE WITH $480.
WHO IS IN?
>> PLEASE.
>> Jeff: WHO WANTS IT?
EVERYONE'S IN FOR $20.
>> GO.
>> LET'S GO.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY COMING UP.
ALL RIGHT.
FIND YOUR NOTE.
>> I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO TRICK YOU GUYS.
>> PLEASE, PLEASE.
>> WHY WOULD I DISPLACE TRUST?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DAN.
GRAB YOURS.
YOU SAW IT SITTING THERE.
WHY ARE YOU ALREADY SO
EMOTIONAL?
>> I LOVE MY WIFE LIKE YOU READ
ABOUT, AND ON DAY TWO IT WAS MY
WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
>> Jeff: BUT YOU JUST BOUGHT
IT FOR $20.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NICE.
MIKE, DID YOU...
>> YOU DIDN'T DO IT.
>> WOW.
>> MIKE DIDN'T DO IT?
>> HE DIDN'T DO IT.
I KNEW YOU WEREN'T GOING TO DO
IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GIVE MINE BACK.
THAT'S COOL.
I'LL GIVE IT BACK.
>> SO MUCH FOR YOUR TRUST, MIKE.
>> I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T DO IT.
THAT WOULDN'T GO WITH MY
CONSCIENCE.
THAT GOES AGAINST WHO I AM AS A
PERSON.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO IT'S CLEAR YOU HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR IT.
THIS IS AN ADVANTAGE IN THE
GAME.
>> $480.
$480.
>> Jeff: MIKE, CAROLYN, DAN
ARE IN.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON UP.
$480.
IT'S EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
DO, RIGHT?
>> DRAW STRAWS.
>> THE WINNING ROCK IS WHITE.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> Jeff: ON THREE EVERYBODY
REVEAL.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR WHITE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> YEAH, BABY!
>> Jeff: DAN HAS WON THE
ADVANTAGE.
YOU GUYS CAN HAVE A SEAT.
DAN, YOU JUST BOUGHT AN
ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME.
KEEP IT SEALED.
WHEN YOU GET BACK, OPEN IT IN
PRIVATE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
THIS AUCTION IS OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> I TOLD MIKE TO GO BEFORE ME.
HE TURNED AROUND AND WENT BACK.
AND IT BROKE MY HEART.
AND HE MIGHT HAVE JUST LOST MY
TRUST.
>> I'M SO UPSET.
I SPENT $100 TO GET MYSELF OUT
OF THE FOOD AUCTION AND I WAS
LIKE, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
I WAS DEVASTATED.
SO I'M WALKING BACK TO CAMP, AND
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN I'M LIKE,
OH, MY GOD, THERE'S A CLUE FOR
ME.
WOW.
I JUST GOT A MAP AND IT SAYS,
"TRIBE CAMP" AND IT HAS AN X AND
IT SAYS DIG.
THEY'RE PROBABLY GETTING BURGERS
AND FRIES, BUT MAYBE I GOT
SOMETHING WETTER.
IT'S SHOCKING HOW THIS GAME CAN
CHANGE IN YOUR FAVOR JUST LIKE
THAT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS THE WORST DAY
EVER, BUT THIS COULD BE HUGE FOR
ME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I GOT A NOTE, "YOU BOUGHT
YOURSELF OUT OF THE AUCTION, AND
YOU ALSO BOUGHT YOURSELF A
PERSONAL STASH OF RATION, ENOUGH
TO LAST YOU FOR THE REST OF THE
GAME.
THE INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE THE
SHARE, IF ANY, IS UP TO YOU."
WOW.
THE BIBLE SAYS IT'S BETTER TO
GIVEN THAT RECEIVE, SO EVEN
THOUGH THESE SNACKS ARE FOR ME,
WE'VE ALL BEEN OUT HERE FOR 25
DAYS.
EVERYBODY'S STARVING, SO I'M
GOING TO GO AHEAD AND SHARE.
MAYBE THIS WILL GIVE ME SOME
BROWNIE POINTS WHEN IT COMES TO
PEOPLE TRYING TO VOTE ME OUT, I
DON'T KNOW, BUT I THINK IT'S
GOING TO BE A NICE GESTURE, NO
HARD FEELINGS.
>> CLOSE YOUR EYES.
>> CLOSE YOUR EYES?
>> JENN, READ THAT.
>> YOU BOUGHT YOURSELF OUT OF
THE AUCTION, AND YOU ALSO BOUGHT
YOURSELF A PERSONAL STASH OF
RATION, ENOUGH TO LAST YOU FOR
THE REST OF THE GAME.
>> JENN, GET THE FIRST PIECE OF
THAT JERKY, PLEASE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
HANG ON TO THAT.
>> RODNEY...
>> I SCREWED UP BIG TIME AT THE
AUCTION.
BUT I KNOW THAT THERE WAS AN
ALLIANCE FORMED THAT WAS COMING
FOR ME.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO SIT THERE
AND WATCH IT HAPPEN.
>> BLOW IT UP RIGHT NOW.
>> BECAUSE IF I DON'T OUT THIS
ALLIANCE IMMEDIATELY, DAN,
SIERRA AND MYSELF ARE GOING
HOME.
>> THE ONLY REASON WHY I ALMOST
DIDN'T TAKE MY LETTER IS BECAUSE
I KNOW THAT YOU'LL FLIPPED
RODNEY, AND I KNOW AT TOMORROW
NIGHT'S VOTE IS GOING FOUR FOR
ME, AND I KNOW THE FOUR, ONE,
TWO, THREE, AND FOUR.
I KNOW BEYOND A SHADOW OF A
DOUBT.
I'VE HEARD CONVERSATIONS THAT I
WAS NOT SUPPOSED TO HEAR.
DAN'S THREE FAMOUS WORDS,
"FLIPPERS NEVER WIN."
GREAT GAME PLAY, RODNEY.
HE FLIPPED.
>> I DIDN'T FLIP.
WE'RE SITTING RIGHT HERE.
>> YOU FLIPPED.
>> YOU'RE STILL HERE.
WHO DID I FLIP ON?
>> WE'LL SEE TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> YOU WILL SEE, AND YOU'RE
RUINING IT FOR YOURSELF.
WE ALL GOT OUR LOVED LETTERS AND
YOU'RE BRINGING THE MOMENT DOWN
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING NUTS RIGHT
NOW.
YOU BETTER RELAX, BRO.
YOU BETTER RELAX.
>> I'M TELLING YOU.
I KNOW WHAT I KNOW.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU KNOW.
YOU LOST YOUR DAMN MIND.
>> I KNOW WHAT I KNOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'M JUST GLAD THEY'RE ALL
HERE.
DON'T BE MAD BECAUSE YOU GOT
BUSTED.
>> NOBODY GOT BUSTED.
>> YOU LOST YOUR DAMN MIND.
>> WHEN WE GET BACK FROM THE
REWARD, MIKE'S TELLING ME
THERE'S FOUR AGAINST ME AND DAN,
RODNEY FLIPPED.
ON THE BLUE COMERS, SO MIKE
FEELS THE URGE TO JUST LET IT
ALL OUT.
THIS IS A SYMPTOM OF BEING
EXHAUSTED AND PARANOIA AND HE
HAS THE WORST TIMING EVER.
WE HAVE LETTERS FROM OUR LOVED
ONES.
WE JUST WANT TO SIT DOWN AND
READ THEM.
I'M DIGGING IN.
I CAN'T WAIT ANYMORE.
I'M SORRY.
>> DO YOUR THINK, SIERRA.
>> PICTURES.
>> OH, MY GOSH, LOOK AT YOUR
HAIR IN THE PICTURES.
LOOK AT YOUR HAIR.
>> THEY SENT PICTURES OF MY
ANIMALS.
>> REMEMBER, PLAY SMART BUT BE
TRUE TO YOURSELF.
COME HOME SAFE, DAD.
>> I MISS YOU SO MUCH IT HURTS.
ALL MY LOVE.
>> ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT, I DO
APOLOGIZE FOR BRINGING ALL THAT
UP.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL MOMENT.
I JUST OUTED THE ALLIANCE THAT
WAS TRYING TO GET ME OUT TODAY.
NOW THEY'RE ALL MAD AT ME
BECAUSE I RUINED THE MOMENT.
FOR EVERYBODY.
BUT THIS IS A GAME.
AND I'M HERE TO WIN.
HOPEFULLY MY STRATEGY WORKS.
IT MAY NOT, BUT AT LEAST IT'S
OUT IN THE OPEN NOW.
>> WHAT MIKE WAS SAYING WAS
TRUE, BUT I JUST GOT TO USE IT
TO MY ADVANTAGE, SO I'M GOING
AFTER WHAT I NEED RIGHT NOW,
WHICH IS DAN'S VOTE.
>> HEY THERE, BIG GUY.
>> LOVE YOU, MAN.
>> THAT WAS SO UNCALLED FOR.
>> YOU DIDN'T EVEN GET YOUR
EXPERIENCE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT, MAN.
>> HE'S GONE OFF THE DEEP END.
>> IF THIS NOT "SURVIVOR," I'D
BATTLE MIKE OUT IN THE STREET,
BUT IN "SURVIVOR," I HAVE TO
BEAT HIM WITH MY MIND AND MY
WIT.
BUT BECAUSE OF WHAT HE DID, HE
MADE MY JOB EASY.
THAT'S THE MOST DISRESPECTEDFUL
THING.
HE DOGGED YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> HE'S LET THIS GAME TAKE OVER
HIS MIND, BRO.
THAT'S JUST PLAYING LIKE...
>> HE SHOWED HIS COLORS, MAN.
MIKE TOOK A REALLY NICE MOMENT
AND RUINED IT.
THAT HURT ME.
BECAUSE MIKE IS MY FRIEND.
BUT HE IS CONVINCED THAT RODNEY
HAS FLIPPED, WHICH NOW PUTS
MIKE, MYSELF AND SIERRA ON THE
BOTTOM END OF THE FOOD CHAIN.
WHO IS RIGHT?
DON'T KNOW.
>> $480 SPOT.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU BOUGHT YOURSELF AN EXTRA
VOTE.
WHEN YOU INTEND TO USE THE VOTE,
YOU MUST ANNOUNCE IT AFTER JEFF
SAYS, "I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES."
THIS VOTE WILL COUNT LIKE ANY
OTHER AT THAT TRIBAL COUNCIL."
I COULDN'T HAVE IMAGINED THIS IN
MY WILDEST DREAMS.
I WAS EXPECTING AN ADVANTAGE IN
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
BUT TO GET A SECOND VOTE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT THIS
MEANS TO ME?
IT'S LIKE THE WILLIE WONKA
GOLDEN TICKET.
OH, MY GOD.
>> YESTERDAY WHEN WE WERE
GETTING BACK THE CAMP.
>> YES.
>> I WAS VERY APPRECIATIVE FOR
WHAT YOU SHARED.
I JUST THINK THERE'S MORE TO THE
STORY.
HE SAID THAT HE HAD TO DIG DOWN,
OPEN THIS BOX AND THERE WAS ALL
KINDS OF STUFF IN IT, AND HE
BROUGHT IT BACK TO CAMP.
WELL, WHERE'S THE BOX?
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK THERE'S MORE THAN
WHAT HE GAVE US, ABSOLUTELY.
>> SUPPOSEDLY WILL SHARED ALL
THE FOOD WITH US.
THESE RATIONS THAT ARE SUPPOSED
TO LAST THE REST OF THE GAME,
WHICH IS A LITTLE SUSPECT TO ME.
>> I WANT THE FIND OUT WHERE HE
HID THAT FOOD, MAN.
>> HE JUST GAVE US THIS.
>> EVERYBODY'S SPREADING THESE
RUMORS THAT THERE'S MORE FOOD
OUT THERE.
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TO HIDE STUFF
FROM US.
SHIRIN, JENN, MIKE ARE LIKE,
WE'RE GOING TO EXPOSE HIM AND
CALL HIM OUT.
>> I JUST HEARD THAT THOSE THREE
ARE SAYING THAT I'M LYING THAT
THERE WAS MORE FOOD AND THAT I'M
HIDING IT, WHICH IS A CROCK.
I'M ALREADY MAD BECAUSE I DIDN'T
GET A LETTER OF MY FAMILY, BUT
WHEN I DO A GENEROUS ACT AND YOU
QUESTION THAT... I CHOSE TO
SHARE THAT WITH YOU GUYS AND YOU
QUESTION THAT.
MISS GREEDY ASS.
ALL YOU'VE BEEN DOING IS RUNNING
YOUR DAMN MOUTH.
SHIRIN, ALL YOU DO IS EAT AND
TALK.
WHAT ELSE CAN FIT IN THERE?
>> DO YOU REALLY HAVE TO SPEAK
TO ME THAT WAY?
>> I AM SPEAKING TO YOU THAT
WAY.
DON'T EVER QUESTION MY
CHARACTER, DOLL, FOR REAL.
WILL CAME BACK TO CAMP FREAKING
OUT.
MIKE WAS MISSING, JENN WAS
MISSING.
WILL STARTS TEARING INTO ME LIKE
A CRAZY PERSON.
>> YOU ALL WANT TO TALK, LET'S
TALK.
LET'S DO IT, BABY.
>> WHY DON'T YOU KEEP YOUR MOUTH
SHUT AND YOU'LL STAY HERE
LONGER.
IT'S CRAZY.
>> WHEN YOU GET CALLED OUT,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU DON'T WANT THE HEAR THE
TRUTH.
>> NOBODY EVEN LIKES YOU.
I CAN GUARANTEE THERE'S NOBODY
IN THE UNITED STATES AT HOME
THAT IS MISSION YOU.
>> AND THEN HE JUST STARTED
DIGGING IN WITH THE PERSONAL
ATTACKS.
>> WE ALL HAVE LOVED ONES THAT
LOVE AND CARE FOR US.
YOU HAVE NOTHING.
>> HAVING GROWN UP IN FAMILY
TORN APART BY DOMESTIC VIOLENCE
AND THEN VERBALLY ASSAULTED MY
ENTIRE CHILDHOOD, I GET WORKED
UP ABOUT IT.
>> YOU HAVE NOTHING.
YOU HAVE NO FAMILY, YOU HAVE
NOTHING.
>> STOP WITH THE PERSONAL
ATTACKS.
>> DUDE, I'LL DO WHAT I WANT.
>> HE'S MAN OF GOD, HE PRAYS
BEFORE EVERY MEAL.
>> GOD DON'T LIKE UGLY.
I'M EXPOSING UGLY.
GO ON WITH YOUR LITTLE BITCH
MIKE AND GET THE HELL UP OUT OF
HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU HEARD, BRO.
>> OTHER THAN MIKE, EVERYONE IS
SITTING THERE SMILING LIKE, THIS
IS FUN, ISN'T IT.
TO ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN, IT'S
DISGUSTING.
LIKE I HAVE NOBODY IN MY LIFE
WHO LOVES ME AND LIKE HOW I'M
LIKE A LOSER AND...
>> WHAT ARE PEOPLE GETTING SO
PERSONAL FOR?
>> THE PAST COUPLE DAYS I
HAVEN'T REALLY WANTED TO BE
HERE.
BUT THOSE PEOPLE SUCK SO BAD.
I THINK I'LL STICK AROUND JUST
SO I CAN [BLEEPED] UP THEIR
GAME.
>> AT THIS POINT ME, SHIRIN AND
JENN, WE ONLY HAVE EACH OTHER,
BUT WE'RE STILL IN THIS GAME.
AND I'M GOING TO KEEP WORKING
EVERY ANGLE I CAN UNTIL EITHER
SOMETHING BREAKS OR I GO HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
HOW IS EVERYBODY DOING 27 DAYS
INTO THIS GAME?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> NOT GOOD.
NOT GOOD.
>> Jeff: JUST STRUGGLING?
>> UM, WHEN THEY CAME WITH WITH
THEIR LETERS FROM HOME, IT JUST
HURT.
AND I WAS WONDERING IF I TOOK
MYSELF OUT OF TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, WHICH PUTS ME AT RISK
OF BEING VOTED OUT AND LOSING $1
MILLION, I'M WILLING TO DO THAT
FOR THOSE LETTERS.
FAMILY MEANS MORE TO ME THAN
MONEY.
SO THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW I FEEL
ABOUT IT.
IF EVERYBODY HERE FEELS GOOD
WITH WILL SITTING OUT, THEN WILL
CAN SIT OUT AND I'LL HAVE YOUR
LETTER WAITING BACK AT CAMP,
BUT, WILL, IN THE FAIRNESS OF
THIS GAME, THE INTEGHTD OF IT,
EVERY SINGLE PERSON HAS TO
AGREE.
IF ONE PERSON SAYS, NO YOU CAN'T
DO IT.
DOES THAT SEEM FAIR TO YOU?
>> YEAH, THAT'S FAIR.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL DO A SIMPLE SHOWING OF
HANDS.
ANYBODY HERE OBJECT?
>> SHOCKING.
>> Jeff: SHIRIN THE ONLY ONE.
>> HE BOUGHT WHAT HE PRESIDENT
AT THE AUCTION.
HE BOUGHT OUT.
HE MISSED OUT ON THE LOVED ONE'S
LETTERS AND THAT'S THE WAY THE
GAME WORKS.
>> Jeff: WILL, CAN'T DO IT.
>> THAT'S FINE.
SO LET'S DO IT, BABY.
LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY.
LET'S GET TO IT THEN.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, TYLER.
I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
>> BRING IT TO YOU.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE METAL TONGS TO
TRANSPORT A BALL ACROSS A SERIES
OF TEETER TO THERS.
WHEN YOU REACH THE END, YOU'LL
PLACE THE BALL IN THE STAND AND
HEAD BACK.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU FALL OFF OR
THE BALL DROPS, YOU HAVE TO GO
BACK TO THE START.
FIRST PERSON TO PLACE ALL SIX
BALLS IN THEIR STAND WINS
IMMUNITY GUARANTEED A ONE IN
EIGHT SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND BECOME THE THIRD MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
WE'RE GOING THE DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
A SIMPLE-LOOKING CHALLENGE.
THE TONGS ARE VERY HEAVY, AND
IT'S HARD TO BALANCE THAT BALL.
RIGHT OUT OF THE GATE THE GUY
WHO DIDN'T WANT TO PARTICIPATE
IS IN THE EARLY LEAD.
WILL.
WILL DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
THERE GOES MIKE.
MIKE DROPS.
THERE'S DAN.
>> NOPE.
>> Jeff: DAN DROPS.
A STEEP LEARNING CURVE ON THIS
ONE.
HERE COMES TYLER SLOW AND
STEADY.
HAS REACHED HIS FINISH.
TYLER AT HIS STAND.
TYLER HAS HIS FIRST BALL AND IT
IS ON THE STAND.
TYLER HEADS BACK.
RODNEY DROPS.
MIKE COMING BACK.
THERE GOES DAN AGAIN.
MIKE IS AT HIS STAND.
MIKE HAS HIS FIRST.
>> OH, WHAT IN DAMNATION.
>> Jeff: DAN DROPS.
HE WAS ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
DAN'S GOT TO HEAD BACK.
IT IS TYLER WITH ONE, MIKE WITH
ONE.
JENN DROPS.
SHIRIN STILL TRYING TO GET OUT
THERE.
HERE COMES MIKE TRYING TO PICK
UP THE PACE.
THERE'S TYLER WITH HIS SECOND.
TYLER DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO COME BACK.
HERE COMES RODNEY.
HE'S GOT SOME MOMENTUM GOING.
HERE COMES MIKE.
MIKE'S GOT IT FIGURED OUT NOW.
MIKE IN THE LEAD.
RODNEY WITH HIS FIRST.
MIKE HAS TWO.
RODNEY WITH ONE.
TYLER WITH ONE.
THERE'S DAN WITH HIS FIRST.
SIERRA HAS HER FIRST.
HERE COMES TYLER.
TYLER ALMOST AT THE END OF THE
SECOND TEETER TOTTER DROPS.
HERE COMES CAROLYN.
MIKE NOW WITH HIS THIRD.
MIKE IS SCREAMING ACROSS THIS
COURSE NOW.
HE'S GOT A RHYTHM AND IT IS
WORKING.
THAT IS THREE FOR MIKE.
THERE'S TYLER WITH HIS SECOND.
CAROLYN WITH ONE.
HERE COMES DAN WITH HIS SECOND.
SIERRA WITH HER SECOND.
OH, SIERRA DROPS AT THE LAST
SECOND.
WILL...
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: WILL DROPS.
HERE COMES MIKE.
MIKE JUST BARELY CLEARS THAT
SECOND TEETER TOTTER.
MIKE NOW WITH HIS FOURTH.
RIGHT NEXT TO HIM IS TYLER WITH
HIS THIRD.
IT IS MIKE AND TYLER RIGHT NOW.
EVERYBODY ELSE WAY BEHIND.
HERE COMES MIKE AND TYLER RIGHT
BEHIND HIM.
MIKE HAS A ONE-BALL LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
THAT IS FIFE FOR MIKE IF HE CAN
GET IT.
AND HE DOES.
MIKE HEADING BACK FOR HIS SIXTH
AND FINAL BALL.
TYLER WITH HIS FOURTH.
IT IS A RACE TO THIS FINISH.
DAN DROPS AGAIN.
TYLER COMING BACK WITH HIS
FIFTH.
TYLER DROPS.
GOT TO HEAD BACK.
OPENS THE DOOR FOR THE WIN RIGHT
HERE.
MIKE WITH HIS SIXTH BALL.
TAKING HIS TIME.
FOR IMMUNITY.
MIKE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
GUARANTEED A ONE IN EIGHT SHOT
OF WINNING THIS GAME.
>> YEAH, MIKE!
NO ONE ELSE GET TOO EXCITED.
>> THANKS, JENN.
>> I NEEDED IT.
I NEEDED IT.
>> Jeff: MIKE, COME ON OVER.
>> JUST WHEN I NEEDED IT MOST,
BABY.
>> Jeff: IS THAT RIGHT?
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
>> Jeff: FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN FOR MIKE.
MIKE CANNOT BE VOTED OUT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU'RE GUARANTEED A 1-8 SHOT IN
THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 27
DAYS OUT HERE, SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT AND BECOME THE THIRD
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
SOUNDS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING AFTERNOON,
ESPECIALLY WITH WILL AND SHIRIN.
>> BRING THE POPCORN, BABY.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE BEST TRIBAL
EVER.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> ONE OF THE WORST THINGS THAT
COULD HAPPEN IS THAT MIKE WON
IMMUNITY, SO MY GAME HAS TAKE AN
HUGE HIT.
THIS CAMP HAS TURNED INTO A DAMN
CIRCUS.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPEN, TRIBAL
AIN'T GOING TO GO EXACTLY HOW WE
WANT IT TO GO.
>> WHEN YOU WIN IMMUNITY, YOU DO
THE HAPPY DANCE.
YOU DO THE HAPPY DANCE WHEN YOU
DO SOMETHING GOOD.
IT FELT AMAZING.
AND IT COULD NOT HAVE COME AT A
BETTER TIME IN THIS GAME BECAUSE
I WAS 100% ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
TONIGHT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK TODAY?
>> SHOULD WE GET SHIRIN OUT?
>> NO, MAKE HER LIFE MISERABLE.
JENN'S A BIGGER THREAT.
GET RID OF THE THREAT.
SHIRIN'S NOT A THREAT.
TONIGHT'S GOING TO BE A VERY,
VERY IMPORTANT TRIBAL BECAUSE WE
NEED TO BRING UP THE NUMBERS.
I WOULD LIKE TO VOTE OUT SHIRIN,
SHE HAS NO SOUL, NO WORTH, NO
NOTHING, BUT JENN IS GOOD AT
CHALLENGES.
>> I THINK WE SPLIT 3-3.
>> THERE'S NO QUESTION THAT ONE
OF THEM GOES HOME.
WE STAY STRONG.
THEN WE DO IT AGAIN AND AGAIN.
>> THIS IS LIKE SURE VERY --
"SURVIVOR" 101.
WE HAVE SIX STRONG.
THEY CAN'T WIN.
>> LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION:
WOULD YOU RATHER SEE TYLER GO OR
MAMA C GO?
>> I WOULD RATHER SEE MAMA C GO
BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE HER?
>> WOULD YOU THROW THAT VOTE
THAT WAY?
>> I WOULD ABSOLUTELY DO THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE ANY OF THOSE
PEOPLE ON THE OTHER SIDE
WINNING.
>> I THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
SPLIT THE VOTE BETWEEN JENN AND
ME.
>> THAT'S A GREAT SCENARIO.
I'M ABOUT 99% SURE SIERRA'S
DONE.
SHE'S BARELY EVEN LOOKING AT ME,
BUT I'M NOT SO SURE ABOUT DANO.
IF WE DID HAVE DAN, THAT WOULD
GIVE US FOUR.
WE COULD BLINDSIDE MAMA C.
>> AT THIS POINT I WANT THE STAY
IN THIS GAME BECAUSE I DON'T
LIKE THOSE PEOPLE, AND I WANT TO
VOTE THEM OUT, BUT IF THIS IS
GOING TO WORK, IT'S UP TO DAN,
WHO IS DUMB AS A BOX OF ROCKS
SOME MY ENTIRE GAME IS IN DUMB
ASS' HANDS.
>> THOSE FOUR, YOU CAN'T TELL ME
YOU DON'T SEE THEM AS TIGHT.
>> I'M TELLING YOU THAT I SAW US
ALL TIGHT.
>> MIKE, ALL OF US HAVE TALKED
ABOUT FINAL FIVE, FOUR AND
THREE.
ALL OF US HAVE.
WE'RE ALL LOOKING AT THE END
GAME.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THEY'RE
GOING TO MAKE THE MOVE EARLY.
>> I THINK THEY THINK THEY HAVE
DAN.
>> YEAH.
BUT THEY DON'T GOT DAN.
>> DAN WOULD BE STUPID TO FLIP.
>> YEAH.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
AND I PUT YOU GUYS IN THIS
POSITION.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> BUT YOU'VE ALIGNED YOURSELF.
>> I HAVE NO CHOICE TO ALIGN
MYSELF.
BUT YOU AND SIERRA ARE THE ONLY
TWO THAT I'VE GIVEN MY WORD ON
THAT I WANT TO GO TO THE FINAL
THREE WITH, AND I WOULD STILL
HONOR THAT.
ONE MILLION PER SEPTD BECAUSE WE
ARE BLUE STRONG.
I HAVE BEEN BLUE, BLUE, BLUE
SINCE DAY ONE.
>> THEY'VE BEEN DOWN THERE ALL
DAY LONG.
>> WHY IS HE DOING THAT?
>> THE MORE TIME DAN SPENDS WITH
THEM, THE MORE DANGEROUS HE
BECOMES.
>> AT THIS POINT I'M LIKE, OH,
MY GOD, IS DAN IN?
IS DAN OUT?
BECAUSE DAN HAS NOT PROVEN
HIMSELF TO BE THAT SMART IN THIS
GAME.
BUT I DO HAVE MY IDOL, AND IF
MIKE GETS TO HIM, I MIGHT HAVE
TO USE IT.
>> WHO DO YOU TRUST IN THIS
GAME?
RODNEY, WHO IS ALL OF A SUDDEN
EVERYBODY'S BEST FRIEND NOW, WHO
YOU YOURSELF HAVE SAID IS THE
MOST DESPICABLE, VULGAR AND FOUL
HUMAN BEING THAT YOU'VE EVER MET
AND WILL ATTACKING A 29-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN, COMING INTO CAMP CALLING
ME A BITCH?
I'VE HAD YOUR BACK.
THEY DON'T HAVE YOUR BACK, DAN.
THEY ARE USING YOU.
YOU AND ME BUILT THIS CAMP THAT
WE'RE LIVING AT RIGHT NOW WITH
WITH OUR BARE HANDS.
I'VE SWEATED AND I'VE BLED WITH
YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> IN THESE TRENCHES.
WHO DO YOU TRUST?
WHO HAS DEVELOPED TRUST WITH
YOU?
I GAVE IT MY BEST SHOT.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'LL COME
AROUND TO MY WAY OF THINKING OR
NOT.
I WOULD LIKE THE THINK DEEP DOWN
IN HIS HEART OF HEARTS DAN DOES
STILL WANT TO WORK WITH ME.
>> WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO VOTE
CAROLYN TONIGHT?
>> IT COULD BE MIKE IS RIGHT.
FOUR OF THEM ARE ABOUT TO SELL
US DOWN THE RIVER.
OR MAYBE HE'S LOST HIS MIND AND
WHAT UPSETS ME THE MOST IS I AM
THE SWING VOTE TONIGHT, WHICH IS
MY WORST NIGHTMARE.
>> I'M GOING TO ASK EVERYONE
AROUND THE CAMPFIRE A QUESTION,
INCLUDING ME.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF PLAYING
THE GAMES.
IF I GO WITH THEM, THAT'S MY
CHOICE.
I MAKE MY OWN DESTINY.
NOBODY DICTATES MY FUTURE BUT
ME.
MY CHOICE.
MY CHOICE, NOT YOURS, NOT YOURS
AND NOT THEIRS.
MINE.
IF I GO AGAINST MIKE AND I'M
WRONG, I'LL NEVER FORGIVE
MYSELF, BUT YOU HAVE TO TRY TO
PUT YOUR EMOTIONS ASIDE BECAUSE
IT'S A GAME.
EITHER WAY, IF I'M ABOUT TO MAKE
A $1 MILLION DECISION OR A $1
MILLION MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
HALI AND JOE VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
WILL, YOU SAID BRING POPCORN.
YOU SAID THIS IS GOING TO BE AN
ENTERTAINING TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> IT SURE.
IS.
>> Jeff: I'M READY.
>> THERE WAS AN INCIDENTS THAT
HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
SHIRIN WAS SAYING, YOU HAD ALL
THIS FOOD, YOU DIDN'T SHARE YOUR
SNACKS.
>> FALSE, FALSE.
>> HOW DARE YOU QUESTION ME
SAYING THAT I'M HIDING FOOD WHEN
I SHARED IT WITH EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF YOU.
SOME PEOPLE I DON'T LIKE.
AND I DIDN'T GET TO EAT TO THE
THE AUCTION.
I DIDN'T GET THE LOVE LETTERS.
I'M LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS IS
WHAT I GOT FOR YOU.
IT SET ME OFF.
>> Jeff: YOU EXPLODE.
>> 150,000% I EXPLODED.
>> BUT, JEFF, TO BE CLEAR,
THAT'S NOT WHERE HIS YELLING
INCIDENT.
HE SAID TWO THINGS ABOUT THE
ACTUAL INCIDENT AND HE STARTED
PERSONALLY ATTACKING ME.
>> I DIDN'T PERSONALLY ATTACK
YOU.
>> HE SAID MORE PEOPLE LIKE HIM
IN THIS GAME THAN IN MY ENTIRE
LIFE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> THAT I HAVE NO SOUL, THAT HE
NEEDS THE PRAY FOR ME, AND IT
WAS ALL PERSONAL ATTACKS.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
GAME.
IT HAD EVERYTHING TO DO WITH ME
PERSONALLY.
IT WENT WAY BEYOND THE GAME, AND
YOU KNOW WHY I DON'T HAVE
FAMILY, LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT
FOR A SECOND, JEFF.
YEAH, IT'S SO FUNNY AND SO GREAT
TO PUT ME DOWN FOR NOT HAVING A
FAMILY.
I DON'T HAVE FAMILY BECAUSE MY
BIOLOGICAL FATHER IS JUST LIKE
YOU, VERBALLY ASSAULTED ME ALL
THE TIME.
>> I DIDN'T VERBALLY ASSAULT
YOU.
>> SHUT UP!
>> I JUST CALLED YOU OUT.
>> YOU VERBALLY ASSAULTED ME.
>> YOU GET CALLED OUT, YOU PLAY
THE VICTIM.
>> AND I AM A VICTIM OF DOMESTIC
VIOLENCE, AND THIS IS WHY OUR
FAMILY WAS TORN APART, AND THAT
IS WHY I DO NOT HAVE FAMILY AT
HOME, AND HE IS MAKING LIGHT OF
THAT.
>> I AIN'T MAKING LIGHT OF THAT
WHILE A WHOLE SLEW OF PEOPLE
JUST WATCH LIKE IT'S
ENTERTAINMENT.
>> Jeff: SHIRIN, IS THE
LAUGHTER RELEASE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: EVEN A LITTLE BIT
CATHARTIC?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SIERRA, TRY TO GIVE ME A PICTURE
OF WHERE WE ARE FROM THIS
STANDPOINT.
FOUR BLUE COLLARS, THREE WHITE
COLLARS, TWO NO COLLARS, HOW
DOES EVERYBODY'S INDIVIDUAL
POINT OF VIEW TOWARD LIFE IMPACT
THE GAME ON DAY 27.
>> JEFF, I THINK IT SAYS IT BEST
BY WE ARE WORLDS APART.
YOU CAN COMPLETELY FORGET HOW
THIS GAME STARTED BECAUSE WE ARE
NINE INDIVIDUALS WHO ARE
DEPRIVED, STARVING, WANTING $1
MILLION.
WE'RE ALL FIGHTING FOR OURSELVES
AT THIS POINT.
>> Jeff: DAN, THE BLUE-COLLAR
TRIBE IN PARTICULAR WAS VERY
TIGHT.
THERE WAS A LOT OF TALK OF
LOYALTY, THIS IS HOW
BLUE-COLLARS BEHAVE.
DOES THAT MAKE IT TOUGH FOR YOU
TO BE IN A SITUATION IN WHICH
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO VOTE AGAINST A
BLUE-COLLAR?
>> IT'S VERY TOUGH.
AS A FAN, YOU THINK TO YOURSELF,
I CAN PARK MY EMOTIONS.
I CAN COME OUT HERE AND PUT THEM
ASIDE.
THAT'S CRAP.
THAT'S ABSOLUTE CRAP.
YOU GET OUT HERE.
YOU GET TO KNOW THESE PEOPLE.
YOU MAKE CONNECTIONS WITH THESE
PEOPLE.
WE'VE BONDED OVER A LIFESTYLE.
>> Jeff: MIKE, WITH YOUR
IMMUNITY WIN TODAY, YOU SAID,
NEVER NEEDED IT MORE THAN I NEED
IT TODAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THESE PEOPLE HAVE DECIDED THAT
I'M A MASSIVE THREAT IN THIS
GAME.
BUT THERE'S A FOUR-CORE ALLIANCE
RIGHT NOW, RODNEY, MAMA C, TYLER
AND WILL.
THOSE FOUR WILL WALK TO THE END
OF THIS GAME.
SIERRA, DAN, YOU TWO ARE GOING
HOME FIFTH AND SIXTH.
>> Jeff: RODNEY, YOU WANT IT,
YOU WANT IT.
>> BECAUSE THIS MANIAC AT THE
AUCTION ALMOST MADE IT SO DAN,
TYLER AND CAROLINE COULDN'T GET
THEIR LOVE LETTERS BECAUSE HE
TOOK HIS $20 BACK.
>> THEY STILL GOT THEIR LETTERS.
>> LET ME FINISH.
>> THEN WHEN WE'RE ABOUT TO OPEN
UP OUR LETTERS, THIS IS AN
ALLIANCE.
THIS DUDE JUST WENT OFF IN A
MANIC STATE AND THAT'S WHY HE'S
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
SO I DON'T CARE WHAT HE HAS TO
SAY NO MORE.
I WAS GOING TO KEEP IT COOL, BUT
I'LL COME AT YOU WITH FACTS.
EVERYBODY'S NODDING BECAUSE THEY
KNOW IT'S REAL.
>> Jeff: WOW.
SHIRIN, DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO GET VOTES TONIGHT.
>> YES.
I THINK 2 PLAN IS TO SPLIT THE
VOTES BETWEEN JENN AND ME SINCE
MIKE HAS IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: SO YOU THINK IT'S SIX
VERSUS THREE.
>> I THINK IT'S FOUR PLUS TWO
>> Jeff: CAROLYN, YOU'RE
SHAPING YOUR HEAD.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE SIX STRONG AND
YOU'RE PICKING OUT THE OTHER
ALLIANCE, IT'S A NO-BRAINER.
THEY'RE IN THE PART OF THE SIX.
>> Jeff: DAN, DO THE TENSIONS
FALL ON DEAF EAR, OR DO YOU HAVE
TO LISTEN AND GO THROUGH IT AND
THINK, OKAY, LET ME THINK ABOUT
THIS ONE.
>> I'D BE STUPID NOT TO LISTEN.
YOU HAVE TO WEIGH OUT YOUR
OPTIONS BECAUSE IT'S NOT JUST
ABOUT GETTING TO THE END OF THE
GAME.
AT THIS STAGE, IT'S HOW YOU GET
TO THE END OF THE GAME.
AND IT'S WHO YOU PUT OVER THERE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
TYLER, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE A FIRECRACKER, JENN.
>> JUST BECAUSE YOU KNOW EVERY
SINGLE SEASON OF "SURVIVOR"
DON'T MEAN YOU CAN PLAY THE
GAME, SISTER.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JENN.
SHIRIN.
JENN.
TWO VOTES JENN.
SHIRIN.
THAT'S TWO SHIRIN.
JENN.
CAROLYN.
SHIRIN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES SHIRIN, THREE
VOTES JENN, ONE VOTE CAROLYN.
JENN.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES JENN.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JENN.
YOU NEED TO BRING MY YOUR TORCH.
JENN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> BYE, GUYS.
GOOD LUCK, AND PLAY NICE, ALL
RIGHT?
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE GOOD NEWS
IS YOU'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
THE BAD NEWS IS YOU'RE LEFT WITH
EIGHT PEOPLE WHO WANT TO PLAY SO
BADLY THEY WILL STOP AT NOTHING
TO WIN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> YOU ARE SO MUCH MORE OF A
THREAT NOW.
>> MIKE IS RUNNING OUT OF
ALLIES.
>> I HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE.
I'M PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE.
>> WHILE TYLER TURNS ON ONE OF
HIS OWN.
>> GAME ON.
I GRABBED DAN'S BAG.
HE GETS AN EXTRA VOTE.
>> WOW.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE SUCK SUPER
HARD.
WILL, MAN.
I HATED RODNEY AND MAMA C.
I CAN'T WAIT THE WATCH THE REST
OF THIS TRIBE DESTROY EACH
OTHER.
I JUST HOPE THEY'RE NOT ON THE
JURY ANY TIME SOON SO I DON'T
HAVE TO SEE THEIR FACES.