translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
- After 17 days...
- Where's Jeff?
Nagarote and Escameca
eventually merged.
You merged!
One tribe, competing
for a million dollars.
And at the first
individual immunity test,
Joe held out longer
than all the others.
Joe wins individual immunity!
- Close to the council...
- We can't have Joe.
- So let's eliminate his right arm, Hali.
- Yes, very well.
...Mike wanted to test
Will's loyalty.
If I see Hali's name tonight,
I can trust Will.
But the real power struggle
was between the Blues, targeting Jenn,
and the Colorless,
which targeted Kelly,
with the White Collars in the middle...
They need our votes.
deciding
who would take control.
Wherever we go, it will change
this game decisively.
At the council, Shirin remained
with the Colorless,
while Carolyn, Tyler and Will
sided with the majority.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it...
But a majority doesn't matter
if an idol is played at the perfect time.
Yeah, I
really don't want to leave tonight.
Seventh person eliminated: Kelly.
And in the end, Kelly was eliminated.
Kelly, the tribe has spoken.
There are 11 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Welcome to Survivor,
ladies and gentlemen!
We got down to business.
Well done, ladies!
- Good game !
- Well done, Jenn!
Seeing Kelly leave
broke my heart.
It shouldn't have happened.
I'm very sorry,
and I blame Mike for that.
Mike is the leader,
he changed the vote.
It must have been Hali,
he changed it at the last moment
to test Will's loyalty.
Mike is
a stupid slob, that's all.
Mike is at the controls
and looks at the result!
Seven against four now.
- I say.
- Then hang on to me.
Listen...
Give me your love.
- I gave it to you!
- I...
- I'm the only one to have voted Hali!
- That was Mike!
- It was Mike!
- I know, he wanted me to vote Hali!
Look, whatever.
We got you, me, Tyler...
Mama C ...
There's Mama C Carol,
we're all in on it.
I love my Blues
but it will become very interesting
when we are only seven.
- Yeah, okay.
- But Mike is in charge.
We'll leave the controls to him.
But once Joe, Hali,
Jenn and Shirin are gone,
We will take control.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
It clearly didn't
go the way I wanted tonight.
Sorry to disappoint you
by still being here, Mike, but...
I knew I was targeted,
so I played my idol.
And Kelly left.
But I respect
this shot was...
- It was pretty.
- [???]
Joe, Hali, Shirin and I
were thrilled.
To the angels.
The others were
speechless, shocked,
and sad, "poor Kelly"!
We do not care ! It was great !
- Well...
- But I appreciate it.
The Colorless are back
we are ready to win.
I love putting the bronx
in the other alliances.
I think we can
still have fun,
find stuff
to screw up for others.
I want to put the bronx on
while I can,
because it cracks me up.
How many doses did you take?
Three. I believe that
was the general consensus.
uh well...
Add a little more.
Just a little more.
I was told it was three.
I tell you something else.
So...
Since the arrival of Joe
and his charlots,
they run the kitchen,
decide the portions...
But hey, when I get angry,
I walk away,
I'm going to kick
a tree or something,
and I come back cool, calm and serene.
But why...
I'd rather
peel the skin myself.
- As you wish.
- I like to eat next to my skin
and chew it.
For me, respect is earned.
Here, for me,
there is something to trip up.
I'm not being a hypocrite.
I have to respect
you to show you respect.
If I don't respect you,
you will know it.
It's not much,
just to leave the skin.
In that case, I'll do what
I want. How are you?
- It's just salami.
- Just salami.
I know, so...
Why are you interfering
in what I do?
Nope ? If it's just salami,
Does it matter if I take
the skin off for Tyler or me?
- I was just saying.
- So say it.
- I said it.
- [???]
- Yeah.
Shiri, Sherry,
whatever her name is,
she is out of place,
she has nothing to do here.
Nobody supports it.
But hey, it's a game.
We are seven, the four of them.
Basically, it's over for them.
We have to eliminate the waste.
Over here everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Absolutely.
- Yes.
Today you will cross
a series of beams,
collecting bags of puzzle pieces along the way .
With each bag collected,
you will drop it off and leave.
The first three to bring
their three bags to the end
will advance to the final round,
where to use these parts
to solve
a puzzle in the shape of an anchor.
The first to complete his puzzle
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
The winner of the race
will be taken into the
rainforest canopy.
You will descend
using a zip line.
Downstairs, a picnic will be waiting for you.
A pizza picnic.
Nice afternoon in perspective.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Let's go. For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Dan falls heavily, straight away.
He has to start over.
Shirin falls, she starts again.
These beams are not easy.
And you have to keep your balance
while untying the bags.
Here is Joe with his first bag.
And this is Mike.
Joe passed.
Jenn passed. Mike passed.
Hali passed.
And this is Sierra and Tyler.
Tyler takes a big leap,
and he's past.
We need three people
with the three bags.
Dan passed.
And this is Rodney,
and Will, he made it.
Everyone is on the 2nd bag,
except Shirin, still on her 1st.
I can't!
Carolyn falls,
she has to start over.
Here is Joe, with his 2nd bag.
Joe flies over the ordeal.
On his heels: Mike.
Joe and Mike lead.
We need the first three,
along with the three bags.
Here is Hali, with her 2nd bag.
This is Sierra, with her 2nd bag.
Carolyn fails again.
2nd bag for Jenn.
And this is Tyler. A lot of people
are in on it.
Here is Joe, with his last bag.
Joe qualifies.
Rodney to ...
Not Rodney Graves!
Mike qualifies.
There is one place left.
We have Joe, we have Mike...
...And Hali qualifies!
Good. It's Hali
Joe and Mike.
The first to finish
wins a nice reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
- Go on !
- First step: empty the bags.
Go Mike!
You go-y Joe !
You assemble an anchor.
A rusty anchor.
One Overall, two Colorless,
who clash.
- Mike is off to a good start.
- That's good, Mike!
Joe tries to move on.
Hali begins to progress.
Some parts
may fit in more than one place,
but there is only one way
to complete it.
Another piece for Hali.
Hali seems well launched now.
Joe moves a few coins.
He acts quickly.
Mike hasn't made much progress.
Thanks, Jeff.
- Another room for Hali.
- Yeah, Hali!
Another room for Joe.
- Mike gets left behind.
- Calm down. Calm.
Five pieces left for Hali,
four left for Joe.
If they are not mistaken,
they are both very close.
It's on the last pieces
that it gets complicated.
Hali moves a few pieces,
she is at five again.
It's inevitable. Close to the goal,
you'll realize it's wrong,
and you will have to move a piece.
Joe moves a whole portion,
giving
Mike a chance to come back.
Mike does not give up,
he continues to fight.
Go Mike!
Another room for Mike.
Mike is in on it again.
Joe is trying to figure
something out.
Hali tries out a new combination.
Something is wrong.
Only four pieces left for Mike.
Four pieces left for Joe.
Or even three.
Mike begins to panic.
Two more for Joe.
Joe is launched.
More than one piece, it's the last!
Joe made it!
Joe wins the award!
Joe, come closer!
Well done, Joe!
Thank you my friend.
Undefeated so far
in the individual part of the game.
Beautiful afternoon. Zip line, pizza...
Joe, choose three people
to accompany you.
I choose Tyler.
Tyler, come closer.
Will, come join Tyler.
In the last event,
Mama C ensured,
she deserves the reward
today.
- So, Mama C.
- Carolyn, come closer!
Good. You are four, but a good
round number would be five.
- Serious ?!
- Choose one last person...
- Damn it !
- ...to accompany you.
Damn it ! I'm
the most hungry, so...
You eat the most, too.
No. [???], then...
If you don't take me,
it doesn't matter, we are seven welded,
and that's fine with me.
It will be as it will be.
Rodney therefore withdraws from the choice.
No. But I don't care.
I am lucid.
And I'll stay clear, Jeff.
Who will it be, Joe?
You have one spot left.
Super-fan!
Super-fan.
Serious ? Serious ?
- Oh my God !
- And that's why. That.
Oh my God !
It is a unique experience.
We have the five leaving
for a beautiful afternoon.
Take your things, on the way,
enjoy!
- Thanks Jeff.
- Cheer.
Have fun !
Really good !
I stay cool.
I am here to play.
Damn, I hate you.
I have nothing for you. Take
your things, return to camp.
Joe's victory
was a disaster,
because he will probably have a clue
on the immunity idol
during the reward.
This kid is amazing.
How am I going to beat him?
This is the moment of truth.
I won the reward,
and it was fantastic to float
above the jungle.
I had never
used a zip line,
and Lord,
it was super cool!
There was me
There you are, Carolyn!
Yeah !
It's crazy!
... et Shirin.
Who's next ?
To me !
Oh my God !
Start braking!
- Brake!
- I braked!
You came way too soon.
You have come to the bottom.
That's a tree. Better to avoid it.
I couldn't believe my luck.
I got to zipline
with Carolyn, and...
Shit !
I don't like her, I don't want
her to eat pizza
and may she have a cool adventure!
- Cinnamon rolls!
- Cinnamon rolls.
- Come sit down, buddy.
- Yeah.
Lord,
I was so excited.
There's watermelon
and pizza and soda...
I take an orange.
- Who wants a red one?
- I do not care.
Looking at it, Joe made
an interesting choice,
because he took no Blue,
because obviously,
the Blues want his skin.
- Cheers, everyone!
- Health !
I was happy with it. It was well seen.
I thought I noticed something
in Carolyn's bottle.
Rodney was pissed
we didn't put rice in it.
- I would like more soda.
- Here !
I do not want it anymore.
And so, Jen...
I took it, and immediately,
I saw that there was
a message at the bottom.
And so he started to...
I tried to swallow it,
put it in my mouth.
But I saw Tyler
looking at me.
What's that one?
This is delicious.
Tyler saw me,
so I'm thinking of a plan
for us to read it together,
and what we are going to do.
I take a little.
- Yeah, he finished the previous one.
- Sorry.
No problem.
We will have to question it.
- He was...
- You're going to get scolded.
It was hot, you wouldn't have liked it.
Out of the corner of my eye, I saw Joe
almost choking on a clue.
I could have denounced him
at the time.
But I kept silent.
This index opened up
new options.
If Joe finds the immunity idol,
it also opens up
new options.
Dawn was barely breaking,
and Tyler was wide awake, presumably
waiting for me to get up.
I'll share the clue
with Tyler,
which will bring us closer.
I sit with my eyes
wide open, watching,
as if I was sleeping.
Joe and Tyler get up,
bring dishes,
as if they were going to the river.
I knew that today
would be the mad dash,
for I assumed there had been
a clue to the hidden idol.
All along, I track them,
from tree to tree,
a la James Bond.
I jump in these bushes,
I climb this tree,
I watch through the leaves,
I try to stay camouflaged,
out of their sight.
"Explore near a tributary.
The power sought is
near a sea of ​​green,
defying gravity
in its concealed hollow."
So it's...
Why would Joe show
Tyler a clue about the idol?
Unless you want to curry
favor with him.
Hey, guys!
How are you this morning ?
I slept very badly.
Yeah, I stink
of campfire and ashes.
Joe reads the clue, and
in an instant Mike is upon us.
I didn't know what he had seen,
he could have seen me
reading the clue with Joe.
I have to be very careful
not to alienate my allies.
And so, what to say to Mike?
So...
The to the index.
But he didn't tell anyone.
So he's near the river,
near a sea of ​​green,
defying gravity in a hollow.
I told him
what the clue said.
Then began a mad dash
to find Joe,
and Mike led
the pack of insanity.
Joe's on camp?
I believed it with you.
Not. On the index,
and Joe is nowhere to be found.
Wherever it is,
that's where the clue leads.
All right, we need to find Joe.
Joe left alone.
He's looking for the idol
right now.
And nobody...
...don't watch Joe.
I was changing.
He was following the path, this way,
I don't know where he went.
We have to find Joe before
he finds the idol, so that...
So we can eliminate him,
and it won't be me.
'Cause I honestly feel
that when Joe is gone,
if I have nothing in my pocket,
I'll be next.
So I'm going to get Joe.
Sure enough, I walk over
and find Joe.
I realize I want to enlarge
the target behind his back.
I haven't seen him find an idol
or put it in his pocket.
So I went to the river.
Well done, little brother!
- Good game !
- I do not know what you're talking about.
- You have it.
- He found her?
Yeah, he has.
I do not know what you're talking about.
Basically, I yelled:
“Bravo, you found the idol!”.
He tried to deviate,
but I won't let him.
I'll say I believe he has it,
that I saw him put
it in his pocket... Or not.
You know I have
to break your neck, huh?
- I do not have a choice.
- No, of course.
I do not have a choice.
It's a game.
That's the best part.
Mike shows up...
"You, then!
I can't believe you got it!"
And blah blah blah.
Well done, bro.
Yeah, Mike messed up my plan.
Mike said I had it,
he's convinced of it.
- And you don't have it?
- Nope.
But they all think I have it.
The good thing is. So...
- If I remain cushy, they will believe it.
- Yeah.
In a hollow...
Are you worried
about that damn idol?
In.
It's you who amaze me,
to be honest.
But really.
- You're like me, a fan.
- Yeah.
How come fans
can't count?
Why join a minority?
I have plans, you see.
You're Joe's underling.
This is how you are perceived.
Seriously.
The game is over for you.
- Your game is over.
- You don't understand my game.
Yes that's it !
Once again, another fan
who can't count.
Shinini,
or whatever his name is,
I can't remember
her name, she annoys me so much!
Someone slap this woman!
For the love of God,
slap her, shut her up!
Good Lord !
Do us this favour!
Hope
his torch is extinguished!
You are an easy target.
If Joe wins immunity tomorrow,
and if he has the immunity idol,
do you think he will give it to you?
Exact. So that makes you
a very easy target.
Dan is trying to tear me down.
He hurls insult after insult at me.
I really felt sorry for him.
I let it go, saying to myself:
"And after ?".
There are only two kinds
of people in this game.
Those who do nothing
and get eliminated for that,
and those who overdo
it annoy everyone and get fired.
You are the example.
You are solely responsible.
And that's just the truth.
In fact, I try to be nice.
Really.
I spent the day
chasing after the idol.
I'm at a termite nest
and I'm trying
to sustain me a little.
It gives me strength
to keep looking.
Still no luck in
the idol quest for Mike.
It's such an exhausting game,
physically and mentally.
It's rough.
That's the rough part of the game.
But...
I have to find her.
It must.
So...
Work awaits me.
It is not an easy task.
Don't think you'll find
an idol by snapping your fingers.
It's impossible.
We have to keep looking.
Look in every corner,
every crack.
Those who find
idols in this game,
are
the hardest working ones in this game.
God's goodness !
This is what we do!
Dance of Happiness!
Is this for real?!
You think
nothing is right.
Keep digging deep inside of you,
when that's all you have left.
And this,
this is what you find.
And you know what ?
I will not share.
Because this protection,
I need it for myself.
Now I have a chance
to get rid of Joe.
So if Joe doesn't win
individual immunity,
Joe has to go.
It's that simple.
Oh my God !
Over here everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
Yes sir !
- First of all, Joe, I get it back.
- Yeah.
They don't help me!
It's a trick.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will move
a puzzle piece
through
three sliding mazes.
When you have taken him through
the three labyrinths,
you will use this piece
to complete
a sliding puzzle.
The first to finish
wins immunity,
make sure to continue the game.
The losers will go to the council,
where after 22 days,
someone's quest for the million
and the title of Ultimate Survivor
will experience failure.
Shirin, how
are you feeling? A puzzle !
No beams, no obstacles...
A puzzle.
That's what I expected.
I'm a computer scientist,
that should be my department.
It comes back to the fact
that I am a super fan.
I'm always
so excited to be here.
And I want
to be here so much that...
- I'm freaking out.
- So you have...
I have so much energy, Jeff!
- I have to contain her.
- Summon her!
It's the opposite of a bomb, I...
- Yes this.
- You get the idea?
Well, we draw the places
and we start.
Let's go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
You have a puzzle piece,
she has to go through
three sliding mazes,
then comes the sliding puzzle.
Joe starts fast.
Sierra falls, but she passes.
There are Hali, Tyler,
Dan, Carolyn, Shirin.
And this is Jenn.
And this is Will.
Good last: Rodney.
Shit !
Joe proceeds to the 3rd maze.
Shirin is on the 3rd.
This is Tyler and Mike.
Shirin, Joe, Tyler and Mike
took the lead.
Carolyn goes to 3rd.
This is Sierra. This is Dan.
This obstacle must be overcome.
Joe passed the 3rd.
Joe attacks the sliding puzzle.
Shirin passed the 3rd.
Tyler passed the 3rd.
This is Sierra.
This is Mike.
Everyone passes now.
This is Dan.
This is Will.
Jenn joins them.
The only ones out of it are Rodney
and Hali.
Now complete the puzzle.
When it's good, you'll know.
Shirin predicted
that she would be good.
That remains to be seen.
Dan is fully into the puzzle.
Rodney finally arrives at his puzzle.
Hali arrives at his.
Joe would love to win
a 3rd time in a row.
I got it !
Dan thinks it's good.
- You have it ! Well done, Dan!
- Cheer.
And ...
...is wrong !
Everyone stays in the game.
You have to be fast AND be right
to win this race.
Joe won the first two
individual events.
Can he win three times in a row?
Now !
Dan thinks it's good now.
Dan is wrong again!
Bon sang!
Dan thought he found it twice,
he was wrong both times,
giving others a chance.
Mike is making progress.
Jeff, Jeff!
Joe thinks it's good.
Joe found it!
Joe wins immunity!
3 individual victories in a row!
Joe, come closer!
Well done, Joe!
Once again,
individual immunity is for Joe,
undefeated in
three consecutive events.
If you weren't scary before,
now you are.
- Thanks, Jeff...
- Joe, safe again tonight.
to the council. As for you,
after 22 very rough days
in this game,
someone will leave tonight.
Take your things,
return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Congratulation.
Joe won. That's all
he does: win events.
A real prototype
of pure white American.
Who wouldn't want him
to win Survivor?
If it had been my choice,
Joaquin would have made it.
There wouldn't be all this cinema.
It would be easy
to eat rice and beans.
But we will have to activate
in all directions, because of Mike.
Today I was offered a trial
on a silver platter, puzzles,
and... Joe wins.
Joe wins it all.
I would love to win an event,
it would be an accomplishment.
But at this point
everyone thinks
that I am harmless,
weak in everything,
and I hope it will
save me a few days of play.
I'm not too worried.
Shirin, hein?
If everyone
agrees, that's fine with me.
He thinks Shirin has the idol.
I do not think so.
From where ?
- From the yellow camp.
- From your side.
I say that because
I saw her fight
until the last day,
- searching the hills...
- Exactly.
...to confront Joaquin,
- yelling at him...
- Yeah.
If each side had an idol,
where is the white collar one?
Carolyn and Tyler
seem pretty sure
that Shirin doesn't have it.
Probably because
she didn't mention it.
And I don't think she's a
good enough player to shut up.
But maybe it is.
Maybe she
's a learned idiot.
I'm leaning more towards the "dumb" side.
But Shirin...
She will never win anything.
Very well. So who ?
These three Colorless.
- They're so close.
- Just.
Remove a leg from this tripod
and it will collapse.
- Hali.
- I say Hali.
- So Hali.
- Looks like...
Looks like the majority
wants to vote Shirin.
- I'm just afraid that...
- I...
No one thought
Jenn had an idol.
Dan came to see me, he said:
"I'm hallucinating, you're a fan
and you can't count!".
- And I...
- What?
"What ?" And he tells me that we are seen
as Joe's puppets,
- and blah blah blah.
- This guy is not well.
I would entrust my children
to Rodney rather than to Dan.
What did Dan tell you?
Where to start ?
Eliminating Dan would be awesome.
He was unnecessarily
hurtful to an adult.
I haven't forgiven him.
So to hear that others
feel the same way about Dan
I go back to morality,
because it confirms to me
that I am not crazy.
But we are missing a vote.
I want a girls alliance
, no doubt.
That, I tell you.
My Blue alliance
is aiming for a girl,
but is that really
what i want to do?
I want girls at the end.
So I have to decide
if I go with the girls
or if I stay
with my Blue alliance.
Now is the time for the girls
to put him on the spot.
Why not vote Dan?
OK.
I love the dynamic
of this girl band.
Together we can
strengthen each other.
And if Sierra joins us tonight,
we need another vote
to fire Dan.
So let's fire Dan!
- OK, Dan.
- OK.
Be misogynistic with girls
and the girls will eliminate you!
Dan!
I want to eliminate Dan.
Everyone wants to eliminate it.
Everybody.
And then what happens?
After that, we reassemble,
but there will be no more
a hefty alliance of Bleus
and another of Sans Couleur.
We will have fired
one of the pivots of the Blues.
Yeah.
- It's true.
- This may be our last chance,
with this balance of power,
to eliminate one of them.
They are in control,
but how long can it last?
Some of my allies
are very dangerous.
I would love to aim for Mike and Dan.
I support you !
I hope to strike before
the Blues realize what is happening.
They don't owe you anything.
You are a threat to them.
Tyler, what were the reactions
on the camp after the last council,
where Jenn played her idol
and where all the jaws
are unhooked?
Some were
a little depressed, that's for sure.
Kelly was appreciated.
And there was talk of a
chainsaw dividing this group.
But the lines were
already blurring again, it was being discussed again.
It wasn't "them against us",
it was a large group
of Survivors.
Sierra, is that your impression too?
Absolutely.
I don't think the line
is firmly drawn.
I can choose
the alliance that I want.
Mike, how
sure are you of the vote,
of the outcome you imagine,
with those with whom you think you will vote?
I'm 150,000% sure
of what I'm going to do.
But we got
a hell of a lot of players there,
and you all know what to say,
how to flatter
the ears of others.
So, will you follow someone who
maybe buys you pizza?
Or someone who provides
food for you from the start?
Dan, after the last advice,
are you a little worried, given
how quickly it can change?
As a big fan of the game, yes,
expect bombs.
We just hope they
don't explode on you.
But you have to believe
in your covenant and stick to it.
Five magic words, Jeff:
weathervanes never win.
Jeff, that's completely wrong.
The weathervanes win.
Tony turned around a million times
and won brilliantly.
It's a scare tactic
he uses on his allies .
so that no
one votes against him.
Hali, five words:
weather vanes never win.
Do you think he is stating a fact
or that it sends a message to those
who would consider returning?
I think he's sending a message,
but he has to remember
that we are the Merica tribe.
And if you look at history,
what if the settlers
had never returned
against the greatest
empire in the world?
You imagine ?
Since we are the Merica tribe,
the weathervanes have
a superb historical base
to win this game.
- Absolutely.
- Thanks.
Hey good!
Bright.
Pepper !
Good. It's time to vote.
Will, over to you.
You derailed.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Dan.
Status.
Equality. Two Dan votes,
two Hali votes.
Dan. Three Dan votes.
New equality. Three Dan votes,
three Hali votes.
Dan.
Status.
Halli. Five Hali votes,
four Dan votes.
Eighth person eliminated
and first member of the jury...
Halli. That's six, that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
What is this mess ?
Sorry.
Hali, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
I love you, Merca!
- Hey, Hali!
- Hi !
Drink a beer to my health!
We talked a lot tonight
about drawing lines in the sand.
With 10 players still in play,
the lines drawn tonight
could be washed out
by the tide tomorrow.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor....
Everyone takes hits.
Go Joe!
It's very strange to watch.
And someone is considering
throwing in the towel.
It's not funny,
people suck.
I have nothing left here
except despair.
I was shocked, I did
n't think I was leaving tonight.
I thought this girly thing
was gonna work.
I got screwed.
Honestly I understand
why Sierra and those who
voted for me did.
It's well played.
I'm ready to go get myself
a whiskey
and a big bowl of ice cream.