>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING THINGS UP.
AFTER A SURPRISE SWITCH, KELLY
WAS THE ONLY BLUE-COLLAR MEMBER
ON AN UNDERMANNED NAGAROTE
TRIBE.
>> I AM DEFINITELY SCARED TO
DEATH.
>> Jeff: WHILE THE REST OF THE
BLUE-COLLAR TRIBE ENJOYED A 4-3
ADVANTAGE, BUT NOT ALL OF THEM
WERE HAPPY.
>> I FEEL LIKE MY OLD TRIBE ARE
CRAPPY PEOPLE, BUT I HAVE THREE
NEW PEOPLE.
>> IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT
BALLGAME.
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, RODNEY
GREW CLOSE.
>> RODNEY IS LIKE MY FRIENDS
BACK HOME.
>> I'M SO GRATEFUL YOU GUYS ARE
HERE.
>> Jeff: WHILE SIERRA TRIED TO
DISTANCE HERSELF FROM HER FORMER
TRIBE.
>> I WANT TO GO WHERE I'M
WANTED, AND I DON'T THINK THAT'S
WITH THE BLUE COLLARS.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE... ESCAMECA WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM TRIBAL.
MAX AND SHIRIN BATTLE FOR TITLE
OF MOST ANNOYING TRIBE MATE.
>> IS THAT PLANTAR'S?
>> WHO IS MORE ANNOYING?
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE A HORSE RACE.
IS IT SHIRIN?
NO, HERE COMES MAX WITH HIS FOOT
WART.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
MAX WON.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT.
LEAVING SHIRIN ALL ALONE.
MAX, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
13 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> MAX WAS A FRIEND OF MINE AND
MY CLOSEST ALLY IN THIS GAME,
AND I WAS TOTALLY BLIND SIDED.
IT'S A HEARTBREAKER.
>> ARE YOU NOT GOING TO WORK
WITH ME FROM NOW ON?
>> I DON'T KNOW, SHIRIN.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN TRUST
YOU.
EVERY SINGLE DAY THE ONLY PERSON
YOU EVER TALKED TO IS MAX.
>> MAX TALKED TO ME.
>> NO, SHIRIN, YOU WERE HIS
LITTLE PUPPET.
WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR THREE DAYS.
>> I'VE BEEN TRYING TO SPEND ALL
MY TIME WITH HIM.
>> EXACTLY.
WHY?
I FELT WE WERE BUDS.
>> WE NEEDED NUMBERS.
>> WELL, WHEN I THINK LOYALTY, I
THINK REAL LOYALTY, NOT FAKE
LOYALTY.
>> IS ANYONE LEFT IN THIS GAME
WILLING THE PLAY WITH ME?
I DON'T THINK SO.
THAT'S A SAD REALIZATION.
IS THAT SOMETHING ABOUT ME AND
ABOUT MY PERSONALITY?
WHAT DO I HAVE TO CHANGE?
>> I GUESS YOU WERE KIND OF
SHAKEN UP BY LAST NIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I REALLY THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO
BE WILL.
IT WAS HARD.
>> MAX DID ANNOYING THINGS THAT
WERE GETTING UNDER EVERYONE'S
SKIN.
AND THEN LIKE IF YOU WANT ME TO
BE STRAIGHT, THEY WERE SAYING
YOU DID SOME ANNOYING THINGS,
TOO.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD ME BECAUSE I
FIND MYSELF IN THIS GAME IN A
POSITION THAT'S ANALOGOUS TO
WHERE I GREW UP.
I GREW UP IN RICH ORANGE COUNTY
SUBURB WHERE THE MAJORITY OF MY
CLASSMATES WERE BEAUTIFUL AND
SKINNY, AND I STOOD OUT FOR NOT
BEING ANY OF THOSE THINGS.
AND I CONSTANTLY FELT LIKE I WAS
FIGHTING FOR PEOPLE TO LIKE ME,
LIKE I WAS FIGHTING FOR PEOPLE
TO SEE THE GOOD QUALITIES IN ME,
AND I THINK THIS PROBABLY...
THERE'S PROBABLY A LOT OF THIS
SCENARIO TAPPING INTO THAT.
I'M TRYING TO DO NOW WHICH I WAS
INCAPABLE OF DOING BACK THEN,
WHICH IS DEAL WITH IT, ADAPT,
FIX IT.
>> IT'S FOURTH DAY, AND I HAD TO
GO DOWN TO THE WATER.
AND WAVE TOOK MY UNDERWEAR.
NO UNDERWEAR.
>> BANANA HAMMOCK UNDERWEAR.
>> IT WAS A BANANA HAMMOCK.
IT WAS NOT A THONG.
IT DID NOT GO UP MY BUTT, OKAY.
>> I'VE BEEN ON THESE BEACH WITH
THE SAME PEOPLE TELLING THE SAME
GARBAGE OVER AND OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY MISERABLE.
I WAS HOPING IN THE SWITCH UP I
COULD GET SOME NEW ENERGY, MAYBE
GET MATCHED UP WITH SOME PEOPLE
I KNOW ARE LIKE ME.
>> SICK OF BEING AROUND THE SAME
DAMN PEOPLE.
SAME STORY OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY WE GOT TO STAY
TOGETHER SO WE CAN KEEP
OURSELVES SANE HERE.
>> I WAS SO HAPPY JOAQ WAS ONE
OF THOSE FACES.
ONE GUY IS A BIBLE BUMPER FROM
TEXAS, A HICK FROM MAINE,
ANOTHER ONE IS FROM UTAH.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR SOME TYPE OF CONNECTION IN
THIS GAME, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I WAS LOOKING FOR MAYBE A LITTLE
BROMANCE, MAYBE A HOMEY TO
CHILL.
WITH
>> I DON'T THINK I TRUST MIKE
BECAUSE HE'S A SOUTHERN BOY.
HE GOES CHURCH EVERY SUNDAY.
DO YOU GO TO CHURCH EVERY
SUNDAY.
HE GOES TO CHURCH EVERY SUNDAY.
WE'RE HAVING SUNDAY FUN DAY.
HE DOESN'T HAVE SEX.
>> IN WAY.
>> HE'S CELIBATE.
HE HASN'T HAD SEX IN LIKE EIGHT
YEARS.
>> YOU'RE LYING?
>> I SWEAR TO GOD.
WHAT DO WE HAVE IN COMMON.
YOU DON'T DRINK, YOU DON'T
PARTY.
>> JOAQUIN IS A POTENTIAL DUDE I
CAN WORK WITH.
WE'RE BOTH ABOUT GIRLS.
WE'RE BOTH ABOUT HAVING FUN,
PARTYING, NOT SETTLING DOWN.
>> WE'VE DEVELOPED A
RELATIONSHIP, WE'RE LIKE APPLES
AND ORANGES.
SO OBVIOUS, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
AND I CAN TELL FROM LIKE FIRST
TIME I SAW YOU, YOU WORK HARD.
>> WE WORK HARD.
WE PARTY HARDER.
IT'S SIMPLE.
IF YOU MAKE IT TO THE END, YOU
GOT MY VOTE.
SO YOU AUTOMATICALLY.
>> I WANT THE MONEY TO STAY ON
THE EAST COAST.
>> YEAH.
>> MIAMI, ME AND YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY BROTHER.
>> I'M GOING TO BE BATMAN.
HE CAN BE ROBIN.
WE MIGHT HAVE TO SCREW SOME
PEOPLE OVER EVENTUALLY.
IN THE MEANTIME, NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT I'M DOING.
ALL THESE FOOLS WHO THINK I'M
DUMB, HE TALKS LIKE AN IDIOT,
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT I GOT
PLANNED FOR THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ESCAMECA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW NAGAROTE TRIBE.
MAX VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: ON MY GO, BOTH TRIBES
WILL RACE UP A TOWER AND THROUGH
A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
ONCE YOU'RE AT THE TOP, ONE AT A
TIME TRIBE MEMBERS WILL LAUNCH
SANDBAGS ATTEMPTING TO HIT
TARGETS OUT IN THE FIELD.
FIRST TRIBE TO HIT ALL SIX
TARGETS WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> OH, YEAH, WE DO.
>> Jeff: THIS EVENING THE
WINNING TRIBE WILL WITNESS A
TRULY MAGICAL EVENT.
YOU'LL BE TAKEN TO A TURTLE
SANCTUARY WHERE UNDER THE STARS
YOU WILL WATCH TURTLES MIGRATING
FROM THE SEA BACK TO THE BEACH
WHERE THEY WERE BORN TO LAY EGGS
TO CONTINUE THEIR LIFE CYCLE.
WHILE YOU'RE WITNESSING AND
ENJOYING THIS NATURAL WONDER,
YOU WILL FEAST ON BEEF STEW, MAC
AND CHEESE.
>> TALK TO ME, JEFF.
>> JEFFREY!
>> Jeff: HOT CHOCOLATE.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
ESCAMECA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
CANNOT SIT OUT THE SAME PERSON
IN BACK-TO-BACK CHALLENGES.
DAN, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST STAGE IS GETTING UP THIS
MASSIVE TOWER AND THROUGH THE
OBSTACLES.
>> THERE YOU GO, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: NAGAROTE FLYING UP.
ESCAMECA FLYING UP.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: GOT TO WATCH YOUR
FOOTING AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY
ACROSS THAT ROPE BRIDGE.
ESCAMECA IS FLYING THROUGH THIS.
>> YOU GOT IT.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: NAGAROTE TRYING TO
KEEP UP.
>> NICE, NICE, NICE.
>> Jeff: ESCAMECA IS BURNING
THROUGH THIS.
ONCE EVERYBODY'S TO THE BELL,
FIRST PERSON CAN GO UP.
START LAUNCHING SANDBAGS.
IT'S GOING TO BE RODNEY FOR
ESCAMECA.
WILL PULLING UP THE REAR FOR
NAGAROTE.
ONCE AGAIN A BIG EARLY LEAD FOR
ESCAMECA.
RODNEY LAUNCHES THE FIRST BAG.
HE'S SHORT.
WAY SHORT.
>> COME ON, JENN.
>> Jeff: JENN GOING TO THE TOP
FOR NAGAROTE.
IT IS RODNEY FOR ESCAMECA, JENN
RODNEY LAUNCHES AGAIN.
JUST SHORT.
HERE GOES JENN FOR NAGAROTE.
JENN SCORES THE FIRST HIT FOR
NAGAROTE.
KELLY COMING OUT NOW.
NAGAROTE HAS AN EARLY LEAD.
RODNEY SCORES FOR ESCAMECA.
WE'RE TIED 1-1678 HERE COMES
JOAQUIN NOW FOR ESCAMECA.
HERE COMES THE WIND THAT'S GOING
THE REALLY SEND THEM FLYING.
>> COME ON, KELLY.
>> Jeff: KELLY SCORES FOR
NAGAROTE.
NAGAROTE LEADS 2-1.
JOAQUIN FIRES.
JUST MISSES.
HALI NOW UP FOR NAGAROTE.
>> GOOD SHOT.
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN SCORES FOR
ESCAMECA.
WE'RE TIED 2-2.
HALI WITH A SHOT AT THAT SAME
TARGET.
SHE'S OFF.
HERE COMES SIERRA.
WE'RE TIED ONCE AGAIN.
2-2.
SIX TARGETS TOTAL.
SIERRA LAUNCHES.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: AND HITS ON HER FIRST
SHOT.
ESCAMECA NOW IN THE LEAD 3-2.
HERE COMES MIKE.
MIKE FIRES, GOING FOR THE SHORT
TARGET.
JUST MISSES.
HALI JUST MISSES.
HALI COMING DOWN.
GOING TO SEND SOMEBODY ELSE UP.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN NOW FIRING
FOR NAGAROTE.
MIKE FOR ESCAMECA.
>> OH, OH, OH.
>> Jeff: AND HE'S GOT IT.
ESCAMECA SCORES THEIR FOURTH.
ESCAMECA LEADS 4-2.
SIX TARGETS TOTAL.
CAROLYN, YOU GOT TO GET IT
GOING.
CAROLYN, LOOKS GOOD, AND IT IS.
NAGAROTE SCORES THEIR THIRD.
IT IS 4-3.
NAGAROTE CLOSES THE GAP.
HERE GOES JOE LOOKING FOR NUMBER
FIVE.
>> YOU GOT IT, JOE.
YOU GOT IT, JOE.
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
SHIRIN NOW UP FOR NAGAROTE.
SITTING ON HER BUTT.
AND SHE HITS.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WE'RE TIED, 4-4.
TWO TARGETS LEFT FOR BOTH
TRIBES.
HERE COMES WILL.
WILL SCORES FOR ESCAMECA.
ESCAMECA NOW WITH ONE TARGET
LEFT.
ESCAMECA LEADS 5-4.
>> GOOD JOB, WILL.
YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: WILL HAS GOT TO KEEP
MOVING.
WILL SCORES FOR NAGAROTE.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
AND IT'S 5-5.
THIS IS IT.
>> COME ON, JENN!
>> Jeff: JENN BACK UP FOR
NAGAROTE.
TYLER FOR ESCAMECA.
THIS IS IT.
JUST MISSES FOR ESCAMECA.
>> COME ON, JENN.
YOU GOT THIS.
YOU CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS!
NAGAROTE WINS REWARD.
>> I BELIEVE THAT WE CAN WIN.
I BELIEVE THAT WE CAN WIN!
>> Jeff: THAT WAS AN EXCITING
CHALLENGE AND NAGAROTE DID WIN.
I REALLY THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE A SPECIAL NIGHT TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ENJOY YOUR EVENING.
ESCAMECA, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> WINNING THE REWARD IS HUGE
FOR ME.
THAT GIVES ME A CHANCE TO BOND
WITH THESE PEOPLE BETTER.
AT THIS POINT I KIND OF HAVE TO
BECAUSE MY BUTT IS ON THE LINE.
>> IS THAT A PILLOW?
OH, MY GOD.
[CHEERING]
>> WINNING THE REWARD WAS
BEAUTIFUL.
IT WAS LIKE DAVID AND GOLIATH,
LIKE ALL YOU NEED WAS TO PUT A
SLINGSHOT IN OUR HAND AND WE
TOOK DOWN THAT GIANT.
>> I'M GETTING A BITE OF THAT.
>> AND THEN AS IF THAT WEREN'T
ENOUGH, EXTRA SPECIAL MACARONI
AND CHEESE, TONS OF BEEF STEW.
I FELT LIKE MY FIRST CHILD WAS
BORN, LIKE THAT'S HOW EXCITED I
WAS ABOUT THIS REWARD.
>> LOOK, THERE'S UTENSIL, GUYS.
>> WOW, THIS IS LIKE SOLID
CHEESE.
YOU'RE GOING TO FREAK OUT.
>> BEING THE UNDERDOGS THAT WE
ARE, WE WERE DOWN AND OUT AND
THEN WE PICKED OURSELVES UP AND
WE WON.
>> DO YOU WANT SOME HOT
CHOCOLATE?
>> THE TEAM IS DEFINITELY
GELLING, EVEN SHIRIN, WE'RE
TOLERATING HER AT THIS POINT.
>> THEY'RE EATING RICE, WE'RE
EATING BEEF.
YEAH, BABY.
>> RODNEY IS GOING TO BE LIKE, I
WOULD HAVE DESTROYED THAT THING.
WHAT A TOOL.
REWARD WAS REALLY GOOD FOR ME.
I WAS SUPER EXCITED TO BOND OVER
A MEAL AND MAYBE EVEN ALL GET
SICK TOGETHER, WHICH DIDN'T
HAPPEN.
>> NAGAROTE!
>> AND GETTING TO LOOK FOR
TURTLES ON THE BEACH.
>> OKAY, GUYS.
WE'LL SEE SOME TURTLES.
GRAB YOUR FLASH LIGHT AND LET'S
GO.
>> IT GAVE ME A CHANCE TO
CONNECT WITH THEM ON A HUMAN
LEVEL AND THAT'S LIKE MY BEST
SHOT AT STAYING IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW.
I THINK WE ALL DID THAT.
I THINK WE ALL HAD A MAGICAL
TIME TOGETHER.
>> OH, WOW.
>> YOU HAVE THE TURTLE HERE.
>> THEY'RE SO HUGE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE BIGGEST
TURTLE I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> WOW, THAT THING IS BIG.
>> SHE COMES FROM THE WATER.
SHE STARTS DIGGING THE HOLE AND
THEN LAYING 120 EGGS.
ONLY ONE WILL SURVIVE.
>> WOW.
>> THE TURTLE GUIDE TOLD US HOW
THE SEA TURTLES HAUL THEIR GIANT
SELVES UP THIS BEACH, DIG A
HOLE, LAY 100 SOME ODD EGGS AND
ONLY ONE OF THOSE EGGS MAYBE
WILL MAKE IT TO THE OCEAN.
>> THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> SHE'S COVERING IT UP NOW.
>> YEAH, SHE'S COVERING THE
NEST.
>> THAT'S REALLY AWESOME.
IT MADE ME REALIZE THE TURTLE
CHANCES IN LIFE ARE WAY WORSE
ODDS THAN ME WINNING "SURVIVOR."
>> SHE'S PROTECTING THE EGGS.
>> I HAVE A ONE IN 14 CHANCE AT
WINNING $1 MILLION, COMPARED TO
A ONE IN 100 CHANCE AT LIVING,
SO THAT'S COOL.
>> I WANTED THAT MAC AND CHEESE
SO BAD.
>> I'M ABOUT TO BRING UP THAT
CRAB TRAP.
>> I'M GOING TO SEE IF I CAN GET
SOME FISH.
>> YOU AND DAN HAVE AN ISSUE?
>> I HAVE AN ISSUE WITH ALL OF
THEM.
THE DAY THAT I KNEW WE WERE
GOING TO SWITCH WAS THE BEST DAY
OF MY LIFE.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU THE CHANCE TO
GIVE IT RIGHT BACK TO THEM.
I'M SO EXCITED.
THESE BLUE COLLARS, THEY WERE IN
SHAMBLES.
SIERRA WAS THE ODD WOMAN OUT,
WHICH IS PERFECT.
SO IT'S BASICALLY LIKE, HERE YOU
GO, JOAQUIN.
YOU HAVE ALL THE AMMUNITION.
IT'S LIKE AN EASY LAYUP FOR ME.
OBVIOUSLY IT'S ME AND TYLER, YOU
KNOW THAT.
TYLER'S THE MOST TRUSTWORTHY,
HONEST, GENUINE PERSON IN THIS
CAMP.
>> I GET THAT.
>> THE THING IS JOE IS REALLY
STRONG.
WE DON'T WANT JOE PLAYING TOO
FAR INTO THE GAME.
AND YOU AND RODNEY ARE LIKE...
>> NO.
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
>> NOT EVEN RODNEY?
>> NO.
>> WE NEED FOUR.
>> YOU WANT ME TO SUCK UP TO
RODNEY?
>> I THINK I CAN TAKE CARE OF
ROD NISM RIGHT OFF THE BAT WE
HIT IT OFF.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE PEOPLE FROM
MY OLD TRIBE SUCK, AND I DON'T
TRUST THEM.
SO MY BIGGEST CONNECTION AT THIS
POINT IS WITH JOAQUIN.
HE MAKES ME FEEL COMFORTABLE.
HE LOOKS ME STRAIGHT IN THE EYE.
HE'S LIKE ONE OF MY BROS FROM
HOME.
HE'S ALSO TIGHT WITH TYLER, AND
THESE TWO SEEM TO BE THE MOST
TRUST WORTHY PEOPLE I'VE MET TO
DATE.
HOWEVER, JOAQUIN'S TIGHT WITH
RODNEY, WHO IS JUST AWFUL.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF I CAN PLAY
THIS GAME WITH HIM.
>> I KNOW YOU PROBABLY DON'T
WANT NOTHING TO DO WITH ANY OF
THEM.
>> I NEED SOMEBODY HONEST.
I'M LITERALLY REACHING FOR
STRAWS AT THIS POINT.
>> WHAT'S UP, CHAMP?
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THESE
GUYS?
>> I LIKE THIS RIGHT HERE.
SIERRA IS STILL MAD AT ME.
>> I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH
HER.
>> YOU CAN'T GET MAD AT PEOPLE
AND HOLD GRUDGES.
>> SIERRA GOT MAD AT ME BECAUSE
I SAID SOME BAD THINGS ABOUT
HER, BUT GUESS WHAT, THIS IS A
GAME.
TABLES TURN AND TIME HEALS ALL.
IN ORDER TO WIN THIS GAME, I
HAVE TO PUT MYSELF IN THE BEST
POSITION AND GET THE NUMBERS.
>> THEY CAN'T KNOW.
>> YOU GOT TYLER.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE A WALK.
A WALK.
>> IF IT'S ME, JOAQUIN, SIERRA
AND TYLER ALL ON THE SAME PAGE
AND WHEN THE TIME COME, I CAN
FLIP AND TAKE OVER THIS ENTIRE
GAME.
>> WE DID HAVE A LITTLE BEEF.
>> PRIME TIME STORY.
PRIME TIME STORY TO TELL FOR THE
REST OF YOUR LIFE.
>> AT THIS POINT I'M IN A GREAT
POSITION.
I HAVE SO MANY NUMBERS IT'S NOT
EVEN FUN EYE.
I CAN SEE MY HAND BEING RAISED
LIKE ROCKY BALBOA WINNING THIS
DAMN THING AT THE END.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, ME
AND JOAQ ARE LIKE THIS.
I HAVE HIM LIKE THIS, LIKE A
YOYO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
THIS KID, HE'S GOING TO LISTEN
TO ANYTHING I SAY.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE THESE
CHALLENGES GET BLOWN, JOE'S
GOING FIRST.
I'M TELLING YOU, PUT YOUR TRUST
IN ME, I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS PLAN ALL DAY.
ALL DAY, ALL NIGHT LONG.
WHEN JOE GOES, I DEVELOP TRUST
WITH JOAC.
THIS IS MY IDEA.
I PRESENT IT TO MIKE.
IF WE BLOW NEXT IMMUNITY AND GET
IT OUT OF THIS GAME BEFORE WE GO
TO THE MERGE, WHO DO WE HAVE TO
DEAL WITH?
>> WE HAVE THIS GAME ON LOCK.
BEFORE WE GET AHEAD OF
OURSELVES, WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THE CHALLENGE GETS THROWN OR
THIS WHOLE PLAN GETS SCREWED.
>> DON'T GET ME WRONG, IT
WOULDN'T HURT MY FEELING IF WE
LOST.
>> RODNEY AND HIS GREAT VAST
PLAN OF, OH, I'M SUCH AN AMAZING
STRATEGIST AND I'M SO GOOD AT
THIS GAME THINKS WE SHOULD THROW
A CHALLENGE SO WE CAN GET RID OF
JOE.
VERY RARELY IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" DOES IT WORK OUT IN
YOUR FAVOR TO THROW CHALLENGES.
BUT IN THIS PARTICULAR INSTANCE,
I THINK WE HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
SITUATION.
MY REAL ALLIANCE IS WITH KELLY,
WHO POOR GIRL IS ON THE OTHER
SIDE ALL BY HERSELF, BUT I THINK
KELLY'S A FIGHTER, ENOUGH THAT
SHE'LL FIND A WAY TO MAKE IT TO
THE MERGE, ESPECIALLY IF WE CAN
THROW A COUPLE CHALLENGES AND
KEEP HER SAFE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THING FIRST.
JOAQUIN
.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
DROP THE CURTAIN AND RECREATE IT
ONCE YOU HAVE IT MEMORIZED.
FIRST TO GET IT RIGHT SCORES A
POINT.
FIRST TRIBE TO SCORE THREE WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
ESCAMECA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
IT IS SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
ALL RIGHT.
JOAQUIN, TAKE SPOT ON THE
SIT-OUT BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST PAIR COME ON UP.
IT IS RODNEY TAKING ON CAROLYN.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
FIRST ROUND.
HERE WE GO.
CAROLYN DROPS ON RODNEY.
RODNEY LOOKS CONFUSED.
NOW IT'S A RACE TO GET THE ITEMS
UP THERE AND GET ON YOUR MAT.
SIX ITEMS.
THAT'S A LOT TO REMEMBER.
CAROLYN SHE'S FIRST ON HER MAT.
CAROLYN HAD IT FIRST.
SHE HAS JUG, HUMAN SKULL, ANIMAL
SKULL, CAN THAT BRA, MESSAGE IN
A BOTTLE.
YOU ARE RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: NAGAROTE LEADS 1-0.
NEXT PAIR IS SIERRA TAKING ON
HALI.
>> YOU GOT THIS, HALI.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
THEY BOTH DROP AT THE SAME TIME.
SIERRA HEADING BACK.
HALI COMING BACK.
WHO IS GOING TO FINISH FIRST,
AND WILL THEY BE RIGHT?
SIERRA QUICKLY WITH TWO ITEMS.
>> YOU GOT THIS, SIERRA.
>> YOU GOT IT, HALI.
>> TRUST YOUR GUT.
>> Jeff: HALI THINKS SHE HAS
IT.
SHE STEPS ON THE MAT.
HALI WAS FIRST.
SHE HAS LANTERN, LARGE CANDLE,
MESSAGE IN THE BOTTLE,
CANDLESTICK HOLDER, CANDLE LAW
BRA AND BROWN JUG.
HALI IS RIGHT.
NAGAROTE LEADS 2-0.
NEXT PAIR COME ON OVER.
NEXT TWO.
IT IS JOE TAKING ON WILL.
COULD BE THE FINAL MATCHUP OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
WILL CAN WIN IT FOR HIS TRIBE
RIGHT HERE.
HERE WE GO.
JOE RACES BACK.
WILL RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
JOE NEEDS TO GET IT RIGHT TO
KEEP HIS TRIBE ALIVE.
JOE THINKS HE HAS IT.
STEPS ON HIS MATT.
WILL ON HIS MATT.
JOE HAS BIG CANDLE, CANDLESTICK
HOLDER, CANDELABRA, LANTERN, BIG
CANDLE.
JOE IS RIGHT.
NAGAROTE LEADS 2-1.
PLAYING TO THREE.
NEXT TWO.
IT IS SHIRIN TAKING ON DAN.
NAGAROTE COULD WIN IT RIGHT
HERE.
>> LET'S GO, SHIRIN.
>> Jeff: DAN PULLS IT.
RACING BACK.
COULD BE THE FINAL MATCHUP OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> COME ON, SHIRIN.
>> Jeff: DAN IS MAKING SOME
PROGRESS.
DAN THINKS HE HAS IT.
HE'S ON HIS MAT.
SHIRIN STEPS ON HER MATT.
DAN HAS BROWN JUG, LANTERN,
MESSAGE IN A BOTTLE, ANIMAL
SKULL, LARGE CANDLE,
CANDLESTICK.
DAN IS RIGHT.
WE'RE TIED 2-2.
>> SORRY.
I FEEL BAD.
>> Jeff: THIS IS IT.
NEXT TWO.
>> BRING IT HOME, BABY.
BRING IT HOME.
>> Jeff: IT IS A SHOWDOWN FOR
THE WIN AND IMMUNITY.
MIKE VERSUS KELLY.
TWO BLUE COLLARS NOW ON OPPOSITE
TRIBES.
>> YOU GOT THIS.
COME ON.
DEEP BREATHS.
>> COME ON, KEL.
>> Jeff: SIX ITEMS.
IT IS 2-2.
HERE WE GO.
KELLY PULLS.
MIKE STILL LOOKING AT A CURTAIN.
THE CURTAIN WAS CLOSED.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> Bianca: MIKE THINKS HE HAS
IT.
KELLY THINKS SHE HAS IT.
MIKE IS WRONG.
KELLY, THINK YOU'RE RIGHT OR
WRONG?
>> WRONG.
>> Jeff: YEAH.
KELLY IS WRONG.
BOTH WRONG.
RESET AND GO AGAIN.
>> COME ON, KELLY.
COME ON, KELLY.
YOU GOT IT.
>> YOU GOT THIS, BABE.
YOU GOT THIS.
WE ARE TIED.
>> LISTEN TO ME.
I'M GIVING IT TO YOU.
JUST LISTEN TO WHAT I SAY.
>> Jeff: IT IS THE SAME SIX
ITEMS.
HERE'S YOUR SECOND SHOT AT IT.
>> ONE AND FIVE ARE THE SKULLS.
TWO BOTTLES IN THE MIDDLE AND
TWO THINGS TO LIGHT.
>> Jeff: KELLY PULLS.
BOTH RACING BACK.
ONLY SIX ITEMS PROVING VERY
DIFFICULT FOR TWO BLUE COLLARS.
KELLY TRYING AGAIN TO MEMORIZE
SIX SIMPLE ITEMS.
YOU DON'T GET HIT THE ROUND, I'M
GOING THE MOVE IT BACK THE FIVE
ITEMS.
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: MIKE'S BACK FIRST.
KELLY IS BACK.
MIKE IS WRONG AGAIN.
KELLY, YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
>> YEAH.
I'M WRONG.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE WRONG.
WE'RE GOING THE LOSE ONE ITEM
AND MAKE IT FIVE ITEMS.
COME ON BACK.
>> COME ON, KELLY.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: SIX ITEMS PROVED TOO
DIFFICULT.
WE'LL GO BACK TO FIVE ITEMS.
>>LY CALL OUT THE ORDER, BUT I'M
GOING TO SWITCH THE BOTTLES.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
>> YOU HAVE THE TWO BOTTLES AND
THE CANDELABRA.
>> GOTCHA.
>> MIKE DRAWS FIVE ITEMS THIS
TIME.
SOMEONE IS GOING TO GET IT
RIGHT.
>> LOOK AT MINE AND SWITCH THE
BOTTLES.
>> Jeff: IT'S ALMOST LIKE
THEY'RE WAITING FOR THE OTHER TO
STEP ON THE MATT AND END THE
MISERY.
MIKE GOT TO HIS MAT A STEP
BEFORE KELLY.
THAT IS NOT RIGHT.
KELLY HAS HUMAN SKULL, BROWN
JUG, MESSAGE IN A BOTTLE,
CANDELABRA AND ANIMAL SKULL.
IF KELLY'S RIGHT, NAGAROTE WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU GUYS ARE CERTAIN, AND YOU
ARE RIGHT.
NAGAROTE WINS IMMUNITY SENDING
ESCAMECA TO TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
NAGAROTE, CONGRATULATIONINGS.
BIG WIN, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
>> YEAH, BABY.
>> Jeff: ESCAMECA, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE SIXTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> WHEN I KNEW MIKE WAS THROWING
THE CHALLENGE AND HELPING ME
OUT, I THINK THAT'S FIRST TIME I
TOTAL EVER TRUSTED SOMEBODY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK WITH MY
BLUE COLLAR TRIBE, WHERE I
BELONG.
>> I WISH YOU WOULD HAVE WENT
INSTEAD OF ME.
>> LISTEN, I COULD HAVE DONE
EXACTLY LIKE YOU GUYS.
I COULD HAVE DONE WORSE.
IT'S LIFE.
IT GOES ON.
>> SORRY, Y'ALL.
>> BY THROWING THE CHALLENGE
TODAY, A LITTLE SOMETHING INSIDE
OF ME DIED IN THIS GAME.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE TO YOU.
>> BUT HERE'S THE DEAL, I'M
STARTING TO NOT TRUST RODNEY.
I GOT THIS GIRL GIVING ME THIS
LITTLE PERSON OF RICE.
>> JOAQUIN IS JUST DRAFTING
RODNEY IN EVERY SECOND, MORE AND
MORE, AND IN THIS GAME, WHENEVER
YOU START SHOWING YOU'RE TOO
CLOSE TO SOMEBODY, YOUK WITH A
POWER COUPLE, AND THE POWER
COUPLES HAVE TO BE SPLIT UP
BEFORE THEY CAN START MAKING
POWER MOVES.
>> HEY, HERE'S WHAT WE NEED TO
TALK ABOUT.
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT TRIBAL
TONIGHT.
>> OKAY.
LISTEN, JOE IS GOING FIRST, BRO.
JOE IS GOING.
>> WE GOT EVERYBODY ON BOARD.
-- HE HAS NO IDEA.
IT'S OVER.
>> 100%?
>> WE ALREADY KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BROTHER.
>> WE KNOW WHAT'S UP.
>> TODAY AT THE CHALLENGE, WE
CAME TO DO ONE THING AND ONE
THING ONLY, AND THAT WAS TO BLOW
IT.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
MIKE LOOKED LIKE AN ABSOLUTE
IDIOT, WHICH WAS HILARIOUS, BUT
IT WORKED OUT PERFECTLY.
NOW WE'LL GET JOE OUT OF HERE.
HE'S A THREAT, SO HE'S GOING
HOME NOW.
>> BRO, WE CAN'T LOSE SIERRA.
SIERRA IS KEY.
>> THIS GAME IS ABOUT ME AND
YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT ANYBODY
ELSE, BRO.
>> WE'RE TAKING... I'M TELLING
YOU, THIS IS GOING TO BE A WALK
IN THE PARK.
>> WHO ELSE WOUND YOU WANT THE
SHARE THIS MOMENT WITH?
I'M TALKING RED SOX-YANKEES.
I HAVE SO MUCH LOVE FOR YOU.
>> BRO, THIS IS SO PERFECT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
HONESTLY, I THOUGHT IT WAS ME
AND TYLER AGAINST THE WORLD, BUT
NOW RODNEY IS MY RIGHT-HAND GUY.
AND SIERRA OWES ME ONE.
I TOOK HER OUT OF THIS SITUATION
WHERE SHE WAS LIKE THE ONE TO
GO.
SO, YOU KNOW, JOE'S DEFINITELY
GOING HOME.
AND IT SHOULD BE A WALK IN THE
PARK FROM NOW ON.
>> JOE, WHERE'S YOUR HEAD AT?
>> MAN, I'M DOWN TO DO ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING.
EVERY TIME I TRAW TO TALK TO
JOAQUIN TO SEE WHERE HIS HEAD'S
AT, HE'S GOT A PUPPY DOG
FOLLOWING HIM.
>> I THINK THOSE TWO
WHITE-COLLAR BOYS ARE PLAYING US
FOR A FIDDLE.
THEY'VE REELED RODNEY RIGHT IN,
AND I'M AFRAID THEY'RE GOING TO
BE REELING SIERRA IN AND US
THREE ARE GOING TO BE ON THE
OUTS.
>> TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
RODNEY CAME TO ME AND WAS LIKE,
WE GOT TO GET JOE OUT FIRST.
>> I WAS HOPING TO REACH OUT TO
TYLER AND JOAQUIN, BUT THEY
DON'T TALK TO ME AT ALL.
I THOUGHT THE THREE OF US COULD
WORK TOGETHER, BUT IT SEEMS THAT
THEY'RE GUNNING FOR ME, SO I'M
KIND OF SCREWED.
>> WHEN WE FIRST GOT HERE IT WAS
LIKE SIERRA, SIERRA, SIERRA, WE
THOUGHT SHE WAS ON THE OUTS.
>> SHE WAS.
>> SHE'S STILL REALLY MAD AT
DAN.
UNDERLYING ISSUE, SHE'S REALLY
NOT HAPPY.
>> AND I'VE DONE NOTHING BUT
GROVEL, BUT I THINK AS LONG AS
IT'S NOT HER NAME AGAIN, SHE'LL
GO ALONG WITH ANYTHING.
>> AT THIS POINT, MY OPTIONS ARE
LIMITED, SO YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE
BEST OF THE WORST SCENARIO.
AND HOPE IT WORKS OUT.
>> SIERRA WOULD BE THE SWING.
>> YEP.
>> IF WE HAD SIERRA, WE'LL SEND
JOAQUIN HOME.
>> AT THIS POINT, JOE IS WITH
US.
UNFORTUNATELY SIERRA AND I
DEFINITELY HIT A ROUGH PATCH.
I BLEW IT.
HANDS DOWN.
NO EXCUSES.
NO GETTING AROUND IT.
I SCREWED UP.
AND NOW WE NEED TO BRING HER
BACK INTO THE FOLD.
>> LOOKING AT RODNEY WITH
JOAQUIN, WE HAVE TO SEPARATE
THOSE TWO.
LISTEN, I SCREWED UP.
I WANT TO EARN YOUR TRUST BACK,
BUT WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
WE GOT RID OF HER BEST FRIEND
BECAUSE SHE WAS GETTING TOO
CLOSE, AND WE HAVE TO DO THE
SAME THING.
AGREED?
>> AT THIS POINT I HAVE TWO
SEPARATE ALLIANCES SAYING, COME
WITH US, WE'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU,
AND IT'S NICE, IT'S REFRESHING
TO HAVE PEOPLE WANT ME.
HOWEVER, TO HAVE MY OLD TRIBE
HURT ME SO BAD AND NOW SAY THEY
NEED ME, IT MAKES ME SICK TO MY
STOMACH.
>> JOE WOULD VOTE FOR JOAQUIN,
AS LONG AS IT ISN'T HIM, HE'LL
BE HAPPY.
RODNEY ON FIRST VOTE LEAVES THE
THREE OF US, PLUS JOE.
WE STILL HAVE THE NUMBERS, BUT
AS SOON AS WE HIT JOAQUIN,
RODNEY IS GOING TO EXPLODE.
JUST CLOSE YOUR MOUTH, OPEN YOUR
EARS AND JUST WATCH WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> I HATE DAN.
AND AT THIS POINT, I'M JUST VERY
ANGRY.
THE BLUE COLLARS, THEY DON'T
CARE ABOUT ME.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO KEEP ME
AROUND.
THEY'RE JUST USING ME FOR THE
MOMENT.
>> EVERYBODY'S WRITING JOE'S
NAME.
EVERYBODY.
>> I'M WITH YOU, MAN.
>> I'M JUST THE TYPE OF PERSON,
I PLAY WITH MY HEART AND MY
HEAD, AND, OF COURSE NEW YORK
THIS GAME, IT'S GOING TO GET ME
IN TROUBLE.
AT THIS PILOT I'M PLAYING BOTH
SIDES.
I DON'T KNOW, NOT ONLY WHO TO
TRUST, BUT WHO IS GOING TO BE
BETTER IN THE LONG RUN.
YOU CAN CHOOSE ONE PATH AND IT
MIGHT TAKE ME TO THE FINAL
THREE.
YOU NEVER KNOW, AND I STILL AT
THIS POINT DO NOT KNOW WHICH
ROUTE I'M GOING TO TAKE.
BUT EITHER WAY, IT COULD CHANGE
THE WHOLE GAME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO AFTER THE SWITCH WE END UP
WITH FOUR BLUE COLLARS, TWO
WHITE COLLARS AND ONE NO COLLAR.
JOE, WHEN YOU GOT BACK TO CAMP,
DID IT APPEAR THE FOUR BLUE
COLLARS WERE VERY HAPPY THAT
THEY HAD STAYED TOGETHER IN THIS
RANDOM REDRAW?
>> ON THE SURFACE, THEY SEEMED
LIKE ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
BUT EVERY FAMILY IS IMPERFECT,
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE FEUDS AND
CRACKS AND ME, JOAQUIN AND TYLER
WERE DEFINITELY TRYING TO FIND
THOSE AND EXPLOIT THEM A LITTLE
BIT.
>> Jeff: DAN, DID YOU SENSE
THAT, THAT THESE THREE WERE
TRYING THE LOOK FOR SOME WAY IN?
>> YEAH.
THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN SOME
OPPORTUNITIES TO EXPLOIT.
TO SAY THERE WERE CRACKS IN THE
ARMOUR, THERE'S NO TWO WAYS
ABOUT IT.
THERE'S DYSFUNCTION HERE.
SO I'M DEFINITELY CONCERNED.
>> Jeff: SO TYLER, WHAT DO YOU
LOOK FOR?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO PICK UP
ON?
>> HONESTLY, JEFF.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
WHAT WE FOUND WAS BAD BLOOD AND
ANIMOSITY AND A LOT OF IT SEEMED
TO REVOLVE AROUND SIERRA.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, IS THAT TRUE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL, I WAS
MISTREATED.
I WAS TOLD HOW I SUCK AT
CHALLENGES, HOW I DON'T HELP
AROUND CAMP, JUST EVERYTHING YOU
COULD PUT ON ME, THEY DID.
>> NOT ALL OF US PICKED ON YOU.
>> WHEN IT WAS GOING DOWN, MIKE
STOOD IN AND SAID, YOU GUYS, YOU
HAVE TO STOP.
I'LL GIVE HIM THAT, BUT I FELT
MORE APPRECIATED IN 24 HOURS
WITH THESE PEOPLE THAN I FELT 11
DAYS WITH THESE THREE BEHIND ME.
>> Jeff: WOW.
MIKE, THIS IS NOT GOOD NEWS.
YOU'RE NOW IN A SITUATION WHERE
IF SIERRA WANTS TO MOVE TO THE
OTHER SIDE, THE GAME FLIPS AND
YOU, DAN AND RODNEY ARE IN
TROUBLE.
>> WELL, I MEAN, THE FOUR OF US
HAVE BEEN TOGETHER NOW FOR 16
DAYS.
BUT I DON'T FEEL THAT WE ARE A
FOURSOME OF IMPENETRABLENESS.
AND IF THESE THREE WERE ABLE TO
SEE SOME TYPE OF CRACK AND WOO
ONE OF US IN, I'M DEFINITELY
AFRAID TONIGHT, 100%.
>> BUT, JEFF, THAT'S THE BEAUTY
ABOUT WHEN YOU DROP YOUR BUFFS.
OPPORTUNITIES OPEN.
THERE WAS DEFINITELY SOME
PROBLEMS WITH ALL OF US, BUT I
GOT THREE NEW PEOPLE OVER HERE,
I GOT THREE PEOPLE I'VE BEEN
DEALING WITH, YOU KNOW, FOR 16
DAYS DRIVING ME NUTS.
I MEAN, WHAT'S GOING TO BE THE
BEST OPPORTUNITY FOR ME?
>> Jeff: JOAQUIN, WOULD YOU
HAVE EVER IMAGINED THAT YOU'D BE
SITTING AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
THINKING, I'M NOT AS CONCERNED
AS I THOUGHT I WOULD HAVE BEEN A
FEW DAYS AGO.
>> I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS GOING
TO GO THIS WAY, JEFF, BUT WHEN
PEOPLE COME UP TO YOU AND
BASICALLY EXPLAIN THEIR
REASONING FOR HATING EACH OTHER,
IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN ANY EASIER
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: JOE, IS THERE ANY
PART OF YOU THAT'S WONDERING HOW
MUCH OF WHAT THEY'RE SAYING IS
TRUE AND HOW MUCH OF WHAT
THEY'RE SAYING IS WHAT THEY
THINK YOU WANT TO HEAR?
>> YEAH, THESE FOUR COULD SIT
THERE AND SAY, LET'S KNOCK 'EM
OUT ONE BY ONE, BUT
STRATEGY-WISE, I'M ON THE VERY
BOTTOM, AT LEAST JOAQUIN HAS
TYLER.
I GOT NOBODY.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, ONE OF THE
HALLMARKS OF WHAT YOU HAVE SAID
AS BLUE COLLARS IS THAT WE DO
ULTIMATELY TAKE CARE OF EACH
OTHER.
>> JEFF, IT WASN'T THAT MY NAME
WAS WRITTEN DOWN.
IT WAS WHEN WE GOT BACK TO CAMP
AND I GOT ATTACKED PERSONALLY.
I CAN'T TRUST PEOPLE WHO DO
THAT.
>> Jeff: BUT NO MATTER HOW
MUCH YOU DON'T LIKE SOMEBODY,
YOU'VE GOT FOUR RIGHT THERE.
WHY NOT SIT TOGETHER FOR A
COUPLE MORE VOTES.
>> RIGHT.
NEW YORK I MEAN, I'M NOT STUPID,
I GET THAT.
THERE ARE SOME GENUINE
FRIENDSHIPS THAT I'VE GAINED
WITH THESE PEOPLE, SO I HAVE TO
LOOK AT IT AS A WHOLE AND BE
LIKE, WHO DO I TRUST AT THIS
POINT.
>> Jeff: MIKE, IT'S KIND OF
LIKE YOU WERE DATING AND THEN
SOMEBODY DID SOMETHING WRONG,
BUT YOU STILL LOVE, YOU WANT TO
COME BACK, BUT YOU GOT TO WORK
IT BECAUSE THERE'S ANOTHER GUY
OVER THERE AND HE'S WOOING HER,
AND IN THIS CASE IT'S SIERRA.
[LAUGHTER]
SMILES ASIDE, WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU CAN'T JUST SIT THERE AND
SAY, SIERRA, IF YOU GOT TO GO,
YOU GOT TO GO.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY YOU
HOPEFULLY CAN BELIEVE IN THE
TRUST THAT YOU HAVE MADE EARLY
ON OR THE TRUST THAT YOU HAVE
MADE WITH NEW FRIENDS, BUT YOU
NEVER KNOW WHO YOU CAN TRUST
UNTIL YOU LEAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND THAT'S A VERY, VERY, VERY
SCARY PREDICAMENT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: IT SOUNDS LIKE THE
DECISION OF WHO TO SEND HOME
TONIGHT COULD BE A VERY BIG ONE
FOR THIS GROUP.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> SORRY, RODNEY.
>> JOAQUIN, LOOKS LIKE IT'S ME
OR YOU TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JOE.
JOAQUIN.
JOE.
TWO VOTES JOE, TWO VOTES
JOAQUIN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JOE.
THREE VOTES JOE, THREE VOTES
JOAQUIN.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT, JOAQUIN.
PLEASE BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JOAQUIN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, TONIGHT'S CONVERSATION
CENTERED AROUND CRACKS.
YOUR SUCCESS IN THIS GAME
DEPENDS ON YOUR ABILITY TO
REPAIR OR EXPLOIT THOSE CRACKS
DAY BY DAY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> TEAMING UP BEHIND MY BACK?
>> Jeff: RODNEY FEELS BETRAYED
BY HIS BLUE-COLLAR FAMILY.
>> PEOPLE WHO DID ME WRONG TODAY
ARE GOING TO PAY.
>> Jeff: BUT IN "SURVIVOR"
THERE'S ALWAYS TIME FOR REVENGE.
>> I FELT EXTREMELY DISRESPECTED
BY THESE BLUE, SO YOUR NUMBERS
ARE DUNSO.
>> I TOTALLY GOT BLINDSIDED BY
THE FOUR.
I HAVE A GOOD GUESS.
I'M SURE MIKE WAS OBSESSED WITH
SIERRA.
I WAS GETTING TOO CLOSE WITH
SIERRA AND RODNEY.
THEY WERE FEELING LIKE I WAS
PULLING THEIR TRIBE AWAY THERE
THEM.
GET THIS GUY OUT OF HERE.
BUT THIS IS MY FAITH.
I'M GOING THE TAKE WITH IT A