translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Throw away your bandanas!
We change things.
After a surprise change,
Kelly was the only Blue
in a tribe that was undermanned.
I'm terrified.
The other Blues
enjoyed a 4-3 advantage.
But not everyone was happy.
I think
my former teammates suck.
But I have 3 new people.
It's a brand new game.
On the camp, Joaquin
and Rodney grew closer.
Rodney looks
like my buddies back home.
I'm so glad to have you.
These people fear a lot.
Sierra was looking to
distance herself from the old Blues.
I want to go
where I am wanted.
And I don't think it's
with the Bleus de Travail.
At the last immunity test...
Escameca wins immunity!
Away from the council!
...Nagarote failed to follow.
Bon sang!
Approaching the board...
Allies Max and Shirin
clashed
for the title
of the most annoying team member.
Is it a plantar wart?
Yeah. Sorry, that's disgusting.
Who is the most painful?
It's like a horse race.
Is it Shirin? No, here is Max
and his plantar wart!
And at the council, Max prevailed...
Fifth person eliminated...
...leaving Shirin isolated.
Max, the tribe has spoken.
There are 13 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The advice
was shocking to me.
Max was my friend
and my closest ally.
It was a complete surprise.
And it's heartbreaking.
So you won't work
with me from now on?
I don't know Shirin.
I don't know
if I can trust you.
Day after day,
you only spoke with Max.
'Cause he
always drew me aside to talk,
especially here, he was freaking out.
Non, Shirin.
You were his puppet.
You treated me
like a nobody,
we've been here three days.
- I was spending time with them.
- Exactly.
Why ? To recruit them?
- I thought we were friends.
- To ensure a majority.
OK. Well, when I think of loyalty,
I think true loyalty,
not false loyalty.
Is there anyone
left who wants to play with me?
I do not believe.
Sad observation. Is it me,
is it my personality?
What should I change?
You must be a little
shaken up from last night.
Yes. I really thought
it would be Will and...
- It was hard.
- Yeah.
Max did things
that annoyed everyone.
And to be frank,
you also do annoying things.
It's really hard for me,
because the position in which
I constantly find myself here
reminds me of
what I experienced in my childhood.
I grew up in a wealthy
suburb of Orange County.
My classmates were
mostly handsome and thin.
I was out of place,
being neither.
I constantly felt like
I was fighting to be liked,
so that we can see...
The good qualities in me.
And there's probably
quite a bit of that here.
But I'm trying to do now
what I couldn't do then,
to know how to manage the situation,
adapt, fix things.
It was the fourth day
I had to go in the water.
And a wave swept away my underpants.
Plus the briefs.
It was a sticky thing!
It was not a tight thing,
nor a thong!
It didn't
fit in my ass, OK!
I'm on this beach
with the same people,
who tell
the same bullshit over and over again.
It's really depressing.
I was hoping for a mixture to
find a new energy,
maybe finding myself with people
who I know look like me.
- Always the same faces, fed up!
- Yeah.
The same stories
over and over again.
We gotta stick together
if we wanna stay sane.
I was really happy
that Joaq was one of the new ones.
Because clearly, no one binds
to the kid from the east coast!
You got a bigot from Texas,
a hick from Maine,
another one from Utah...
I was waiting
for some form of link in this game.
I was looking for a friendship,
a friend to hang out with.
Listen.
I don't think I can
trust Mike.
He's from the South, he goes
to church every Sunday.
- Do you do that? No.
- Nope.
- And the relaxation of Sunday, then?
- Yeah.
- [???]
- Exactly.
- He doesn't fuck.
- It's not true !
He is single. He doesn't fuck.
- Kind for eight years.
- You kidding.
I swear to God.
So what do we have in common?
You don't drink,
you don't party...
Bon sang ...
Joaquin, at this point,
he's someone
I can work with.
We like girls, we like to have fun,
party, don't settle down...
We're developing
a relationship, bro.
Exactly.
We are day and night.
It's obvious, isn't it?
It's clear.
And you know...
I knew it the first moment.
If we work a lot,
we will party even more.
- Yeah.
- It's simple.
Let me tell you something.
If you make it to the end, you have my vote.
- The same.
- So automatically...
I want the money
to stay on the east coast.
- Yeah, on the east coast!
- Miami, you and me!
Clear, my brother!
I will be Batman and he will be Robin.
We may have to betray people,
but in the meantime,
no one knows what I'm doing.
All those who believe me finished,
"he talks like a moron"...
Wait and see what I have planned!
Over here everyone!
Escameca, discover
the new Nagarote tribe.
Max was eliminated at the last council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Yeah !
- Absolutely !
At my top, you will climb a tower,
overcoming a series of obstacles.
Once at the top, one by one
you will pull sandbags
to targets below.
The first tribe
to hit all six targets
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Oh yeah!
Tonight, the winning tribe
will witness a
truly magical event.
You will go to
a turtle sanctuary,
where under the stars you will look
turtles migrate
from the sea to the beach,
where they were born, to lay eggs
and perpetuate their life cycle.
While witnessing
this wonder of nature,
you will feast
on beef stew,
pasta gratin,
- Talk to me, Jeff!
- Come on, Jeffrey!
Talk to me !
Hot chocolate.
Hot chocolate ?
- Hot chocolate !
- I know it's worth it.
Escameca, you are one more.
Someone will not participate.
It can't be
the same person twice in a row.
Dan. Take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute
to get organized and we'll start.
OK, here we go. For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
First step:
climb this huge tower
and overcome obstacles.
Come on guys, it's good!
Nagarote flies to the top.
Escameca flies to the top.
Come on !
Watch your feet
when crossing this rope bridge!
Escameca flies over the obstacle.
- Its good.
- Nagarote tries to follow.
Well, well!
Escameca is going all out!
When everyone is in the barrels,
a 1st person can go up.
Well, that's good!
Start shooting!
- It's Rodney for Escameca.
- Come on Will!
Will brings up the rear for Nagarote,
once again.
Escameca took a nice advantage.
Rodney pulls the first sack.
Too short.
Go Jenn!
Jenn climbs to the top for Nagarote.
It's Rodney for Escameca,
Jenn pour Nagarote.
- And There you go !
- Rodney shoots again.
Just too short.
And this is Jenn for Nagarote.
Jenn scores
the first point for Nagarote.
- Yes !
- Kelly is coming up now.
Nagarote took the lead.
Rodney scores for Escameca.
Tie, 1-1!
Now here is
Joaquin for Escameca.
The wind is picking up,
these bags are really going to fly!
Kelly scores for Nagarote.
Nagarote leads 2-1.
Joaquin shoot.
Just missed.
Hali is now riding for Nagarote.
Nice shot.
Joaquin scores for Escameca.
Tied, 2-2.
- Come on Hali!
- Hali is aiming for the same target.
It missed.
This is Sierra.
Still tied, 2-2.
Six targets in all.
- Sierra shoots.
- Attractive !
And score the first time!
Escameca now leads, 3-2.
This is Mike.
Mike aims for the nearest target.
Just missed.
- Hali just misses.
- We change !
Hali comes back down,
someone will take his place.
It's good, it's good!
Carolyn is
now shooting for Nagarote,
Mike for Escameca.
And he touches!
Escameca scores a 4th point.
Scales men 4-2.
Six targets in all.
Carolyn must persevere!
Carolyn. It's gone well.
And it's good !
3rd point for Nagarote.
- Go on !
- Nagarote closes the gap.
Joe is looking to score a 5th point.
It's good, Joe!
Just missed.
Shirin's turn for Nagarote.
She sits down!
- And she scores!
- Yes !
Tied, 4-4!
Two more targets
for each tribe.
This is Will.
Joe is still trying
to hit a target.
And There you go !
Joe scores for Escameca.
- Go ahead, Tyler!
- More than a target for Escameca.
It scales mene 5-4.
It's okay, Will!
Will needs to activate.
Will scores for Nagarote.
New equality!
5-5, everything is played there!
Jenn, back for Nagarote.
Tyler for Escameca.
- Come on Tyler!
- It's happening there!
Just missed for Escameca.
Come on Jenn, it's good!
You can do it.
That's it !
Nagarote wins the reward!
We can win, I believe in it!
An exciting event,
and Nagarote, a great victory!
I think the evening
will be special for you.
Take your things,
return to camp. Have a good evening !
Escameca, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
Winning the award,
for me, is huge,
because it gives me a chance
to relate better to these people.
At this point, I rather have an interest,
because I am in the hot seat.
Is it a pillow?
Oh my God !
Winning the award
was splendid.
It was David versus Goliath.
It was enough
to give us a slingshot
to bring down the giant.
Cut the bread!
- Oh my God !
- That, I want a piece!
And in case that's not enough,
extra pasta gratin,
tons of beef stew...
Oh yeah !
It was as if I had had
my first child.
To tell you
how excited I was!
Look, utensils!
Wow, there's no shortage of cheese!
Being the outsiders,
we were depressed.
And then we recovered,
and we won.
- Hot chocolate ?
- Thanks.
I'll fill it up a bit.
The team begins to bond.
Even Shirin, we tolerate her
at this point.
It's too good.
They eat rice, we eat beef.
Yeah, baby!
Rodney is going to say,
"I would have destroyed that thing!
I need protein!".
What a moron !
The reward
clearly benefited me.
I was excited to
bond over a meal,
and maybe even throw up together,
which didn't happen.
- Nagarote!
And go see
the turtles on the beach...
Good.
Let's go see some turtles.
Take your flashlights.
Let's go!
It gave me
a human connection with them.
It's my best chance
to stay in the game.
It was the same for everyone.
We shared a magical moment.
Oh wow!
Good. Here is the turtle.
They are huge!
Oh my God !
- Oh my God !
- It's the biggest one I've seen.
How big is she!
She comes from water.
Big turtle.
She starts digging and then...
She lays 120 eggs.
But only one will survive.
The guide explained to us
that sea turtles move
their huge bodies on the beach,
dig a hole,
lay a hundred eggs,
and that only one of these eggs
may reach the ocean.
It's incredible.
She covers them.
Yes, it covers the nest.
It was awesome.
I was fascinated, but also,
I realized that turtles were
much less likely to live
than me to win Survivor.
She jumps on the sand
to protect the eggs
from predators.
I already have a
1 in 14 chance of winning a million,
compared to a one in 100 chance
of living. So that's cool.
Oh my God, I did it!
You did it !
I was so craving
pasta gratin!
- You have no idea.
- So much !
I'll bring that crab trap back.
I'll go to the river, see
if I can catch any fish.
Perfect. We have a little time.
Do you have a problem with Dan?
I have a problem with all of them.
The day I knew
we were going to mingle,
It was the best day
of my life, I...
Swing my bandana.
Really ?
I'll give you a chance
to get your revenge.
I am very excited.
I'm coming here,
and these overalls,
it was the mess.
Sierra stood out,
which is perfect.
Basically it was...
"Go-y, Joaquin!
You have all the ammo."
It was the perfect setup.
Tyler and I
are together, you know that.
He is the most reliable,
honest and genuine person on this camp.
I realize that.
But Joe is very strong.
We don't want it to go too far.
OK.
And you and Rodney are...
No kidding. Not even Rodney?
Surely not !
He treats me with contempt
and he's a cunning one.
- So...
- There must be four of us.
So I have to put up with Rodney?
I think I can handle Rodney.
We got along right away.
My former teammates suck.
And I don't trust them.
So...
My best contact
so far is with Joaquin.
He puts me at ease.
He looks me in the face.
He is like my friends.
He is also close to Tyler.
And these two seem to be
the most trustworthy
that I have encountered.
But Joaquin is also
close to Rodney,
which is awful. I don't know
if I can play with him.
You probably don't want
anything to do with them.
I need someone honest.
I cling to the branches there.
How's it going, champ?
What do you think of these guys?
I like this company.
It's just...
I need to speak with Sierra.
Is she still mad at me?
I know, we talked about it.
We cannot hold a grudge.
Yeah.
Sierra is mad at me for
talking badly about her.
But you know what? It's a game.
The wind is turning.
Time erases wounds.
To win, I have to position myself well
and see the balance of power.
They must not know
that we are associated with Sierra.
- It's certain.
- We agree ?
- Do you have Tyler?
- We're welded.
It's gonna be a walk.
A walk.
If it's Joaquin, Sierra, Tyler
and I, on the same page...
When the time comes,
I can turn around
and take control of the game.
We had words, but...
Now we're going together
to the promised land,
it will be historic.
Historical. You can
talk about this all your life.
At this point,
my position is excellent.
I have so many allies
it's not even funny.
I'm so confident that I
can already imagine someone raising my hand,
like when Rocky Balboa
wins at the end.
Let me tell you something.
Joaq and I are like that.
I hold it like this,
like a yo-yo.
You understand ?
This kid will follow everything I say.
We gotta make sure we
lose the trial
for Joe to go first.
Trust me,
I thought about it all day.
- Me too, last night.
- All day, all night.
Joe gone, I'll build
trust with Joaq.
It's my idea,
I pitched it to Mike.
If we lose immunity on purpose
and that we eliminate Joe before the merger,
who will oppose us?
We have all the cards
in hand, but we have to act.
No precipitation.
We must first
make sure that we lose,
otherwise the whole plan falls apart.
Don't take it badly,
but I would suffer,
if we lost.
"I'm such a good strategist,
so good at this game!"
He thinks we should lose
immunity to eliminate Joe.
Losing on purpose
rarely pays off in Survivor.
But in this specific case,
I think we have
a very special situation.
My true ally is Kelly.
The poor thing is on the other side,
all alone.
But I think
Kelly is a fighter,
enough to find the way
to achieve fusion.
Especially when...
We lose one or two
events on purpose and we protect it.
Over here everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
- Yes !
- First of all, Joaquin...
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today we are going to
test your memory.
It is very simple. I will
show you a series of objects,
in a specific order.
When you have memorized them,
you will pull a lever,
drop a curtain,
and reproduce the sequence.
The first person
to succeed scores a point.
The first three-point tribe
wins immunity,
is out of the vote.
The losers go to the council,
where someone will be
the sixth person eliminated.
Escameca, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Good. Joaquin,
take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute to
get organized and we'll start.
Good. First pair,
step forward!
Rodney confronts Carolyn.
Come on buddy!
Immunity is at stake.
First run.
Let's go.
Carolyn raises the curtain.
Rodney looks puzzled.
It's who will place the objects the fastest and return to the mat.
Six objects. Lots to remember.
Carolyn, first on the mat.
Carolyn was the first.
She has: brown jug,
human skull, animal skull,
candelabrum, candlestick
and bottle by the sea.
- It's just !
- Yes !
Nagarote leads 1-0.
Next pair!
The next two
are Sierra versus Hali.
You will get there, Hali!
Let's go.
The two raise
the curtain together.
Sierra returns. Hali returns.
Who will finish first?
And will it be fair?
Sierra quickly places two objects.
It's good, Sierra.
- Hali proceeds backwards.
- It's okay, Hali.
Follow your instincts!
Hali thinks it's good,
she goes to the mat.
Hali was the first.
She has: lantern, large candle,
bottle in the sea,
candlestick, candelabra and brown jug.
Hali is right.
Nagarote leads 2-0.
Next pair, come closer!
The next two
are Joe versus Will.
Perhaps the last confrontation
of this ordeal.
Will can now give
the victory to his team.
Let's go.
Joe pulls the lever.
He returns, Will on his heels.
Joe must succeed to keep
his tribe in the game.
Joe thinks it's good,
he goes to his mat.
Will is on his own.
large candle, candle
holder, candelabra,
lantern, large candle,
candelabra.
It's just.
Joe is right.
Nagarote leads 2-1.
We go to three points.
To the next two!
Program affronte Dan.
Nagarote can win now.
Allez Shirin!
Dan pulls the lever and comes back.
- Maybe the last showdown.
- Come on Shirin!
And progress.
Dan thinks it's good.
He is on his mat.
Shirin goes to her mat.
Dan has:
brown jug, lantern,
bottle in the sea,
animal skull,
large candle, candle holder.
Dan is right. Tied, 2-2.
I suck at that.
This time, there it is.
The next two!
Bring us victory!
It's a showdown
for victory and immunity.
Two Labor Blues, now
in competing tribes.
It's good, come on!
- Breathe well!
- Come on, Kel!
Six objects. We are at 2-2.
Let's go !
Kelly pulls the lever.
Mike stands staring at a curtain.
The curtain was closed!
I don't know.
Mike thinks it's good.
Kelly thinks it's good.
Mike se trumpet.
Kelly, do you think that's fair?
- Nope.
- Yeah. Kelly is wrong.
Both are wrong.
We start again.
- Come on, Kelly!
- It's okay, Kelly!
It's good, it's good!
There is a tie, 2-2.
Listen to me, I'll leave it to you.
- What ?
- Listen to me, I'll leave it to you.
They are the same six objects.
Here is your second chance.
1 and 5 are the skulls.
Two bottles in the middle.
And two light things.
Kelly pulls the lever.
Both come back.
- Skulls in 1 and 5...
- Six objects only,
which cause difficulties
for two Work Blues.
Kelly tries to
remember again
of six simple objects.
If you can't find it,
we'll go down to five items.
- Its good.
- Michael, first on his mat.
Kelly is on her mat.
Mike is wrong again.
Kelly, you shake your head.
- Yeah, that's wrong.
- Indeed, it is false.
We're going to remove one object
and go to five.
Come, let's start again.
Come on, Kelly!
Let's go.
Six items was too much.
We go down to five.
I'll say the order out loud
and reverse the bottles.
Let's go.
Skulls: 1 and 5.
- The two bottles and the candelabra.
- Its good.
Mike pulls the lever.
Five objects this time.
Someone will do well!
I'm confident !
Look at mine
and reverse the bottles.
It's like they're waiting
for each other to hit the mat
and ease their suffering.
Its good.
Mike reached his mat
just before Kelly,
but he is wrong.
Kelly has:
human skull, brown jug,
bottle in the sea,
candelabra, animal skull.
If Kelly is right,
Nagarote wins immunity,
is shielded from the board.
Are you sure of yourself?
And you're right.
Nagarote wins immunity,
sending Escameca to the council,
where someone will be
the sixth person eliminated.
Nagarote, congratulations!
Big win,
no advice tonight.
Give it to Hali!
Yeah, baby!
Escameca, tonight, advice,
where someone will be
the sixth person eliminated.
Take your things, return
to camp. See you tonight at the council.
When I found out that Michael
was losing on purpose to help me,
it was the first time in my life
that I completely
trusted someone.
Without reservation. "He protects me."
I can't wait
to get back to my blue tribe.
This is where I belong.
Head held high ! Stay proud.
- Sorry.
- No, no need to be sorry.
You should have gone there for me.
No, listen.
I could have done
the same, or worse.
That's life. And she continues.
[???] Sorry.
Losing on purpose today,
a little something
died in me, in this game.
I won't lie to you.
But here's the thing.
I'm starting to get suspicious of Rodney.
...And this girl gives me
a very small portion of rice.
One to each.
Joaquin pulls Rodney closer to him,
more every moment.
And in this game
when you show yourself
very close to someone,
you become a strong pair.
Strong pairs
must be separated immediately,
before you can
make big shots.
We need to talk.
- Let's talk about the board.
- OK.
Listen. Joe leaves first.
Joe leaves.
Everyone is leaving.
He doesn't suspect a thing.
- We'll talk later.
- 100% safe.
Let's pretend
we haven't talked about strategy.
We are already clear.
We know what's going on.
Today, in the test,
we were resolved on one thing,
namely to lose it.
Mission accomplished.
Mike came across as an idiot,
it was hilarious.
But it worked perfectly.
Now we have to get Joe out.
He is dangerous.
So he will leave.
Hey, my brother!
We can't lose Sierra.
Sierra is crucial.
- Listen. This game is for us.
- I say.
I don't care about others.
- So if anyone...
- We'll go all the way.
I tell you, it will be a walk.
Who else would you like to
share this moment with?
It's like the Yankees
and the Red Sox.
I know, it's like...
- I have so much love for you!
- My brother ! My brother !
It will be perfect.
It's gonna be perfect.
I'm really excited.
Initially, I thought it would be
Tyler and me against the rest of the world.
But now
Rodney is my right arm.
And Sierra owes me.
She was supposed to be next,
I pulled her out of the shit.
So Joe leaves.
And from there
it will be a walk.
Joe, what's your position?
I'm up for anything.
Whenever I want to speak
with Joaquin, see where he is,
his little puppy is with him.
I think those two
white collars are kidding us.
They hooked Rodney,
and I'm afraid they'll do Sierra
and that we are outvoted.
And to be honest, Rodney
came up to me and said,
"We have to fire Joe first."
I was hoping to approach
Tyler and Joaquin,
but they don't speak to me.
I thought
we could collaborate,
but apparently
they're targeting me, so...
I'm fucked, basically.
When we arrived,
it was Sierra, Sierra, Sierra.
We thought she was on the sidelines.
- She was.
- She's still mad at Dan.
Underlying problem:
she's really not happy.
And I got down on my stomach.
But I think until
his name comes out,
she will accept everything.
At this point,
my options are limited.
You have to make the best
of the worst-case scenario.
Hoping it works.
Sierra would be the key.
Yup.
If we had Sierra,
on virerait Joaquin.
At this point, Joe is with us.
Alas, Sierra and I,
we really clashed.
I screwed up, hands down.
No excuses, no procrastination.
I screwed up. And now
we have to bring her back to us.
Seeing Rodney with Joaquin...
These two need to be separated.
Listen, I screwed up.
I want to regain your trust.
But you worried us.
We eliminated her best friend
because they were too close.
And we have to do the same.
Joaquin leaves first.
OK ?
At this point, I have
two alliances telling me:
"Come with us,
we'll take care of you."
And it's nice,
it's refreshing to be desired.
But my old tribe
made me suffer a lot,
and now they need me?
It makes me want to vomit.
Joe would vote for Joaquin.
As long as it's not him,
he's fine.
Rodney, on the first vote,
with the three of us and Joe,
we remain in the majority.
But as soon as we get Joaquin,
Rodney is going to explode.
Let it explode!
Just... shut your mouth,
open your ears,
and see what happens.
I hate Dan. And at this point,
I'm just very angry.
The Blues don't care about me,
they won't keep me.
They are using me
for this occasion.
- Everyone votes Joe.
- OK.
- Everybody.
- I am with you.
What do you say ?
I'm the type to play
with my heart and my head.
Of course, in this game,
it will get me in trouble.
At this point, yes,
I have it both ways.
I don't know...
not only who to trust,
but also who will be best
in the long run.
I can choose a path
that will perhaps lead me to the final.
We never know.
And at this point, I don't know
yet which path I'm going to follow.
But either way,
it could turn the game upside down.
Good. After mixing,
we end up with
three Overalls,
two White Collars and one Colorless.
Joe, arriving at the camp,
it seemed that the Blues were
very happy to be together
in this random redistribution?
On the surface, it looked like
a happy, united family.
But every family is imperfect.
There are quarrels, breaches,
and Joaquin, Tyler and I
tried to find them
- and exploit them.
- Dan.
Did you feel that these three
were looking for the flaw?
Yes, there may have been
opportunities to exploit.
From there to talk about flaws...
Let's not beat around the bush,
there are malfunctions.
So I'm concerned.
Tyler, what are you looking for?
What are you trying to take into account?
Honestly, Jeff,
I didn't have to do anything.
We found bad vibes
and animosity.
And it seems to
revolve a lot around Sierra.
- Sierra, is it true?
- Absolutely.
After the last advice,
I was mistreated.
I was told that I was
useless in the tests,
that I did nothing on the camp...
Everything that I could be reproached for,
I have been reproached for.
We haven't all
blamed you.
When it happened,
Mike stood up and said:
"guys, that's enough",
I admit.
But I felt more
appreciated in 24 hours
with these people than in 11 days
with these three.
Wow. Mike, this is not good.
You're in a situation where,
if Sierra wants to pass,
the game rocks,
and Dan, Rodney and you,
you are in trouble.
Well, we four,
we have been together
for 16 days now.
But I don't think
we're a foursome
completely impenetrable.
What if these three saw flaws
and attracted one of us...
Yeah, I'm definitely
a little scared tonight, 100%.
But Jeff, that's the beauty
of throwing the bandanas away.
Opportunities arise.
There were clearly
problems between us,
but I have three
new people here,
three others with whom
I have been with for 16 days,
that drive me crazy...
What will be the best
opportunity for me?
Joaquin, would you have imagined
that you would be at the council,
to say to yourself:
"I'm not as concerned
as I would have thought.",
a few days ago ?
I didn't think
it would turn out like this, Jeff.
But when people
come to see you
and explain to you, basically,
why they hate each other,
it couldn't have been
easier for me.
Joe, is a part of you
wondering
what is true in what they say,
and what falls under what they
want you to hear?
Yes, these four can
very well say:
"let's eliminate them one by one".
But on a strategic level,
I am in the worst position.
At least Joaquin has Tyler.
Me, I don't have anyone.
Sierra, one of the trademarks
of the Blues,
it was that you helped each other.
Jeff, it wasn't having
my name written on it.
I was attacked
personally on my return to the camp.
I can't trust
people who do that.
But even if
you don't love someone,
you are four. Why not
stick together for a few more votes?
Yes. I'm not stupid,
I get that.
I made real friendships
with some people.
So absolutely,
I have to consider the whole
and ask me who
I trust at this point.
Mike, it's kind of
like a romantic relationship,
and someone did something
wrong, but you still love each other,
you want it to resume,
but you have to work on it,
because there's this other guy,
and he flirts with her.
In this case, it's Sierra.
Smiles aside, what are you doing?
You can't just say:
"OK, Sierra, if you have to go,
you have to go.".
At the end of the day, we hope
to be able to believe in trust
that we developed earlier,
or in the one created
with new friends,
but you never know
who you can trust
before leaving the board.
And it's a
very, very scary situation, Jeff.
It seems that the decision
of who will leave tonight
could be very important
for this group.
It's time to vote.
Dan, over to you.
Sorry, buddy.
Joaquin, looks
like it's you or me tonight.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Joe.
Joaquin.
Two votes Joe, two votes Joaquin.
Three votes Joe.
Joaquin.
Three votes Joe, three votes Joaquin.
One vote remains.
Sixth person eliminated...
Joaquin.
Bring me your torch.
Joaquin, the tribe to parl.
It's time to go.
Tonight
's discussion revolved around loopholes.
Your success in this game
depends on your ability
to repair or exploit
these cracks, day after day.
Take your things,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor....
Team up behind my back?
Rodney feels betrayed
by his blue family.
Those who wronged me will pay.
But in Survivor...
Where's Jeff?
...we always find
time for revenge.
You merged!
These Blues disrespected me.
So your coming
of age is a joke.
I didn't see it coming.
These four, I don't know
which ones, got me good.
I have my idea.
Mike must have been
obsessed with Sierra,
I was getting too close
to her and Rodney.
They must have thought
that I was taking their tribe from them,
and so, "Let's get it out!".
But it's my destiny
and I accept it with a smile.