>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> WE GOT THE NUMBERS.
>> YEAH.
>> WE MAKE A MOVE.
>> Jeff: RODNEY WAS PUTTING
TOGETHER A STRONG ALLIANCE.
>> I'M ALWAYS RIDING WITH
NUMBERS, BABY.
LOOKING BEAUTIFUL FOR RODNEY,
ISN'T IT.
>> Jeff: BUT BEING IN CHARGE
DOESN'T ALWAYS LEAD THE
HAPPINESS.
>> EVERYBODY'S HAD A BREAK, BUT
I'VE LISTEN LOCKED IN MY CELL
24/7.
I'M PISSED.
>> Jeff: TYLER AND CAROLYN
DISCOVERED THE PARTY OF DAN'S
ADVANTAGE.
>> I GRABBED DAN'S BAG.
HE GETS AN EXTRA VOTE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: AFTER EXPOSING
RODNEY'S SECRET ALLIANCE.
>> IT'S A GREAT JOB YOU ALL
FLIPPED RODNEY...
>> EVERYONE WAS TARGETING MIKE.
>> WE GET HIM OUT RIGHT NOW,
HE'LL NEVER KNOW.
>> I KNOW THEY ARE COMING FOR MY
HEAD.
>> Jeff: BUT HE WAS
UNSTOPPABLE AT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
RODNEY IS OUT.
MIKE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
FOR THE SECOND TIME IN A ROW.
AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL...
>> I'M PULLING OUT A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, JEFF.
>> Jeff: HE REVEALED HIS IDOL
TO SHAKE UP THE SIX.
>> SHIRIN'S VOTING FOR TYLER.
I'M VOTING FOR ONE OF THE OTHER
FOUR, AND YOU TAKE YOUR CHANCES.
>> Jeff: AND ALTHOUGH TYLER
AND WILL CHANGED THEIR VOTE.
>> 11th PERSON VOTED OUT,
THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
SHIRIN.
SHIRIN WAS SENT HOME.
SHIRIN, THE TRIBE HAD SPOKEN.
SEVEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> I THINK DAN VOTED FOR TYLER
AND TYLER VOTED FOR DAN.
>> I BET YOU ARE WRONG.
I PUT A STAR ON MINE.
I VOTED FOR SHIRIN.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I VOTED FOR SHIRIN, TOO.
>> LET'S NOT DO THIS.
LET'S NO DO THIS.
STAY FOCUSED.
>> I'M JUST LETTING...
>> YOU AIN'T GOT TO.
YOU HEAR ME?
>> ONE OF YOU IS GOING HOME NEXT
TIME, SO BETTER START
SCRAMBLING.
>> WHEN WE GOT BACK TO CAMP
AFTER TRIBAL, THEY CALLED A
LITTLE TEAM MEETING OF THE SIX.
AND IT WAS KIND OF FUN.
IT WAS KIND OF FUN TO START
WATCHING PEOPLE SCRAMBLE BECAUSE
FOR THE PAST THREE VOTES, I'VE
BEEN SCRAMBLING.
RIGHT NOW I'M SAFE WITH MY
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO THAT TARGET IS TAKEN OFF OF
ME AND THEY'LL START TURNING ON
EACH OTHER.
THE FALL OUT OF ALL THIS WILL BE
INTERESTING TO WATCH, AND THAT'S
FOR SURE.
>> I HAVE TO WRITE SOMEBODY'S
NAME DOWN OTHER THAN MINE.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
>> I CAN'T WRITE SHIRIN.
>> YES, YOU COULD HAVE.
I KNEW IT WAS A BLUFF.
>> BUT WHEN YOUR NAME IS THE
OTHER ONE THAT'S ALREADY BEEN
OUT THERE, I HAVE TO WRITE
SOMEBODY ELSE'S OUT THERE.
IF I DON'T, I'M DONE.
I PUT DOWN DAN'S NAME THINKING,
LOOK, MAN, I HAVE TO DO WHATEVER
I CAN TO STAY ALIVE.
>> WHO IS THE ONLY OTHER NAME I
CAN THINK OF THAT'S GOING TO BE
ON THE BLOCK?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> NOTHING HAPPENED.
IT'S FINE.
>> I DIDN'T WRITE YOUR -- I
WROTE YOUR NAME DOWN.
>> OKAY.
I'M JUST COMING TO YOU AND
TELLING YOU THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE FACT THAT I GOT TWO VOTES
GIVES ME REASON FOR PAUSE.
SO THAT'S BAD ON WILL AND TYLER,
BECAUSE THEY DID FLINCH.
MIKE IS STILL PUBLIC ENEMY
NUMBER ONE RIGHT NOW.
BUT HERE'S THE PROBLEM: MIKE HAS
AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
HE'S GUARANTEED ONE MORE TRIP.
>> LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TOLD
ME WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
THIS IS A GAME.
RIGHT?
YOU AND I ARE GOING FAR.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
WE ARE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
ALL RIGHT?
LAST NIGHT'S VOTE SO THE SIX ARE
MORE THAN WILLING TO VOTE FOR
EACH OTHER AND THAT DAN IS MOST
LIKELY AT THE BOTTOM, WHICH IS
WHY HE GOT VOTES, BUT I WAS ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK, AS WELL, SO
I DON'T HAVE TOO MANY LIFELINES
REMAINING.
I VOTED FOR DAN, AND I PLAN ON
DOING IT AGAIN.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CALL DAN
EXTREMELY GULLIBLE.
I JUST CALL HIM EXTREMELY LOYAL,
BUT IN THIS GAME, THEY'RE KIND
OF ONE IN THE SAME.
>> TODAY IS DAY 30.
>> RODNEY'S BIRTHDAY!
>> THANKS, GUYS.
APPRECIATE THAT.
>> TODAY'S MY BIRTHDAY.
HOPEFULLY WE GOT A REWARD.
HOPEFULLY I GET OUT OF HERE.
I'VE BEEN STUCK ON THIS BEACH
FOR 30 DAYS DOING THE SAME DAMN
THING OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
WE GOT TREE MAIL.
>> READ IT, GIRL.
>> FOR AN OPPORTUNITY TO NOURISH
YOUR SOUL, JUST RACE THROUGH.
YOU ALSO MAY BE FEEDING YOUR
BELLY IF IT'S YOU WHO CAN
DOMINATE THE STUMPS.
>> I NEED THIS PICK-ME-UPPER,
MAN.
>> FEEDING YOUR SOUL?
>> FOR AN OPPORTUNITY TO NOURISH
YOUR SOUL, RACE THROUGH A FEW
LITTLE LUMPS.
YOU ALSO MAY BE FEEDING YOUR
BELLY, IF IT'S YOU WHO CAN
DOMINATE...
>> PEOPLE DON'T KNOW HOW TIGHT
ME AND WILL ARE.
MAMA C, SHE HAS A LOT OF LOVE,
TOO, AND THEY'RE GOING THE TAKE
ME ON THIS REWARD.
>> I HAVE FAITH IN MY REWARD
TODAY.
IF I DON'T GO ON THE REWARD, IT
WILL BE A SAD, SAD DAY.
MY WHOLE GAME WILL CHANGE, BUT
GUESS WHAT, THE CHANCES OF THAT
HAPPENING ARE 0.000% CHANCE
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW MUCH FAITH I
HAVE IN THESE PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU WILL BE DIVIDED
TWO INTO TEAMS OF THREE.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL WORK TOGETHER
TO UNSPOOL RIBBONS TO RELEASE A
KEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE KEY, BUILD A
LADDER, CLIMB TO THE TOP AND USE
THAT KEY TO RELOWS A BAG OF
BALLS.
YOU THEN MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH A
NET SWING TO THE FINISH WHERE
YOU WILL ATTEMPT TO LAND THOSE
BALLS IN A SERIES OF TARGETS.
FIRST TEAM TO GET ONE BALL IN
EACH OF THE FIVE TARGETS WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WRING -- BRING IT IN.
>> ISN'T THAT GREAT?
>> WONDERFUL.
>> Jeff: TODAY YOU WILL BE
AMBASSADORS OF GOODWILL FOR
"SURVIVOR" AND DELIVER SOME
MUCH-NEEDED SUPPLIES TO SOME
VERY WORTHY CHILDREN FROM A
LOCAL ORPHANAGE.
THIS TRUCK IS FILLED WITH THE
KIND OF THINGS THAT BACK HOME WE
JUST TAKE FOR GRANTED, SCHOOL
SUPPLIES, CLOTHING, BEDDING,
SPORTS EQUIPMENT.
YOU WILL ALSO TREAT THESE KIDS
TO AN AFTERNOON OF BARBECUE --
CHICKEN, STEAK.
>> RIBS?
>> Jeff: PORK.
FEED YOUR SOUL, FEED YOUR BELLY
AND CHANGE SOME LIVES IN THE
PROCESS.
>> HELL, YEAH.
>> Jeff: ONLY SIX PEOPLE ARE
PARTICIPATING IN THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU HAVE SEVEN.
THAT MEANS SOMEBODY IS GOING TO
SIT OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO DO A SCHOOLYARD
PICK TO SEE WHO WILL NOT BE
CHOSEN.
THEN WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
DAN WAS A CAPTAIN.
HE CHOSE TYLER AND RODNEY.
CAROLYN WAS A CAPTAIN.
SHE CHOSE MIKE AND SIERRA.
WILL WAS NOT PICKED.
WILL HAS NO SHOT AT THIS REWARD.
HERE WE GO, FOR REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> HOP OVER.
BOTH OF US.
>> Jeff: TEAMWORK IS CRITICAL
IN THIS FIRST STEP.
YOU'RE UNSPOOLING THESE RIBBONS
TO RELEASE THE KEY FROM THE VERY
TOP.
IF YOU GET TIED UP, LIKE TYLER
JUST DID, IT'S GOING TO SLOW YOU
DOWN.
>> GO.
>> Jeff: MIKE IS THROUGH.
HERE GOES SIERRA.
>> STOP, STOP.
>> Jeff: TYLER IS THROUGH.
HERE GOES DAN.
>> GO, DAN.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, MAMA C.
GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: MIKE, SIERRA AND
CAROLYN IN THE LEAD OVER TYLER,
DAN AND RODNEY.
THERE COMES THE KEY FOR RED.
ONCE YOU HAVE IT, UNBUCKLE AND
HEAD OUT.
MIKE, SIERRA, CAROLYN WORKING
TOGETHER.
>> WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD.
NOW YOU GOT BUILD THE LADDER
FROM BOTTOM TO TOP.
FIVE LADDER RUNGS.
GOT TO FIGURE OUT THE ORDER.
AND BUILD IT FROM THE BOTTOM TO
THE TOP.
AND ONE PERSON GOES UP TO GET
THE BAG.
RED WITH THEIR FOURTH PLANK.
RED WITH THEIR FIFTH PLAFNLG
THEY HAVE THEIR LADDER BUILT.
MIKE HEADING TO THE TOP.
BLUE HAS THEIR THIRD.
THEIR FOURTH.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT!
THERE YOU GO.
RODNEY HAS THE FIFTH PLANK.
MIKE HAS THE BAG.
HE'S THROUGH.
RODNEY HAS THE BAG.
HE'S DOWN.
HERE GOES DAN AND TYLER.
EVERYBODY GOT TO GO UP AND OVER.
NOW YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH THE
NET SWING WORKING TOGETHER
AGAIN.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: MIKE HELPING BOTH
WOMEN UP.
SIERRA'S IN.
CAROLYN'S IN.
READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE.
NIGHT.
IT'S TYLER AND RODNEY TRYING TO
GET DAN THROUGH THIS VERY NARROW
SWING.
RED STILL IN THE LEAD.
SIERRA IS OUT.
CAROLYN IS OUT.
IT IS A RACE TO THIS FINISH.
MIKE IS THROUGH WITH THE BAG OF
BALLS FOR RED.
>> GO, MIKE.
ONE PERSON STARTS LAUNCHING THE
BALLS.
BOTH TEAMS ARE THROUGH.
>> WHERE THE BALLS?
>> GRAB THEM.
>> Jeff: RODNEY LEFT THE BALLS
BEHIND.
YOU GOT TO GO BACK THROUGH.
GOT TO GET THROUGH WITH THE
BALLS.
RODNEY LEFT THE BALLS BEHIND.
HUGE TIME LOSS.
THAT GIVES MIKE A BIG HEAD START
ON LAUNCHING THE BALLS.
RODNEY'S NOW GO TO GOT ALL THE
WAY BACK THROUGH THAT NET SWING
AND THE PANIC IS SENDING --
SETTING IN.
MIKE IS NOW LAUNCHING BALLS FOR
RED.
BIG ADVANTAGE FOR RED.
RODNEY'S THROUGH.
NOW BLUE CAN GO.
RED WITH A BIG TIME LEAD TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT HOW THIS CATAPULT
WORKS.
MIKE'S HAD A FEW SHOTS NOW TO
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> YES, YES.
>> Jeff: MIKE SCORES FOR RED.
>> THAT'S IN.
>> Jeff: DAN LAUNCHES AND
SCORES FOR BLUE.
DAN LAUNCHES AND SCORES AGAIN
FOR BLUE.
BLUE WITH TWO NOW.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: MIKE LAUNCHES AND
SCORES AGAIN.
WE'RE TIED 2-2.
>> NOPE.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
BLUE WITH A THIRD.
BLUE NOW LEADS 3-2.
>> THANKS.
>> Jeff: THAT'S NOT GOING TO
HELP.
IT DROPS IN THE SAME SPOT.
>> LET US TRY, MIKE.
>> DAN WITH A FOURTH.
THAT'S FOUR FOR BLUE.
IT WOULD BE A BIG COMEBACK.
>> MIKE, THEY'RE FOUR.
THEY GOT FOUR.
>> Jeff: MIKE TRYING TO CATCH
UP.
THERE'S A THIRD FOR RED.
IT IS 4-3.
>> MIKE, CAN I GO OR NO?
>> NEW YORK I GOT IT.
>> MIKE!
>> Jeff: MIKE NOT GIVING IT
UP.
SIERRA WANTS IN.
MIKE WON'T GIVE HER A SHOT.
DAN THE WIN RIGHT HERE.
>> THAT'S IT.
THAT'S GAME!
>> Jeff: OH, IN AND OUT, OVER
THE TOP.
>> JUST KEEP SHOOTING, BRO.
>> Jeff: MIKE SCORES AGAIN.
WE ARE TIED NOW.
IT IS 4-4.
MIKE VERSUS DAN FOR THE WIN.
>> COME ON, MIKE!
>> Jeff: MIKE CAN GET IT RIGHT
HERE.
WILL IT DROP?
AND IT DOES!
MIKE, SIERRA, CAROLYN WIN
REWARD!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU, JESUS.
THANK YOU, JESUS.
GOOD GAME, GUYS.
>> SORRY.
SORRY.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN, SIERRA,
MIKE, NICE REWARD.
YOU GET TO GIVE BACK AND ALSO
REWARD YOURSELF WITH SOME
MUCH-NEEDED NUTRITION.
TYLER, RODNEY, DAN, NOTHING FOR
YOU.
RODNEY, YOU CONTINUE TO BE SHUT
OUT OF THESE REWARDS.
>> MY BIRTHDAY TOO TODAY, JEFF.
I MEAN, IT WENT FROM POSSIBLY
THE BEST BIRTHDAY EVER TO THE
WORST.
THIS IS THE WORST FEELING EVER.
I'M 30 DAYS IN AND I HAVEN'T
LEFT THE BEACH.
>> ARE YOU HOPING THAT ONE OF
THESE THREE WILL FEEL FOR YOU ON
YOUR SPECIAL DAY AND GIVE UP
THEIR REWARD FOR YOU?
>> IT'S UP TO THEM.
I'M NOT GOING TO PRESSURE THEM
AND PLEAD THE CASE.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
TODAY, JEFF, IT IS RODNEY'S
BIRTHDAY, AND MY HEART GOES OUT
TO HIM THAT HE HASN'T BEEN ON
REWARD.
I LOVE YOU, HOT ROD, BUT I GOT
TO GET SOME FOOD IN ME, TOO,
BROTHER.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN, YOU OR
SIERRA ANY INTEREST IN GIVING UP
THIS REWARD TO RODNEY.
>> THIS IS ALSO A
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME OPPORTUNITY
THAT I DON'T KNOW I CAN PASSES
UP AT THIS POINT.
>> PRETTY SAD.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S SAD, RODNEY?
>> I THINK MAYBE WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT IS IF IT WAS AN
INDIVIDUAL, WE WERE GOING TO
PICK RODNEY, RODNEY WAS GOING TO
BE THE FIRST PICK, BUT SINCE IT
BECAME A TEAM, I PERSONALLY DID
NOT SAY I WOULD SEPARATE FROM MY
TEAM.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE MADE COMMENTS
AND SAID SOME THINGS, BUT WHEN
YOU GO BACK FROM YOUR WORD, IT
KIND OF... IT'S MY BIRTHDAY, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S MY DAMN BIRTHDAY, BUT IT IS
WHAT IT IS?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
CAROLYN, SIERRA, MIKE, FUN
AFTERNOON IN STORE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, ENJOY
IT.
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
WILL, TYLER, RODNEY, DAN, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
>> PEOPLE AREN'T YOUR FRIENDS.
THEY SHOW YOU HOW CUTTHROAT THEY
CAN BE.
YOUR OWN DAMN BIRTHDAY AND THEY
DON'T TAKE YOU ON REWARD.
THEY JUST TURNED ME INTO THE
PSYCHOTIC PERSON I AM.
>> CAROLYN, SIERRA, MYSELF GET
TO JUMP IN THE BACK OF THIS
TRUCK LOADED DOWN WITH TOY,
BAGS, BALLS, SCHOOL SUPPLIES AND
WE GET TO GO TO THIS ORPHANAGE
WHERE IN THIS TRUCK WE GET TO BE
AMBASSADORS OF GOODWILL FOR
SURVIVOR.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> COMING TO YOU.
TO SEE THE FACES OF ALL THESE
LITTLE BOYS AND GIRLS WHEN WE
PULLED UP.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> IT BUILT ME UP INSIDE BECAUSE
I JUST ENJOY BEING AROUND KIDS.
AND BEING A KID BECAUSE I'M A
BIG KID.
>> WHO'S PLAYING?
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
LET'S DO IT.
>> GOOD SAVE.
THE ONLY THING I CAN THINK IN MY
HEAD ARE THESE BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL LITTLE CHILDREN.
DON'T HAVE A MOM.
THEY DON'T HAVE A DAD.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> I RIDE HORSES.
I'M A COWGIRL.
THAT'S MY JOB.
I HAVE A BABY HORSE AT HOME THAT
LOOKS THE SAME.
I LOVE HORSES.
THIS IS ONE OF THE COOLEST
EXPERIENCES I'VE EVER HAD, TO
COME HERE AND MEET THESE AMAZING
CHILDREN WHO ARE SO GRATEFUL AND
SPEND TIME WITH THEM.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> ANNA.
>> ANNA?
I COULDN'T ASK FOR A BETTER
REWARD TODAY.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU.
>> ENCHILADAS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WE'RE SO EATING.
>> LOOK AT THAT PLATE.
>> THIS IS INSANITY.
>> AMAZING.
>>
>> TODAY MIGHT BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE OF A SPECIAL DAY FOR
RODNEY, BUT THIS WAS A REALLY
SPECIAL DAY FOR US, AS WELL.
THIS IS YOUR EXPERIENCE.
>> RODNEY IS GOING TO BE PISSED
OFF AT ME BECAUSE I DIDN'T GIVE
UP THIS REWARD, BUT WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT IT, THIS IS NOT A
HORRIBLE BIRTHDAY.
YOU'RE ON "SURVIVOR," FOR GOD'S
SAKE.
>> YOU'LL, HONESTLY, THERE'S
NOBODY ELSE AT OUR CAMP THAT I
WOULD WANT THE SHARE THIS WITH
THAN YOU TWO.
SERIOUSLY.
>> I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN ON A REWARD
WITH MIKE BEFORE, SO I GOT A
CHANCE TO SEE HIM IN A DIFFERENT
LIGHT.
>> I LITERALLY FEEL LIKE A KING
RIGHT NOW.
>> MIKE HAS A LOT OF POWER IN
THIS GAME RIGHT NOW.
HE DOES WIN CHALLENGES AND HE
DOES HAVE AN IDOL.
SO HE'S NOT GOING HOME AND WE
HAVE TO VOTE ONE OF THE SIX OUT.
THAT'S WHY I'M WORRIED ABOUT
MYSELF, AND, YEAH, I'M THINKING
ABOUT ALIGNING MYSELF WITH THE
PEOPLE THAT I THINK ARE GOING TO
TAKE ME FURTHER IN THIS GAME.
SO MAYBE IT'S TIME TO JOIN
FORCES.
WHO KNOWS?
COULD HAPPEN.
>> WASHING DISHES ON MY
BIRTHDAY.
NO COCONUTS OR ANY FRUIT,
NOTHING, THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
0 FOR 5 ON REWARD CHALLENGES AND
A BUNCH OF SCUMBAGS WHO
NEGLECTED ME ON MY BIRTHDAY WHO
CLAIM TO BE "SURVIVOR" FAMILY.
ALL BETS ARE OFF NOW.
BUNCH OF SCUMBAGS.
UNREAL.
CAROLINE AND SIERRA, THEY ABOUT
IT GOING TO THE END.
THE ONLY PEOPLE GOING TO THE END
UNDER MY WATCH IS ME.
THAT'S IT.
>> JUST LET HIM COOL OFF.
THAT'S RODNEY.
HE'LL COOL OFF.
>> WELL, WE'LL SEE HOW A LOSS
COMPLICATES THINGS AROUND HERE
FOR THE NEXT 24 HOURS FOR
RODNEY.
>> HERE HE COMES.
>> I'M SORRY, MAN.
>> YOU REALLY BELIEVE MAMA C,
THOUGH.
I KNOW FAR FACT YOU WOULDN'T DO
THAT TO ME.
YOU COULD HAVE INDIVIDUALLY TOOK
YOURSELF OUT, LIKE I KNOW YOU
GUYS WOULD HAVE.
I'M REALLY PISSED AT MAMA C,
THOUGH.
ON MY BIRTHDAY.
[BLEEPED] ME OVER LIKE THAT.
SEE SIGH I KNOW SHE WOULD, BUT
MAMA C, HER FOURTH REWARD.
THIS IS WHAT IS "SURVIVOR'S"
ABOUT, BABY.
I WENT ON EVERY SINGLE REWARD.
>> I UNDERSTAND HIM BEING HURT.
I UNDERSTAND HIM BEING UPSET.
BUT EVEN IN MY OPINION, THAT WAS
A BIT MUCH.
>> HEY, LISTEN, THIS IS GOING TO
SET UP REALLY NICE.
ONE THING I LEARN IS MY TEMP
KERR GET ME IN TROUBLE OR SET ME
FORWARD.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THE ULTIMATE
BLIND SIDE EVER.
I'M GOING TO TELL THAT I'M
CHECKED OUT.
I WANT TO BE VOTED OUT I WANT TO
BE ON THE JURY NEXT.
MIKE'S NOT GOING TO PLAY HIS
IDOL AND WE GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
PRETTY DAMN SMART.
>> I DO NOT THINK FOR A SECOND
THAT IT'S GOING TO WORK.
>> I REALLY THINK RODNEY IS
SLIPPING OFF INTO THE ABYSS.
AND THAT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME,
YOU KNOW, LET HIM HAVE HIS
MOMENT OF EXPLOSION.
HOPEFULLY HE'S ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK, AND THEY WON'T SEE ME AS
A TARGET.
WE'LL SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT.
>> THIS WHOLE SHOW ABOUT RODNEY
WANTING TO QUIT AND THIS AND
THAT COULD BE A LITTLE IFFY.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, MIKE'S GOING
HOME.
MIKE IS GOING HOME.
>> WE SAT AROUND AND ESSENTIALLY
WATCHED RODNEY STORM AROUND,
KICK THE DIRT, CURSE, SPIT,
FIGHT.
HE'S LOST IT.
HE'S GOING CRAZY.
WHICH IS SCARY.
BECAUSE RODNEY IS IN MY
ALLIANCE, AND I CERTAINLY CAN'T
RELY ON HIM, AND MIKE MOST
LIKELY WILL PLAY HIS IDOL.
>> WHAT IF MIKE PLAYS THE IDOL
AND VOTES ME AND I'M GONE.
>> I DON'T THINK HE'S GOING TO
PLAY THE IDOL.
WHY WOULD HE PLAY IT IF I'M
ACTING SO GOOD?
>> BECAUSE IT'S "SURVIVOR."
PEOPLE HAVE TO ANTICIPATE CRAZY.
>> BUT HOW CRAZY IS THAT,
THOUGH?
>> IT IS CRAZY.
>> IT WOULD BE STUPID FOR MIKE
TO BUY THE STORY, AND I'M THE
FIRST ONE THAT MIKE WANTS GONE.
I'M GOING TO BE THE ONE HE VOTES
FOR.
IF WE JUST LEAVE IT INTO MIKE'S
HANDS.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
>> THE BEST TIME OF YOUR LIFE ON
MY BIRTHDAY WHEN SOMEBODY COULD
HAVE STEPPED UP AND LET ME GO.
I'M SAYING I WANT THEM TO VOTE
ME OUT AT TRIBAL AND I'VE HAD
ENOUGH.
HOPEFULLY MIKE DOESN'T PLAY HIS
IDOL.
>> I WISH TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
TODAY SO YOU COULD PUT MY NAME
DOWN.
OKAY.
HAVE FUN.
HAVE FUN WITH YOUR LITTLE GAME.
A BUNCH OF FAKE-ASS PEOPLE AND
I'M DONE.
I NEED TO GET HOME TO MY FAMILY.
MAMA C, SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
LIKE A MOTHER.
YOU'RE LIKE A SON TO ME?
THAT'S LIKE YOU LEAVE YOUR SON
HOME AND GO OUT PARTYING AND
LEAVE YOUR SON AT HOME DOING
CHORES WHEN YOU WERE OUT ON MY
BIRTHDAY.
IT'S ALL FAKE.
>> WHY SHOULD THEY GIVE UP THEIR
REWARD WHEN YOU LOST THE
CHALLENGE?
>> IF IT WAS ANY OTHER DAY.
>> IT'S ANOTHER DAY.
IF I HAVE TO HEAR THAT...
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU ARE GOING TO HEAR IT.
YOU WRITE MY DAMN NAME DOWN.
>> WHY QUIT NOW?
>> I'M NOT WRITING YOUR NAME.
IT TOTALLY MAKES MORE SENSE.
>> I SEE RIGHT THROUGH THE
PLANE.
FEEL LIKE I'M SAFE SO I DON'T
PLAY MY IDOL.
THAT AIN'T HAPPENING, BROTHER.
I'M IN THE AN IDIOT, JUST
BECAUSE I TALK SLOW DON'T MEAN I
THINK SLOW.
>> WRITE MY DAMN NAME DOWN.
>> GO HOME.
>> MIKE DIDN'T BY THE ACT FOR A
SECOND.
HE JUST STOPPED THAT
CONVERSATION.
MIKE HAS HIS IMMUNITY IDOL AND
WE'RE BACK TO SQUARE ONE.
>> LAY IT ON ME.
YOU THINK MIKE'S GOING TO VOTE
FOR ME NEXT TIME.
>> HE'S EITHER GOING TO VOTE FOR
YOU OR DAN.
>> IF I DON'T WIN IMMUNITY.
>> YOU GOT TO WIN IMMUNITY.
>> RIGHT.
>> I NEED THE START THINKING
ABOUT DIFFERENT OPTIONS, AS
WELL.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR...
>> WE WOULD USE IT WHEN WE NEED
IT.
>> OKAY.
>> WOULD CAROLYN BE WILLING TO
PUT DOWN THE WHITE COLLAR IDOL
TO SAVE ME?
I HOPE SO.
MY TRUST IS IN MAMA C.
I'M ALSO HER CLOSEST ALLIANCE
MEMBER.
AND IF THINGS GET DOWN TO THE
WIRE, YOU HAVE TO TRUST PEOPLE
IN ORDER TO GET FURTHER.
THE POINT IS, YOU NEED TO START
BRINGING YOUR IDOL THE WAY
STUFF'S GOING DOWN.
>> WELL YEAH,.
>> FROM A STRATEGIC GAME
PERSPECTIVE, I'M PLAYING THE
GAME HARD.
I KNOW THAT TYLER TRUSTS ME.
SO I THINK MIKE DOESN'T REALLY
HAVE ANYBODY ELSE TO WORK WITH.
SO I ACTUALLY DO FEEL LIKE I'M
THE ONE IN CHARGE RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I'LL TAKE BACK BOTH NECKLACES.
SORRY, CAROLYN.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE IT
UP, BUT YOU MUST.
TODAY WE ONLY NEED ONE NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE ON A VERY SMALL
PERCH WHILE LEANING BACK HOLDING
ON TO A ROPE.
EVERY FIVE MINUTES YOU'LL MOVE
FURTHER DOWN THE ROPE, MAKING IT
MORE DIFFICULT, WHEN YOU CAN'T
HOLD ON ANY LONGER, YOU'LL DROP
IN THE WATER AND YOU'RE OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
SIX SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY IN POSITION.
PUT YOUR HANDS DOWN TO THE THIRD
KNOT AND LEAN BACK, AND HERE WE
GO.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE IN THIS
CHALLENGE, SO AS IT GETS TOUGH
AND YOU WANT TO PULL IT CLOSER,
LIKE TYLER'S ALREADY WANTING TO
DO, CAN'T DO THAT.
THIS IS JUST LEANING BACK AND
HOLDING ON FOR DEAR LIFE.
RODNEY, YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
STRUGGLING.
>> I AM, BROTHER.
32 DAYS OF THIS [BLEEPED], IT
HURTS, BROTHER.
I'M JUST...
>> Jeff: EMOTIONALLY OR
JUST...
>> EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: AND IS THIS RELATED
TO YOUR BIRTHDAY?
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT WAS A BIG
DEAL.
WORST BIRTHDAY OF MY LIFE.
I DID DISHES ON AN ISLAND THAT I
HAVEN'T LEFT IN 32 DAYS.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
IT'S THE WORST.
>> Jeff: THIS WOULD BE TOUGH
TO DO ON DAY ONE.
YOU'RE ON DAY 32.
WHERE ARE YOU FEELING IT, DAN?
>> ALL IN MY HANDS.
>> Jeff: IS IT BECAUSE OF ALL
THE WORK YOU'VE DONE WITH YOUR
HANDS.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF THE CUTS.
A LOT OF THE BUG BITES.
JUST MY OWN FAT ASS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO START
THE FEEL THAT PULL, AND JUST AS
I SAID IT, WILL FELT THE PULL.
WILL IS THE FIRST PERSON OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
>> NOPE.
DAN IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE NOW,
JOINING WILL.
AND WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE.
RODNEY STRUGGLING A LITTLE BIT.
HOW YOU DOING, CAROLYN.
>> GOOD.
LOVING LIFE, JEFF.
BEST ADVENTURE EVER.
>> Jeff: THE TEMPTATION IS TO
TRY TO INCH YOUR WAY BACK UP
THAT ROPE.
MAKES IT VERY FRUSTRATING.
THIS CHALLENGE CAN CATCH UP TO
YOU WITHOUT MUCH WARNING.
JUST LIKE THAT SIERRA DROPS.
RODNEY DROPS.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE, IT IS
CAROLYN, TYLER AND MIKE.
TYLER STRUGGLING.
BUT STILL IN IT.
30 SECONDS LEFT AND WE WILL MOVE
DOWN TO THE NEXT KNOT.
CAROLYN TRYING TO GET A GRIP.
MIKE LOOKING VERY STRONG.
WHAT YOU'RE DRAWING ON RIGHT NOW
ARE THOSE RESERVES, THE BOTTOM
OF THE TANK.
EVERYBODY JUST DIGGING IN,
FINDING THAT PLACE INSIDE.
ALL RIGHT.
I WANT YOU TO START THINKING
MOVING FURTHER DOWN ON THE ROPE
NOW.
IT WILL REALLY GET TOUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY MAKE YOUR MOVE.
WE'RE LIVE WHILE YOU'RE DOING
IT, WHICH MEANS THIS CHALLENGE
IS STILL GOING AS YOU MANEUVER
YOUR WAY DOWN.
CAROLYN DROPS DOWN.
EVERYBODY'S DOWN NOW TO THE NEXT
NOTCH.
MIKE CAN'T HANG ON.
CAN'T MAKE THE TRANSITION.
MIKE IS OUT.
TYLER DROPS OUT.
CAROLYN WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
FOR THE SECOND TIME IN A ROW.
>> I AM SO EXCITED.
>> GOOD JOB, MAMA.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN, COME ON OVER
HERE.
>> WAY TO GO, MAMA C.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN YOU DIDN'T
WANT TO GIVE UP THIS NECKLACE,
AND ONCE AGAIN IT IS YOURS.
CAROLYN SAFE AGAIN TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GUARANTEED A 1-6 SHOT AT WINNING
SURVIVOR.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME TONIGHT, SOMEBODY
WILL JOIN THE JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> THE GOOD NEWS IS MIKE HAS TO
PLAY THAT IDOL.
2 BAD NEWS, I GOT TWO VOTES LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND RIGHT NOW
THERE'S A LOT OF TALK ABOUT MY
ADVANTAGE, WHICH MAKES ME AN
EASY TARGET.
I WON MY SECOND IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
WOO WOO.
SO EXCITED.
BUT IT'S NOT CUT AND DRY HOW TO
PLAY THIS GAME NOW BECAUSE
THERE'S SO MANY OPTIONS.
SO YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE YOU
FIGURE OUT THE RIGHT MOVE.
>> GUYS, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> DOES IT PUT FEAR INTO ME THAT
MY NAME COULD GET WRITTEN DOWN?
OF COURSE IT DOES.
I FEEL LIKE ONE OF THREE PEOPLE
ARE GOING HOME TONIGHT, ME, MIKE
OR TYLER.
BUT MIKE'S PROBABLY GOING THE
PLAY HIS IDOL TONIGHT, SO THE
ODDS ARE ON EITHER TYLER OR
MYSELF BECAUSE THEY SEE TYLER AS
A THREAT, AND MY NAME KEEPS
GETTING WRITTEN DOWN.
>> GUYS VOTE MIKE, GIRLS VOTE
TYLER.
MIKE VOTES GETS THREE VOTES.
MIKE IS GOING TO VOTE FOR TYLER.
AS FAR AS DAN'S CONCERNED, WE'RE
GUNNING FOR TYLER, BUT VOTING
FOR DAN IS NOT REALLY A BAD IDEA
BECAUSE WE GET RID OF THE
ADVANTAGE.
>> WILL ALSO VOTED FOR ME.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> JUST SAYING.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT WITH
WILL.
>> YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING,
THOUGH?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, MAN?
>> MIKE'S STILL GOING TO BE
HERE.
YOU'LL BE HERE.
>> I WAS THINKING DAN.
DAN'S GOT THIS ADVANTAGE.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE ARE THREE PEOPLE IN
THIS GAME WHO HAVE ADVANTAGES
GOING INTO TONIGHT'S TRIBAL,
MIKE HAS AN IDOL, CAROLYN HAS AN
IDOL AND DAN HAS AN ADVANTAGE IN
VOTING.
I WAS CON DURING IF MAYBE WE...
DAN'S ADVANTAGE MAKES HIM A HUGE
THREAT IN THIS GAME.
>> OH, HELL YEAH.
>> DOWN THE ROAD.
>> THE LAST TRIBAL I WAS THE ONE
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
I COULD BE EASILY GOING HOME
TONIGHT, SO MY PLAN TONIGHT
WOULD BE TO THROW FOUR VOTES AT
MIKE, ANOTHER TWO VOTES GO AFTER
DAN AND WE KNOCK OUT BOTH AN
IDOL AND THE ADVANTAGE.
DAN GOES HOME.
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE A
4-3 VOTE, FOUR FOR ME, AND I'M
VOTING TYLER.
>> MIKE IS GUNNING FOR TYLER.
AND THIS COULD BE THE ONLY
OPPORTUNITY FOR ME TO SIDE WITH
HIM.
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S THE
RIGHT MOVE TO MAKE RIGHT NOW.
>> I REALLY, REALLY, HOPE MAMA C
IS 100% ON BOARD WITH ME RIGHT
NOW BECAUSE MY OPTIONS OF WHO TO
WORK WITH AT THIS POINT ARE A
LITTLE BIT LIMITED.
>> I TALKED TO WILL.
HE AND I ARE ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> DAN.
>> SO YOU GUYS WILL VOTE MIKE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES MIKE.
HE HAS TO PLAY HIS IDOL.
HE'LL PLAY IT FOR SURE.
AND THEN YOU, ME AND WILL VOTE
DAN.
>> THAT ADVANTAGE IS GOING TO
COME BACK THE HAUNT US IF WE
DON'T GET RID OF IT NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S A TOSS-UP BETWEEN DAN
AND TYLER AS TO WHO NEEDS TO GO
FIRST.
TYLER AND I HAVE A BOND.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SINCE
LITERALLY DAY THREE, BUT HE'S
THE ONLY ONE WHO KNOWS I HAVE AN
IDOL, SO HE CAN BLOW UP MY GAME.
BUT DAN'S ADVANTAGE GIVES HIM AN
EXTRA VOTE, SO THAT'S A BIG
THREAT.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A GAME FOR $1
MILLION, AND I'M HERE TO PLAY
THE PLAY THE GAME, SO GAME ON,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
>> Jeff: WE NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
HALI, JOE, JENN AND SHIRIN VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, MIKE, LAST FEW TRIBALS IT'S
BEEN A TIGHT PICK.
I'M GUESSING TONIGHT THEY WOULD
LOVE TO TAKE OUT YOU, BUT BASED
ON THE LAST TRIBAL, YOU HAVE
YOUR HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I BELIEVE I HAVE IT WITH ME
TONIGHT, THAT'S FOR SURE.
SO ONE OF THE SIX WILL BE GOING
HOME TONIGHT, THAT'S GUARANTEED.
>> Jeff: SO WHO SHOULD BE
WORRIED TONIGHT?
>> I BELIEVE THAT TYLER SHOULD
BE WORRIED.
I BELIEVE THAT DAN SHOULD BE
WORRIED.
I MEAN, JEFF, I'M ENJOYING THIS
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST.
I'VE BEEN ROOTING FOR PEOPLE TO
CHANGE SOME THINKING FOR THREE
TRIBAL COUNCILS NOW.
I MEAN, I GOT THE FIREWORKS OUT,
THE POPCORN, SOME PEPSI.
>> IF YOU HAVE PEPSI AND
POPCORN, PLEASE GIVE ME SOME
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT 150 POUNDS AND
I'M STARVING.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: DAN, ALSO AT THE LAST
TRIBAL, YOU GOT TWO VOTES.
AND I HAVE TO GUESS THAT IT WAS
A SURPRISE.
>> YEAH.
AND I DID FIND OUT RIGHT AWAY
WHO BOTH OF THEM WERE.
IT'S TOUGH WHEN YOU SEE YOUR
NAME WRITTEN DOWN.
NOBODY WANTS TO SEE THAT.
AS MUCH AS NOBODY WANTED TO SAY
WHO WAS ON THE BOTTOM OF THE
SIX, THAT PAINTED A PRETTY
CAREER PICTURE TO ME.
>> Jeff: SO HOW CONCERNED ARE
YOU THAT IT MIGHT BE YOU?
>> I'M GREATLY CONCERNED.
>> Jeff: TYLER, WHAT HAPPENED
AFTER THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YOU GO BACK TO CAMP, DID YOU
SCRAMBLE THIS AFTERNOON?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I CALL IT
SCRAMBLING, BUT I TOOK A
AMENDMENT OR TWO TO TOUCH BASE
WITH EVERYBODY THAT I'VE BEEN
ALIGNED WITH AT ONE POINT OR
ANOTHER, BUT MIKE IS A
CHARISMATIC GUY.
I'VE BEEN ON HIS CHOPPING BLOCK
FOR A WHILE NOW.
>> Jeff: MIKE, HAS THERE BEEN
A LOT OF SPECULATION ABOUT THE
ADVANTAGE THAT DAN GOT AT THE
AUCTION?
>> I THINK EVERYONE HAS
SPECULATED ON IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS, BUT I
HOPE IT WAS WORTH $480.
>> Jeff: CAROLYN, THERE'S GOT
TO BE A LOT OF CONCERN THAT DAN
HAS THIS ADVANTAGE, THERE'S ONLY
SEVEN PEOPLE LEFT, SIX AFTER
TONIGHT.
>> IT'S SOMETHING TO WORRY ABOUT
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
ADVANTAGE IS.
IT COULD BE ANOTHER HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, IT COULD BE THE
SPECIAL POWERS IDOL THAT TONY
HAD, SO AN ADVANTAGE IS SOMEWHAT
OF A THREAT.
>> Jeff: DAN, HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAVE APPROACHED YOU AND SAID,
LET'S USE IT, TELL ME WHAT IT IS
AND MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
>> EVERY SINGLE PERSON HAS
APPROACHED ME, AND WHETHER
PEOPLE KNOW WHAT MY ADVANTAGE IS
OR NOT IS ACTUALLY IRRELEVANT.
THEY KNOW I HAVE AN ADVANTAGE.
THAT ALL BY ITSELF MAKES ME A
BIGGER TARGET.
>> Jeff: SIERRA.
THIS IS THE PERFECT TRIBAL TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
IT DOESN'T GET BETTER THAN
SEVEN.
>> EXACTLY.
AND HONESTLY, I THINK THERE'S
GOING TO BE A REALLY BIG MOVE
MADE TONIGHT AND EVERYBODY'S
GOING TO BE SHOCKED AND I THINK
IT'S MAYBE A MOVE THAT
EVERYBODY'S BEEN WAITING FOR.
I'M KEEPING EVERY OPTION OPEN.
>> Jeff: TYLER, ARE WE AT A
POINT IN THE GAME IN WHICH
YOU'RE TAKING OUT A THREAT IN
CHALLENGES OR ARE YOU LOOKING TO
KEEP THE PEOPLE THAT YOU THINK
YOU CAN BEAT?
>> I THINK YOU'RE STARTING TO
THINK ABOUT THE FIVE, FOUR,
THREE ARENA, AND WHO YOU CAN
BEAT.
FOUR OF US ARE LEAVING, AIFER
EVERY DECISION YOU PERSONALLY
MAKE AND EVERY NAME YOU WRITE
DOWN, YOU BETTER GIVE DAMN GOOD
THOUGHT TO.
>> Jeff: WHAT IF IT IS YOU
WALKING OUT?
WILL YOU BE SURPRISED?
>> WOULD BY SURPRISED?
YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
RODNEY, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH
THIS BREAKS MY HEART.
>> I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET YOU
OUT OF THIS GAME FOR A LONG TIME
NOW.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
PLAYING IT FOR ME, JEFF.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR MIKE WILL NOT
COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MIKE.
DOES NOT COUNT.
MIKE.
DUDS NOT COUNT.
MIKE, DOES NOT COUNT.
TYLER.
ONE VOTE TYLER.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, TYLER.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
TYLER, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> WELL, IF THERE'S ONE THING
THAT SHOULD BE MOST CONCERNING
IS THE ADMISSION THAT EVERYBODY
WANTS TO TAKE THE WEAKEST TO THE
END.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TINED FOR SCENES
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"... THE.
>> THE ALLIANCE ALWAYS KNEW
EVENTUALLY WE WERE GOING TO HAVE
TO TURN ON EACH OTHER.
>> Jeff: THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE
CRUMBLES.
>> YOUR ALLIANCE CRUMBLES FOR
YOU.
>> YOUR ALLIANCE IS GUNNING FOR
DAN IS VOTING YOU 1 MILLION
PERCENT.
>> WHAT CAN I SAY?
I LEFT IT ALL ON THE FIELD, SO
TO SPEAK.
MY TACTICS TO GO AFTER DAN
TONIGHT WERE RIGHT, IT'S JUST
THAT THE REST OF THE GROUP
DIDN'T FOLLOW SUIT.
I HAD A BLAST.
I REGRET NOTHING THAT I DID.
EVERYTHING THAT I DID WAS TO MY
FULL POTENTIAL.
IT'S JUST DIFFERENT TO GET AHEAD
IN THIS GAME IF YOU'RE NOT
WINNING CHALLENGE, AND
UNFORTUNATELY I CAME UP A LITTLE
SHORT TODAY.