translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Carolyn found the immunity idol...
Oh my God !
...while the White Collars adopted
the Colorless way of life.
Why did our camp
become a naturist camp?
What's going on ?
Among the Bleus de Travail,
the hard work was beginning to weigh.
Without wanting to piss off,
everyone must move.
There are things
to do for survival.
- At the last immunity test...
- Come on Will!
For Will,
it's an absolute disaster.
Worker's Blues
gain immunity and reward,
sending the Colorless
to the council!
As we approach the first
council of the Colorless...
Do not touch me !
...Nina struggled to fit in...
You would think that my tribe
would try to make me feel included.
...while Vince
tried to recruit Will.
Si on sort Jenn ...
- We keep control.
- Exactly.
Now is the perfect time
to take action.
But Will promised to follow
the young people to eliminate Nina.
- We're dividing... the votes.
- We're going to split.
Girls, you vote Vince.
We will vote for Nina.
Hope Will is with me,
because otherwise, it will confuse
a lot of plans.
But at the council,
Will decided to follow
his own agenda...
Sorry, bro.
But you have to go.
...by eliminating Vince...
Vince.
Bring me your torch.
...leaving Nina alone,
in the worst place.
Vince, the tribe has spoken.
There are 16 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What happened there?
Many things.
That snake Vince wanted
to do it upside down.
I think Vince
has woven many webs
with all of us.
I wanted to follow
the split vote plan,
but instead,
Will voted for Vince.
Frankly, I do
n't trust him that much anymore.
It made me a little nervous.
I do not know. It's good, it's good.
- It turned out well.
- Did you trust us?
If I trusted you?
It was to the point that
I didn't know who to trust.
For me, what happened
on the council... You have to think about the future.
And I didn't
trust Vince.
So I extended my chances
in this game, that's what it's all about.
I play chess, not checkers.
- Yeah.
- I know I'm next.
Whatever you say,
I know you will.
So could you just make
me not feel left out
waiting to fire me?
I thought we were going to
eliminate Jenn by surprise,
and it didn't happen,
Will didn't follow.
Coming to the board,
I thought I had a solid trio.
When I left the board,
I had once again become an outsider.
No need to whisper behind my back.
You know it.
You can be here and I there,
- I won't hear you.
- Nina...
I can only help the tribe
win trials.
It's my only way to stay.
I know I'm next.
I know it.
Why do you think you've already left?
You are not going to
eliminate each other.
- That's...
- Don't give up till the end.
Did you think
Vince was going to leave tonight?
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
Everything can happen.
- Come on, Nina!
- Don't give up until the end.
- How many times...
- Stop being like that!
- How many times have I...
- Enjoy it, Nina!
Directly, Nina does her Nina,
starts to cry,
is all upset
and brings her deafness back to the surface.
Nina, you're
only talking about your hearing!
I got it, you're deaf.
We all understand.
Stop using
it as an excuse.
Monkey teaching White Collar
how to live in nature.
Mom and Dad Howler Monkeys
do somersaults.
You will never believe
what I saw.
Sex between monkeys.
- Really ?
- From beginning to end.
I'll make it short for you.
Taste.
Shirin is crazy.
She arrives: "Hey, friends!
Monkeys
show their parts!".
That's how it is
when a woman wants a baby.
I'm left speechless.
Lots of "hoo! hoo!"
of the male for a while.
How can you work in
business being this crazy?
No hugs afterwards, nothing.
Nature. This is what I saw.
Nature should
excite you more than that.
Shirin spent the morning
talking about howler monkeys.
And she's just as annoying,
loud and intrusive as they are.
They did it again,
three, four, five times.
It's weird, it's strange.
She gives off something
that doesn't stick.
She's clearly trying
to fit in, and it shows.
But that just paints
a big target behind his back.
Boom!
Oh my God ! It tastes like water!
- This is our best water to date.
- Yeah.
We need to eat.
A good fish, that sounds good to me.
- I would prefer comfort.
- And me a blanket.
- Really ?
- Yes, it allows you to sleep.
- I...
- You sleep all night.
- I slept 5 hours from the beginning.
- Bullshit.
- By night.
- By night ?
- Never !
- [???]
- ...hate us, because we tell the truth.
Hate you.
Hate us. Because we tell the truth.
That you don't like it doesn't
change anything.
Oh, go to bed, Dan!
My best trait might just
be my worst trait.
And it's my mouth.
I have a hard time closing it.
But my position is not
as bad as before.
I know how to learn from my mistakes.
Sometimes it takes an anvil
to fall on my head, but I'm learning.
We didn't ring you.
Yeah, and your mom [beep].
Never mothers, brother.
Dan and I were laughing.
I don't remember what I said to him,
but he replied:
"Your mother [beep]".
Dan goes out of his way
to make us laugh.
He wants to be
on all the jokes.
But actually, Dan, you're not funny.
Don't talk about my mom,
don't disrespect my family.
At home, if you call
my mother a [beep],
then it gets serious,
it's war,
I'll quickly show
up and jump down your throat.
You're lucky
to be in Survivor.
Candy.
You look really serious.
I did not think
the emotional proletarians,
but these guys are.
Watch what you say, man!
Watch what you say!
As a cop, I take a step back,
I watch and I analyze,
and I know when to intervene.
Sometimes if there's a fight,
we don't rush,
because when
we finally arrive,
they fought well
and are calmed down, appeased,
and we arrive:
"Okay, is that settled?".
But Rodney likes to add more.
Relax, everyone.
Dan sees himself as one of my friends.
But he's just sinking,
and we'll see where that takes him.
He crossed the line.
And not just a little.
The waves look gorgeous.
- Hey say!
- Yeah.
- Do you want to go surfing?
- Yeah !
It would be nice.
Hali and I have been watching
these waves from the start.
Perfect rolls.
And it was killing us
not being able to surf.
So why not enjoy it ?
Driftwood is used
as planks.
It's rounded below, flat above.
It's perfect !
Bodysurfing
was a great idea.
Surfing is probably
my 3rd passion in life.
So when she proposed it,
I was like, "Yeah, I got you!"
It is typically Colorless.
I guarantee you the other
tribes don't even think about it.
But Colorless
like to have fun.
Nothing is too serious here.
Why is everyone taking
this game so seriously?
What do you see ?
The lizard is good.
Win parts,
paranoia seems to have diminished.
You got it ?
Yeah.
It's edible.
It's a beautiful day,
the waves are beautiful, everything is shining.
Everything seems OK. I just want...
Continue to be the provider.
I found the snack!
Another lizard!
Everyone stay
in good spirits,
and develop
camaraderie in the team.
- I'm fine today ?
- Yeah.
After last night? Satisfied...
- ...to be there?
- Yeah.
- Glad to be here.
- OK.
Don't think you're not...
Welcome. I feel
like you feel left out
but this is not the case.
Nina, I love her, but...
I think she felt
alone again.
I'll try to be
a little friendlier with her.
Keep playing, okay?
My mother was an
interpreter for the deaf.
My 3 sisters and I, kids,
we learned sign language.
I have always frequented
the deaf community a lot.
It's something
I keep on hand.
It's really difficult.
It's hard. I mean...
I don't...
Nobody's used to that.
- Yeah.
- I want you to play.
I want you to enjoy
it and have fun with us.
Joe and I had a good chat.
He just wanted to tell me
to have some more fun.
Just keep playing, okay?
Before I lost my hearing,
I was in sales,
so I was white collar.
But I am no longer.
Listen...
When I lost my hearing
having a regular job
no longer mattered.
So I really am
Colorless,
but these people are much more
free-spirited than I am.
Are you going to try the lizard, Nina?
- Nope.
- Just to taste.
For me ! Do it !
I discover that I have limits.
Take some !
I have to change or I will leave.
Pretty good !
I tell you,
it doesn't look like a lizard,
looks like... Chicken.
Come on, Nina, do it for Survivor!
In search of the idol.
It's about spotting
something that stands out.
She must be here.
The whole tribe searches for the idol.
So I watch the fire.
I am relaxing.
I rather enjoy myself.
Because I already have the idol.
So I don't
need to look for her.
Funny !
Could we say that we stop?
Could we have a truce?
Win the next event,
wait for the next clue to search?
- Hey, Joak!
- What's new ?
Do we make a truce and
only look for it after the ordeal?
When do we get another clue?
Since you're looking for her
more than anyone...
Not really.
She says she's gonna stop
- if we all do it.
- Good.
The problem is,
I never trusted you.
If you're tired of searching,
go sit down.
You do not trust me ?
From the beginning ?
- Yeah.
- Why ?
Because you are paranoid
and that you panicked
for no reason from day one.
- Really ?
- I do not remember.
What did I say?
What did you say ?
Shirin is like a leech
that won't let go
and the most annoying person
I've ever met.
It's like mosquitoes,
at night,
constantly ringing
in your ears, and...
Lord !
Why do not you talk to me ?
I'm busy
looking for something.
As you should.
Should I? Why this ?
Joaquin was not himself.
There was fury
behind his words.
Which turns out great for me,
because that means he ca
n't maneuver in this game.
What is the problem ?
Why can't we go back?
You just have to go home.
I don't need a babysitter.
I'm in a bad position
and I can't find the idol.
I will do
what will benefit me in the long run.
Tyler and I
have good contact.
So I showed him the clue.
He's my boy,
he has to see him.
"Near
where you quench your thirst,
you will satisfy
your craving for power.
It's tucked away in a corner,
no need to climb."
Joaq showed me
the clue to find the idol.
On the second day,
Carolyn showed me the idol.
But it was important that Joaq
show me this confidence.
I appreciate you taking
this step of trust, and...
- You're my man.
- I want to win, bro.
Go on...
When you make the effort
to show this to someone,
it brings a form of unity.
Here they are again!
Even if Joaquin
is in a bad position,
So far,
I get on well with him.
And Shirin, at this point...
We're as crazy as we look.
Between nudity,
discussions with monkeys
and the fact
that she never closes it,
I have the impression
that if we lose the test,
Shirin will be at the top
of everyone's list.
The man I call Dad
is the pastor of my church,
and he taught me very early
that if you work hard,
you will be rewarded.
So no need to tell me
to do something,
because when I see that something
must be done,
I do.
But this tribe
of work blues,
supposed to have the best
work ethic of the three tribes,
fails on this ground.
And Rodney seems the worst to me.
Rod, do you want to help us
carry this wood?
Yeah, when I've eaten.
I am dizzy.
- You know what I mean ?
- Yes perfectly.
I will work when
I feel like it. How are you?
No one is my father here,
as far as you know.
There is work.
Mike makes his remarks
and I think to myself:
"Okay, that's annoying."
"Be careful what you say,
because you're not the only one getting high."
We worked all morning
without a thank you.
We work blues,
in general,
we tend to criticize
the work ethic of others,
because we think
ours is the best,
that we know how to do it best
and that we work the hardest.
Sometimes it does
n't matter much.
But in the end,
I know in this tribe
I have the best work ethic.
Everyone must do their part.
I know, but...
Not when Mike decides.
We will when we do.
If I go first for going
ahead and saying something,
at least I would have.
Guess what ?
There's no need to work
all day, every day.
We won two races in a row.
No need to be on a mission
every day,
like you from 8 o'clock.
We have all day to work.
Relax, each at their own pace.
You take yourself for the captain.
Is there a "C" on your shirt?
Are you the team captain?
So relax!
Relax ! I'll get
that fucking wood anytime I want.
You're not my father, damn it!
- So put your ass down!
- No, I'm not your father.
"Hey, Rodney, get some wood!"
Whether it's 10 minutes,
20 or an hour, I'll go.
But don't tell me
"here and now", or I won't go.
Everyone here
is stuck with it, for now.
But they all say
the same thing as me.
I am dizzy.
Look at me !
I tremble.
Let me eat
and I'll come help you!
But you want to decide when.
Just let me eat!
When I have my energy,
I will.
I'm upset, there's a reason.
I am motivated and dedicated.
I will do what you want.
But wait until I'm ready.
Not that Mike is ready.
Rodney will do what he wants.
OK ? It doesn't matter
how high you get.
It's a social game. Whether you make
a maximum or a minimum,
it won't get you through.
You have to keep a good mood.
But let me go.
Sorry, I didn't know
you felt bad.
No matter.
Nobody tells me what to do.
That's why
I work alone, you know?
- I see.
- I will when I want.
At the time chosen by Rodney.
This game... We're not
on an oil rig.
"Platform workers,
you have to work really hard,
and if not, you'll be fired."
No, it's a game,
everyone should have fun.
I'm not a slob.
I didn't grow up in that environment.
- You understand me ?
- Absolutely.
I don't live that way. Maybe him,
with his $100,000 ranch.
Because that's
the value of Texas.
In Massachusetts,
a house is worth $400,000.
- Thanks.
- Because people want to live there.
Nobody wants to live in Texas!
OK ?
Mike is the number one target here.
I must remain discreet,
focus on my three "C's",
Cool, Calm and Cooperative,
and it will be paradise.
I will make a pile of wood
under that fucking tree,
and that no one asks me
to go get any more.
All of this largely
started yesterday, for me.
Every time
I feel like I'm getting high
- to do a lot of stuff...
- But so are we!
Wait, wait.
Can I finish?
I let you finish,
I would like to finish.
I don't feel
like the respect I give you
be given back to me.
If anyone gets
respect here, it's you.
Certainly not us.
Do you think
I don't respect you?
When was the last time you said thank you for
something we did?
- Every day.
- When ?
- Name one... Name one.
'Cause we been doing this shit
all morning
and you come back and you laugh.
- "My laundry is not done?"
- That's my humble opinion.
- "Thank you for doing my laundry."
- When do you say thank you for fishing?
When do you say thank you
for the wood?
- When do you say thank you...?
- Everytime.
Everytime ! And every time
we looked for wood,
we were there! Every time !
Each time,
we helped with the wood!
Mike is a big ignoramus there.
I can't stand that.
And of course,
he wants to argue with me.
I know you got a
bible verse on your back,
but that doesn't help
take care of the fire.
Everyone is doing their part,
I really mean it.
We're not looking for wood.
True or false ?
Yeah, there you go.
We don't cook. True or false ?
You cook all the time.
- Are we taking care of the fire?
- And I appreciate it.
Do we take care of the fire?
Shall we fetch water?
We don't take care of the fire?
And how do you think
that fucking fire is burning here?
Did it happen by magic?
Your god? He went downstairs to do that
with his fucking beard?
I don't claim to be
the best Christian in the world,
but I have a relationship with God.
It was very offensive to me.
Honestly, it hurt me
on a personal level.
Like I said, if my
stepping up and talking is my downfall,
well get rid of me!
Mike always says, "If you want
to fire me for this, do it!"
Wishes come true, asshole!
Sorry !
Over here everyone!
White Collars, Overalls,
discover the new
Sans Couleur tribe.
Vince was eliminated
at the last council.
Ready for
today's immunity test?
Yeah !
First,
I collect the idols.
Rendez-la, Shirin!
I will take it!
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today each tribe
will carry a large bucket
to a water tower,
where you will fill it.
You will come back trying
to plug as many holes as possible,
to prevent water leaks.
You will pour what remains
in a barrel and leave.
The first two tribes
to fill their barrel
and raise their flag
gain immunity and reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
Besides not going to the council,
the first tribe to finish...
A huge comfort reward.
Oh my God !
Chairs !
Chairs, blankets,
pillows,
candles, rope
and a tarp.
It will change your life
on the camp.
For the second tribe
to finish: not as many,
but still very useful.
- A tarp.
- Yeah.
For the last, nothing but
a meeting with me at the council,
where someone will be the third
person eliminated from the game.
Overalls,
you are one more.
Someone will not participate.
It's whoever you want. So ?
Lindsey will not participate.
Everyone else, one minute
to get organized and we'll get started.
Let's go. For immunity
and reward.
Survivors, ready?
The White Collars fly over the obstacle
and throw their bucket.
Will, immediately in trouble.
The Colorless
are already behind.
The basics are very simple.
Fill your bucket with water
and try to bring back
as many as possible
before she escapes.
Put your hands down,
you're not plugging the holes.
- Go ahead !
- I go ahead and I come back?
Yeah.
Joe sends Nina forward.
A potentially
very clever strategy, if it pays off.
The Work Blues are back.
It's good, friends!
Bring it back quickly!
Go on !
Here are the White Collars!
The Colorless are back!
The goal is teamwork.
The more holes you plug,
the more water you will have
to pour into your barrel,
and you will therefore have
fewer trips to make.
Reverse it!
The White Collars
have their first bucket.
Go on !
The Colorless are very slow,
but it doesn't matter,
if they plug the holes.
The Colorless pour half
of their water on the ground!
Here are the work blues.
- Go ahead !
- I go.
Again, Nina goes ahead.
I don't understand
why she's not participating.
The Colorless, again
very slow, and at only four,
when they are five.
What you're doing
doesn't work, Colorless!
Les Bleus de Travail, back
with a new bucket full of water.
The White Collars,
back with a bucket.
- One more, come on!
- Its good ?
They leave.
For some reason,
the Colorless find it logical
that Nina is not participating.
On and go!
The Work Blues are back.
Here are the White Collars.
- Go on !
- Will is exhausted.
- Go Will!
- Its good.
- It's the Whites and the Blues...
- It's their last bucket!
- ...like the last time,
vying for first place.
Quick ! Quick !
We must beat them!
You must beat them!
This may be the end.
Go on ! Go on !
Will that be enough?
Nope ! The White Collars
must go back!
- One again !
- Not enough for the Blues! Go away!
It's very tight
between Blues and Whites.
Every drop of water
left in this bucket
can make a difference!
Nina finally helps,
for the first time.
A little more.
Let's go!
- Go for it !
- The Blues are back! Is this the end?
The Whites are coming back,
maybe it's the end for them.
How much water
can they hold?
Run!
Dan, over!
Don't stop!
Another bucket for the Colorless.
Nice, but not enough.
- The Colorless leave.
- Ahead !
Here are the work blues!
Would it be victory?
Here are the White Collars!
Yes ! Worker's Blues
win immunity and reward!
Yes ! White Collar
earn immunity and reward,
sending the Colorless back
to the council.
Overalls, nice finish!
Go get her!
Again, no advice.
no one will leave the Bleus de Travail tribe .
White collars!
Again, a nice finish.
This tribe remains intact.
Overalls, come get
your big reward.
Return to camp.
Pillows!
- Thank you Jeff!
- Oh my God, friends!
White collar, no advice.
Come and get your tarp,
take your things and leave.
- Thanks !
- Congratulation.
Without Color, you lose
for the second consecutive time.
But this time, it seems to
have been a strategic error.
Joe, why did you ask Nina
not to help
plug the holes?
We thought we
might go faster
by placing Nina after the obstacles,
so that she plugs
the holes afterwards.
Maybe it was a bad choice,
in retrospect,
but it seemed like
the best idea at the time.
Colorless, get your stuff,
go back to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
I thought I was in the army,
it was nonsense.
This ordeal
really tore me apart.
She tore me down.
Alas, we have to
go back to the council,
and I think
Nina's time has come.
I just want to say...
I am sorry.
I take responsibility.
I don't know what I was thinking.
- I feel especially bad...
- I didn't know...
- No, but I...
- ...that you made that choice.
Because you thought
I couldn't.
- It's true, and I...
- And I could have...
- I am really sorry.
- I thought...
I'm really, really sorry.
I should never have
made that decision.
We were so close today.
I feel a little responsible,
because I decided
the game strategy.
I should have closed it
and let Nina participate.
I regret this decision,
because I screwed her up.
I know she doesn't want
to leave. Nobody wants it.
So if she wants to fight,
she will fight.
- I should have followed my instincts.
- Nope.
"Want some help
plugging the holes?"
- But no...
- You said: "No, go ahead!"
and I was like, "I should stay,
help plug these holes."
Absolutely. I am really sorry.
I feel bad about...
You know.
For assuming
she would slow us down.
It was a mistake.
I feel really bad.
Life is learning.
We screwed up again.
We tried to avoid
Nina being a factor.
This is the result.
And so,
to the council we return.
It's not your fault.
- It's just...
- It's a game.
- I know I know.
- What are we playing?
- To Survivor.
- OK. Are we playing "Friends"?
- Nope...
- Good.
- It's just... Just that...
- No no.
- ...I don't like losing.
Neither do I.
- But it was a team choice.
- Yeah.
And I supported you.
I supported you.
She's been a dead weight
for a while.
Do you agree to eliminate it?
Absolutely.
And you, Hali?
It's clear.
How do you think the vote will turn
out tonight?
No idea.
- Sorry ?
- I say: no idea.
I think tonight
is between Will and me.
Because the three in control
are Joe, Jenn and Hali.
So I have to convince them
to eliminate Will instead of me.
Have you discussed
who you want to eliminate?
Will was in pain today.
Are you going to vote Will?
Yes, if that's what you do.
- And you ?
- It's been 2 events in a row that he is zero.
One test, still passes,
but two, no.
Nina and Will
won't be long.
Will failed in the event.
It was awkward. And I still do
n't really trust him.
No way. He looks sly.
But OK...
Nina is the killjoy of the team.
Both Will and Nina are
equally bad at proofs.
- I agree.
- Like, Will sucks.
The other day, Will took longer
than her to swim from the boat.
It's true.
I thought he was going to die.
Nina is really frail,
and her attitude sucks.
But Will has a lot of trouble.
How about you and me
voting Will?
Will voted wrong on the last council.
I don't trust him anymore,
he's a snake.
My biggest fear,
in the medium term,
it's that Will
is doing something stupid
and that Jenn and I get
in trouble at the merger.
We're between a rock
and a hard place here.
Who's going to go, Will or Nina?
Let's talk about the previous advice.
It seemed to revolve
around trust,
and ended
with Vince being eliminated, seemingly by surprise.
But it looked like Vince
wasn't the only one surprised.
Will, when you return to camp,
was there
anything to clarify?
Yes, more or less.
I had to follow someone
I trust, hence my vote.
Joe, it's interesting
that this game has so many levels.
Because you are still
in the "tribes" part of the game.
Yet you are already playing
the individual part of the game.
And those trust issues
might come back
if your tribe remains intact.
Absolutely.
You only have one
or two chances,
when you make mistakes,
correct them.
So yes, trust
is a very important factor,
to keep alliances
as strong as possible
while progressing in the game.
Let's talk about today's race.
Your strategy to keep Nina
out of the test
was difficult to understand.
Joe, what was the logic?
Getting 5 people
through the ladder was tricky.
Nina was in danger of tripping, falling
and take everything
with it, so...
Yeah, I screwed up pretty bad today.
But what's left for you, Nina,
it's the fact that they
didn't believe in you enough
- to let you play.
- Exactly.
It really showed me
that because of my...disadvantage,
they don't trust
me for anything.
But hearing played
no role in this test.
I think they see me,
as a person,
as disadvantaged.
Whether it's my ears,
my feet or whatever.
- Because you're deaf?
- Yes.
I do not agree.
No matter how many times
we take Nina aside
to re-motivate
her, restore her morale,
we always come back to his deafness.
That's what irritates me,
because we're trying hard.
Joe,
something is happening in Survivor:
perception becomes reality.
Whatever
the perception of the group,
it is real and true
for its members.
Yes, she also misunderstands us
that she thinks is misunderstood.
I know many deaf people.
I'll be the last to judge
you or anyone on a disability.
Will, I saw you after the ordeal.
You were out of breath.
Do you have reason
to worry?
I had trouble in
the second event, with the buoy.
When I got back, I said,
"It's my fault."
I think that today,
at team level,
it did not work.
But they know
what I bring to the tribe,
and I'm counting on it.
You'd be crazy to keep Will.
Seriously. You can
trust me, I'm strong.
I can win events.
You didn't let
me show you what I can do.
But you were often
emotionally weak,
and that worries me a bit.
I know it's hard for you,
but it's hard for everyone.
We all have our problems.
Stack at the right time!
Hali, could it be that Nina
is in the wrong tribe?
She may not be
Colorless.
I wonder. This philosophy
of taking life as it comes,
we know how to handle
the ups and downs.
For the most part, in
this tribe, we let ourselves go.
But Nina
doesn't work like that.
And yet, Nina, I know
you see yourself as Colorless,
a flexible person who tries
to vary points of view.
Before losing his hearing,
I had a lot of jobs
where I supervised people.
I had the responsibility
a lot of money,
I made budgets,
and that's been 44 years of my life.
It's only been seven years
since I changed a little,
but I still have
that white collar mentality.
In real life, you
may never have to eat a lizard,
you may not have to
be Colorless in your home,
but if you want to stay in this game
and play with this tribe,
you will have to adapt.
You will have to be more
Colorless to fit in.
That's all they say, I think.
I have no intention
of changing who you are.
But to play this game,
you need to be a player.
You know,
I listen to what they say.
It's tough,
but I take it to heart.
And I really think I can
do what you suggest.
I want to be part
of the Colorless tribe.
An interesting tip.
A bit cathartic, hopefully
.
It's time to vote.
Nina, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Will.
Two Will votes, one Nina vote.
Nina.
Equality.
Two Nina votes, two Will votes,
one vote left.
Third person eliminated...
Nina.
Bring me your torch.
Nina, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Survivor is often
about taking short-term losses
to better win in the long run.
Your loss today
implies that no tarp
will shelter you on the camp
and that you are still
reduced by one limb.
The hope is that eventually
it will be worth it.
Take your things,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time,
in a special double episode...
- This mentality sucks.
- It's not... I...
Is that
how your mother raised you?
In every confrontation...
You don't get a face tattoo
without being seriously bothered.
...there is a little blood.
Go on ! Go on ! Go on !
A huge crash!
She's bleeding!
Everyone, stop!
Doctor !
According to them, I am not as free-spirited
as they are.
It may be true.
Maybe being out here in
the wild with complete strangers,
brought out
another from my side.
So I'm going
to draw resources in me
and maybe change that.
These eight days
have clearly changed my life.