translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
18 new castaways
were divided into three tribes.
White Collars, Overalls
and Colorless.
Welcome to
Survivor: War of the Worlds!
Among the Colorless,
it was only harmony
and open arms.
I am completely deaf.
We are a team, we support you.
But Joe's popularity
began to irritate Vince.
- Do we mount this and make the frame?
- I do not think so.
That Joe only wants to do this
his own way is surely going to cause concern.
Among the Bleus de Travail,
only the effort counted.
In one sentence:
the Blues work tear everything.
They made a fire...
...and even found something to eat.
Did you eat a scorpion?
Only one thing was wrong:
Dan's personality.
I am fat.
The bamboo will break and we will fall.
It climbs quickly in the towers.
He's the only one
who doesn't belong here.
Among the White Collars,
business came first.
- My name is Max.
- Joaquin. Marketing director.
But bosses without employees
didn't work.
No one knows how to make a fire.
Why would we know?
We hire an overall for that.
At the immunity test, the difficulties
continued for the Whites.
The Blues win
immunity and reward,
sending White Collars to the council!
And at the first tip,
So, Joaquin's ally,
was the first eliminated.
So, the tribe has spoken.
No doubt:
you are players.
The question is: are you playing well?
Was it the right decision?
The future will tell.
There are 17 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
You just break it.
And you empty it.
Dan! I don't know what you're doing,
but come eat some crabs!
I'm in the water,
the underpants around one leg,
relieving myself,
a wave comes,
I had to hold on with both hands
to not fall head first...
- Have you lost your swimming trunks?
- ...and I lost my slibard.
- You lost your underwear.
- I lost my slibard.
Dan lost his underpants
and made himself
a makeshift underpants,
with the belt around the...
...cut,
his shirt folded so that we
can't see his ass or his penis.
- Did he really slip off your leg?
- Not slipped, ripped off.
- So you don't have a shirt anymore?
- Not on your back.
- You're going to burn.
- It's clear.
- Would you like me to leave?
- Nope.
But you could put on your jeans.
I can't run in jeans,
it would be a massacre.
- I'm dreaming, huh?
- It's real.
Please wake me up!
Socially, Dan plays stupid.
For me, he looked for how to
appear funny or entertaining,
because his image of a big pain in the ass
was beginning to lose its novelty.
So he decided to be
the guy who loses his slibard.
I think this
is his new ploy.
But he is the turkey of the farce,
Cause I want you to leave me alone
long enough
so I can see your ass
kicking off on the board.
Survivor - Season 30 Episode 2
This Will Be My Revenge
Its good.
Carry on, carry on.
That's it.
Now, face blunder.
- And to the hands.
- You're burning, you're burning!
We have fire.
It's the 4th day.
We just started a fire.
Barely.
We have trouble, on the camp,
to organize the subsistence minimum.
Not being textbooks
sets us apart from the Blues.
I wouldn't be surprised
if the Blues made fire,
kicking in the stretchers
and wreaking havoc.
But where we don't have a problem
is that we have a magnificent beach,
where you can go swimming.
Do you mind
if I go swimming?
- Okay with you ?
- Yeah, no worries.
As a fan who studied
and taught this game,
it seems appropriate
to take my hat off
to some
of my illustrious predecessors.
And There you go. The new Richard Hatch
model.
- What is your program today?
- Don't watch this.
I will focus on the fire.
Max is an interesting character.
It has a little colorless side.
The type to do what he wants,
to walk around naked.
It brings a little lightness.
But I don't know
what the show part is,
and how much
of an attempt to distract us
his intelligence
and his knowledge of the game.
Being in Adam's outfit
is no problem for me.
It's liberating, enjoyable,
and it snaps you out of your wet Survivor outfit for a moment .
It is also ideal
for having some privacy.
Because surprisingly,
when you tell people
you are going swimming
and they know you'll be naked,
you have a good chance
of swimming alone.
So it's a bit strategic,
just to have some privacy,
away from the fray.
A little time to reflect.
Where is Max? In water ?
Yes. I just saw his butt.
Max likes this game as much as me,
it's an adventure for him,
what makes me love
him and brings me closer to him.
And he's the type
to start fashions.
In fact, it's often
very convenient to be naked.
Hey, she's bare ass!
What, does that surprise you?
Naked dishes?
I'm sure even
the Colorless don't do that.
Max and Shirin walk around naked
all the time.
Poor Tyler is married,
and it's: "Oh no,
I can't watch!".
- Are you filling the bean pot?
- I fill it with water and wash it.
So I don't wash this?
Uh... Yeah...
He's gonna bring...
He's going to bring back a pot.
The main pot takes a long time
to clean, I'll make those cups.
I have too much pride
to do that.
At least someone proud
in this tribe.
Hey, Nina! You have
a nasty blister on your ankle.
- Sorry ?
- A blister on the ankle.
Owl.
- A blister. On the ankle.
- I'm healing.
I try to get to know Nina better,
to approach her,
because she's nice.
And with her disability,
it's amazing that she's here.
Alas, because she is deaf,
it is very difficult
to converse with her.
"Bring !"
I like !
I like your top.
We could collect
rainwater that way.
- Sorry ?
- Collect rainwater.
Did you see ? Is the crab
still in there?
- The what ?
- Here. You see that ?
- Is the crab still in there?
- Yeah.
How do people
converse with her?
A Colorless is a
good being, who has heart and compassion.
But the girls
are very sarcastic.
Nina wants to be part of the tribe,
to have conversations, to share.
However,
it is very hard for her.
And I find that girls find it
difficult to adapt.
- I want to go swimming naked.
- Me too. I'm too fed up here.
Let's go!
Ever since I lost my hearing,
I've been pushed aside.
Because people don't know
how to do it.
I was hoping
it would be different here.
The girls of the tribe
excluded me at all levels.
From day 1.
The straw that broke the camel,
it's because they went swimming
without offering it to me.
They never ask me
to do anything with them.
I knew from the start
that it would be tough.
But I thought my teammates
would at least try to
make me feel included.
It was nice of you
to invite me.
You never invite me.
- We told the whole tribe...
- And you left.
- Would you have come to swim naked?
- You know what ?
You two have been ignoring me
since day one.
You don't participate
much in conversations either.
You could make an effort.
But you don't even invite me.
Earlier, you were offered
to come swimming, you said no.
You know what, Hali,
don't touch me!
I really didn't
think you would be interested.
I'm having so much fun,
I'm swimming naked with my friend,
I come back and...
Nina is crying.
She is angry and says we are
mean for not including her.
I was like, "Are you serious?"
- We made an adult cry.
In general, a mother
does not want to bathe naked.
She wanted to be a young girl.
Pull yourself together, Nina!
You cry on the 4th day!
I understand that she is used
to more attention.
But we don't do that in this game.
You have to have thicker leather.
So we're probably going to have to
babysit Nina for a bit,
until...
We don't have to do it anymore.
Not the slightest human compassion!
- You know, they're just young.
- I know, they are young, I know.
They are immature.
Nina is very nice,
but it shows that she is lost.
What can I do to help you?
You are already doing everything you need to.
I fully understand his problems.
I hope she recovers.
But at this point, I think she
's already stuck a target on her back.
We have to take care of the water.
Right away.
Without wanting to piss off,
everyone must move.
As a kid, I learned
to work hard.
And that's what I do
in the game.
But Mike keep
breaking 'em on me on the camp,
because it always has to be active,
you can never rest.
What do you want to do ?
Do you basketball?
We work hard,
but we also have to have fun.
- Dan, can you help me with the rice?
- Yeah, when she's fired.
I had to work hard
all my life.
So it's in my nature
to be a hard worker.
So it's frustrating for me,
being a real worker,
to see others just...
I want to play basketball too
but there are tricks
to do for survival.
We shouldn't have to tell
adults what to do.
Without wanting to piss off:
go get some wood!
We agree ?
You still have to pick it up.
What's going on there?
At work !
Mike pisses people off.
We have a pile of wood 1m50 high.
Why get excited?
I may not bring back the most
wood, but I don't inflate anyone.
Argue with someone
and you are sure to be targeted.
The bad news:
I didn't catch any blue crabs.
The good news:
we have plenty of other kinds!
- Oh my God !
- Gosh !
That's great.
- Can you give me a hand?
- Light.
What's going on ?
It's painful
to be around people who...
No matter what job I do,
it goes unnoticed,
because Joe reaps the laurels.
"Joe does this, Joe does that."
I probably work
harder than anyone here.
But on the camp,
there is only for Joe.
He has this "young braggart" side,
he wants to prove himself.
I totally understand.
I was young too.
Now I'm 32,
my hormones have calmed down,
and I know how to let it go.
But Joe likes to be
the center of attention.
And it pisses me off.
I need recognition
and assurance.
If I do something
If I give you a piece of advice,
it doesn't often go well.
Generally, yes.
For me, everything is fine.
OK. I know you get excited fast
and want to act,
but it's like shelter.
I felt a lot of ego.
You wanted to do it your way.
I just think my way
of doing things is more efficient.
- It's the right way for me.
- But not for me.
From the start, Joe and Vince have been
battling for power.
Both want to be the alpha male.
And it makes other people uncomfortable.
Recognize that
you take over the projects.
For shelter, I was...
Yeah.
Of course, I sometimes
objected to your idea.
Vince took me aside
and said,
"Admit that
you do this and that."
Frankly,
I didn't know what to say.
I think he has some issues
that he has to deal with on his own.
He wants to be the provider.
He wants to make the decisions.
It's in his personality.
But he's out of control,
and I don't like that.
We're moving forward,
we're over this bullshit?
- Yeah, no, seriously.
- I want this to work, really.
Yes. Yes.
Joe said it all,
and I want to believe him.
But there. In my life
I am surrounded by people
that I can take for a
long time in my arms,
ten seconds of beauty,
bliss, peace.
But with Joe,
I don't feel that.
- I don't trust those three.
- Me neither, not at all.
Vince, I'm all for
Will and you.
Good.
They have preconceptions about me,
just because of that.
It is unfair.
So my loyalty is to you.
Did things really
improve between you and Vince?
I doubt he trusts me.
His eyes penetrate you
to look into your soul,
to see if you're lying.
That's how I feel
when he talks to me. Like, stop!
Because he speaks to you very close.
Vince kinda freaks me out
with his "in-your-face" bullshit.
I don't doubt for a moment
that he will do something totally crazy
which will put the whole tribe
in trouble.
He's just super paranoid.
He is intuitive. Probably a lot
smarter than you think.
I think Vince is dangerous.
He is on another planet.
He's just a little too
"Colorless" for his own interest.
Overalls, Colorless,
discover the new White Collar tribe.
So was eliminated
at the first council.
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yes !
First,
I collect the idols.
- You'll have to take it from me.
- Wow, really?
Dan doesn't move an inch.
Give it too. Thanks.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
For today's test,
one after another you will dive
and swim to a platform,
where you will find buoys
attached to a rope.
You'll maneuver
them through a series of obstacles
and swim to the platform.
Then it's on to the next.
Once
the five buoys have been collected,
you will throw them in a basket.
The first tribe to place
their five buoys in the basket
gains immunity and reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
In addition to not going to the council...
For the first tribe,
a large fishing kit.
Everything you need to
catch fish is here.
For the second tribe,
smaller but still effective...
A line, bait and a harpoon.
It will definitely change your life.
Overalls, Without Color,
you have to do without a person.
- I want to do it.
- OK.
Really ? Kelly?
I'll surprise you
for a big one, don't worry.
Kelly does not participate
in the Bleus de Travail.
Without Color, who does not participate?
Nina does not participate.
One minute to get organized
and we'll get started.
Let's go !
For reward and immunity!
Survivors, ready?
It's Vince for Colorless,
Dan for Overalls
and Tyler for White Collar.
Dan said:
"You will underestimate me,
I will show you!".
Let's see how he does.
Vince goes up. Dan goes up.
Tyler goes up.
Vince is the first in the water,
followed by Dan for the Blues!
Good job !
Tyler is now in the water
for White.
Vince approaches the second obstacle.
This is Dan and Tyler.
There are five buoys in all.
It's very hard. Sounds simple,
but you have to go down and up.
Nice work by Vince
for the Colorless.
He increases his lead.
Dan, second for the Blues.
Tyler, third for the Whites.
We have to get out of the water!
Vince is stuck!
Dan catches up with Vince, who is in trouble.
Go, Blues!
Vince comes out of the water.
He wasted a lot of time.
Go, Colorless!
Tyler has arrived.
Go, White Collars!
Well done from Dan,
catching Vince.
It's still very tight.
The Blues are leading.
The Colorless are just behind.
Carolyn gives her all
for the White Collars.
Carolyn moved
to White Collar.
Hali does not waste a second.
Sierra remains very calm
for the Blues.
Carolyn tries
to make up time.
The Colorless take the lead.
Here is Sierra for the Blues.
Hali is out. Type!
Tap, Hali!
Go, Colorless!
Dan helps Sierra.
Go, work blues!
Go, White Collars!
Jenn flies over this course.
It increases
the lead of the Colorless.
Mike has regained a lot of time
for the Labor Blues.
Here it is in the water.
Max tries to come back up
for the White Collars.
It's between Jenn and Mike.
Without Color against Work Blues,
as in the 1st event.
Max is in the water with
the third Cols Blancs buoy.
Jenn arrives with
the third Colorless Buoy.
- Go on !
- Let's go !
Jennifer has arrived. Vince helps her.
Hit the post, Jenn!
Go, Colorless!
Will is in the water.
Tap, Mike!
Go, work blues!
Lindsey is in the water for the Blues.
Go on, Max, come on!
Go, White Collars!
Shirin is in the water.
Will crosses the barrier
for the Colorless.
Lindsey is in the water
for the Work Blues.
Shirin has some catching up
to do for the White Collars.
It's between Will and Lindsey.
Overalls and Colorless,
always shoulder to shoulder.
Shirin is in the water for White.
Can she make up time?
Will slows down
on this second obstacle.
Lindsey takes the lead
for the Labor Blues.
Shirin regains time.
She catches up with Will!
Lindsey has the fourth.
Type!
Go, work blues!
Rodney is in the water.
Will, still stuck in the water.
Shirin passed Will.
Will is all tangled up.
The White Collars, now 2nd.
Go, White Collars!
Joaquin is in the water
for the fifth and final buoy.
Rodney is in the water for the Blues.
He's making progress.
Joaquin is progressing for the Whites.
Look at this !
It's between Rodney and Joaquin!
For Will, it's an absolute disaster.
It's good, we can come back!
Everything is possible !
Will finally released his buoy.
Joaquin has now passed Rodney.
The Whites are going to finish first,
although they were dead last!
Go, Colorless!
Joe is finally in the water.
Joaquin has arrived.
Start untying your rope!
Look Joe! He flies over the course
and tries to make up time.
Joaquin is already shooting.
Joaquin scores for the Whites.
Rodney has arrived for the Blues.
Joe overcame the obstacle.
Sierra shoots for the Blues.
Joe left last,
but he's not giving up.
The Colorless
are staying in the game.
White scores
a second point!
The Colorless prepare
to shoot. Joe has arrived!
Come on, Colorless!
You are always in the game!
The Blues score. 1 to 2 !
Joe shoots for the Colorless,
Joaquin for the Whites.
White scores again!
Three for the Whites!
The Whites are unleashed!
4th point from Joaquin for the Whites!
Two for Sierra!
Always zero for Colorless.
Far too short. Vince tries. Missed.
Joaquin could win...
Oh, it comes out!
Sierra...
And three for the Blues!
The Colorless do not manage
to place the slightest buoy.
The Whites,
who were dead last...
Joaquin wins for the Whites!
There is one spot left!
It's between the Overalls
and the Colorless.
Four for the Blues of Work.
The Colorless
begin to panic.
They don't get anywhere.
Sierra could win...
It is done !
The Blues of Work
gain immunity and reward,
sending the Colorless
to the council!
White collar, congratulations.
Work blues,
still no advice for you.
- I will take it.
- This time, you take it.
The Blues, the Whites, enjoy
the evening and the fishing equipment.
Return to camp.
The Colorless,
it was not in your plans,
but see you tonight at the council,
where someone will be the second
person eliminated from the game.
Return to the camp.
We'll see you at the council.
Tonight, someone is going to leave.
And when it comes to Joe and me,
it's the Cold War, missiles pointed.
We are ready to shoot.
It's gonna get crazy.
- I can't believe we lost.
- I say !
We didn't put a single bullet.
Sorry for not being able to conclude.
Not serious. It's not your fault.
It was group work, group
failure, whatever.
It sucks.
One of us has to go.
We screwed up the test,
and now we're going to the council.
It will be very interesting,
because this is the time when we have to
make decisions.
And being the Colorless,
that's not one of our strengths.
How is it going ?
You're okay ?
What's wrong ?
All ?
- Are you depressed?
- Just exhausted, that's all.
- Will is degrading.
- He is tired.
- He hardly slept all night.
- And me only two hours.
- Is it his asthma...?
- He has poor health.
Yeah.
We all feel the lack
of sleep and food.
But Will's exhaustion
showed during the ordeal.
And that worries me.
But it remains an opportunity to eliminate
a strong player by surprise: Joe.
It's our only chance to get Joe out.
But if we do that, I don't know
if we'll win any events.
I know Will's not well,
but if we change our plans,
we will leave all three.
Vince, Will and I
need to stick together.
Otherwise we'll all leave,
and I could be the first.
Because after my scandal,
I know they want me gone.
So I'm very nervous.
We might be able to
win a few trials.
Depends on whether Will
can recover.
- Let me test the waters with him.
- Yes please.
How do you see all this?
Without canard.
What would you like to happen?
I do not know.
How about we take Vince out?
Cut off the head of the snake,
and let it break from this game.
I don't trust him at all.
I would like to fire Vince,
but I have concerns about Nina.
In his place, I would seek
the idol through thick and thin.
So, her first
or Vincent first?
The game has just started.
Let's keep the team strong,
let's take it down.
At this point, it's a shame,
but Nina is the weak link.
She's 54,
and her hearing isn't helping.
She knows she is in the worst position.
She's probably looking for the idol.
We need to pay attention.
What if we did that?
How about dividing the votes?
You two vote for Vince,
- and you and me...
- You vote for Nina?
If she doesn't play it,
we'll vote again, and she leaves.
I'm allied with the girls
and Will is the fourth.
I hope
he is honest with me.
I have my doubts because he spent a
lot of time with Nina.
But you have
to trust in this game,
so let's hope
Will is with me,
because otherwise, it will confuse
a lot of plans.
Everything rests on you.
Joe wants me to eliminate Nina
with the girls and him.
I do not want to do it.
We have a lot in common.
She thinks she's left out
because of her deafness.
I know how she feels,
being the only black guy in the game.
But since we know
they're going to split their votes,
if Vince, Nina and I eliminate
one of them, we control the tribe.
Listen a little.
They want to split the votes.
You, Nina and I can
take out Joe or one of the girls.
Will told me that these three are
trying to split the votes.
This is huge, because now
is the perfect time to take action.
In my heart, in my gut,
I want to get rid of Joe.
He is very, very dangerous.
But Joe is really strong
in trials.
This is a considerable asset.
Am I ready to do without?
You want Joe gone, huh?
The thing is,
I have zero trust in Jenn.
She wants you gone, that's for sure.
She's mean to Nina.
Let her go!
- Besides, if we take Jenn out...
- We keep control.
Yes, and we keep a strong player
who will not want to leave.
And we can win races.
- If I get tricked...
- You don't... I'm telling you no.
Trust me. We have the votes.
I spoke with Vince.
He wants Jenn gone.
- So you and I are voting Jenn.
- Seriously ? Really ?
- And then we control the votes.
- This will be my revenge.
- But Will, how are you feeling?
- Every defeat depresses me.
Not that. Your health.
- How is your health ?
- Everything is fine.
- Everything is fine ?
- Yeah.
Want to change your vote?
Vince is concerned that your health
will harm us in trials.
Because of a test?
I carded in the first.
He screwed up in both.
Apparently Vince is telling
the others that I'm not well,
because of my performance
in today's event.
That's bullshit !
That I get stuck
didn't cost us the ordeal.
Not scoring a point
cost us the event.
It annoys me.
- If he's trying to get me...
- He's not trying to take you out.
I do not know.
If he wants me gone, that changes everything.
At this point there's so much
conspiracy and intrigue
I don't know who to believe anymore.
These three are close.
Joe probably only came to see me
only because they need
my vote. But at the same time,
can I really
trust Vince?
I am both
terrified and excited.
I am the decisive vote,
I decide who will leave.
God knows what will happen.
But it won't be sad.
Behind you, torches.
Grab one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
OK, colorless.
Let's talk about group dynamics.
Nina, what divisions do you see?
People who
agree or disagree.
In the beginning, I saw Hali and Jenn
often together,
then I saw Joe join this duo,
and Will and I hang out together
because we have a lot in common.
But it's hard to be the oldest.
Young people often leave me out.
But that's part of the game.
The social interactions
of people from different backgrounds.
It's hard for me, because I ca
n't always hear the conversations
and everything that happens,
and I don't want to be
the pest who says:
"What? What are you saying? Huh?".
I had a little bout of depression
from feeling so alone.
Jenn, on the one hand, you could say:
"We have to help Nina, she does
n't hear like us, let's make an effort.".
On the other, we could say:
"We all have our problems".
What is your point of view ?
I had never dated
someone who is hard of hearing.
So I sympathize.
But it's a game.
And people go along with it.
Vince, if there's a threesome
based on age and interests,
and another of two
on the same logic,
where are you ?
Right in the middle, I guess.
I like cohesion. That's my nature.
I try to be the cement
that holds it all together.
Joe, if Vince is in the middle,
a most interesting situation,
because if he thinks: "These three are too
close, I don't want to be number 4.",
he goes with Nina and Will,
and then we have a
power struggle in this tribe.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
We assessed each other, and he'll
probably land where he belongs.
I think tonight,
the person who has to leave, will leave.
Jenn, is it correct to assume
that Joe, Hali and you are together?
Based on what I heard?
Sure.
It would be silly to say: "Oh no,
they argue sometimes, that's all!".
No one in this game is stupid.
I do not think so.
But we have to maintain the workforce.
You can't lose all the time.
And clearly, some people
are less good in the tests.
This is a major concern,
as the tribe needs to stay strong.
Will, Jenn says some
are not good at trials.
Your ears must be ringing a little
after today.
Oh yeah !
Water is Black's kryptonite.
She got me today.
I got tangled up with this buoy.
Did you say to yourself, at one point,
"I have to go see Nina and Vince,
to form a trio."
Yes, we talked about it.
We form a trio, they are a trio,
we get a tie and advise.
But we don't know who
to trust. Yet it must.
If you choose wrongly,
your flame goes out.
Vince, watching
from home is one thing,
it's quite another to be here,
right in the middle of it, as the vote approaches,
without knowing if it is you!
It could totally be.
How do you handle
all levels of thinking
necessary to
stay in this game?
Jeff, for the past six days,
I tried to follow
my gut more than my head.
I was able to chat
with a few people,
and if I had doubts
about them before, I no longer have too many.
Jenn, what would you like to
see happen tonight?
I would like to see
our original plan apply.
I would like that.
But I could be in danger.
I do not know.
Nothing worse than feeling
safe in this game.
You raise a point.
Even if you three seem close
and have a grip on events,
you're right,
it could be you.
It could. But it's cool
to be here. That's the advice!
I've been watching this
since I was eight.
I always feel like I'm
watching you on TV.
I can't believe
I'm here, I'm losing my mind.
You have no idea.
Will, if you win your case,
what will happen tonight?
If I win, I'll join
the tribe, drink lukewarm water,
the insects will
still feast on this chocolate,
and I will see you less.
I don't want to see you again until the end.
Looks like it's going to be
a very important vote,
very early in the game.
It's time to vote.
Nina, over to you.
It's nothing personal.
It's strictly strategic.
Nina, you're just not
the strongest in the tribe.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Jenn.
Two Jenn votes,
one Vince vote, one Nina vote.
Two Jenn votes, two Vince votes,
one Nina vote. One vote remains.
Second person eliminated
White Collars vs Overalls
vs Colorless...
Vince.
Bring me your torch.
Did you vote for Vince?
Vince, the tribe has spoken.
- It's time to go.
- Good game.
First vote,
first surprise elimination.
Not bad. But this game
has only just begun.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Want to go surfing today?
The paradise of a tribe...
Hali and I were watching those waves.
Why not enjoy it ?
...is another man's nightmare.
I see something needs to be done
and I do it.
Let me eat
and I'll come help you!
Every time we found
wood, we were there! Every time !
Holy players!
They did a good job.
Because I would have taken them all out.
It is one of the greatest
experiences of my life.
I like to explore
every element of my being,
aspects that would otherwise remain
unspoken or unexplored,
at every opportunity.
And that was fantastic!