translated to english from Addic7ed french: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Joe, Shirin and Jenn were
stuck at the bottom of the ladder...
We are all fucked.
No matter.
against a majority alliance
of seven.
I will only go to the end
by taking big risks.
But Shirin had a plan
to make things happen.
She alerted Mike to a
secret alliance within the Seven.
Carolyn's got Will in her pocket,
she's got Rodney,
- and Tyler is with them.
- Yeah.
Shirin is smart enough
to realize
that there is a group
in our group.
I see it well.
At the council, everything was played
between two Colorless,
Joe and Jenn.
Ninth person eliminated,
second member of the jury...
In the end, they eliminated Joe,
the most dangerous
in the tests.
Joe, the tribe has spoken.
There are 9 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I have a concrete plan.
Tell me
what you think.
We're eliminating Mike now.
Right after this immunity.
We can take him out now,
he won't see it coming.
Mike will frantically try
- to strike.
- I say.
We got rid of Joe yesterday,
the most dangerous in the game.
And straight up, Rodney approaches me
with this new tactic
consisting of bumping into Mike
before he gathers his troops
and his charisma and jumps on us.
And Rodney's idea could turn out to
be very good.
Good idea.
Keep it under your elbow.
- Yeah.
- And we'll talk about it.
Absolutely.
Hey, we have the final quartet, there!
I surprised Rodney,
Will, Tyler and Mama C,
and the power has clearly shifted.
Rodney turned
on the Blues.
He is no longer part
of my alliance.
I know they want my head.
That's why I have a lot
of work ahead of me.
From today.
Over here, everyone!
Welcome to Survivor Auctions.
This morning in the mail,
you all got $500.
Wagering will be
in $20 increments.
We do not share the prizes,
and bidding will stop
without notice.
So if you like something,
bet on it. We begin ?
Good.
The first batch will remain covered.
- 20.
- 20 for Jenn.
- 80.
- 80 for Jenn.
Once, twice...
Sold to Will. Approach!
Probably grilled ass.
Here's what you bought, Will.
My God !
It's a message.
Take it back to your place,
- open it and read it.
- Index.
Bitch!
“You have acquired
your foreclosure from the auction.
Pack your things
and head back to camp."
You never know what to expect
at auction.
Shit.
- Eat for me, friends!
- We love you, Will!
Will, take the message.
- Go back to the beach.
- Bye, Will.
See you later, buddy.
- It's horrible !
- The cow !
Are you going
to fire others like this?
- We never know.
- I won't forgive you.
Let's make it more fun
by showing you what it is.
Fried chicken and waffles.
- 300.
- Ouah, Shirin...
Wow, straight!
Directly 300. You want it.
Yeah.
- Sold to Shirin for $300.
- Well done, Shirin!
- Happy for you !
- The most expensive fried chicken.
I didn't want to bid
on an in-game advantage.
For me, the important
thing was to get there.
Enjoy! Shirin didn't want
to wait for an advantage.
Sierra, you nod.
Many of us feel threatened.
So many will hold back.
Does anyone want to say it clearly?
"I don't bid on food."
Dan, Carolyn, Mike,
you are not interested in food.
You expect an advantage.
I knew that when
the auctions came,
I would starve.
It's all that matters.
Oh my God ! $100!
- $100!
- Sold to Jenn.
All or part of my alliance
has turned against me.
- 100.
- Sold to Sierra.
Rodney, here's what you have.
A steak, my hen!
No food in the world is worth
what an edge
in this game is worth to me.
As it seems everyone who
wanted food got it,
let's move on to what you expect.
The advantage.
But before putting it into play,
let me tempt you
with something else.
Love from your home.
Messages written by your loved ones
especially for you, at this stage
of the game, to perk you up.
More value than a benefit?
In the past,
whatever the winning bid,
Jeff let everyone
buy them at the same price.
I'm serious.
- Someone bet $20.
- 20.
Sierra, you bet 20?
Once, twice...
- Sold to Sierra. Approach! $20.
- Cheer.
The price is set at $20.
Anyone who wants to buy their letters
for $20 can do so.
What puts Dan, Carolyn
- and Mike in an interesting position.
- Everyone does it.
Let's do it all for $20
and we will fight for the advantage
fairly for 480.
Who walks ?
Please ?
- Mike, are you walking?
- Who wants some ?
- Go on !
- Everyone walks at 20?
- Go on.
- It's fair.
- Let's go.
- We'll get them all!
Everyone come closer!
Good. Find your messages.
I will, I will not...
- ...Trapping you.
- Please. Please.
I won't... Why
would I betray your trust?
You go-y.
Dan, take yours.
You saw him.
Why are you so moved already?
I love my wife
like in the novels.
And the second day here was
our wedding anniversary.
I can not explain it.
But you bought it. For $20.
- Thanks.
- Good. Owl.
- Mike, did you...
- He didn't.
Wow !
- Mike didn't?
- He did not do it.
- I knew it.
- Okay, so I'll give mine back.
What bullshit.
I give it back.
So much for trust, Mike.
I can not do that.
It would weigh on my conscience.
It goes against who I am.
Good.
You clearly expected it.
This is an advantage in the game.
- 480.
- 480. Dan is in on it.
- Carolyn's in on it. Mike too.
Well, come closer!
$480
is all you have.
You know what's going to happen, right?
- Draw lots.
Good.
The winning stone is white.
No problem.
At 3, each reveals.
We are looking for white.
One two three.
Yeah !
Dan gained the advantage.
You can sit down.
Dan, you purchased
an in-game perk.
May it remain sealed, and when you return...
- Ok thank you.
- ...open it in private.
Good. These auctions are over.
Take your things,
return to camp.
I told Mike
to go ahead of me.
He turned around.
And it broke my heart.
Maybe he just
lost my trust.
I'm pissed.
I spent $100
to exclude myself from the auction.
And I thought to myself...
It's not possible.
I was devastated.
And so, I return to the camp,
and suddenly, oh my God!
There's a clue for me!
Wow !
I got a card
that said "camp"
and there is a cross,
and it says "dig".
They probably eat
burgers and fries,
but maybe I have better.
It's crazy how this game can
turn to your advantage,
just like that.
I thought I was living the worst day,
but it could be huge.
Oh my God !
It's a big box.
I have a message.
"You have excluded yourself from the auction,
but you also bought yourself
a personal stock of rations,
enough to
last until the end of the game.
What
you will or will not disclose,
it's up to you to decide."
The Bible says it's better to
give than to receive, so...
I'll bring it all back.
Even though these snacks are for me,
we've all been here 25 days,
everyone's starving,
so I will share.
It might be worth a few
points when they want to eliminate me.
It will be a nice gesture, they will see
that I have no grudge.
How are you ?
I'm doing well.
Do me a favor.
- Close your eyes.
- Close eyes ?
Jenn, read this.
"You have excluded yourself from the auction,
but you also bought yourself
a personal stock of rations,
enough to
last until the end of the game.
Oh my God !
Jenn, get a piece of jerky.
- No no no. Guard it !
- No, friends.
It's a game. Let me do
what I want with my food.
And I want all the details!
Mama C, what did you eat?
Rodney turned around.
It's only for that
that I almost didn't buy this.
I screwed up at the auction.
But I know that an alliance
was formed against me.
And I'm not going to
stand idly by.
And I'm going to blow her up.
Now.
For if I do not reveal
this covenant immediately,
Dan, Sierra and I,
where he left.
If I almost
didn't take my letter,
it's because I know
that you're going to turn around, Rodney.
And I know that at tomorrow's vote,
there will be four voices against me.
And I know which ones.
One, two, three and four.
Without a shadow of a doubt.
I overheard a conversation
that I wasn't supposed to hear.
Dan's famous words:
"Weather vanes never win."
Nice strategy, Rodney.
He returned !
No way. You're still here.
- Yeah !
- You turned around.
You betrayed the Blues.
You're still here.
Who have I betrayed?
- We will see tomorrow.
- Yeah, and you're screwing it up, you idiot.
We've all had
letters from our loved ones,
and you're ruining the moment
by freaking out there.
You better calm down.
- I'm telling you...
- You better calm down.
- I'm telling you, I...
- I know what I know.
- Yeah, you know what you know.
You know what you know,
you broke a hose.
I know what I know.
Oh my God !
I'm glad
they're all here.
Don't get mad because
you got caught turning around.
- Nobody got caught because...
- You lost your mind, mate.
Returning from the award,
Mike said to me:
"They are four
against Dan and me.
Rodney betrayed the Blues."
And Mike feels the urgent need
to unpack everything.
It's a symptom
of fatigue and paranoia.
And his timing was catastrophic.
We have letters from our loved ones,
we just want to read them.
I'm going, I ca
n't wait any longer. Sorry.
Do your thing, Sierra.
- We exchange our photos?
- Oh my God !
Look at your hairstyle in these photos!
Oh, pictures of my animals!
You have [???] ?
Oh my God !
"Remember
what I always said:
be smart, but stay honest.
I like you. Father.
Come back to us in good health."
“My eyes are getting wet
writing this.
I miss you so much
it hurts.
All my Love. I ss."
Actually, I apologize
for bringing all that up.
It's a very special moment.
I denounced the alliance
that wanted to take me out.
And now
they're all mad at me
because I wasted the moment.
But it's a game,
and I'm here to win.
I hope my strategy
will work.
It might fail, but at least
now everyone knows it.
What Mike said is true.
But I have
to use it to my advantage,
so I'm going to get
what I need: Dan's vote.
How are you, big boy?
- [???]
- I love you, brother.
I love you too.
I don't know where it came from,
it was really inappropriate.
- I do not know.
- You almost missed this experience!
I can't believe it.
- He threw a fit.
If we weren't in Survivor,
I'd face Mike to the face,
like real men
do on the street.
But we in Survivor,
gotta beat it with my mind,
be smarter than him.
And with what he has done,
he makes it easier for me.
I had never seen anything
so disrespectful.
- He faked you.
- I say.
So much so that you almost
didn't have that.
The game has gone
to his head, my brother.
It's playing...
He showed his true face.
Mike ruined a beautiful moment.
And it hurt me.
Because Mike is my friend.
But he's convinced
that Rodney turned around,
which now places
Mike, Sierra and me
at the bottom of the food chain.
Who is telling the truth? I do not know.
Let's see what that $480 got me.
“Congratulations. You have acquired
an additional vote.
When you
intend to use it,
you'll have to announce
it after Jeff says:
"I will count the votes".
This vote will count
like any other
during this council."
Brothel!
I couldn't have imagined it
in my wildest dreams.
I expected an advantage
in the next immunity test.
But getting a second vote?
Do you have any idea
what this means to me?
It's like Willy Wonka's golden ticket !
Oh my God !
Were you on camp yesterday
when Will
described his return to camp?
Yeah.
- I very much appreciated that he shared.
- Yeah.
But I don't think
he told us everything.
He said he had to dig,
open that box,
that there was a lot of stuff
and that he brought it back.
But where is the box?
Yeah.
- Surely there's more.
- 100 %.
Officially, Will
shared all of his food.
These rations should be enough for him
until the end of the game.
What...
...seems a little suspicious to me.
I just want to find
where he stashed this food.
Will has a ton more food.
What do you mean ?
He just gave us
the stuff he doesn't like.
A rumor circulates,
saying that there is more food.
You're hiding things from us.
Who says that, Shirin?
that they will reveal everything
and denounce you.
I learn that these three say
that I lie, that there is more food
and I hide it.
It's a bunch of bullshit.
I am already [???]
because I didn't get
a letter from my family.
But if I'm being generous
and you doubt me,
that you doubt my integrity?
That, no.
I chose to share with you.
And you doubt me?
Is there room
for anything else, Miss Cupid?
You just open it!
Is there room for something else?
I know you [???],
all you do is eat and talk!
Is there room for something else?
- Do you really have to talk to me like that?
- Yes, I talk to you like that.
Never
question my integrity, seriously.
Will came back to camp
totally freaked out.
Mike was absent,
Jenn was absent,
and Will starts
to lash out at me.
Honestly, like crazy.
So let's be honest!
You want to talk, let's talk!
Swallow or spit!
- Let's go!
- Shut up and you'll stay longer.
- Come !
- That's crazy.
Don't just stand there
and get attacked.
When you are told things to your face,
- this is what happens.
- Nope.
You don't want to hear the truth.
Nobody loves you.
I guarantee you that in the United States,
right now,
nobody misses you.
And then, he added
some in the personal attacks.
We all have loved ones who
love and care about us.
You have nothing.
Growing up in a family
ravaged by domestic violence
and having been verbally abused
throughout my childhood,
it annoys me.
You have nothing.
You have no family, you have nothing.
- Stops personal attacks.
- I do what I want.
- Nobody talks to you.
- Listen to him, he is a man of God,
- he prays before each meal.
- In effect.
- Thank you Lord !
- God does not like ugliness.
- I denounce the ugliness, there.
- Yeah.
Get on your little bitch,
Mike, and get the hell out of here.
You understood me.
I think the worst
part is that other than Mike,
everyone
stood there smiling,
"It's funny, isn't it?".
And let it happen...
It's disgusting.
Mike wasn't there,
so he came after me.
What was said?
that I have no one who loves me,
that I am a loser...
- Why is it getting so personal?
- I do not know.
He was quite violent.
It's not good.
In the last few days,
I didn't really want to stay anymore.
But these people fear so much
that I'm staying
to screw up their game.
Can I have a hug ?
At this point, Shirin, Jenn and I,
we only have the three of us.
But we are still in the game.
And I'll keep
trying every approach
until I find
the loophole or leave.
Over here, everyone!
How is everyone doing
after 27 days in this game?
- Not bad.
Not good.
It's difficult ?
When they came back with
the letters from their loved ones...
It was hard.
I was wondering...
If I withdrew
from this immunity challenge,
thus taking
the risk of being eliminated
and lose the million dollars,
I'd be willing to do that
for those letters.
Family means more
to me than money, so...
That's all I'm saying.
This is what I think.
If no one here has any objections,
then Will can give up,
and his letters will be waiting for him at the camp.
But, Will, in fairness,
all those present
must agree.
If someone says no,
we can't do it.
- Does that seem fair to you?
- Yes it's right.
Good. We're going to do it by a show of hands.
Anyone who opposes...
What a surprise.
Shirin is the only one.
He bought his thing at auction,
he was expelled, he missed the letters.
It's the rule of the game.
Will, I can't do this.
Not serious.
So, for the integrity
of the game, let's go!
Good. So let's come to immunity.
First of all, Tyler, I'm taking her back.
- I'll bring it to you, boss.
- Thanks.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will use metal clamps
to carry a ball
crossing
a series of seesaws.
Once at the end, you will place
the ball on a support
and leave.
If, at any time,
you fall or drop the ball,
you will have to start over.
The first person to place
their six balls on the rack
wins immunity, secures
a one-in-eight chance of winning this game.
Losers will go to the board
where someone will be eliminated
and will become
the third member of the jury.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Alright, here we go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
A seemingly simple test.
The clamps are very heavy.
Balancing that ball
is tough.
Straight away, the guy
who didn't want to participate
takes the lead. Will.
Will lets go, he has to start over.
This is Mike.
Mike lets go. Dan is there.
- Nope.
- Dan lets go.
There is a severe learning phase.
Here comes Tyler,
slowly but surely.
He reaches the finish
and his support.
Tyler places his first ball...
And it's on the rack.
Rodney lets go.
Mike returns.
And here's Dan again.
Mike is supporting her.
Mike places his first.
Dan loose, he was at the end.
Dan has to start over.
Tyler has one, Mike has one.
Jenn lets go.
Shirin still tries to leave.
Here is Mike, trying
to pick up the pace.
This is Tyler, with his second.
Tyler lets go, he has to start over.
This is Rodney. It seems well launched.
This is Mike.
Mike has taken the hit now.
Mike is in the lead.
First for Rodney.
Mike has two.
Rodney has one, Tyler has one.
Dan places his first.
Sierra places her first.
This is Tyler.
Tyler, almost at the end
of the second seesaw, lets go.
This is Carolyn.
Mike is on his third.
Mike is flying over the course now.
It has a rhythm, and it works.
That's three for Mike.
This is Tyler, with his second.
Carolyn has one.
Here's Dan with his second.
Sierra with her second.
Oh, Sierra lets go
at the last second!
- My God !
- Will let go.
This is Mike.
Mike narrowly crosses
the second seesaw.
Fourth for Mike.
Right next to it, Tyler is on three.
It's between Mike and Tyler
at the moment.
All the others...
...are far behind.
This is Mike, and Tyler right behind.
Mike has a head start
at the moment.
It will be the fifth for Mike
if he can place it.
And it's done! Mike goes back
to get his 6th and last ball.
The fourth for Tyler.
It's the final sprint.
Dan lets go again.
He returns with his fifth.
Tyler lets go, he has to start over.
Nice opening on the victory.
Mike with his sixth ball.
He takes his time.
For immunity.
Mike wins individual immunity!
Ensures a one in eight chance
of winning this game.
Yeah Mike!
- Do not get too excited, the others!
- Thank you, Jenn!
I needed it. I needed it.
Mike, come closer!
When I needed it most!
- It's true ?
- And how !
First individual immunity
won by Mike.
Mike can't be eliminated
on the board tonight.
You're getting a 1
in 8 chance in this game.
As for you guys,
after 27 days here,
someone will be eliminated and
become the 3rd member of the jury.
I feel that the afternoon
is going to be interesting.
Especially with Will and Shirin.
Get out the popcorn!
This will be the best advice
ever.
Take your things,
return to camp. See you tonight.
- Cheer.
- Thank you, Jeff.
One of the worst things possible:
Mike gaining immunity.
My game took a big hit.
This camp has become a real circus.
Whatever happens, it won't be
the advice we want it to be.
When you gain immunity,
we do the dance of happiness.
We do the dance of happiness
when we have done something good!
It was awesome.
And the timing was perfect,
because I was definitely
in the hot seat tonight.
I can't believe
he won.
Yeah.
Neither do I.
On vire Shirin?
No. Let's ruin his life.
Jenn is more dangerous.
Let's eliminate the danger.
Shirin is not dangerous.
This advice is going to be very important.
For we have to separate these three.
Personally,
I would like to eliminate Shirin.
She has no soul,
no value, nothing.
But Jenn, she
's good at trials.
So she has to go.
- So we divide, 3-3.
- Yeah.
One of them is leaving, that's clear.
We stay strong.
And we will do it again, and again.
It's a little...
Basic Survivor.
We are six welded.
They can't win.
I have a question for you.
Would you rather see
Tyler go or Mama C go?
Rather Mama C,
I don't like her masses.
Would you vote that way tonight?
Absolutely.
I don't want any
of these people to win.
I think they're going to split
the votes between Jenn and me.
In the best case.
I'm 99%
sure Sierra rolled over.
She barely looks at me.
But for Dan, I have my doubts.
If we had Dan,
we would be four.
And we could eliminate
Mama C by surprise.
At this point,
I want to stay in the game.
Only because I don't like
these people and want to eliminate them.
But if it should work,
it depends on Dan,
who is dumb as a broom.
And so, my whole part
is in the hands of a moron.
My brother.
You must see
how close they are.
For me, we all are.
Mike, we've all talked about being
the bottom 5, the 4, the 3.
All of us.
We all have our eyes on the final.
But that doesn't mean
they're going to act so soon.
They must believe they have Dan.
Yeah. But...
They don't have Dan.
Dan would be stupid to turn around.
Yeah.
I understand that I put you
in this situation.
I understand.
- But you teamed up...
- I had no choice!
But you and Sierra are the only ones
I promised the final three.
And I'm always
ready to honor that.
At 1,000,000%.
Because we are the United Blues.
I've been blue, blue, blue,
since day one.
They spent the day there.
Why is he doing this?
The more time Dan spends with them,
the more dangerous it becomes.
At this point, I worry:
Is Dan still with us?
Because he has not shown to
be very smart in this game.
But I have my idol.
And if Mike turns it over,
I might have to use it.
Who do you trust?
In Rodney?
Who is everyone's
best friend all of a sudden?
Of which you said yourself
that he is the most despicable,
vulgar and revolting being you know?
And Will, attacking
a 29-year-old woman,
who calls me a bastard?
I have your back covered.
They won't, Dan.
They use you.
You and me, we built
this camp on which we live,
with our bare hands.
I sweated and bled with you.
- In those trenches.
- Absolutely.
Dan, who do you trust?
Who has developed
trust with you?
I did my best.
I don't know if
he will come around to my point of view.
I would like to believe
that deep in her heart,
Dan always wants
to collaborate with me.
Would you be willing
to vote Carolyn tonight?
Mike might be right.
These four are
going to let us down.
Or maybe
he's lost his mind.
What obsesses me is that
I am the pivotal vote tonight.
And it's my worst nightmare.
Five minutes ago,
everyone around the fire
doubted you.
Including me.
If you're pissing off the band, then...
That's enough.
I'm tired of these little games.
If I go with them, it's my choice.
I decide my fate.
Nobody but me
dictates my future.
My choice. My choice. not yours,
not yours, and not theirs.
Mine.
If I oppose Mike
and I'm wrong,
I will never forgive myself.
But you have to leave emotions
aside, because it's a game.
By the way, I'm going to make
a million dollar decision.
Or make a
million dollar mistake.
Now here are
the members of the jury.
Status.
And Joe, eliminated at the last council.
Well, Will, you said:
"Bring out the popcorn, this is going to be
an entertaining tip.".
A little, my nephew!
I'm ready.
Looks like you are too.
Let's just say that.
An incident happened yesterday.
Shirin said,
"You have all this food,
- you do not share", this, that.
- False.
- Fake.
- How dare you doubt me?
To say that I hid something to eat
while I shared with everyone!
Including people
I don't like.
And I didn't eat
at auction like them,
nor had letters like them.
But I said,
"Here's what I got for you,
let's party!".
And we doubt that?
I saw red.
Good. So you explode.
At 150,000%, I exploded.
But Jeff, to be clear,
his yelling didn't stop there.
He said two things
about the incident itself,
- then he attacked me personally.
- No way.
He started saying that I had
no family, that I was a loser,
and that he is more loved in the game
than me in all my life.
- But it's true !
- That I have no soul,
- that he must pray for me.
- It's true.
Only personal attacks.
It had nothing to do with the game.
It was purely personal.
It went way beyond the game.
And you know why
I don't have a family?
Let's talk about that for a second, Jeff.
It's too funny, too great
to denigrate me because I have no family.
I have no family
because my biological father,
- like you, verbally abused me.
- I did not do this.
- I just...
- Absolutely... Shut up!
I put you face to face with the truth.
- You were verbally attacking me.
- And this is how you react.
That's what you do.
You play the "victim".
- I was a victim of domestic violence.
- She's a "victim".
That's why my family
was torn apart.
And that's why I don't have one.
- And he doesn't care.
- No way.
While a bunch of people
watched it like a show.
Shirin, are you laughing in relief?
Yeah.
- Maybe even a little cathartic?
- Yeah.
Good.
Sierra, give me an idea
of ​​where we are from that point of view.
Four Overalls,
three White Collars, two Colorless.
How each person's visions of life
do they influence the game,
on the 27th day?
Jeff, worlds separate us.
You can forget how
the game started,
because we are nine individuals
deprived, hungry,
and wanting $1,000,000.
It's every man for himself at this point.
Dan, the blue tribe, in particular,
was very tight.
We talked a lot about loyalty,
"Working Blues are like that."
Does it make it difficult
to potentially have to
vote against a Blue?
It's very difficult.
As a fan, it says:
“I can store my emotions.
I come here
and put them aside."
Bullshit.
It's pure bullshit.
You get to know these people.
You bond with them.
And we bonded
over a lifestyle.
Mike, by winning immunity
today,
you said, "I
needed it more than ever".
Absolutely. These people
decided that I was
very dangerous in this game.
But there is a
main covenant of four.
These four will go to the end of the game.
Sierra, Dan, you'll start
fifth and sixth.
Rodney, you...
You want it, you want it!
Because this freak, at auction,
nearly deprived Dan, Tyler and Carolyn
of letters from their loved ones,
- taking back his $20.
- They got their letters.
Let me finish !
Then we would
open our letters,
this guy tells us: "There is
an alliance, and an alliance...".
This guy freaked out,
that's why he's in danger.
I don't care what he says.
I wanted to stay cool,
But I attack you with facts,
and everyone agrees
because they know it's true.
Wow !
Shirin, do you expect to
receive votes tonight?
Yes. I think the plan is
to split the votes between Jenn and me
- since Mike has immunity.
- So it would be 6 to 3.
It's four plus two against three.
- The two being Dan and Sierra.
- Yeah.
Carolyn, you're shaking your head
like you don't believe it.
I think what we've established,
is that when six solders
eliminate another alliance,
it's obvious,
they don't belong to the six.
Dan, are the arguments
falling on deaf ears,
or do you have
to listen to them to the end
and say,
"OK, let me think about it." ?
I would be stupid not to listen.
You have to assess your options.
Because it's not just
about reaching the end of the game.
At this point,
it's the how that matters,
and who you send there.
Well, it's time to vote.
Tyler, over to you.
You're quite the number, Jenn.
It's not because you know
all the seasons of Survivor
that you know how to play, my daughter.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an
immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Jenn. Two votes Jenn.
Plan. Deux votes Program.
Jenn.
Shirin.
Three Shirin votes,
three Jenn votes, one Carloyn vote.
Jenn. Four votes Jenn.
Tenth person eliminated
and third member of the jury.
Jenn.
Bring me your torch.
I will miss you.
Jenn, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Good bye and good luck !
And play nice, huh!
See you soon !
- Bye, Jenn!
- I love you !
The good news:
you've come this far.
The bad: there are
eight people so motivated
that they will stop
at nothing to win.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
You are so much
more dangerous now!
Mike is running out of allies.
I have nothing more to lose
at this point.
I'm already public enemy number one.
While Tyler betrays
one of his own.
Ahead ! I need a way
to look in the bag.
I took Dan's bag.
- He has an extra vote.
- Wow.
Many of these people
fear a max.
Will seemed like a nice guy,
but he looks picky.
Sierra, I don't know,
she just sucks.
I hated Rodney,
but I really hate Mama C.
Just like I hate Dan.
It's fake ass, it kills me.
But I can't wait
to see the rest of this tribe
destroy each other. I just hope
they don't get on the jury too soon,
so as not to see their faces again.