translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
After the merger,
no one took
their second chance for granted.
You have to be operational from the start,
in the new school Survivor.
Two hidden idols
had already been found.
I like !
Joe kept winning...
Joe wins
his second immunity test!
...and Wentworth, Abi and Ciera
were at the bottom of the ladder,
struggling to stay alive.
I'm so sick
of their bogus plans.
I will try everything I can
hoping
to provoke a reaction.
On the board, it was clear
that Survivor's game had evolved.
For me, there is no
bottom line.
There is no
usual hierarchy.
And Wentworth decided
to take the game into his own hands...
This is a hidden immunity idol.
...ending
Savage's second chance.
Eighth person eliminated
and second member of the jury...
Unbelievable.
There are 11 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Hashtag: hidden immunity idol.
- It was epic!
- Sacred...
I would just like to say...
Wait, I'd like to start.
I was a little nervous,
I felt betrayed
by some,
I play, that's all.
- It was terrible !
- Good game !
I was going to explode, at the council.
Great gods!
Good morning !
I am Kelley Wentworth,
and I just idolized
Andrew Savage on the way out.
And that answers our doubts
about idols!
- In effect !
- It's true !
- Where did you find it?
- I do not know !
I've come so far
since Blood vs. Water.
A hidden idol!
A great shot from Kelley Wentworth!
It's as
if I wasn't the same anymore.
I wanted to take risks,
make shots...
I haven't felt
this good in 21 days.
But it has to be one of the 3 girls
next time.
We can't let them,
all of a sudden,
become friends with Tasha and Jeremy.
- None of that!
- And I'm screwed.
We have to break
this circle of witches.
Kimmi calls Ciera, Wentworth and Abi
"the three witches".
It's like
the three witches in Macbeth,
who stirred their cauldron,
bous, bous, stirs and disturbs!
Abi is boiling,
she is hot-blooded.
Ciera is restless:
"Let's take action!"
And Wentworth stirs up trouble,
she comes out idols.
I don't wanna end up
like King Duncan,
murdered overnight.
I want to be the one
who murders in the night.
- It worked fine.
- It was perfect.
Absolutely perfect.
These witches are good,
they've cooked up something epic.
But how do I get from them
the potion that will serve me?
It was hot yesterday, huh?
One less. Savage is gone.
- Kelley must have had some kind of clue.
- She must have known something.
And she found it. That's crazy.
- Damn lucky!
- Yes !
Savage's departure really pisses
me off.
He was another man
no one really loves
which served as my shield.
But even though
I trust Stephen
and may an idol protect me,
I need two idols
because they're going to come after me.
I have to search,
break my ass, again.
Oh my God !
- This idol will come back.
- Yeah.
- We have to find her.
- I say.
Hey Keith, and here?
I look for places
that stand out.
Yeah. Oh I see.
We have to find that idol.
Because now people are
really thinking, "Joe won 2 immunities.
If he loses, he has to go."
I spent 30 minutes today
looking for an idol
which will be crucial for my survival.
I just don't know where she is.
What are you doing ?
I need...
- Go do your thing.
- Yeah...
- Here ?
- I'd rather be alone.
Just ten minutes, if that's okay.
I'll be done in ten minutes, I
promise.
I come across Joe,
who was looking for an idol.
He knows he is in danger
and he is nervous. And I love that.
I caught Joe looking for the idol,
desperately.
The low.
He searched everywhere.
- The low ?
- Near the mail tree.
Basically, there's this group of eight
who vote together, in principle.
But there is paranoia among them.
It's great for me.
I really hope people
are finally ready to play.
Lord, please
let's take a big swipe
at the next tip!
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the reward test?
- Yes !
Today you will be divided
into two teams of five.
At my signal, you will build
a staircase with wooden posts.
Then you will cross a maze
and go down a slide.
Then, a person will guide a key
through a rope obstacle.
With this key,
you will open a chest.
Two teammates
will use the coins in it
to solve a puzzle revealing
the three numbers of a combination.
The 1st team
to find the combination
and raised his flag
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes !
The five winners will leave here
for a spa at the Survivor.
First, your first shower
in 22 days.
Oh my God !
Then you will have
a traditional Khmer massage,
to improve your circulation
and heal your sore muscles.
Then you will eat
spa food: sandwiches,
salad, dessert.
You will return to camp
regenerated, refreshed
and well fed.
This event was first contested
in Intelligence vs. Muscle vs. Beauty.
Tasha and Spencer were still
in the game and on the same team.
Spencer did the puzzle.
They lost.
Another big
2nd chance opportunity.
We are going to form the teams
like a schoolyard, and therefore,
one person will not participate.
Let's go!
We have our two teams.
Tasha was captain.
She chose Fishbach,
Spencer, Joe and Ciera.
Wiglesworth was captain.
She chose Keith,
Wentworth, Kimmi and Jeremy.
Abi was not chosen,
no reward for her.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
The first goal
is to build a staircase
which will take you to the top of the maze.
The only problem,
is that the length of a post
does not necessarily correspond
to his position.
Because each hole
has a different depth.
A small pole
may go towards the end
and a big one,
towards the start.
Hence the need to collaborate.
And these poles are very heavy.
No, move over, Spence.
You will notice
the gradual slope.
If it doesn't gradually rise to the
top, it's wrong.
When you progress,
you will know it.
It will be possible to progress
from one post to another.
The Violets seem to be off to a good start.
They start to find the trick.
It's always chaos
among the Greens.
They don't make much progress.
The Violets take the lead.
Another fair post.
Is it good ?
Yes it's good ! Ahead !
The Violets took the lead.
Go through the maze.
No it is wrong !
The Greens
are still at a standstill.
Green should be like this.
The Violets are in the lead.
Joe goes back down.
Big advance for the Violets.
The Greens
are still at the posts.
Come on, Fishbach!
You are here for that!
This is Spencer. Go for it !
A person now!
Joe will take care of guiding the key
through the rope obstacle.
When you have passed,
everyone will follow.
The Greens are far
from aligning their posts in order.
Joe almost passed,
increasing the lead.
Go ahead, everyone!
Huge lead for the Violets.
It doesn't play.
The Greens may
never catch up with them.
Go on !
Two people on the puzzle
for the Violets, Spencer and Ciera.
While the Greens
are totally lost.
Where do we put it?
This could be the worst beating
of Survivor's story.
Spencer, in search of redemption.
He made this puzzle
the first time he competed in
this event and he lost.
- [???]
- Indeed.
Total disaster for the Greens.
Let's put this one here.
Five people, nine posts,
and they're getting nowhere.
Which gives
Spencer and Ciera plenty of time to collaborate.
- You are looking for three numbers...
- Yes, like that.
...to find the combination
and win the reward.
A new piece for Ciera.
The Greens are always busy
with their posts.
They finally found it! Ahead !
I do not believe.
Spencer and Ciera slow down
after making rapid progress.
Go on !
Jeremy descends and falls heavily.
Wiglesworth falls.
This is Kimmi.
- Lord, my ass!
- Keith.
A person !
You go-y !
It is Jeremy who will guide the key
through the rope obstacle.
Can he get there quickly?
It's good, it's good.
They have the three numbers.
Are they in the correct order?
This is the next question.
The numbers in the puzzle must
be found in the combination.
Otherwise, they must be changed.
Come !
Come on !
Jeremy has passed!
For victory ! Did they find?
That's it.
Reward and redemption
for Spencer and Tasha,
with a nice reward
at Survivor's spa.
Nice reward.
You're off to Survivor's spa,
it should be a nice afternoon.
Grab your stuff,
go ahead and enjoy!
- Thank you, Jeff!
- Congratulations to you !
- Have fun.
- See you.
Jeremy, Keith:
I have nothing for you.
Take your things,
return to camp.
We were way off.
It was awkward.
This day is a mess.
Dirty day.
Last night was ugly,
Savage left.
Today is ugly.
There are ups and downs.
Today is low.
Oh my God !
Look at this food!
Welcome to the spa!
Oh my God !
We got an incredible reward.
Massage, fresh water shower...
To good friends!
To this great reward!
Eating in this game
is really valuable.
It keeps your mind
and body level.
Serve yourself !
It's happiness on the table.
As the immunity test approaches,
it gives us
an advantage over others.
Oh my god,
these rolls are delicious!
- Spencer, will you pass me the rolls?
- Yes.
There is strategy
in a reward.
It gives you time
with different people
that you
might not have at camp.
So, are we talking strategy
or just food?
' Cause obviously
I'm in the wrong place,
so it's not like...
I have nobody.
My closest ally was Kass.
The more the game progresses, the
less there are voices.
Every voice
should be used strategically.
Wentworth, Abi and Ciera
are more thoroughly
than the dominant alliance,
because they are desperate.
They are the ones who deserve to be here.
I will just say this, as the queen
of those who say things:
I know some of you
are very close to Jeremy.
But I promise you
that to go to the end with him
is to lose.
In this season of Survivor,
everyone sees the hierarchy
and everyone wants to overthrow it.
So, play it old fashioned,
with a covenant of five
that contains a quartet,
which contains a trio,
which contains a duet...
It won't hold.
It will dissolve.
What do you think of Wigles?
- Wigles also...
- She would win.
Precisely, it has
the "first season" aspect,
She was
very smart...
- Socially, she speaks to everyone.
- It's true.
Everyone loves Wigles.
There are groups of votes
that make sense at some point
and which can evaporate
the next day.
Everything moves much faster
and very differently
than in the past in this game.
So, clam, all the crabs
and winkles tonight,
and we'll save two large clams
for tomorrow.
I'm pissed that we lost.
And especially at this point.
We got run over.
But with just
five other people,
busy cooking and talking,
they will leave me alone.
And I went to find the idol.
I went
near the mail tree.
I dug around and everything.
There was nothing.
The 1st idol I found
was in a tree,
under leaves.
I thought, "There's a big tree
by the mail."
Oh my God !
I turned around,
he was right in front of me.
It's really crazy!
I'm not kidding, honey!
I'm not kidding.
"Well done, this clue will lead you
to the idol, but you will have to..."
Oh my God !
“You will have to be cunning and discreet.
Tonight, when everyone has gone to bed,
you will take action,
follow the map
and look for the lantern.
There you will find
the security you seek."
That's more or less the path
we took in the merger.
I was having a bad day.
But it looks like it's getting better.
I'm too impatient!
I love that.
At moonset,
the winning team returned from the spa,
and everyone was lying down,
ready to go to sleep.
"It's going to be piece of cake.
I'll just get up,
they won't mind."
You know, you go down and...
Come on, whatever!
They are all around the fire,
to discuss.
Nobody ever does that!
It was crazy.
Don't stay up all night!
Finally, I said...
I'm going to the bathroom.
This food smeared me.
And I drew.
I walked away.
It is dark night.
There are rocks, trees,...
I don't even know what's there.
There are snakes and all,
and here I am, brushing
the branches from my face.
I see a torch.
From a distance, I see a light.
So I headed
in that direction.
I bring!
Look at this !
And There you go !
This season,
there are no two identical idols.
And hanging from the lantern
was this beauty.
It's number 2!
It took me two years,
but now I have two idols!
Two hidden idols!
With two idols,
I can be more aggressive.
It's the rules! He's an idol!
She's Val's idol.
This is Val's idol.
And the other one is Val's idol.
She is magnificent.
I love it !
Val is my wife
and my best friend.
I can't
keep it inside me anymore.
I do all this for her.
I just want
to make her life easier,
make
J. and Cam's life easier,
and make
my future child's life easier.
I don't even know
if it's a boy or a girl,
it bothers me a bit.
I know some
people are after me.
I have to find the right time
to use these idols.
I just want Val to win.
She deserves it more than me.
Damn it !
For me, nothing has
changed between us.
Alright, fine.
Joe and Wiglesworth
grow very close.
It's a kind
of brother/sister relationship,
aunt/nephew or whatever.
A relationship that seems to be developing
and that makes me a little nervous.
I trust Kimmi, you,
to Keith.
- But not to the three girls.
- Nope.
They share the arrogance
of finding themselves formidable.
Some want my exit
as much as yours.
You know.
I'm fed up with the way
the game is going.
There are very dangerous people.
And everyone is too shy
to act against them.
But my 2nd chance
is to have my own game,
and be able to say,
"Here are the moves I made."
So I want to build something
with the three witches.
Because they are at the bottom of the ladder
and ready to do anything to act.
I don't know
if we trust each other...
We don't trust each other,
that's normal.
Like... I don't know.
Clearly, I'm open to anything
at this stage of the game.
I could work with you,
but without telling you what to do.
To save themselves the loaves,
we will write everything you tell us.
So, who would be your big shot?
Everyone wants to take him out
if he loses.
It will eventually happen.
I do not know.
I think that...
Who are the other
powerful players?
She has connections with everyone.
She is nice to everyone.
– His social game is on top.
- And a strategy with everyone.
Except us.
I could vote Wigles.
Abi, Kelley Wentworth and I
are clearly at the bottom.
But Kelley Wentworth
unsheathed this idol
and blasts Savage.
Now
people are confused,
they come to us, want to talk.
And it's funny. "Where have you been for
the past 40 days?"
It's a complicated game.
It's really stupid to let
things happen. Really stupid.
It would really change the game.
I'm in.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the reward test?
- Yes !
First of all, Joe,
I'm getting it back again.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will be balancing
on triangular platforms,
in water,
feet perched
on very narrow points of support.
At regular intervals,
you will climb,
increasing the difficulty.
If you fall, it's lost.
The last person to hold
gain immunity
and ensures a one in ten chance
of winning this game.
The losers: on the board,
someone will become
the third member of the jury.
The last time
this event was contested,
it was in Survivor Cagayan.
Once again,
Spencer and Tasha took part.
Both lost.
Great 2nd chance opportunity.
We draw the seats
and we go in the water.
It's raining cats and dogs.
One more hurdle
in an already difficult ordeal.
Let everyone
be on the first level.
Let's go.
You can't touch
hands or buttocks.
If you fall, it's lost.
I leave you a few seconds
to find the balance,
then I will count.
Five, four,
three,
of them,
and,
this test is on.
Everyone is well settled.
It's still pouring rain.
This round will last ten minutes.
Then we will go up.
The difficulty will increase.
Keith, how are you?
I would like not to wear a 49.
It would definitely help me.
ELAPSED TIME:
8 Minutes
It seems to be going very well
for everyone.
You are living on the 24th day
of Survivor Second Chance.
The greatest adventure game
ever made.
A complicated game.
And your success in this game
usually depends on your ability
to make the right decision
at the right time.
I will give you a chance
to change your situation
in this game now.
But that will require
an instant decision.
The 1st person to touch their buoy
gain an advantage,
but renounces to win immunity.
Spencer dives.
Two people
are swimming towards their buoy.
Who will reach it first?
It's Fishbach!
An advantage in the game
for Fishbach.
Spencer fails.
It was tight.
This might be the
million dollar decision
that he had to take.
No one else
was tempted.
Fishbach, when did you decide:
"Something is going on,
- I'm interested."?
- Instantly.
Spencer, when
did you wonder
if you were going to jump or not?
Clearly,
a millisecond too late.
And now we're going all the way.
Only ten minutes left
in this first round.
Then we will go up.
One level.
Let's go.
Make the transition to the top.
The test does not stop.
You can use hands, buttocks
or whatever you want,
but if you fall, it's lost.
I will count.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and...
Wentworth falls,
unable to transition.
Jeremy is struggling, he falls.
Ciera falls.
Kimmi falls.
Tasha lutte,
she does not succeed.
Five people failed to
make the transition.
They are only four.
All retain a chance
of winning immunity.
This round will last 20 minutes.
Joe is the only one struggling
right now, but he's holding his own.
It's all that matters.
Abi looks like a statue.
- How are you feeling, Abi?
- Very good.
I could spend the day there.
We're halfway through this round.
The rain intensifies again.
It starts to agitate the water.
Joe moves a lot,
but he always recovers.
Wiglesworth looks
like a statue of Angkor Wat.
Abi is very calm.
Keith begins to waver.
Stay focused.
He loses his balance
with no chance of recovering.
They are only three.
Joe moves more,
but he is still there.
No need to do
things beautifully in Survivor.
ELAPSED TIME:
29 Minutes
Only 15 seconds left
in this round.
After that, we'll be
on one foot.
Abi has never been so close
individual immunity
this season.
The game does not pause
during the transition.
Not allowed to touch.
Here we are.
We walk on one foot.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and...
Wiglesworth, you gotta lift that foot!
Kelly, you're out.
It's too late.
Kelly took too long
to make the transition.
It's lost.
It all happens there.
No more time limit.
The last person up there
wins the necklace.
Nice recovery from Abi.
Joe is the only one to win
individual immunity this season.
Joe recovers well, again.
Abi is wavering now.
I have a foot cramp!
Fatigue sets in.
The cramps seize the muscles.
- Can she do it?
- Oh yes.
This is the heart of Survivor, right here.
It's the flood!
Balanced on one foot,
for immunity.
Joe struggles to hold on.
Abi holds one of his feet,
to reduce muscle tension.
Do not ! Abi tombs!
Joe wins
his third individual immunity!
Joe, come here!
Well done, Joe!
For the 3rd time in this game,
Joe, safe tonight at the council,
guaranteed to have a one in ten chance
of winning this game.
Another thing to settle.
You've landed an advantage,
here it is.
Thanks a lot !
You can open it privately.
Everyone else,
someone's leaving tonight.
Return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
It was awesome.
Jeff Probst said, "Stephen wins!"
It's not worth immunity,
but it's almost as good.
But, tonight,
this thing with Wiglesworth,
it's going to happen.
No matter how, it's gonna happen.
And maybe
I'll bust my advantage.
Well done, Joe!
No one can beat Joe.
He will win all immunities,
forever.
Joe won immunity, and that's fine with me,
because I need us to start
eliminating the witches.
I don't want them
to get too much power.
We have to separate these three girls.
We split the votes
or something like that.
We have eight votes.
We gotta do five Wentworth,
three Ciera,
and the three witches
will do what they want.
Council is approaching
and some in the grand covenant
are longing
to eliminate Wentworth or Ciera.
But we're going to split the votes.
So we want
Wentworth gone.
And Ciera is plan B.
Yeah. Guys vote Wentworth.
- How many guys do we have?
- Five.
- Five guys and three girls?
- Ah OK.
In this moment,
we want Wentworth gone.
She's really smart,
she's played an idol before.
She builds her resume.
She must go.
I won this mysterious perk
in today's immunity challenge.
Let's see...
"Your quick and risky decision
gives you the right
to steal a vote from the board."
It's amazing !
This is a decisive advantage.
It's incredible. This is...
It's beyond my wildest dreams.
"Wait your turn to vote
and then announce to Jeff
your wish to use the advantage.
You will then choose
who you want to steal their vote from.
This person will not vote,
and you will have a 2nd vote."
Let's bury that.
In Survivor White Collar,
Overalls, Colorless,
Dan had won the right
to vote for the council for a second time.
But being able to steal a vote
can overturn the entire power dynamic
of the game.
Unless I screw up,
I have the power of madness.
But I won't use it tonight.
I know I am safe.
It would be a waste.
For tonight,
being smart and sneaky will suffice.
But this could allow me
to win the game.
Wiglesworth, then.
Are you in?
If you think
others would.
I can definitely find...
At least one more person.
I'm 100% in.
If this surprise elimination works
and that Wiglesworth leaves,
is that new people
are ready to work with me.
I feel much more
confident in the game.
If it works.
I just hope I don't leave tonight.
We shake the coconut tree a little.
The girls want Wiglesworth.
If all three of us vote
Wiglesworth, she jumps.
Let's see what it would look like
if we did.
What would our situation be?
First, there would be six of us,
with the girls.
In very good position.
We cannot stay
at the bottom of the ladder.
Let's reverse the game.
Sort Wiglesworth
- will turn the game upside down.
- Are we really down?
We 3, here, we are not
the top of a tribe of 11.
I don't want to be allied
with the worst placed
and make me go out with them.
I want to build a group of votes.
We are talking about groups of votes,
which will change with each council.
I would love Wiglesworth to be
gone from the game now.
Most...
Basically, in your opinion,
the way to achieve this
is to rely on three people
who cannot be trusted.
Would I like to take
control of the game? Yes !
Can I achieve this in a way
that doesn't destroy my game?
No problems with economy,
calculation or statistics
never confused me as much
as this one.
Are you sure
that Wentworth, Ciera and Abi
- want out Wiglesworth?
- Yes.
- Are you sure they're in?
We all said we'd take out
one of the three witches.
So with Stephen, I hesitate.
He is fidgeting...
Everyone tries to play their own game.
I want us to be in agreement.
Stephen remains the one
I trust the most.
You ask me
to trust three girls
who don't want to
hear from me.
I ask you to
trust them momentarily.
It's a story of voting groups,
not alliances.
I try to lock my wedding ring
and manage these other...
groups of votes.
Looked ! It's going to rain again!
It seems like.
My problem
is, if we take out Wiglesworth,
four people on the camp
will have been taken by surprise.
Kimmi, Tasha,
I don't want to have to worry.
But I want to make
the right decision, do the right thing.
I just don't want to
switch sides too quickly.
Oh, this fire feels good!
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Savage,
eliminated at the last council.
You look frozen.
I'm.
It is really cold.
Even thinking clearly
becomes difficult.
Keith, it's a part of the game
that you kind of want,
because that makes it epic,
and at the same time, it affects you.
Yeah, for sure.
I must have slept 2 hours
in the last 36 hours.
We didn't eat anything.
It's hard to concentrate,
my thoughts are confused.
- It's real !
- We know !
Too real.
Wentworth, you received the majority
of votes at the last council.
Without your idol,
you'd be sitting there
and Savage would still be here.
Yes. I hope this shot
opened the eyes of some
and that people
are ready to act this time.
I don't know if this vote will be
as decided as some think.
Ciera, if the game is as smooth as
it seems,
to be at the bottom of a board
means absolutely nothing
for the following.
Absolutely anything can happen.
We saw Kelley release an idol,
it scared some people a little.
At this stage, it is:
"play or we will play you".
Joe, one hell of a statement.
"Play or you will be played."
Yes. If you think
someone is after you,
better to act first.
As Ciera says,
it's have or be had.
Jeremy.
Since it is a question of fluidity,
at the last vote,
nine people were together.
nine people,
it's a huge alliance,
and more than that,
this game revolves around
groups of votes.
Some are in one group,
some in another.
I'm still trying to sort this all out.
do you agree with Jeremy's analysis?
There are small factions
of people working together,
but temporarily?
Yeah.
However, that doesn't mean
we don't build trust.
nor that this confidence
evaporates at the time of the vote.
Spencer says it very clearly.
The votes, ultimately,
tell the truth.
Absolutely.
What do you hope to
see happen tonight?
I hope everyone will keep their word
and will play its part.
Are you confident?
Rather yes.
Fishbach, do you think
we are experiencing an evolution of the game?
No one has ever talked
about this kind of strategy.
I definitely think
the game is changing.
Alliances are not
as sharp and defined
than previously.
You have to give your word to people
while remaining flexible.
And they can be in return.
But yet, Jeff,
even with the voting groups,
you need
2 or 3 trusted people.
Because in the end,
the group of votes
with the strongest alliance
will dominate the game.
So who among you
is really worried
at the idea of ​​leaving
to the point of having the heart beating?
Abi, Tasha, Fishbach,
Spencer, half of the group
really cares!
Yes, and they have the courage
to admit it in front of their allies,
before those with whom
they have a relationship of trust.
Good. Someone is about
to leave.
It's time to vote.
Abi, over to you.
I'm voting for you,
because it's part of the plan.
Hoping it works.
Sorry, girl.
I really hope it will work.
There's only room
for one Kelley on this island.
I will count the votes.
This is the hottest moment of the evening!
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Ciera.
Wentworth.
Wiglesworth. Equality.
Two Wiglesworth votes,
two votes Ciera,
two votes Wentworth.
That's three Ciera votes.
Wiglesworth.
That's three Wiglesworth votes.
Four Wiglesworth votes,
three Ciera votes,
two Wentworth votes.
Ninth person eliminated
and third member of our jury...
Bring me your torch.
Kelly, the tribe has spoken.
In effect.
It's time to go.
This advice seems to confirm
that an evolution is happening
in the way you play Survivor.
I can't wait
to see where it takes us.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Try to warm up.
Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Relecture: Creature, flosm92
Synchro: Creature
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The rain is relentless...
I just need
a ray of hope.
People ask me
if Survivor is cool.
Survivor is not cool.
A cruise, that's cool.
...and imposes a decision
that could change the game.
Make up your mind,
reach out.
Let everyone reveal.
I was hoping not to leave so soon.
I know that I was eliminated,
because I am dangerous.
I thought
the 3 girls would vote for me.
For the other two votes,
I have my idea.
I hope it wasn't Joe.
It's a very different game
than last time.
It's not really my style.
So let them take advantage of it.