>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": WITH 11 PEOPLE STILL
IN THE GAME, EACH HAD THEIR OWN
AGENDA.
JEREMY WAS FINDING IDOLS.
>> TOOK ME TWO YEARS BUT NOW
I'VE GOT TWO IDOLS.
>> Jeff: CIERA WAS USING
VOTING BLOCKS TO STAY ALIVE.
>> ARE WE TALKING STRATEGY AT
ALL?
WE NEED TO MAKE A MOVE BEFORE
IT'S TOO LATE.
>> Jeff: AND STEPHEN WAS
TARGETING BIG THREATS.
>> I NEED JOE OUT.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE-- FIRST PERSON TO
TOUCH THEIR BUOY EARNS AN
ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME.
STEPHEN GAINED AN ADVANTAGE.
>> THIS IS BEYOND MY WILDEST
DREAMS.
>> Jeff: AND JOE CONTINUED TO
DOMINATE.
JOE WINS HIS THIRD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
BACK AT CAMP, CIERA, WENTWORTH,
AND ABY WERE ON THE BOTTOM.
>> WE'LL WRITE DOWN WHATEVER YOU
TELL US TO WRITE DOWN.
>> THIS IS A HUGE OPPORTUNITY TO
TRULY SHIFT THE GAME ON ITS HEAD
IS THERE BUT HE NEEDED JEREMY
AND SPENCER TO FURN ON THEIR
ALLIES.
>> PEOPLE ARE GOING TO COME BACK
TO CAMP BLINDSIDED.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL THE
GUYS FLIPPED.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT, THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
BLINDSIDING JOE AND HIS CLOSEST
ALLY.
KELLEY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> YES, THEY HAVE.
>> Jeff: WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT?
>> SO AT TRIBAL TONIGHT,
STEPHEN, SPENCER, AND MYSELF
BLINDSIDED KELLY WIGLESWORTH.
I STILL THINK WE COULD JUMP BACK
TO OUR POWER GROUP, OR WHATEVER
WE WANT TO CALL IT, AND TAKE OUT
ANOTHER ONE OF THE GIRLS.
MAYBE CIERA CAN GO.
>> EVERY VOTE, IF I CAN'T CLEAN
UP, THEY'RE GOING TO COME AFTER
ME NEXT.
I KNEW I WAS GOING TO HAVE TO
COME RIGHT BACK AND TALK TO
TASHA.
I KNEW SHE WAS GOING TO BE
UPSET.
>> WE COULDN'T TELL YOU.
WE COULDN'T TELL YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
>> SO THEY LEFT ME OUT OF THE
VOTE.
BUT IN THE VOTING BLOCK
SITUATION, IT'S LIKE ONCE YOU
HAVE THE NUMBERS FOR YOUR BLOCK,
YOU DON'T NEED ANYBODY ELSE.
THAT IS THE GAME THAT WE'RE
PLAYING.
>> YOU'RE STILL IN THE POWER.
ALL RIGHT?
>> YOU GET ONE OPPORTUNITY TO
LEAVE ME OUT OF THE LOOP.
THAT WAS THEIR ONE OPPORTUNITY.
THEY DON'T GET ANY MORE CHANCES.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT?
>> SHE-- SHE WAS JUST TOO MUCH.
SHE'S, LIKE, IN EVERYONE'S
BUSINESS ALL THE TIME.
>> YEAH... I'M PRETTY ( BLEEP )
PISSED RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M TRYING TO KEEP IT
TOGETHER AND NOT LOSE MY
( BLEEP ).
>> SO WHO ALL VOTED FOR
WIGLESWORTH?
>> US.
THREE GIRLS.
>> I VOTED CIERA.
NO WORRIES.
I'M STILL HERE SO I'M GLAD ABOUT
THAT.
AND I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
>> LET'S JUST NOT LET THOSE
GIRLS GET--
>> NO, COME ON.
NO WAY.
>> WE ALL KNOW WHERE THEY'RE AT.
>> ONE OF MY BIGGEST ALLIES IN
THE GAME WENT HOME, SO ALL THE
MORE REASON FOR ME TO WIN THE
NEXT IMMUNITY.
BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE COMING FOR
ME.
>> THIS SUCKS.
>> I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT IT
WOULD BE LIKE THIS WITHOUT A
BREAK.
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN A PRETTY
DECENT SPOT RIGHT NOW IN THE
GAME.
YOU KNOW, I WAS ON THE BOTTOM
WITH WENTWORTH AND ABI AND
SLOWLY I STARTED TO CREEP MY WAY
UP A LITTLE BIT AND HOPEFULLY I
CAN KEEP THE MOMENTUM.
THIS RAIN IS A BITCH.
WE'RE ALL STUCK INSIDE THE
SHELTER.
THAT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
>> SEE I TOLD YOU, FIRST IT WAS
THUNDER AND THEN COMES
LIGHTNING.
>> CAN WE EAT DRY RICE?
>> I'M ABOUT TO.
>> THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT FOOD
AND COLD AND ALL THAT, BUT I'M
HERE TO WIN A MILLION DOLLARS
CUT AND DRIED.
I AIN'T STARVING TO DEATH.
I'LL MAKE IT.
THIS IS DAY 25.
LET'S SEE, 35.
YEAH, I'M TWO WEEKS OUT.
I'LL SIT HERE FOR 50 DAYS FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS.
I MEAN, DANG.
WHEN DO YOU GET A SECOND CHANCE
FOR SOMETHING CRAZY LIKE THIS?
( LAUGHS )
DANG.
THAT LOOKS BAD.
I FEEL LIKE ANY MINUTE I COULD
LOSE A TOE.
PEOPLE ASK ME IF "SURVIVOR" IS
FUN.
I TELL THEM, HELL NO.
IT AIN'T FUN.
GOING ON A CRUISE IS FUN.
GOING FISHING IT FUN.
GOING TO PLAY GOLF IS FUN.
THIS AIN'T FUN.
LOOK AT ME.
GOLLY!
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: TASH, TELL ME WHERE
THIS GROUP OF PEOPLE, THESE
HUMANS ARE AT EMOTIONALLY?
>> WE'RE EXHAUSTED.
THE WEATHER DEFINITELY TAKES THE
ENERGY OUT OF YOU.
IT'S CRAZY THE LEVEL OF EFFORT
THAT EACH OF US ARE PUTTING INTO
THIS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND YET, CIERA, YOU
CAN'T REALLY KNOW WHAT A HIGH IS
IF THERE'S NOT A LOW TO COMPARE
IT TO.
THAT'S WHERE YOU GET THE
MEANING.
>> I THINK WHEN WE HAVE A
LITTLE, SWEET MOMENT, NO RAIN
FOR 10 MINUTES, IS SO AWESOME,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE THESE LOWS ARE
SO LOW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S
FLIP IT TODAY AND LET ME TELL
YOU WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
FIRST, AND YOU CAN TELL ME
HONESTLY IF YOU THINK IT'S WORTH
IT.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, WE'RE
GOING TO DIVIDE INTO TWO TEAMS
OF 5. WINNING FIVE WILL BE TAKEN
AWAY FROM THIS.
>> OH!
UWILL HAVE A ROOF OVER YOUR HEAD
YOU'RE ALREADY IN.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BE WARM,
BLANKETS TO WRAP AROUND.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: ALL KINDS OF FOOD.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: AND IN ADDITION, THE
BACKCROP WILL BE A CAMBODIAN
CIRCUS.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: FOR THE FIVE WHO
DON'T WIN, BACK TO CAMP, MORE
RAIN, MISERABLE SHELTER.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S HOW THE
CHALLENGE IS GOING TO WORK.
THREE PEOPLE FROM EACH TEAM WILL
BATTLE FOR A BALL.
YOU'LL THEN WORK TOGETHER TO GET
THAT BALL INTO A BASKET WHILE
THE OTHER TEAM IS TRYING TO STOP
YOU ANY WAY THEY CAN.
EVERY TIME YOU GET A BALL IN THE
BASKET AND SCORE A POINT, FIRST
TO THREE WINS REWARD.
LET'S DO IT.
>> LET'S DO IT!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE
OUR TWO TEAMS FROM OUR SCHOOL
YARD PICK.
IT IS WENTWORTH, KIMMI, FISH
BACK, JEREMY AND KEITH.
TAKING ON TASHA, ABI, JOE,
CIERA, AND SPENCER.
WE FIRST RAN THIS CHALLENGE BACK
IN SEASON 18 "SURVIVOR TOKEN
KEYNES, FISH BACK WAS THERE AND
HIS TRIBE SCORED THE WINNING
BASKET.
FIRST ROUND WILL BE TWO MEN, ONE
WOMAN.
JOE, SPENCER, AND CIERA FOR
PURPLE.
FOR GREEN IT'S GOING TO BE
EMY, FIS FISHBACH AND WENTWORTH.
IT WILL BE FIRST TO THREE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
WE'RE ON!
GO!
JEREMY AND JOE BATTLING.
JOE HAS IT.
>> LET'S GO, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: OVER TO SPENCER.
CAN HE DO IT?
NO, MISSES.
JEREMY NOWS THAT.
FISHBACH WITH A BIG TAKEDOWN OF
JOE.
JEREMY SCORES FIRST POINT!
GREEN LEADS ONE-ZIP.
THIS ROUND IS TWO WOMEN AND ONE
MAN.
FOR GREEN IT'S GOING TO BE
KIMMI, KEITH, AND WENTWORTH BACK
IN, TAKING ON TASHA, ABI, AND
JOE BACK IN.
GREEN LEADS ONE-ZIP.
WE'RE PLAYING TO THREE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
KIMMI AND TASHA BATTLING FOR IT.
KEITH KNOCKS IT DOWN.
WENTWORTHS THAT.
JOE'S GOING TO TAKE DOWN WEPT
WORTH.
>> KILL HIM!
LOCK HIM UP IN YOUR ARMS!
>> Jeff: JOE TOSSES KIMMI TO
THE GROUND.
KEITH TRYING TO GET FREE.
>> KEITH, YOU GOTTA FIGHT FOR
THAT!
>> Jeff: KIMMI HAS BEEN
HOLDING JOE DOWN.
JOE NOW HAS IT.
JOE MOVING AROUND EVERYBODY.
DRAGGING WENTWORTH.
PUSHES KIMMI DOWN.
>> COME ON!
JOE TO TIE IT UP.
YES!
>> YEAH!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: PURPLE SCORES.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
IT'S OVER.
NEXT ROUND, IT IS JEREMY, KIMMI,
AND FISHBACH TAKING ON JOE,
CIERA, AND SPENCER.
WE'RE TIED 1-1.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
JEREMY AND SPENCER GO DOWN HARD.
BIG BATTLE.
>> GET HIM!
GET HIM!
>> Jeff: JEREMY SPRINTING AWAY
FROM EVERYBODY!
JOE TAKES HIM DOWN.
BALL IS LOSE NOW.
FISHBACH HAS IT.
RAIN STARTING TO COME DOWN
HARDER.
JEREMY WITH A LONG SHOT, CAN'T
DO IT.
SPENCER HAS IT, HE'S A
BREAKAWAY!
SPENCER SCORES, PURPLE TAKES THE
LEAD, 2-1!
NEXT MATCH-UP, IT IS JOE BACK IN
AGAIN WITH ABI AND TASHA TAKING
ON JEREMY, WENTWORTH, AND KIMMI.
PURPLE LEADS 2-1, CAN WIN IT
RIGHT HERE, PLAYING TO THREE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
TASHA HAS THE BALL.
IT'S LOOSE.
JOE AND JEREMY TAKE EACH OTHER
DOWN.
NOW IT'S THE WOMEN BATTLING FOR
THE BALL AS BOTH GUYS ARE OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> KIMMI, KILL HER!
>>
>> GOOD JOB, ABI!
>> Jeff: TASHA NOW HAS KIMMI
DOWN TRYING TO GET THAT BALL.
ABI NOW TAKES WEPT WORTH DOWN.
ABI AND WENTWORTH GOING AT IT.
ABI IS NOT LAYING OFF OF
WENTWORTH, OPENING THE DOOR FOR
TASHA TO TAKE THAT BALL.
TASHA HAS THE BALL.
BUT SHE'S ALSO GOT KIMMI, RAIN
POURING DOWN.
>> KIM, HOLD ON FOR DEAR LIFE
FOR EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: KIMMI AND TASHA
BATTLING FOR IT.
TASHA DRAGGING KIMMI.
THERE IT IS.
SHE'S FREE!
PURPLE WINS REWARD!
HUGE EFFORT BY EVERYBODY!
25 DAYS INTO THIS GAME.
>> AWESOME JOB!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WIG WIN
FOR JOE, TASHA, CIERA, ABI, AND
SPENCER.
GET YOU OUT OF THE WATT, YOU CAN
START GETTING WARM NOW.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: HEAD OUT.
GET WARM.
I WISH I HAD SOMETHING TO MAKE
IT BETTER BUT I DON'T.
I GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, TRY TO STAY
DRY.
>> TO BE ABLE TO WIN A REWARD
AND TAKE, YOU KNOW, AN AFTERNOON
TO GET DRY FOR A LITTLE BIT,
HAVE CONVERSATIONS WITH PEOPLE
OUTSIDE OF THE SHELTER.
IT'S A HUGE ADVANTAGE.
>> WOOO!
>> WINNING, JUST STICK IT TO
THEM.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> HAVING BEEN WET FOR TWO DAYS
STRAIGHT, GOING ON A REWARD HAS
NEVER BEEN MORE IMPORTANT.
AND GET ALL THIS CAMBODIAN
CULTURE THAT I'VE NEVER
EXPERIENCED, AND THE OPPORTUNITY
TO FORM THE BONDS YOU NEED TO
MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
WHOOO!
IT MIGHT THE BE IMMUNITY BUT IT
FEELS AS IMPORTANT AS IMMUNITY.
>> YEAH!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THAT LITTLE BOY IS IS, LIKE
THE EXACT SIZE OF MINE.
>> YOUR LITTLE SON IS THAT
LITTLE?
>> A LITTLE BIT BIGGER.
>> OH, MY GOSH, SO CUTE.
>> THE COOLEST THING FOR ME IS
TO BE ABLE TO SEE ALL THE
FAMILIES AND ALL THE KIDS WATCH
THIS PERFORMANCE.
IT DEFINITELY MADE ME MISS MY
HOME MORE THAN EVER.
>> HOW YOU DOING, GIRL?
>> IT'S JUST SEEING ALL THESE
KIDS, AND IT JUST MAKES ME MISS
MY BABIES.
I'M REALLY, REALLY, REALLY
STARTING TO MISS MY KIDS AND MY
HUSBAND, AND I THINK IT JUST PUT
INTO PERSPECTIVE FOR ME THEY'RE
FINE, AND THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
AND THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO KEEP
TRUCKING ALONG FOR THEM.
ALMOST DONE, RIGHT?
>> ALMOST DONE.
>> ALMOST THERE.
>> SO I NEED TO TAKE ANY
ADVANTAGE I CAN GET.
THIS GAME IS CONSTANTLY CHANGING
SO THIS REWARD IS THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO BE ABLE TO SAY
SAYILY," LET'S MAKE A PLAN."
RIGHT NOW THERE ARE 10 OF US AND
WE ONLY NEED SIX.
WHY DO WE NEED JEREMY, STEPHEN,
OR KIMMI.
>> STEPHEN'S ADVANTAGE IS SCARY.
>> THAT'S WHY HE NEEDS TO BE
TOTALLY BLINDSIDED.
>> STEPHEN IS A HUGE THREAT, AND
HE JUST GOT THIS ADVANTAGE.
EVEN MORE OF A REASON TO
BLINDSIDE HIM AND GET HIM OUT OF
HERE.
>> I THINK STEPHEN IS THE MOST
DANGEROUS PLAYER IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW.
>> LET'S GET RID OF STEPHEN.
>> DONE.
CIERA PITCHED THIS IDEA THAT US
FIVE AT THE REWARD SHOULD
BLINDSIDE STEPHEN.
I'VE WANTED STEPHEN OUT FOR A
WHILE.
IT SOUNDS LOOK A GOOD PLAN, BUT
I CAN'T BANK ON THEM, ESPECIALLY
WHEN I KNOW THEY WANT ME OUT OF
THIS GAME.
>> WE'VE JUST GOT TO PUSH
THROUGH.
THIS SUCTION, BUT JUST PUSH
>> I KNOW.
MY SON WAS IN THE HOSPITAL FOR
49 DAYS, AND I SAT THERE THROUGH
THAT.
>> THAT IS WORSE THAN THIS.
>> THAT WAS 1,000 TIMES WORSE
THAN THIS.
MY OLDEST SON HAS KIDNEY DISEASE
AND WHEN YOU SIT AND PUT THINGS
IN PERSPECTIVE, IF HE CAN DO
THAT, THEN I CAN CERTAINLY
ENDURE THESE ELEMENTS OF
"SURVIVOR," BECAUSE ALL MY
STRENGTH FOR BEING OUT HERE
COMES FROM MY BOYS.
>> IS THAT YOUR SHIRT?
>> JOE'S.
>> I THOUGHT OF PUTTING IT ON,
TOO.
SO, GOOD.
>> THE HELL WITH JOE.
I'M STAYING WARM.
>> IT WAS TOUGH TODAY BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, KEITH IS FIGHTING TWO
PEOPLE AT ONCE.
AND THEN JOE IS JUST PUSHING TWO
GIRLS DOWN.
>> WE TRIED!
WE TRIED.
>> HE'S THE BIGGEST GUY OUT HERE
BY A MILE.
YOU'D BE WINNING ALL THESE
REWARDS, JEREMY, IF HE WASN'T IN
THE GAME.
>> JOE IS A BIG THREAT.
>> IT WOULDN'T BOTHER ME A BIT
IF JOE GOES.
HE'S GOOD AT CHALLENGES.
HE'S WINNING EVERYTHING OUT
HERE.
THAT'S KNOT TO STOP.
EITHER BY ME, JEREMY, SPENCER,
SOMEBODY, GIVE OF REST OF THE
LOW PACK A CHANCE OR SOMETHING.
>> EVERYONE WANTS JOE GONE.
>> HONESTLY, THE THING IS WITH
JOE, HE MADE HIS OWN BED.
LIKE, YOU CAN'T KEEP WINNING
IMMUNITIES LIKE THAT.
LET'S JUST GET JOE OUT OF HERE.
THIS IS GREAT BECAUSE FOR SO
MANY DAYS IN THIS GAME, I'VE
JUST FELT, LIKE, ON THE BOTTOM,
BUT I FEEL LIKE THESE VOTING
BLOCKS DEFINITELY OPENED UP A
LOT OF DOORS FOR CIERA, ABI, AND
MYSELF.
>> HE'S PLAYING EVERY SIDE,
UNDERSIDE, INSIDE, OUTSIDE.
>> HE'S PLAYING EVERY PERSON BUT
IN A REALLY ARROGANT WAY.
>> YES.
FINALLY WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME
PAGE.
EVERYONE KNOWS HOW IMPORTANT IT
IS THAT JOE DOESN'T WIN
IMMUNITY.
>> I'M READY FOR HIM TO GO.
>> IT'S TIME.
>> I'M READY.
>> HE'S HAD HIS STORY.
I'M LITERALLY SHIVERING.
IT IS FREEZING OUT HERE.
IT'S MISERABLE.
BUT I THINK I'VE GOT MY FINGERS
IN BASICALLY EVERY POT RIGHT
NOW, AND ESPECIALLY WINNING THAT
GAME ADVANTAGE, I THINK I'M IN A
REALLY GREAT POSITION RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, NEVER SAY THAT ON
"SURVIVOR" THAT YOU'RE IN A
GREAT POSITION BECAUSE THAT'S--
THAT'S THE DEATH KNELL.
THAT'S WHEN YOU GO HOME.
BUT I THINK MOVING FORWARD I
HAVE A LOT OF ROOM TO MANEUVER
IN THIS GAME.
( THUNDER )
>> IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
FREEZING CODE RAIN, WE'VE BEEN
WET FOR DAYS, I HAVEN'T EATEN
FOR DAYS, AND SUDDENLY I START
HAVING TERRIBLE STOMACH ISSUES
AND IT TAKES ME OUT OF THE
SHELTER IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
MONSOON OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
>> POOR GUY.
>> EVERYONE IS MISERABLE.
YOU KNOW, EVERYONE IS AT THEIR
LOW, BUT I'M SCARED THAT MY BODY
IS BREAKING DOWN.
I CAN'T GO ON LIKE THIS.
LITERALLY, I JUST CAN'T.
LIKE, EVEN THOUGH YOUR BODY
CAN'T, STILL HAVE TO SAY, "YES,
YES I CAN" YOU KNOW, "YES I
WILL."
I'M JUST EXHAUSTED.
THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS I'VE
BEEN DOWN, I'VE BEEN DOWN AND
DOWN.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN IT WILL END.
>> THE RAIN HAS BEEN GOING FOR
DAYS.
MY STOMACH IS REALLY SUFFERING.
EVERY PART OF ME IS JUST, LIKE,
GIVEN UP.
I JUST NEED SOME, LIKE, SOME,
LIKE, RAY OF HOPE YOU KNOW.
JUST, LIKE, THE SUN TO COME OUT
FOR 15 MINUTES OR SOMETHING.
( THUNDER )
I'M NOT QUITTING.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M QUITTING.
I GOTTA GO AGAIN.
I JUST WENT 30 SECONDS AGO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
>> STEPHEN DOES NOT LOOK GOOD.
I FEEL BAD FOR HIM.
HIS STOMACH IS MESSED UP, AND
HIS FEET ARE SWOLLEN.
HE LOOKS SO BAD.
I'M HOPING HE'S OKAY BECAUSE I
NEED SOME LOYALTY AROUND ME, AND
STEPHEN IS AN HONEST GUY.
>> WHAT'S UP.
YOUR FOOT?
WHY ARE YOU LIMPING AROUND.
>> I'M JUST A MESS.
>> I LOVE "SURVIVOR," BUT IT'S A
TOUGH GAME.
EVERY DAY, IT'S TOUGH.
WE'RE FREEZING.
THE WIND IS COLD.
AND THE SHELTER IS HORRIBLE.
IT DOESN'T HOLD UP AGAINST THE
ELEMENTS OUT HERE PUP CAN'T EVER
GET WARM, SO WE'RE JUST HUDDLED
UP TOGETHER.
IT SUCTION.
WE NEED SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
IF WE CAN GET WARM AND GET
EVERYTHING DRY FOR ONE DAY,
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BEFORE WE
GET TO THE CHALLENGE, I WANT
EACH OF YOU TO TAKE ONE BLACK
ROCK, ONE WHITE ROCK.
TAKE ONE OF EACH.
YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD, KEITH.
>> I'M JUST WONDERING WHAT WE
GOT UP NEXT.
>> WHEN JEFF GAVE US THE WHITE
AND BLACK ROCK, OUR HEADS WERE
ALL SPINNING.
WHAT COULD THIS BE?
JEFF HAD SOMETHING UP HIS
SLEEVES.
>> Jeff: WE'LL GET TO THE
STONES LATER.
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JOE, GOTTA TAKE IT BACK AGAIN.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE ON ONE FOOT ON
A SMALL BLOCK WHILE BALANCING A
BALL AGAINST AN OVERHANGING
PIECE OF WOOD.
IF AT ANY POINT THE BALL DROPS,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A
ONE-IN-NINE SHOT AT WINNING THIS
GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE FOURTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WE'VE DONE THIS CHALLENGE ONE
TIME.
KEITH'S SEASON.
KEITH PARTICIPATED AND DID NOT
WIN.
AND THE GOOD NEWS IS FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN A FEW DAYS, WE
HAVE CLEAR WEATHER.
FISHBACH, HOW BAD HAS IT BEEN?
>> IT'S BEEN TERRIBLE.
WE HAVEN'T EATEN IN DAYS.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN DRY IN DAYS.
AND I ACTUALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE NIGHT LAST NIGHT HAD SEVERE
GASTRO INTESTINAL DISTRESS-- YOU
CAN HASHTAG THAT.
IT FELT LIKE I WAS GOING FROM A
"SURVIVOR" LOW TO A PERSONAL
LIFE LOW.
>> Jeff: YOU GUY STILL HAVE
HALF A MONTH TO GO OUT HERE.
>> THANK GOD.
>> Jeff: I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
THE OPPORTUNITY TO GREATLY
IMPROVE YOUR SHELTER. NOT WHAT
YOU WERE EXPECTING, IS IT?
>> NOPE.
>> Jeff: RIGHT NOW, A
CONSTRUCTION CREW IS AT YOUR
CAMP.
THEY ARE READY TO REDO YOUR
SHELTER.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: WE WILL WATERPROOF
THE ROOF.
WE WILL GET YOUR FIRE GOING IN
THE CENTER.
IT WILL BE COVERED.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM US?
>> Jeff: I WANT FIVE PEOPLE TO
GIVE UP THEIR SHOT AT IMMUNITY
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WE HAVE A DILEMMA BETWEEN I
AND WE.
THIS DECISION COULD EASILY BITE
YOU IN THE ASS, WHICHEVER WAY
YOU GO.
>> Jeff: WHITE ROCK MEANS I AM
WILLING TO SURRENDER MY SHOT IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
I WILL GIVE UP FOR THE BETTER OF
THE GROUP.
THE BLACK ROCK MEANS CAN'T DO
IT.
I'M COMPETING.
I WANT IMMUNITY.
SO THIS REALLY COMES DOWN TO
TRUST BECAUSE IF YOU COULD ALL
TRUST EACH OTHER, THIS IS EASY.
FIVE PEOPLE DO IT, IMPROVE YOUR
SHELTER.
DONE.
BUT THIS IS A GAME FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> SURVIVING IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY, BUT MY
MIND IS JUST RACING WITH ALL
THESE QUESTIONS.
WHO I DO THINK IS GOING TO GIVE
UP ONE FOR THE TEAM AND WHO DO I
THINK IS GOING TO COMPETE IN THE
CHALLENGE?
>> Jeff: MAKE YOUR DECISION.
PUT YOUR PALM OUT.
WHITE MEANS I'M GIVING UP.
I'M LOOKING FOR FIVE WHITES.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
EVERYBODY WILLING TO GIVE UP
THEIR SHOT EXCEPT FOR JOE AND
KEITH.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: SPENCER, FISHBACH,
JEREMY, KIMMI, WENTWORTH, CIERA,
ABI, AND TASHA, ALL SAID I WILL
GIVE UP MY SHOT AT SECURITY IN A
MILLION-DOLLAR GAME WITH ONLY 10
PEOPLE LEFT.
GOOD NEWS IS, WHEN YOU GO BACK
TO CAMP, YOU WILL HAVE A BIG
SHELTER.
THE MORE INTERESTING NEWS, TWO
PEOPLE SAID NOT DOING IT.
JOE AND KEITH.
KEITH, DID YOU DEBATE THIS OR
WAS IT EASY?
>> I'M A COMPETITOR, AND I
WANTED TO PLAY.
I KIND OF FIGURED JOE WAS IN
THERE.
I WANT TO WIN THAT NECKLACE
RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: JOE, DID YOU CONSIDER
IT?
>> I TOTALLY CONSIDERED IT.
I WAS BACK AND FORTH, BACK AND
FORTH, AND FOR A SPLIT SECOND I
SAID YOU KNOW WHAT, I THINK THE
RAIN AFFECTS MORE PEOPLE HERE,
LIKE ME, PERSONALLY, I CAN SUCK
IT UP.
>> Jeff: BIG DECISION IN A BIG
GAME OF "SURVIVOR: SECOND
CHANCE."
THOSE OF YOU WHO SURRENDERED,
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
JOE AND KEITH, TAKE YOUR SPOTS,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EIGHT PEOPLE GAVE UP
THEIR SHOT AT IMMUNITY TO
IMPROVE THE SHELTER.
JOE AND KEITH ARE GOING TO
BATTLE IT OUT FOR IMMUNITY.
YOU HAVE ONE FOOT ON THE BLOCK.
YOU'RE BALANCING THE BALL IN
BETWEEN YOUR BOWIE AND THE
OVERHANGING PIECE OF WOOD.
JOE LOOKS GOOD.
KEITH LOOKS GOOD.
THIS CHALLENGE FOR IMMUNITY IS
ON.
KEITH HAS DONE THIS CHALLENGE.
HE ACTUALLY MADE IT FAIRLY DEEP.
DIDN'T WIN.
JOE, ON THE OTHER HAND, HAS NOT
LOST AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
HE IS THREE FOR THREE.
NOBODY HAS FELT THAT NECKLACE
OTHER THAN JOE.
YOU BOTH MADE BIG DECISIONS WHEN
YOU DECIDED TO COMPETE.
YOU WANT TO MAKE IT WORTH IT.
THE ONLY WAY TO DO THAT IS TO
WIN.
IT DOESN'T TAKE LONG FOR THE
FATIGUE TO START TO SET IN.
THE QUESTION IS WHO CAN STAND
THEM THE LONGEST?
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE EVERYTHING
YOU TWO HAVE TO OUTLAST THE
OTHER.
JOE WITH A LITTLE BIT OF
MOVEMENT.
WHEN YOU'RE AS TIRED AS YOU GUYS
ARE, IT'S SO EASY TO HAVE A
LAPSE IN YOUR CONCENTRATION.
>> JOE IS SLIPPING.
>> Jeff: KEITH WITH A TINY BIT
OF MOVEMENT.
KEITH DROPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
JOE WINS HIS FOURTH INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, REMAINS UNDEFEATED.
NO SECOND CHANCE REDEMPTION FOR
KEITH.
JOE, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
FOR THE FOURTH TIME IN THIS GAME
THE ONLY PERSON TO WIN
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN,
JOE, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
GOING HOME.
WILL IT BE ONE OF THE EIGHT OF
YOU WHO VOLUNTARILY GAVE UP YOUR
SHOT AT IMMUNITY?
ONE THING WE KNOW FOR SURE-- IT
WON'T BE YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> OF COURSE, JOEY AMAZING, WINS
ANOTHER IMMUNITY.
AT LEAST NOW, HAVING THE
SHELTER, BEING DRY, SUDDENLY WE
CAN NOW PLAY AGAIN.
AND MY THOUGHT RIGHT NOW IS
MAKES THE MOST SENSE TO TAKE OUT
CIERA.
SHE'S SO FIXATED ON AGGRESSIVE
GAME PLAY BECAUSE SHE KNOWS
SHE'S IN TROUBLE WHICH IS
TERRIFYING.
>> WHEN WE CAME BACK TO CAMP AND
WE SAW THE SHELTER BUILT, THE
FIRE GOING, IT WAS JUST SUCH AN
AMAZING FEELING.
IT WAS JUST LIKE, WOW.
I CAN ENDURE ANOTHER 13 DAYS, NO
PROBLEM.
>> THIS IS AMAZING!
>> BEST SHELTER EVER.
>> YOU GUYS, LOOK AT THIS
SHELTER.
>> I KNOW.
>> THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> WE WILL BE WARM.
>> THIS WENT FROM ONE OF THE
LOWEST POINTS OF ALL OF OUR
LIVES TO THE MOST INCREDIBLE
SHELTER, BUT WHEN YOU GIVE UP
POTENTIALLY YOUR LIFE IN THE
GAME, IT'S LIKE YOU'RE SELLING
YOUR SOUL TO THE DEVIL.
>> ALL I WAS TRYING TO DO WAS
TAKE DOWN THE GOLDEN BOY.
>> IF KEITH IS SAFE, SOMEONE WHO
SACRIFICED IMMUNITY FOR SHELTER
AND TEA AND COFFEE, WILL ENJOY
NONE OF THOSE THINGS AND WILL BE
HEADED TO THE JURY.
WHO'S NEXT.
>> ONE OF GIRLS.
>> HERE'S WHAT I'M THINKING.
IF WE TAKE OUT CIERA NOW--
>> YOU WANT TO DO CIERA TODAY.
>> YEAH.
CIERA IS NEXT TO GO BECAUSE
SHE'S TOO DANGEROUS.
HER SWEETNESS, YOU NEVER THINK
WITH HER THAT SHE'S SO DEVIOUS,
BUT CIERA IS SOMEONE WHO IS
WILLING TO MAKE BIG MOVES,
ADVANCE HER CAUSE IN THE GAME.
I THINK GETTING RID OF HER, I
THINK I WOULD WORK WITH
WENTWORTH.
I EVEN THINK ABI I WOULD WORK
WITH.
I ALSO HAVE AN ADVANTAGE.
I WILL NEED THAT LATER IN THE
GAME AND I DON'T WANT TO WASTE
IT TOO EARLY.
>> SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> THE GUY WHO IS LIMPING AROUND
WITH AN ADVANTAGE IN HIS POCKET.
>> PROMISE?
>> PROMISE.
IT'S STEPHEN, STEPHEN, STEPHEN,
STEPHEN, STEPHEN.
>> POOPY PANTS?
>> WHAT.
>> POOPY PANTS.
>> STEPHEN.
>> I KNOW.
POOPY PANTS.
>> AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME,
I'M JUST HOPING THAT THE PLANS I
SET IN MOTION TO BLINDSIDE
STEVEN AND GET RID OF THAT
ADVANTAGE PLAY OUT.
AND I THINK THAT PEOPLE WOULD BE
SILLY NOT TO TAKE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO FLUSH STEPHEN OUT
OF THE GAME AND FLUSH THAT
ADVANTAGE.
BUT IN CASE HE PLAYS AN
ADVANTAGE ME AND WENTWORTH ARE
GOING TO WRITE DOWN KIMMI, AND
EVERYBODY ELSE WRITE DOWN
FISHBACH.
>> HEY, I WANTED TO SEE WHERE
YOU WERE.
LIKE, IF WE GO WITH THE GIRLS,
LIKE, IT'S THE CIERA SHOW, AND
EVERY MOVE THAT SHE'S HERE
THAT'S MADE IS ON HER RESUME.
LIKE, ALL SHE DID WAS THROW OUT
SPENCER-- THROW OUT STEPHEN'S
NAME YESTERDAY, DISPFS LIKE,
BOOM, DONE.
LIKE THE GODFATHER.
THIS ONE'S NEXT.
THE THING THAT CIERA HAS DONE SO
SUCCESSFULLY IS SHE'S BASICALLY
UNHINGED SEVERAL GROUPS.
AND MY QUESTION IS WHY ISN'T
ANYONE TAKING CIERA OUT TO FREE
UP HER PEOPLE WHICH WOULD BE
WENTWORTH AND ABI?
IF WE UNHINGE CIERA'S CREW,
THEY'RE UP FOR GRABS.
>> YEAH, TOTALLY.
CIERA STILL SITS THERE AS AN
EASY VOTE, BUT FOR ME, I FEEL
LIKE IT'S IN MY BEST INTEREST TO
GET STEPHEN GONE AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE.
NOW IT'S JUST A MATTER OF
CONVINCING ENOUGH PEOPLE TO MAKE
THE RIGHT MOVE.
I DON'T BELIEVE ANYTHING THE
GIRLS SAY, BUT THEY WANT ME,
TASH, HIM, AND KEITH TO VOTE
STEPHEN.
>> OH, WE'RE DOING STEPHEN?
>> THAT'S WHAT THE GIRLS JUST
MADE US COMMIT TO STEPHEN.
>> YES.
>> OUR FIRST THING WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE CIERA.
>> WHATEVER WE DECIDE WE HAVE TO
DO, WE'RE TOGETHER NOW.
THIS IS IT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THERE'S NO OTHER--
>> ARE WE SURE THAT'S WHAT THE
GIRLS ARE DOING.
>> RIGHT.
>> THEY'VE REITERATED THAT
SEVERAL TIMES.
>> IT'S WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
>> I FEEL LIKE CIERA IS THE
BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, SHE IS.
>> THE ADVANTAGE DOES SCARE ME,
THOUGH.
MY HEAD IS IN TWO PLACES.
I REALLY WANT CIERA GONE
TONIGHT, AND I REALLY WANT
STEPHEN GONE TONIGHT.
I THINK CIERA, I KNOW SHE'S A
LIAR.
I KNOW SHE'S PLAYING EVERYBODY,
WHILE I THINK STEVE SEN JUST A
BIGGER THREAT IN THE FACT THAT
HE HAS AN ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME
WHICH NO ONE KNOWS WHAT IT IS.
>> WHY DON'T WE ALL VOTE FOR
STEPHEN?
>> WE ALL VOTE STEPHEN.
>> HE'S NOT PULLING ANYTHING
OUT.
AS LONG AS IT'S A BLINDSIDE, WE
ALL VOTE STEPHEN.
>> IT'S A BAD MOVE.
SOME PEOPLE SAYING MAYBE THEY
WANT TO VOTE STEPHEN OUT BECAUSE
OF HIS ADVANTAGE.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE THAT'S A GREAT
IDEA RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TWO IDOLS.
BUT I NEED STEPHEN.
STEPHEN AT LEAST HAS MY BACK.
I WANT STEVE TONE STAY.
STEPHEN TRUSTS ME.
CIERA HAS NO LOYALTY TO ANYBODY.
SHE'S A FREE AGENT.
SHE'LL FLOAT ANYWHERE JUST TO
KEEP GOING.
>> OKAY.
>> STEPHEN WILL STAY WITH US.
>> IF STEPHEN HAS THE ABILITY TO
MAKE A MOVE, HE WILL.
AND THAT ADVANTAGE MIGHT GIVE
HIM THE ABILITY TO MAKE A MOVE.
SO JEREMY IS ADAMANT.
IT'S GOT TO BE CIERA.
IT'S A MISTAKE TO GET RID OF
STEPHEN.
I WILL NOT FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
STEVE NEN THIS GAME.
STEPHEN WHO HAS AN ADVANTAGE.
STEPHEN WHO IS CLOSER WITH KIMMI
THAN ANY TWO OTHER PEOPLE IN THE
GAME, WHO COULD EASILY FLIP ON
US, MOREACY EASLEY THAN CIERA.
>> YOU'RE GIVING HER SO MUCH
TRACTION.
WE'VE GOT TO WRAP THIS UP,
THOUGH.
>> THIS IS A REALLY CLOSE
DECISION, MAYBE THE MOST
IMPORTANT DECISION OF THE GAME.
BUT WHEN BOTH OF US ARE 100%
CONVINCED THAT THE OTHER IS
WRONG, ME THAT STEPHEN MUST GO,
AND JEREMY THAT CIERA MUST GO,
SOMETHING HAS TO GIVE.
SOMETHING HAS TO BREAK.
I HOPE STEPHEN'S GOING HOME.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IS GOING
TO HAPPEN AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
KASS, SAVAGE, AND WIGLESWORTH,
VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT THE WEATHER.
IT HAS BEEN ALMOST NONSTOP RAIN
FOR THE PAST SELF DAYS.
WENTWORTH, AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE, YOU WERE CROUCHED IN
THE WATER ALMOST LIKE YOU WERE
READY TO JUST GO AHEAD AND SINK
UNDER AND DROWN YOURSELF.
>> IT WAS WARMER TO BE SITTING
IN THE WATER THAN TO BE STANDING
UP WITH THE RAIN COMING DOWN ON
MY COLD BODY.
THAT WAS HONESTLY THE FIRST TIME
I'VE, LIKE, CRIED IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> THIS IS LITERALLY THE LOWEST
I'VE EVER FELT IN MY LIFE.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH, WHAT WAS
YOUR LOWEST POINT?
>> MY LOWEST POINT WAS HAVING
SEVERE GASTROINTESTINAL DISTRESS
AT THE VERY PEAK OF THE STORM.
I FELT JUST COMPLETELY
OVERWHELMED, YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS
FEELING THEY COULDN'T DO IT
ANYMORE BUT I KNEW I HAD TO.
>> Jeff: SO THAT BRINGS US TO
TODAY.
I OFFERED YOU A SHOT TO CHANGE
THINGS.
BUT IN EXCHANGE, FIVE OF YOU,
HALF THE GROUP VTO RISK GIVING
UP IMMUNITY, KNOWING TRIBAL WAS
HOURS AWAY.
CIERA, WHAT WAS YOUR VERY FIRST
THOUGHT?
>> THE VERY FIRST THOUGHT THAT
WENT THROUGH MY HEAD IS I'M
WILLING TO GIVE UP MY SPOT FOR
THE TEAM BUT WHO ELSE IS?
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO COME TOGETHER
TO SURVIVE.
AND I WANTED TO SHOW THAT I WAS
GIVING A LITTLE AS FAR AS MAKE
US STRONGER.
>> Jeff: TASHA, BEFORE YOU
MADE YOUR DECISION, WHAT DID YOU
THINK?
>> MY FIRST QUESTION WAS WHO'S
GOING TO BE SELFISH AND WHO'S
GOING TO BE UNSELFISH?
AND I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
LIVE WITH MYSELF HAD I NOT CHOSE
THE UNSELFISH CHOICE.
>> I CAN INTERJECT REAL QUICK?
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> FIPUT OUT THAT WHITE ROCK, I
GO HOME TONIGHT.
NO QUESTION ASKED.
>> Jeff: KEITH, WHEN YOU CHOSE
THE BLACK ROCK, YOU KNEW THERE
WAS A CHANCE YOU MIGHT BE IN THE
MINORITY.
>> YEAH, JEFF, BUT I'M A
COMPETITOR.
I MEAN, I WAS JUST TRYING TO,
YOU KNOW, KILL THE GOLDEN BOY.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: SPENCER, SHOULD KEITH
BE WORRIED TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T THINK KEITH'S
DECISION IS GOING TO SWAY
WHETHER OR NOT HE'S OKAY
TONIGHT.
I DO KNOW THAT IF KEITH DOESN'T
GO HOME, SOMEONE IS GOING TO
SECOND GUESS WHAT THEY DID
BEFORE THE CHALLENGE FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> Jeff: SO FISHBACH, IF KEITH
IS SAFE, THAT MEANS ONE OF THE
EIGHT WHO VOLUNTEERED TO GIVE UP
THEIR SHOT WILL BE BLINDSIDED
TONIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK THAT THERE
ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT CLUSTERS
OF POWER HERE, AND I TRULY HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN
AT THE VOTE TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, IT STILL
FEELS AS THOSE THESE VOTING
BLOCKS ARE STILL MOVING AND THE
QUESTION IS WHERE ARE THEY GOING
TO BE WHEN WE SAY, "IT'S TIME TO
VOTE."
>> IT'S JUST CRAZY.
LIKE, TODAY, THERE WAS A GROUP
THAT HAD A PLAN, AND YOU SEE ONE
OR TWO PEOPLE WALK OFF THIS WAY,
ONE OR TWO PEOPLE WALK OFF THAT
WAY.
AND YOU'RE LIKE WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> Jeff: TASHA, HAS THERE BEEN
ANY TALK ABOUT FISHBACH'S
ADVANTAGE?
>> THERE HAS BEEN A LOT OF TALK,
ESPECIALLY PEOPLE THAT ARE
WORKING CLOSELY WITH STEPHEN
FROM A STRATEGIC STANDPOINT.
>> Jeff: AND, FISHBACH, IF
ANYONE HERE HAS AN IDOL, NOBODY
MAY KNOW.
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE BECAUSE YOU DID IT IN
FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
>> YEAH AND KNOW WHAT, WHEN I
JUMPED OFF THAT PLATFORM, THAT
THOUGHT CROSSED MY MIND.
"I'M PUTTING A BIG TARGET ON
MYSELF RIGHT NOW."
>> Jeff: JEREMY, IT'S
COMPLICATED.
EAH, YOU WANT THA ADVANTAGE, BUT
NOW EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU HAVE THE
ADVANTAGE AND IT'S A BAD
ADVANTAGE BECAUSE YOU HAVE A
TARGET ON YOUR BACK NOW, IT'S
TERRIBLE.
>> IT'S A DISADVANTAGE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: FISHBACH, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE VOTE.
BECAUSE ALLIANCES ARE SHIFTING
SO MUCH, YOU CAN'T COUNT ON
THREE OR FOUR OTHER PEOPLE
VOTING WITH YOU.
SO WHAT DO YOU BASE IT ON?
>> THINGS ARE CHANGING SO
QUICKLY, YOU BASE YOUR VOTE ON
WHO YOU THINK IS GOING TO.
YOU FOR TWO DAYS.
>> Jeff: SO THEN, CIERA, THE
ONLY CERTAINTY YOU HAVE IS THE
VOTE YOU MAKE.
>> YEAH, IT REALLY COMPLICATES
THINGS BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVEN'T
ESTABLISHED LINES YET.
>> Jeff: BUT IS IT KIND OF
EXCITING THAT IT SOUNDS LIKE
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER
BLINDSIDE?
>> IT IS EXCITING TO SEE HOW THE
VOTES ARE GOG PLAY OUT, HOW THE
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO VOTE AND IF
THE PEOPLE WHO SAY THEY WERE
GOING TO VOTE ONE WAY VOTE ONE
WAY.
IT COULD BE ME THAT WAS
LINDSIDESIDED AND THAT WILL SUCK
BECAUSE THAT MEANS I SHOWED A
WRONG COLOR ROCK AND IT WOULD BE
A MILLION-DOLLAR MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: TASHA IS THAT HOW WE
HAVE TO LOOK AT THIS, A
MILLION-DOLLAR MISTAKE?
>> YEAH AIR, MILLION-DOLLAR
SHELTER.
>> Jeff: LET'S FIND OUT WHO IT
IS GOING TO BE, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
SPENCER, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITIED --OL AND WANTS
TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE
TIME TO DO SO.
>> YEAH, JEFF.
MY DECISION COMES DOWN TO WHO
CAN I TRUST MORE GOING FORWARD?
THAT'S FOR FISHBURN.
>> Jeff: FOR FISHBACH.
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTE CAST FOR FISHBACH WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL TALLY THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, FISHBACH.
DOES NOT COUNT.
FISHBACH, DOES NOT COUNT.
>> I'M WITH YOU.
ALL THE WAY.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH, DOES NOT
COUNT.
CIERA.
TWO VOTES CIERA.
KIMMI.
ONE VOTE KIMMI.
THAT'S TWO VOTES KIMMI, TWO
VOTES CIERA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
CIERA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> WELL PLAYED, WELL PLAYED.
>> SORRY.
>> I WOULD DO THE SAME THING FOR
YOU.
>> Jeff: CIERA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> LOVE YOU ALL.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT SEEMS ONLY
FITTING IN A VERY UNPREDICTABLE
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR" THAT
ANOTHER TRIBAL COUNCIL WOULD END
WITH A BIG MOVE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> TONIGHT I GUESS WAS MY NIGHT
TO GO.
I HAVE BEEN TELLING PEOPLE LET'S
PLAY HARD, LET'S PLAY THIS GAME.
I GOT PEOPLE TO PLAY A LITTLE
AND I CAN GENUINELY SAY I WENT
OUT WITH A FIGHT, AND AT LEAST I
CAN GO HOME WITH THAT PEACE.
>> COMING THROUGH WITH THAT
>> THAT WAS VERY CLASSY OF YOU,
>> SO TONIGHT AT TRIBAL, JEREMY
PULLS OUT AN IDOL.
I HAD NO IDEA HE HAD ONE.
AND PLAYS IT ON ME.
AND HE SAVED MY LIFE IN THIS
GAME, AND I OWE HIM FOR THAT
>> THAT WAS A PRETTY GOOD ONE.
THEM DUDES DON'T TRUST YOU.
>> I KNEW IN TRIBAL COUNCIL I
WAS GONE.
>> I KNEW YOU DID.
>> I'M SITTING THERE LIKE I
GOTTA DO IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I OWE YOU MY LIFE IN THIS
>> I TOLD YOU, MAN, WHEN YOU
HAVE MY BACK I GOT YOUR BACK,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I KNOW THAT STEPHEN WILL HAVE MY
BACK, AND I THINK STEPHEN WANTS
TO TAKE ME ALL THE WAY TO THE
END, AND I LIKE THAT.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> THAT WAS COOL, RIGHT?
>> WHEN YOU MAKE MOVES LIKE
THAT, A BIG MOVE LIKE THAT, I
KNOW THERE'S GOING TO BE A HUGE
TARGET ON ME NOW AFTER DOING IT,
BUT THIS GAME IS SO CRAZY, I
FEEL LIKE EVERYBODY'S STILL IN
IT, SO I HAVE WIGGLE ROOM TO
MAKE THE NEXT MOVE.
LISTEN, SPENCER, I DON'T WANT BE
>> IT'S LIKE A NEW GAME EVERY
TIME GET BACK FROM TRIBAL.
LISTEN, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
LIKE, I WOULD DO THE SAME THING
>> JEREMY PULLED A FAST ONE,
PRETTY SURE I'M BEING LIED TO.
SO MAYBE IT MAKES SENSE TO JUMP
WITH WHOEVER ELSE IS WILLING TO
>> I THOUGHT ABOUT IT, I AM
ANNOYED AT MYSELF TO HAVE BEEN
SO-- ABSOLUTELY DIDN'T SEE THAT
COMING.
ZERO, ZERO.
I WAS TOSSING AND TURNING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, EITHER.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK OF MYSELF
AS HAVING GOOD RESIDENT OFF
PEOPLE, I THINK OF MYSELF AS
KNOWING THE GAME REALLY WELL, I
CALL MYSELF A KNOW IT ALL.
AND LAST NIGHT I KNEW NOTHING.
FOR EVERY VOTE THIS SEASON I
BASICALLY KNEW WHAT WAS GOING
ON, AND YESTERDAY I DIDN'T KNOW
AT ALL.
( THUNDER )
>> IS IT GETTING WORSE, STEPHEN?
>> YOU NEED TO DRY THOSE OUT FOR
REAL.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHEN YOU
SAY, "DRY THEM OUT?"
>> WHEN EVERYTHING IS WET, IT
DOESN'T HEAL AS FAST SO ALL
THOSE CUTS AND BITES WILL STAY
OPEN, EACH GETTING MORE
INFECTED.
>> YEAH, THAT'S GROSS.
>> ON TOP OF THIS FEELING OF
DEFEAT I HAVE, EVERYTHING ELSE
IS FALLING APART, TOO.
MY FEET HAVE SWOLLEN UP TO
MONSTER SIZE.
IT'S VERY PAINFUL FOR ME TO
WALK.
I HAVE EATEN OR SLEPT IN DAYS.
I DO FEEL LIKE I'M AT A LOW,
JUST FEELING COMPLETELY
OVERWHELMED BY EVERYTHING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TIME FOR A CLASSIC.
URVIVOR" FO "SURVIVOR" FOLKLORE.
TONIGHT I'M GOING TO TELL YOU A
STORY ABOUT CAMBODIAN HISTORY.
YOU WILL RACE INTO THE JUNGLE TO
A SERIES OF FIVE STATIONS WHERE
YOU HAVE A QUESTION AND THREE
ANSWERS.
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE THE
RIGHT ANSWER, GRAB A WRAPPED
MEDALLION, HEAD BACK TO THE
START.
IF YOU ANSWER CORRECTLY, YOU'LL
GET A GOLD MEDAD DAALION.
IF YOU ANSWER INCORRECTLY,
YOU'LL GET A WOODEN MEDALLION.
YOU HAVE TO TOSS IT INTO THE
FIRE AND HEAD BACK.
THE FIRST PERSON TO ANSWER ALL
FIVE QUESTIONS CORRECTLY WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER WILL BE
PICKED UP AT YOUR BEACH BY
CHOPPER.
>> OH!
>> WOW!
>> WHAT!
>> CHOPPER.
>> Jeff: BE TAKEN ON THE
STARLING RESORT, A BEAUTIFUL
SPOT ON ANOTHER ISLAND.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: WHY WHEREYOU'LL HAVE
STEAK, CHICKEN WINGS, COCKTAILS,
THE WORKS.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: SHALL WE GET STARTED?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: TONIGHT I'M GOING TO
TAIL A STORY ABOUT ONE OF THE
MOST REVERED LEADERS IN
CAMBODIAN HISTORY, KING JAVARDIN
VII.
HE REIGNED DURING THE 12th
AND 13th CENTURY, CONSIDERED
ONE OF CAMBODIA'S GREATEST TIMES
IN HISTORY.
HIS ARMY INCLUDED HORSES,
ARCHERS, AND FEMALE WARRIORS.
HE WOULD OVERWHELM HIS OPPONENTS
WITH THOUSANDS OF CHARGING
ELEPHANTS.
AT THE START OF HIS REIGN,
HINDUISM WAS A STATE RELIGION,
AND THE FAMOUS ANCHOR, WAS THE
LARGEST RELIGIOUS COMPLEX AND
LARGEST CITY IN THE WORLD.
IT WAS A MASSIVE UNDERTAKING
REQUIRING 500,000 STONE BLOCKS
TOB FLOATED DOWN A RIVER FROM A
QUARRY 25 MILES AWAY.
IT TOOK 30 YEARS TO COMPLETE.
AND IT WAS GEOGRAPHICALLY EQUAL
IN SIZE TO MODERN-DAY LOS
ANGELES.
BUT, JEVADIMIN WAS BUDDHIST, NOT
HINDU.
SO HE BROKE 400 YEARS OF
TRADITION WHEN HE MADE BUDDHISM
THE NEW STATE RELIGION.
THEN HE SET OUT TO BUILD HIS OWN
TEMPLE, THE BAYON TEMPLE AIR,
TRIBUTE TO BUDDHISM.
50 TOWERS SPANNING THREE
FOOTBALL FIELDS WITH OVER 200
FACES CARVED INTO THE SIDES OF
TEMPLES.
AND TODAY, THOSE TWO TEMPLES,
THE BAYON AND ANGKOR ARE
REGULARLY LISTED AS ONE OF THE
TOP TOURIST ATTRACTIONS ON
EARTH.
ALL THE QUESTIONS YOU'RE GOING
TO ANSWER TONIGHT ARE BASED ON
THE STORY I JUST TOLD YOU.
>> WOW!
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY GRAB A
TORCH.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: FOR REWARD, EVERYBODY
GOOD?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
LET'S GO!
YOU GOTTA MOVE!
ONE PERSON'S GONNA WIN!
BE FAST ON YOUR FEET!
YOU CAN GO TO ANY STATION IN ANY
ORDER YOU WANT.
JAYVARDMIN WAS... A BUDDHIST.
>> WHICH OF THE FOLLOWING IS
TRUE ABOUT BAYON TEMPLE?
IT WAS BUILT WITH A STONE FROM
25 MILES AWAY.
>> Jeff: SPENCER IS BACK
FIRST.
THE QUESTION IS, IS HE RIGHT?
YOU WON'T KNOW UNTIL YOU GET
HERE AND UNWRAP IT.
IF IT'S GOLD, PUT IT ON YOUR
STAND.
IF IT'S WOOD, THROW IT IN THE
FIRE AND HEAD BACK.
GOLD MEANS YOU'RE RIGHT.
WOOD MEANS YOU'RE WRONG.
KEITH IS WRONG, HE'S GOT TO HEAD
BACK.
SPENCER'S RIGHT.
WENTWORTH HAS HER FIRST ONE
RIGHT.
FISHBACH IS RIGHT.
JEREMY'S RIGHT.
ABI HAS IT RIGHT.
SHE'S IN IT.
>> Jeff: KEITH BACK.
HE WAS WRONG THE FIRST TIME.
DID HE GET IT RIGHT THIS TIME?
IT'S COMPLICATED BECAUSE THERE
ARE THREE ANSWERS WHICH MEANS
IT'S NOT AN AUTOMATIC YOU'LL GET
IT RIGHT.
EVERYBODY NOW COMING BACK WITH
THEIR SECOND.
>> GOOD GRIEF!
>> Jeff: KEITH MISSED AGAIN.
JOE'S WRONG.
HE'S GOT TO HEAD OUT.
THAT'S GOING TO OPEN THE DOOR
FOR SOMEBODY TO TAKE THE LEAD
WITH TWO.
IT IS FISHBACH WITH TWO UPON.
HE'S HEADING OUT.
WENTWORTH IS WRONG.
SPENCER'S RIGHT.
HE'S GOT TWO.
>> Jeff: IT IS SPENCER,
JEREMY, FISHBACH WITH TWO.
WENTWORTH, JOE, AND TASHA WITH
ONE.
ABI HAS HER SECOND.
SHE WAS RIGHT.
ABI'S JUST SLOW.
MORE PEOPLE COMING BACK.
JOE WRONG AGAIN.
FALLING OUT OF THIS QUICKLY.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
ATTACHED TO THE LITTLE DISK IS A
LITTLE PIECE OF PAPER AND IT
SAYS, "IDOL CLUE."
>> Jeff: WENTWORTH, SHE HAS
HER SECOND.
I TOOK THE IDOL CLUE OFF,
STUFFED IT IN MY PANTS AND KEPT
GOING.
ANYONE COULD HAVE COME AND
PICKED THAT ONE ANSWER, AND THEY
COULD HAVE HAD THE CLUE.
HOW LUCKY AM I?
>> Jeff: SPENCER'S RIGHT.
HE HAS HIS THIRD.
IT'S SPENCER IN THE LEAD.
FISHBACH IS WRONG.
IT IS NOW SPENCER SLOWLY IN THE
LEAD WITH THREE.
WENTWORTH HAS TWO.
APARRI HAS TWO.
JEREMY HAS TWO.
FISHBACH HAS TWO.
AND TASHA HAS TWO.
>> 12th AND 13th
CENTURY.
THAT'S THE 1100s AND 1200s.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH COMING BACK.
JOE COMING BACK.
HE'S BEEN TERRIBLE IN THIS
CHALLENGE SO FAR.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ABI HAS HER THIRD.
SHE HASN'T MISSED YET.
FISHBACH IS RIGHT WITH THREE.
SPENCER HAS HIS FOURTH.
LOOKING FOR ONE MORE!
>> SORRY, ABI.
>> Jeff: ABI COMING BACK WITH
HER FOURTH.
JEREMY STILL WORKING IT.
JEREMY HAS HIS THIRD!
FISHBACH COMING BACK LOOKING FOR
HIS FOURTH.
ABI MISSES FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THAT'S GOING TO COST HER.
FISHBACH LOOKING FOR HIS FOURTH.
SPENCER BACK WITH HIS FIFTH.
THIS COULD BE IT FOR THE WIN.
FISHBACH IS RIGHT WITH HIS
FOURTH.
IF HE'S RIGHT, BIG REWARD FOR
SPENCER.
TASHA JUST LOOKING OVER.
HE'S LOOKING FOR GOLD.
SPENCER'S WRONG!
OPENS UP THE DOOR.
WE'RE STILL GOING.
>> Jeff: IT IS SPENCER AND
FISHBACH BOTH WITH FOUR.
SPENCER COMING BACK.
FIR BACK RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
IT COULD COME DOWN TO THIS.
THIS IS IT.
FISHBACH HAS IT.
FISHBACH WINS REWARD BY SECONDS
OVER SPENCER.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> Jeff: DID YOU HAVE IT
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I DID.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH, COME ON
OVER.
>> GOOD JOB!
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: NICE JOB.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Jeff: BIG REWARD.
>> IT IS.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BE PICKED UP
AT YOUR BEACH ROCK STAR STYLE IN
A CHOPPER, TAKEN TO A STARLING
RESORT WHERE YOU WILL HAVE A
GREAT DAY.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO COME WITH
YOU.
>> I HAVE A LOT OF DAMAGE
CONTROL TO DO.
LAST NIGHT PROVED MY ALLIANCE
WASN'T AS STRONG AS I THOUGHT
THEY WERE, I NEED TO TAKE TASHA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: CHOOSE ONE MORE AND
THAT IS IT.
>> THERE'S ONE GUY, I'M ONLY IN
THE GAME BECAUSE OF THIS GUY,
IT'S JEREMY, 100%.
YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T BE HERE TO
WIN THIS REWARD IF IT WEREN'T
FOR HIM.
>> Jeff: AS FOR THE REST OF
YOU, I GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
EVERYBODY HAD BACK TO CAMP.
THANKS FOR PLAYING SURVIVOR
FOLKLORE.
>> STEPHEN, THE "SURVIVOR"
KNOW-IT-ALL, MAKES A VERY
QUESTIONABLE DECISION.
HE TAKES TASHA AND JEREMY WITH
HIM ON REWARD.
I THINK IT'S BECOME REALLY CLEAR
THEY ARE TIGHTER WITH EACH OTHER
THAN I WILL BE WITH THEM AND I
NEED TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
>> RUNNING ON MY MONSTER FEET
WAS VERY HARD.
>> YEAH, YOU QUIT MILKING THAT
FOOT, FISH.
YOU WERE RUNNING LIKE A DEER OUT
THERE.
>> THE REWARD CHALLENGE WAS VERY
FUN.
IT WAS CRAZY.
I DID NOT WIN.
BUT BINGO.
I GOT AN IDOL CLUE.
>> JEREMY, FIRST REWARD!
THAT'S EXCITING!
I DON'T CARE THEY LOST REWARD.
THIS HAVING AN IDOL CLUE IS HUGE
IN THIS GAME.
"CONGRATULATIONS YOU HAVE FOUND
A CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL BUT IT WILL REQUIRE YOU TO
PICK THE RIGHT MOMENT TO MAKE A
VERY BOLD MOVE ATTACHED TO THE
UNDERSIDE OF YOUR SHELTER DEAD
CENTER IS THE SECURITY YOU SEEK.
THE ONLY THING STOPPING YOU FROM
GETTING IT IS THE FEAR OF
GETTING CAUGHT."
>> I WONDER WHAT TIME THEY'RE
GOING TO COME GET YOU ALL.
>> I CAN'T SEE.
I CAN'T SEE UNDER THE SHELTER AT
NIGHT.
I DIG MY HAND UNDER THERE, BUT I
DON'T KNOW IF IT'S UNDER THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS
EXACTLY.
I THINK TOMORROW IS PROBABLY A
GOOD OPPORTUNITY BECAUSE THREE
PEOPLE WILL BE ON REWARD IS,
LIKE, THREE LESS BODIES I HAVE
TO KEEP AN EYE ON AND WORRY
ABOUT.
>> THIS GAME HAS BEEN SO
UNPREDICTABLE AND WE HAVE BEEN
TALKING SO MUCH ABOUT VOTING
BLOKDZ, EVERY VOTE IS A
DIFFERENT BLOCK.
BUT I THINK JEREMY PLAYING HIS
IDOL FOR ME SHOWED THERE IS
STILL TRUST IN THIS GAME.
>> OH, GEEZ.
SO I WANTED TO BRING MY CLOSEST
ALLIES WITH ME.
AND IT LOOKED LIKE THE PERFECT
PLACE TO REAFFIRM THOSE
RELATIONSHIPS AND MAKE THOSE
BONDS MORE CONCRETE.
TO GREAT EXPERIENCES AND
RELATIONSHIPS WE HAVE CREATED ON
"SURVIVOR" SO FAR.
>> CHEERS.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
>> TASH AFS ONE OF MY FIRST
ALLIES BUT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL SHE
WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
BUT I FELT MORE THAN I NEEDED TO
GO ANYTHING I NEEDED TO REPAIR
MY ALLIANCE WITH TASHA, BREAK
BREAD AND COME UP WITH A PLAN
MOVING FORWARD WITH THEM.
>> STEPHEN, I APPRECIATE YOU,
MAN.
>> I WANTED TO.
WE'VE BEEN TIGHT SINCE THE VERY
BEGINNING OF THIS GAME.
I THINK THERE MAY BE SOME
SUSPICION AND MISTRUST.
IN THE SPIRIT OF OPENNESS I WANT
TO TELL YOU WHAT MY ADVANTAGE
IS.
I CAN STEAL A VOTE.
>> OH!
>> SO FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER
SOMEONE WILL NOT BE ABLE TO CAST
A VOTE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND I
WILL GET A SECOND VOTE.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> THAT IS A THREE-VOTE SWING.
>> THAT'S A GAME CHANGER.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WE'VE BEEN
PLAYING THE VOTE-TO-VOTE GAME.
EVERYONE HAS BEEN TRYING TO CUT
EVERYONE'S THROAT.
WE HAVE TO HAVE TRUST.
>> I HATE TO THROW A WRINKLE IN
THIS, BUT JOE, IF HE KEEPS
WINNING.
THAT DUDE, AS SOON AS HE LOSES
HE HAS TO GO.
>> JOE, THAT'S IT, HE'S OVER.
>> I'M IN 100%.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M GLAD WE HAD THIS TALK.
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THE
CHOICE OF BEING TASHA AND
JEREMY?
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
>> OH, I THINK THAT JEREMY, YOU
KNOW, PLAYED HIS IDOL FOR
STEPHEN.
SO STEPHEN'S OBVIOUSLY REPAYING
HIM.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE BLIND NOT TO
SEE THEM THREE, OTHERWISE THEY
WOULD HAVE TOOK ME.
AND THEN YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
SAYING, "WHAT IN THE WORLD IS HE
DOING TAKING KEITH?"
>> IN A SEASON WHERE THERE'S NO
ALLIANCES AND THERE'S THESE
VOTING BLOCKS AND THE GAME IS
CONSTANTLY SHIFTING, STEPHEN
KIND OF THREW HIMSELF OUT THERE
AND DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT
BECAUSE HE CHOSE TO TAKE JEREMY
AND THEN HE CHOSE TASH.
>> SEE YOU GUYS IN A LITTLE BIT.
>> AND FISHBACH AND KIMMI,
THEY'VE BEEN TOGETHER QUITE A
WHILE.
SO I KNOW NOW THAT THERE'S A
REALLY STRONG CONNECTION THERE
THAT I NOW REALLY AM WORRIED
ABOUT.
>> OKAY.
NOW'S OUR TIME.
>> IS SHE GONE?
>> LET'S TALK.
>> I THINK IT'S A REALLY GOOD
IDEA FOR US TO LOCK IN WHAT
WE'RE DOING AND JUST HAVE IT--
HAVE IT SET, HAVE IT SECURED AND
HAVE A BACKUP IN CASE THAT
PERSON WINS.
>> WHAT IS OUR PLAN?
>> I THINK IT MAKES SENSE TO GET
RID OF FISHBACH BECAUSE HE HAS
AN ADVANTAGE, RIGHT?
>> THE ONLY FEAR I HAVE IS IF HE
USES THIS ADVANTAGE TOMORROW,
I'M GONE.
THAT'S IT.
I'M DONE.
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME-- WHY DON'T
YOU LET ME WIN THE CHALLENGE
TOMORROW?
>> UM, NO.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO WIN THEM
ALL.
>> I'M TRYING REALLY HARD TO
TRUST THE ONES CLOSE TO ME, BUT
JOE IS VERY SKETCHY, AND
SPENCER, TOO.
I FEEL THAT THEY THINK THAT THEY
ARE PLAYING EVERYONE, AND I
DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE TRYING TO
PLAY ME AND THE PLAN THAT WE PUT
TOGETHER.
SO I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GOING TO
GO WITH THE PLAN.
>> SO DO WE WANT TO GO STEVEN
AND TASH.
>> BUT IF STEPHEN WINS IMMUNITY,
THE PLAN IS TASHA.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT'S IT.
THERE'S NO NEED TO EVEN-- NO
NEED TO EVEN QUESTION ANYTHING
ELSE.
>> PERFECT, DONE.
SO WE'RE SITTING THERE AND I'M
LIKE, GREAT, WE'VE GOT A PLAN,
WE'RE GOOD.
BUT MY GOAL TODAY IS TO SNATCH
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL OUT
FROM UNDERNEATH THE SHELTER IN
ORDER FOR THAT TO HAPPEN, I NEED
EVERYBODY TO BE OUT OF CAMP.
>> YOU WANT TO TAKE THE BOAT
OUT?
>> YEAH, LET'S TAKE THE BOAT
OUT.
>> YEAH, GO.
>> WE READY.
>> I'LL WAVE AT YOU ALL.
>> LUCKY FOR ME, THE SUN IS OUT.
JOE AND SPENCER GO OFF TO GO
FISHING.
KEITH AND KIMMI ARE GOING TO GO
GET SOME SNAILS AND SOME CRABS.
SO THAT JUST LEAVES MISS
ABI-MARIA.
HOME GIRL WILL NOT LEAVE THE
SHELTER!
>> YOU WANT SOME COFFEE?
>> I'M OKAY, THANK YOU.
ABI IS LIKE AN ANNOYING LITTLE
SISTER, LIKE A LITTLE PEST.
ANY OTHER TIME, ANY OTHER TIME
OF THE DAY SHE WILL BE OFF IN
THE WATER, WALKING DOWN TO THE
ROCKS.
BUT FOR SOME ODD REASON TODAY,
SHE IS MAKING COFFEE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT SHE'S
DOING.
I'M LIKE, MY WHEELS ARE
SPINNING.
HOW I DO GET HER OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THE OTHERS COME BACK.
>> QUIET DAY.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M JUST PRETENDING TO BE
SLEEPING HOPING SHE WILL LEAVE,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN A RAY OF
LIGHT, ABI GOES, "I THINK I'M
GOING TO GO LAY IN THE HAMMOCK."
I'M LIKE, "YES!
YES!"
I'M LIKE, OKAY, THIS IS MY
CHANCE.
I, LIKE, WADDLE OVER TO UNDER
THE SHELTER, STICK MY HAND
UNDER, GET IN, LIKE, THIS IS
REALLY, REALLY SCARY.
I'M TRYING TO GET THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL UNDER THE SHELTER.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, EVERYONE COMES
BACK IN.
>> FISHY, FISHY, FISHY.
>> I AM FREAKING OUT, "A,"
BECAUSE THAT WAS THE MOST
STRESSFUL THING I'VE DONE IN
THIS GAME BESIDES GETTING THE
FIRST IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND "B," I HAVE AN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
NUMBER TWO.
>> I'LL LEAVE IT THERE FOR A
MINUTE.
SO I AM READY TO SHAKE UP THIS
GAME A LITTLE BIT.
STRESSFUL, VERY STRESSFUL.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT YOU GUYS READY TO GET
TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JOE, FOR THE FOURTH TIME, I'VE
GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE ONLY YOUR FEET.
ON MY GO YOU'LL RELEASE A ROPE
WHICH WILL DROP PLOKS INTO A
BASKET.
YOU WILL THEN STACK THOSE BLOCKS
AND PLACE A FLAG IN THE MIDDLE
USING JUST YOUR 10 LITTLE
PIGGIES.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE AT TRIBAL,
GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WHEN WE FIRST DID THIS IN "BLOOD
VERSUS WATER," KEITH AND JEREMY
BOTH PARTICIPATED, BOTH LOST.
JEREMY WENT TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
THAT NIGHT AND--
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND WAS VOTED OUT.
SO A HUGE SECOND-CHANCE
OPPORTUNITY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST STEP IS UNSPOOLG THAT ROPE
WHICH IS NOT NEARLY AS EASY WHEN
YOU JUST HAVE YOUR TOES TO WORK
WITH.
WENTWORTH FIRST DOWN WITH HER
BLOCKS.
ABI HAS HERS.
KIMMI HAS HERS.
JOE HAS HIS HELP JEREMY'S GOT
HIS.
KEITH HAS HIS.
IF ANY OF YOUR BLOCKS FALL YOU
CAN PICK THEM UP WITH YOUR HAND
THROW THEM BACK IN YOUR BASKET.
ONCE YOU HAVE YOUR BLOCKS, START
WORKING ON IT.
SPENCER STILL TRYING TO GET HIS
PLOKS DOWN, LOSING A LOT OF TIME
IN THIS.
SPENCER FINALLY HAS HIS PIECES
FREE.
JOE OFF TO A FAST START.
KIMING OFF TO A QUICK START.
WENTWORTH DOING A NICE JOB.
JEREMY HAS HIS FIRST LEVEL,
WORKING ON THAT SECOND LEVEL.
KEITH IS ON HIS SECOND LEVEL.
ABI IS STARTING ON HER SECOND
LEVEL.
EVERYBODY OFF TO A QUICK START
ON THIS FIRST LEVEL.
EXCEPT FISHBACH, SLOWEST OUT OF
THE GATE WITH ONLY TWO PIECES ON
THE BOTTOM.
>> I GOT-- I GOT SOME PROBLEMS
WITH MY FEET HERE.
>> Jeff: YOUR FEET LOOK
PREHISTORIC.
WOW.
YOU HAVE HAD A ROUGH GO.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: JOE TRYING TO PLACE
THAT FIRST PIECE ON HIS SECOND
LEVEL.
THE MORE YOU MOVE UP, THE MORE
PRECARIOUS IT BECOMES.
YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE YOU HAVE
THEM STACKED RIGHT ON THE
BOTTOM.
IF NOT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
PROBLEMS LATER ON THE TOP.
SPENCER IS NOW IN THIS.
SPENCER HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
TIME IN TERMS OF STACKING THEM.
KEITH KNOCKS A COUPLE OFF.
THAT'S GOING TO SET HIM BACK.
JEREMY KNOCKS A COUPLE OFF.
THIS IS WHERE PATIENCE WILL PAY
OFF.
RIGHT NOW, WENTWORTH STARTING TO
WORK ON HER THIRD LEVEL.
IT IS NOW WENTWORTH IN THE LEAD,
JOE RIGHT BEHIND.
JOE NOW WORKING ON HIS THIRD
ROW.
KEITH HAS NOW FINISHED HIS
SECOND ROW.
KEITH NOW WORKING ON HIS THIRD
ROW.
SPENCER FINISHES HIS SECOND ROW.
SPENCER NOW WORKING ON HIS THIRD
ROW.
IT IS KEITH, SPENCER, WENTWORTH,
AND JOE.
JOE PLACES HIS SECOND BLOCK ON
HIS TOP ROW.
KEITH PLACES HIS SECOND BLOCK.
KELLY STRUGGLING NOW WITH THAT
TOP ROW.
IT'S HARD.
YOU'VE GOT TO LIFT THESE BLOCKS
HIGHER.
YOU'VE GOT TO LIFT FROM YOUR
CORE.
JOE PLACES A THIRD BLOCK.
IF JOE WINS HIS FIFTH INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, HE WOULD JOIN AN ELITE
GROUP.
ONLY FIVE PEOPLE HAVE EVER WON
FIVE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITIES IN
ONE SEASON.
>> OH!
WHAT!
>> Jeff: JOE JUST HAD A
SETBACK.
A LOT OF BLOCKS JUST FELL FROM
JOE, AND HE'S GOT TO GO
BACKWARDS NOW AND PICK IT UP.
SPENCER PLACES HIS THIRD ON THE
TOP ROW.
OH, BUT DISASTER FOR KEITH.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
YOU ARE NOT OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE UNTIL SOMEBODY PLACES
THAT FLAG BECAUSE IT GETS MORE
AND MORE DIFFICULT THE HIGHER
YOU GO.
SPENCER NOW PLACES HIS FOURTH
BLOCK ON THE TOP ROW.
IT IS NOW SPENCER IN THE LEAD,
JOE HAS REPAIRED ALL THE DWJ AND
IS NOW BACK IN THIS.
JOE PLACES HIS FOURTH ON THE TOP
ROW.
SPENCER PLACES HIS FIFTH.
IT IS NOW SPENCER AND JOE.
JOE PLACES HIS FIFTH.
THE LAST PERSON TO RELEASE HIS
BLOCKS IS NOW IN IT TO WIN IT.
SPENCER PLACES HIS SIXTH.
JOE HAS FIVE.
SPENCER HAS SIX.
THIS WOULD BE A HUGE
COME-FROM-BEHIND FOR SPENCER TO
DETHRONE JOE.
SPENCER PLACES HIS SEVENTH.
SPENCER PLACES THE LAST BLOCK ON
THE TOP ROW, SNOW PLACES HIS
SIXTH.
SPENCER WITH THE EIGHTH BLOCK ON
THE TOP ROW.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
SPENCER NOW HAS ONE STEP LEFT,
THAT IS THE FINISH FLAG FOR THE
WIN.
JOE PLACES HIS SEVENTH.
SPENCER FOR THE WIN.
CAN HE GET IT IN THE HOLE?
JOE DOWN TO HIS LAST PIECE IN
THIS THIRD SECTION.
SPENCER STRUGGLING.
HE GOT IT!
SPENCER WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY!
>> WHOOO!
>> BRINGING JOE'S STREAK TO AN
END.
>> GOOD JOB, SPENCE.
>> GOOD JOB, SPENCER.
>> AWESOME, SPENCER.
>> DANG, THAT WAS GOOD.
>> Jeff: SPENCER, INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> GOOD JOB, SPENCER!
>> Jeff: YOU ARE SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, WILL NOT GO
HOME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 29
DAYS SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
AND BECOME THE FIFTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
ONE THING IS FOR CERTAIN, IT
WILL NOT BE YOU.
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> TODAY, I DID NOT WIN
IMMUNITY.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN SAFE FOR 29
DAYS, AND NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN, I
DON'T HAVE THAT NECKLACE AND
THAT POWER AND THAT SAFETY, I'M
VULNERABLE TO GOING HOME.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME, I'M
REALLY NERVOUS.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> YOU WERE RIGHT THERE, RIGHT?
>> JOE HAS LITERALLY NEVER BEEN
UP FOR ELIMINATION IN THIS GAME,
NOT ONCE IN 29 DAYS.
AND TODAY FOR THE FIRST TIME HE
IS.
>> I WASN'T EVEN TOUCHING IT AND
IT FELL OFF AND KNOCKED OVER
THREE OUT OF NOWHERE.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO TAKE
OUT JOE SINCE DAY ONE.
>> GOOD WIN, MAN.
>> THANKS.
I DIDN'T THINK THAT WOULD BE MY
CHALLENGE.
>> AND I HAVE JUST BEEN SPOILED
AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN AND
AGAIN AS HE HAS WON IMMUNITY
AFTER IMMUNITY AFTER IMMUNITY.
AND NOW, I FINALLY HAVE MY SHOT.
YOU WILL BE HERE A MONTH, AND
ONE OF US WILL NOT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE NEED TO HAVE,
LIKE, A FRANK CONVERSATION.
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT ABOUT JOE?
>> JOE'S A THREAT AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED.
>> HE IS A THREAT.
HE WINS A TON OF IMMUNITIES.
HE COULD GO ON ANOTHER RUN.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK JOE IS THE BIGGEST
CHALLENGE GUY, LIKE, HE COULD
JUST KEEP WINNING.
WE WANT TO GET HIM WHEN HE
DOESN'T HAVE PROTECTION.
>> RIGHT.
>> JOE, RIGHT?
>> IF JOE ASKS YOU, YOU'RE
VOTING ABI.
>> OKAY.
>> AND IF ABI PULLS US ASIDE,
THEN WE'RE JUST SAYING JOE.
>> FINE.
>> JEREMY, GOOD?
EVERYBODY GOOD.
>> LET'S HAVE PEACE OF MIND FOR
THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON.
>> YES.
>> THE FOUR-- KIMMI, STEPHEN,
JEREMY, AND TASHA-- ARE GOING TO
TARGET JOE, BUT IT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN BECAUSE I HAVE FIVE
PEOPLE, WHICH INCLUDES JOE.
DO NOT RIGHT JOE, IT'S FISH THE
PLAN IS TO BLINDSIDE STEPHEN
FISH BACK.
>> PLEASE TELL ME IT'S NOT ME
TONIGHT.
>> IN THE SMIENDZ OF SOME IT IS
YOU.
>> LIKE STEPHEN.
>> YES.
>> YOU HAVE TO TRUST US.
>> AND I DO.
>> YOU ARE SAYING.
>> HERE'S THE THING, IF I GO
HOME TONIGHT, I'M GOOD WITH IT.
>> YOU ARE NOT.
>> GET OUT OF THAT MENTALITY.
>> OKAY.
TONIGHT IS A REALLY BIG TEST.
I'M REALLY RELYING ON MY SOCIAL
GAME WHAT I'VE TRIED TO DEVELOP
IN THIS GAME THAT I DIDN'T
REALLY DEVELOP AND HAVE IN THE
LAST GAME.
>> FIVE IS SOLID.
STICK WITH THE PLAN, AND WE ARE
GOOD.
>> I'M HOPING THAT PEOPLE ARE
STICKING TRUE TO BLINDSIDING
STEPHEN, AND I GUESS TIME WILL
TELL.
TRIBAL IS ONLY A COUPLE OF HOURS
AWAY, AND I'M HOPING FOR THE
BEST.
>> WHAT'S THE STORY?
>> JOE, RIGHT.
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU GUYS WANT TO
DO?
>> YEAH, RIGHT?
>> YEAH YUP, THAT SOUNDS
ACTUALLY, AWESOME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YEAH.
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU DON'T BELIEVE
ME.
>> I'M TALKING TO YOU, AND
YOU'RE LIKE-- WHAT DO YOU WANT
FROM ME?
I'M TELLING YOU I WANT TO WORK
WITH YOU.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
>> THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
>> OKAY.
THE PLAN IS ABI IS VOTING FOR
JOE, AND JOE IS VOTING FOR ABI,
BUT ABI IS INSANE.
SHE IS SUSPICIOUS OF ME BECAUSE
SHE'S SUSPICIOUS OF EVERYONE.
THIS IS A GAME WHERE YOU HAVE TO
TRAWFT PEOPLE WITH YOUR FATE IN
THIS GAME, AND I HAVE TWO
CONVINCE JOE THAT WE ARE VOTING
FOR ABI.
>> I DON'T LIKE IT, BUT I'M
TRYING TO BELIEVE WHAT'S
BELIEVABLE.
>> SHE WAS SARCASTIC ABOUT IT.
>> SHE'S NOT IN A GOOD PLACE.
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY I THINK
SHE THINKS IT'S HER.
>> I TOLD HER--
>> I DON'T THINK SHE BELIEVES
ANYTHING AT THIS POINT.
>> JOE IS VERY SHADY.
HE IS HAVING A LITTLE POWWOW
WITH JEREMY AND FISHBACH, SO
I'M, LIKE, WHAT THE HECK IS
GOING ON HERE?
I DO NOT TRUST JOE AT THIS
POINT.
>> WHO ARE YOU GOING TO VOTE
FOR?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
I'M GOING TO HAVE THO CHOOSE AT
TRIBAL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
>> OH, GOD, ABI IS FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
>> I THINK JOE IS PLAYING YOU
AND ME.
>> NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T.
I THINK THAT THIS PLAN WE HAVE
TO GO WITH.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I HAVE SOME DECISION TO MAKE.
>> FIFEEL ANYTHING WEIRD TONIGHT
AND PEOPLE DO NOT STICK WITH THE
FISHBACH PLAN, THE IDOL IS
COMING OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT, ABI, WHAT'S GOING
ON?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S GOING
ON.
>> THE PLAN THAT WE MADE
YESTERDAY IS GOING ON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AND YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE UNHAPPY.
>> I'M COOL.
I'M READY TO GO HOME IF I HAVE
TO TONIGHT.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME,
THOUGH.
>> BUT I'M READY TO IF THAT'S
WHAT IT IS.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
>> BUT IT'S NOT.
>> OKAY.
WHY ARE YOU FREAKING OUT?
IS EVERYTHING OKAY WITH YOU?
LET IT BE.
I MEAN, TO ME, IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO GOES HOME.
I WILL DECIDE THAT AT TRIBAL.
>> ABI IS ON THE WAR PATH, AND
I'M SCARED THAT ABI'S GOING TO
REACT, VOTE FOR JOE, AND THIS
ENTIRE PLAN IS GOING TO GO DOWN
THE TIEWKS BECAUSE THERE'S NINE
PEOPLE LEFT.
WE HAVE FIVE, AND I NEED
EVERYONE TO STICK TO THIS PLAN.
ABI, IF TEE DON'T STICK WITH THE
PLAN, IF WE DON'T VOTE FOR
STEPHEN, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> AM I GOING TO HAVE TO JUST GO
TOTALLY AGAINST THE PLAN FROM
YESTERDAY?
I CAN VOTE FOR FISHBACH OR JOJO.
I HAVE TWO OPTIONS.
WE'LL SEE.
>> THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I KNEW
WAS GOING TO HAPPEN WITH ABI,
AND IT'S HAPPENING.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WE HAVE TO VOTE FOR JOE.
>> JOE HAS AN IDOL.
>> NO, HE DOESN'T.
>> YOU'RE SURE?
>> NO.
>> BUT HE HAS TO.
THAT'S THE PLAN.
I MEAN--
>> HE GETS THE MAJORITY OF THE
VOTES.
THAT'S WHY IF HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE IDOL, HE GOES HOME.
>> THERE COULDN'T BE MORE
PANDEMONIUM RIGHT NOW.
BUT I HAVE AN ADVANTAGE, AND MY
ADVANTAGE ALLOWS ME TO STEAL A
VOTE, AND NOW I HAVE THE NUMBERS
TO SPLIT THE VOTES RELIABLY.
EITHER WE LOSE JOE OR WE LOSE
ABI AND JOE'S IDOL,.
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO PLAY MY
ADVANTAGE TONIGHT.
WILL YOU VOTE FOR ABI AND NOT
JOE?
>> I'M QOOL THAT, BUT WHAT'S THE
GOAL?
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SPLIT THE
VOTES, BUT USING MY ADVANTAGE.
>> OKAY.
BUT, LIKE, I KIND OF WANT TO
KNOW WHAT THE PLAN IS.
>> I CAN STEAL A VOTE FROM
SOMEONE.
>> RIGHT.
>> I GOT ENOUGH TRUST GOING WITH
THEM THAT STEPHEN REVEALED TO ME
WHAT HIS ADVANTAGE WAS, AND I
WAS ABLE TO SEE THAT IT WOULD
DESTROY EVERYTHING, EVEN THOUGH
I'VE DONE EVERYTHING RIGHT TO
PUT WHAT I WANT TO HAPPEN INTO
PLACE, IT COULD ALL GO TO CRAP.
STEPHEN HAS AN ADVANTAGE.
ABI IS THE MOST UNRELIABLE
PERSON HERE.
WE ALSO HAVE THE POTENTIAL FOR
AN IDOL.
AND A REASON TO BLINDSIDE JOE.
OUR PLAN THAT WE HAMMERED OUT IS
TO TAKE OUT STEPHEN.
BUT IF I GO THAT ROUTE, I RUN A
BIG RISK.
AND IT SCARES ME TO DEATH.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
KASS, SAVAGE, WIGLESWORTH, AND
CIERA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, JOE, BIG STORY HAS TO BE
THAT FOR FIRST TIME SINCE WE
MERGED, YOU ARE NOT WEARING
IMMUNITY.
>> OH, YEAH.
ALL AFTERNOON I'VE BEEN MULLING
THAT OVER IN MY HEAD, AND THE
ONLY THING I CAN REALLY DO IS
HOPE THE TRUST I BUILT WITH
PEOPLE CAN TAKE ME A LITTLE
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: ABI, WHAT DO YOU READ
INTO THAT WHEN YOU HAVE SOMEBODY
LIKE JOE SAYING, "THERE'S REALLY
NOTHING FOR ME TO DO OTHER THAN
HOPE WHAT I THINK IS GOING TO
HAPPEN IS GOING TO HAPPEN?
I'M NOT GOING TO SCRAMBLE."
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU ABOUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN THE GAME IF
ANYTHING.
>> IT TELLS ME THERE ARE
ALLIANCES, CLEARLY, AND IT ALL
DEPENDS ON--
>> TRUST.
>> YEAH, WHICH ALLIANCE IS THE
ONE THAT'S MOST LOYAL TO YOU.
>>
>> Jeff: TASHA, KEITH BRINGS
UP TRUST, AND YET, EVERY SINGLE
TRIAL INVOLVING OUR JURY,
BLINDSIDE, BLINDSIDE, BLINDSIDE,
BLINDSIDE.
>> SO FAR, THERE'S BEEN NO TRUST
AT ALL.
>> RIGHT.
I THINK AS WE GO CLOSER TO DAY
39 WE ALL ARE STARTING TO
REALIZE THE VOTING BLOCK MAY NOT
BE THE MOST EFFECTIVE METHOD
GOING FORWARD.
I NEED TO START FINDING THAT
CORE TWO OR THREE, FOUR PEOPLE
THAT I CAN SAY,UN" WHAT?
I'M GOING TO LOCK IT IN WITH
YOU.
LET'S DO THIS."
>> Jeff: WENTWORTH, TASHA IS
SAYING THE LAYER OF THE VOTING
BLOCK HAS ELIMINATED THE LITTLE
TRUST YOU MIGHT HAVE HAD FROM
YOUR ALLIANCE THAT YOU KNEW YOU
WERE GOOD WITH.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF.
THERE DEFINITELY ARE ALLIANCES
AT THE REWARD CHALLENGE STEPHEN
CHOSE TASHA BECAUSE HE SAID HE
NEEDED TO MEND FENCES WITH AN
ALLIANCE MEMBER.
>> THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN AN OLD
COLLOQUIALISM.
I SHOULD HAVE SAID VOTING BLOCK.
>> IT CAME OUT.
I'M SAYING, IF YOU USE THE WORD
REQUESTED ALLIANCE," THERE IT
IS.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH AT THE LAST
TRIBAL THERE WAS A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT THE ADVANTAGE.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S A SCARY
THING ADDING ONE, BIG, GIANT
UNKNOWN THAT COULD UPEND
EVERYTHING.
SO I COULD UNDERSTAND WHY IT
WOULD BE VERY THREATENING AND
PUT A GIANT TARGET ON ME AND I
THINK IT DID.
>> Jeff: SO ARE YOU GENUINELY
CONCERNED AGAIN, GIVEN LAST
TRIBAL, AND ALL THE VOTES YOU
GOT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK LAST TRIBAL
SHOWED THE IDOL MAKES PEOPLE
WANT TO SPLIT VOTES, AND THAT
MAKES IT VERY EASY FOR ANOTHER
GROUP OR FACTION TO VOTE MY WAY.
>> Jeff: WOW.
SPENCER, SO COMPLICATED.
>> INSANELY COMPLICATED.
I MEAN SPLIT VOTES, IDOLS,
MYSTERY ADVANTAGES.
THERE ARE SO MANY PERMUTATIONS
OF WHAT COULD HAPPEN, AND WE'RE
IN THIS LIMB B LIMBO OF THROWING
OUT WHAT-IFS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> Jeff: ABI RING TRUE TO YOU?
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF TALK.
THERE WERE A LOT OF NAMES BEING
THROWN.
IT WAS JUST, LIKE, ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
I ACTUALLY HAVE A HEADACHE.
I CAN'T EVEN THINK STRAIGHT.
IT'S BEEN WILD.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH WHAT ARE THE
HAT WIL WIL BE ANOTHER BLINDSIDE
TONIGHT.
>> REALISTICALLY, I THINK AT
THIS POINT, 33%.
>> Jeff: IF FISHBACH IS RIGHT,
AND THERE IS A LOW RISK OF
BLINDSIDE.
>> JEFF, I'LL BE CANDID, I THINK
A SHIFT IS STARTING TO HAPPEN.
VOTING INTLOKS GOTTEN US THIS
FAR, BUT I THINK YOU NEED PEOPLE
YOU CAN TRUST TO GET YOU TO THE
END.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
JEREMY, YOU'RE UP.
>> JEFF.
I'D LIKE TO REMOVE A LITTLE BIT
OF MYSTERY AND THREAT IN THE
GAME AND PLAY MY ADVANTAGE.
>> Jeff: WHY DON'T YOU
EXPLAIN, STEPHEN, WHAT THE
ADVANTAGE IS.
>> I AM ABLE TO STEAL SOMEONE'S
VOTE, AND CAST IT MYSELF.
THAT PERSON WON'T BE VOTING AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL I GUESS FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY.
AND I WILL BE VOTING FOR THEM
INSTEAD.
>> Jeff: WHOSE VOTE ARE YOU
GOING TO STEAL?
>> I'M GOING TO STEAL JOE'S
VOTE.
>> THIS MEANS STEPHEN GETS TWO.
>> Jeff: YEAH.
SO TO BE CLEAR, JOE, YOU WILL
NOT GET UP TO VOTE.
FISHBACH, WHEN YOU VOTE, YOU
WILL VOTE TWICE.
JOE, HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> OH, IT STUCKS!
BUT IT'S THE GAME.
SO... IT'S GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
JEREMY, YOU'RE UP.
>> WITH MY VOTE, I AM GOING TO
VOTE FOR ABI.
AND THE WITH JOE'S VOTE, JOE
WILL BE VOTING FOR JOE.
THIS HAS BEEN 29 DAYS COMING SO
I WANT TO TAKE A SECOND AND
MARINATE IN IT.
THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY, ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ
THE DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JOE.
ABI.
FISHBACH.
JOE.
TWO VOTES JOE.
ABI.
TWO VOTES ABI.
JAB.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ABI, TWO
VOTES JOE, ONE VOTE FISHBACH.
FISHBACH.
THAT'S TWO VOTES FISHBACH.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES FISHBACH, THREE
VOTES ABI, TWO VOTES JOE, ONE
VOTE LEFT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
>> WOW, NICE.
GREAT JOBS, GUYS.
GREAT BLINDSIDE.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
THAT WAS REALLY AWESOME.
>> GIRL, I TOLD YOU.
>> Jeff: FISHBACH, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE ONLY
PREDICTABLE THING ABOUT THIS
GAME HAS BEEN THE
UNPREDICTABILITY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
>> Jeff: TODAY WE BROUGHT YOUR
LOVE TO YOU.
FAMILY BRINGS EVERYONE'S SPIRITS
UP.
>> I'M READY.
>> Jeff: UNTIL IT ALL COMES
CRASHING DOWN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: MEDICAL, MEDICAL,
MEDICAL.
>> IS HE OKAY?
>> THEY'RE RIGHT HERE YOU, IN
GREAT HANDS.
>> CLEARLY I WAS BLINDSIDED.
I THOUGHT I HAD LOCKED UP THE
SPLIT BUT I THINK SPENCER MUST
HAVE TURNED.
INCH WAS SPLITTING THE VOTES, WE
COULD HAVE ALL VOTED FOR JOE.
I WENT OUT BIG.
I PLAYED THE VOTE STEAL AND IT'S
BEEN AWESOME.
I'VE HAD TREMENDOUS HIGHS.
I'VE HAD TERRIBLE LOWS.
AND I'M GRATEFUL FOR BOTH