translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Second chances
are never easy.
So many things depend on me.
My wife is pregnant.
I would like to see her belly grow.
Some struggled
to express their emotions.
When my girlfriend started saying
"I love you",
I didn't say it back.
I try to have feelings.
Others struggled
to stay alive.
If I don't win immunity,
I'm finished.
At the final immunity challenge,
Joe lost for the first time.
Spencer wins
individual immunity!
I don't have the necklace
and I'm really nervous.
On the field,
Stephen thought he could convince
everyone to eliminate Joe.
I've been trying to eliminate Joe
since day one.
But Spencer had her own plans.
Abi, if we don't vote Stephen,
I think Wentworth, you,
Keith and I are going to be in trouble.
At the council,
Spencer got satisfaction...
Eleventh person eliminated
and fifth member of our jury.
Wow. Attractive.
...shocking Jeremy, Tasha and Kimmi.
- The tribe has spoken.
- Thanks.
There are eight left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
- Great shot last night.
- That was crazy.
Didn't you think that would put
the souk in the different groups?
- Or do you think you can...?
- Yes, I thought about it.
The game is again very open.
For the 1st time, I made a move.
I took Stephen out by surprise.
But I can't
become the robot to play
who treats people like pawns.
Even if I don't want
to go all the way with Jeremy,
I doubtless have an interest
in maintaining our relationship.
I want to make sure
we're still okay.
It's the case.
I still trust you.
I didn't want Stephen to leave.
Now I feel in danger.
I'm not sure of anything anymore.
We're just gonna have to
figure out our positions.
It will be like before,
like picking up where we left off.
It's true.
These groups of votes
constantly fluctuate.
I do not like it.
I like to be in the center of everything
and know what's going on.
That's what I was thinking.
If Joe doesn't win,
- it will go away, clearly.
- Oh yes.
- Everyone is in.
- Yes !
After the advice
I felt
completely taken in.
I realized that I had to
take my destiny into my own hands.
So we take out Joe.
That leaves four wives.
The girls would have the hand.
I would love a women's wedding ring.
You see, we do
what everybody wants: Joe,
and before they realize it,
we have them.
- I mean...
- I'm so happy. I like.
- Really ?
- Yes, I am.
Without warning,
Kimmi offers me
a kind of feminine alliance.
If we take Joe out
and that the girls collaborate,
there's nothing Jeremy,
Keith or Spencer can do.
If one of the guys comes out,
there will be four women
- So it must be Joe.
- I agree.
So we can take out Spencer,
then Keith,
and at the end, Jeremy.
I didn't leave my family
to come here to play pawns.
I came to win.
It's time for me
to take action.
Over here, everyone!
Tasha, how does it
feel to last 30 days?
Jeff, to have lasted 30 days,
I feel fantastic.
Jeremy, how hard is it
to play a second time
and leave your life behind,
knowing that
"I am here for my family"?
I have no contact with my home,
I don't know what they do,
how are they...
Finally...
Wow, just talking about it...!
As you know,
an important part of Survivor
is visiting relatives.
And most of the time,
we bring
your loved ones to you.
Not always.
- Sometimes we do something else. - Shit !
Today, we will do
absolutely nothing else.
Today
we brought you love.
Oh my God !
I'm ready !
Jeremy.
This is your wife, Val.
Go get her!
It's a little boy.
It's a boy.
I knew it !
Val tells me, "It's a boy."
I will have a son!
It's crazy.
But I don't want others
to know just yet.
I don't think anyone had ever
run so fast towards their loved one.
Well...
In this game,
I constantly think of my family.
Nothing matters more.
Good. Val, take a seat over there.
- Jeremy, go back to your seat.
- I love you.
Say goodbye.
This is your cousin, Christina.
I can not believe !
This is...
- ...not true !
- I say !
We are more sisters
than cousins.
It's just... love.
It's love !
Oh my God !
All right, Christina,
take a seat next to Val.
Damn it ! Great !
Spencer, who would you like to see?
- My friend.
- OK.
Spencer has a girlfriend! Marcela!
Health !
- You're super skinny!
- I miss you so much !
Yeah Spence!
I like you.
Saying "I love you"
means a lot to me.
I have struggled with this since childhood.
It's like
I fought this difficulty
with so many people I loved.
And the fact of having said "I love you"
shows me that this change is real.
It's not artificial, it's true.
Because I really like Marcella.
Your mother came
during your first participation.
She is here again.
Vera, come!
- You are my mother and my best friend.
- Yes.
- Still.
Still.
He's my angel.
She's my angel, you know?
Well, join the others!
- I love you.
- Hello.
So, Keith, who do you want to see?
Keith wants Dana!
Come on, Big D!
Yes sir ! What's new ?
everybody ! It's her !
Damn it !
After that, everything is easy!
How did you meet each-other ?
He went to college
in Arkansas, where I'm from.
It's a boost
for each of us!
Alright, one last hug.
Alright, darling. I like you.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
This is your father, Dale!
Hi Dad !
Oh my God !
How does it feel to come back?
You participated in this game.
I got a whole new respect
for loved ones
who stay at home.
It's really painful,
especially knowing the hardness of the game.
But we come out better.
- Well, one last hug.
- Come on, Dad.
Joe, on your first time,
you told
as a child
you imagined making Survivor.
And that included
the appearance of your father
in a scene just like this.
But it didn't happen.
It happens now.
This is your father, Pat.
Come, Pat!
You did it !
You made my dream come true.
Look at me !
Joe, you clearly have
a very strong family connection.
Yeah, uh...
Family
is what matters most
in my life.
I want to thank you
for giving me this moment.
Give him a hug!
I like you.
Or a kiss! Even better !
Thank you !
Kimmi, you waited
more than anyone
have a loved one
visit you in Survivor.
Here is your father.
My dad ! My dad !
Oh my God ! My dad !
I did it !
I'm so proud!
Thank you dad !
It's the best gift
that my father
can be part of my dream.
One last hug.
- Good bye I love you !
- Thank you dad !
Okay I will try !
Good.
We have a
reward event to compete in.
Today,
you will have to dig
up bags in the sand.
Then you'll spin
around a pole
to pick up another bag,
which will make your head spin.
You will then cross a beam
where your last bag is.
With the parts
contained in the bags,
you will reconstruct a word.
The first person to find
wins the reward.
- Do you want to know what it is?
- Yes !
A good old fashioned American barbecue .
The winner will return to camp
with their loved one.
It is a
truly unique experience.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Well, on and go!
For a barbecue
and love!
Survivors, ready?
Come on, Spencer!
Looking for a rope.
When you have it, shoot it!
Kimmi has hers, as well as Joe.
When you see the first bag,
untie it!
Keith a le sien.
Kimmi at her temple.
Keith has his second bag.
Untie it, Keith!
- Joe has his second bag.
- Oops, sorry, Keith!
Jeremy has his first bag.
Jeremy has his second bag.
Kimmi leads.
Keith is right behind.
Come on Kimmi!
Kimmi is already spinning around the post.
Your head will spin very quickly .
Keith has his three bags.
Tasha has her third bag.
Joe has his third bag.
The faster you turn,
the faster you'll be done,
and the more confused you will be!
Come on, Tasha!
You need five bags in all.
Jeremy is now spinning.
Everyone's head is spinning.
Keith has his fourth bag.
Kimmi has her fourth bag.
Almost, Tasha, almost!
Kimmi can't move
so much it's spinning!
Keith gives it a shot.
Will it get there?
Nope ! He has to start over.
Your head is spinning
and you have four bags.
There is a fifth
to untie on the beam.
Kimmi has to try again.
Tasha has her four bags.
- My God !
- You're in on it, Kelley!
Kelley has his.
Spencer has his.
That's good, sweetie!
It's good for Keith,
attack the puzzle!
Take your time !
Keith now leads.
- Jeremy has his fifth.
- Take your time, Jeremy!
Come on Kelley!
Kelley has her fifth sack.
It's good for Joe.
Come on, Joe!
Abi falls, she has to start over.
Concentrate !
Spencer is on her fifth sack.
He has already made a comeback
in the final immunity challenge.
Can he do it again?
Spencer has her fifth bag.
Spencer is in on it.
I don't see what it is.
Looking for a word.
I don't see what it is, Jeff.
We have Joe, Keith, Spencer,
Your loved ones are there,
in Cambodia!
Tasha has her five bags,
she can attack.
Kimmi falls again.
which is great,
is that you can
suddenly find
and win without warning.
Stay focused, Kelley!
Abi thinks she has something,
she tries it.
Is she right?
Don't look at others,
do the job!
Wentworth thinks she has something,
she tries.
Abi spells a word.
Wentworth spells a word.
Everyone starts to panic,
what is it?
Wentworth places another block.
And another.
Spencer looks aside,
clueless about what it is.
“Food” is the word!
Wentworth wins the award!
Love with his father
and a barbecue on the camp!
I had gone on "redemption".
- Good boy !
You will return to the camp
where a splendid barbecue
awaits you.
You just have to
choose three teammates
and their loved ones,
to accompany you.
My God, Jeff!
It is too hard !
Come here, Big D!
- Brother.
- Brother !
Thank you so much, Kelley!
Kimmi has been talking about visiting relatives
for quite a while.
It's very hard for me,
but she really wanted to
see her father.
- Thanks.
- Sorry, folks.
There are four people left.
Choose one more.
I know how much that award
meant to Joe, so Joe.
Yeah, Joe!
I love you !
In other words,
Christina, Val, Marcella,
- we have to say goodbye to you.
- I love you !
I like you.
Good, you ten.
Go and enjoy
this unique experience,
- thanks to Wentworth.
- Thanks.
Tasha, Spencer, Jeremy,
I have nothing for you.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Enjoy.
Coming back to camp
with my father by my side,
and other relatives,
it was beautiful, so cool.
Everyone
was super excited to be there.
Cheers, Mom!
You are here, in Cambodia!
I can't believe it!
- [???]
- Nice to meet you, Joe!
Big D is here!
Who would have thought
that she would come to Cambodia?
Me ! I told
you you would bring her!
To see a member of his family,
especially his wife...
I don't know,
I need to see someone.
It doesn't matter if he's my
5th cousin on my father's side.
Any relative!
But Big D
was the ultimate reward.
Did you paint it?
Yeah, it took me a while.
You know, in your absence,
I thought of something
what i have to tell you,
because I'm not young anymore.
I never had a friend like you.
Really ?
When I was younger,
I didn't open up to people.
I have always been a loner.
Most...
You are such a good son, Joe.
You are my hero.
My friend.
When I was a kid,
with my father, we were close,
but he was not very affectionate.
He was a little...tough.
And he never really said
"I love you".
So that he can
share this with me,
it was really special.
I will remember it all my life.
I like you. Unconditionally.
Exactly.
What do you think of his choices?
It didn't really surprise me.
But it still sucks.
Kelley choosing
who was going to accompany him,
it was...
So many little strokes in the heart.
One, and another, and another...
I had never felt
so much grief.
I had to take a moment
for my head to regain control.
At this point, I only have one option:
get back into the game
and do everything possible
to win.
Surely you still have doubts
after the Stephen blow.
But it was against Stephen,
not against you.
But how do you see the rest?
What would you think
of us three in the final trio?
It suits me well.
- All three.
- I am on it.
Absolutely.
It's perfect.
I have an option: go with Spencer
and Jeremy to the final trio.
And on the other side,
the girls were talking
about a female alliance.
So I think I
have two viable options.
So what's next?
What do you think
of Joe's position?
Joe settles down quietly.
He could say:
“I played physically,
but also socially.
I was the most dangerous,
and I'm still here."
We have to do something.
At this stage,
how many chances
will we have to take Joe out?
I let an opportunity slip away,
because I had a big shot to play
and I needed his help.
But Joe is the type,
if you leave him a centimeter,
to take a kilometer.
If he takes off, I'm finished.
So for me, it is obvious
that at the first opportunity,
I have to get him out.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
- Yes.
First, Spencer,
I have to get it back.
I know you would like to keep it.
It is so nice !
- It will be again.
- I like this !
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will be
balancing a wooden statuette
on a pole.
Regularly,
we will lengthen the pole,
increasing the difficulty.
If the statuette falls, it is lost.
The last person to hold
gain immunity,
ensures a one in seven chance
of winning this game.
The losers: on the board,
someone will become
the sixth member of the jury.
And today...
He will be the first man
and the first wife.
Two people will have immunity.
Everyone's odds
just got better.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Let's go!
One over four ! Go on !
Well, on and go.
Take all of your first section.
Place your wooden statuette there,
hands at the bottom of the pole.
Put all your hands down.
Let's go.
Have everyone
add a pole section.
This will be your first test.
You must make the transition
holding
your statuette in place,
then place your hands all the way down.
So you have to
lift this pole.
Everyone
made the transition well.
We will add a pole section
every five minutes.
ELAPSED TIME:
20 Minutes
You now have
three meters of pole,
with a wooden statuette
above the head.
Remember it when it falls.
Don't stay below.
Kimmi loses her balance.
His statuette falls.
Kimmi is the first eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
No immunity for Kimmi.
Abi can't pull herself together.
Abi is eliminated.
There are only two women left.
et Tasha.
A man and a woman
will have more willpower than the others.
Who can last the longest?
ELAPSED TIME:
25 Minutes
Alright, let's add
a new boom section.
No sudden movement,
the game does not stop.
You will have all the time you need.
Here we go, go!
Tasha fails
to transition.
Tasha is eliminated.
Kelley Wentworth
wins individual immunity.
She'll be safe
at council tonight.
And just behind,
Spencer loses his statuette.
Jeremy does not survive the transition.
Jeremy loses his statuette.
Many things at once.
There are only two left, Keith and Joe,
trying
to make the transition.
Let's go, guys!
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and.
Here we go again,
with Keith and Joe.
For immunity.
We are now
at 4.2 meters of pole.
Wentworth already has immunity.
Who will be
safe like her tonight,
on the board?
Will it be Keith?
Or will it be Joe?
ELAPSED TIME:
30 Minutes
Well, it's time
to add a new section.
Let's go.
Catch
your last section of pole.
But if the statuette falls
during the transition, it's over.
I will count.
Lots of movement at Joe.
Lots of movement in Keith.
Both still hold.
Let's go.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and.
Hold on, Keith!
Here we are.
And now we are waiting for the end.
Almost five meters of pole,
to maintain a small statuette
in balance,
to take one more step
to victory
and the million dollars.
Things are moving a lot
at Joe now.
The pole leans enormously.
Joe, nice recovery.
We had to give everything,
this pole was going to fall.
It leans a
lot again with Keith.
Can he straighten it out?
And he does!
We think it's over
and the two men counterattack.
Your neck is sore.
Your body is tired.
You're mentally exhausted,
but you can't give up.
It's too much tension!
ELAPSED TIME:
1 Hour 20 Minutes
This ordeal has now lasted
for 1 hour and 20 minutes.
It's long.
You look straight up,
to balance a statuette
at the end of a long pole.
- What ? Nope !
- Keith wins individual immunity!
He is fine ?
Doctor ! Doctor !
Doctor !
- What ?
- He is fine ?
Joe! He is fine ?
- Oh my God !
-Joe!
He is fine ?
Free up space for doctors!
Oh, my God, he passed out!
Oh my God !
The doctor is there,
you are in good hands.
- Very good hands.
- Oh my God !
Can you hear me, Joe?
- He fainted.
- It's scary.
He didn't want that.
Take his blood pressure.
Joe, the medical team is here.
They take care of you, my friend.
Gently.
Dr. Joe, just so we can follow,
what's going on here?
He's exhausted his energy reserves in
the last hour.
There is a lack of sugar in the blood.
His body couldn't hold on any longer.
- He collapsed.
- My legs went numb.
Alright, Joe. Stay calm.
Can we get
some shade for him?
Can we bring an umbrella?
Joe, are you feeling better enough
to realize what happened?
Yeah.
I blacked out,
that's all I remember.
I wanted to win so badly!
I love this game.
I want to play
it as hard as I can.
I believe this effort has proven that.
Your legs gave out.
It's your body
trying to bring you down,
to get horizontal,
to bring blood to the brain.
What is happening now.
I think it will be fine.
So Joe, the good news,
According to Dr. Joe,
is that even
if you feel very bad,
you do not risk
being removed from the game.
It is temporary.
You already look much better.
Let's go slowly, step by step.
I will sit down.
I went to immunity
thinking I'd win
and I find myself on my back,
wondering what happened.
I risk
being eliminated from the board again.
- Well done, Joe!
- Yeah, Joe!
There is no security
in Survivor.
It's a tough situation for me.
The game continues.
A great effort,
that all these emotions
should not make us forget.
You will be safe at the council,
no risk of leaving.
Well-deserved ! You are safe.
No risk of leaving.
I have to tell you, all of you.
When we came up with the idea
for Second Chance Survivor,
that's what we hoped for.
A group of people
ready to surpass themselves
as they would never dare
at home,
in their normal lives.
Take your things,
return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Well done, everyone!
It was crazy.
- Nice duel!
- It was creepy.
Sit down and rest.
No doubt, yeah.
My last memory,
it is to have seen stars.
And then, just... "I'm going to fall."
The immunity test
was like a crazy football match.
Gender Brazil - Germany.
And watch Amazing Joe lose
against a 52 year old guy...
It was great!
Now his time has come.
Kimmi really wants
to make a girls alliance.
Oh really ?
Oh my God !
And Tasha is in.
The wind has turned.
So we eliminate Joe,
and then we'll decide
what's best for us.
Let Joe give himself
until he faints,
it's frightening.
I can't fight this.
So he has to go.
And when we get it out,
the girls will have control.
- You want to discuss ?
- Yup.
- You can get up ?
- Yeah.
Right now it sucks '
cause I don't have the immunity
and I'm exhausted.
But I went to the last board
without the necklace
and I'm still here.
So I'm pretty confident
I can do it again.
At this point I wonder
who is most likely
to just make it to the end.
Without a doubt:
Think about it. Everyone wants
to sit by his side.
And on every vote
where she's not eliminated,
the risk
of it reaching the end increases.
It's true.
Fighting
him would be easy money.
Exactly.
I want real players
to go all the way.
I hear well.
At the end of the day,
I need Abi out.
And Jeremy is smart.
So I think it will take.
And I think it took.
What do you want to do ?
Because it would be easy
to say, "Let's go Joe!"
Do we do this or do we go after Abi?
That's the thing.
The girls want to make
a female alliance.
But you have to trust me.
It will not arrive.
I've been faithful since day 1.
And I will remain.
I planned to eliminate Joe
and Tasha tells me about
this girl's alliance project.
Oh my God !
Are you nervous about this
girl alliance thing?
- I'm not nervous.
- I tell you...
- It's so quiet right now...
- I know.
It's pretty quiet.
It's never that easy.
I spoke to Jeremy and Spencer
about the girl's alliance.
I didn't want to risk
let them learn it
from someone else,
because it would create mistrust.
But I only made
them suspicious
which could mean trouble.
This female alliance thing
is making me nervous.
What do you think ?
I'm worried either way.
If we keep Joe, I'm terrified.
If we take Joe out, I'm terrified.
Oh my God.
The problem,
I'm not
100% convinced
that Tasha
's idea of ​​the final trio
includes us, Jeremy and me.
Tasha might think to herself:
"I can beat an Abi.
I can beat a Kimmi.
I can beat Wentworth."
So we have to nip
this female alliance in the bud.
If we can get Keith
and we still have Joe...
But who is the fifth?
We need Tasha.
We must be sure of her on this one.
If these girls take control,
Spencer and I are done for.
Game over for us.
Have Tasha on my side
is therefore crucial.
I don't trust
these girls.
Alright, so we're taking Abi out.
Joe stays in the game
and he wins all...
Do you think he'll win it all?
You couldn't beat him today.
Neither does Spencer.
Joe escaped a tip
and I don't want
it to escape to another.
But at this point, it's a dead end.
What was this confabulation?
Do people still vote for Joe?
No... I know Tasha, yes.
100 %.
I don't want to go to the council
without knowing what will happen.
We have to come to an agreement.
We're going to make
a million dollar decision.
It makes me extremely nervous.
Now here are the members of the jury.
Ciera
and Fishbach,
eliminated at the last council.
Joe, one of the most dramatic moments in all of Survivor,
today,
when you collapsed.
How do you feel ?
How are you.
I'm clearly not on top.
I'm used to giving it my all,
in sport, but nothing like it.
It is a lesson in humility.
I too have my limits.
Kimmi, how did you feel
seeing that?
The battle between the two
was epic.
It was stunning to watch.
And seeing someone break down
is scary.
realizing
that he was going to recover,
How fast does
your brain say to itself:
"Let's be honest, it's a game." ?
Yes, well,
that crosses your mind, of course.
He remained standing
until he passed out.
He could do that
in any hardship
and reach the end
by defeating us all.
Everyone must have thought of this:
"Damn, this guy is ready to pass out
to win an event!"
Jeremy, are you also able
to say, "Back to game mode,
he doesn't have immunity."
Yes, as soon as you are reassured about his fate,
you say to yourself:
"Well, Joe doesn't have immunity.
Shall we take him out?"
But you have a strategy
and she won't change
because Joe doesn't have immunity.
You don't have to wear blinders,
because the next votes
will be crucial.
- Crucial.
And, Jeremy, that's where the bill
groups of votes,
preferred to alliances,
starts to climb.
Because a covenant,
in theory, we can
more or less count on it.
Voting groups,
as you explained,
change every day.
Voting groups are cool,
but at a certain point,
like now,
when we get down to business,
you have to choose an alliance.
Because we don't want to end up
at the bottom of a group of votes
in the last part of the game.
What does it imply
as we prepare to vote?
I think everyone knows
who is in danger.
Do you
think everyone knows that?
I always feel like I am,
so I'll say I am.
Abi. Why ?
With every advice,
I feel at the bottom of the ladder
because of my connection
to Wentworth and Ciera.
I think it will continue
to haunt us.
I think you are dangerous,
because everyone
would like to take you to the end.
She is ideally placed
to survive this vote,
and to the next, and to the next...
And yet, she is still there.
I'm far from sure
not to leave tonight.
It's a possibility.
But see, she stands very straight,
happy as a rooster.
Spencer, Joe brings up the subject
people who would be dragged into the final
because they couldn't win.
They still take
a place in the final trio.
- Potentially yours.
- Exactly.
When the person you would love
to have by your side at the end
doesn't actually help you
get to the final trio,
it becomes a problem.
Abi, what will happen tonight?
Is it all wind,
because we already know what's going to happen?
There is mold.
And it affects other players.
We have to get rid
of the bad apple.
what will happen tonight?
I hope the people I told
that I will do
what I said I would do
will stick to this plan
and we will move forward.
Otherwise,
it will
go boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
The most dangerous,
one after the other.
Four is enough
after this vote.
If you don't have a fully trustworthy quartet ,
you will be 8th, 7th, 6th.
Good. It's time to vote.
Wentworth, over to you.
You are musty. You must leave.
And please change your haircut.
I feel terrifying
that this vote will determine
whether I will win or not.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
A vote Joe,
One vote Abi, one vote Tasha.
Joe. Two votes Joe.
Joe. That's three votes Joe,
One vote Abi, one vote Tasha.
Twelfth person eliminated
and sixth member of our jury...
Joe. Bring me your torch.
Joe, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck to everyone.
Especially boys.
It's time to go.
The question for this board
seems to be:
Was an alliance
formed tonight
or was it just the perfect opportunity
to release a dangerous player?
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
After a big surprise elimination,
Jeremy and Spencer are worried.
I'm really concerned.
We are in a mess.
My game escapes me.
But betrayal
isn't the only danger in Survivor.
- How are you ?
- I need help !
I have no regrets.
I don't think I could have
done anything better.
I played as best I could.
I had a blast
and achieved many goals.
Just to have been able
to bring my father,
it was a million dollar experiment .
It's thanks to the fans.