translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
At the last immunity test,
Joe gave it all and lost.
He is fine ?
Doctor ! Doctor !
After his discomfort,
Joe was fighting
to survive in the game.
For every vote
where Abi is not eliminated,
the risk of it reaching the end
increases.
It's true.
But the women wanted to eliminate
the most dangerous.
Joe can say:
"I was the most dangerous,
and I'm still here."
We have to do something.
Fearing a female alliance,
Jeremy and Spencer faced
a difficult decision.
If we keep Joe, I'm terrified.
If we take Joe out, I'm terrified.
At the board,
Keith was left out of it .
when Jeremy and Spencer
voted with the women,
sending Joe to the jury.
Joe, the tribe has spoken.
With ever fewer people
and an absence of alliances,
uncertainty is at its peak.
There are seven left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Good advice.
This board was a real show.
Joe was eliminated.
- It's better that way.
- Yes it's better.
He had the change of his coin!
No one has
much sympathy for Joe there.
Everyone is very happy
that he is gone
with arms and baggage.
You know what ? Good riddance !
Hey, now we all have a chance
to win events!
- Marvellous !
- It's cool.
That's exciting.
I hadn't thought of that.
We can all win events
now.
I was a bit shocked.
I was left out of it.
They fired Joe.
It was a good time for that.
I wish I had known.
I want to date Tasha.
So I have to talk
to a few people.
What were the votes?
Two... Wait.
One Tasha, two Abi, five for him.
Six for him.
Keith decided to vote for me.
So I'll keep an eye on it,
' cause he's the last
one I want to see ally with the boys
or some of the girls.
Keith stuck
a target on his back.
- Day 33, Kels!
- Bravo, my hen!
Who would've believed that ?
Three of the original Hunahpu.
- Yes, it's crazy.
- In the last 7.
- You believe it ?
- I can not believe.
- Who would've believed that ?
- Not me.
- I say !
- It makes me quite happy.
There are 7 people left.
At this point, every decision
can affect your strategy.
So I don't close myself to anything.
I have to preserve my options.
That's what I've been doing all along.
It's a good position,
but it's also a little stressful,
because what is the right choice?
For the moment, I ignore it.
Well...
- What do you think of last night?
- I am very concerned.
I have serious regrets.
Very serious.
Do you think we're in trouble?
Oh yes. We are in a mess.
At the last council,
I released a god of trials: Joe.
Now I gotta hope
there's a group of 4 for me,
because it is the new magic number,
with seven players.
Tasha worries me.
Yeah. Me too.
It could be dangerous.
We have to make sure of his loyalty.
Otherwise, we're screwed.
Next, we need to make
sure Kimmi is with us.
Otherwise, we're screwed.
It's ridiculous.
With Jeremy, we realized
that a feminine alliance
could sweep us away,
even though Tasha told me:
"Honestly, my idea of ​​the final trio,
it's you and Jeremy."
But if the girls' story
is real,
I have no options.
And I don't want to play again
from the bottom of the ladder.
It's exhausting, demoralizing,
I feel my game slipping away.
It's always scary.
I hope I can stay the course
to the finish line.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Yes !
- Yeah !
Today
you will be tied to a rope.
On my signal, you will unroll it.
When you think you've had enough,
you'll put together a bridge.
Then, with sandbags,
you will knock down blocks.
The first person to finish
wins the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes !
The winner will leave for Siem Reap,
to the temples
where your journey began
33 days ago.
You will be blessed by the monks,
enjoy
delicious food
and spend the night in the temples.
This is truly a unique opportunity
to do something
exceptional.
Damn it !
This event was contested
for the 1st time in season 29.
Keith had won.
A 2nd chance for Keith
to win again.
We draw your places
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
First step: unwind the rope
until you think you
have enough to go all the way.
Sneaking through these corners
is very difficult
trying
to give slack to the rope.
This rope will be with you
all the way.
Nothing is easy in Survivor,
especially on the 33rd day.
Spencer rushes,
hoping to have enough.
Keith leaves in turn.
Tasha follows suit,
like Jeremy.
Wentworth arrives with his rope.
Kimmi gathers hers again.
Aby too.
We go to the second step:
build a bridge, step by step.
Keith and Spencer are side by side.
Then comes Jeremy, then Tasha.
Abi still gathers her rope.
She is left behind
in this event.
A question arises :
do they have enough rope
to go to the end?
It's now Jeremy, Keith,
Jeremy and Keith are side by side
in this event.
Spencer tries to stay in the game.
Keith came by,
he's going to throw his bags.
Jeremy doesn't have enough rope.
He finished his bridge.
Big drop!
A nice throw from Keith.
They must completely
disappear from the table.
The moment of truth.
Does Keith have enough rope
to retrieve his bags?
Eh yes !
Spencer passed.
Jeremy tries to untangle his rope.
Rope management
comes into play,
as expected.
Another shot on goal for Keith.
Spencer tries to retrieve her bags.
He doesn't have enough rope.
Spencer needs to go back to the start
and take more rope.
Which clears the way for Keith,
who throws sack on sack,
continuing to knock down blocks.
Tasha crossed her bridge,
she can throw bags.
It's between Keith and Tasha.
Spencer returns,
attempting to bring more rope.
Tasha needs to collect bags
and she is way off.
Jeremy is back, he throws.
Can he go up?
Two come down.
Another nice throw for Keith.
And another !
Keith only has two blocks left!
Jeremy is still shooting.
He's out of bags,
does he have enough rope?
He doesn't have enough rope.
Keith could win a second time.
And it's done!
Keith does it again
and wins the individual award!
A return to Siem Reap!
Well done, Keith!
Keith, come here!
Nice victory.
The only person to have
won this event. Twice !
I really like that !
You will leave today
for Siem Reap,
these magnificent temples.
Choose a person
to accompany you.
This is where the game
gets very interesting again.
Oh my God !
I thought about it all along.
Kelley helped me, I'm helping him.
Oh my God !
Thank you very much, Keith!
She chose us, my wife
and Kimmi,
and Abi and...
Uh... so...
Keith, you can bring
one more person.
- You don't even look!
- Spencer, come on!
Why Spencer?
No real logic.
I still go back
to when we could go,
and I look at Jeremy, he...
You know,
he's been married for 12 or 15 years,
Val and him are serious.
I forget his name...
Tasha.
Tasha's little cousin , but...
Spencer, it's still new...
His girlfriend...
She came all the way here
and he couldn't see her for 5 minutes.
I take him.
If it seems logical,
hooray for me.
Otherwise, too bad for my apple.
- That's Keith Nale's logic.
- Keith Nale and his ramblings.
you look a little frustrated.
Oh no !
Whether I'm in reward
or on the camp,
I take every opportunity.
Sometimes be on camp
is as advantageous
as being a reward.
So get to work!
Keith was exhausted, I understand that.
But he couldn't even remember
my name!
Not
to mention explaining his reasoning.
Is he really playing the southerner
who is just there for the trip?
Or is he really that dumb?
afternoon and night
should be amazing.
Tasha, Abi,
I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
The rest of you,
enjoy your reward!
- Congratulations, Keith!
- Thanks.
Keith, Spencer and I are going
for this incredible reward.
I must try
to take advantage of these two.
I haven't had a strong alliance
in the whole game.
And in this game, you need allies,
to a certain extent.
Or at least trusted people.
Because... It's essential.
- A great test.
- In effect.
It would have been a great reward.
Keith is impressive
in the trials.
Keith is strong.
In effect.
He is very underrated.
He's the new child prodigy.
What do you have in mind?
What do you want to do ?
Y'all think
Keith should be next?
- Yes.
- Me too.
Because if we keep
losing the trials...
It is a problem.
It's the 33rd day
and I have to reach the 39th.
I want to appear
like a puppet to take to the end,
that's why
they might want to take me.
Using people
is key in this game.
And I love to see them wrestling,
and scheming,
and lose your mind.
Why not ?
I am a villain.
Bad guys have more fun.
What are your reservations
about Keith?
I don't really have any.
So what's the problem ?
The problem,
it's because you still dread
an alliance between girls.
It stays in the back of your mind.
So let's talk about it.
It is totally false.
I trust you.
If the girls all say,
"Let's get Keith out!"...
It is an option.
But I have regrets,
we should have kept Joe and fired Abi.
I'm not going to get upset that I
didn't leave as a reward.
I will eat on the 39th day.
Give me that breakfast
and let me explain to the jury
why I deserve the million.
That's all I want.
Keith has to go.
We have to play this shot like that.
It's only for two days.
You won't have all the control.
I understand,
you want to reach the final,
but you can
only do it with people you trust.
And you can trust me!
At this point,
Jeremy needs to let go a bit,
let me have a shot.
And if he says "no",
I'll find someone else.
People had better get on board
or they'll stay at the quay,
because Fox takes off!
Watch your feet!
The last time we were there,
we didn't look the same.
It's certain ! Oh my God !
Now
we are as disintegrated as that.
It's clear.
I have never seen a
better reward.
Cambodian temples...
It's incredible
to the point of slapping me
every two minutes.
I hallucinate to be here, to see this.
It feels like
Raiders of the Lost Ark.
It's true.
Indiana Jones
probably came here.
33 days ago
I walked through this place
and an incredible adventure
awaited me.
Now come back here
and see these temples,
while I do what
I wanted to do with this 2nd chance:
show through this game
how much I have changed
and use it to win.
It pumps me up more than necessary
for the last six days.
If I am asked:
"Hey, where has Keith been for
the past 30 days?
In a temple in Cambodia
or in a shuttle
returning from Mars?"
I would answer: "He came back from Mars,
he couldn't be in Cambodia."
To say if it's amazing.
It is really impressive.
You don't see that every day.
Frankly, I don't see
how we could do better.
We had this
very cultural experience.
I would never have done this otherwise.
Of all the awards,
this one was tops.
That's wonderful.
My journey in this game
has not been ideal,
I've been
at the bottom of the ladder a lot,
so with this 2nd chance,
I want to prove that I can do it.
And so close to the end of the game, it's...
I'm almost there !
In Cambodia!
To the incredible things
that surround us!
What was that called?
Do you know what we call
this dance, these dancers?
Oh my God !
It looks so good !
Here we are !
Some wine ? Some spaghetti ?!
Keith Nale, thank you very much!
Oh my God !
Sit down!
What do you think is going on at camp
?
- They're trying to recruit Abi?
- She's not mad, is she?
- After today, surely, yes.
- But no.
- She won't go with...
- Jeremy?
Jeremy, Tasha and Kimmi,
seriously?
There will be no problem with Abi.
As a reward with Spencer and Keith,
it's the perfect time
to see where they are.
I want to reach the final trio.
That's the goal of the game.
If you said "final trio" to me,
that would be fine with me.
To me too. It would be fantastic.
You just have to make it happen.
It's possible.
We're close,
just a few days away.
Exactly.
When you're in reward,
with so few people in play,
you're probably going to
make a final threesome deal.
Wentworth, Keith and I
made a pact
to go to the final.
But it's too early to determine me
for a trio or another.
If I had to choose, I would love to
face Abi and Keith.
The thing is,
you have to make it happen.
Who do you think
of for the next votes?
I'm disappointed: Jeremy.
Jeremy might be ideal
to come out second,
because they might expect it.
We should start with Tasha.
Next, Jeremy.
We could use Abi
to have the majority.
Cheers, Keith!
Use this foursome and fire Tasha.
I want Tasha gone.
Now it's serious.
Everything is fine,
as long as our 4th is feeling well,
is a wise and rational player
who will make the right decisions
for the group.
The problem is that our 4th is Abi.
Which is none of that.
We will wake up on the 38th day,
us and Abi.
I say.
Do you mind
if I go talk to Jeremy?
Can I put the rice there?
Yeah.
We are taking care of it.
Talk as much as you want.
I don't want any discomfort.
This is how.
I would prefer to be included,
but if you don't want...
We can do both.
Tasha asked if I was okay
with her talking to Jeremy.
But it takes four people there,
to return the game.
And I think I have
more aces up my sleeve than Jeremy.
It annoys me. Go chat.
No, there is no rush.
We'll go later.
We're just going to relax.
No problem.
Is Abi Scorpio?
Scorpios are crazy.
I have two at home.
That's why I suck.
What did I miss?
I don't know how you do it.
Can you imagine going
out with this girl?
I can't even imagine it.
We have to be careful
with everything we say with Abi.
I've come too far
to let Abi-Maria Gomes
ruin my game.
I don't think
we start with Keith.
How about starting with Abi?
What about the threat that is Keith
in the trials, then?
You will all have to do well
in the tests.
But Abi is the shot to play.
We can't risk a mess
as the final approaches.
Keith is a credible danger,
but Abi is very volatile.
If I say something wrong,
if I make a joke that's wrong,
she could ruin my game.
She will switch sides
in the blink of an eye.
What's the point
of trying to go all the way
if you don't trust
your partners?
It's the last big shot
we can make.
If we screw up this vote, we're finished.
Tasha said,
"How about we take Abi out?"
That would be one less girl
to worry about.
So I like this idea.
You think Spencer
is with us for sure.
- Me, I...
- Definitely.
Let's see what he will say.
Tasha has her doubts about Spencer.
She's not sure
he's strong.
It is possible for him to change sides.
He could tell
Kelley and Keith anything
and ruin our plan.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for today's challenge?
- Yeah !
First,
I need to get the two necklaces.
- OK.
- Thank you, Keith.
One will suffice today.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will overcome
a series of obstacles on the water.
At the end, you will collect a key
and come back.
With this key you will open
a chest full of puzzle pieces
and solve a
five-piece puzzle.
Who finishes first wins immunity
and ensures a one in six chance
of winning this game.
The losers: on the board,
someone will become
the seventh member of the jury.
2nd chance today
it's the puzzle.
In the first event
of our 30th season,
it was one of 3 puzzles to choose from.
Nobody chose it.
The 2nd chance therefore concerns the puzzle,
which can finally be resolved.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity and insurance
to have a one in six chance!
Survivors, ready?
All ways are good
to attack these obstacles!
Everyone is in on it.
Jeremy and Spencer took the lead.
If you fall,
you have to start over the obstacle.
Jeremy and Spencer, side by side.
This is Keith and Wentworth.
You should be careful.
This ordeal will do damage.
Spencer has fallen, he has to go back!
Jeremy will be the first in the water.
All the others are far behind.
Kimmi and Abi bring up the rear.
Ahead !
Spencer is back.
Big fall for Keith.
Jeremy is at his buoy,
trying to grab the key.
Kimmi takes a big fall.
Keith is in the water.
When you have the key, come back!
Ahead !
Tasha struggles to keep up.
Jeremy and Spencer lead.
Keith and Wentworth
are right behind.
Spencer is fast in the water.
Jeremy and Spencer
arrive at the same time.
Spencer regained a
lot of time in the water.
Spencer leads now.
35 days brought you here.
What you do now
will bring you to the 36th day.
It all happens there.
Kimmi and Abi return.
Tasha is still on her buoy.
Spencer gives it her all.
Jeremy is on his heels.
Meet Keith!
Spencer takes a big hit!
How are you ?
Spencer has to back off,
giving Jeremy an opportunity.
Spencer took it right in the chin!
Spencer passed.
Forward, Keith!
This puzzle has only five pieces,
it can be resolved in an instant.
Coming first
can make the difference.
That's what you're here for!
To see what you are worth!
Tasha is still struggling.
It's Jeremy
This is Wentworth,
Help and Kimmi.
Tasha is still in the water,
struggling.
Only five pieces in this puzzle.
When you find,
it will be instantly.
And it will be over immediately.
It's not lost yet
because there is no question
of gaining ground here.
It's a puzzle
that you solve at once,
what Spencer just did!
Spencer wins
individual immunity,
solving the puzzle
in less than 15 seconds!
Unbelievable !
A one in six chance
for Spencer.
Security !
Security ! Go get Tasha!
I need help !
Medical team, forward!
I swallowed a lot of water.
Be still for a moment.
Do you hurt somewhere?
- I have trouble breathing.
- Relax.
Was it just swimming?
You didn't bump?
I was just out of energy.
I had a hard
time and I kept drinking the cup.
Inhale deeply.
The medical team is there,
they will take care of her.
Don't worry, everything will be fine.
Tasha, it's Jeff.
You are in very good hands.
So, doc?
Apparently Tasha was in the water.
Purely and simply exhausted,
she couldn't hold on any longer.
When we start to drink the cup,
we get scared, panic sets in.
Is that what happened to you, Tasha?
It'll be OK.
His oxygen level is good.
His lungs look good too.
There is no water in it.
She is in no danger.
No problem with his lungs.
I think it will be fine.
When you're ready,
we'll bring you back.
- I am ready.
- It's certain ?
OK.
You scared me.
I scared myself.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
What's going on ?
I think we're all exhausted.
35 days, even the small
daily gestures...
- It's frightening.
- ...cost you.
How do you feel,
after going through this,
knowing that it will be ok,
but still
calming down?
It's frustrating.
We all give everything we have,
and I had nothing left.
Can we finish the other part
of this story,
namely a huge
Spencer win?
Sure.
- You stay seated, huh?
- Yeah.
Spencer, come here!
I have to tell you.
We tested this puzzle a lot.
No one has ever finished
it so quickly.
Never.
It was amazing. Congratulation.
You're safe
tonight at the council.
You are guaranteed to have
a one in six chance of winning.
As for you,
someone is going to leave tonight.
Tasha, you're surrounded
by a firefighter t-shirt
and the two firefighters holding it.
It shows the camaraderie
of this group.
And yet tonight
in a few hours,
someone will be eliminated.
The game never stops.
Only one certainty tonight:
it won't be you.
Congratulation.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council. Cheer.
Tasha almost drowned.
She swallowed a ton of seawater.
It can happen very quickly.
But with Spence and Kelley,
we talked about it, at the reward.
We're recruiting Abi, that's four.
And boom Tasha,
boom Kimmi, boom Jeremy.
And we meet at four. Easy !
- Well done, my daughter.
- Oh thank you.
- How are you ?
- Better.
You're going to have
to tell me about the ordeal!
I missed it.
In the immunity test,
my mind tells me "swim!",
as it would say "live!",
and I feel like I'm drowning,
I drink the cup.
It's very scary.
- Did you sink?
- Several times.
My legs wouldn't move.
I'm already not
the best swimmer.
I'm from the Midwest.
I'm comfortable in the pool,
but the ocean is something else.
And I lost my footing.
I'm going to put
my mind to it.
She got scared.
She needs to walk a bit
to think about it.
- It is understandable.
- Yes, it's scary.
At this point,
I'm very nervous for tonight.
Because I suspect
that Wentworth, Keith and Spencer
may have bonded over the reward.
I have to make sure
that Spencer is still
with Jeremy, Kimmi and me.
Because Abi has to go.
- I have not changed my mind.
- Tasha?
We four?
I know you have
some unity.
We can count...
- ...on the 4 of us, I think.
- All 4 together.
We all agree.
If there are four of us,
the rest doesn't matter.
As long as we're close.
- It suits you ?
- Very well.
- Everything is fine ?
- As long as... None of us...
As long as I stay,
that's all that matters, in the end.
I should just think
about who to take to the final at this point.
- Four is enough.
- It's solid...
I shouldn't come stalking you
in Chicago, huh? Or you ?
Or you in Brazil?
- Everything is fine.
- You'll never find me.
I just have to reach the final.
And my resume
has grown a bit, too.
Here's the plan.
We can't leave Wentworth, Abi
- et Keith ...
- Keith.
...go until the end.
- That would be an abomination.
- In this season.
In another season,
maybe, you bring a puppet.
In this season
it would be doing a disservice
to the fans who chose us,
- to all the great strategies...
- It was a great game.
...to surprise eliminations...
Why...?
- If it's the final trio... Seriously?
- Really ?
Alright, seriously.
It's Abi.
What do you think ?
I wanna do what I said
what makes sense to me:
play with you.
- Were you able to talk to Kimmi?
- Oh yeah.
- So that's the plan?
- On the 39th day, friends.
- Let's go.
- On the 39th day.
I've been controlling my destiny in this game
for quite a while
and I don't want to give it up.
So tonight at council,
my two options are:
go with Kimmi, Jeremy and Tasha
and target these weak players
that everyone wants to take to the end,
like Abi.
- It better be 4 "Abi".
- There's interest.
It better
be 4 "Abi", damn.
My other option is to go
with Wentworth, Abi and Keith
and eliminate the big shots.
Praying to go all the way
with these dream puppets.
It's a breaking point.
The last seven.
It is a point of no return.
Now here are the members of the jury.
Ciera,
and Joe, eliminated at the last council.
Let's start with the reward.
Keith, you win
your second straight individual event.
Big reward,
a return to where it all began,
to the temples of Siem Reap.
Right where it all started.
We were able to eat
in a thousand-year-old temple.
It never happens!
We don't do better.
Spencer, how was it?
It's quite a unique experience.
Oh yeah.
That's the kind of reward
that makes you feel a connection
to the country where you play.
On the one hand, Keith chooses you,
you and Wentworth,
and this friendly trio
enjoys a great reward.
But four people
remain in the camp.
Yeah. great experience,
but I won't lie,
I wondered what was going on,
what I was missing.
That's a lot of time away from camp.
Tasha,
the other big event to discuss,
it was during today's event,
you were a little overwhelmed in the water
and had to be rescued.
How are you now?
It was tough all day.
And I imagine that after such a dose
of adrenaline and energy,
back at camp,
you must have been exhausted.
Exhausted, mentally, physically.
I tried to look good...
I thought I was drowning.
It's frightening.
what impact does such an event
have on the game?
Any event in Survivor
is an opportunity for change.
Kimmi, was there
any talk about idols?
The subject always comes up.
We say to ourselves: "She could be there,
are there enough of us
to vote one way
while having a plan B
in case an idol comes out?"
Keith, Kimmi said something
that I have rarely heard on the board.
"Are there enough of us?"
Which implies a group.
I think this vote will put us
back where we need to be.
Spencer, again: "we",
"where We must be".
Yes. I'm officially
in the "we" club.
Jeremy.
and Spencer says,
"Yeah, I'm a 'we' too."
I was at camp today
and I saw about
five clusters of votes.
So there are five "us".
Everyone is in a "we".
Tasha, are you okay?
There are 4 or 5 groups of "us"?
At this point, I believe many
are keeping doors open.
But focusing on it
they may be missing opportunities
to concrete something,
because if you have a concrete "we",
it will be more favorable
for all "us".
Is anyone here
really confident
in the idea that his "we"
will establish his domination?
I'm pretty confident.
My "we" will establish its dominance.
- I love this franchise.
- Let's go! It's time to vote!
Spencer,
does that make you shake your head?
I admire his confidence.
Because I'm still very nervous.
This necklace is great for tonight,
but if my "we" doesn't prevail,
it is hardly useful for tomorrow.
Jeremy.
How much confidence do you have
in your "we" tonight?
In which "we"?
Abi, when you hear that,
does it bother you
or excite you?
It's exciting, cause I wonder
which "we"
I myself should choose.
I like to take risks,
so we'll see.
"We will see.
It's time to find out which "we" will
assert their dominance tonight.
It's time to vote.
Abi, over to you.
Sorry, I just want to
be here again tomorrow.
We'll see what comes of it.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Abi.
Tasha. Equality.
Two Abi votes, two Tasha votes.
Abi.
That's three votes Abi,
two votes Tasha.
two Tasha votes, one Keith vote,
one vote left.
Fourteenth person eliminated
and seventh member of our jury...
Abi. Bring me your torch.
Good luck to you.
Abi, the tribe has spoken.
Good game.
It's time to go.
Another surprise elimination.
The perfect introduction
to what could be
the most unpredictable conclusion
in Survivor history.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time
in the Survivor finale.
- You don't give anything.
- You neither !
So close to the end
no one will give up
their 2nd chance without a fight.
All that matters now
is to survive.
They won't expect it.
Come to council tonight! Buy
a ticket! It could be epic!
For the first time
in 31 seasons...
Join us for the final
and the live reunion,
December 16.
I really didn't think I was leaving.
The only time
I feel safe
I am taken out by surprise.
I will be at the final board
and I'll decide
who wins a million dollars.
It was a great experience.
I think I have matured
and I don't have to be
with these freaks anymore!