>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": SECOND CHANCES ARE
NEVER EASY.
>> I GOT SO MUCH RIDING ON ME.
MY WIFE IS PREGNANT.
I WANT TO BE THERE TO SEE IT
GROW.
>> Jeff: SOME WERE STRUGGLING
WITH THEIR EMOTIONS.
>> WHEN MY GIRLFRIEND STARTING
SAYING LIKE, "I LOVE YOU," I
DIDN'T SAY IT BACK.
I'M TRYING TO HAVE FEELINGS.
>> Jeff: WHILE OTHERS WERE
FIGHTING TO STAY ALIVE.
>> IF I DON'T WIN IMMUNITY, I'M
GONE.
>> Jeff: AT THE IT LAST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, JOE LOST FOR
THE FIRST TIME.
>> Jeff: SPENCER WINS
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
>> I DON'T HAVE THAT NECKLACE,
AND I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
>> Jeff: BACK AT CAMP, STEPHEN
THOUGHT HE COULD GET EVERYONE ON
BOARD TO VOTE OUT JOE.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO TAKE
OUT JOE SINCE DAY ONE.
>> Jeff: BUT SPENCER HAD PLANS
OF HIS OWN.
>> ABI, IF WE DON'T VOTE FOR
STEPHEN, I THINK YOU AND
WENTWORTH AND I AND KEITH ARE IN
A LOT OF TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SPENCER GOT HIS WAY, 11th
PERSON VOTED OUT, AND FIFTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
>> WOW, NICE.
>> Jeff: SHOCKING JEREMY, TASH
AAND KIM.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> IT WAS A CRAZY ONE.
>> YOU DIDN'T THINK THAT WAS
GOING TO, LIKE, MESS UP NUMBERS
AND STUFF?
OR YOU JUST FEEL LIKE--
>> I DO FEEL LIKE IT.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE THE GAME IS
ONCE AGAIN, LIKE, REALLY OPEN.
>> OKAY.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME, I MADE A
MOVE.
I BLINDSIDED STEPHEN, BUT I
CAN'T BECOME THE GAME BOT WHO
TREATS PEOPLE LIKE PAWNS.
SO EVEN IF JEREMY ISN'T SOMEONE
I WANT TO GO TO THE END WITH,
HE'S PROBABLY SOMEONE I NEED TO
KEEP A RELATIONSHIP WITH.
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
WE'RE STILL GOOD.
>> WE'RE STILL GOOD.
LIKE, I STILL TRUST YOU.
>> I DIDN'T WANT STEPHEN GONE.
NOW, I FEEL LIKE I'M IN TROUBLE.
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
ANYTHING.
>> WE SHOULD JUST, LIKE, FIGURE
OUT WHERE THINGS STAND.
IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE IT HAS
BEEN.
IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE PICKING UP
THE PIECES,UN.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
THESE VOTING BLOCKS JUST KEEP
MOVING AND I DON'T LIKE THAT
FEELING.
I LIKE TO BE IN THE MIDDLE OF
EVERYTHING AND KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON.
>> THIS IS WHAT I'M THINKING.
>> OKAY.
>> IF JOE DOESN'T WIN, HE'S
DEFINITELY GOING.
>> OH, YES.
>> EVERYBODY'S ON BOARD WITH
THAT.
>> YES!
AFTER TRIBAL, I FELT COMPLETELY
BLINDSIDE AND I HAD REALIZED I
NEED TO BE IN CONTROL OF MY
DESTINY.
SO WE GET RID OF JOE.
THAT'S FOUR WOMEN.
AND GIRLS HAVE AN UPPER HAND.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO DO THAT ALL
WOMEN.
>> BECAUSE EVERYBODY WANTS TO.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND THEN BEFORE THEY REALIZE
WHAT'S HAPPENING, WE ALREADY
GOTTEN THEM.
>> I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
I LOVE THIS.
>> ARE YOU--
>> I'M IN, YEAH.
OUT OF THE BLUE, KIMMI
APPROACHES ME WITH THIS PLAN OF
AN ALL-GIRLS ALLIANCE.
IF WE VOTE OUT JOE AND THE GIRLS
ARE WILLING TO WORK TOGETHER,
THERE'S NOTHING THAT JEREMY,
KEITH, OR SPENCER COULD DO.
>> IF ONE OF THE GUYS GO, THEN
IT'S GOING TO BE FOUR WOMEN THAT
CAN RULE.
SO, IT'S GOT TO BE JOE.
>> I AGREE.
>> THEN WE CAN GET OUT SPENCER.
>> YUP.
>> WE CAN GET OUT KEITH.
>> YEAH.
>> AND JEREMY.
>> I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE AND
LEAVE MY FAMILY JUST TO BE
SOMEBODY'S PAWN.
I CAME OUT HERE TO WIN.
SO IT'S TIME FOR ME TO MAKE MY
MOVE.
>> Jeff: TASH AHOW DOES IT
FEEL TO HAVE LASTED 30 DAY?
>> JEFF, TO MAKE IT TO 30 DAYS,
I'M FEELING FANTASTIC.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, HOW HARD IS
IT TO PLAY A SECOND TIME AND
LEAVE YOUR LIFE BEHIND KNOWING
I'M OUT HERE FOR MY FAMILY?
>> I HAVE NO COMMUNICATION WITH
HOME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY'RE DOING.
WHATEVER.
>> Jeff: WOW, EVEN TALKING
ABOUT IT.
WELL, AS YOU GUYS KNOW, A BIG
PART OF "SURVIVOR" IS THE LOVED
ONE VISIT.
AND MOST OF THE TIME, WE DO
BRING YOUR LOVED ONES TO YOU.
NOT ALWAYS.
SOMETIMES WE DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
TODAY, WE ARE NOT DOING ANYTHING
TODAY WE BROUGHT YOUR LOVE TO
YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> I'M READY!
I'M READY!
>> Jeff: JEREMY, HERE'S YOUR
WIFE, VAL.
>> GO GET HER!
>> I KNEW IT!
>> SO VAL SAID, "IT'S A BOY."
I'M GOING TO HAVE A SON.
THAT'S WILD.
BUT I DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO KNOW
RIGHT NOW.
THEY DON'T NEED TO KNOW.
>> Jeff: JEREMY THAT WAS, I
THINK, THE FASTEST SPRINT TO A
LOVED ONE I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> I MEAN, LIKE, THIS WHOLE
GAME, ALL I DO IS THINK ABOUT
FAMILY.
THERE IS NOTHING MORE IMPORTANT
THAN FAMILY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
VAL, TAKE YOUR SPOT OVER HERE.
JEREMY, HEAD BACK.
SAY YOUR GOOD-BYES.
TASH AHERE'S YOUR COUSIN,
CHRISTINA!
>> WHAT!
WHAT!
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE IT!
>> OH, WHAT!
>> I KNOW!
I KNOW!
>> WE ARE LIKE MORE SISTERS THAN
COUSINS.
IT'S JUST-- IT'S LOVE.
>> IT'S LOVE.
IT'S LOVE!
>> OH, MY DPOIVE!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHRISTINA,
TAKE YOUR SPOT NEXT TO VAL.
>> OH, MAN, AWESOME!
>> Jeff: SPENCER, WHO WOULD
YOU LIKE TO SEE?
>> MY GIRLFRIEND.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
SPENCER HAS A GIRLFRIEND!
MARCELLA.
>> THERE YOU GO, SPENCE!
>> SAYING "I LOVE YOU," IS A BIG
DEAL TO ME.
AND IT'S SOMETHING I'VE
STRUGGLED WITH SINCE CHILDHOOD.
AND IT'S LIKE I FOUGHT THROUGH
FEELING THAT WAY WITH SO MANY
PEOPLE THAT I'VE LOVED.
AND THE FACT THAT I DID SAY "I
LOVE YOU" IT SHOWS ME THAT THIS
CHANGE IS REAL.
IT'S NOT MADE UP.
IT'S HAPPENED.
BECAUSE I COLOVE MARCELLA.
>> Jeff: ABI, YOUR MOM CAME
THE LAST TIME YOU WERE ON THE
SHOW.
YOUR MOM IS HERE AGAIN.
VERA FIGEROA, COME ON OUT!
SHE'S MY ANGEL.
>> SHE IS MY ANGEL.
UNDERSTAND ME?
>> Jeff: UH-HUH.
ALL RIGHT, JOIN THE THE OTHERS.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> CIAO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KEITH, WHO
DO YOU WANT TO SEE?
KEITH'S WIFE, DANA, COME ONUT
BIG "D"!
>> BIG "D," EVERYBODY!
IT'S HER!
OH, MAN.
THIS WILL GET ME OVER THE HUMP
NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> GOD.
>> Jeff: HOW DID YOU GUYS
MEET?
>> HE WENT TO COLLEGE IN
ARKANSAS, WHERE I'M FROM.
>> Jeff: L.A., LOWER ARKANSAS.
THIS IS A BOOST FOR EVERY ONE OF
US!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONE LAST
HUG.
>> ALL RIGHT, BABY.
BE GOOD.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: WENTWORTH.
>> YES?
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR DAD NOW!
>> HEY, DAD!
OH, HI, DAD!
>> Jeff: DALE, WHAT'S IT LIKE
TO BE BACK HERE?
BECAUSE YOU DID PLAY THIS GAME.
>> I HAVE A WHOLE NEW RESPECT
FOR THE LOVED ONES WHO STAY
HOME.
I REALLY DO.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> IT HURTS REALLY BAD.
ESPECIALLY WHERE WE KNOW WHAT
THE GAME DOES TO YOU.
BUT YOU COME OUT BETTER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HIM
ONE LAST HUG.
>> ALL RIGHT, DAD.
>> Jeff: JOE, THE FIRST TIME
YOU PLAYED, YOU SHARED A STORY
AS A KID GETTING ON "SURVIVOR,"
AND PART OF YOUR VISUALIZATION
INCLUDED YOUR DAD WALKING
THROUGH A SCENE JUST LIKE THIS.
BUT IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
IT'S HAPPENING NOW.
HERE'S YOUR DAD, PAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
COME ON, PAT!
>> YOU DID IT.
YOU DID IT.
>> Jeff: SO, JOE, YOU GUYS
CLEARLY HAVE A VERY STRONG
FAMILY BOND.
>> YEAH.
WHEW.
FAMILY'S THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IN MY LIFE.
AND I JUST WANT TO THANK YOU FOR
GIVING ME THIS MOMENT.
FOR REAL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HIM A
HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: OR A KISS.
MUCH BETTER.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: KIMMI, YOU'VE WAITED
LONGER THAN ANYONE ELSE TO HAVE
A LOVED ONE VISIT YOU ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> YES!
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR DAD.
>> OH, MY DADDY!
MY DADDY!
OH, MY GOD, MY DADDY!
OH, CANADA!
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU.
DADDY!
THIS IS THE BEST GIFT!
THAT I COULD GIVE MY DAD IS TO
LET HIM BE A PART OF MY DREAM.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ONE LAST
GOOD-BYE HUG.
>> OKAY, B.B., LOVE YOU.
>> THANK YOU, CANADA.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE A
REWARD CHALLENGE TO GET TO.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE TO DIG UP BAGS IN
THE SAND.
YOU WILL THEN SPIN AROUND A POST
TO RETRIEVE ANOTHER BAG.
THIS WILL MAKE YOU DIZZY.
YOU WILL THEN HAVE TO MAKE YOUR
WAY ACROSS A BALANCE BEAM WHERE
YOU'LL COLLECT YOUR LAST BAG.
YOU'LL THEN USE THE PIECES
INSIDE THE BAG TO SOLVE A WORD
PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO GET IT RIGHT
WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT IS?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GOOD, OLD-FASHIONED,
AMERICAN BARBECUE.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: THE WINNER WILL GO
BACK TO CAMP WITH THEIR LOVED
ONE.
IT TRULY IS A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
EXPERIENCE.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR A REWARD OF BARBECUE AND
LOVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
LOOKING FOR A ROPE.
ONCE YOU HAVE IT, PULL IT UP.
KIMMI HAS HERS.
JOE HAS HIS.
WHEN YOU SEE YOUR FIRST BAG,
UNTIE IT.
KEITH HAS HIS.
KIMMI HAS HERS.
KEITH HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
OPEN IT UP, KEITH, UNTIE IT.
JOE HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
>> SORRY, KEITH.
>> COME ON, COME ON, COME ON!
>> Jeff: JEREMY HAS HIS FIRST
BAG.
JEREMY'S GOT HIS SECOND BAG.
KIMMI IN THE LEAD.
KEITH RIGHT BEHIND.
>> COME ON, KIM!
COME ON, KIMMI!
>> Jeff: KIM ALREADY SPINNING
AROUND THAT POST.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET DIZZY VERY
QUICKLY.
KEITH HAS HIS THREE BAGS.
TASHA HAS HER THIRD BAG.
JOE HAS HIS THIRD BAG.
THE FASTER YOU SPIN THE FASTER
FINISH AND THE MORE DIZZY WILL
YOU GET.
>> GO, TASHA!
EXPWHR YOU'RE LOOKING FOR FIVE
BAGS TOTAL.
JEREMY NOW SPINNING.
EVERYBODY GETTING DIZZY.
KEITH HAS HIS FOURTH BAG.
KIMMI HAS HER FOURTH BAG.
>> ALMOST, TASHA, ALMOST!
>> Jeff: KIMMI CANNOT CANNOT
MOVE SHE'S SO DIZZY.
KEITH IS GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
CAN HE MAKE IT?
NO, KEITH HAS TO GO BACK.
NOW YOU ARE DIZZY WITH FOUR BAGS
AND YOU HAVE TO UNTIE A FIFTH ON
A BEAM KIMMI HAS TO TRY IT
AGAIN.
TASHA HAS ALL FOUR BAGS.
>> YOU'RE STILL IN IT, KELLY!
>> Jeff: KELLY HAS HERS.
SPENCER HAS HIS!
>> YOU GOT IT, BABY!
>> Jeff: KEITH HAS HIS "P" GO,
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: IT IS KEITH NOW WITH
THE LEAD.
JEREMY HAS HIS FIFTH.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, JEREMY.
>> GO, KELLIY, LET'S GO.
>> KELLY HAS HER FIFTH BAG.
>> Jeff: ABI FALLS SHE HAS TO
GO BACK.
SPENCER WORKING ON HIS FIFTH
BAG.
HE HAS COME FROM BEHIND BEFORE
IN THE LAST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
AND PULLED IT OUT.
CAN HE DO IT AGAIN?
SPENCER HAS HIS FIFTH BAG.
NOW SPENCER'S IN IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: IT IS ONE WORD YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: IT IS JOE, KEITH,
SPENCER, WENTWORTH, ABI, AND
JEREMY.
YOUR LOVED ONES ARE HERE IN
CAMBODIA.
TASHA HAS HER FIFTH.
SHE CAN START WORKING ON IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: KIMMI FALLS OFF
AGAIN.
THE GREAT THING ABOUT THIS IS
YOU CAN GET IT IN AN INSTANT AND
WIN IT OUT OF NOWHERE.
>> STAY WITH IT, KELLY.
>> Jeff: ABI THINKS SHE HAS
SOMETHING.
SHE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
IS SHE RIGHT?
WENTWORTH THINKS SHE HAS
SOMETHING.
SHE'S GOING TO TRY SOMETHING
NOW.
ABI IS SPELLING A WORD.
WENTWORTH IS SPELLING A WORD.
NOW EVERYBODY IS STARTING TO
PANIC.
WHAT IS IT?
WENTWORTH PLACES ANOTHER BLOCK
AND ANOTHER ONE.
SPENCER LOOKING NEXT DOOR.
NO IDEA WHAT IT IS.
NOURISHMENT IS THE WORD!
WENTWORTH WINS REWARD!
>> DAD!
>> Jeff: LOVE WITH HER DAD AND
A BARBECUE BACK AT CAMP!
>> I WAS GOING FOR REDEMPTION.
>> GOOD JOB, KELLY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO YOU
GUYS ARE GOING TO GO BACK TO
CAMP WHERE WE HAVE A BEAUTIFUL
BARBECUE SET UP FOR YOU.
YOU JUST NEED TO PICK THREE
TRIBE MEMBERS AND THEIR LOVED
ONES TO JOIN YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD, JEFF, THIS IS SO
HARD.
KEITH.
>> COME ON, BIG "D"!
>> ABI.
>> ABI!
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, KELLY!
>> KIMMI'S BEEN TALKING ABOUT
HER LOVED ONE VISIT FOR A REALLY
LONG TIME, SO THIS IS REALLY
HARD FOR ME, BUT I KNOW SHE
REALLY WANTS TO SEE HER DAD.
I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FOUR
PEOPLE LEFT.
CHOOSE ONE MORE.
>> OH!
>> I KNOW HOW MUCH THE FAMILY
REWARD MEANT TO JOE, SO, JOE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOE.
>> HI.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, THAT MEANS
CHRISTINA, VAL, MARCELLA, GOT TO
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOU GUYS.
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> LOVE YOU!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, 10 OF YOU
GO BACK AND HAVE A
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE
THANKS TO WENTWORTH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: TASHA, SPENCER,
JEREMY, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP, ENJOY.
DAD AT MY SIDE AND THE OTHER
LOVED ONES IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL
THING.
IT WAS SO COOL.
AND I COULD TELL EVERYONE WAS SO
EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU!
>> THANK YOU!
>> TO SEE A FAMILY MEMBER,
ESPECIALLY YOUR WIFE, I DON'T
KNOW, I NEEDED TO SEE SOMEBODY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE CARED IF YOU
BROUGHT MY FIFTH COUSIN FROM MY
DADDY, JUST SOME KIND OF
RELATIVE, BUT BIG "D" WAS THE
ULTIMATE PRIZE.
>> YOU PAINTED THAT WHOLE THING?
>> YEAH, IT TOOK ME A WHILE.
>> YOU KNOW,IMENT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU BECAUSE... AS
YOU GET OLDER, I NEVER HAD A
FRIEND LIKE YOU.
>> REALLY?
>> MM.
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP, I NEVER
WANTED TO LET ANYBODY IN.
THAT'S WHY I'VE BEEN A LONER MY
WHOLE LIFE.
BUT YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD SON, JOE.
YOU'RE MY HERO.
RESPECT MY FRIEND.
>> GROWING UP AS A KID, ME AND
MY DAD, WE WERE CLOSE, BUT HE
WASN'T VERY AFFECTIONATE.
HE WAS A LITTLE BIT TOUGH, AND
HE NEVER REALLY SAID, "I LOVE
YOU."
SO FOR HIM TO BE ABLE TO SHARE
THAT WITH ME WAS SOMETHING SO
SPECIAL AND, LIKE, AH!
I'LL REMEMBER IT FOR THE REST OF
MY LIFE.
I LOVE YOU UNCONDITIONALLY.
>> EXACTLY.
EXACTLY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ALL
THEIR PICKS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT OUR
PICKS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF WHAT I EXPECTED.
>> AH!
IT STILL SUCKS.
KELLEY CHOOSING WHO TO COME WITH
HER ON REWARD WAS, LIKE, THESE
TINY LITTLE SHANKS TO THE HEART
ONE BY ONE BY ONE.
I'VE NEVER FELT HEARTACHE LIKE
THAT.
I JUST HAD TO TAKE A MOMENT AND
LET ME HEART CATCH UP WITH MY
HEAD.
THERE'S NO OPTION AT THIS POINT
BUT FOR ME TO GET MY HEAD BACK
IN THE GAME AND DO EVERYTHING IN
MY POWER TO WIN.
I KNOW YOU PROBABLY STILL FEEL
WEIRD ABOUT STEPHEN, BUT IT WAS
THE THING AGAINST STEPHEN.
IT WAS NOT A THING AGAINST YOU.
>> BUT HOW DO YOU, LIKE, PROCEED
FORWARD?
>> WELL, HOW DO YOU GUYS FEEL
ABOUT US IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
FOR ALL THREE.
>> I'M IN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS PERFECT.
I HAVE ONE OPTION TO GO WITH
SPENCER AND JEREMY TO THE FINAL
THREE.
AND THEN ON THE OTHER SIDE, THE
GIRLS WERE TALKING ABOUT AN
ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE.
SO I THINK I HAVE TWO VIABLE
OPTIONS.
>> SO WHAT'S THE NEXT MOVE?
>> HOW DO YOU GUYS FEEL ABOUT
JOE IN THE GAME NOW?
>> I THINK JOE IS SETTING
HIMSELF UP NICELY.
HE CAN SAY, "I NOT ONLY PLAYED A
PHYSICAL GAME.
I PLAYED A SOCIAL GAME.
I AM CLEARLY THE BIGGEST THREAT,
AND I'M STILL HERE."
SO WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
>> AT THIS POINT, I DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY CHANCES THERE ARE GOING
TO BE TO GET JOE OUT.
I LET ONE OPPORTUNITY GO BECAUSE
I HAD A BIG MOVE TO MAKE, AND I
NEEDED JOE'S HELP FOR IT.
BUT JOE IS A GUY WHO YOU GIVE
HIM AN INCH, HE WILL TAKE A
MILE.
HE GETS MOMENTUM, AND I'M DONE.
SO IT MAKES ALL THE SENSE IN THE
WORLD FOR ME, THE SECOND I GET
THE CHANCE, TO GET THIS GUY OUT
OF HERE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
SPENCER.
I MUST TAKE IT PACK.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE IT
UP.
IT FEELS SO GOOD.
>> IT WILL FEEL GOOD AGAIN.
>> Jeff: I LIKE IT!
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE A WOODEN STATUE
ON A POLE.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS, WE'LLED --
ANOTHER SECTION OF POLE, MAKING
IT MORE DIFFICULT.
YOUR STATUE DROPS, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A
ONE-IN-SEVEN SHOT AT WINNING
THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON OF OUR JURY.
AND TODAY, IT IS THE FIRST MAN
AND THE FIRST WOMAN.
>> WHOA!
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: TWO PEOPLE WILL HAVE
IMMUNITY.
EVERYBODY'S ODDS JUST KNOT A
WHOLE LOT BETTER.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPORTS AND GET
STARTED.
>> OOOH!
>> Jeff: LET'S DO IT.
ONE IN FOUR.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR FIRST
SECTION.
PLACE YOUR WOODEN STATUE ON IT.
HANDS AT THE BOTTOM OF THE POLE.
EVERYBODY PUT YOUR HANDS AT THE
BOTTOM.
HERE WE GO.
WE ARE ON.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY ADD ANOTHER
SECTION OF POLE.
THIS WILL BE YOUR FIRST TEST.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE TRANSITION
WHILE KEEPING YOUR STATUE IN
PLACE.
AND GET YOUR HANDS BACK DOWN TO
THE BOTTOM, WHICH MEANS YOU HAVE
TO RAISE THAT POLE HIGHER.
EVERYBODY MADE THE TRANSITION
NICELY.
WE WILL KEEP ADDING A SECTION OF
POLE EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: YOU'RE NOW AT 10 FEET
OF POLE WITH A WOODEN STATUE
OVER YOUR HEAD.
BE MIND WILL OF THAT WHEN IT
DROPS.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
KIMMI LOSES BALANCE.
KIMMI DROPS.
KIMMI'S THE FIRST ONE OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
KIMMI, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY FOR KIMMI.
ABI CANNOT GET IT BACK.
ABI IS OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO TWO WOMEN,
WENTWORTH AND TASHA.
ONE MAN, AND ONE WOMAN WILL WANT
IT MORE THAN THE OTHERS.
WHO CAN HANG IN THERE THE THE
LONGEST?
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ANYTHING TO ADD
ANOTHER SECTION OF POLE.
NO QUICK MOVES BECAUSE WE'RE
STILL ALIVE.
I'LL GIVE YOU PLENTY OF TIME.
HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY MAKE YOUR MOVE.
TASHA CANNOT MESSENGER THE
TRANSITION.
TASHA IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
KELLEY WENTWORTH WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AND RIGHT BEHIND THAT, SPENCER
DROPS OUT.
JEREMY CANNOT SURVIVE THE
TRANSITION.
JEREMY DROPS.
A WHOLE LOT HAPPENING AT ONCE.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO, KEITH AND
JOE.
TRYING TO MAKE THIS TRANSITION.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND WE ARE BACK ON WITH KEITH
AND JOE FOR IMMUNITY.
WE ARE NOW AT ABOUT 14 FEET OF
POLE.
WENTWORTH ALREADY HAS IMMUNITY.
WHO WILL JOIN HER TONIGHT WITH
SECURITY A TRIBAL COUNCIL?
WILL IT BE KEITH OR WILL IT BE
JOE?
ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME TO ADD
ANOTHER SECTION.
HERE WE GO.
REACH FOR YOUR LAST SECTION OF
POLE.
BUT IF YOU DROP DURING THIS
TRANSITION, IT'S OVER.
I'M GOING TO COUNT YOU IN.
HERE WE GO, FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONES.
>> HOLD IT, KEITH!
HOLD IT, KEITH!
THIS IS IT.
WE PLAY IT OUT FROM HERE.
16 FEET OF POLE BALANCING A
SMALL WOODEN STATUE TO MOVE ONE
STEP CLOSER, TO WINNING THIS
GAME.
A MILLION DOLLARS.
JOE WITH A LOT OF MOVEMENT NOW,
HUGE BEND IN THAT POLE.
JOE A NICE RECOVERY.
THAT TOOK EVERYTHING.
THAT POLE WAS ON ITS WAY OVER.
KEITH WITH A LOT OF BEND IN THAT
POLE AGAIN.
CAN HE GET IT BACK?
AND HE DOES.
JUST WHEN YOU THINK IT'S OVER,
BOTH GUYS BATTLE BACK.
YOUR NECK IS HURTING.
YOUR BODY'S FATIGUED.
YOU'RE MENTALLY EXHAUSTED, BUT
YOU CANNOT GIVE UP.
>> THIS IS TOO TENSE, MAN.
WE'RE NOW ONE HOUR, 20 MINUTES
INTO THIS CHALLENGE.
THAT IS A LONG TIME.
YOU'RE LOOKING STRAIGHT UP.
BALANCING A STATUE.
A LONG SECTION OF POLES.
>> Jeff: KEITH WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> IS HE OKAY!
>> Jeff: MEDICAL!
MEDICAL!
>> WHAT!
>> IS HE OKAY!
JOE!
IS HE ALL RIGHT!
>> JOE!
>> IS HE ALL RIGHT.
>> GUYS, CLEAR A LITTLE SPOT FOR
MEDICAL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
HE, LIKE, PASSED OUT.
>> BUD, WE'RE RIGHT HERE WITH
YOU, YOU'RE IN GREAT HAPPENS.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> JOE?
CAN YOU HEAR ME, JOE?
( BEEPING ).
>> HE LITERALLY, LIKE, PASSED
OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT H WE WANTED.
>> THAT'S SCARY.
>> Jeff: JOE, YOU'VE GOT OUR
MEDICAL TEAM HERE.
THEY'RE TAKING CARE OF YOU,
BUDDY.
>> OH!
>> TAKE IT EASY, MAN.
>> Jeff: DR. JOE, JUST SO WE
CAN CATCH UP, WHAT'S RAEPG RIGHT
NOW.
TO THE POINT WHERE HE'S NOT ABLE
TO SUPPORT HIMSELF.
HE JUST COLLAPSED.
>> MY LEGS WENT NUMB.
>> DON'T WORRY, JOE.
JUST TAKE IT EASY, MAN.
>> Jeff: YEAH.
CAN WE BRING IN AN UMBRELLA?
THANKS.
JOE, ARE YOU STARTING TO COME
BACK ENOUGH TO REALIZE WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> YEAH.
I JUST BLACKED OUT, AND THEN
THAT'S THE LAST I REMEMBER.
I JUST WANTED IT SO BAD.
I LOVE THIS GAME, MAN.
I WANT TO PLAY IT, LIKE, AS HARD
AS I CAN.
>> Jeff: I THINK THIS EFFORT
JUST SHOWED YOU ARE.
>> YOUR LEGS JUST COLLAPSED.
>> Jeff: SO, JOE, THE GOOD
NEWS IS WHAT DR. JOE IS SAYING
IS THAT EVEN THOUGH YOU CLEARLY
FEEL MISERABLE, YOU'RE NOT IN
ANY DANGER OF BEING PULLED FROM
THE GAME.
THIS IS TEMPORARY.
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> LET'S VERY GENTLY, IN STAGES,
GET YOU UPRIGHT.
>> SIT UP, SIT UP, SIT UP.
I GO INTO IMMUNITY TODAY
THINKING I'M GOING TO WIN, AND
NOW I'M ON MY BACK GOING WHAT
HAPPENED?
AND I'M VULNERABLE AGAIN TO
GETTING VOTEDLY OUT AT TRIBAL.
>> GOOD JOB, JOE!
>> ALL RIGHT, JOE!
>> THERE'S JUST NO SAFETY IN
"SURVIVOR," YOU KNOW?
IT'S A TOUGH, TOUGH SITUATION
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: GAME CONTINUES.
WENTWORTH.
>> GOOD JOB, KELLEY.
>> Jeff: GREAT EFFORT NOT TO
BE LOST IN THE DRAMA OF ALL
THIS.
YOU ARE SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
KEITH.
>> KEITH!
>> Jeff: WELL EARNED.
YOU ARE SAFE.
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I GOTTA SAY THAT THE GROUP OF
YOU, WHEN WE HAD THIS IDEA FOR
"SURVIVOR: SECOND CHANCE," THIS
IS WHAT WE HOPED FOR.
A GROUP OF PEOPLE WILLING TO
PUSH THEMSELVES FURTHER THAN
THEY WOULD EVER DARE PUSH
THEMSELVES BACK HOME IN THEIR
NORMAL LIVES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> THAT WAS PRETTY CRAZY.
>> THAT WAS A GOOD ONE, WASN'T
IT.
>> THAT WAS SCARY, MAN.
>> SIT DOWN AND REST.
>> IT JUST TOOK A LOT OUT OF ME.
>> I BET, YEAH "P."
>> THE LAST THING I REMEMBER IS,
I SEE STARS.
AND THEN IT WAS JUST, LIKE, I'M
GOING DOWN.
>> THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WAS,
LIKE, WATCHING A CRAZY SOCCER
MATCH, YOU KNOW, BRAZIL AGAINST
GERMANY.
AND TO SEE JOE THE AMAZING LOSE
TO A 52-YEAR-OLD MAN, IT WAS
AWESOME.
AND NOW, IT'S TIME FOR HIM TO
GO.
>> OH, SHE DOES!
OH!
OH, MY GOD!
>> AWESOME!
>> THE TIDES HAVE TURNED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SO WE GET RID OF JOE AND THEN
WE DECIDE WHAT'S BEST FOR US.
THE FACT THAT JOE PUSHED HIMSELF
UNTIL HE PASSED OUT, THAT IS
FRIGHTENING.
BECAUSE, LIKE, I CAN'T COMPETE
WITH THAT.
SO HE'S GOT TO GO.
ONCE WE GET HIM OUT OF HERE, THE
GIRLS ARE IN CONTROL OF THIS
GAME.
>> YOU WANT TO TALK?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN YOU GET UP?
>> RIGHT NOW, IT SUCTION BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE IMMUNITY, AND I'M
EXHAUSTED.
BUT I WENT IN TO THE LAST TRIBAL
WITHOUT THE NECKLACE, AND I'M
STILL HERE.
SO I'M PRETTY CONFIDENT THAT I
CAN DO IT AGAIN.
AT THIS POINT IN THE THE GAME,
LIKE, I'M THINKING WHO'S THE
MOST DANGEROUS PERSON TO JUST
GET TO THE END.
HANDS DOWN, ABI.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
IN EVERYONE'S MIND, THEY WANT TO
SIT NEXT TO ABI.
AND WITH EVERY VOTE THAT SHE'S
NOT VOTED OUT, SHE BECOMES MORE
AND MORE DANGEROUS TO MAKE IT TO
THE END.
>> YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
SITTING NEXT TO ABI WOULD BE
EASY MONEY.
>> EXACTLY.
I WANT PLAYERS TO GO TO THE END.
>> YEAH.
I HEAR YOU.
WRIERKS WHAT IT COMES DOWN TO IS
I NEED ABI OUT OF THIS GAME AND
JEREMY'S A SMART GUY, SO I THINK
IT'S GOING TO STICK, AND I THINK
IT DID STICK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
BECAUSE, I MEAN, IT'S EASY TO BE
LIKE, "LET'S GET JOE OUT."
>> YEAH.
>> HERE'S THE THING.
THE GIRLS WANT TO DO AN ALL-GIRL
ALLIANCE.
BUT YOU GUYS HAVE TO TRUST IT
WILL NOT BE ALL GIRLS.
I'VE BEEN LOCKED IN SINCE DAY
ONE.
AND THAT'S IT.
>> I WAS PLANNING ON VOTING OUT
JOE, AND THEN TASHA TELLS ME
THIS TALK ABOUT AN ALL GIRLS'
ALLIANCE.
OH, MY GOD.
>> ARE YOU GUYS SERIOUSLY
NERVOUS ABOUT THIS ALL-GIRL
THING?
>> NO.
I'M NOT NERVOUS ABOUT THE ALL
GIRLS.
IT'S JUST SO QUIET RIGHT NOW.
>> IT IS A LITTLE CALM.
>> IT'S NEVER THIS EASY.
>> SO I TOLD JEREMY AND SPENCER
ABOUT THE ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO RISK
HAVING THEM FIND OUT ABOUT IT
FROM SOMEONE ELSE.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD CREATE
DISTRUST.
HOWEVER, ALL I DID WAS MAKE THEM
SUSPICIOUS, WHICH COULD MEAN
TROUBLE.
>> I'M CONCERNED EITHER WAY.
IF WE KEEP JOE, I'M TERRIFIED.
IF WE GET RID OF JOE, I'M
TERRIFIED.
>> YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
>> THE PROBLEM IS I'M NOT 100%
CONVINCED THAT TASHA'S IDEA OF
FINAL THREE WITH MYSELF AND
JEREMY.
TASHA MIGHT HAVE THE THOUGHT IN
HER HEAD, I CAN BEAT AN ABI.
I CAN BEAT A KIMMI.
I CAN BEAT WENTWORTH.
SO WE HAVE TO SQUASH THESE GIRLS
BEFORE THEY GET ANYTHING
STARTED.
>> IF WE CAN GET KEITH, AND IF
WE STILL HAVE JOE.
>> BUT WHO'S THE FIFTH?
WE NEED TASHA.
>> WE'VE GOT TO LOCK HER IN,
THEN.
IF THOSE GIRLS TAKE OVER THE
AME, H ME AND SPENCER, WE'RE ALL
DONE.
OUR GAMES ARE OVER.
SO HAVING TASHA ON MY SIDE IS
CRUCIAL RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY, SO, YOU VOTE OUT ABI.
AND THAT LEAVES JOE IN THE GAME,
AND THEN HE WINS OUT.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO WIN
OUT?
>> YOU COULDN'T BEAT HIM TODAY.
SPENCER COULDN'T BEAT HIM TODAY.
JOE ESCAPED ONE TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND I DON'T WANT HIM TO ESCAPE
ANOTHER ONE.
BUT AT THIS POINT, IT'S A
STALEMATE.
>> WHAT IS THAT POWWOW ABOUT?
>> ARE PEOPLE STILL WRITING JOE?
>> I KNOW TASHA IS 100%.
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL NOT KNOWING WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
SO WE NEED TO COME TO AN
AGREEMENT.
WE'RE ANYTHING TO BE MAKING A
MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION, AND I'M
NERVOUS AS HELL ABOUT THAT.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
KASS.
SAVAGE.
WIGLESWORTH.
CIERA.
AND FISH BACK, VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
JOE, ONE OF THE MOST DRAMATIC
MOMENTS IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY
TODAY WHEN YOU DROPPED.
HOW ARE YOU FEEL?
>> I'M OKAY.
I'M NOT GREAT BY ANY MEANS.
I MEAN, I'VE PUSHED MYSELF.
YOU KNOW IN SPORTS, BUT NOTHING
LIKE THIS.
AND IT'S-- IT'S HUMBLING.
I HAVE MY BREAKING POINT, TOO.
>> Jeff: KIMMI, WHAT WAS IT
LIKE WHEN YOU SAW THAT?
>> I MEAN, IT WAS AN EPIC BATTLE
BETWEEN THEM.
I MEAN, JUST WATCHING IT, IT WAS
JAW DROPPING.
AND TO SEE SOMEBODY GO DOWN, I
MEAN, IT WAS FRIGHTENING FOR US.
>> Jeff: SO, WENTWORTH, ONCE
YOU REALIZED HE'S GOING TO BE
OKAY, HOW QUICKLY DOES YOUR
BRAIN GO, ALL RIGHT, I GOTTA BE
HONEST.
I AM IN A GAME.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT DEFINITELY
CROSSES YOUR MIND.
I MEAN, HE STOOD THERE UNTIL HE
PASSED OUT.
LIKE, HE COULD COTHAT IN ANY
CHALLENGE AND BEAT ALL OF US TO
THE END.
I MEAN, IT HAD TO HAVE CROSSED
EVERYONE'S MIND LIKE, HOLY CRAP.
THESE GUYS WILL LITERALLY PASS
OUT TO WIN A CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, ARE YOU ABLE,
ALSO, TO SAY, BACK TO GAME MODE?
DUDE DOES NOT HAVE IMMUNITY?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, AS SOON AS YOU
FIND OUT THAT HE'S ALL RIGHT,
YOU START THINKING, ALL RIGHT,
JOE, DOESN'T HAVE IMMUNITY.
DO WE TAKE HIM OUT?
BUT YOU HAVE A GAME PLAN, AND
IT'S NOT JUST GOING TO CHANGE
JUST BECAUSE JOE DOESN'T HAVE
IMMUNITY.
YOU CAN'T HAVE BLINDERS ON.
BECAUSE THESE NEXT FEW VOTES
ARE-- ARE CRUCIAL.
>> CRUCIAL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> CRUCIAL!
>> Jeff: AND, JEREMY, THIS IS
WHERE THE INVOICE OF VOTING
BLOCKS VERSUS ALLIANCES STARTS
TO GET VERY EXPENSIVE, BECAUSE
THE THING ABOUT AN ALLIANCE IS
THEORETICALLY YOU CAN COUNT ON
IT TO A CERTAIN POINT.
THE THING.
A VOTING BLOCK AS YOU GUYS HAVE
BEEN EXPLAINING IT'S NEW EVERY
KAY.
>> AT SOME POINT, ESPECIALLY
RIGHT NOW WHEN YOU'RE GETTING
DOWN TO THE NITTY-GRITTY, YOU
GOTTA START PICKING AN ALLIANCE,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT TO END UP
ON THE BOTTOM OF THE VOTING
BLOCK AT THE LAST PART OF THE
GAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN
IN TERMS OF US GETTING READY TO
VOTE?
>> I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE KNOW WHO
IS ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK RIGHT
NOW.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK EVERYONE
KNOWS WHO IS ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK?
>> I ALWAYS FEEL LIKE I AM, SO
I'M GOING TO THROW MY HAND UP
SAYING I AM.
>> Jeff: ABI, FOR WHAT REASON?
>> EVERY TRIBAL I FEEL THAT I'M
ON THE BOTTOM BECAUSE OF THE
CONNECTION I HAVE WITH WENTWORTH
AND CIERA.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO KEEP ON
HAUNTING US.
>> WELL, I THINK YOU'RE A THREAT
IN THE GAME BECAUSE EVERYONE
WOULD WANT TO TAKE YOU TO THE
END.
SHE'S IN THE PERFECT SPOT TO
MAKE IT PAST A VOTE, ANOTHER
VOTE, ANOTHER VOTE.
AND YET SHE'S STILL HERE.
>> BUT I'M NOT CONFIDENT THEY
WON'T BE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
I DO FEEL THERE IS A
POSSIBILITY.
>> AND, YET, LOOK, SHE'S SITTING
UP STRAIGHT, HAPPY AS A CLAM.
>> Jeff: SPENCER, JOE BRINGS
UP THIS CONVERSATION ABOUT WHO
YOU MIGHT CRAG TO THE END
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T WIN.
THEY'RE STILL TAKING UP A SPOT
IN THE FINAL THREE.
AND IT MIGHT BE YOUR SPOT.
>> EXACTLY.
WHEN THIS PERSON THAT YOU'D LOVE
TO SIT NEXT TO DOESN'T ACTUALLY
HELP YOUR CHANCES OF GETTING TO
THE FINAL THREE, THAT'S WHEN IT
BECOMES A PROBLEM.
>> Jeff: ABI WHAT, DO YOU
THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT?
IS THIS ALL A BUNCH OF NOTHING
BECAUSE WE ALREADY KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> THERE IS A MOLD GOING ON AND
IT'S AFFECTING THE OTHER
PLAYERS.
AND I THINK WE HAVE TO GET RID
OF THE BAD APPLE.
>> Jeff: AND, JOE WHAT, DO YOU
THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT?
>> I HOPE THAT THE PEOPLE THAT I
SAID TODAY THAT I WAS GOING TO
DO WHAT I SAID I WAS GOING TO DO
STICK TO THAT PLAN AND WE
CONTINUE MOVING FORWARD.
BECAUSE IF NOT, IT'S GOING TO GO
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
THE BIG THREATS IN THE GAME
RIGHT DOWN THE LINE.
IT ONLY TAKES FOUR AFTER THIS
VOTE.
AND IF YOU DON'T HAVE FOUR THAT
YOU CAN ABSOLUTELY TRUST, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE 8, 7, 6.
>> Jeff: OTHER, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
WENTWORTH, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE MOLDY.
YOU GOTTA GO, AND, PLEASE, GET A
HAIRED CUT.
YOU LOOK LIKE A CLOWN.
>> I HAVE THE TERRIFYING FEELING
THAT THIS IS EITHER A WINNING OR
A LOSING VOTE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JOE.
ABI.
TASHA.
ONE VOTE JOE, ONE VOTE ABI, ONE
VOTE TASHA.
JOE.
TWO VOTES JOE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JOE, ONE VOTE
ABI, ONE VOTE TASHA.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
JOE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: JOE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, Y'ALL.
BOYS, BEST OF LUCK.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, THE QUESTION OF TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL SEEMS TO BE WAS AN
ALLIANCE FORMED TONIGHT, OR WAS
THIS JUST THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO TAKE OUT A BIG
THREAT?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff:NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": AFTER A HUGE
MINDSIDE, JEREMY AND SPENCER ARE
WORRIED.
>> I'M DEEPLY CONCERNED.
>> I THINK WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
>> I FEEL MY GAME SLIPPING AWAY.
EXPWHR BUT BACKSTABBING ISN'T
THE ONLY DANGER IN "SURVIVOR."
OH!
YOU OKAY?
>> I NEED HELP!
>> I HAVE NO REGRETS.
I DON'T LEAVE ANYTHING BACK
BEHIND ME AND SAY I COULD HAVE
DONE THIS BETTER OR THAT BETTER.
I TRIED TO PLAY THE BEST GAME
THEY KNEW HOW, AND HAD SO MUCH
FUN AND I WAS ABLE TO REACH SO
MANY GOALS AND JUST GETTING MY
DAD OUT HERE, THAT ALONE FOR ME
WAS A MILLION-DOLLAR EXPERIENCE,
AND I HAVE THE FANS TO THANK