translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
The Ta Keo prospered
and had formed a solid quintet...
We are the final quintet.
I try to recruit
as many people as possible.
...while the
Angkors barely made it.
We are in hell.
It does not work.
But at the last
immunity test...
Woo tire.
...they finally won...
Angkor wins immunity!
...sending Bayon to the council.
On the field,
Wiglesworth and Spencer
were in the minority.
I stay on Kelly.
But Monica wanted change.
We might want
to preserve the female workforce.
She is unpredictable
and will switch sides.
And indeed, everything changed in the council,
when Monica was taken by surprise.
Monica, the tribe has spoken.
There are 15 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Terry !
Alright, c'est Probst!
- My friend, I need to talk to you.
- OK.
Come.
We'll be right back.
- Come to the beach.
- OK.
I got a call from your wife.
Your son, Danny...
He's at the hospital.
Your wife and the doctor
think
it's serious enough
for you to come
in to be present.
I know it's a shock,
waking up in the middle of the night.
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't serious.
No hesitation.
I'm going to get my bag
and uh... tell them.
- Fine, let's go.
- And then we go.
- I accompany you.
- Ok thank you.
- What's going on ?
- Everybody is here ?
How are you ?
My boy, Danny,
he was hospitalized.
My wife and the doctor
think it would be better
for me to go home.
- Oh my God !
- Oh Terry!
For me, there was no hesitation.
Terry !
I appreciate you all, and everything...
You helped me...
Helped fulfill
a new dream, and...
I couldn't have done it
without the wonderful people
that you are. Admirable.
We love you.
Thank you very much for everything.
I'll just take my bag.
You have to be a parent
to understand the shock of being here
and to learn that your child
is sick, that you have to go home.
I can only imagine.
Be well, good luck,
give them a beating!
- Everything will be fine, Terry!
- Good luck !
- I will miss you.
- You also.
Having to leave like this
is worse than a medical evacuation,
worse than anything you can
imagine in Survivor.
It reminds us
how quickly
things can change.
Let's win for Terry.
Let's win for him.
I don't like being
cold in the back like this.
Hold fast.
We'll take you home.
I sympathize.
He's a good father.
We will think of him
Hoping that it will be fine,
that everything will be fine when he returns.
Over here, everyone!
Angkor, discover
the new Bayon tribe.
Monica, eliminated at the last council.
Angkor and Bayon, discover
the new Ta Keo tribe.
Quoi ?
Sans Terry.
Terry Deitz was pulled from the game
following a family emergency.
Oh no !
His wife called,
one of his children is sick.
He had to go home.
Oh my God !
- Savage, you're a father.
- Yeah.
Imagine learning in the middle of the night
that your child has a problem,
and you don't know what.
I would run to the airport.
We are all
fans of this game,
but family
is more important than all that.
Wiglesworth.
Can you explain
to someone who has no children
what is this instinct?
You have it, Savage has it.
We would do anything for his child.
If necessary, if it was faster, I would
swim.
That Terry left like this...
We all sympathize.
It's awful.
Ciera,
you are a young mother, too.
How do you react ?
We discussed with my husband,
of what could bring me home.
I love this game,
but I love my family infinitely more .
Joe, what is the impact on you
as a tribe?
I think last night
it hit us all.
But the game goes on,
and Terry will be proud of us.
How are the other two tribes doing?
Bayon?
How's the vibe
at your place, Jeremy?
We are a small family.
Savage, has this tribe
grown stronger?
Despite the many
difficulties encountered?
This quartet is incredibly tight,
we can't wait to continue
our winning streak.
I'm glad to know
that we have
three close-knit tribes.
Because the amazing thing about Survivor
is that the game never stops.
So today is absolutely perfect
for a mix of teams.
Everybody throw down their bandana,
one more time !
We love you Terry.
The three most beautiful
words in the world, for me:
"Throw away your bandanas."
There will be two tribes:
Ta Keo and Bayon.
Angkor no longer exists.
Everybody,
unpack your bandanas.
Savage had Ta Keo, I was delighted.
Because if I had to choose
someone I was very close to,
it was Savage, without hesitation.
Take a seat on your new mats.
There have been two mixes now.
There are so
many past relationships,
I can't see
how people will associate.
It's a beautiful... Add a swear word.
Welcome to your home !
Kass. You threw away your bandana,
fired another Ta Keo,
and there you are again.
I'm happy,
because we have the rice and the chicken.
I have some doubts about Spencer,
because hey, you know...
We don't necessarily like each other very much.
In the heart of the matter!
Let's go !
Kass and I had a fight,
and at times we hated each other.
So, my agreement
with my sworn enemy
will determine my future in this game.
Wentworth,
in a new group of seven,
six of which were together at the start.
Do you immediately think
that you will be left out?
I'm the only original Ta Keo,
I know.
But I know some of them,
we collaborated in the last tribe.
So I'm excited
and I just want to win.
This mix is ​​perfect for me.
We have a perfect target in Wentworth.
But I always feel
to run a risk.
Because we have a lot
of dominant males.
It terrifies me.
Ready for your first
reward event
- as new tribes?
- Yes !
Today,
one member of each tribe
set off on a slippery course,
grabbing a ring along the way.
You will then try
to reach a pole by throwing it.
The first to succeed
scores a point.
The first tribe to three
wins the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes sir !
It will be a good way
to get to know each other.
A Survivor-style picnic,
delivered to your camp.
You chicken free,
pasta gratin,
and for dessert, brownies.
All is said.
One minute to get organized
and we'll get started.
Well, on and go.
For starters, Ta Keo,
who do you line up?
It will be Savage
against Jeremy,
in this first round.
The first to place
his ring on the post
scores a point.
It takes three.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Jeremy is moving.
Savage launches.
Jeremy has the ring,
Savage is right behind.
Jeremy scores before Savage,
and Savage,
less than half a second later!
That's crazy !
We don't get any tighter!
Bayon leads, 1 to nothing.
Next duel.
It will be Kass
against Fishbach.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Come on, Stephen, come on!
Get up, Stephen, get up!
Come on, buddy, come on!
Faster !
Kass wastes no time,
she has her ring.
- Stephen has his.
- Come on, Stephen!
Kass almost scores.
Steve, you calm down!
Fishbach,
can he do it now?
Right on the post!
- Right on it!
- Relax !
Don't spin it!
Kass can equalize now.
And she does!
Equality!
1 - 1 !
I am sorry.
Have faith in yourself!
We trust you,
trust yourself!
Go on !
Next duel.
It's Abi for Ta Keo,
Kimmi for Bayon.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
It's too short
for both women.
Kimmi will try to walk.
It is not easy.
Kimmi has her ring, Abi has hers.
Kimmi lance.
Kimmi, it does not hold!
Do not ! Do not ! Do not !
Carry on!
Abi thought it was over!
Abi can give Ta Keo the advantage.
Ta Keo leads,
2 - 1 !
Next round.
- It'll be Woo...
- Yeah, Woo!
...against Joe.
Dress up well, Joe!
Joe needs to score
for Ta Keo to stay in the game.
Go-y, Big Joe!
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Woo se lance.
Joe launches.
The two quickly reach the ring.
Woo... No!
And it's done!
Bayon scores!
Equality!
We go to sudden death!
This is the showdown!
From the first shot!
Everything will be played there.
Wiglesworth
against Wentworth.
The one who marks
win for his tribe
fried chicken, pasta gratin.
Let's go. For victory.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Wentworth se lance.
It's too short.
The two women are standing.
The first ring
wins for its tribe.
Almost, do it again!
- Go ahead !
- Its good.
Wentworth, for the win.
No, it doesn't!
Wiglesworth can win.
And There you go !
Wiglesworth wins for Ta Keo!
Huge reward!
Ta Keo, big reward.
A Survivor-style picnic
delivered to your camp.
You don't have to do anything but
enjoy it.
Take your things, leave.
- Enjoy the afternoon.
- Thank you, Jeff!
Bayon, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
Considering the makeup of my tribe,
I couldn't be happier.
I have Abi and Woo.
After what we went through at Angkor,
we are inseparable.
If I could just reunite
old Bayon, Kass and Ciera,
that would be the perfect equation.
I'm not about to leave.
Oh my God !
These brownies
are bigger than a fist!
Well done, everyone!
It was amazing!
Coming to this new
Ta Keo tribe, I thought...
to the great meal I was going to make,
but I had in the back of my mind
a stubborn thought:
how the hell
am I going to get by in this tribe?
How was Ta Keo,
the last days ?
We were relaxed because...
I know you don't believe it,
but the four of us who stayed
we were the calmest,
the least conspiratorial.
I can believe it.
When Kass and I had to do
what seemed impossible
and interact,
it was a little weird.
We were suspicious.
Can I have a piece of watermelon?
You can have ten.
I really didn't know
how to act.
So I tried
to treat her like the others.
But it never worked
in the past with Kass.
Do you realize we're here?
We got out of this hell!
No, you have no idea
how hard that was!
What we experienced in Angkor
was so traumatic
that having this victory,
this food,
was one of the best times
of my life. Honestly.
It seems silly...
A magnificent moment.
- Health !
- Your Keo! Health !
- Cheer !
- Health !
As soon as I looked at the other six,
I thought,
"I have five people."
Two former Bayon, Kass and Ciera,
and my Angkors.
How long have you been in Chicago?
Spencer is a great kid.
If I had a son,
I would like him to be like him.
Big heart, super brave.
I love this kid.
But I'll tell you,
and it's going to sound brutal.
I know that deep down,
Kass can't stand Spencer.
And I'm going to use it
to my advantage.
Tell me, if we lose immunity,
what do you want to do?
- What do you think ?
- I do not know.
Ciera and I are solid.
Abi, Woo and I... Inseparable.
So we have three of us.
As you wish.
- Great.
- And I know what you want.
- Are you speaking on behalf of Bayon?
- Spencer has to go.
- Yeah.
I would love to fire Spencer again.
I didn't want him
in my tribe.
I wanted to play Second Chance
without the Bledsoe.
- That's it. We five.
- Good.
Parfait.
what we said to each other,
it's like you'd say to Spencer,
"Ciera is leaving."
It will be a total surprise.
He won't see it coming.
Savage says,
"We're gonna fire Spencer and tell him..."
It's me who's leaving.
Me ? Uh, wait a bit!
It shows
who he trusts
that he'd rather expose me
than Woo.
Woo is not an original Bayon.
- You're not leaving.
- I believe in you.
- It's for the surprise.
- No shenanigans. Everything is fine.
When your name is mentioned,
it's never good.
I am ready to do
a lot of things for the team.
It's not part of it.
One, two, three, Ta Keo!
Voilà.
- Don't let him down!
- Of course not !
Don't set it on fire, either!
Oh, no one...! He is...
Oh, good! Good boy !
Kimmi ...
- How did he fall?
- Thin !
- Oh, my God, Joe!
- I say.
You have your work cut out for you,
because you are a Ta Keo.
I say. I knew I
would be in trouble here.
- You're the easy vote.
- I say.
- We have to figure out how to save you.
After the mixing of tribes,
strategically, I am well placed.
I have an original covenant from Bayon,
and on the Ta Keo camp,
myself, Kass, Ciera,
Kelley and Keith,
we made a deal.
So I wanna keep Kelley
around,
to have a majority in the merger.
You're stronger than Stephen and Kimmi.
I say.
This is the main argument.
It's certain.
Of course, I'm the easy vote.
I realize that.
But I have an immunity idol,
and if Joe wants to protect me,
I will hide behind him
as long as possible.
Thank you.
What do we do,
we stay the six together?
- What do you want... ?
- Fire Wentworth, okay?
I don't think we're losing, but...
Are we relying on strength?
I love Kimmi
but... on the tests...
I'm just saying...
For our first vote...
I say: "Bayon in force."
Why fuck this now?
The Bayon elders say,
"Let's stay between Bayon."
Joe says, "No.
Let's keep Wentworth and target Kimmi."
He's already trying to push
the core alliance
to tear each other apart.
Joe dit Kimmi.
- I do not like it.
- Of course not.
In fact, Joe betrayed
the Bayon alliance.
It's Survivor. We must react.
I don't trust him.
I would be happy to fire him.
Like, right away.
But I...
I don't want to start with Joe.
Stephen sticks to his guns,
he wants Joe out.
But I need a shield.
I need Joe
for as long as possible.
I don't want to be the biggest guy.
Good. We will discuss it.
At the reward event,
Jeremy said, "Be more confident,
believe in yourself!”
And you know what?
I give everything to win Survivor.
It doesn't
necessarily show up in the tests.
I know I'm no good at it.
You kidding.
You think-y. [???]
I have other strengths.
When it comes to strategic moves,
For me, that's the essence of the game.
The social strategy.
Building alliances, maintaining them,
target the right person
at the right time.
He's trying to take us out
to save Wentworth.
- He's not with the Bayons.
- OK.
It would be unexpected,
but in the long run...
You think it's a mistake,
that it's too soon.
Yeah.
If I can't drag
my allies into this shot,
I failed.
Rare are the opportunities
to eliminate its main competitors.
And... You know...
What annoys me, actually...
God, I can't
believe I'm crying!
It's the idea that...
That I could miss...
God, it's too stupid!
Missing that second chance,
missing my...
I invested myself so much,
the last time,
but I still failed.
And I'm investing so much
this time...
And the idea that I might fail,
because I would not have been able to convince
my team to do the necessary...
I blame myself for so many years
not to have eliminated
the young prodigy, the last time.
But wait for the game
to come to you and let it slip away,
that would be a real failure,
not to take control
when you have the chance.
It would be such a nice shot.
Such a nice shot.
It would be THE blow
which would set
the tone for the whole season.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
- Yes !
- Yes sir !
First of all, Ciera,
I take back the idol.
Merci.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will take part
in a taste test.
You will have to swallow
Cambodian specialties as soon as possible.
Who finishes first
scores a point for their tribe.
The first to four points
wins immunity,
is out of the vote.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be eliminated.
We did
this test 14 times.
Kelly, you were there originally.
Kimmi did it in season 2,
in Australia.
She didn't even try
to swallow the beef brain.
Savage took part,
just like Ciera,
who did not pass the 1st round.
Each tribe,
for the 1st round,
will line up two team members.
We will begin.
Here we go, round one.
Kimmi et Tasha
against Woo and Spencer.
Go ahead, reveal.
Oh Kimmi.
Oh my God !
It's alive ?
It'll be OK.
Each has two tarantulas to swallow.
The first duo to finish
scores the point.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready? Go!
Show me an empty mouth!
- Okay!
- Good, Tasha!
There are some guts in there.
And a little juice.
Kimmi you mal.
Everyone has their tarantulas
in their mouths, except Kimmi.
It's good for Spencer. Step back.
Avale!
It's good for Woo!
Ta Keo scores the 1st point!
Jeremy and Keith
against Savage and Ciera.
Everyone, reveal.
Giant water beetles.
There will be some tripe and juice.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
It's crispy and juicy.
Bravo, Keith ! Super, Jeremy !
Jeremy is on 2nd.
Savage is now on 2nd.
It's good for Savage and Jeremy.
Come on, Keith!
It's now between Ciera
and Keith, for the point.
It would be real redemption
for Ciera.
Come on, Ciera, it's good!
It's good for Keith!
Equality,
1 - 1 !
Very nice effort.
Fishbach and Wentworth
versus Kass and Abi.
Go ahead, reveal.
A pork groin.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
Go !
From the outset, everyone bites
frankly into it.
Abi goes there with a good heart.
- It's good, swallow!
- It's good, Abi!
Do you see that! First to finish!
Abi a fini.
New Showdown:
Kass against Wentworth.
They are left with the same amount.
Kass spits out a piece.
And it is successful!
Bayon scores and leads,
2 - 1 !
Good game !
We move on to individual face-to-face meetings.
Joe versus Wiglesworth.
Unveil.
A fried frog.
You're going to rock, Joe!
Bayon lead 2 - 1.
Survivors, ready? Go!
Come on, Joe!
Kelly stuffs everything!
- Go ahead, Kelly!
- Take it easy, Joe, she's got too much.
Joe takes it one piece at a time.
Two very different strategies.
Kelly could equalize now.
The tremble!
Il tremble, Kelly !
Kelly succeeds for Ta Keo!
She beats Joe!
Tied, 2 - 2.
Next round:
Woo, Kimmi.
Go ahead, reveal.
Pork brain.
I haven't eaten pork
in 30 years.
So, jumping straight
to the brains...
It's a bit extreme.
So I'm going to let Woo
eat some brains.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
Go !
- [???]
- Bon appetit!
Cheers !
Brain!
Sounds easy with Woo.
Not even five seconds!
Ta Keo leads,
3 - 2.
Next round.
Ciera, Wentworth.
Unveil.
Scorpion.
Ciera,
if you win,
you win the event for Ta Keo.
If you lose,
there will be a tie, 3 - 3.
Big pressure.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Come on Ciera!
Ciera could win
for her tribe.
It would be an amazing
second chance story.
Avale, avale!
Wentworth can equalize for Bayon,
to play another round.
The losers go to the council,
where someone will be eliminated from the game.
Wentworth scores for Bayon!
Ciera fails once again.
Tied, 3 - 3.
Ciera, why the tears?
I feel bad
for letting them down...
But no.
...but I'm proud
to have simply...
Once !
Kass versus Tasha.
Last dish.
Unveil.
Baluts.
Lord, this is violent.
Duck embryos.
Here we are, for the win.
The first to finish
sends the other tribe to the council.
Huge challenge.
Hands on the table until my signal.
Survivors, ready? Go!
Damn, yeah!
All at once!
Kass, don't vomit!
Don't look, turn around!
Kass is in trouble
with just a small piece.
And it goes up.
It's like the last time.
Everything is reassembled.
Go ahead, girl!
Ali's footwork now!
Tash succeeds for Bayon!
Bayon wins immunity
and sends Ta Keo to the council,
where someone will be eliminated from the game!
Bravo !
Kass, are tears
a physical reaction to tasting
Or an emotional reaction?
Both, I believe.
I felt like throwing up,
which made me cry a little.
And then, disappoint the tribe.
Bayon,
immunity is yours.
- Well deserved.
- Well done, Tasha!
No advice for Bayon.
Take your things,
return to camp.
- Enjoy the evening.
- Count it!
Good job.
Wow, really?
I haven't eaten
for 16 days, Jeff!
Ta Keo, I only have one date for you
tonight at the council,
where someone will be eliminated from this game.
Take your things,
return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
We have advice tonight.
I would love to eliminate Spencer
again.
If he was the first person
whose name I write,
I would be overjoyed.
Put a sad smiley on his box
and send him home.
Spencer Bledsoe, zero percent
chance of winning this game!
We lost the trial
and we have to face the council.
We already discussed who
we wanted to eliminate in such a case.
So for now,
if everything goes as planned,
we all vote spencer.
Everyone knows the plan.
It's locked.
Everyone has to say "Ciera".
So everyone says "Ciera".
But you don't have to worry.
Do not stress.
If he asks me,
I'll say I don't know.
- Don't let anyone see you talking to Ciera.
- OK.
Arriving here, in Ta Keo,
in the majority,
I finally feel
in harmony with the game,
and I can play.
What do you think will happen
tonight?
For me, Ciera has to go.
I'm on the sidelines,
at least for now.
But I wanted to play with Savage
from the start.
I think he's a good guy
I can trust.
Woo knows, Kass knows,
Abi knows, I know,
and now you know.
It's incredibly hard for me
to lead him on like this.
This kid is great.
But nothing will stand
in the way of my second chance.
So tonight,
everyone votes for Spencer.
Ciera votes for him.
- OK ?
- Yeah.
This will be one
of the surprise eliminations
the most devastating and unexpected
in Survivor history.
I am not joking.
It's my 2nd chance.
I will not have a 3rd.
Alright, here's the thing.
I don't like
that being my name.
Who does Savage think he is?
It was weird, he said,
"We'll say Ciera."
I said to myself: "Where does this come from?"
We're supposed to stay between Bayon,
and now there's Woo? It annoys me.
Terry
's departure triggered something in me.
This is my 2nd chance,
it could be my last.
And I want to go all out
to be able to say to my family:
"I gave it my all."
That's what I think.
I'd like to eliminate Spencer
before the merger.
It would be stupid to keep Woo
rather than Spencer.
Ciera wants to eliminate Woo.
I didn't want to play with Spencer.
I was happy not to be
in his tribe so far.
And when everyone said,
"Let's take out Spencer first!",
it was almost
served to me on a platter.
But then you have to step back.
Because there is better to do with him
for the moment.
We should talk.
I don't want to rehash Cagayan...
Non.
...but it would be nice
to review everything.
Yeah. Stuff happens.
And some might benefit you.
Because you seem out of place to me.
I really like Savage.
So it's interesting.
Savage said,
"Why not aim for Spencer?
We'll tell him it's Ciera."
Savage is after me?
When did he say that?
Right after the feast.
We were in the shelter.
If Kass is telling the truth,
that Savage sees me
as a target,
it only remains for me to choose
where to flee.
I'm leaning towards
a surprise elimination of Woo...
Do we have a good group for that?
Ciera, Abi, me and you,
that's four.
I'm fooling around with the devil tonight.
I might have to play with Kass.
I will finally have my revenge
on Spencer Bledsoe.
Two ideas are circulating.
Savage, Wiglesworth et Woo
think Spencer is going to leave.
Spencer, Abi and Ciera
think Woo is going to leave.
We agree ?
I will have no hesitation.
I have no interest
in doing anything else.
We are too strong like this.
I have the opportunity
to write "Spencer"
and say goodbye to him.
At this moment,
it remains a possibility,
given the votes.
This is the first advice
of my second chance.
Which Kass will show up?
Calme-Kass or Chaos-Kass?
The little angel and the devil
are both on my shoulders.
"Spencer !"
"Woo !"
"Calme !"
"Chaos !"
They are there !
What's going to happen ?
Even I don't know.
For those who haven't
come to the board yet,
grab a torch
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
We are on the 16th day
of this
Second Chance experience.
It's really this:
a chance to see if you can
change the way you play
and improve your result.
Savage, what
have you been working on?
My personal game.
Develop deep relationships
starts with identifying
reliable and loyal people.
I think I've done it well.
Spencer, what's
your second chance been around so far?
Come in this game,
and see people
for what they are: people.
And it's difficult in a game
where you have to trick, dominate, last.
Absolutely. This is perhaps
the hardest context for this.
And, however, the most important.
Woo,
some would say
that what harmed you the 1st time,
is not having seen
that Tony was manipulating you
for you to make
a million dollar mistake.
Yeah, absolutely.
In my 1st season, I failed
to understand that to succeed
in this game,
you have to know how
to be ruthless.
I'm at peace with that.
Kass, there's all these
2nd chance stories,
but you continue to play.
How do you navigate
in so many
levels of relationships?
Yes, it's hard to follow.
I was in Bayon,
at first, with Savage.
Are we still welded between Bayon?
I know Woo from Cagayan.
Spencer, you know...
Ciera and I have been together
since day 1.
So who is close to whom,
and why?
This is very fun.
Is it Chaos-Kass
or the new Kass?
I don't know which Kass is here tonight.
Savage, this must be
a little disconcerting.
You never know
if Chaos-Kass is angry,
or if she's telling the truth,
or if she's about to take you out.
I was with Kass for a long time
in the original Bayon.
I have to say
that I haven't seen Chaos-Kass yet.
I saw a kind and loyal Kass.
Ciera, what do you think
of all these relationships?
How do you manage them?
Managing people
is one of my strengths.
I meet someone
and I follow my instincts.
I know Savage was with me,
but he bonded with Woo.
Everything flows
of the battle between your instincts,
your heart, and your brain.
Savage,
do you feel uncomfortable
when your name is mentioned,
whatever the sentence and the reason,
to the board?
Non.
And why ?
Because I have no doubts
about tonight.
My judgment is my judgment.
If I screw up, it's my fault.
Ciera, when you hear that,
"I'm confident,"
this is where Survivor
gets fun.
If everyone
plays at the highest level,
everyone is confident.
And yet, someone is going to leave.
It's the scariest part of the board.
We all have a second chance,
and we all have our plans.
And someone's plan
isn't going to work.
Spencer, it's all here.
Someone's plan
isn't going to work.
Yeah. Everyone is confident,
to varying degrees.
And that won't be the case
when you take out the extinguisher.
Good. It's time to vote.
Wiglesworth, over.
I write your name
for one reason only.
You are too good at this game.
My fate tonight
is in the hands of Chaos-Kass.
God help me!
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Spencer.
Woo.
Three Spencer votes, one Woo vote.
Two votes Woo.
Wow. Equality.
Three votes Woo, three votes Spencer,
one vote remains.
Sixth person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
Wow.
Bring me your torch.
Merci.
Surprise elimination!
Woo, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
This season,
the game is played at a very high level.
In other words, you will have to continue
adapt your game
if you want to go all the way.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
It's a hard way
to quit the game,
but I had a blast.
This game is hardest,
mentally as well as physically,
so win or lose,
it's the fulfillment of a lifetime.
And I'm thrilled
to be part of the Survivor family.
Team Survivor ST
http://survivor-st.forumgratuit.org/
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro : Lény
Re-synchro version HD : aymeric000
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The merger is coming.
"Congratulations, you merged!"
The game is launched. When we reach
fusion, things will change.
And Chaos-Kass is back.
The limit is drawn.
Everyone thinks about their partners
and the manipulations to be put in place.
Don't get in the way of my second chance!
You released the beast.
For ten years, I waited for
my 2nd chance in Survivor.
But when Jeff woke me up
in the middle of the night,
going back to my family
was my only thought.
My son Danny needed
a heart transplant.
And he got her, and he's fine.
And to think that I thought I was the one
who had a second chance!
The survivor of the 2nd chance,
here it is!
Le don d'organes peut donner
une 2e chance dans la vie.
Découvrez comment aider quelqu'un
à devenir un vrai survivant.
Allez sur donatelife.net.
CBS Aide.