translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Survivor is the most
physically demanding
and emotionally challenging
game shows.
It spares you nothing...
Are you retiring from the game?
...while giving you the opportunity
to show who you are.
For those who win...
The winner of Survivor Cagayan!
...the reward is great:
a million dollars,
and a peak that
may never be reached again.
But for those who lose...
Did Woo make
a million dollar mistake?
...the consequence is often
a continuous nightmare of "what if...?",
which never ends.
Until now.
I'm happy to say,
Kelly Wiglesworth:
you will have a 2nd chance!
Get on stage!
This season,
for the very first time,
we offer Survivor to fans.
20 former players
who only played once
were selected
by national vote.
They have a 2nd chance
to finish what they started.
Some have waited
more than a decade.
They came to Cambodia,
a country with an impressive,
moving and powerful history
which arouses emotions.
She vividly reminds
you that the past can haunt you
and provides inspiration
to seize a 2nd chance.
15 years ago, I was in Borneo,
the 1st season,
and I almost won.
Win the 1st edition
of Survivor...
I lasted 39 days
and lost by one vote.
That's why I'm here.
It has been tickling me for 15 years,
little by little.
I am much stronger
and much smarter.
I am a mother now.
I gave life.
I can do anything at this point.
My life is a dream.
I have the perfect wife.
My children are wonderful.
I have a great job.
Nothing negative in my life, except...
My exit has haunted me for 12 years.
I didn't get over it.
To cure my Survivor ailment,
I have to give 1000%.
I will give my all in this game.
And it's going to be epic.
During my last participation,
frankly, I was arrogant.
Kass.
Zero chance of winning this game.
I saw Survivor
as a game of chess.
But I have matured a lot.
I grew emotionally.
People are not pieces,
you have to connect humanly.
Being emotionally more lucid,
I think I am, in my life,
in the best dispositions
to play and win this game.
My experience in Australia
was abbreviated too quickly.
I want a 2nd chance
to achieve my dream: go all the way.
The temple of Angkor Wat
is a perfect metaphor for the game.
We are a little damaged,
but we can consolidate.
14 years is a long time
to finish the last chapter.
Last time
I played with my dad.
- You mustn't give the impression...
- No.
...to be aggressive,
to say what to do.
playing with my dad
caused my downfall, clearly.
I probably should have
voted against him.
But that's in the past.
I can use this 2nd chance
to do what I wanted to do
and play better.
I really screwed up the first time.
I was scared at first.
Having discovered that I could
socially navigate the game,
I decided to take action.
Eleventh person eliminated
from Survivor: Blood vs. Water...
Alas, it had to start
with the elimination of my mother.
I like you.
This time I want to be fearless.
I want to be from the start
who I was at the end
and leave everything on the island.
The first time,
I was "Tasha the nice one".
It's the least strategic game
I've ever played.
It's really stupid.
I didn't want to disappoint
my family or the people of my church
by my way of playing.
When I returned
to my church, they said:
"You need to be more aggressive,
lie and betray,
like everyone else!"
So if the Saints
think it's okay,
it's OK !
I'm here to make a million,
and when it's over,
I'll pray for forgiveness.
This 2nd chance
means more than anything to me.
In Australia, I jumped off a pole
for peanut butter.
I gave up a million
doing that.
- Peanut butter!
- Anyone who gives up,
can join me.
Rehashing history,
over and over again, for 14 years,
it reaches you.
Jeff, the tribe has spoken.
This is my chance
to rewrite my own story.
I'm more mature, much smarter,
and I won't give up anything
for peanut butter.
When I was little, with my father,
we were watching Survivor.
It was very hard
not being able to have him come
for the visit of relatives.
I really wanted to do it,
prove to myself that I could go that
far in the game.
Joe, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks, Jeff.
I failed, and it beat me down.
Now is the time for me
to make it happen. Now.
We all have a little devil in us.
I was a bit of a troublemaker
in my season.
Good luck !
Chaos Kass. She lives somewhere
deep inside me.
But if I don't change
someone will have my skin.
I like the trace
I have left so far.
I like chaos.
Only must change
their perception of me.
And at the fusion, if I'm there,
it will be the apocalypse.
When I think back to my season,
I made a lot of mistakes.
I created a lot of problems...
I'm your friend, but fuck me
and you're dead.
It was a mistake.
I threw a coco
on Skupin's head.
- Good God !
- Sorry.
It was a mistake.
I was too rough with Lisa.
You insult my intelligence.
Are you trying to deceive me?
I am not stupid !
I should not have.
But I have a second chance to come back
and correct these small errors.
But I like to have fun.
Bad guys have more fun.
Last time, with my wife,
she occupied half of my thoughts.
You send your wife into exile.
What do you feel ?
I do not know.
It was emotional, with Val.
I really like.
Knowing what she does
is important to me.
I was not focused.
Eighth person eliminated
and second member of the jury...
So I was taken by surprise
by my own allies.
I came back, I cashed.
Now I want the money for Val
more than for me.
I have to go through it all again.
I come looking for redemption.
Welcome to
Survivor: Cambodia, Second Chance!
It's a unique season,
because you are all veterans
who have only played once
and have not won.
In other words: you failed
to achieve your goal.
And you have a 2nd chance
to finish what you started.
To further fuel
your motivation, you have been chosen,
elected by those who looked at you
the first time,
our audience.
Ciera, what does it do?
We didn't choose you
the fans chose you.
It puts pressure.
You don't want to disappoint your family,
let alone America.
You could say
that we would have forgotten you,
that was 14 years ago.
It has been a long time.
Have you often thought
about doing this again?
Often. Very often.
I feel, or hear,
the stage fright in your voice.
A little, yeah.
There is excitement,
stage fright, emotion.
It's very strong.
Joe, you played
in our most recent season.
It's almost like going home,
taking a shower and leaving.
Yeah, the transition
was pretty quick.
And here I am with the great players
I watched growing up.
People who inspired my game.
Some of these great players...
Terry, the beast of trials!
I was like,
"I would love to do that!"
They paved the way for this game.
And we have to turn
to Kelly Wiglesworth.
I'm here, Jeff!
The first finalist
of our very first season,
15 years ago.
It's weird to hear Joe say,
"I grew up with..."
Hey, say!
We are old!
One vote, Wiglesworth.
One vote
allowed Richard Hatch
to beat you.
Do you often think back
to this final piece of advice?
Uh... Every day.
Good. 20 players
of 30 seasons.
All with one thing in common:
you waited for a 2nd chance.
She's there.
Let's go.
In your boats
you will find a bag of bandanas
as well as a map
to your respective beaches.
Two boats on the left.
Peih-Gee,
Vytas,
Deitz,
Your tribe is called Ta Keo.
Ta Keo!
Two boats on the right.
and Kimmi.
Your tribe is called Bayon.
The tribes are named
after temples in Angkor Wat,
a site crossed while coming here.
Good. On this ship,
enough to make camp life
much easier.
At my top,
you'll get off the boat,
will come on this one
and gather
all the material possible.
But there is a surprise.
100 meters behind this boat,
there is another boat.
Suspended on this boat:
a large bag of rice.
The first person
to collect the bag
earns it for his tribe.
The dilemma is therefore:
how long to
spend on this boat
to gather the necessary
for the camp,
and when to leave with the raft
to try to have the rice?
Shit !
This is, in fact,
your first test.
And it starts now.
Get on the boat,
gather gear, quick!
Before another takes it all!
Nothing is easy in Survivor.
Spencer arrives first.
Here is Joe.
Come on, get moving!
Climb!
20 people trying
to collect as many as possible!
15 years for some of you.
All this accumulated energy
is finally released.
Here we are, your 2nd chance
is now!
People up, people down!
Everyone collaborates!
Stephen, catch!
At some point, you will have to detach
your raft and go towards the rice.
It's the sissy game!
There are pots
and pans.
Watch your heads,
it's flying everywhere!
Varner lowers
a large load.
What has value,
what does not?
That's right Jeremy, get that down!
We must go.
Ta Keo is on the go!
Bayon prepares to leave.
It's the race for rice!
Once ready,
release your raft!
You have a machete
to cut the rope.
The Ta Keos are on their boat.
Varner frees her.
The Ta Keo are free.
The Bayons are on their boat.
Joe cuts the rope.
Its good ! Come on, let's go!
It's rice racing now.
Which tribe will collaborate best
from the start of the game?
Fifteen years ago,
Wiglesworth was a river guide.
Now
she is swimming in front of the raft.
Ta Keo took the lead.
Bayon is in big trouble.
Their raft almost sinks.
- Can someone swim?
- Yup.
Carry on. Bring me closer.
Wiglesworth is always
faster than the raft.
She's done for.
Go on !
I go.
Good luck.
Yeah, Joe!
Joe is in the water for Bayon.
He springs into action
and tries to catch up with Wiglesworth.
- Joe is coming, go!
- Alright, I'm going.
We have a showdown!
Woo is in the water for Ta Keo.
- Come on, Joe!
- Come on, Woo!
It overtakes Wiglesworth.
Joe tries to catch up to Woo.
Woo will be the first to the boat.
Woo has the rice for Ta Keo!
On the way to your beaches!
"Second chance", let's go!
39 days,
20 people,
a survivor !
When I spotted the flag,
I wanted to cry,
I was so excited!
Like when I got
my first black belt.
A great honor.
- Great ! Good game !
- Glad to be here!
In this "2nd chance",
I don't just play for myself,
I play for everyone
who voted for me.
Nice to meet you.
We put the rice here, Vytas!
It might sadden Kimmi,
but we can kill him.
Nice to meet you
in the flesh!
Yes ! Neither brother nor father,
everything is fine!
- A hug ?
- And how !
- Mr. Jeff Varner!
- I gave you a hug from afar.
It's a bit like...
the 1st day of Borneo was repeating itself.
So where do we start
building?
My first thought was:
let's set up camp!
We use this sagging tree,
we put a beam up to the bag, there,
okay with you ?
We'll get some air over here.
For me it is important
to work hard
and to be useful on the camp.
And we immediately saw
who were the workers.
me, wow...
Do we put the frame like this?
...and Vytas and Spencer.
- Not like that.
- Oh, like that!
- This way.
- Very well.
When people won't know
where to sleep and it's raining,
I hope they remember
I was there, building the shelter.
But we don't do more
"old school Survivor" than I do!
Hey, since your brother
was old school,
- I make you "old school" honorary!
- Thanks !
I played a long time ago.
There is a huge difference
between old school and new school.
You pass it over here,
and you tie it under there.
Alright, that sounds good.
One of the differences today,
is that the game starts
almost immediately,
as soon as we reach the beach.
Whereas in the old school
it was more like:
"We need shelter and fire."
Let's put this here, so that
the support is fixed.
My social game,
for the past 9 years,
haunted me somewhat.
By building the shelter,
I heard my wife say to me:
"Don't let people
walk away alone!
Make sure
to participate in the social game!"
Because it's a big part
of Survivor.
- How do you feel ?
- Excited to be here.
You will be the backbone!
You know how to make fire,
that kind of stuff.
Better than me, for sure.
Better than most.
- We'll see.
- The Beast of Trials!
I'm good as a team now.
My son is a Survivor fanatic.
He made me a file
on everyone.
He said,
"Ally with Spencer!
He's a good guy,
solid, loyal..."
Children of Terry,
Thank you for your father's trust in
me!
Because I don't trust anyone.
I will play according to my interests.
- I support you.
- I know you're tough.
I want to play with
strong, rational people.
It means a lot to me,
really.
I'm a
new school player,
but I'm a fan
of all schools.
So it's important for me
to have real relationships
and know what people think.
I will have more face-to-face
the first three days here,
this time,
than during all Cagayan.
Have you seen my bag?
I can't find it anywhere.
I'm worried about my bag.
He was there.
- Whose is this?
- Not for me.
- Did you have anything in it?
- Yes, my bracelet.
I'm worried,
because my bag has disappeared.
He can not be found.
Abi, do you want to take this bag?
- I want my bag.
- Sure.
My bracelet is in it.
I have this leather bracelet,
with gold stuff,
not real gold, but hey,
It's kind of my superpower bracelet .
It was hanging on this tree
and it is nowhere to be found.
It's very strange.
Abi is obsessed with her bag.
She doesn't need anything in it
except her bracelet.
Too weird.
The last time, in the Philippines,
my emotions took over.
It contributed to my downfall.
I would like to check all the bags.
My bracelet is in it,
and my bag can't be found.
- Did you look at the ones on the tree?
- Yeah.
This time, I planned to control
my emotions and my character.
It's part of the game
I want to play now.
But it's so hard
not to get your fangs out!
Take that, nail!
I have the rhythm!
- Is it okay, Kimmi?
- Yeah !
Well done, my daughter!
It's hollow!
The tribe seems
in very good spirits.
Everyone works
and gets along well.
One seems to have
a very peaceful mantra.
I hope, by coming a second time,
to be able to rewrite my story.
It comes back to you, Tash?
I can give
my basic weaving class again.
We didn't have palm fronds,
so I'm in training.
One of my three talents
in life.
Isn't it crazy
to be here again?
- Yeah, amazing.
- I am so happy.
I love that.
We can't hang on to it,
but it should hold.
I never imagined coming back,
but here I am!
Glad to be there!
Let's build the frame.
The last time, I advanced
cushy a good time.
Even without alliance,
I reached 4th place,
it's not nothing.
But finishing 4th is hard to swallow.
I'm not going to change much,
maybe make some adjustments.
We're just making the awning.
He doesn't need to go very far.
It could be right there.
This 2nd time
is going to be very different.
No fumbling this time!
It's a new season.
We forget everything.
It's from the past.
It's season 31,
and all is well between us.
I feel the tribe.
I knew, in my season,
that I was seen as a threat.
So I thought,
"Let's talk to Keith!"
All I hope
is that if Keith hears my name,
he will come and tell me.
- In my head, we were OK.
- For me too.
I'm trying to act strategically
and think this season.
So I wanted Tasha,
probably the strongest woman here.
As long as it's not me... I
'm fine.
And I wanted Savage.
Savage looks outspoken from the collar.
Another physical threat.
I tell you, I support you.
We agree.
- What about Fish?
- I do not feel it.
But above all, I wanted Joe.
No better shield than him.
A great group there.
Savage is in.
- I like it.
- Cool.
And it worked out well.
It would be silly to screw this up.
Everyone works.
I think we have the
strongest group.
We can move forward in the game.
We could make some noise.
We have to stick together
and support each other.
I must tell you.
True story.
My daughters are going to kill me, but...
They're 17 and 15.
We were watching your season.
I am sitting between my two daughters.
And my eldest,
without really thinking about it, said:
"He is perfect."
And the younger one says:
I said, "Girls, I'm here!"
I learned last time
that I was the most dangerous.
You have to act to make sure
you progress in the game.
So either the dominant males
kill each other,
or they team up
and work together.
In the case of Jeremy and Savage,
I think we all agree
to help each other.
Hey, guys!
You are serious!
Come on Andrew!
Andrew, you're a crack!
- He felled that tree!
- He just killed him.
It falls !
And that's it for the tree!
Guys really impress me.
Seriously, that changes everything.
I feel like the last time:
out of place in my tribe,
with guys different from me.
Fishbach, a fish out of water,
once again!
The history of Tocantins
could repeat itself.
I was lost,
and I bonded with someone
who was in his element.
And we went all the way.
JT was too awesome,
he tore me down in the end.
I won't make the same mistake.
I wish I was...
more in my element here.
With construction and everything.
What can I do but sit
down and clap?
All these big badass in my tribe,
it's my nightmare!
- Are you good at weaving?
- Nope.
Either I will have total control
of my tribe...
It makes no sense !
...or I will make crates of them
and quickly explode in flight.
I need water.
I am dizzy.
- It's hot.
- Let's take a break.
Go quietly.
There is a lot of excitement.
- I say. A lot.
- The adrenaline. It climbs and...
We're all knackered, yeah.
When I first played,
I ended up in a female tribe.
And they wanted my skin.
I had the chance
to get into their good graces.
- Glad we're together.
- Yeah me too.
Some say,
"He manipulated those women!"
But no. I just manipulated
some of their views.
This is the heart of Survivor.
And I'm good at it.
- Where do you come from ?
- Hong Kong.
I have a very good friend
who looks like you.
Chinese, freckles,
she's very beautiful.
- Thanks.
- Very beautiful.
But I don't want to
come across as a manipulator.
Because it is dangerous,
especially at the beginning.
- We never spoke.
- I say ! It's nice to be here!
- In old Blood vs. Water!
I say !
I want women to think,
"He's nice, he's helpful,
he's great,
I want to get to know him better."
Do not stress !
Vytas ...
I see Vytas as a bootlicker.
I saw it that way in its 1st season,
and it's the same now.
Go ahead, Woo, drive that nail in!
From the outset, I wanted to embark
the people who interest me
and lock the thing,
from the start.
Because having a second chance
is a rare opportunity,
especially in this game.
I'm not going to spoil it.
Vytas has plenty of connections.
I don't know
if you noticed it,
but Vytas is related to Terry through Aras,
Aras and Terry having played together.
- It's just.
- And Aras and Terry are super close.
So Vytas and Terry too.
They will probably hide from it.
Vytas has way too many links,
overall, in the game.
And he also has obvious connections
with the other tribe.
Ciera and Vytas performed together.
They are super close.
You are very observant.
I don't see any of that.
- I have to get in the bath.
- Everything is fine !
- It's been a while.
- You have to restart the machine.
Shirin has an impressive speed.
This train is on,
and I'm glad to be on board.
I am on board. It doesn't matter
who takes me to the woods,
I answer "yes".
- I don't know Kelley.
- Peih-Gee...
- Kelley...
- I don't know her, but I love her.
So let's hire her.
Good grief, grandma, calm down!
I just arrived!
The driver decides
the speed of the train,
and she's on her toes...
What's bugging my ass?!
- And Peih-Gee?
- We'll see later.
- I do not know her.
- Let's get some water.
Peih-Gee... We'll see that by feeling.
My first time, in Australia,
it was all for the adventure.
There was no strategy.
I haven't played for 15 years.
Do we do this now?
I'm not in my element.
I don't know what to do
or where to turn.
I don't know
if it's to have waited 15 years,
but it's the right time for me.
I will be 50 next year.
It's quite a milestone.
Most men
go through a crisis at this age.
They buy a Corvette,
cheat on their wives.
I go to Survivor.
It's not a crisis,
it's a quest.
The 2nd half of my life begins
with Survivor Second Chance.
I feel so weird,
it's like...
I'm the old one, but I feel
like a newborn.
- Okay, where's my bracelet?
- In one of the hanging bags.
No, I looked everywhere.
She has my bag!
- You found it !
- Is that Peih-Gee's bag?
- My bracelet!
It has his name on it.
I do not know what to think.
But I found my bracelet.
It was a bag
with a label: "Peih-Gee".
I stick my hand to it,
and the first thing I get out of
it is my damn bracelet.
It's very interesting, isn't it?
Are you going to say something?
No. But now I know.
I found my bracelet
in Peih-Gee's bag.
- I found my bracelet...
- Really?
- ...in Peih-Gee's bag.
- Not possible !
- Promised sworn.
- Did she take it by accident?
I don't want to say anything,
I give him the benefit of the doubt.
She has no reason
to steal my bracelet.
But in my head, I say to myself:
"Maybe she was trying
to wake up the Brazilian dragon."
You know what ? Let her stuff
that damn bag into [beep]!
But even if sometimes, deep inside me,
I want to scream,
to let my character
take over,
I can't afford it.
This is my second chance,
I have to play it smart.
It's very strange, because...
I've talked about it a lot, haven't I?
- In effect.
- Abundantly.
Abi-Maria generated weirdness
around this bracelet which,
according to her, I had taken.
I wanted to settle it with her,
so she won't think
I stole that bracelet from her.
They tell me your bracelet
was in my bag.
Yeah, it was in your bag.
Do you know what happened?
- There was a bag without a label.
- Yeah, that was mine.
And I didn't realize,
I thought it was empty,
so I took it and...
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
I wanted you to know,
I know you've been looking for it.
Yes, I looked for it for quite a while.
During my last participation,
I didn't create
the relationships I should have.
I have learned :
make friends, but keep
your enemies even closer.
So, no hard feelings?
Don't go thinking...
Like I said,
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
Look,
they're trying to make a fire!
It's a big part of the game.
Even the most important.
Fire, water, shelter.
We feel it!
It's coming !
It didn't work out in my season,
so I don't know,
but to concentrate the light,
we can take a leaf
and make a pinhole,
- it focuses...
- Or a drop of water.
This second chance
it sets the tone for everyone,
"this time that's it".
I was afraid of not being chosen,
having betrayed someone.
But people surely know
that I'm going to play, that it's going to blow up.
A lot of people are there
to prove something.
I'm just here to win.
No matter how.
Where did Stephen go?
I do not know.
I believe he is "looking for an idol".
Oh really ?
Gone to look for wood,
I couldn't help
looking for an idol.
Because if I can't find it,
someone else will.
But this beach is huge,
there are lots of trees.
I went to this disgusting swamp,
it was very filthy.
I can't imagine Jeff Probst
hiding an idol in this swamp.
But the game is on.
It's a perfect place
for an idol.
A crazy pond
in the middle of nowhere.
I need the idol,
or create a strong bond
with someone
who hopefully
won't hold it against me
for being a binocular.
I'm sure my trick
has been noticed.
I hope it won't
mark me. Probably, yes.
"Fishbach is looking for the idol!"
Zut !
You are there, my brother.
- You and it is!
How beautiful it is.
We have fire!
It's teamwork!
Teamwork is magic!
- Great !
- It's not great ?
- This is what to do!
- Well done, Joe!
I remain amazed
that Joe made a fire.
And starting from scratch!
And I prayed above!
- It's thanks to you !
- Did I pray or what?
Joe was amazing.
In this environment,
with this humidity,
We found Mother Nature
on the 1st day by making a fire.
And that, in my opinion,
this is a very good sign for the future.
Cheers to Survivor!
I feel dirty.
- That's the game !
- After just one day.
After just one day.
Everything turns.
2nd day, and it's like
I've never played.
It's hard.
It's hot.
I want to cool off.
This game is way too fast.
I can't follow.
But I play hard.
I try not to show it,
but I play hard.
Who do you see regrouping, so far?
Make sure we agree.
- The ones from the shelter, I think.
- The ones from the shelter?
- Yeah.
- Against those on the beach.
- We are in those of the beach?
- I do not know.
'Cause I did both,
you know?
I walked on the beach
and worked on the shelter.
There are two divisions
on this beach.
Those who built the shelter,
the old school.
The old school
wants to do it the old way.
You work, and that's your value.
The new school
just wanna hit the beach
and recruit me into an alliance.
But I don't want to betray
those in the shelter, my people.
- I'm in a funny situation.
- Me too.
I believe we are in the same place.
If you had to pick someone
to go first...
I believe Shirin
wants to eliminate Vytas.
We should aim for someone like Abi.
It's my 2nd chance,
and I'm in the unknown,
I am lost.
Old school, new school,
what to do?
- Hello !
Hello Sunshine !
We need water.
I have to consider how
I played last time.
I didn't take
enough risks.
We don't always get a second chance.
I'm not going to spoil it.
And in general, the immunity idol
is already in the camp when we arrive.
So I expect,
in a "second chance" season,
there must be one.
All those palm fronds!
It hard bump.
I chose to go for
leaves and coconuts.
I knew it would give me
the opportunity to look for the idol.
Let's put some stuff in the way,
and if somebody comes,
I'll say, "I put that there
for you to bring back."
Yeah !
Sneaky, sneaky!
Where is the idol?
Damn it.
Everything looks the same here!
Little idol, where can you be?
Where can you be?
yuck. Not in there.
I searched for quite a while.
And then
I pass a tree...
Oh, brothel!
Brothel!
Not possible. Oh my God !
It's incredible.
I think I just
found the immunity idol.
Oh my God ! Yes !
It is enormous ! Oh my God !
I hope... What is it?
"Congratulations! You have found
the clue leading to the Immunity Idol."
Alright, I got a little carried away.
"What you seek
is within your reach,
but will require audacity.
At the end of the immunity test,
you will place your raft
on a support with four tripods.
Hidden under the right front tripod
is the idol.
But are you fearless enough
to take her in full ordeal,
in front of your unsuspecting comrades
?
If so, immunity is yours."
Usually
the idol is somewhere on the camp.
That she's on trial is crazy,
because everyone can see you
if you are not discreet enough.
It's incredible.
If, on trial,
I think I can do it...
I am so happy !
...I'll try to take it.
Otherwise, it will be super blatant.
Bayon, it's time!
Go on !
It's time to go.
This is our official flag.
He tears up !
"15 years waiting to come back...
The first race ever!
Then a first player is eliminated...
And then we're not kidding."
The first event ever contested?
Our first test
will be the very first test
of the very first Survivor.
And to have had the first mail
after having waited so long,
I was a bit nervous.
It's Survivor,
but this is a family.
We are ten, strong and in tune.
And in this ordeal,
everyone here will be on their toes.
And we support each other.
Mail makes me nervous.
Everyone knows I'm
one of the smallest here.
The first time,
I was trying to minimize it,
not to make
a big deal out of it.
Now
I just want to do my part.
I think I'm stronger.
Then we come back down and let go,
we take it all out.
All the negative.
Joe does yoga!
I don't do yoga.
In the morning, I get up, have
a coffee and go to work.
Like 99% of Americans.
Nobody wants to see me lean
forward, [???] and all that.
Joe is a free spirit,
long hair, great.
He's great on the camp.
He brings things back,
cuts things up.
But yoga... It's Joe.
...finishing to inhale.
Today we did...
Not yoga, "joega".
And frankly,
I was a little distracted.
I was trying to breathe,
but I was only thinking of one thing:
Joe's body.
How to concentrate?
Look at the !
But we have a good state of mind
to win this event.
I'm excited.
We are pumped up.
Put your feet back. So.
Pull your butt back.
Flat heels. Lower the torso.
Here it is, like this.
It is a modified version
of the dog pose.
Feel the tension in the chest.
Before the test,
Vytas showed me
some yoga positions.
Reminds you :
- against the tree, like this...
- I'll try to remember.
- Against the boat, like that...
- You'll give me a little quiz.
And that's good
if you're feeling hunched over.
He does too much sometimes!
He's so yoga, and...
Chrinavasana, monkey position,
vanamasala mala.
You lift your chest.
You arch your back, you release
the armpits, and the collarbone.
Vytas plays the fool,
he tries to flirt, and it annoys me.
It's absolutely not sexy.
Go away ! Like an insect.
Oust!
So I want Vytas out.
He died for me. He annoys me.
You can even do it
against cover, for example.
The thing is...
- She looks at your idol!
- I don't want to see his idol.
- Abi wants yoga?
- Nope.
- How do you feel ? Your body ?
- Great.
Abi is not easy to deal with.
People annoy him very quickly.
She sent me
negative vibes this morning.
I wouldn't be surprised
if she whispered "let's turn Vytas".
I have to make sure
she doesn't get too comfortable.
Because the first time
I lacked lucidity,
I was too confident.
A) we want to win the competitions.
But B), if we don't win,
we need Spencer on our side.
I was thinking of firing Abi
from the start.
Fire Abi is smart,
because we can rally everyone.
Because no one likes it.
But the day
has only just begun.
Someone might do
something really stupid later,
pass the test.
But if the tide turns against Abi,
I will just have to let it go.
Over here, everyone!
First immunity test.
I had only one obsession:
the immunity idol.
I only had that in mind.
- Ready for today's challenge?
- Oh yeah !
I love this enthusiasm!
Today,
the two tribes will swim
to a raft,
where you will light a torch.
You will use
it to light a series of fires
up to a support
where you will place your raft.
Then one person per tribe
will make a long pole
out of sticks and string.
With this pole,
you will recover a key.
The 1st tribe to open their portal
and light the last fire...
gain immunity.
Unvoted.
You all know
that's what you want in this game.
It's security
and certainty.
Without, you risk trouble.
Furthermore,
you also play
for a reward.
A huge Survivor-style fire kit.
Flint,
kerosene, matches,
a tarp for your wood.
Something to make your life easier.
Losers:
council, where someone
will be the first person
eliminated from Survivor Second Chance.
This trial is very special
in the history of Survivor.
"The Quest for Fire" was
the very first test
from the very first episode.
Kelly Wiglesworth was there.
She lost.
Thanks for reminding me, Jeff!
It is therefore a second chance
with very high stakes.
One minute to organize yourself
and here we go.
Let's go.
Immunity and fire are at stake.
Survivors, ready?
Here we are, your first test
for a second chance!
The raft can only move forward
when everyone is there.
Tasha arrives last.
Come on, forward!
Ta Keo part in premier.
Bayon is just behind.
We must collaborate
to move this raft.
You have to communicate well.
Keith holds the torch for Bayon.
Spencer is going to take
the torch for Ta Keo.
Quick !
Spencer lights
the first fire for Ta Keo.
Keith lights the 1st fire for Bayon.
It's neck and neck.
Spencer lights the second fire.
Keith lights the second fire
for his tribe.
Keith lost his fire.
- Light it up, Keith!
- We have to turn it back on, Keith!
- Light it up!
- Keith is wasting precious time.
- Come on, Keith!
Spencer, for Ta Keo,
lights its third fire.
Come on, Keith!
- Keith struggles to rekindle the fire.
- Don't drop the torch!
Keith attempts to light
the third fire for Bayon.
Its good !
Spencer lit
Ta Keo's fourth fire.
Bayon is now slowing down.
Ta Keo widens the gap.
Spencer lit the 5th fire of Ta Keo.
Get out of the water!
Keith reaches out for Bayon.
Its good !
The Ta Keo are in the lead.
They continue to light the fires.
Keith still struggles with fire.
He is wasting time.
Keith lit
Bayon's fifth fire.
The Ta Keo
lit all their fires.
You must now place
your raft on the support.
Kelly Wiglesworth gets down to business.
Come on, Kelly, you're going to rock!
Sticks and string
to create a pole
long enough to retrieve the key.
I look back
and say, "Damn!
I missed an opportunity
to take an idol."
I really want the idol,
but without being seen.
Otherwise, I could be targeted.
The Bayons finally arrive.
Who will do it?
It will be Joe,
- at work for Bayon.
- Come on Joe!
Kelly pour Ta Keo.
- That's good, Kelly!
- Joe, she's finished.
You have to get there on the 1st try.
The pole must be
long enough and strong enough
- to retrieve the key.
- One again !
Keep going, you're leading wide!
It's easier said than done.
The key is far away.
- It's great, you sure!
- She has finished.
Gently !
Kelly will give it a shot,
see if it's long enough.
- Hold it straight.
- Very straight.
- Go ahead, Joe!
- It won't last.
Not long enough, Kel!
It's way too short for Kelly.
She will have to add sticks.
You can do it, Joe!
- No more sticks!
- Quick !
- Go! Go! Go !
- You rule !
- Take your time !
- Joe's gonna give it a shot.
Is his pole
long enough and strong enough?
It seems quite long.
Is it strong enough?
A big immunity at stake.
Nobody wants to leave.
Can it get there?
Joe tries to reach this key,
he turns around.
Is his pole strong enough
to unhook it?
Wiglesworth now launches.
Can she get there?
Joe is on the key,
he tries to lift her.
Get up, get up!
Wiglesworth is on the key.
Joe has the key.
Wiglesworth fails.
Joe slowly moves the key.
Don't drop her!
That works ! Joe has the key!
Fonce, you go-y !
Can he bring her back? Yes !
Spencer gets in there and tries
to come back up for the Ta Keo.
He will only have one try.
The Bayons are on the padlock
while Spencer
tries to reach for the key.
Can he do it ?
He's on it.
Nope ! Too short !
The Bayon come through the portal!
There is only one fire left to light!
For victory
and the 1st trial
of Survivor Second Chance.
Bayon wins immunity!
They send Ta Keo to the council.
Unbelievable !
I screwed up.
Bayonne, congratulations.
First test.
No Bayon member
will be leaving tonight.
Take your reward,
return to camp,
enjoy the evening.
Thanks, Jeff!
15 years later,
- same result.
- Same result.
Do you feel
a bit responsible?
Absolutely.
100% responsible.
We had a good lead,
and that's where we lost it.
It's my fault, I take it.
- Seriously, it's fine.
- You are moved.
Is it because
you don't like to disappoint?
- She didn't disappoint us.
- She's great.
Do not worry.
Ta Keo, I have nothing for you
except a date with me at the council.
And we're off to the board...
immediately.
We don't have a second
to discuss
game, strategy. Nothing.
It makes me nervous to death
to go to the council
without having been able to organize themselves.
We have a tribe with Abi-Maria,
Jeff Varner
and all the service freaks.
If the worst comes true,
it could be cataclysmic.
Behind you, torches.
Grab one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If your fire disappears,
you too.
So, Spencer.
What does this 2nd chance mean,
now that you're here,
chosen by those
who watched you play?
It's even more heartbreaking
when you think about it.
If you leave tonight,
you disappoint yourself,
your friends, your family,
and as a bonus, all those who wanted
you to have this 2nd chance.
Woo, what did you notice
in the first few moments?
Because sometimes
from the outset, people plot,
talk, combine...
Absolutely.
Immediately,
a great division was created.
There's the old school:
"Hey, let's build the shelter!",
and then the new school:
"Let's strategize,
let's talk!"
And it was very clear.
- Deitz, okay with that?
- Yes.
I'm old school.
We were busy building,
without much opportunity to speak.
Then, a little later,
we sat down with a few
and started talking.
It's a big part of the game.
It's a huge part of the game!
Yes, it was a revelation
to see it happen so quickly.
Really.
Peih-Gee.
Is it important
to assess your situation
to your 1st participation
and to adapt
to place you well the 2nd time?
That's the whole idea of Second Chance.
Have you learned from your mistakes?
Are you able to fix them?
I tried very hard
to differentiate camp life,
developing relationships...
You can't get stuck
in 1st time mistakes.
Abi, what is your second chance about?
It's about growing,
learning from my mistakes.
In certain situations,
I could have exploded.
And I knew how to contain that, to hold myself back,
achieve a new level
of confidence.
Vytas, you have a unique item
in your 2nd chance.
You have a loved one who
not only played, but won.
Yes. Not only did Aras win,
he beat Terry.
Of course I would like to win.
But if Deitz beat me,
Aras will always laugh
at me and say:
"I beat Deitz
and you didn't."
Wiglesworth,
what will be the impact of
to have left directly
from the ordeal for here,
without having had time
to discuss in small groups?
It will surely have
a strong impact on the vote.
I don't know if anyone
knows where it is.
Me, like everyone else,
I try to keep up.
Jeff, people know
what's going on tonight.
It doesn't matter what they say.
A lot of work has been done,
on this beach for
the past three days.
Vitas, what do you think?
Will it be a random,
instinctive vote?
Or are there already clans?
Enough people have spoken,
know who
they want to work with,
where they are located.
So it's not random at all.
Woo, how important
is tonight's vote?
It is crucial, it will set the tone.
And personally,
I have no idea. I'm here,
and honestly,
I don't know what I'm going to do.
And, Abi, interestingly,
that's where you want to see
who Woo is looking at.
Exact. There, I see the division.
- Clearly.
- And where is she?
Clearly, a male thing.
Jeff, there is no
"male thing".
At this point, the unity of the tribe
is most important
in the choice of vote.
Abi, you can't stand still.
I'm nervous.
If you leave tonight,
what will your story be?
It will be heartbreaking.
I am not ready to leave.
Woo, how does it feel to hear
"that would be heartbreaking"?
Yes, it is rough, of course.
But in the end,
it's about getting along well
with others.
He will clearly vote against me.
I am fixed.
And beyond that, Abi,
it taps on what you said you
want to improve.
- Your social skills.
- Exact.
We can always do better.
We always learn,
every day, little by little.
Are you worried about making
the wrong choice tonight?
I think my gut
tells me who to vote for.
And I think I'm picking up some signals.
varner
Wiglesworth mentions signals.
How important is it,
knowing that it was different
in your time?
It is enormous.
I've only been picking up signals
for three days,
so much so that I slept very little
and did few of the things
I would have done in Australia.
It's a whole other world
and I don't know if my old school friends
participate in this new world
as intensely as I do.
I'm fully in control.
And I can't wait to see
the outcome tonight.
Before we vote,
am I missing something?
There is an elephant here. Is there
something huge that went unnoticed?
If so, we'll find out.
It's my second chance.
I don't want to spoil it.
It's an important night.
Good. It's time to vote.
Whoa, over to you.
I'm sorry, Vitas.
I wanted to play with you.
But you still have a
lot of work to do.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
Vytas.
Abi.
Help.
Trois votes Vytas,
three votes Abi.
Vytas.
Help.
Quatre votes Vytas,
four votes Abi,
there are two votes left.
Vytas.
Cinq votes Vytas,
four votes Abi,
one vote remains.
First person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
Vitas.
Bring me your torch.
Vytas, the tribe has spoken.
- It's time to go.
- No hard feelings.
It's a terrific game.
No problem.
This vote illustrates one thing
very clearly:
your second chance
can end at any time.
So you have to
make the most of it.
And as you came to the council,
fire, in the form of flint,
will be waiting for you at the camp.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lny, flosm92
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Sorry that you don't like me
and that I annoy you.
Abi is playing the same good old game.
Fuck me and I'll kill you.
While Varner
tries to change his.
These threats must disappear.
I don't like these people.
It was a revelation.
Shake your ass and play!
I remember saying,
before coming here:
I would rather not get caught
than get caught and go first.
And it sucks.
I tried to find people
to work with,
and they seem to have found me
dangerous, it's a sign of respect.
They were afraid of me,
and they were right.