translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
With three tribes in play,
each had its own story.
Ta Keo...
Joe picks up a coin on his own.
...was at the top of his game.
Ta Keo wins immunity!
I doubt we'll lose
any trials.
Bayon had yet to lose,
but was far from unity.
Spencer and Wigglesworth
are in the minority.
As for Angkor...
I hate this place!
...it was a disaster.
Neither resources nor shelter.
It must change.
We are in hell.
And they lost their second
immunity test in a row.
Angkor returns to council
for the 2nd time in a row!
Approaching the board,
Savage et Tasha
wanted to eliminate
the greatest strategic threat.
- Jeff has to go.
- He's very cunning.
But Abi had a grudge against Woo.
He voted against me twice!
It all comes down to winning events
versus trust and loyalty.
I have to weigh the pros and cons.
At the council, Woo pleaded his case.
Abi, I promise you,
here and now.
I will stay loyal.
And it was Varner who was eliminated.
The tribe has spoken.
There are 16 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The friends,
thank you for believing in me.
Thanks for believing in us.
Thank you, Abi.
I really appreciate.
I'm here, I can
continue to fight.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for everything, my brother.
Four tips in 11 days,
I never get used to it.
I hope I can
delay the next ones,
now that we are strong.
- It was really hard.
- I say.
He is better off where he is.
We have to win races.
But if we don't recover quickly,
we could leave all four.
- You were really good, Woo!
- Yeah, he was...
- Woo was fighting!
- He was fighting !
- Like never !
- He had to ! I was freaking out!
I had to decide
between Varner and Woo.
And I kept Woo.
I don't like
people to be indebted to me.
But if he still writes my name,
he is dead in my eyes.
- Cheer.
- Give me a hug !
- You know that I love you.
- Me too.
You are my little sister.
Oh my God !
We did it ?!
I would never have believed it.
I would have said you were losing your mind.
Six days ago, I said to myself:
mission impossible.
Not only the conditions,
but the mental toughness
to climb from the bottom to the top.
We did damn well.
I wouldn't want to relive
the last five days.
Non.
But that's part of the game.
And I play it.
And I'll keep playing it
until my situation changes.
Attention !
Zut !
Nothing in the net?
Cunning little bastards!
Kimmi, Wigglesworth et al.,
we like to get up to get
clams and crabs.
I got it !
Yeah !
- Owl !
- Great !
We bring back the protein
for the boys.
We are the feeders.
And that's fine with us.
Because women should
stay strong and united.
Ah! Big clams!
- Clams?
- Yes !
- Do you need the hammer?
- Nope !
We shouldn't take
all the big clams.
We'll put them aside
in the basket.
We're going to exhaust the whole area.
It will renew itself,
and then they move.
But compare how many we found
on the 1st day, and now.
Because we go less far.
No matter.
Do you want to eat or not?
Of course, but...
We'll put them in the bag.
No need to eat it all now.
- We'll save some for tomorrow.
- We should stop fishing them.
- No more clams.
- No, I want to eat!
I know, Kimmi, but we're draining
the sea of ​​its clams.
I know Kimmi tryna harvest
all
possible large clams,
so i try to encourage him
not really
always picking up the maximum,
because we could be here
another 27 days.
And if we continue to eat
everything in the sea,
there won't be much left.
There is three.
That's all I bring.
That's a big difference
in this Second Chance.
I don't live day to day
but rather considering
the end of the game.
I mustn't close any doors,
the game is far from over.
Kimmi, we got you some crab.
Yes, we have crab and clams.
And that delights me.
I have to work
on my patience a little more,
because Monica tends to wear him out.
I say to myself:
what we find, we eat.
The ocean won't run out
if the six of us eat something.
a wish
it's better than two to get it.
She doesn't know that?!
She's like,
"Leave them in the ocean!"
- Lord !
- We have to eat, shit!
"No need to eat.
Let's leave them in the ocean,
otherwise we will deplete
the resources of the entire ocean."
Is...
No. No, darling, no.
You know what ?
If my biggest problem here
is Monica,
is that I'm doing well.
Instead of being very emotional
in my reactions,
I avoid making waves.
I just have to remember:
self-control !
I am more mature and wiser.
But I'm not used to
giving me opinions
that I don't care about.
Over here, everyone!
Ta Keo, Bayon,
discover the new Angkor tribe.
Varner, eliminated at the last council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Oui !
Today,
three members of each tribe
will be tied together.
The fourth will be in a barrel.
On my signal you will roll it
to a series of masts,
where the person in the barrel
has to collect bags of balls
then return to the barrel.
Once the three bags have been collected,
you will have to roll them
in order to place them in targets.
The first two tribes to finish
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes !
For the first...
Comfort.
Chairs, pillows, blankets,
hammock, candles
and tarp.
Oh my God !
In addition, some refreshments will be waiting for you at the camp .
A nice way
to recover from a tough ordeal.
For the second:
not as exciting, but effective.
A tarp.
It will protect you from
the sun and the rain.
For the third: nada.
Nothing at all.
This event has only been played
once, in Blood vs. Water,
Ciera's season.
Your tribe participated and lost.
So it's a second chance for Ciera.
Ta Keo, Bayon,
you have two more members.
The same cannot be discarded
in 2 consecutive events.
Those who do not participate here
will take part
in the immunity test.
I'm out.
Who does not participate, Ta Keo?
Deitz et Kass.
Bayon, what about you?
Fishbach et Wigglesworth.
You four
take a seat on the bench.
The others, I'll give you
a minute to organize yourselves.
Alright, here we go.
For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
It's Woo,
Monica
and Wentworth in the barrels.
- Your Keo!
- It's teamwork.
You have to reach the first pedestal
so they can get out of the barrel
and release the bag of balls.
- Come on Kel!
- Go ahead, Ta Keo!
- Are you okay, Monica?
- Go ahead, Bayon!
Go ahead, Angkor!
You have to get out of the barrel, climb
and release that bag of bullets.
This is where you will win
or lose time.
Wentworth, lightning fast!
Wentworth has its own!
Woo has his!
Monica is slower.
Ahead !
Come on !
The Angkors are gone,
the Ta Keos are gone.
Monica is still on the 1st bag.
Bayon wastes a lot of time
with Monica in the barrel.
Now
the Bayons can go again.
Come on !
On your side ! On your side !
- Go on !
- Forward, Kelley!
Wentworth ressort.
Woo came out.
He wastes no time.
Bayon goes in all directions.
Come on Monica!
I'm upside down.
Woo has the 2nd bag for Angkor.
Wentworth has the 2nd sack for Ta Keo.
They are going to get
their 3rd and last bag.
Monica, again,
very slow for Bayon.
It's like the Sunday picnic
of the parish.
Move on !
Monica finally has the 2nd bag for Bayon.
Woo has the 3rd bag for Angkor.
Wentworth has the 3rd sack for Ta Keo.
Go on ! Go on !
Monica is on the 3rd sack for Bayon.
- Big circles!
- Make circles!
You have to put it on the base!
Go ahead, Angkor!
Your Keo is good!
Everybody out !
You can throw the balls!
Monica finally has the 3rd bag for Bayon.
Woo lance pour Angkor.
Yeah, Woo!
Keith pitches for Ta Keo.
Come on, Keith!
Bayon, we have to speed up!
Come on, forward!
Go ahead, Bayon!
It will be Jeremy for Bayon.
Everyone
is now on the balls.
You have to place the six balls,
each in a hole.
Yeah, Keith, good!
Keith places 1st for Ta Keo.
Presque !
Yeah, Woo!
Woo places 1st for Angkor.
Tied, 1-1.
Jeremy springs into action.
- Cheer !
- Good ! Good !
And here is Bayon
back in the race.
Tie, 1 everywhere.
- Yes, Keith!
- Keith sets up a 2nd one for Ta Keo.
- Yes !
- Woo up a 2nd for Angkor.
New equality.
A 3rd for Keith.
A 3rd for Woo.
New equality.
Bayon is again left behind.
Good ! Ouch!
You will succeed !
Woo up a 4th for Angkor.
Angkor leads with 4.
Come on, Keith!
Keith sets up a 4th.
Equality.
Jeremy still shoots for Bayon,
without much success.
- You want ?
- Yeah, come on.
Spencer comes to replace Jeremy.
You have to have the touch.
- Yeah !
- Cheer !
Spencer sets up one for Bayon.
- And There you go !
- Yeah !
Two in a row for Spencer,
3 points for Bayon.
A 3rd in a row for Spencer!
Equality!
4 everywhere!
Yes Keith! One more !
Keith places 5th for Ta Keo.
Ta Keo now leads with 5.
The first two to finish
win a reward.
Keith succeeds for Ta Keo!
Ta Keo wins comfort
and refreshments
on the field!
Bayon and Angkor
are vying for 2nd place.
Angkor is at 4,
Bayon is at 4.
It's good, my brother!
And a 5th for Angkor!
Angkor is at 5, more than one!
It's always good, Spencer!
Ah! Go home !
Spencer just misses.
Woo can make his tribe win.
Angkor wins an award
in the form of a tarp!
Bayon fails.
Ta Keo!
Ciera, your second chance!
It worked ! Redemption!
Nice reward for your tribe.
many objects,
and cold drinks
on your camp,
something to snack on.
Come get your things,
return to camp.
It's a nice catch.
Angkor is not
as big,
and it is perhaps even
above all symbolic,
but it remains a tarp,
which will protect you from the sun
and the rain. Come get her.
Take your things,
return to camp.
- A win is a win.
- A win is a win!
Merci.
Bayon, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
Well done, friends!
Let's see what we have here!
- Jus d'orange.
- [???]
- Health !
- To Ta Keo!
- Another reward!
- To Survivor Second Chance!
Winning is the elixir.
It boosts our confidence.
Another award won!
I'm pretending there
's rum in it, so watch out!
Me too !
We won
chairs with cushions.
Wow, thank you!
Where is my crown?
We have a nice hammock,
pillows,
fresh fruit...
This is tropical camping!
Are we going to look for fish?
- We have fruit.
- We have pineapple juice.
We have all the necessary food.
And if we miss it,
we go to the supermarket, right there,
and we grab something!
- Good luck !
- Thanks !
I'm having fun !
It's awesome !
It goes well.
But I'm worried about the merger.
We have to discuss it.
What is our plan?
I see the merge like this:
we need a close-knit group of five.
If we stay five together, we five,
- Everything will be alright.
- Yeah.
But everyone, in my season,
wanted to get me out right away.
"Joe is the biggest target.
Joe is dangerous on the races."
I have no interest in eliminating you.
The difference
with the last time,
in this Second Chance,
is that I try to recruit
as many people as possible
to have a majority in the merger.
Because I always feel
like I'm the most dangerous.
But I'm clearly playing
the 1st half of the game
much better than last time.
We are the final quintet.
As long as we remain allies,
we just have to find
something to be in the majority.
We are five welded,
with Deitz next door.
And personally,
I saw Terry's branch
since the shift change.
So I really like
this group of five, without Deitz.
But may Terry continue
to feel good!
- Oh yeah !
- No problem.
It's all new to me.
That was my problem the first time.
I didn't ally myself with anyone.
And here I have four.
This is the first time we've approached Keith
to say, "Let's do this!"
At 5, not just at 2!
At 2, we're not going anywhere.
But 5 could take me to the end.
- Have fun !
- [???]
Good luck !
Do we roll it?
[???]
The trend seems to be: gain
immunity, lose reward.
Today we lost.
And I was very hungry.
So, with Jeremy,
we took the boat
to go fishing.
Have fun !
The original four Bayons
remain tightly knit.
Wigglesworth and I
are in the minority.
But Jeremy is outspoken,
he's a straight guy.
We can make connections
and become a strong duo
that could become a force.
- Have you ever done this?
- No, Joe does it all the time.
- It's his element.
- Yeah, he loves it.
I hold it.
The first time, I came
to Survivor as a super-fan.
I saw these guys,
like Ozzy, or even Joe,
fish, spear,
supply their tribe.
- Let's see how it goes.
- Let's go!
I think I've always seen myself
like a weird and brainy kid
unable to do that.
But here I am, and I do.
I don't like Survivor vicariously anymore
, I live it.
It's one of those Survivor dreams
that I thought about a lot
and I finally realize.
It was a great moment,
I was proud of myself.
That's a tarp!
Yeah.
All those rainy days and nights
at Chuck E. Cheese paid off.
To finish second, for us,
is to finish first.
It was good.
The victory was great,
morally and spiritually.
- We have a winning streak.
- Yeah.
We have to win immunity tomorrow.
I have here a 2nd chance,
and my mom is clearly
a big inspiration to move forward.
What was wrong
with your mother's heart?
She had
a big heart attack.
The doctor arrives:
"Your mother only has
a few days left,
We put her on the top of the list
for a transplant."
And thank God,
we received a call:
"Hey, we have a heart for your mother!"
"Oh, formidable !"
So she had her transplant,
at the time of season 28.
To see someone like her
go through what she went through,
and never give up,
because she loved us
and would never have left us,
it inspires me a lot
to keep fighting
for what I want.
- That's crazy.
- Nice story, Woo.
It's scary.
Life is Beautiful.
Life is precious.
I love life.
My mother had a second chance.
I clearly play for her
and also for all those
who voted for me.
Because without them, I wouldn't have
this second life in this game.
My grandmother went through the same thing
and didn't have the same luck.
I lost my auntie, too,
very early.
Woo pissed me off a bit.
I think he uses this story
to draw people to him.
Of course, it could have happened to him,
and his mother, and I sympathize.
But hey, I had a tendon transplant
in my knee.
I also have a piece
of someone else's body.
Woo plays very well.
His way of getting your sympathy
with the story of his mother...
- Oh, sure!
- It's a great story, great,
but, Lord!
I was like, well...
Yeah, clear...
Should I start
unpacking everything too?
- Exactly.
- Nope.
Woo and Abi,
It's day and night.
With Abi,
I need all my resources
just to be with her.
She still worries.
It's alive !
It's hard work,
working with Abi.
Woo ?
We can give him his
marching order just before the council,
and it will roll.
Abi ?...
She won't do that.
In the event of a merger,
it will be twice as hard
to maneuver with Abi.
It's a ticking time bomb.
But at the same time,
she saved my place.
I don't want to decide
based on emotions and fire her.
I want to make
the right decision for my game.
But for my sanity,
it might be necessary.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, I take back the idols.
Kimmi.
Wentworth.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
at my signal,
you will climb a tower,
crossing a series of obstacles
to the top.
From the top
you will throw sandbags,
to hit a series of targets.
The first two tribes
hit all their targets...
gain immunity, shielded from the vote.
Losers go to the board
where someone will be the 5th person
eliminated from the game.
This event was run
for the first time
last season.
Joe's tribe participated in it and...?
Lost.
A second chance for Joe
to rewrite history.
Ta Keo, you are 2 more.
You cannot discard
the same 2 times in a row.
It was Deitz and Kass
last time.
- Who will it be?
- Kelley and me.
Ciera and Kelley
are not participating at Ta Keo.
Bayon.
Last time, Wigglesworth
and Fishbach did not participate.
Who will it be this time?
Jeremy et Monica.
Jeremy and Monica at Bayon.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we begin.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Go to the carpet
and send a first team member.
It will be Joe,
Spencer and Savage,
who go first.
Joe is upstairs.
Spencer is on his heels.
- This is Savage.
- Come on, Savage!
There's a hit to take
with the "Survivor" slingshot.
Spencer shoots first.
It's too short.
Savage, too long.
Joe scores on the first down!
Go ahead, Ta Keo!
When you score,
you have to change.
Everyone must shoot
at least once.
Spencer scores!
Go ahead, Bayon!
Wigglesworth s'élance.
Savage touches! Go for it !
Here is Woo!
Equality.
1-1-1.
- Close, Keith!
- Keith just misses.
Wigglesworth va tirer.
Go ahead, Bayon!
Wigglesworth touche !
Bayon now leads 2-1.
Woo touch!
Go ahead, Angkor!
Tied, 2-2 for Bayon and Angkor.
1 for Ta Keo.
Keith misses again.
This is Fishbach for Bayon.
He's hitting the wrong target!
Fishbach scores for Angkor!
It will count!
Big mistake !
- Way back!
- Keith shoots again.
- Yes, Keith!
- Keith scores for Ta Keo.
Fishbach only managed
to give Angkor a point.
It was nothing !
Tasha scores first time
for Angkor!
Deitz brand for Ta Keo!
3 for Ta Keo,
2 for Bayon,
- 4 for Angkor.
- Fine, Abi, come on!
Abi could make Angkor win
on this one.
They haven't
won immunity yet.
Far too short.
- I stop!
- Abi comes back down.
Here is Woo.
Kimmi tire.
It's too short.
Woo is back for Angkor,
he could win now.
Woo tire.
Above.
Kimmi tire...
- ...and almost scores for Angkor!
- Come back down!
Kimmi comes back down.
Spencer goes back.
Come on Kass!
- Come on, Kass, go all out!
- This is Kass for Ta Keo.
- Come on, Woo!
- Woo shoots
For victory.
And he scores for Angkor!
Angkor wins immunity!
There is one spot left!
- Kass completely misses his shot.
- Kass, come down!
Spencer scores for Bayon!
He comes back down.
This is Wigglesworth.
We now have
3 for Bayon, 3 for Ta Keo.
- Come on, Joe!
- Here's Joe for Ta Keo.
Angkor won
its first immunity.
No advice tonight for them.
- Come on, Joe!
- Joe is back for Ta Keo,
as well as Wigglesworth for Bayon.
Come on, Joe!
Its good.
Joe touches for Ta Keo.
Come back down!
4 pour Ta Keo, 3 pour Wigglesworth.
One more for Ta Keo.
- This is Keith.
- Thoroughly! Really thoroughly!
Too short for Kelly.
She comes back down.
Spencer returns.
- Keith shoots for the win.
- Louder, Keith!
Much stronger!
Spencer will try to equalize.
He assured in this test.
- Come on, Spence!
- Come on, Keith!
Keith just misses.
Can Spencer equalize?
He just misses.
Keith, for the win...
Its good !
Ta Keo wins immunity
and send Bayon to the council!
Yeah, Ta Keo, come on!
- Better to be a hammer than a nail!
- Congratulations, friends!
I boy!
Angkor, congratulations.
Woo, you're not even waiting
for me to bring it to you!
First immunity for Angkor,
no advice.
Ta Keo, once more.
Immunity.
No one will leave Ta Keo.
Drive the point home, Keith!
Angkor, Ta Keo,
get your stuff,
go back to camp.
No advice tonight
no one is leaving.
As for the Bayon tribe,
most of you have
n't even been to the council yet
after 13 days of play.
Monica, how will this impact
this band?
It can
only strengthen us, in fact.
We'll find out what's going on,
who is trustworthy,
who is loyal.
Going to counseling
is not a problem.
We will be fixed this evening.
Take your things,
return to camp.
See you tonight at the council,
where someone will be the 5th person
eliminated from Survivor Second Chance.
Clearly
it's Wigglesworth and me
who we face
to find out who will leave.
The alliance of the 4 original Bayon
remains very united.
She will be hard to break.
I hope that at least
some of the bonds
I've made will hold.
I'll say it once
so as not to add too much:
I am really sorry.
There are four original Bayon,
and then there's Wiggles and Spencer,
who are on the sidelines.
We win, we lose.
Sorry for not doing better.
I just wonder:
Who do I trust the most?
For the rest of the game.
Do I trust Spencer?
Or Wigglesworth?
How are you ?
Yeah, but I hate
going to the council.
It sucks.
I don't believe any
of them have the idol.
No, me neither.
I have more faith
in Wigglesworth, but I think
- that Spencer...
- ...needs us anymore.
Yes. So who are we targeting?
I stay on Kelly.
- Are we aiming for Kelly?
- Always Kelly.
I would find it strange
that Wigglesworth
don't ask what's going on.
- Yeah.
- You see ?
Being at the bottom of the ladder,
which I'm used to,
I have to impose myself
in the discussions.
So how are you?
- Ça me va.
- Wigglesworth ?
- Yeah.
- OK.
- We all agree.
I just wanted
to keep up to date
and make sure Wigglesworth
was the target.
And you, it's good,
- do you trust me?
- Yeah.
Kelly worries us more,
in case she...
Mon instinct,
being of an anxious nature,
is to check again and again
that I risk nothing.
But these people
are looking for loyalty.
And it depends a lot
on the impression you give.
It becomes essential
to appear sincere, calm, confident.
It goes against
of everything in me that loves this game,
but I have to play it cool.
Kelly,
I think she will leave.
I'm not sure I
want to eliminate Wigglesworth.
I think that...
garder Wigglesworth
could benefit my game.
In the hope of, perhaps,
create a female alliance.
We might also want to
preserve the female workforce.
Because there, we are equal.
We have four original Bayons.
It's our roots.
Suddenly, Monica is looking
to create something between girls.
I don't know where she's going,
she's gonna ruin something.
- We four must stick together.
- OK.
- 100 %.
- It is all good.
Monica playing Survivor,
it puts us in danger,
it is unpredictable
and will switch sides.
It's a fucking snake
hiding in the grass.
A snake hiding in the grass.
My ambition is to reach the end.
And there will be casualties.
Monica doesn't play
for the Bayon Tribe.
Monica plays for Monica.
And she'll walk over us,
thinking she's got us.
But she will be the turkey of the farce.
We were talking, okay?
I asked
his opinion: Spencer or Kelly?
And she goes: "Shouldn't we
preserve the female workforce?"
She wants to leave or what?
I don't know what she...
We have to hit her. She must...
- It's a snake.
- She's unpredictable.
She's gonna screw it all up.
We are in a great position.
I'm just thinking:
if we go to Monica,
with Spencer on our side?
Spencer will agree to anything,
he has no one else.
I don't want this,
but if she keeps saying that,
- "Let's keep the girls"...
- To sow discord.
What if Monica
went to see Kelly and Spencer:
"Hey, I'm coming with you
and we're taking out Jeremy or Steve!"
We three have to take Monica out
by surprise.
Monica... I don't know what she's doing.
Why tell Kimmi
to keep the girls?
Why do that ?
So it would be cool to see
Monica walk away after that.
I would just like to mention the fact
that sends a negative signal
to Bayon to eliminate a Bayon.
She will be the first Bayon eliminated.
I'm terrified of the idea
of ​​a change of tribes.
I know it.
Jeremy, Kimmi and I
have to decide tonight
in which direction to go.
It could have
a lasting impact on the game.
If he sorts Monica,
we betray the old Bayon,
our original tribe.
So who knows what will happen
in case of change or merger?
It could violate
many bonds of trust.
In one way,
Monica and Wigglesworth
pose the same risk.
We can't trust Monica.
She will betray anything that moves.
And Wigglesworth
has many connections to Ta Keo.
Eliminating it now
would make a lot of sense.
It is difficult to establish
which is the most dangerous.
For those of you
who don't have a torch,
grab one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because the fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
Fishbach.
Counseling
can benefit a tribe.
Monica brought it up to the test,
it can solidify a tribe.
Do you have this impression
that it could be positive?
This game is based on trust.
You can't prove trust
before voting on the board.
Monica,
the most obvious, a priori,
would be that the four old Bayon,
Kimmi, Stephen, Jeremy and yourself,
just have to choose
between Wigglesworth and Spencer.
Is it the dominant feeling
that the allies must stick together?
I think so.
It's also mostly
based on trust
and on the loyalty
that we feel towards certain people.
Wigglesworth.
Was that your impression today?
Is it you or Spencer?
Absolutely.
And my actions
since we've been together
will take me, I hope,
until tomorrow morning,
and I will remain with this tribe.
Jeremy, is that the mark
of an old school player?
Because what Kelly says is actually
quite wise and full of common sense.
Yes, that makes sense.
But that's old school.
The new school is more erratic.
"I need it now,
I need to know if I am.
I will do my best
to hold out until the next day."
Spencer, that's you.
You embody the new school.
Erratic, game expert,
always thoroughly.
Yeah, you could say that.
And I here, for the first time
in my career in Survivor,
the very first time
i have a close knit tribe
with which I feel good
to face the tests
and play as a team.
Because this game is still tribal,
it is not yet individual.
And I've never experienced this before.
Based on that, I say,
"This is my group."
Jeremy, looking to the long term,
it is sweet music
to your ears.
Yes, that's good to hear
for the long haul.
And also, with Kelly,
she is loyal, hardworking,
it is also positive
for the future of the group.
Jeremy, what will
tonight's vote be based on?
loyalty, trust,
strength in trials...
So far, nothing to decide between
Spencer and Wigglesworth.
Both are strong
in trials
and pledged their loyalty.
Well, we'll see.
Et Kimmi,
another thing
to consider in this vote,
this is the type of signal sent
to the other candidates still in play.
The ten original Bayons
were tightly knit.
As long as they see
that it's one of the ex-Ta Keo,
Everything will be alright.
But no one knows
what is happening on the camp.
Monica, is this vote locked?
Yes I think so.
Kimmi, is it hard
to eliminate someone?
Or is it rather exciting:
"I really play!" ?
It sucks to end
someone's hopes and dreams.
But I have to go beyond
the emotional aspect.
I came
knowing it was a game.
I will continue
to follow my path.
Stephen, does emotion play
a role in voting for you?
Or is it just the strategy,
getting to the end,
and this time, I will win?
The strategy is based on emotion.
You have to build real connections
to build real alliances.
Good. It's time to vote.
Monica, over to you.
I hate writing your name.
But you would do wonders
if we let you go further.
Sorry, Spence.
You are a brave guy,
but I have to follow the majority
on this one.
You coined the phrase:
"I didn't come here
to make friends."
And yet,
you have more than me in front of you.
I hope I have convinced
this tribe that it is.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Kelly.
Spencer.
Kelly. Two Kelly votes.
Monica.
Two Kelly votes,
one Spencer vote, one Monica vote.
Monica.
That's two votes Monica,
two Kelly votes, one Spencer vote,
one vote remains.
Fifth person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
Monica.
Bring me your torch.
Monica, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
If we were to wonder again
whether this tribe is playing
old school or new school,
this surprise
elimination removes all doubt.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Team Survivor ST
http://survivor-st.forumgratuit.org/
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro : Lény
Re-synchro version HD : aymeric000
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Big hits
are all about timing.
- You kidding.
- Think about it.
It could be the hit
which would set the tone
for the entire season.
But the presence
of one of the Survivors in the game
is about to end.
It's worse
than you could imagine.
Alright, c'est Probst!
I'm a little shocked, but that's okay.
I really wanted to stay
much longer.
I didn't expect
to come out so soon.
You never know what to expect.
I was officially
eliminated by surprise.
My second chance
is a little disappointing.
I don't know what I
could have done otherwise.
It's hard, but it's a game.
You have to recover
after being eliminated.