>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," 20 RETURNING PLAYERS
GOT ANOTHER SHOT AT THE GAME
THEY LOVE.
>> I REALLY MESSED UP MY FIRST
TIME, AND THIS TIME I WANT TO BE
FEARLESS.
>> Jeff: AT BAYON, THEIR
SECOND CHANCE COULDN'T HAVE
STARTED ANY BETTER.
>> IN PARADISE.
>> WE GOT SOME FISH.
>> I WANT TO HAVE FUN OUT HERE.
I WANT TO DO STUFF.
I JUST LOVE IT OUT HERE.
THIS IS GREAT.
>> Jeff: AT TA KEO...
>> YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT ME
BEHIND MY BACK.
>> Jeff: ABI AND PEIH-GEE
CONTINUED TO FIGHT, LEAVING ABI
ALL ALONE.
>> SHE'S GETTING LAUGHED AT BY
HER PEOPLE.
THERE'S ANOTHER HUMAN BEING OUT
THERE FLOUNDERING, THAT'S JUST
WRONG.
>> Jeff: AT THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE...
>> I CAN'T.
>> Jeff: TA KEO LOST FOR THE
SECOND TIME IN A ROW.
BAYON IS RIGHT, IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
BACK AT CAMP...
>> ARE WE STILL TOGETHER?
>> Jeff: SHIRIN AND SPENCER
FOUND THEMSELVES ON THE OUTS.
>> EVERYTHING STARTED GOING
REALLY WELL, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
IT COLLAPSES IN FRONT OF ME.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
SPENCER PROMISED TO CHANGE HIS
WAYS.
>> THIS CHANGE WILL HAPPEN.
IT'S ABOUT FORMING
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, SHIRIN
WAS SENT HOME.
18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
REAL QUICK, I'M SO GRATEFUL TO
BE HERE...YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
SEE ME RUNNING AROUNG HERE WITH
CRAZINESS.
I WANNA BE A STRONG TEAM.
I'M STILL NOT THE STRONGEST
SOCIAL PLAYER OUT HERE.
I'M COMPLETELY ON THE OUTS.
SO I HAVE TO CHANGE.
I'M THRILLED TO BE HERE FOR
ANOTHER COUPLE DAYS.
IN THIS SEASON, WHICH IS ABOUT
CHANGE, AND ABOUT SECOND CHANCE
OF YOU AS A SURVIVOR PLAYER & AS
A PERSON, THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO CHANGE HAVE BEEN
REWARDED.
SO IF I CAN MAKE THE CHANGE I
KNOW IS WITHIN ME HAPPEN,
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY HOPE.
>> I'M JUST GLAD SHE'S GONE,
MAN.
>> ANY OF US MAKES IT TO THE
ACTUAL FINAL, THAT IS A FEATHER
IN YOUR CAP AS FAR AS WHAT YOU
DID TO GET RID OF ONE OF THE
MOST STRATEGIC PEOPLE I'VE EVER
MET ON "SURVIVOR."
I HAVE SIMPLY GONE FROM THE
BOTTOM UP TO THE TOP WITHOUT ANY
FEAR OF GETTING VOTED OUT.
>> IT'S PERFECT.
NOBODY'S ALIENATED.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
>> THE NUMBERS ARE ON OUR SIDE,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN TERRY DIETZ
HAS THIS SOCIAL GAME.
I'M KIND OF PROUD OF MYSELF, YOU
KNOW?
IT WORKED OUT GREAT.
AND THERE'S STILL SPENCER TO
VOTE OUT AT THE NEXT TRIBAL IF
WE HAVE TO GO.
BOY, I'M ON TOP OF THE WORLD
RIGHT NOW.
LIFE IS GOOD.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> TASHA ALWAYS WITH THE SMILE.
>> I'M GLAD TO BE HERE, JEFF.
>> Jeff: BAYON GETTING THE
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW TA KEO
TRIBE.
>> WHAT'S UP, YOU GUYS?
>> Jeff: SHIRIN VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
VARNER, DID GETTING RID OF
SHIRIN PUT THIS TRIBE IN A SPACE
WHERE IT NOW FEELS LIKE, OKAY,
WE CAN WORK WITH THIS GROUP?
>> HELL, YEAH.
>> Jeff: DO YOU AGREE WITH
THIS?
YOU'RE HAPPY WITH HOW THINGS ARE
GOING?
>> AFTER LAST NIGHT WE FEEL LIKE
WE GOT THE TEAM UNITY BACK.
TAKING ON THIS CHALLENGE TODAY,
WE NEED IT FOR ADDITIONAL TEAM
SPIRIT.
>> Jeff: HOW ARE YOU HOLDING
UP?
>> GREAT.
I LOVE THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
IT'S GOOD TO HEAR THAT BOTH
SIDES ARE HAPPY WITH THE WAY
THINGS ARE GOING, WHICH MAKES IT
A PERFECT OPPORTUNITY TO CHANGE
THINGS UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT'S INSANE.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
WE'RE SWITCHING TRIBES.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> Jeff: THE THING THAT MAKES
THIS SWITCH UNIQUE IS WE ARE
SWITCHING FROM TWO TRIBES TO
THREE TRIBES.
>> SHUT THE FROM THE DOOR.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK.
SIX OF YOU WILL END UP ON THE
BAYON CAMP.
SIX OF YOU WILL END UP AT THE TA
KEO CAMP.
AND SIX OF YOU WILL GO TO A NEW
BEACH WHERE YOU WILL HAVE TO
START FROM SCRATCH.
YOU'LL HAVE THE SAME SUPPLIES
YOU HAD WHEN YOU BEGAN THIS
GAME, BUT YOU WILL HAVE TO BUILD
A NEW SHELTER.
>> OH, COME ON.
>> Jeff: SO, SAVAGE, WHAT IS
HAPPENING EMOTIONALLY RIGHT NOW
FOR YOU?
>> I'M SCARED.
I'M SCARED.
THERE'S SO MUCH LOVE ON THIS
TRIBE.
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY OVER.
THERE SO I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS
IS GOING TO PLAY OUT, BUT IT
SCARES THE CAP OUT OF ME.
>> WHEN JEFF SAID IT WAS A SWAP,
MY HEART STOPPED.
I HAVEN'T HAD THE BEST LUCK ON
"SURVIVOR" IN TERMS OF SWAPS AND
TWISTS.
I HAVE THE SAME KIND OF HAUNTING
FEAR I HAD 12 YEARS AGO.
I DON'T WANT TO SWAP.
>> Jeff: SHALL WE GET TO THE
DRAW?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, DEAR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR FATE
RIGHT HERE.
>> PURPLE.
>> Jeff: JEREMY GOING TO CLOSE
HIS EYES.
VARNER DOESN'T WANT TO LOOK.
NOBODY WANTS TO LOOK.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY REVEAL.
>> HELL, YEAH.
HELL, YEAH.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> Jeff: IF YOU'RE ON BAYON,
MOVE OVER TO THE BAYON MATT.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THIS
CAMP.
>> Jeff: IF YOU'RE TA KEO,
MOVE TO THE TA KEO MAP.
AND IF YOU HAVE YELLOW, YOU'RE
RIGHT IN THE CENTER.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO WE HAVE OUR THREE TRIBES.
BAYON, SO FOUR OF THE ORIGINAL
BAYON MEMBERS ARE STILL
TOGETHER.
MONICA, JEREMY, FISHBACH AND
KIMMI.
AND WIGLESWORTH AND SPENCER FROM
TA KEO JOIN THEM.
THE NEW TA KEO TRIBE, FOUR
MEMBERS FROM THE BAYON TRIBE,
KEITH, KASS, JOE AND CIERA NOW
JOIN DIETZ AND WENTWORTH.
>> IT'S A DANGEROUS GAME GOING
INTO A MIX-UP, BUT LOOKING AT
THE TRIBES AS A WHOLE, OUR GIRLS
ARE STRONGER.
OUR GUYS ARE STRONGER.
WE'RE IN A REALLY, REALLY GOOD
SPOT TO TAKE CONTROL OF THIS
GAME.
>> Jeff: IN THE MIDDLE, YOUR
TRIBE NAME, ANGOR.
THE NEW ANGOR HAS FOUR PEOPLE
FROM THE OLD TA KEO TRIBE, LOU,
VARNER, PEIH-GEE AND ABI.
THEY'RE JOINED BY TASHA AND
SAVAGE.
SAVAGE, YOU WERE PRETTY HONEST
IN SAYING YOU WERE SCARED.
NOW YOU END UP ON A TRIBE THAT
HAS TO START OVER.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING RIGHT NOW?
>> OVERWHELMED.
IF THEY GO BY TRIBAL LINES, I'M
IN SERIOUS TROUBLE, AND WE HAVE
A COUPLE DAYS OF UNBELIEVABLY
HARD WORK AHEAD OF US.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, IT'S
DEVASTATING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
BAYON, ANGOR, TA KEO, GRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> I NEEDED SOME WAY TO GET OUT
OF THE SITUATION WHERE I WAS
PINNED ON THE BOTTOM, AND NOW
IT'S LIKE "SURVIVOR" GODS HAVE
LOOKED AT ME AND SAID, SPENCER,
YOU DO DESERVE A SECOND CHANCE,
HERE'S WHERE YOU WERE.
WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
>> HEY, TASHA.
>> WE HAVE NO FOOD.
>> WE HAVE NOTHING.
>> OH, MAN.
>> NOTHING.
NO BAMBOO.
>> THAT'S REALLY BUMMING ME OUT.
>> LET'S CHECK OUR LITTLE BOAT.
>> THAT DUDE IS GOING TO TO GET
A LOT OF --
>> DUDE, LET'S BE SMART.
LET'S STAY WITH OUR FOUR.
GET THESE GUYS OUT OF HERE.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
NOTHING CRAZY.
DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
>> NO, NO.
NO.
>> IT'S HARD HAVING TO START
OVER.
NOT ONE SHRED OF FOOD, NO
BUILDING MATERIALS, BUT IT COULD
BE WORSE.
I COULD BE IN THE MINORITY OVER
HERE.
SO IT IS A LUXURY.
THAT'S THE ONLY LUXURY.
THE ONLY LUXURY WE HAVE IN THIS
NEW TRIBE IS THAT WE'VE GOT TWO
PEOPLE AHEAD OF YOU IN LINE TO
BE VOTED OFF.
WHERE DID THOSE TWO RUN OFF TO?
>> I'M NOT SURE.
>> OKAY.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK, HOPEFULLY A
COUPLE OF THEM ARE ON THE OUTS.
LET'S PROMISE THEM WE COME BACK
TOGETHER AND MERGE, WE CAN ALL
PLAY TOGETHER.
I AM IN THE MINORITY ON THIS NEW
TRIBE.
BUT IF ANYONE COULD SURVIVE
THIS, I CAN.
WHAT I LEARNED THE FIRST TIME I
PLAYED WAS I'M STRONG IN HEART.
I'M HERE TO WIN THIS GAME.
AND I'M GOING TO PLAY THE CARDS
THAT I'M DEALT.
>> ANYTHING DOWN THAT WAY?
>> WELL IS ALL THE WAY DOWN ON
THE POINT.
>> TERRY.
NICE THE MEET YOU, BUDDY.
I KNOW KELLY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> HEY, JOE.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI.
>> WE GOING TO RUN THE TABLE OR
WHAT?
>> OH, MY GOD, WE CANNOT LOSE
ANYTHING.
>> LOOKING AT NEW TRIBE, WE HAVE
THREE OR FOUR NUMBER-ONE DRAFT
CHOICES.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE THE LUCK.
IT'S SICK.
WE HAVE TO BRING THE CHICKENS IN
AND THE RICE.
I KNOW I'M WITH KELLY.
THERE'S.
TWO WE HAVE A WORKING
RELATIONSHIP.
WE DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS, BUT I
DON'T THINK WE'RE GOING THE NEED
THE NUMBERS.
A LITTLE BIT OF CONFIDENCE IN
THERE THAT I DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE
GOING TO LOSE A CHALLENGE.
>> YOU GUYS DYING?
>> WE'LL GET THE FIRE UP AND
HAVE A LITTLE CHICKEN FOR
DINNER.
>> THANKS FOR WELCOMING US,
GUYS.
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
CHICKEN RICE.
PERFECT.
>> THAT'S NICE.
>> IT IS NICE.
>> IT'S A GOOD GROUP.
WE GOT REAL LUCKY WITH THIS ONE.
WE SCORED.
>> I THINK WE'RE FINE.
IT MAKES ME LESS ASSURED A
LITTLE BIT.
NOW WE CAN WIN.
WE HAVE TWO STRONG PEOPLE, TERRY
AND KELLY.
KELLY IS SUPER STRONG.
>> I FEEL LIKE I CAME OUT SO
WELL IN THIS SWAP.
HAVE KASS, ME, JOE AND KEITH,
ALL FOUR OF US FROM BAYON.
>> THIS IS A GREAT TRIBE.
>> AS LONG AS US FOUR STICK
TIGHT, WE HAVE NUMBERS, AND WE
SHOULD BE JUST FINE.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> FEELING GOOD IN.
>> UH-HUH.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> WE'RE PRETTY GOOD.
DO YOU LIKE TERRY?
IS HE A GAD DUDE?
>> YEAH.
HE'S GOOD.
WE WERE WORKING TOGETHER BEFORE.
SO IF OUR TRIBE LOSES, DIETZ OR
MYSELF WILL BE ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
I JUST HAVE A FEELING THAT THE
FOUR ARE GOING TO STICK TOGETHER
FOR THE NUMBERS.
>> DO YOU THINK TERRY COULD HAVE
AN IDOL?
>> ALL I KNOW IS HE AND SPENCER
WERE THE TWO LOOKING FOR IT THE
MOST.
TERRY WOULD GO OFF FOR HOURS.
THE IDOL IS STILL IN MY BAG, BUT
I'M PUSHING TERRY UNDER THE BUS,
JUST LIKE KICKING HIM UNDER.
THERE GO UNDER THAT BUS, TERRY.
GO, GO.
>> SO HOW DOES THIS COMPARE THE
YOUR GUYS BEACH?
>> THIS IS SO NICE.
IT'S WIDER.
>> OUR BEACH, WE HAVE A LOT MORE
TREE COVER.
>> WELL, WELCOME HOME, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HERE AT THE NEW BAYON, WE
HAVE JEREMY, KIMMI, STEPHEN AND
MYSELF.
AND WE ARE IN THE MAJORITY AS
THE ORIGINAL BAYON MEMBERS.
WE ALSO HAVE SPENCER AND HE'S IN
THE MINORITY.
>> I COULDN'T HAVE ASKED FOR
ANYTHING BETTER.
>> I LOVE THIS NEW TRIBE.
IT'S SO LIBERATING NOT TO BE IN
CAMP MACHO ANYMORE.
I WAS IN THE BOTTOM OF OUR
TRIBE.
THEN WE SWAPPED AND FOR THE
FIRST TIME EVER I KNOW I'M SAFE,
SO I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER.
>> I'M TRYING TO CUT IT IN HALF.
I JUST HAVE NO IDEA HOW TO DO
THAT.
AND MY MACHETE SKILLS ARE
TERRIBLE.
>> I'M SOMEONE WHO HAS PLAYED
PRETTY LOGICALLY IN THE PAST,
BUT I'VE FAILED WHEN IT COMES TO
UNDERSTANDING EMOTIONS OF
PEOPLE, AND THAT'S BEEN A HUGE
FLAW.
AND SO I'M TRYING SOMETHING NEW
ON THIS TRIBE.
I'M TRYING TO HAVE FEELINGS.
WHEN MY CURRENT GIRLFRIEND
STARTED SAYING, LIKE I LOVE YOU,
LIKE I DIDN'T SAY IT BACK.
>> REALLY?
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO...
>> NO, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO.
>> SHE STILL, LIKE FEELS LIKE...
>> YOU HAVEN'T SAID IT YET?
>> NO.
>> OH, SNAP.
WOW.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE... I'M NOT THAT EASILY
EMOTIONAL, WITH ANYONE.
I STILL HAVE THAT...
>> GUARDED.
>> I'M TRYING TO APPROACH THIS
GAME IN A WAY THAT I CAN FORM
BONDS THAT WILL ACTUALLY BE
HELPFUL, AND THAT WILL CARRY ME
FURTHER, SO WHEN I TELL JEREMY
ABOUT SOMETHING REALLY HONEST,
WHICH IS MY CONCERNS ABOUT, YOU
KNOW, ME AND MY GIRLFRIEND, AND
WHEN I ASK HIM AND REALLY TRULY
CARE ABOUT WHAT HE SAYS, I WANT
TO GET TO KNOW HIM BECAUSE IT'S
SOMETHING I HAVEN'T TAKEN THE
TIME TO DO BEFORE, AND IT MIGHT
JUST MAKE THE DIFFERENCE IN MY
GAME.
>> YOU THINK I'M HANDLING THAT
WRONG.
>> NO, BECAUSE WHEN YOU DO SAY
IT, IT'S GOING TO MEAN SO MUCH
MORE.
I THINK YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT...
>> THINKING ABOUT IT TOO MUCH?
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW.
>> I'M SURE I'M THINKING ABOUT
IT TOO MUCH.
>> WHEN SPENCER JOINED UP, HE
NEEDED TO TALK TO ME.
IT'S GOOD TO SIT DOWN AND TALK.
HE'S A STAND-UP GUY, SOMEONE YOU
CAN REALLY CONNECT WITH AND
TRUST.
HE'S FUNNY AND I'M BIG ON THE
KID.
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE VAL.
GOING THROUGH "SURVIVOR" LAST
YEAR WITH HER, IT MULTIPLIED IT
BY LIKE TEN.
I THINK WE COULD DEFINITELY HAVE
A BOND.
I'M NOT SURE HOW LONG WE'LL KEEP
HIM, BUT WE CAN USE HIM FOR
RIGHT NOW.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
WHEN YOU SEE HER, I THINK THAT
WILL OPEN YOUR EYES A LITTLE
BIT.
WOW, LIKE I REALLY MISUS HER.
>> THAT WOULD BE A POWERFUL
THING FOR ME IF I GOT THAT
CLARITY.
>> THAT WOULD BE COOL.
>> I HATE THIS PLACE.
>> THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR," I WAS ON ONE OF THE
MOST HORRIBLE TRIBES IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
I'VE WITHIN HERE BEFORE.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE NOT TO
HAVE FOOD.
HAVE SHELTER.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO FIGHT
TO STAY IN THIS GAME, SO THIS,
THIS IS JUST ROUND TWO FOR ME.
>> YOU ARE TOTALLY DRY.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> I'M IN THE DRY.
>> YOUR DRESS IS DRY.
>> MY DRESS IS NOT DRY.
>> YOU GOT THE GOOD SPOT IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> YOU WANT TO SWITCH.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> NO, IT'S AWESOME.
I'M GLAD.
>> I'M NOT DRY.
>> ABI HAS A LITTLE BIT OF
RESENTMENT AGAINST PEIH-GEE FOR
SOMETHING.
THAT WORKS IN MY FAVOR.
THERE'S STILL TIME LEFT IN THE
DAY THE STRATEGIZE AND CONVERSE,
AND I'M GOING TO USE EVERY
MINUTE OF IT.
>> SO TELL ME A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
YOUR GUYS TRIBE DYNAMIC.
>> AS A GROUP IT WAS REAL
HARMONIOUS, AND WE'RE GOLDEN.
WE'RE GOLDEN.
BUT THE POINT IS WHEN WE COME
BACK TOGETHER, I CAN GUARANTEE
UCT COATING CAN JOIN US.
>> MY OLD MEMBERS FROM TA KEO
WANT TA KEO STRONG, BUT PEIH-GEE
AND I HAD SOME ISSUES BACK AT TA
KEO, AND TASHA SORT OF WHISPERED
SOME SWEET NOTHINGS IN MY EAR.
>> IT'S JUST SOMETHING TO THINK
ABOUT.
IF YOU AND SOMEONE ELSE...
>> THIS IS MY SECOND CHANCE.
I WANT TO GO TO THE END, SO I
REALLY, REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
>> I WANT TO MAKE THE JURY.
I DIDN'T MAKE THE JURY FIRST
TIME.
I MADE IT RIGHT THERE AT IT AND
WENT HOME.
>> YOU COULD BE.
THERE THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
>> OKAY.
TALK TO ME A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> BOTH TRIBES HAVE FOUR OF OUR,
TWO OF YOURS.
IF THEY LOSE, THEY'RE GOING
HOME.
AND WE COME TO A MERGE.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED US.
LIKE YOU WILL NEED US.
>> SAVAGE AND TASHA WANT ME TO
COME AND JOIN THEM.
THEY WILL GET ME TO THE JURY.
ISN'T THAT A LOVELY INVITATION.
IF YOU WANT TO DO THIS, WE CAN
TOTALLY DO THIS.
>> IT'S JUST SOMETHING TO THINK
ABOUT.
>> I WANT TO SAY, HEY, YOU, YOU,
YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM.
THOSE TWO WE COULD GET RID OF
LIKE THAT.
>> I'M IN A TOUGH SPOT.
YOU FOUR ARE TIGHT.
>> I'M ALWAYS OPEN.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
MAKING DEALS.
THEY'RE RUNNING UP THE BEACH AND
TALKING TO EVERYBODY.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE NOT
TAKING AWAY ABI AND MARIA AND
PEIH-GEE, BECAUSE THERE'S A LOT
THAT COULD GO WRONG.
>> WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT, WATCH
OUT.
WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT.
HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
GET HIM OUT.
WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT.
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> SPENCER AND WIGLESWORTH,
THEY'RE BOTH COZYING UP TO US
BECAUSE IT'S 4-2 RIGHT NOW.
SO WE HAVE AN UNBEATABLE
ADVANTAGE, BUT THE IDOL IS
SOMEWHERE ON THIS ISLAND, AND IT
COULD DESTROY EVERYTHING.
>> I HATE THERE ARE IDOLS OUT
THERE.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA WHERE
IT IS.
>> YOU KNOW, NOT ONLY IS IT A
GREAT TOOL FOR MYSELF TO HAVE,
BUT IT'S A REAL SYMBOL THAT
BONDS AN ALLIANCE TOGETHER.
>> WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF WE
FOUND THIS IDOL FOR OUR
ALLIANCE.
THAT WOULD BE SO STRONG.
IT WOULD MAKE US STRONG.
I WOULD BE IN A POWER POSITION
ON A STRONG TRIBE WITH PEOPLE I
TRUST AND PEOPLE I LIKE.
SO ONE OF US NEEDS TO FIND THAT
IDOL.
>> THIS LOOKS LIKE THE KIND OF
PLACE IT WOULD BE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T SEE ANYTHING IN HERE,
BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP LOOKING,
CONSTANTLY.
>> I'M SO FRUSTRATED LOOKING FOR
THAT THING.
IT'S IN THE HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IS IT ON THE GROUND?
IS IT IN A TREE?
IS IT HIGH UP?
IS IT IN THE WATER?
LIKE I DON'T KNOW NOTHING.
IT COULD BE ANYWHERE.
BUT THIS IS MY SECOND CHANCE,
AND I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO WORK
HARDER THIS TIME.
>> THE IDOL HAS TO BE SOMEWHERE
NOTICEABLE.
IT'S GOT TO BE SOME CRAZY TREE
OR JAGGED ROCK THAT'S JUST
OBVIOUS, BUT SO FAR IT'S NOT
OBVIOUS TO ME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, GOT TO KEEP
LOOKING.
>> THERE WAS A LITTLE TREE FULL
OF LEAVES, AND I STARTED DIGGING
IN IT, AND THE THING JUST POPPED
OUT.
I WAS SO PUMPED.
CONGRATULATIONS YOU HAVE FOUND A
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, ON THE BACK
OF A THIRD BOX IS MY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
FINALLY, TWO SEASONS IT TAKES,
AND I FINALLY FIND SOMETHING,
BUT IS IT AN IDOL?
NO, IT'S NOT AN IDOL, IT'S A
CLUE TO AN IDOL THAT I HAVE TO
GRAB WHEN 18 PEOPLE ARE PLAYING
AROUND ME.
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT WORK.
WE'RE GOING TO GET.
THIS I'M GOING TO BRING THIS
THING HOME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO YOUR FIRST
IMMUNITY IDOL AS THREE TRIBES?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
MONICA, I'M TAKE THAT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS ALONG WITH A SECOND
IDOL.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK:
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, EACH
TRIBE WILL PUSH A CART THROUGH
AN OBSTACLE COURSE.
AT EACH TOWER, YOU RECEIVE A
KEY.
YOU'LL USE THAT KEY TO UNLOCK A
CHEST.
PUT THE CHEST ON THE CART AND
CONTINUE ON.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL THREE
CHESTS, YOU MUST THEN
DISASSEMBLE THE CART, SLIDE IT
THROUGH A BARRICADE, PUT IT BACK
TOGETHER AND MAKE YOUR WAY TO
THE END WHERE TWO TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL USE THE PIECES INSIDE THE
CHEST TO ASSEMBLE A GIANT DRAGON
PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SECOND
CHANCE."
THIS WAS THE VERY FIRST
CHALLENGE OF BRAINS VERSUS BRAWN
VERSUS BEAUTY.
SPENCER, TASHA, KASS ALL
PARTICIPATED ON THE SAME BRAIN
TRIBE, A MISERABLE PERFORMANCE.
THEY LOST, WENT TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO BECAUSE EACH OF YOU ARE ON A
DIFFERENT TRIBE RIGHT NOW, THIS
SECOND CHANCE WILL OFFER
REDEMPTION FOR TWO OF YOU, AND
FOR ONE OF YOU HISTORY WILL
REPEAT ITSELF.
BIG STAKES.
TAKE A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ALL THREE TRIBES FAST OUT OF THE
GATE.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET THAT KEY.
SPENCER HAS THE KEY FOR BAYON.
WOO WORKING ON THAT KEY FOR
ANGKOR.
HE'S GOT IT.
KELLY HAS THE KEY FOR TA KEO.
UNLOCK THAT CHEST AND GET IT ON
THE CART.
CAN'T MOVE FORWARD UNTIL YOU
HAVE YOUR CHEST ON YOUR CART.
TA KEO FIRST OUT OF THE GATE.
BAYON HAS THEIRS.
ANGKOR RIGHT BEHIND.
KELLY HAS THE SECOND KEY FOR TA
KEO.
SPENCER STRUGGLING, TRYING TO
GET THAT SECOND KEY.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, SPENCE, TAKE
YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: WILL HAS THE SECOND
KEY FOR ANGKOR.
SPENCER FINALLY HAS THE KEY FOR
BAYON.
KELLY HAS THE THIRD KEY FOR TA
KEO.
BAYON HAS THEIR SECOND CHEST.
ANGKOR HAS THEIR SECOND CHEST.
TA KEO HAS ALL THREE CHESTS.
HEAD OUT.
HERE GOES BLUE.
HERE GOES SPENCER LOOKING FOR
THOSE THIRD KEYS.
>> WATCH THE WHEELS.
WATCH THE WHEELS.
>> JEREMY?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> KIMMI.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: SPENCER HAS THE THIRD
KEY FOR BAYON.
JEREMY WORKING ON THE LOCK NOW.
WILL HAS THE THIRD KEY FOR
ANGKOR.
BAYON HAS THEIR THIRD CHEST.
ANGKOR HAS THEIR THIRD CHEST.
HEAD OUT.
>> GO, GO, GO.
GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY HAS TO TAKE
THEIR CART APART NOW.
PEOPLE HAVE TO GO OVER, PIECES
HAVE TO GO THROUGH.
A LOT OF STRATEGY COMING INTO
PLAY IN HOW YOU GET THESE PIECES
THROUGH.
TA KEO IS STILL IN THE LEAD.
BAYON RIGHT BEHIND.
ANGKOR STILL IN LAST.
ONCE EVERYTHING IS THROUGH, YOU
REASSEMBLE THE CART.
GOT TO KEEP MOVING.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> PULL IT!
>> Jeff: IT'S A RACE TO GET
THESE PUT BACK TOGETHER.
TA KEO GETTING THEIR CART BACK
TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE ALL THREE
CHESTS ON YOUR CART BEFORE YOU
CAN HEAD OUT.
GO, TA KEO.
VERY DIFFICULT SET OF OBSTACLES.
DO YOU RUN OVER THEM?
DO YOU CLEAR THEM OUT OF THE WAY
IN WHAT DO YOU DO?
BAYON HAS THEIR THREE CHESTS ON.
ANGKOR HAS ALL THREE CHESTS ON
THEIR CART, START WORKING ON IT.
THERE GOES TA KEO.
TA KEO IS LOSING A LOT OF TIME
TO MOVE THOSE OBSTACLES.
IT PAID OFF.
TA KEO MADE QUICK WORK OF THAT
OBSTACLE.
IT IS NOW BAYON AND ANGKOR
FIGHTING FOR SECOND PLACE.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: ANGKOR DIGGING DEEP
RIGHT NOW.
TA KEO BACK WITH THEIR THIRD
CHEST.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
JOE AND KASS WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR TA KEO.
ANGKOR IS AT THE FINISH.
BAYON IS AT THE FINISH.
GOT TO GET YOUR CHEST OUT HERE
BEFORE YOU CAN START WORKING ON
THE PUZZLE.
JOE AND KASS WITH A NICE BIG
LEAD.
ANGKOR WITH THEIR THIRD CHEST.
BAYON WITH THEIR THIRD CHEST.
PUZZLE MAKERS GO TO WORK.
EVERYBODY ELSE ON THE MATT.
IT IS PEIH-GEE AND TASHA, MONICA
AND SPENCER, JOE AND KASS HAVE
THE FIRST SECTION COMPLETED.
BIG LEAD FOR TA KEO.
SPENCER AND OPINION CA -- MONICA
STRUGGLING.
TASHA DID THIS PUZZLE FOR HER
TRIBE THE FIRST TIME SHE PLAYED.
MONICA AND SPENCE STILL WORKING
ON THAT FIRST SECTION.
THERE IT IS.
MOVE ON.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: JOE AND KASS HAVE ONE
SIDE OF THE SECOND SECTION
COMPLETE.
SO A HUGE LEAD FOR TA KEO AS
THEY WORK ON THAT SECOND SIDE.
JEREMY COMING IN FOR MONICA NOW.
IT IS NOW JEREMY AND SPENCER.
HERE COMES A SWAP FOR TASHA.
JOE AND TASHA FINISH THE SECOND
SECTION.
MOVING ON TO THE THIRD SECTION
OF THE PUZZLE.
JEREMY HAS PICKED IT UP FOR
BAYON.
IT IS NOW TA KEO, BAYON AND
ANGKOR IN THAT ORDER.
ANGKOR HAS A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
UP.
KASS AND JOE WORKING TOGETHER
REALLY WELL.
THIS IS ALL BUT OVER FOR TA KEO.
ONE PIECE LEFT.
TA KEO HAS IT!
TA KEO WINS IMMUNITY.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
IT IS BAYON OR ANGKOR.
WHO IS GOING BACK THE CAMP AND
WHO IS GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL?
>> NOT US.
>> Jeff: THAT'S IT.
BAYON IS DONE WITH THEIR SECOND
SECTION.
THEY CAN MOVE ON TO THEIR THIRD
AND FINAL PUZZLE PIECES.
WOO HAS IT.
SECOND SECTION COMPLETED.
BAYON NEW WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
SECTION.
ANGKOR WORKING ON THEIR THIRD
ANGKOR IS BACK IN THIS.
YOU CAN SEE THE PANIC IN
SPENCER.
BAYON DOWN THE FIVE PIECES.
ANGKOR AT TEN PIECES.
>> PEIH-GEE'S GOT THE OTHER ONE
IN HER HAND.
>> Jeff: QUICKLY.
CAN THEY DO IT?
JEREMY WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
WILL WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
MAKE IT EIGHT.
JEREMY WITH ANOTHER PIECE FOR
BAYON.
THEY'RE DOWN TO TWO.
BAYON VERY CLOSE.
ONE PIECE LEFT.
>> THE RED SHOULD BE AT THE
BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: THAT'S IT!
BAYON WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM
THE VOTE.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: SENDING ANGKOR TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE THIRD PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SECOND CHANCE."
>> NICE JOB, YOU GUYS.
>> WE GOT A RAT.
WE GOT A RAT.
>> Jeff: TA KEO, REDEMPTION
FOR KASS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
>> REDEMPTION FOR KASS.
>> Jeff: BAYON, REDEMPTION FOR
SPENCER.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM THE BAYON
TRIBE.
NO REDEMPTION FOR TASHA.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> Jeff: TALK TO ME ABOUT WHAT
WAS HAPPENING AT THE END OF THE
CHALLENGE.
A LOT OF CHATTER BACK AND FORTH.
VARNER, WHAT WAS HAPPENING?
>> I LOOKED AT WIGGLES AND TASHA
JUMPED BECOME AND SAID, "WE GOT
A RAT, WE GOT A RAT."
>> JEFF, WE'RE TRYING TO BOND.
THAT DOESN'T SEND A GOOD
MESSAGE.
>> I MADE A DEAL WITH YOU AND TO
TURNED RIGHT AROUND AND MADE A
DEAL WITH HER.
>> JEFF, YOU'RE WRONG.
>> ARE WE STILL AN ALLIANCE?
>> YES, YES.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE A DEAL
WITH ME?
>> Jeff: SO, WOO, YOU'RE
FRUSTRATED?
>> IT'S NO SURPRISE I GET THE
LAST WORD AT THE VERY LAST
SECOND.
DISAPPOINTED AGAIN.
>> Jeff: TA KEO, BAYON, GRAB
YOUR STUFF.
ANGKOR, SOMETIMES IT'S ALL HOW
YOU LOOK AT IT.
THIS COULD BE THE BEGINNING OF A
GREAT UNDERDOG STORY, BUT IN
ORDER TO BE AN UNDERDOG, YOU
HAVE TO HIT ROCK BOTTOM, AND IT
LOOKS LIKE THE BEGINNING OF
THAT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> TASHA CALLED ME A RAT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A BIG OLE
MESS AND I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT A
WAY TO GET OUT OF IT.
>> THIS MORNING I THOUGHT
GUARANTEED I'M GOING HOME, BUT
VARNER'S MELTDOWN AFTER THE
CHALLENGE, I THINK PAINTED A
HUGE TARGET ON HIS BACK.
>> GOOD EFFORT, EVERYBODY.
>> EVERYONE ON THIS TRIBE LOOKED
AT HIM LIKE, OH, MY GOSH, YOU
CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
>> HE'S LIED BEFORE.
>> I WAS LIKE A LITTLE KID
INSIDE JUST GIDDY.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE HE JUST
HANDED ME AMMUNITION ON A SILVER
PLATTER.
>> PEIH-GEE, IF YOU TAKE ME OUT
OF THE PHYSICAL PART OF THESE
CHALLENGE, IT'S NOT GOING TO GET
EASIER.
JEFF'S NOT PULLING HIS WEIGHT AT
CAMP.
HE'S SLEEPING ALL DAY.
HE STARTS SCRAMBLING, HE'S
CALLING PEOPLE OUT.
>> I NOTICED THAT.
>> WHAT I WOULD ASK IS THAT YOU
GUYS TRUST ME AND THAT WE VOTE
HIM.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> WELL, PEIH-GEE, YOU WANT TO
HAVE A TALK, JUST YOU AND I FOR
A SECOND?
>> YEAH.
I THINK YOU MADE A REALLY GOOD
CASE.
GOOD LAWYER.
>> THANKS.
>> HE MAKES A GOOD POINT.
IF WE VOTE OFF TASHA OR SAVAGE,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE MANY MORE
CHALLENGES TO COME.
>> I KNOW.
>> VARNER, WE'RE STILL IN THE
MAJORITY.
>> IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE TO JOIN
UP WITH SAVAGE AND TASHA.
ARE THEY GOING TO BE LOYAL?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE EVERYTHING
DESPERATE PEOPLE SAY WITH A
GRAIN OF SALT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AFTER I SAW HOW UNPREDICTABLE
VARNER IS, I THINK HE NEEDS TO
GO NEXT.
BUT WOO DID VOTE FOR ME, AND HE
DETESTS ME, TOO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH I CAN
TRUST HER.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO
EVERYBODY.
>>THEY WANT US TO VOTE OUT JEFF?
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
>> WE'RE THINKING ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, YOU HAVE TO MAKE UP
YOUR MIND.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
VOTING THESE GUYS.
>> I KNOW THAT I'M ON THE BOTTOM
WITH YOU GUYS AND I'M IN THE ON
THE BOTTOM WITH THEM.
SO I'M GOING TO VOTE WITH THEM.
I ALREADY MADE UP MY MIND.
SO IT'S UP TO YOU WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO.
>> WE WERE TIGHT SINCE WE'VE
GOTTEN HERE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE COOL.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT US.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHO IS GOING
TO BE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
THIS IS A CONVERSATION THAT
DOESN'T NEED TO HAPPEN RIGHT
NOW, PEIH-GEE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, WHERE DID ALL
THIS ANIMOSITY COME FROM?
SHE'S LIKE, I'M NOT WITH YOU AND
WOO.
I KNOW I'M ON THE BOTTOM WITH
YOU GUYS.
I'M VOTING WITH THEM.
THAT'S HOW I'M VOTING.
THAT MADE UP MY MIND, I WANTED
HER GONE.
>> I DON'T LIKE HOW SHE'S
TALKING TO ME.
I WANT TO VOTE HER OUT.
>> SHE'S STRONGER THAN JEFF.
SHE IS.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO VOTE YOU
GUYS OUT, BUT...
>> YEAH.
>> I'M LOOK AT TASHA.
SHE'S LOOKING AT ME STUNNED.
>> I DON'T LIKE HOW SHE'S
TALKING TO ME.
>> IT'S SO EASY.
IT'S SO EASY TO CREATE SUSPICION
OR MISDIRECTION BETWEEN PEIH-GEE
AND ABI.
PEIH-GEE WANTS TO VOTE ABI.
SO YOU AND TASH VOTE PEIH-GEE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW QUICKLY
EVERYTHING CHANGED ON THIS
TRIBE.
>> I CAME BACK TO THIS CAMP
THINKING I WAS DONE, BUT IF I
CAN TAKE THIS CLOUD THAT'S OVER
ME RIGHT NOW AND SLING IT OVER
SOMEBODY ELSE, I'M GOING TO DO
IT.
>> THAT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> THIS MAKES SENSE TO ME.
>> THAT'S IT.
I APPRECIATE YOU AND WOO.
I LIKE YOU GUYS SO MUCH, I WANT
TO WORK WITH YOU GUYS.
>> OPTIONS ARE OPENING UP.
PEIH-GEE WILL BE VOTING ABI, AND
ABI WILL BE VOTING PEIH-GEE.
THE THING ABOUT ABI IS YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO GET,
AND PEIH-GEE, SHE'S INDECISIVE.
SO IT'S HARD.
IT'S A TOUGH DECISION, BUT IT
FEELS FANTASTIC TO HAVE THE
TABLES TURNED.
SAVAGE AND I WERE DOWN 4-2.
ALL HOPE SEEMED LOVES.
BUT HERE WE ARE MAKING THE
DECISIONS ON WHO WILL GO HOME
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: SAVAGE AND TASHBACK
GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
AS PART OF THE RITUAL AS TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BECAUSE FIRE REPRESENTS
YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
SO SAVAGE, LET'S START BY GOING
BACK TO THE SWITCH.
FIRST REACTION WAS WHAT?
>> I COULDN'T PROCESS IT.
IT WAS TOO MUCH IN TERMS OF THE
MASSIVE AMOUNT OF WORK TO GET
JUST REASONABLE SHELTER,
REASONABLE CAMP, AND THEN TO SEE
THAT THERE'S TWO BAYONS AND FOUR
TA KEOS, TOUGH TO PROCESS.
>> Jeff: SO PEIH-GEE, IS IT A
FAIR ASSUMPTION TO SAY SAVAGE
AND TASHA WOULD PROBABLY BE IN
TROUBLE SIMPLY BASED ON HISTORY.
>> THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
WHEN YOU'RE IN A SWAP AND YOU'RE
IN THE MINORITY FROM THE
ORIGINAL TRIBE, YOU'RE IN
TROUBLE.
>> Jeff: NOW LET'S FAST
FORWARD TO TODAY'S CHALLENGE
WHERE A MELTDOWN OCCURRED.
>> HI.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WHAT WAS
HAPPENING THERE?
>> I WAS SENDING A SIGNAL TO
SOMEONE ON THE OTHER TRIBE I
CARE ABOUT, AND TASHA JUST JUMPS
OUT OF NOWHERE AND CALLS ME A
RAT, AND I WASN'T BEING A RAT.
I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE I WAS BEING A
RAT.
AND THAT JUST HIT ME.
I'VE HAD NO SLEEP.
I'VE HAD IN FOOD.
I'M EMOTIONAL.
AND HONESTLY, I DON'T REMEMBER
IT.
IT WAS AN EMOTIONAL MELTDOWN
THAT I DON'T RECALL.
>> Jeff: TASHA, I HAVE A
FEELING YOU REMEMBER IT.
>> I DO.
AND, JEFF, MY MAMA ALWAYS TOLD
ME, KEEP YOUR FAMILY BUSINESS AT
HOME.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER ISSUES WE
HAD, WE SHOULD HAVE KEPT IT
AMONGST THE FAMILY.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT THERE WAS
COMMUNICATION WHEN OUR FAMILY'S
RIGHT HERE.
SO MY INITIAL THOUGHT WAS, TAKE
'EM OUT NOW SO THAT WE DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT LOYALTY
LATER ON.
>> Jeff: SO, JEFF, YOU THINK
YOU ARE GOING HOME?
>> PEOPLE CAN OVERCOME ALL KINDS
OF THINGS.
WOULDN'T BIT GREAT IF I COULD
ESCAPE WITHOUT ONE VOTE?
>> Jeff: IS THERE A PLAN?
WHO SHOULD GO HOME?
>> I'VE HEARD SO MANY NAMES
THROWN AROUND, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHO IS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: WHOSE NAME HAVE YOU
HEARD THROWN AROUND?
>> I'VE HEARD ABI'S NAME THROWN
AROUND.
I'VE HEARD PEIH-GEE'S NAME
THROWN AROUND.
I'VE HEARD MY NAME THROWN
AROUND.
SO I GUESS SAVAGE AND TASHA HAVE
FOUND THEIR WAY FROM THE BOTTOM
OF THE HEAP TO THE TOP.
>> Jeff: TO THE TOP?
>> YES.
I THINK ALL THE CHOICES AND
DECISIONS OF WHAT HAPPENS HERE
TONIGHT COME FROM THE TWO OF
THEM.
>> Jeff: SO ABI, IF HE'S
TELLING THE TRUTH, THE FOUR OF
YOU, PEIH-GEE, YOURSELF, VARNER
AND WOO ARE NOT ALL TOGETHER,
WHICH IS THE CRASH SAVAGE WOULD
NEED.
>> RIGHT, AND I HAVE A STRONG
FEELING I MAY BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: BASED ON WHAT?
>> BASED ON CONVERSATIONS AROUND
CAMP I WASN'T PART OF.
I'M NOT THAT NAIVE.
>> Jeff: PEIH-GEE, IF IT'S
YOU, IS THERE ANYTHING YOU CAN
SAY TO SWAY THEM?
>> THIS GAME IS CRAZY.
I WANT TO BE WITH PEOPLE I FEEL
SOLID WITH AND I TRUST.
YOU ALL CAN TRUST ME.
IF I GAVE YOU MY WORD.
I'M GOOD WITH IT.
I'M STEADY.
I'M LOYAL.
>> Jeff: PRETTY GOOD PITCH,
ABI.
WHAT'S YOURS?
>> MINE IS PRETTY SIMILAR TO
HERS.
I'VE BEEN WORKING AROUND CAMP,
AND I'VE BEEN WORKING REALLY
HARD AND HAVING STRONG.
MY LEVEL OF COMMITMENT IS HUGE
BECAUSE I AM A COMMITTAL PERSON.
>> Jeff: SO, JEFF, NOW YOU'VE
HEARD ALL THE FEEDBACK.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TONIGHT?
>> I SAID IT EARLIER.
I HAVE NO IDEA, BUT I BELIEVE
WHAT I SAID.
SAVAGE AND TASHA ARE IN CONTROL
OF TONIGHT'S VOTE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PEIH-GEE, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'VE WANTED YOU OUT SINCE DAY
ONE.
HOPEFULLY IT WILL WORK THIS
TIME.
>> YOU TALK WAY TOO MUCH.
YOU CAN SHUT YOUR MOUTH, TAKE A
CHILL PILL, GIRL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE ABI.
PEIH-GEE.
ABI.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES ABI, TWO VOTES
PEIH-GEE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PEIH-GEE, TWO
VOTES ABI, ONE VOTE LEFT.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR" SECOND CHANCE,
PEIH-GEE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> WELL PLAYED, GUYS.
WOO, GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: PEIH-GEE, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
WELL, ONE OF THE KEYS THE
LASTING IN THIS GAME IS YOU HAVE
TO BE ABLE TO ADAPT ON A DIME IN
ANY SITUATION.
IF YOU DON'T, YOU'RE GONE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," ANGKOR IS IN MISERY.
>> WE SURVIVE A NIGHT IN THIS
HELLHOLE, NO RESOURCES, NO
SHELTER, NOTHING.
THIS IS A DEAD COVE.
WE'RE IN HELL RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: BUT THEY'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONES WHO ARE SUFFERING.
>> WATCH OUT!
>> THEY GOT ME GOOD.
I GUESS I GOT BLIND SIDED.
I FEEL REALLY DISAPPOINTED IN
TASHA AND SAVAGE BECAUSE I
TRUSTED THEM.
OBVIOUSLY IT WAS MISPLACED.
I WASN'T EXPECTING.
THIS I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO GO
A LOT FURTHER.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT, IF THEY WANT
TO THROW THEIR LOT IN WITH ABI,
GOOD LUCK TO THEM.
SHE'S A HANDFUL.