translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
After a surprise change...
Throw away your bandanas!
...Second Chance Survivor
went from two tribes
to three tribes.
Angkor, Bayon
and Ta Keo.
The new Ta Keo tribe was
building trust.
We have four choice pieces.
It's insane!
The new Bayon tribe was
building relationships.
Do you know about relationships?
I try something new,
I try to have feelings.
While the Angkor tribe
had to rebuild everything.
Nothing to eat ? Do we have rice?
The only evidence...
We stay united, the four.
...was that Tasha and Savage
were in the minority.
But they weren't
ready to give up.
When we meet again,
you can join us.
My former members of Ta Keo
want to stick together,
but Tasha whispered a
few sweet nothings in my ear.
In the immunity test,
Jeremy found an idol in secret.
Angkor lost the test...
Bayon wins immunity!
They send Angkor to the council.
... and Varner got out of his hinges.
I made a deal with you,
then he made a deal with her.
I am in the middle of a beautiful mess.
I should not have done that.
Facing the council,
the old Ta Keo
couldn't get along.
I know I'm down with you.
I will vote with them.
Tasha and Savage took advantage of this.
You, me, Tash,
on vote Peih-Gee.
Savage and I were dominated.
But this turnaround
is a treat.
At the council, Woo voted for Abi.
Again.
Third person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
But it was Peih-Gee who was eliminated.
Wow, good luck.
The tribe has spoken.
Second time you write my name.
There are 17 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I can't believe it, I'm here!
I dodged.
Upon returning from the race,
I thought I was screwed.
But I didn't get a single vote.
Thanks. I'm grateful.
Know that I am loyal to you.
I have always been to Abi.
Tell me what to do
to prove it to you.
I owe them
and it makes me sick.
I have to lick their ass.
But this is my second chance,
so I'll do whatever it takes.
Honestly, Peih-Gee
shouldn't have left.
Varner should have left.
What he did on trial
was worse than anything.
It's a jackal,
it should have been him.
I feel very good.
I came here
at the bottom of the ladder.
I thought Savage or I
was going to leave.
But now we have control.
Varner is the source
of all discord
and the shouting matches.
- I agree.
- What I am saying,
is that you do not risk anything.
You are not about to leave.
No way.
Tasha, what just happened
makes me uncomfortable.
- Come talk about it.
- No, not in private.
It bothers me that you take
someone who just voted for me
apart.
To chat with him in private.
But Abi, I didn't lie to you.
I didn't take you by surprise.
I supported you. So...
What is the problem ?
Be allied with Abi
makes me a little nervous,
because she lacks a lot
of self-confidence.
She's a bit paranoid.
It makes her totally unpredictable.
Woo, you've been plotting
to eliminate me since...
...a long time, hmm?
It bothers me to receive
these votes at the council.
Especially when you come from a tribe
like Ta Keo,
where all conspire against you.
Sorry to vote for you, but...
To me, it's starting
to feel personal.
I am delighted
to be in the majority,
but my ears are open.
And Woo voted against me
twice.
If it was up to me,
he would be the next to go.
At the last immunity test,
I found the idol,
but I could not rejoice.
I found it and I was...
I'm so happy !
Finally ! It took me two years,
but I finally have my idol.
What a beautiful object!
I love it !
- So, the idol?
- Nothing.
I think back to Mike,
last season: in a tree.
- I want to climb to watch.
- Yes, but...
I follow you, but which tree to choose?
It's my idol.
I won't tell anyone.
So I told Stephen
we really had to look.
Because I don't want him
to suspect me of having it.
We can start here.
you go this way,
I'll go that way. And we put the package.
We have to find her.
That's all we got.
Stephen must think
I'm still looking for her.
And that she will be for us.
I want to keep him close to me.
At some point,
they will come after me.
I want him then to come and say to me,
"They're going to come after you."
I can then play my joker.
I would love to be Stephen's JT.
We could be friends for life after that.
I'll give you second place.
If that's okay with you.
Well, that's not enough for me.
We survived a night
in this hellhole.
Not bad.
- Not bad.
- Hey, say!
This cove is dead.
I say. Well and truly dead.
Our new camp...
No resources, no shelter,
Nothing at all.
Wish me luck !
I am disgusted. At first
I was in heaven, I was the boss,
the sea was generous.
Now I am literally
in a Survivor ghetto.
There is nothing here.
Here you are again, welcome!
I wish I had
better news.
It's very difficult. It's not
like we're resting,
to be fed,
lying in hammocks.
I have a snail.
Merci.
We are in hell.
You are hungry ?
I'm starving !
Why ? What is it ?
"One more day on the beach,
to get wet and stomp.
Victory is up for grabs.
Some will party,
others will sulk."
- Reward !
- A feast !
It's a reward event,
and it's great,
because I'm starting to wither away.
So I'm very excited.
But do we still have the energy
to succeed?
Over here, everyone!
Bayon, Ta Keo, discover
the new Angkor tribe.
Peih-Gee,
eliminated at the last council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Oui !
Today you will run in the water,
collect a sandbag
and will come back.
Then using a board,
you will send it into a net.
The first two
to place their three bags
in the net, win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes !
For the first:
a barbecue Survivor kit.
Grill,
wok, sausages,
vegetables...
Everything for a great evening.
For the second: smaller,
but just as cute.
For the latter:
nothing.
- Is it worth it ?
- Is it worth it !
But, surprise: each tribe will
select a person
to run the whole race.
It's a hero's trial.
You will put all your eggs
in one basket.
Angkor, who will it be?
Who are you lining up?
- I will do it.
- Savage is going to compete for Angkor.
Bayon, who are you lining up?
- Do you want to do it, Jeremy?
- Yes I will do it.
Jeremy is going to compete for Bayon.
Who will compete for Ta Keo?
I go.
Deitz will compete.
We have Savage
versus Jeremy versus Deitz.
The others, take place on your mats.
We will begin.
Well, on and go.
For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Come on, Jeremy!
- Come on, Savage!
- Go ahead !
It's much harder than you think
to run in water!
Take the first bag and come back!
Terry has his.
Jeremy at her temple.
Savage has his.
Everyone comes back.
All three are trying
to conserve some energy.
This board will need some.
Go easy, Terry!
Deitz and Jeremy arrive first.
That's Savage.
Now we have to launch it
with your board,
propel him to the net.
It is adjustable.
It will take a few tries.
Deitz ...
...place son premier !
Deitz repart for Ta Keo.
- Jeremy, just too short.
- A bit stronger !
Savage will give it a shot.
That's good, Savage!
Savage, too long.
Deitz accrues his advance for Ta Keo.
Jeremy will try again.
Let's go for Jeremy, and Savage.
Jeremy scores and leaves for Bayon!
That's good, Jeremy!
Savage misses, he has to start over.
Go-y, check, Andrew !
New try.
Savage mark!
- Savage leaves.
- Come on, Andrew, it's good!
Everyone
goes to get their second bag.
Deitz, en tête, a le sien.
Well, Deitz!
Slowly but surely!
After only ten days of play,
we can already see the impact
lack of sleep
and undernourishment.
Deitz strides back.
Jeremy on his way home.
Savage has his second bag.
Come on, Savage!
Deitz has a nice lead for Ta Keo,
can he capitalize on it?
- Go ahead, boy!
- It's good !
Far too long.
We quickly forget
what we did the first time!
- Come on, Bayon!
- Jeremy, back with his 2nd bag.
- Savage, still in the water.
- Savage, you're in on it!
- Jeremy, too short.
- Almost !
Deitz, fort et loin.
Savage is in on it again!
Get it right the first time!
Equality, one bag each!
Go ahead, do your thing!
Savage...
...score on the first try!
Savage takes the lead for Angkor!
- Come on, Savage!
Deitz tire.
Deitz places his second bag, he leaves.
Come on, Deitz, it's good!
Jeremy tries to place his 2nd bag.
And he succeeds!
Jeremy can go get
his third and final bag.
They are all in the water now.
Jeremy tries to climb back up
with big strides.
Savage has his 3rd bag, he's coming back.
I'm almost there.
- Come on, Savage!
It would be a whole new story
if Angkor won.
Here is Deitz who is accelerating.
- He wins over Savage.
- Come on Terry!
The two men give everything!
Go for it !
- In one try !
- In one fell swoop!
In one try !
It's between Deitz and Savage,
For victory !
For the win, buddy!
Deitz tire.
The rate!
Savage could win now!
- Its good !
- Savage!
And he does!
Angkor wins the reward!
He remains in second place.
Deitz, and Jeremy,
still in on it.
Life has just changed for Angkor.
Savage is exhausted.
- Thank you so much !
For second place
and the reward.
Deitz and Jeremy have their chances.
It's okay, Jeremy!
Jeremy, way too long.
Its good !
It's okay, he'll get there.
- Come on Terry!
- Allons-y, Terry!
- Deitz tire ...
- And There you go !
- ...and score!
Ta Keo wins the award!
Nothing for the Bayon tribe.
- Cheer !
- Thanks.
Angkor, how important
wears this victory?
We haven't eaten anything
for days.
And Andrew did this
purely out of love for this tribe.
Angkor, a great reward.
Everything you need
for a superb barbecue on the camp.
Pack your things,
enjoy your campfire.
Congratulations to you !
Bravo, Andrew !
Your Keo. This is not a complete kit,
but it's not bad.
Come take your reward
and return to camp.
Bayon, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
What haunted me
in particular in Pearl Islands,
it was to know
if I had done my part,
if I had done enough
to convert the essay.
Today,
I gave it my all and we won.
If I feel legitimate?
Totally.
Oh, my God, let's eat!
- We're going to eat !
- God bless Savage!
You are a bloody legend!
- Thank you, Savage, God bless you!
- You are a legend, my brother!
When we barely eat
for four days,
you reach your limits.
So when Jeff said
"Angkor wins",
I almost fell to my knees.
It was one of my best moments
in Survivor.
To say that I am about
to eat with you, friends!
Sure !
- This is a major motivation.
- Sure !
They had incredible faith in me.
Because that's all,
when you're starving.
And I was up to it.
It's greasy, I have grease
on my fingers!
Immunity is in your pocket!
This little tribe now knows
that we are big
enough against the hefty guys opposite.
And it's huge, it changes everything.
'Cause now
we can walk full throttle
and not go to the council.
Angkor !
If we lost at Survivor
the first time,
we have to change something.
I made a big mistake
last time in Cagayan.
Strategically,
I think I played very well.
But not socially.
Most everyone thought
I was gonna get here,
act like crap
and get them in trouble.
I was probably at the top
of all the lists of people to go out.
I took that to heart.
I read the book "How to make
friends and influence people".
He says to be
as sincere as possible,
to sympathize with people.
I know it may surprise
to see Chaos-Kass apply
individual development methods
.
But I had to look
at my game and what I have to do.
This morning upon awakening,
I see Kass by the tree
detach pearls from his bag
with the machete.
"But what is she doing?"
I don't trust him.
She nicknamed herself "Chaos-Kass"!
It's his thing
to do sneaky things,
like a false idol.
No. Go to the other side.
I see her on the beach,
and she says to me: "Go away!"
So I know
she's up to something.
It's Chaos-Kass, let's go!
Happy belated birthday !
A little bit of Bayon
to feel good at Ta Keo.
That's super sweet, Kass!
A little lucky charm.
Merci.
I thought you were making
a fake idol.
I know, I figured
everyone would think so,
but I wanted to surprise you and...
"It's a birthday present,
a lucky charm for today!"
Thanks, Kass.
This is so cute. Thanks.
The person
who will win Second Chance
will be someone
who knows how to evolve and change.
For me, it comes
down to being more open.
Man of little faith!
As if I had the skills
to make an idol!
So, Spencer,
where are you and Wiggles?
- Strategically, you mean?
- Yeah.
- She voted against me.
- Yeah ?
- You were next, huh?
- I was next.
The facts:
four Bayon and two ex-Ta Keo.
I knew right away
that Wigglesworth and I
got off to a bad start.
Which prompts me
to throw it to them.
Would you vote against Kelly
if necessary?
Yes. Some over there...
- His vote belongs to them.
- Who ?
- Terry, Woo, Varner...
- It's clear.
My tribe must know clearly
that there are people
Kelly will go back to
in the future.
Wigglesworth has a close connection
- with Terry, and Woo...
- So she has Terry and Woo.
- ...and these people...
- And even Wentworth, right?
She is fine with all of them.
Spencer dit
that Kelly Wigglesworth
has a ton of allies.
But I don't think it's
entirely sincere.
I don't know
if she is in good faith.
He's a bit tricky.
My first reaction was:
"Women should be strong
and stick together."
Not only to stay in number,
with the hope of perhaps
creating a female alliance,
but also to limit
the number of boys.
I will always have a hard
time trusting him.
Looks like we all have
something to think about.
When we have lost a test,
Spencer will have to go first.
I'm in 100%.
Me too. I love that.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First, I collect the idols.
- Kimmy.
- Yes sir.
Kass.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
a team member will be your voice.
The others will be blindfolded.
By voice commands only,
the voice will guide
the blind crew
to collect very large
and very heavy puzzle pieces.
When you've got them all,
take off your blindfolds
and work together
to solve the puzzle.
The first two tribes to finish
gain immunity.
Unvoted.
The losers: advice,
where someone will be the 4th person
eliminated from Second Chance.
Bayon, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
- Me.
- Monica won't participate.
Ta Keo, one more member.
Who will it be?
- Yeah, me.
- Ciera won't participate.
Monica and Ciera, sit down.
The others, a minute of organization
and we begin.
We have our voices.
It's Jeff for Angkor,
Kimmy for Bayon,
Kass for Ta Keo.
Let's go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Angkor One and Two, keep it up!
Angkor One, a little to the right!
Communication is the key.
Turn right !
Louder, Kimmy,
I can't hear you!
The tribe that will communicate best
will succeed.
Turn around, Terry!
On your right !
Downstairs !
No, not this one!
Andrew, to the left!
Behind you, Andrew!
Voilà !
There are 16 puzzle pieces.
It's a lot.
All heavy and unwieldy.
Very difficult to carry
by one person.
To the right !
The Bayons brought back
their first coin.
Angkor One, turn around!
- The Angkors brought back their 1st piece.
- Put it down, Joe and Kelley!
The Ta Keo brought back
their first coin.
Equality, one everywhere.
- Its good ?
- Yes, put it down.
Second piece for Angkor.
Second play for Bayon.
Here are the Ta Keo,
with their 2nd and 3rd.
Keith, left!
Keith, pose ! Keith !
Put it down!
Hard to hear
when everyone is screaming.
Pose !
I can not hear !
Pose, it's good!
Third piece for Angkor.
Abi, right there, go...
Third play for Bayon.
Kass, give me something!
Joe !
Deitz is still waiting for help.
As if he was waiting
to be called, in class.
The teacher doesn't see it.
Straight ! Pose!
Angkor leads with four pieces.
- Keith!
- Three for Bayon and Ta Keo.
U-turn, Terry!
Kass, help us!
I'm yelling at someone else!
I can not hear.
- Pose!
- Do we pose?
4th piece for Bayon.
16 pieces.
Still many parts
to find.
Angkor leads with 11.
They won the last award.
They would love another win.
Ten for Bayon.
- Seven for Ta Keo.
- Kass, yes?
The Ta Keo are dead last.
Keith !
I can not hear.
Deitz, like the guy at a party
no one wants to talk to,
waiting to be asked to dance.
Joe !
Joe picks up a coin on his own.
These pieces are massive!
But Joe doesn't expect help.
Joe, back with another piece.
He did it all on his own.
Pose!
Another piece for Ta Keo.
11 for Angkor, 10 for Bayon.
New for Ta Keo.
Another piece for Ta Keo.
Joe put Ta Keo back in the running.
Andrew !
Another piece for Angkor.
Savage, exhausted.
This ordeal is going to hurt.
- How are you ?
- Nope !
Pose!
Whore !
Oh shit !
To be the voice is not enviable
in this test.
Joe sprints!
Ta Keo now leads with 15!
All right, Joe!
Big return of the Ta Keo,
who were good last!
More than a room for Ta Keo.
Two for Bayon and Angkor.
And it's not even half,
there is still the puzzle to solve!
- Pose!
- More than one room for Angkor!
Spencer, yes!
And 15 for Bayon!
Last piece for everyone!
Andrew, roll it to the right!
Attention !
Towards me !
Joe and Deitz
are currently in binomial.
Terry was really alone.
- Now he has a partner.
- Ahead ! Laid !
Sixteenth piece for Ta Keo!
Take off your blindfolds, get to work!
Sixteenth for Angkor!
Take off your masks!
- Come on, you have to give it your all!
- I see nothing !
- Big immunity at stake!
- Too much light !
Oh my God !
- Do we pose?
- Sixteenth for Bayon!
Take off your masks!
Everyone is on the puzzle.
It's a corner.
It's a cube.
There is a drawing on each side.
This is the badge
of your tribe's flag.
You live with.
You know what he looks like.
The more you progress,
the easier it will be.
I think it's going there.
Spencer gets involved for Bayon.
He takes matters into his own hands.
One of the biggest difficulties
of this puzzle
is the weight and size of the pieces.
Just moving them
is a huge job.
The sun is beating down hard.
Everyone feels it.
Varner, here!
Tasha starts giving orders.
Whore !
Verner dropped the coin on himself.
It is the wall on one side.
Angkor spent a lot of time
moving a lot of pieces.
They don't seem to have made
any progress.
Mince !
It's a race
between Ta Keo and Bayon.
The Bayon are progressing a lot...
If they're right.
They were the last
to collect their pieces,
but advance the most on the puzzle.
Like that, yes.
- Spencer thinks he's got something.
- Well done, Spencer!
Bayon is very close.
Bayon, for the victory!
Bayon wins immunity!
There remains the second place!
- Carry on!
- When it counts!
It's between Ta Keo and Angkor,
who are fighting to ensure
not to go to the council.
The Ta Keo lead.
The Angkors can go back up,
if they find the strength.
They literally sleep
on the coins.
Ta Keo, ever closer
with each room.
I can't hold this alone.
Exhaustion is visible
on the faces of the Angkors.
Almost as if they were waiting
for Ta Keo to win.
Let it stop.
- Only one room left for Ta Keo.
- Jeff!
Ta Keo wins immunity!
Sending Angkor to the council
for the second time in a row!
Yo, frérot!
Bayonne, congratulations!
- Cheer !
- Thanks !
Well done, everyone!
No one will leave Bayon,
and no one will leave Ta Keo.
It's a team victory. Cheer !
Angkor, the council, once again.
I have to ask the question.
Savage, have you given up?
We couldn't take it anymore.
I have never known that.
Even in college football,
we were far from it,
and yet I gave it my all.
I've never known that, Jeff.
It's almost scary.
I can't stand anymore.
I can't think.
Angkor, I would like to tell you
that something positive
awaits you at the camp.
But I can not.
Bayon, Ta Keo,
get your stuff,
go back to camp.
No advice tonight.
- Well done, everyone!
- Cheer !
Angkor, you alone await a date
with me tonight at the council,
where someone will be the 4th person
eliminated from Second Chance.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Nice effort, friends.
Varner, you have guided us well.
- We did our best.
- Yeah.
Damn it !
All the positives
brought by the food, he...
- ...flew away.
- Gone, man.
We approached this day
by saying
that we were going to decimate them
and stay on top.
And we got knocked out
by the most physical test
in which I participated.
So we hit rock bottom,
gotta get back to the board
and fire someone.
Varner, how are you?
It's my little toe.
It's going to hurt a lot for a few days.
I am not dangerous to anyone.
For information...
Varner is not
physically dangerous!
Thanks to Abi,
Savage and I came up
from the bottom of the ladder
to, apparently, its summit.
Nevertheless, Abi is unpredictable.
She will make a decision, firm,
and a few minutes later,
she no longer knows.
And that worries me.
The last thing we need
it's that he's talking to Abi.
- He's very cunning.
- Yes.
- Jeff has to go.
- Yeah.
It's you or me.
And I think that's me.
- You think ?
- Yes.
They don't tell me anything.
They came
and took over.
And Abi having officially
changed sides,
they have control,
nothing can be done.
It's clearly Woo or me tonight.
Abi is totally in their pocket,
she completely
turned her back on us.
But I have one thing for me:
I never voted for Abi,
I saved her twice,
so if it's Abi who decides,
I could get away with
it again.
You know, when we got here,
we were dominating, 4 against 2,
and there we go
towards the elimination
of all ex-Ta Keo,
and that worries me a bit.
What do you think ?
I thought about it too.
It's nice to be coveted.
They make me so comfortable.
- My position is really good.
- Don't get too comfortable!
- No, I know.
- I understand that they are friendly.
- Because they need you.
- Yes.
How about we take out Varner?
Let's not forget that you voted
against me twice!
Woo gave his arguments.
I will not take them into account,
because he says he
wants to work with me,
but then
he stabs me in the back.
I will go with people who appreciate
my personality
and what I have to offer.
Put yourself in my shoes !
Understand the situation.
You followed the majority,
I understand that.
Without resentment.
But what impression
does it give me, do you think?
I tried to rekindle
my relationship with Abi,
but she was rather angry.
I actually
voted against it twice.
She wants me.
If she seeks retaliation,
of revenge against me,
I could
get in trouble at the council.
Woo worries me.
What is...
- In what ?
- He voted against me twice!
- So what are you...
- He's not loyal to me.
Something in him wants to eliminate me.
Listen.
Varner, in my opinion,
should have left last time.
More Woo...
He hasn't proven anything to me so far.
Abi south block:
"I don't trust Woo.
He wrote my name twice."
But Woo can help us
win trials.
But Abi is stubborn.
If you say "blue",
she will say "yellow".
Who do you think
we'll lose immunity with?
Woo or Varner?
Who handicaps us the most?
Yes, but Varner protected me.
Often. He proved his loyalty to me.
I understand...
You should give him
the benefit of the doubt
to want to think about dating Woo.
Yes. No. If you want
to be loyal to Jeff...
He was to me.
If it can help you sleep...
That's not it, Tasha,
don't be silly.
- I'm trying to...
- I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
I'm trying to allay your fears.
I think,
I think, I think.
- And I'm listening.
- Woo wasn't loyal to me.
What frightens me,
is that Varner
is very manipulative.
At any time,
he could deploy his talents,
and I would lose Abi.
Are we okay?
I adore you, you know that.
We worked well together.
I miss you a bit.
We don't talk anymore,
we don't mess around like before.
I miss my "Abi moments".
Abi is the central piece of the puzzle.
You may have to
follow your wishes.
Otherwise, Abi will be angry.
You took your time!
This evening,
a big decision awaits me.
It all comes down to winning events
versus trust and loyalty.
And I hate having to...
be the one who decides.
Varner, let's talk about the cane.
Is it a consequence
of the ordeal of the day?
Yes. One of those big pieces
crushed my foot.
It is purple, painful.
Today was a nightmare.
I have never known that.
Being unable to collect
thoughts or even go...
...pee... What the
fuck is that?
Dealing with times like this
it empties you.
But I think back to the millions
who voted for me
and I continue.
Woo,
a part of you must say to itself:
"Varner seems like
an easy choice now."
- He is hurt.
- Absolutely.
Varner and I
feel like we're at the bottom of the ladder.
And it's hard
but it is a question of lasting
more than the other.
And I can outlast him,
that's for sure.
Abi, Woo says it's him or Varner.
- Do you agree ?
- Yes.
So is this vote easy
or difficult?
I do not know.
I've been thinking all day
and I'm still undecided.
I mean...
Varner has been very loyal to me
throughout the game.
But we want to win races.
Savage,
you could say that Varner
didn't help you much,
in any of the tests.
True.
But this is Survivor.
You have to think about the future.
When the merger comes,
Woo is a beast.
Do we want to face it individually
in trials?
It deserves consideration.
But the merger
is not about to happen.
- You don't know.
- He's still full of immunities.
I will be an asset to you.
Varner, no.
Woo will be your nemesis.
I am not at all
physically dangerous.
For no one.
Woo, you can't escape
your physical power.
You will always be seen
as a contender for victory
if you reach
the individual part.
Sure. But...
I'm the center player
who will stay loyal,
who will give everything for his alliance.
But you're not in the covenant.
You voted against.
You voted against Abi.
- Twice.
And I've been loyal to them
at the last tip.
- And if I can plead...
- Yes.
Tasha,
you're a little closed towards me,
you must see me as a rogue,
but i trust you
and I'm loyal to you.
Savage,
I am totally loyal to you.
We have a lot in common.
We are old school.
Oui.
And Abibi, I've been loyal to you
since day one
Because I love you.
I won't vote for you,
I didn't vote for you,
I am loyal to you
to the end.
I hope
you will do the same to me.
Abi.
It was a good plea.
It was a good plea,
and I don't know what to do.
Tasha, give us
your weighing of interests.
Because both have good arguments.
I just know that to win,
we need strong people.
That's Woo.
Loyalty, physical ability.
- That's what I weigh.
- And I have both.
I give you loyalty
and physical strength.
You give it to her,
you didn't give it to me.
You voted against Abi twice.
Of course, I voted against Abi.
But I tell you now,
I am ready to join you.
Varner a des relations
with all the ex-Ta Keo.
How can you be sure
he won't betray you?
You also have relations with them.
- I'm ready to end it.
- I've already done it.
He plays hard, and I respect that.
But you can play
by protecting your back.
I have the interest of the group
at heart.
With regard to involvement,
one of us has already demonstrated it,
the other has not.
But I've been relating
to you for the past 5-6 days,
and I'm ready to get involved
and stick with it, I promise.
I love confrontation.
No one here is ready to give up.
We vote? Let's go.
Good, you want to vote.
Let's vote.
Whoa, over to you.
Abi.
I promise you, here and now.
I will stay loyal.
Don't eliminate me.
Make sure you don't write "Abi"!
May it not be me.
You card.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol,
it's time to play it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Jeff.
Woo.
Jeff. Two votes Jeff.
A vote Woo.
Fourth person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
Jeff.
That's three, that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
Little bitch.
Forgive me.
Varner, the tribe has spoken.
- It's time to go.
- Thank you, Jeff.
Merci.
You're welcome.
If advice has a bright side,
it's this:
sometimes, if you make the right choice,
you go back to camp
stronger and more united.
We will soon know
if this is the case for this tribe.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Team Survivor ST
http://survivor-st.forumgratuit.org/
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro : Lény
Re-synchro version HD : aymeric000
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
In a season
where everyone gets a second chance,
the most improbable may well
be the most dangerous.
This is the final quintet.
At 2, we're not going anywhere.
But 5 could take me to the end.
If she writes my name again,
she's dead to me.
She is a real snake.
There will be victims.
I have a passion that has been simmering for 15 years.
Suddenly,
this opportunity presents itself,
and it went all over the place.
But when it comes to the adventure of life,
regarding the idea of ​​starting
the second half of my life,
I clearly got
what I needed.
And I'm very grateful.