translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
In a season dedicated
to second chances,
each was trying to change
their story in the game.
I want to do everything
I didn't do the first time.
Go hard or get out.
I create relationships
that have saved me.
I blame myself
not to have eliminated
the young prodigy, the last time.
I'm so invested this time...
At the merger,
the battle for the majority
was raging.
Let's review the list.
You have to be operational from the outset
to be a majority in the first vote.
But for Joe,
the No. 1 priority was to win.
Joe wins
the first individual immunity!
On the camp, Kass was in trouble
and was looking to make a big hit.
If there's five of us, we can take Tasha out.
At the council, Ciera was up for it.
We are old.
Play to win!
But not everyone was ready
to pull the trigger...
First member of the jury...
...leaving Ciera, Abi and Wentworth
at the bottom of the ladder.
Kass, the tribe has spoken.
There are 12 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
A brilliant plan,
perfectly executed.
Yeah, that's good.
The last tip was amazing.
My 1st goal in Survivor:
reach the jury.
I was like,
"Wow, I did it!"
It's rare in life
to have a huge, huge dream,
that follows you for years,
and suddenly it happens!
- It was so good.
- It worked fine.
We are on day 20. My job
is to preserve my alliance,
old-fashioned, and stay the course.
Eliminate the Cieras,
the Abis, the Wentworths.
I think of Ciera: "Play!"
It just means:
"All against the guys!"
That's all.
- You mean Joe?
- Yeah.
They will try something.
At one point.
We just have to find out when.
I keep an eye.
They simmer a big blow,
I see it in their eyes.
The trick is to understand
who they target
and counter it as best we can.
- It's funny.
- The day will be good.
It's certain.
- How are you after last night?
- How are you.
I expected to have votes.
But this game is constantly changing.
At this point,
I'm at the bottom of the ladder.
I will try everything I can
hoping
to provoke a reaction.
You are in the majority,
my hands are tied.
I think Stephen
wants to hit the big time.
He waits for the right moment.
It's about convincing him
that it's the right time.
It will clearly fracture
at some point.
I want to install things
that will pay off later.
So, I'll tell you.
If it was up to me
I would take action against Joe if he lost.
Ciera is in a bad position,
but we have in common
to want to make the moves
we need
to be in a position to win.
We don't need
everyone, just...
- By a majority.
- ...of six people.
Ciera wants to turn the game upside down.
So do I.
I don't want to be passive
and get knocked down
by a bunch of tough guys.
It's time to act
and target someone
really dangerous.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the reward test?
- Yes !
Today
you will form two teams of six.
At my top, you will paddle
to a series of crates.
You'll jump, untie
them, place them on board, and continue.
When you get 'em all,
you'll stack 'em up
so that no color
repeats on either side.
The first to finish
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yeah !
The six winners
will be taken to Café Survivor.
You will start with iced coffee.
Bagels and fresh cheese.
Cookies.
You will overdose
on caffeine and sugar
and return to camp
bounding like rabbits.
The very first rowing event
took place in season 1,
where Kelly Wiglesworth,
the river guide,
who earns his living by paddling,
lost against Gervase,
15 years ago.
- Do you still remember?
- Well yes.
And he couldn't swim, as a bonus.
I help you a little.
The quote was:
"I lost to the guy
who can't swim."
So, big second chance
for Wiglesworth.
We will form the teams
like a schoolyard
and we'll start.
Here are the two teams
that were formed.
Ciera and Keith.
They will face Tasha,
Fishbach and Abi.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
Everyone must board.
Then you can paddle.
Let's go ! 1, 2, 3!
You have to navigate in the middle.
- Yes yes !
- On the right side, Keith!
Joe and Keith are in trouble.
- Attention !
- What are you doing ?!
One more time,
the wiglesworth team
has difficulty paddling.
Come on, everyone!
You have to go around the flag
before picking up the crates.
All right, those on the left!
She put her team back on track,
perfect equality at the bend.
And now
that you're going to meet...
Block-them, Keith!
...you have to cross
to get to the checkouts.
- Good game !
- [???]
Joe deflected the other team!
- Backward !
Keith is in the water for the Greens.
That's good, Keith!
Abi is in the water for his team.
Closer !
Keith untied the first box.
Abi is still working
on the 1st crate.
Closer ! Left !
Kimmi and Keith are in the lead.
- We have it !
- Keith, get back in the water.
Catch her!
Abi has finally undone the knots.
Ahead !
Joe tries to pull up the 2nd box.
They are heavy!
This is the purple team.
I can do it.
This is Spencer,
for his team's second crate.
He replaced Abi.
Big lead for the Greens.
The Wiglesworth Tribe
has two funds.
Spencer has the 2nd crate on his team.
The Violets are fighting to come back up.
Spencer falls into the water,
he has to come back up!
Go-y, Keith!
Keith unties
the 3rd crate from his team.
- Row!
- Go on !
Joe and Keith work very well
with these funds.
A new cash advance
for the Greens.
You and are you going?
Spencer returns to the water
for the 3rd crate.
Spread them!
It is Joe who fetches
the 4th and last crate.
I have foot.
If it's shallow,
you can push.
As soon as I have it, jump and let's go.
Maintain balance.
Spencer, still on his team's 3rd crate
.
Hey, get closer to him!
Meanwhile,
his team drifts away from him,
forcing Spencer
to swim back to the boat.
- Joe has the 4th crate.
- Let's go!
They're coming back to the beach!
Come on, forward!
Big advance.
- Keith, do you have one?
- I do not know.
- Can I take it?
- Yeah, after him.
Kimmi, is it okay?
Let's go!
All of them work together
with these funds.
Joe carries only one.
That's how it's done in Survivor!
They will have a big lead
on the puzzle.
Come on, Keith, let's go!
Spencer goes back into the water.
They have plenty of time
to catch up.
- Quick !
- It's good.
- I can not stand it anymore.
- It's good. I love you.
The Violets finally have their 4th crate.
Spencer has to get back on board.
Activate!
Kimmi, Ciera and Wentworth
all have their boxes.
Start stacking them!
Come on, we have to cross the beach!
It's gonna take
a lot of teamwork
to make up for lost time.
These crates are hard to lift.
Place them in the structure.
Jeremy wears one on his shoulders.
It does the work of two people.
You have to place the four crates
before attacking the puzzle.
You are now looking to
repeat no colors
on each side.
If you see the same color,
it's wrong.
It will not work.
Like that !
This one is false.
You have to turn it.
Lots of teamwork
at the Violets.
They progress quickly and well,
they go up.
It's very tight again.
Everyone is on the puzzle.
Turn it!
All it takes
is no repeating color.
I have yellow, green, green, red.
Turn it all the way, Savage!
Yes, one more shot!
- Yes !
- If you think you have it...
- ...say it to me !
- We got it, Jeff!
Nope ! There is a duplicate red!
Oh, almost!
Carry on!
Fishbach thought he had it, but no!
You have to try something else.
I am sorry.
Spin it again!
- Green on your side.
- I have green here.
- Here and here.
- Jeff!
Yes that's it !
You have it ! The reward !
For Keith, Kimmi, Ciera,
Huge victory!
I wanted it so much.
the idea behind Second Chance,
it is in particular to get rid
of what has haunted you.
Does it erase
the memory of the defeat
against Gervase 15 years ago?
Yes, I'm not going to lie,
it's awesome!
Nice reward.
You will be taken to Café Survivor.
Coffee, sandwiches, desserts.
It should be a good respite.
And with so many people at stake,
who knows what impact
this will have on strategy?
Grab your things and go.
Good afternoon !
- Thank you, Jeff!
- Thanks !
Tasha, Jeremy, Savage,
I have nothing for you.
Take your things,
return to camp.
The idea that Joe and the girls
share a reward
is terrifying.
I want to eliminate it. But now they have
the opportunity to influence it.
And that could ruin everything.
- Come on, let's go!
- Damn it !
We were taken to the reward
on these little...
How do you call this ?
Motorcycle stuff.
We arrive at this cool little cafe.
Welcome to Café Tuk-tuk!
Serve yourself !
Oh, my... Kimmi! Looked !
- Oh my God !
I was so excited!
It was my very first reward
with food,
all seasons combined,
so it was really special.
It's nice to get a glimpse
of life outside the game,
just a moment.
- It's incredible.
- That's really nice.
We worked together really well.
That's what they missed, I think.
Rewards
are extremely important.
This is the perfect moment,
in a relaxed atmosphere,
to talk about strategy.
when people relax
and then you submit your idea,
they are more receptive.
I see an opportunity
to brainstorm ideas
and build relationships.
When I was talking about playing last night
I didn't mean
that no one was playing.
But in my 1st season,
there was a close-knit group,
of which I was a part,
and I thought I could
make a move afterwards.
But my numbers have shrunk.
At this point, I have nothing to lose.
So I fish.
I cast the line
and wait for it to bite,
hoping someone
wants to play the same game as me.
And I'll tell you.
These four
will not separate.
I promise you.
As long as there are enough of us,
it might be time to act.
I'm with the Bayons.
I proved my loyalty to them,
they know that I am with them.
But Ciera is right.
I know they are welded.
I know that at some point
they won't want me anymore.
Jeremy and Stephen are smart.
Stephen will give it a shot,
within 2 or 3 votes.
He knows the numbers,
he knows his game. Believe me.
Loyalty has its limits.
Myself,
I will not always be loyal.
It is only
to be sure to act at the right time,
with the right people.
What are these things called?
Rickshaws? No.
- Tuk-tuks.
- To-tos, ouais.
I'll take a look.
I will see. I had a Trail 70.
No drunk driving!
Let's see if I can start it.
A gear is engaged, I believe.
Don't break it!
Look at it there!
We will see Keith, in ten years,
retired, on the beach,
and this is what he will do!
I need passengers!
We don't have any beaches
in Louisiana to drive on.
So this is a unique opportunity.
Here I am,
driving a tuk-tuk,
on a beach, in Cambodia.
With my friends.
To drive them around like a taxi.
Let's see if this beauty
is all-terrain!
Now I'm going to pass
my Cambodian driver's license!
It would be nice.
Easy taxi home!
Call, I'll come get you!
I can't get over it.
I'm depressed there.
Move on !
I don't know why it affects me so much.
Sorry to be...
A squealing baby!
Typically, in Survivor,
I think to myself:
no matter the reward.
But miss it, today,
miss the food,
miss the opportunity to bond,
miss the opportunity
to replenish your energy,
it really got me down.
The reward, it helps,
it's super nice, then it's over.
It's that I also partly
lost my season on a reward.
Some of the bonds made there,
I could never catch up with.
- You lost for lack of links?
- Do you think they're getting closer?
In this situation.
I don't know if that's the case usually,
or now.
The people I need to act
on are out there bonding with Joe.
And Joe is the enemy.
It could be terrible for me.
It's my nightmare.
To see it escape me again
because of a stupid
reward trial.
I was thinking.
I don't want to spend days
getting rid of
of all the Ciera and Abi in the world
when there are real threats.
That's not what we're going to do.
So I thought to myself:
if Joe loses, it's time
to get rid of him.
Since day 1,
Stephen has been trying to get Joe out.
I was reluctant,
because I would lose a shield with Joe.
But every time Joe wins,
it enlarges the target
behind him.
So the first time Joe loses,
he could leave.
I don't want
tomorrow to be consecrated...
- Shenanigans.
- And come up with a plan.
I follow you.
If my allies are in,
I'm in.
It all goes back to my loss to JT.
I don't want to be the puppet
we take to the final.
But that means
I take the reins.
I thought if Joe loses,
I could find the voices
to eliminate him by surprise.
It's fusion
in an all-star season,
you have to aim for the strong.
And the low probability
that he anticipates it increases our chances.
This is also my opinion.
He won't see it coming now.
- But...
- Yes, I'm in, but...
Stephen wants Joe out.
He does what it takes to get it.
At each immunity test,
whatever it is,
Joe has a good chance of winning.
It would be foolish not to eliminate him
at the first opportunity.
What's new ?
I wanted to check in with you.
I have a few ideas.
I thought...
If Joe loses,
How about eliminating him by surprise ?
It's a possibility.
There are enough of us for that.
But it should come
by surprise, of course.
Today I heard Stephen
attempt to arrange
Joe's elimination.
These conspiracies,
these lies, these deceptions...
It's disgusting.
Because I have a great alliance with Joe.
I love this guy.
So he's not going anywhere.
I'm going to have to face Stephen.
Let the battle begin!
Stand up company!
What's up, buddy?
- Do you have a minute?
- Yeah.
We have a problem.
Stephen is evil.
He mentions your name.
He said, "Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe!"
It's going to be a big hit
very soon,
as long as he thinks he has
the manpower for it.
This morning, Savage told me
Stephen was after me.
Nothing suprising.
He is intelligent.
And I know I'm dangerous.
I knew it would happen.
But I didn't expect it so soon.
Look me in the eyes.
From the bottom of my heart,
on the lives of my children,
I will never write your name.
At this stage,
I trust Savage.
I think
he has my interests at heart.
But if Stephen has gathered
enough people to take me out,
if I don't win immunity,
I'm finished.
Over here, everyone!
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yes !
First of all, Joe,
I have to take it back.
OK my friend.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will
balance a ball
on a disc held by strings.
Regularly, you will move
your hands back on the rope,
increasing the difficulty.
Yes the tombs bales,
the test is lost.
The last person standing
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be
the eighth person eliminated
and the second member of our jury.
This event
has been contested once.
Keith and Jeremy took part.
Jeremy, were you done...?
- Thank you, Jeff.
- ...Last.
And Keith had won.
An important story
of 2nd chance, then.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Good.
Everyone
is in the first position,
and this test is launched.
Oh my God !
After a few seconds,
Wentworth is eliminated,
immediately followed by Ciera.
That's how quickly
your destiny can change in this game.
You have to be constantly vigilant.
And Kelly Wiglesworth loses her ball.
Jeremy fails
to recover, he is eliminated.
Things go fast in this race.
Kimmi's ball is moving,
can it save her?
Yes, well done.
Abi starts rolling...
Abi fails to recover,
she is eliminated.
More than seven people.
Fishbach is eliminated.
More than six people.
Kimmi's ball is still moving.
As soon as said.
Suddenly, Savage's ball
doesn't stay in place.
He can't control her.
Savage is eliminated.
More than five people.
and Kimmi.
This first round
will last ten minutes.
Then we will back up on the rope
and it will become more difficult.
ELAPSED TIME:
10 Minutes
Everyone moved
to second position.
Your hands are now
further back on the rope.
Which makes things
much more difficult.
We'll stay like this for ten minutes
before stepping back further.
Kimmi is right on the edge.
A new beautiful recovery,
and one more.
Kimmi holds her own
and still succeed.
Luck turns,
Kimmi loses her ball.
More than four people.
Tasha loses her ball and is eliminated.
More than three people.
Three men.
Joe and Spencer.
Keith won the first time,
he would love to put that back on.
Joe and Spencer
would like to take the win.
All three,
keep it up, because it works.
ELAPSED TIME:
20 Minutes
Well, everybody's in position,
hands at the end of the rope.
We can't go any further.
Keith hopes to retain his title.
Joe and Spencer
hope to whisper it to him.
Nothing like wearing this necklace
on arriving at the council.
A little movement in Keith.
But a nice recovery.
A little movement in Joe.
Spencer is eliminated,
no immunity for him.
More than two people.
It's Keith
against Joe,
for immunity.
We'll stay at this section for
another ten minutes.
If you survive it,
we'll add a 2nd ball.
ELAPSED TIME:
30 Minutes
Keith and Joe each have two bullets
on their discs.
Unlimited time in this round.
We continue until the end.
A little movement
in Keith, now.
If it was hard with a ball,
with two, it's definitely
more than twice as hard.
If these balls go
in opposite directions,
it went badly.
You cannot afford
any movement.
Keith won it,
at the same stage,
the first time, in Blood vs. Water.
Joe's balls
start moving.
A little movement in Keith.
A bit of wind.
Joe's balls
move a little more.
The wind begins to pick up,
causing Joe's balls to move.
He stabilizes once more.
Joe's balls
start moving.
Splendid recovery.
The balls are moving again.
Both are moving now.
Movement at Keith.
Keith loses his ball!
Joe wins
his second immunity test!
Well done, Keith!
Joe, come here!
Well done, Joe!
For the second time, immunity.
Only you have worn this necklace.
Joe, safe at council tonight.
As for you others,
after 21 days,
someone will leave tonight.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council. Congratulation.
Thank god I won immunity.
I know my name
has been quoted extensively.
So let Stephen go,
because he's the one who mentioned my name.
We have to take it out.
- Well done, Joe!
- Congratulations, Joe!
You were amazing
with both balls!
I couldn't
let Keith fight me.
You rocked, man!
Not ripped enough.
- Big Joe again.
-Big Joe!
I'm really frustrated.
I've been working to eliminate Joe
since day 1.
And once again,
he gains that damn immunity.
It's like Moby Dick.
Joe is my white whale.
And I am Ahab,
embarked on my mad , single
-minded quest to eliminate Joe,
and it keeps slipping away from me.
What do you have in mind?
Stephen has to go.
He is really dangerous.
I'll talk to Jeremy, so...
And I think
two more are up for it.
For sure.
OK. You hold me informed ?
Eliminating Stephen
would be a pretty big blow.
But for me, it's pretty simple.
Stephen mentioned my name.
So we have to get rid of him.
And I'm going to use
the three girls at the bottom of the ladder to do this.
It's an important vote.
but there is a cool thing to do.
Savage wants Stephen out.
Today ?! No kidding !
And it's great.
- It's fantastic.
- Lord, you are a real demon!
- Yes.
Ciera, Abi and I
are at the bottom of the ladder.
I thought I was completely screwed.
And all of a sudden, Joe says to me:
"We're going to take Fishbach out by surprise."
I went, "Fantastic! I love it!"
I write this name.
- Come what may ?
- Yes.
So that's what I will do. Fish.
It is enormous.
And that's true. I have an idol.
But I don't want to use it so soon
if I can avoid it.
- This has to stay between us.
- Wooden cross, iron cross.
Fishbach. Completely by surprise.
Joe said
he would write "Fish" tonight.
- Wigles said the same thing.
- Very well, I vote Fishbach.
At this point, I'm okay
as long as it's not you or me.
- I'll be silent as a grave.
- Me too.
Good job.
Stephen is really dangerous.
He still pretends to
be all in with the Bayon
and all that, but not at all.
I know he's up to something big.
We have to separate from him.
- What's new ?
Do we agree
or are we still talking?
It's Fishbach.
- Is that the plan?!
- Yeah.
Stephen brings up the name Joe.
He is dangerous.
Now he wants to take Stephen out,
as he is trying to take out Joe.
But that would be bad for me.
Stephen has been with me for 20 days.
We learned to trust each other.
I want Stephen
to accompany me far in this game.
'Cause when the big guys
start killing each other,
I want to have all the ammunition.
He prides himself on being
Survivor's greatest strategist.
I know, I understand you 100%.
But here's the thing.
I don't want to
let these girls go on.
I tell myself...
We know what he wants to do.
And he won't be
able to do it
- without our cooperation.
- True.
I tell myself that we must leave Wentworth
or Ciera.
We get another one out,
and then we can start...
Degrease on our side.
Your arguments are solid.
I will follow the group.
As a lawyer,
I pleaded my case.
I'm used to getting
what I want. But not there.
I'm disappointed,
but Jeremy is not wrong.
These two girls are dangerous.
We just have to determine
which will leave tonight.
What's going on ?
It runs all over the place.
We don't trust Stephen.
But we don't wanna take it out
and create a division so soon.
Damn it !
It makes me nervous.
I was saying to myself.
It will be Stephen,
I'll just reconfirm
with everyone."
But apparently,
Stephen has more connections
than I thought.
What is being said?
No good.
No Stephen?
Savage was in.
Someone has deeper ties to Fishbach.
Exactly.
So who is it, Wentworth or me?
It's me, huh?
I do not know yet.
Wait a minute, we're going to eliminate Fishbach.
The next moment,
the plan falls apart.
Joe has no balls.
He is dead to me.
But the good thing about the council
is that nothing is certain until the end.
I'm so sick
of their bogus plans.
So who are you voting for?
Would it make a difference to you,
whether it's Fishbach or Savage?
We should all vote
for the same person.
- I say the same.
- Let's decide.
I urged people
to wake up and play,
but I play with people
who don't want to act.
So at this point,
I fear for my life.
I'm hoping for a miracle on the council,
ideally.
Here is now
the first member of the jury.
Kass, eliminated at the last council.
Let's pick up where we left off
at the last tip, Ciera.
You thought
people weren't playing.
Has this theme continued
beyond consulting?
Yes. Nothing has changed.
Nobody fights
for their place at the top.
It's frustrating.
I will say it clearly.
Four people control the game.
Everything is here.
So we're going to leave
one after the other,
and that's all.
But if they are only four,
that leaves eight more people
who should be able to swallow them.
We could believe it.
But no one wants to act.
Ciera, if you want
people to take action, do it!
Do you know who the four are?
Yes, Jeff.
The four are: Jeremy,
Stephen or Joe.
- Who is it ?
- You or me, apparently.
Jeremy, there's
a recurring group of names,
systematically referred
to as being the core.
And you are.
Yes, but she claims
that 4 people have control,
and she pulled out five names.
They don't even know
who's in control.
But, Joe,
it doesn't matter if something
is true or not.
Only what people believe matters.
Perception is truth.
So the only security guarantee
in this game,
this is it.
Savage, you were also quoted
as a core member.
What does it do,
to hear his name mentioned?
Yes, we are a handful who
often talk,
we respect each other.
And there are a few other people
on the same level as us.
We decide as a group.
- Ciera.
- Who can swallow that?!
In an alliance, someone
is at the top and someone is at the bottom.
Clearly there are people
playing here.
They play well enough to be
able to say:
"We are allies, all equal.",
and let everyone believe it!
They just have more power.
I'm frustrated with those
who can't see
and hear what they say,
say to themselves that they are not at the top,
but do not act.
It's time to wake up!
We don't just
have former players,
but people who have had time
to think about how to react
in such and such a situation.
So what Ciera says
might be true.
What Ciera says
is probably true.
With former players
maybe they are just waiting
someone change sides,
or that an idol is played.
We haven't seen any.
Spencer, let's talk about idols.
The two times
we brought them up in the council,
it was as if no
one had been looking for them.
Is this still the case ?
I believe most people think
either there are no idols
or they have been found
and waiting to be played.
Savage, what do you think
of the call to make a big hit
launched by Ciera?
It's fascinating.
I think she can do that,
for she is not in the covenant,
but at the bottom of the ladder.
If she was in the place
of such and such another,
she wouldn't say that.
You act like I want
something crazy to happen.
I'm not asking for anything weird,
but that you defend
your place in the game.
I don't find it that big.
For me, there is no
bottom of the scale...
Obviously !
The way it plays out this season
differs from the previous 30 seasons,
which we have all studied and watched.
We mixed up
a dozen times,
we all play hard
there is no
usual hierarchy.
It's different.
But some things
will never change.
In an alliance, someone
is at the top and someone is at the bottom.
Some of you know you're
not in the foursome
and do nothing to fix it.
That's what frustrates me.
Wentworth,
what's going to happen tonight?
Abi, Ciera and I
are clearly at the bottom of the scale.
So it looks like the easy vote
would be one of us. But...
Someone
approached me today
and told me he wanted to take action.
And not the other way around.
So you're saying
they're not so tight-knit,
- because you were approached.
- Exactly.
It's not me at the bottom of the ladder
trying to make a big move.
They came to see me for this purpose.
Why not reveal who,
if you are really
at the bottom of the scale
and desperate?
What if I'm here tomorrow,
having to collaborate with?
Damn it, Joe, it's hard!
Wherever you look,
there is an obstacle!
It's like playing chess
without knowing which piece is which.
It's trying,
that's exciting.
I expected no less.
Good.
Let's see what it will give.
It's time to vote.
Wiglesworth, over.
I would have tried the same thing
if I were in your place.
Fortunately, I am not.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
You know what, Jeff?
I may be all the way down,
but not ready to go.
Oh my God !
It's not true !
- You did not know ?
- Nope !
- I had no idea.
- This is my favorite moment!
Oh my God !
I like this !
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Votes against Wentworth
will not count.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Wentworth. It won't count.
It's funny.
It won't count.
Wentworth.
Yeah, my girl!
Unbelievable.
Eighth person eliminated
and second member of the jury...
Savage.
Two is enough.
Bring me your torch.
Unbelievable.
Shit.
I am loyal to my allies.
I like you.
- Wow !
- Savage,
the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
You have reached the jury!
Oh ! You too!
This evening, the dominant question
was to know
when someone was going to make
a big hit.
Turns out it was tonight.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Relecture: Creature, flosm92
Synchro: Creature
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
We have to find that idol.
All are looking
for an advantage in the game.
I do not know where he is.
But what they don't know
it's just in front of them.
I will give you the opportunity
to change your situation.
The first person to touch their buoy
gains an advantage.
It's... mind-boggling.
No one saw it coming.
Except Wentworth, but...
Devil take me!
I did things
that I hadn't done
12 years ago.
I proved, at least I believe it,
that I could compete
with incredible Survivors.
I played pretty well
strategically.
Except two minutes ago.
I won't lie,
it's heartbreaking.