translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
You will have a 2nd chance!
After being chosen
by America,
20 former players
flew to Cambodia.
They have a second chance
to change the way
they played the 1st time
and finish what they started.
Welcome to
Survivor: Cambodia, Second Chance!
I'm here to make a million,
and when it's over,
I'll pray for forgiveness.
In the Ta Keo tribe...
Have you seen my bag?
My bracelet is in it.
...Abi was fighting against herself.
It's so hard
not to bare your fangs!
- My bracelet!
- Is that Peih-Gee's bag?
But the real battle
was between two styles of play:
the old school
and the new school.
The new school swore
by strategy.
I wanted to board
the people that interest me
and lock the stuff.
The old school was
all about relationships and survival.
We don't do more
"old school Survivor" than I do!
And veteran Varner
found himself stuck in between.
No matter who takes me
into the woods, I say "yes".
In the Bayon tribe,
the strong men bonded.
Everything is fine.
But Stephen couldn't find his place
and his tribe suspected him
to look for an idol.
I believe he is "looking for an idol".
Oh really ?
In an unprecedented twist,
Kelley found a
hidden idol at the immunity trial.
Joe is on the key!
But it was Joe who found success.
Bayon wins immunity!
And it only got worse for Ta Keo.
We're off to the board...
immediately.
At the council,
Varner had to choose sides.
It's my second chance.
I don't want to spoil it.
In the end, Abi had four votes...
First person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
...but it was Vytas
who was eliminated...
The tribe has spoken.
...leaving Terry,
Wiglesworth
and Woo at the bottom.
Your second chance
can end at any time.
And as you came to the council,
fire, in the form of flint,
will be waiting for you at the camp.
There are 19 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The advice was overwhelming.
I didn't
think Varner would switch sides.
It sucks to be at the bottom of the ladder.
I didn't want to start
this 2nd chance like this.
My alliance needs to pull itself together.
Shirin and Spencer set the tone,
forming alliances and plotting.
- I put that there?
- Yeah, go ahead.
We have to defend ourselves.
Or we're screwed.
I'll go get some wood.
Yesterday, we went directly
from the test to the advice.
I have to find the time
to read my idol,
which I treasure.
I don't even know what she looks like
or what the message says.
My idol.
Oui !
This Second Chance season
is already crazy.
I'm really happy
to have some security.
It's splendid.
I'm really excited!
Oh my God !
Yes !
What a great day!
Play a 2nd time
get a 2nd chance...
I want to do everything
I didn't do the first time.
I want to be aggressive,
to be a real player.
It's really important.
It's a second chance.
Go hard or get out.
Oui !
We have a good group, you know?
I would like to decide
who is next.
One of the three, right?
It's okay with me.
After Vytas left,
the impression was
that the new school
had won over the old woman
in the first vote.
Terry, Wiglesworth and Woo
missed the mark.
I betrayed them yesterday.
I hope that shows you
my loyalty.
- Sure.
- Absolutely.
We are nine in this tribe.
With Abi, we are five.
We have nothing to worry about.
Spencer and Shirin
feel comfortable.
But maybe they shouldn't.
I'm serious !
My plan, in eliminating Vytas,
was to show old school
that they have to start playing,
and set the tone
to eliminate Shirin and Spencer.
They play way too deep,
strategically speaking.
I want to take one of them out
of the equation.
I didn't want Abi to leave.
She was the wrong choice.
His time has not come.
Abi, it's easy.
This game is moving like lightning.
And these threats...
must disappear.
It can't just be a name
like that, that's old school.
It's a new day.
Don't look like
you don't know what you're doing.
Yesterday's vote was a revelation.
Shake your ass and play!
We are not in 2001.
I want to eliminate Spencer.
Ou Shirin.
These two are playing.
They have to go.
If I have to go to the end,
it will be with the elders.
Not with them.
Leaving the board
I felt terrible.
But Varner started with a bang
and is playing hard.
Survivor has changed.
My 2nd chance includes Terry Deitz
playing a social game.
Otherwise, I'll be cleared.
- You understand me ?
- Yes. We're going to do that.
I'm looking for a spy hideout!
Nice idea!
I can do anything if I put my mind to it.
I want to have fun here,
I want to do stuff.
Nobody likes to sleep
on bamboos, so I said:
"Let's make hammocks!"
Look at this brave Steve!
Last time,
I was by far the biggest threat.
So in this season
It's nice
to be the one who provides a service.
It is not bad at all !
I want people to need
and want my presence.
The island of paradise!
Devil, yes!
Take a big one,
and then we'll share the little ones.
Cool !
- You don't want another one, sure?
- Not now.
Unbelievable.
Joe always has ideas.
Like, "What to build now?"
"What great new thing
to build to improve Survivor?"
It's crazy
to be in a tribe with Joe,
it's the MacGyver of Survivor.
He's still making a hammock
or go fishing.
We have fish!
There's shrimp on the barbeuc!
Joe is too great
for his own good.
He is too "young prodigy",
"magnificent threat".
Joe is really good at survival.
Joe is the guy
who is perfect at the beginning,
wins all the trials,
build the shelter,
and then you slit his throat
just before the merger.
- You're fine, huh?
- I'm fine.
But I am lucid.
I am not finished.
On the council, I had four votes.
If I was
the one I was
in Survivor Philippines,
I would have exploded.
But I did not do it.
I'm working on it.
I want to change.
I'm trying to act like the new Abi
I want to be.
How did you make the fireplace,
in China, on the fire?
Basically, it protected him
from the wind all around.
- It's easy to maintain...
- So, what's up, Peih-Gee?
- What ?
- What's new ?
A chimney is built
for the fire.
OK.
Seriously, you...
- Seriously, I what?
- Relax.
Seriously,
we're building a fireplace.
Abi is the queen of the movies.
Having to trust
someone like that
to protect my interests
was the scariest thing I had to do in Survivor.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, of course, everything is fine.
I'm just trying
to extend this connection,
this friendship
that grows between us.
I feel like I'm well placed
but Abi is a permanent risk.
She will always be that weight
that must be dragged.
Do I interfere,
so they change the subject?
Why not ?
Let me do.
I will bore them.
Abi is there
to start arguments.
It's carcinogenic to the tribe.
And fatally carcinogenic
to a wedding ring.
Here it is.
Stop! What's new ?
- I offered it to you, you didn't come.
- No, I want to participate in the debate.
Abi is a telenovela
on its own,
you can turn it on and watch
it at any time.
And by tapping on it, you get
various levels of entertainment.
What are all these whispers?
There are things going on
that you don't need to know about.
- Oh yeah ?
- Oh yeah.
I see in Abi someone
that everyone hates,
so someone i can beat.
She is the perfect tool
to help me win
a million dollars.
Follow me all day
and maybe you'll know more.
But you won't be able to
run that fast.
Parfait.
Oh my God ! I enjoy!
Why eat when you have Abi?
In my box, in Chicago...
We had Playboy Enterprises
as a client.
When I met my wife
and she came to my office,
there were Playboys everywhere.
How did you meet her?
My wife
was a top model in South Africa,
and a law student.
She won a beauty contest
whose prize was a trip around the world.
She stopped in America
to see my roommate.
They were friends.
I come back from a trial, in a suit,
and there's the prettiest brunette
I've ever seen,
my house.
I almost fainted.
We could have cut
the chemistry between us with a knife,
across the room. Unbelievable.
Then
she went to California,
then she came back, and...
She is everything for me.
Oh, goodness!
- So she came back.
- She came back.
And we were...
married...
three months later.
- It's awesome.
- Great.
Great story.
In my first season,
the other contestants were horrible.
This time some are great.
If they can make me
a better person
and a better player, I take.
It's so cute.
You have to have
feelings in this game.
I made the mistake, the first time,
to consider that everyone
would put feelings aside,
we would play poker
and someone would win.
I realized that not everyone
behaves like that here.
We are real people.
And I'll be a real person,
all the way.
I try to have fun
and think professionally.
And for Savage to come up with this story
about his wife...
It affects you, it makes you think.
My wife is pregnant,
and I want to see his belly,
to be there to see him grow.
Most...
I won't tell anyone.
I'm exposed enough already.
They'll come after me
as a physical threat.
If in addition
my wife is pregnant,
no one will go through with me.
But I have to take it upon myself.
Val knows how much this means to me.
And for her.
I'm doing this again for her.
Where is Jeremy?
Pardon ?
Should we be worried
about his disappearance?
You don't think
he's looking for idols, do you?
The thing, with Stephen,
it's that he first thinks
Jeremy is looking for an idol.
Rather than
"Jeremy has a wonderful family,
my story may have affected him
and he needed to isolate himself."
It shows me that Fishbach
is in the game 24 hours a day.
He thinks only of this idol,
only the game counts.
No emotion.
Your story, man,
about your wife...
Did that stir you too?
I cried a bit.
It's good, it has to come out.
Stephen was asking
if you were looking for an idol.
He came to tell you that?
It shows what he has in mind.
Fishbach is deprived
some of the things
that mean the most to me
and my tribe.
Morals, values,
loyalty, dignity, courage.
Whether I like it or not,
its time here,
if it depends on me, will be limited.
Dealing with all this craziness...
- Again and again and again...
- Abi?
You had to
babysit, poor thing!
I am...
I railed against her
all day, you have no idea.
I asked him to put
these seeds in the rice,
and she's like, "I have a bad back.
J'arrête, j'ai mal au dos."
Elle était posée dans l'abri, à...
J'ai tout entendu.
Pourquoi tu ne me l'as pas dit ?
Désolée que tu ne m'aimes pas,
que je t'agace
et que tu ne me supportes pas.
Je n'y peux rien...
Je discute avec Peih-Gee,
Abi la surprend, se pointe,
et ça dégénère
en engueulade.
Abi, tu sais bien
que tu te disputes beaucoup.
Avec qui ?
Tu disais à tout le monde
croire que j'avais volé ton bracelet.
Tu parlais dans mon dos.
Comment suis-je censée le prendre ?
- Je ne parlais pas dans ton dos.
- Plusieurs personnes me l'ont dit.
Mets-toi à ma place.
Comment te sentirais-tu
si ton nom sortait 4 fois ?
Abi talks about the votes against her
for the umpteenth time.
I was starting to feel bad,
so I left.
It was very embarrassing.
Painful to watch.
So maybe we got
off on the wrong foot.
Yes, I guess.
See, that's it, you do that,
"Oh, whatever..."
What do you want me to tell you ?
You have already made your decision.
- What can I say ?
- I can work with anyone.
Our friendship is not linked
to a question of numbers.
Of course I was a little embarrassed
of being caught
talking about someone behind her back.
But everyone is fed up with her.
She has no friends on this island.
How are you ?
It feels good.
The people I thought I was allied with
are laughing at me,
and Shirin did not support me.
And I wanted to work with her
because she found that no
one supported her in her season.
I feel really weird here.
It sucks and it hurts.
And I feel alone.
And I said, "Calm down."
Abi goes to the beach.
There are eight of us in the shelter.
And we laugh at her,
his own allies!
And no one supported her.
She's annoying,
and emotionally, it's a disaster.
But there is another human being,
there, struggling.
It is not normal.
I expected more,
especially from Shirin.
You know, Shirin and Spencer
are only there for themselves.
I felt like
they weren't supporting me.
So I'm pretty open to...
anything that can protect me.
It started
to stick well between her and me.
Not only personally,
because we created a bond,
but strategically
during the discussion.
Maybe it's just me,
and the "old school" side,
but if we move forward together,
I will protect you.
The opportunity arose
of my compassion for someone.
I'm laying here,
all alone.
Who came to talk to me?
Toi.
Jeff lit a fire under my butt.
I knew I had to play a social game.
I was a little slow on start-up,
but it's starting to take shape.
- Did you talk well with Terry?
- Yes.
- He's a good guy, huh?
I plan to join him.
Me too.
I want you to stay.
I find you fabulous.
Thanks a lot.
I like your little
mood swings. It excites me.
What sweet music to my ears!
After my allies made me
feel like a fool,
now i feel so good
that people
really want to work with me.
And that they actually find me...
kidding.
We vote en bloc,
and we take out Spencer or Shirin.
I will recruit Terry, Kelley,
Woo, you and me, that's five.
- Good.
- That's a majority.
And those who turned their back on you...
It will be the big day for them!
OK.
Bargain ?
Terry saw the opening
and rushed into it.
My old allies will regret
for not coming to me
when I needed it most.
Over here, everyone!
Bayon, discover
the new Ta Keo tribe.
Vytas, eliminated on the first board.
Oh my God !
Good. Ready for
today's immunity test?
- Oh yeah !
- Yes !
Today the two tribes
will pass through a series of pyramids
while carrying spools of rope.
With this rope,
you will then bring back
a heavy crate on arrival.
Two team members will then use
the pieces that are there
to solve a puzzle.
The first tribe to finish...
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers will go to the board
where someone will be the 2nd person
eliminated from Second Chance.
Plus, you're playing
for a reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes sir !
A Survivor Toolkit,
pretty cool.
Hammer, axe,
chisels, saw,
bamboo nails, rope,
and as a bonus,
on the camp when you return,
materials that will
greatly improve your shelter.
It should improve your sleep
and protect you from the rain.
Big reward.
Bayon, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Who will it be?
- Ciera.
- Ciera won't participate.
One more thing.
I forgot to get the idol!
Ciera.
A 2nd chance for me
to do this properly.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
- Ciera, take a seat on the bench.
- OK.
The others, one minute
to get organized and here we go.
Let's go. For immunity
and reward,
Survivors, ready?
Go !
You must cross this first wall.
Go on !
Cheer ! Help each other!
Bayon flies over the obstacle.
Ta Keo takes longer.
Slipping on this wood
will leave traces!
Bayon took the lead.
On the 2nd wall, everyone, forward!
This one will take more effort.
Help each other! Cheer !
- Its good.
- Go on !
At each stage,
you have to wait for everyone.
It's not good for the skin!
Big fall for Varner!
Go ahead, Bayon!
Go ahead, Ta Keo!
Bravo !
Climb on me.
This will be the most difficult wall.
It will require a lot
of teamwork.
Use rope if necessary.
lots of skin
remained on this wood.
That's why you're here.
For a 2nd chance in this game.
Monica loses more skin.
It will leave wounds,
in addition to some big falls.
Very big fall of Savage!
Go ! Go !
Four people on the crate,
the other five on the carpet.
Come on !
Give it your all, you're in on it!
You have to tie these strings together.
With the rope,
you will pull the crate.
Perfect equality for the moment.
Let's go, the two tribes shoot.
Give it all!
This box is very heavy.
Legs now!
Spencer, Woo,
Deitz and Varner
are stuck.
Give it all!
Bayon has arrived!
To the puzzle team!
All the others, on the carpet!
It's good, it's good! Go on !
Ta Keo is very late.
Kass and Kimmy
are on the puzzle for Bayon.
That's it !
Onward, puzzle team!
Big lead for Kimmy and Kass.
But are they on the right track?
If correct, each piece
will be connected to the next.
Parfait.
Kelly Wentworth
and the Peih-Gee s'attant au puzzle.
Can they make up
for lost time on checkout?
immunity
and a big in-game reward.
Anyone want to retire?
You go-y !
Spencer gets involved.
He hopes to make a difference.
Can he pick up the pace?
- Can he close the gap?
- Its good !
The one that is already there,
with the one on the right.
Too much communication
can create chaos and confusion.
- Nope ! The following !
- Not here !
The following !
All of the Ta Keo
are screaming at Spencer and Peih-Gee.
Joe will replace Kimmy.
He thinks he knows what to do.
Jeremy replaces Kass.
He had time to study it.
Want me to go?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- It's Shirin and Spencer now.
Shirin takes orders
and moves pieces.
No stop !
Oh, my God, I can't do it!
Panic sets in.
It's a nightmare.
I'm going to faint.
There is only one way
to solve this puzzle.
So everything lines up.
The drawing will flow
from one piece to the next.
If it doesn't follow,
it's wrong.
Spencer begins to move forward,
with a new idea.
Is he right ?
Go on ! Go on !
Spencer and Shirin keep
making changes.
Yes Spencer! Yes !
It would be a spectacular comeback
for Ta Keo.
Joe moves pieces now.
He has his idea about their position.
Both tribes
move pieces very fast
and try to come to a conclusion.
But are they right this time?
This here! This here! Yes !
It's the final sprint!
Put it here!
- Its good !
- Yes ! Yes !
The Ta Keos think they have it.
It is not fair !
Jeff !
The Bayons think they have it.
Bayon is right!
Immunity and reward
for Bayon,
who returns Ta Keo to the council!
Bayon!
Bayon, congratulations,
immunity again!
No advice tonight, Bayon.
No one will leave your tribe.
Plus, a nice reward.
Come get it, have a good night!
- Thank you, Jeff.
- I needed a saw.
Ta Keo, I did for you
just a date with me,
tonight, at the council,
where someone will be
the 2nd person eliminated
from Second Chance.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
This event was a nightmare,
and we lost.
But, I hadn't realized it
until now:
Spencer and Shirin had
their destiny in their hands, and they lost it.
Now, one of the two
is going to leave tonight.
What a fair return of things!
- Good effort, friends.
- Exhausting!
Sorry for the end,
but you made it happen.
Do not worry.
- It was rough.
- Everyone did their best.
It's been two events
where we get our ass kicked.
I'm happy
to control the game with Shirin.
I rely on her more
than anyone here.
My old experience of Survivor,
drooling at the bottom of the ladder,
without having anyone to play with
and who to trust, is far behind.
- Did you get rubbed in the sand?
- Nope.
- Do it !
- You'll feel much better!
- Alright, if you want.
- Yeah.
I'll rub you, if you want.
My trick is to eliminate
threats as soon as possible.
Spencer is a huge
strategic threat.
He's the smartest young man
I've ever met.
Shirin is the same,
plus she's sensitive,
she talks to you like you're
best friends, she's a saleswoman.
They are two heads
of the same serpent.
So it doesn't matter which one we cut.
Would you vote
for Shirin or Spencer?
To end it.
You know what ?
I will follow the majority.
I would prefer to eliminate Abi-Maria,
but for now,
I will follow the majority,
which appears to be everyone
except Shirin and Spencer.
They are both dangerous.
I wouldn't want to be
on the wrong side of the vote.
I'll tell you.
This tribe...
It's the mess.
The total mess!
Abi is devastated.
That Shirin
didn't support her last night.
Terry Deitz stayed
with her all night, like a father.
When she woke up, she was
totally loyal to him.
So where are we?
- Toi, Peih-Gee, Wigs, Deitz, Woo ...
- Tout le monde sauf Shirin ...
- OK.
- ...and Spencer.
- Yeah.
- It's finish.
- If you're up for it.
- I'm.
- Don't go straight into the woods!
- But no.
You won't see me talking
to Shirin today.
Promis.
It's very hard for me,
to consider voting
for Shirin or Spencer.
They are my original allies.
Alas, things changed
in the space of 24 hours.
I find myself
in another covenant,
which I don't necessarily like,
but I have to go with the flow.
And so, Shirin and Spencer
are in deep shit.
Even if we lost the race,
I see the future with optimism,
car on a moi, Spencer,
Kelley, Jeff Varner...
But I want to make sure
Abi still feels good.
It always goes
in all directions.
- How do you feel today ?
- Good.
I feel good today.
I'm sorry about last night.
- Sorry for not supporting you.
- I regret.
'Cause I'm loyal
and if I give my word
to a covenant,
it's 100%.
I expected one of you to
come see me.
Who came ? Terri.
Terry came to spend
two hours with me.
Two o'clock.
I'm sorry.
I tried, Shirin. I tried.
I tried to support you,
but you know what?
If you fuck me, you're dead.
You left me there,
all alone.
Abi, I gave you my word,
I voted with you.
What more can I do?
I was crying in front of you.
We got off on my head.
I was like,
"That's really weird."
Varner and Kelley are in on it.
They want to eliminate you
and Spencer.
Are we still together?
No. It's not my type.
Spencer and I
were in the majority
qui a sorti Vytas.
We should have the wind in our sails,
be happy...
But, I don't know how,
we find ourselves in the minority.
We are fucked.
OK. Can you explain?
In a nutshell:
Varner and Abi will vote
with the old school.
For the moment, I oscillate
between frustration and exasperation.
Until a minute ago,
everything was fine for me.
And now
my #1 priority is to protect myself.
My priority must be
to last three more days.
Woo, I want to talk to you.
This is what happens to you.
If you stick with the old school,
they will keep you for the trials.
But you will be at the bottom of the ladder.
And if by chance you reach fusion,
you will be the most dangerous,
and you will jump at the first opportunity.
All of a sudden, Spencer and Shirin
have the nerve to think
that I'm going to betray my tribe
and join them.
Hey, sorry! The majority commands.
- Not that I don't trust.
- You do not know me...
But this is the first time
you've spoken to me.
I say.
I always keep my word.
I am sick
at the thought that I could leave
and that my only option
is to vote for Spencer.
I don't want to vote for Spencer.
I will accept any deal.
It's just that it amazes me
that not once
have you taken me aside.
And now
you come to ask me for a vote.
I'll just answer you...
Never.
My situation continues to darken.
It was to be my 2nd chance,
I wanted a different experience.
But I'm hard taken back
to my first experience,
where everything starts very well
then suddenly collapses
before my eyes.
Everyone here, except for Shirin and me,
is in the majority, against us.
Shirin is my only strong ally.
And now
I'm afraid I have no other choice
than screwing up the only person
I wanted to play with.
So, Varner, how's the vibe
in the tribe right now?
We are all exhausted.
This day cost us a lot.
This ordeal was intense.
Spencer.
It's one thing to want to play again.
But once here
you remember:
"Oh, yeah! We bite!"
Yes. There is a form of amnesia,
regardless of the time elapsed
since the 1st participation.
Then you come back, and you 're like,
"No, that sucks!
We're going to taste!"
Shirin, Spencer's comments
are interesting.
We have a great memory of Survivor,
until we come back.
I don't have such good memories of it.
I had it the first time.
Et...
It's starting to happen again.
Déjà ?
Yeah, already.
Tell me about it.
There were arguments.
Some people
no longer trust me.
I believe I am at the bottom of the scale.
And I hope I can fight
and find my place.
Kelley, what is Shirin talking about?
Was there a big fight?
There was a disagreement
between Abi and Peih-Gee.
I believe this is
what Shirin is talking about.
So, Abi, what was it?
I was sitting on the beach,
and Peih-Gee
and Shirin were talking about me.
I felt betrayed,
in a way, because we were allies.
And I'm very gracious
to Terry.
He is the only one
to have rescued me
when I felt very alone,
when I thought I would be unanimously eliminated
tonight.
Shirin, that's almost verbatim
what you said in your season.
You said of Mike
that he was the only one to rescue you.
Abi said it about Terry.
But in this case, it was you
who hurt him.
It's true, I should have supported her,
gone to see her right away.
I didn't, and...
The game changes very quickly.
- Deitz, you nod.
- Yeah.
Because I was at the bottom of the ladder
two days ago.
And because of this story,
Abi ended up on the beach,
and we developed a bond.
It wasn't
just a strategy thing,
just to develop relationships,
and a lot of good has come from that.
So much so that I don't think I'm
at the bottom of the ladder anymore.
spencer. Shirin thinks of herself
as the very bottom of the ladder.
Is it the consensus
she has to worry about?
Well yes.
No need to beat around the bush.
I am also worried.
Why would you be targeted tonight?
There are several reasons,
but among other things,
because I talk too much about strategy
and not enough to get
to know these people.
Jeff, Shirin et Spencer
are they right to be concerned?
Have you narrowed the choice down
to these two?
Oui.
- Spencer, it's confirmed.
- 100 %.
No need to speak in code.
It will be one of us tonight.
But know it,
Wiglesworth, Terry, Peih-Gee,
Jeff, Abi, Woo et Kelley,
if I'm here tomorrow,
this change will happen.
It's not :
"I create an alliance here
and another there."
It's about creating human connections,
forming relationships
who have basics.
That's what I will do now.
OK ? And I mean it.
It's incredible.
The two people in danger,
Shirin and Spencer,
live very similar stories
to their first times.
Spencer, you had almost
the same speech in your season,
"I will work with whoever wants to,
give me a chance."
And Shirin, you were
at the center of a controversy,
excluded on one side or the other.
What do you think, Shirin?
What lesson to take away from this,
about the ability to change,
or on the situations
in which we put ourselves
again and again ?
Change is difficult.
It's a second chance
to correct the situation.
That doesn't mean we're going to change
overnight.
I made real mistakes.
If I leave tonight
it's my fault.
I'm responsible.
If I don't leave tonight,
if I stay,
it will be a 3rd chance.
It only happens once.
Good. It's time to vote.
Wiglesworth, over.
I know you write my name too.
I have nothing negative
to say about you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote.
Spencer.
Shirin.
Three Shirin votes.
Spencer.
spencer.
Three votes Spencer,
three votes Shirin.
spencer.
Four votes Spencer,
three votes Shirin.
Shirin.
New equality.
Four votes Shirin,
four votes Spencer,
one vote remains.
Second person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance...
Shirin.
Bring me your torch.
Make them drool!
Shirin, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
I was sincere. Thank you.
This season
offer a 2nd chance
to change what didn't work
the first time.
But if you don't change,
history is bound to repeat itself.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Team Survivor ST
http://survivor-st.forumgratuit.org/
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro : Lény
Synchro version HD : aymeric000
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
In a season
where adaptation is key...
If you are unable to change,
it's death.
...everyone has
to be ready for change.
Throw away your bandanas.
We change the tribes.
Of two tribes...
to three tribes.
Oh my God !
I failed to take
my second chance.
I struggled to change
key aspects to make it work.
I was in a very good position
until I freak out
and destroy my game.
I started with a bang, and then...
I committed suicide.