translated from Addic7ed french subtitles: translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Welcome to
Second Chance Survivor!
16 days ago, 20 former players
were getting their second chance
at a game they love.
I have to go through it all again.
I come looking for redemption.
And all of them brought
their past with them.
I feel like the last time:
out of place in my tribe.
Fishbach, a fish out of water,
once again!
Some even had
a common history.
Kass, zero chance of winning the game!
Kass and I had a fight,
and we even hated each other.
And with redemption at stake,
it was clear
that everyone would play hard...
...and quick.
When it merges, it will be the apocalypse.
The Bayon tribe
decided to stick together.
We have the strongest group.
We can move forward in the game.
We have to stick together
and support each other.
But after a surprise mix...
We go from two tribes...
to three.
No kidding !
The ex-Bayon
had to conclude new agreements.
This is the final quintet.
I try to recruit
as many people as possible.
Everyone was shocked
when Terry left the game.
Your son is in the hospital.
But they were even more surprised
by a second mix.
There will be two tribes.
Ta Keo and Bayon.
I'm excited.
I just want to win.
The new Bayon
proved to be the strongest tribe.
Damn, yeah!
And they won
the final immunity challenge.
Bayon wins immunity!
In the new Ta Keo,
Spencer was on the sidelines.
Tonight, everyone votes for Spencer.
I am not joking.
But Spencer and Kass
forgot their past differences.
No one will expect us
to work together.
I didn't want to play with Spencer.
But can it be useful to me,
at this moment?
And at the council, Kass saved Spencer,
knocking out Woo by surprise
and shocking Wiglesworth and Savage.
Surprise elimination!
The tribe has spoken.
There are 13 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What's great
about Second Chance,
is that there are so
many levels of relationships,
that even if you say start from scratch,
you find yourself with someone
who may have betrayed you in the past...
Rough evening.
At the council, I thought everything was locked.
They kept me away.
They are incredible liars.
I thought I was good
at deciphering people...
They are pros.
These people are pros.
Believe that if you were...
You didn't have to come see me,
but if you did,
I would have just said,
"Okay, I understand."
It was nothing personal
against anyone.
It was purely related
to the red flags.
I especially feel betrayed by Kass.
I thought she was
firmly linked to the Bayon.
But after last night,
she became a Ta Keo.
I will not go without a fight.
Fuck them!
Band motherfuckers !
I have a big heart and I am loyal.
And I have supported you
from day 1.
All I'm saying is:
take me to merge
and use me from here.
A merger is coming.
If I have to lay low,
act like
a funky little follower,
the kind to go unnoticed,
what is opposite to me,
I will do.
I have to reach fusion.
We are all on the same
wavelength, we want to win.
Do you promise
not to take it out on me again?
I will not rewrite your name.
I swear.
Savage feels stupid and guilty,
because he was caught
red-handed trying to eliminate me by surprise.
But I'll have to make peace,
because I create relationships,
this time, that saved me.
It took 17 days,
but I finally have a band.
Maybe this is the start
of what should have happened
in Cagayan.
- And it's a second chance.
- But yes.
Kass and I fought a lot
in Cagayan.
But this time,
I have to rely on her.
I really changed
and progressed in this game,
hence my presence today.
Hear, hear!
Princes and princesses!
No bamboo or anything.
Just one page.
Brief and concise.
"Bayon tribe..."
That's us.
"...Go to the end of your beach
and wait for visitors."
- What ?
- Not possible !
- Fusion ?
- A merger at 13?
I'm a Survivor fan.
So soon,
it can't be fusion.
Usually there are 9 or 10 people.
They won't come
to this shithole?!
If it's the merger,
the Intelligence tribe of Cagayan
will be met.
Kass, Spencer and me.
We have a good history
of collaboration.
But it hasn't always been rosy.
So I'm very nervous.
"Tribu Ta Keo.
Gather all the stuff
that you want to keep
for the future
and follow that map
to your new home."
Quoi ?!
What does fusion mean?
It makes me really nervous.
With Savage, who is very disappointed,
who was lied to...
Going to merge
with someone like that worries me.
What do you think is going on?
I don't know,
but we have to stick together.
Remember: someone out there
will feel like they're at the bottom of the ladder.
- Find the flaw!
- Exactly.
That this surprise
turns out to be wonderful!
A wonderful fusion!
I dreamed of achieving fusion.
I suffered.
I pray to the Survivor gods
with all my might
that today brings something positive,
like the merger,
and find my Bayon brothers.
Please !
What's up, Ta Keo?!
We cross the hill,
and suddenly I look,
and I see this little Ta Keo tribe.
More 13 ?
No way it's the merger,
there are too many of us!
Are we all there?
- Go ahead, Keith!
- "Congratulations, you have merged!"
Orange !
Everyone's excited, but...
We say to ourselves: "Oh, oh!
There are really a lot of us!"
Ahead !
When we reach fusion,
we know well
that things will change.
- Welcome back !
- I was tired of confronting you!
- Glad to see you again!
- We've reached fusion!
It's a new game, let's go!
We are like the 1st day.
It's dangerous. But it's funny.
- To the merger!
To the 13 greatest losers
of all time!
Can we start unpacking?
Let's start unpacking, let's see.
I'm super excited.
But I'm freaking out.
I didn't reach fusion
last time,
that was my #1 goal.
So having done it this time,
it is already a step accomplished.
Will you pass me the juice?
But I want to fight my
way to the end.
There is only one winner.
Only one person pockets the million
at the end of Survivor.
I came to play.
- Woo was shocked?
- Woo was very shocked.
- So who voted for him?
-Spencer,
as well as Wigles and Savage.
All voted Spencer.
What about you, Kass?
Did you vote for him?
Non.
I worked with Spencer.
In a strange twist,
he put his fate in my hands.
And I didn't abuse it.
That's crazy !
Chaos-Kass, my saviour!
Last night, I basically decided
to save Spencer.
I feel that he
really trusts me,
because I supported
him and did not lie to him.
Then I can play this card
with him.
I saved him.
I'm officially
in a food coma!
The cheese is starting to weigh on me.
I was alert, ready to pounce.
Because...
Everyone knew
that as soon as the feast was over,
it would be chaos.
I can't wait to talk to you.
Are we staying super tight?
We have a lot to discuss.
You have to be operational from the start,
in the new school Survivor.
We must immediately
create an alliance of seven
to be majority in the 1st vote.
Sit in your hammock, bro!
Like the good old times.
I am the happiest of men.
Back in my
original home, Bayon.
Jeremy, last night's episode
scares me.
You can't imagine
how fast and stealthy they are.
It could have been me.
Everything will happen very quickly.
They might already have
six people against you and me,
without us even knowing it.
The crux of the matter
is Bayon versus Ta Keo.
We must be seven.
So you, me,
Tasha...
And Fishbach?
Fishbach is with us.
Kimmi too.
We could go to Wiglesworth.
She is with us?
That's six.
Wiglesworth told me
she would protect me.
She was not
in the original Bayon,
but she is very loyal,
as far as I know.
And we need seven people.
From a numerical point of view,
I have to do everything to recruit Joe
to confirm
that he wants to be part of the Bayon.
What we will create today and tomorrow
will lay the groundwork
for the next two weeks.
- [???]
- Yeah.
Jeremy, Savage and the others
are clearly together.
- Who else can we recruit, Abi?
- Abi, it's okay.
- I say.
- She can't win.
Who else ?
We are missing someone.
Right now, we have Spencer.
- Good.
- And it's strange.
We are five,
with Abi and Spencer, it's good.
For now, I'm working
with Kass,
Ciera,
Keith,
and we hope to have Joe.
Because on the former Ta Keo camp,
we had a final quintet chord.
So it's good.
According to Kass, we have Abi,
but then there's Spencer and Joe,
which are a bit like free electrons.
I want to talk to them to see
where exactly they are.
To make sure they're in.
It is now clear
that Spencer and Joe
are going to have weight
and control over this game.
Everything is here.
It is crucial.
I was doing my math last night
and I realized the importance
of reconnecting with Joe,
between four eyes,
to confirm
the strength of our bond,
because we need him.
My speech today is:
"We can do it.
Let's stick together, we have the majority.
It is very simple."
On a nos Bayon.
That brings us to day 30.
If everyone is.
So, let's review the list.
I have both of us
Jeremy, Tasha,
Kimmi,
Stephen et Wiglesworth.
We have the old Bayon.
Honestly,
we reach the 30th day,
and then we will advise.
Savage puts his heart
into the game,
and he actually opens it.
I think I can trust him,
but I had a plan with the Ta Keos,
so I don't close any doors.
I'll talk to everyone,
take the temperature.
Tell me, Spencer.
You look concerned.
There are 13 people,
you seem to be saying:
"I can not do it."
I'm having a little trouble
understanding everything that's going on.
I hadn't seen Spencer
in quite a while.
I wanted to reconnect
and make sure
that he was ready
to work with me.
Who do you want to play with?
In view of the two groups,
I trust...
to Kass, Ciera, you,
and even Abi.
I have more confidence in this group
than in Tasha and Savage.
Does it speak to you?
The only two I doubt
because I haven't spoken to them,
it's Joe and Keith.
Keith, it's 100%.
I promise you.
- You think ?
- Absolutely.
It is enormous.
And Joe?
I have to talk to him
to take the temperature
and make sure he doesn't
befriend Jeremy and Savage.
For now,
there are two rival groups.
Apparently Joe and I
are right in the middle.
I wouldn't mind
staying with Joe,
to associate myself with him,
maybe even set up a stunt
with him later.
I had no allies
for more than a day.
- It sucks.
- Yeah.
Me, I did not go to the council,
so my confidence remains to be tested.
- Just.
- I don't know where the people are.
There is clearly a Bayon group.
There's Jeremy...
- Jeremy, Tash.
- Tash, Stephen.
Joe and I were discussing alliances.
I tried to put that
in Joe's language.
"Well, Joe, it's like football.
Here is the field.
If this person,
this one and this one..."
I think there's a quintet here
and another one there.
Basically, we're in the middle.
At this point there is a line,
and I'm on one side
or the other, with you.
We have to protect each other.
I feel like I'm being punished.
It's a rainy day
and I have to pass it
in Grandma's sewing room.
And stay calm.
I have a poem to share with you.
It is called "Greatness of God",
par Gerard Manley Hopkins.
“The world is full
of the greatness of God.
She comes to spring forth,
sudden gleam of gold leaf,
Ample it piles up
like pressed oil squirts.
Why do we laugh at his strength?
And yet nature
never runs out.
At the heart of things
lives sweet freshness.
Because the Holy Spirit covers the world
with a lively breast and ah!
the brilliance of its wings.
Attractive.
- Very pretty.
You should do this for us
every day.
- Another 18!
- Fishbach's poem of the day!
There's a thing between guys
at the Bayons.
They are all together.
I think I have the most links,
have the best chance
of gathering a majority to confront
Savage's clan, Jeremy and Stephen.
This game has changed a lot
since the beginning.
- There is a lot of people.
- Difficult to monitor them.
And with all the mixing
things get really murky.
There is a division.
If so,
you could be targeted, because you're...
formidable in trials.
I'm not... Everyone here
is formidable in trials.
I spoke with Kass,
and I had the impression
that she was looking for information.
But I know
she works with Ta Keo,
so I preferred to give him
a canard about my wedding ring.
The Bayon are not soldered.
It is one of the elements.
You are close to Jeremy.
But not Stephen.
So Bayon, is it over?
That's what I would say.
Kass caused my departure
during my first participation.
I trusted her,
and what did she do?
She betrayed me.
It's my 2nd chance.
No way to give him
another chance to ruin my game.
So what's your plan?
The Bayons in force?
My daughter...
at this stage...
I have the impression...
...that I will follow the advice of the group.
I wanted to talk to Tasha,
and I was telling the truth,
but it was not reciprocated.
It was very clear.
She never trusted me.
She's stuck on Cagayan.
It's our second chance.
It all happens there.
Don't get in the way of my 2nd chance!
You just unleashed the beast.
The dividing lines
will appear today.
- You think ?
- In effect.
Bonjour !
I know Tasha
can be explosive.
And I'm ready to fight it out.
You saved my life.
Sleeping in the back?
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
The original Bayon
will control the game
if nobody is ready
to turn everything upside down.
God, may Chaos-Kass
not do this!
- It went badly yesterday, didn't it?
- Yes.
You told me...
that the Bayons were over.
How could I say that
when that's all I got?
But I asked you to your face.
I said...
Kass, I won't tell you
what I really think,
because I don't trust you.
So, whether you believe
this was a real conversation...
It's the old Tasha.
Didn't you learn?
I'm just saying...
Yes. I learned.
I learned
not to trust you.
That's what I picked up.
Tasha instilled doubts.
It wasn't smart of him.
She gave me food for thought.
I could tell all her allies
that she said to me:
"Bye-bye, Bayon !"
That's the thing. You told me
everything I needed.
Here is the limit. It is drawn.
The game is started.
I want to win Second Chance,
and if I have to use Chaos-Kass,
I will.
I spoke with Kass.
To make it clear,
You took me away yesterday
and told a canard:
"Bayon, it's over."
I did not say...
How could I say that?
You just admitted it.
How could I say
"bye-bye Bayon",
- while I am linked to Bayon?
- You just admitted it.
Kass. Don't imagine
that I'm going to tell you the truth.
You come with your liabilities.
If we start from scratch?
Not when someone lies to me.
Kass !
Let people think
about their allies and their behavior.
I vote Tasha.
Because she doesn't trust me.
Tasha arrives with Kass,
creating chaos on the camp,
accusing some
of betraying others.
But I can use this.
There is clearly
a strong group, Bayon.
I wanted to instill doubt
to separate them.
Let's lie to them
and see what happens.
We have seen Savage
become very close to Woo.
They told Kass and me
that you were a serious threat.
So, Woo and Savage
agreed
to go after Jeremy.
- Nope.
- This is a lie.
It was a comment
made by Woo and Savage,
like what at the merger,
some big guys should leave.
And Joe and you were part of it.
Tasha and Kass were arguing.
And suddenly,
Ciera pulls out something about me.
You just woke up
an angry bull!
I never mentioned
Jeremy or Joe,
and I would never take it out on them,
so don't give that impression,
don't lie.
I do not lie. I will not back down
from what has been said.
We have a nasty raging
two-headed dragon
who is wreaking havoc
on our beautiful little tribe.
We're gonna cut off one of those heads.
Over here, everyone!
Ciera, tell me about the merger.
How was it ?
With all the chaos
and talk about camp,
we do not yet know
what to expect.
We will be fixed at the first council,
so it's a very good time
to wear the necklace.
Ready for your first
individual immunity test?
Oui !
First of all, Ciera,
I'm taking back tribal immunity.
Merci.
Tribal immunity is no more.
Individual immunity
is what you are aiming for now.
Class!
He is splendid.
And it will look great
around your neck.
With that, you are safe from voting.
Without, you are vulnerable.
- Are we coming to the test?
- Yes !
Today,
you will stand
on a narrow beam,
while keeping a ball
balanced on a plate.
Regularly,
you will descend
to a narrower section
and your hand will descend
along the stake,
making the balance more precarious.
If you fall off the beam
or drop the ball,
the test is lost.
The last person to hold
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be
the 7th person eliminated from the game.
This ordeal goes back to Smart
vs. Muscle vs. Beauty.
Spencer, Kass, Tasha,
all three disputed it.
It ended up face-to-face
between Spencer and Tasha.
Tasha won immunity.
So it's a second chance
for Spencer and Kass.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Good.
Let's go.
Everyone places their ball
on their board.
I'll count down from five.
You have to remove your hand
before we get to one. Let's go.
Five,
four, three, two,
and.
Spread your hands.
This test is on.
It will be ten minutes per section,
for those who will hold on.
Stephen Fishbach, 1st eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
There are 12 left, all at once.
After a few seconds,
a first person loses.
In this test,
stop thinking
about what you're doing,
even just for a moment,
will be enough to cause your loss.
ELAPSED TIME:
9 MINUTES
Keith, lots of movement.
- It's over for Keith.
- Damn !
Keith rejoint Fishbach.
Second person eliminated.
Ciera, it's starting to move.
Ciera does not hold.
Third person eliminated.
Kimmi drops her ball.
There are ten seconds left
in this round.
We're almost there, hold on!
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and.
Get your hands on your ball,
you're safe.
You will go down to the 2nd level,
narrower,
and you will place your hands
lower on the stake.
Good.
Let's go.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and.
Spread your hands. Here we go again.
Abi is eliminated, after one second
in this 2nd round.
You support more stake,
and the beam is narrower.
Your room for maneuver is reduced,
in the 2 aspects of the event.
Kass drops his ball.
No 2nd chance redemption
for Kass.
Suddenly,
Wiglesworth drops his ball.
Wentworth drops his ball.
There are now
four men and one woman left,
and this woman
is the only person
to have ever won this event.
ELAPSED TIME:
20 MINUTES
There are 15 seconds left
in this section.
Hold fast !
Five, four,
three,
of them,
and.
Everyone is safe,
move on to the next section.
Everyone is now
on the third section.
I will count.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and.
This ordeal is over.
- Lets go !
- Nice recovery from Savage.
But it does not hold.
Savage is the first out.
There are four left.
This section is very difficult.
Two beginners in this event,
Joe and Jeremy,
two veterans, the only ones
to have already competed in this event,
Spencer et Tasha.
Who will win today?
Jeremy, on the edge,
but he's recovering well.
Nice recovery for Tasha.
Can she do it again?
Nope ! Tasha is eliminated.
Jeremy is eliminated,
and now there are only two left.
Joe and Spencer.
Big 2nd chance stake for Spencer.
He lost to Tasha the first time
this event was contested,
in Intelligence, Muscles and Beauty.
Will he find redemption here,
against one of the game's fiercest
competitors, Joe?
Spencer... wobbles.
Nice recovery,
huge recovery!
Will it hold?
New recovery!
But it does not hold!
Spencer falls!
Joe wins
the first individual immunity!
Congratulations, Joe!
Bravo, Spence !
Joe, come here!
He is so pretty!
- He is magnificent !
- Wonderful !
First victory
in individual immunity.
Safe from council vote tonight.
As for you others,
after 19 days in
your 2nd chance adventure,
someone will fail.
You have the afternoon
to decide who it will be.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
- Congratulation.
- Thanks !
Big decision tonight.
I'm in a position
where Spencer and I
are pivot votes.
I just know that I'm happy
to wear the necklace,
because that's going to be great advice.
- Well done, Joe!
- Congratulation !
Well done, my brother!
Go on !
First immunity.
I just wanted to win.
I wanted to assert myself.
Looks like a gladiator!
All these young stallions...
I wanted to show
that I could compete with them.
Some try a new game,
others still live in the old one.
But Kass and Ciera
did not win immunity.
In my season,
I never lied to anyone.
And here,
The leader was Kass,
with Ciera behind.
They invent
almost believable lies.
That's what makes them so dangerous.
But I'd rather Ciera leave.
I will never forget
what she did.
For me, that's the end of her.
The decision seems easy, right?
After this morning.
Frankly, I can't
trust Ciera.
She's super dangerous.
She invents these lies
which are almost believable...
That's it. They always contain
some truth.
It wasn't the worst.
Kass was much worse.
They maintain each other.
What do we do ?
Kass seems to me the most disruptive.
For this vote,
I'd rather see Ciera go.
She is really dangerous.
To me, she's public enemy number one
and she needs to go.
I'm leaning towards Kass.
It's unanimous.
At this stage,
if the majority wants Kass,
sometimes it is better to
follow the majority.
Because Kass has a ruthless side
and his game is a bit random,
and it scares me.
So what is being said?
For elimination?
Well...
Must be a troublemaker.
Exact.
- What do you think ?
- To Kass.
[???]
This is the shot to play.
Kass ?
No worries for me.
I wondered
which way to go.
But I feel that the majority
takes a certain direction
and won't wait for me.
Kass was the only one who wanted to
play with me in the last vote.
Even if I want to save her,
I'm not sure I can.
- Do we divide?
- I do not think so.
Does Kass have an idol?
I do not think so.
Looks
like everyone is going to vote Kass.
But Kass might have an idol.
It's always good
to split the votes.
- I know I vote for Kass.
- I vote for Kass.
We're enough to get her out.
Let's say she has an idol...
How to counter it?
It's a 4-5 split.
5 Kass, 4 Ciera.
They will never see it coming.
So 5 Kass, 4 Ciera.
Sounds armored, right?
Yes, it is ideal.
I don't like to say that
but if they want to get Kass out,
I'm on it.
She tends to mess things up.
At this point, yeah, I lied: let
her go.
We are clear on who is voting who?
The reconciliation will happen.
It's so ugly to see.
What is this animal
that eats the dead,
The vultures ?
That's it ?
Well, they... Never mind.
I should have anticipated it.
It started with Tasha.
Now I believe Keith
is going to follow the majority.
Why are they talking
so long?
They will split the votes. 5 - 4.
If we had one more person...
They are in the majority
and could split the votes.
So if I had five people
ready to vote Tash,
Tasha would leave.
They divide.
Vote Tasha and recruit Spencer.
Five would be enough for me.
- It's a split vote.
- OK.
If we all vote Tasha, that means
anyone, anywhere,
worth recruiting.
If we get to Spencer in time,
and it rolls with him,
we'll see what we'll see.
As elders,
we know the votes
could be split.
And after today's big
explosive argument,
there is clearly a risk
I'm leaving tonight.
Ideally, I 'd love
Kass to be able to recruit Spencer,
that we can act
before it is too late.
They split the votes.
If there's five of us, we can take Tasha out.
Yeah.
Abi and Ciera are
in, and Wentworth said she would.
- You all vote Tasha?
- Yeah.
This is an opportunity to make a move
that would benefit both of us.
I say.
And I know you got me covered.
- So...
- Let's do it.
Tonight the votes will be split
between Kass, Ciera and Tasha.
Today
it turned sour for no reason.
It will be better after tonight.
My decision tonight
will determine who leaves.
I always saw Tasha
as a friend.
But Kass and Ciera
supported me and saved me.
My luck has really changed.
I had never been in a position
to influence the game.
For those
who don't have a torch yet,
enter one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because the fire represents your life.
If your fire goes away, so do you.
Biggest tip
we've ever had!
Ciera,
today, to the test,
I briefly asked
how it was going.
The response led me to believe
it was pretty chaotic.
Chaotic is still nice.
I knew it would go very quickly
in Second Chance.
But it's crazy beyond words.
Kass, was there a moment,
even for someone like you
that thrives in utter chaos,
where you say to yourself,
"It's too much, even for me." ?
Actually, I'm not
playing the chaos game this time.
It's funny
that supposedly calm people
are at the heart of the chaos
and cause it.
Like who ?
Like Tasha.
Don't play this.
Don't play that with me
now.
Chaos is his domain,
not mine.
If there is chaos,
it's his way,
not mine.
But I will expose your maneuvers.
She told me
the Bayon alliance was over.
No it is wrong.
But Kass, in some ways,
doesn't create lies.
Some of his words are true.
But don't turn them to your advantage
en disant :
"Tasha a dit bye-bye Bayon" !
I don't even talk like that.
Are you talking to Kass or Ciera?
Both.
Ciera, do you fear
being guilty by association?
We never want to
be in the middle of chaos
nor that one is
too interested in oneself,
but my name
was clearly mentioned,
this is the reality of the game.
So, Joe,
it seems to me that even though
Ciera's name was mentioned,
like that of Kass,
that Tasha quarreled with,
it could still
be anyone.
It could be anyone.
But this is the first vote
after the merger,
and everyone is afraid
to choose sides.
And so, the easiest votes
are those three.
Ciera, what do you think
of Joe's comments?
"It seems easy.
It's Ciera, Kass
or Tasha, take your pick."
It shouldn't be easy.
We should aim for the heart.
If this vote is so easy,
you are not playing correctly.
And I don't like to play with people
who are afraid to play.
I want to win.
Playing with people who don't want
to win is no fun.
That's to say ?
Everyone wants to win.
Only one person will win.
Everyone should protect their interests.
I was in a position to play
for 6th place. Do not do that !
Let's play for 1st place,
whatever that means to you.
If it means eliminating me,
go straight ahead!
But play to win!
Spencer,
I imagine you would say,
"But I play!"
"Playing" is different
for each person,
each day.
And tomorrow,
it could be very different.
Fishbach, that's a hell of a comment.
Because usually, in this game, we say:
"Jeff, we are 5 or 6 welded."
Spencer dit:
"Tonight
's vote is tonight's vote.
Tomorrow, everything can change."
This game is moving so fast.
It's so strange.
What fusion
sees three little women
being the likely targets?
Things are changing right now.
Not just in the game,
but in the history
of Survivor strategy.
We are witnessing an evolution
in the way of playing this game.
Spencer, maybe you do
n't need a wedding ring at all,
just voting blocks
for each council.
Looking at the last three days
and the pace of this game,
no change would surprise me.
Ciera, is this the type of game
you are looking for?
Namely, "Yes, I'm with you...
for now."
Not necessarily.
Trust comes into play.
But we want to be in the top 4,
pas 6e, 7e, 8e or 9e.
And some here will be.
When you realize you are,
you go into game mode.
Let's play!
That's all I'm saying.
Good. It's time to vote.
Wentworth, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Kass.
Ciera.
Tasha.
One vote Kass,
one vote Ciera, one vote Tasha.
Kass.
Ciera.
Tasha.
Two Kass votes,
two Ciera votes, two Tasha votes.
Kass.
Ciera.
Savage.
Three Kass votes,
three votes Ciera, two votes Tasha,
a Savage vote.
Kass.
Ciera. New equality.
Four Kass votes,
four Ciera votes, two Tasha votes,
a Savage vote.
Kass. Five votes Kass,
four votes Ciera,
one vote remains.
Seventh person eliminated
from Survivor Second Chance
and first member of our jury...
Kass. Bring me your torch.
Sorry, Kass.
Oh my God !
Kass, the tribe has spoken.
If tonight's advice
give an idea of ​​what will follow,
then it's gonna suck.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Team Survivor ST
http://survivor-st.forumgratuit.org/
Translation: Jack Bauer
Relecture : Lény, flosm92
Synchro : Lény
Re-synchro version HD : aymeric000
Poem "God's Grandeur" by Hopkins
Translation borrowed from Benoît Casas
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
I know he is going to play a big blow.
Everyone is worried about
the big hits to come.
It's time to act, to go
after someone really dangerous.
The only question is:
who will strike first?
Loyalty has its limits.
This time
I wanted to build relationships
and work on my social game.
I think I have succeeded in my change
for 18 days.
I wasn't
in anyone's sights.
Mais j'ai voulu
faire revenir Chaos-Kass
et ça a dynamité mon jeu.
Je me suis fait prendre.
C'est de ma faute.