translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
With the million in sight,
everyone wanted to control
who would go in the end.
Tai had an idol
and a benefit.
"You have won
an extra vote."
He thought he
could control the votes.
I want you to vote Michele.
He wanted to eliminate Michele,
the biggest threat according to him.
For me, it's Michele.
He thought he had the support
of his closest ally, Aubry.
- She's more dangerous.
- Oh, I'm with you.
But pushing too
hard, he bumped into Cydney,
who fought
to keep her ally, Michele.
I will cover you
as much as I can.
At the council,
Tai played his advantage...
I can add a vote
to any board.
...to make sure of the outcome.
It's number two.
But his alliance
turned against him.
Jason, the tribe has spoken.
Leaving the alliance of the four welded
and Tai unsure
of his place in the game.
There are five left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Alright, friends.
Good game.
The people spoke,
they didn't want him.
I'm in shock, folks.
Well, they didn't want him.
- I see.
- And I had to follow my covenant.
That's all, see?
Everyone
absolutely wanted to eliminate him.
I wish I had been warned.
I came home after the council,
I'm trying to figure out
what exactly happened.
I thought the four of us were
voting Michele,
but the four of them voted for Jason.
So I wasted
my extra vote.
They didn't tell me anything.
Being out of
it is the worst that can happen.
The first quality of this alliance
is that we always listen to each other.
The quality of an alliance
is not to be betrayed.
I agree.
However, you've already done it three times
.
From the start, Aubry, you
and Joe know, I say
let everyone speak,
even you, Joe.
But not me.
You are definitely
part of the group,
but to what extent,
I am not sure.
I'm honest with you.
I told you about it. I said, as
for the final square...
As for the final square,
I will be easy to eliminate.
No, that was before you even arrived.
- I was in the group before you.
- I must admit...
Tai used his two votes
against me.
It's obvious
that he wants me out
and it's like a slap in the face for me.
It's a game.
We all knew
it was Jason tonight.
It's in the order of things,
it's very good.
Fortunately, I had the chance
may Cydney protect me,
but I had votes against me.
So I don't know where I am
and I could be
the next eliminated.
Seriously, for me,
there were two alliances,
without you, Michele.
I know it's horrible to say,
but you understand that...
No, but it's okay,
I don't need to understand you.
OK.
As you wish.
I'm still a bit lost.
I don't really know
what happened.
It was Aubry who told me that
he absolutely wanted to eliminate Michele.
It hurts me,
especially from Aubry.
She's the only one
I really trust.
And I feel like
she double-crossed me.
Why am I isolated?
While the band,
especially you and me, agreed
to vote Michele?
And I completely agreed
to vote Jason.
People felt
that when it was discussed as a group,
they were not allowed
to express themselves.
Yes, but I don't impose anything.
And if I don't listen, say,
"We do this,
whether you follow or not."
At least I'll be aware of it.
I should have told you, that's for sure.
You took me by surprise.
I left Tai out of the shot
in the vote
because he has so much
power in the game
that I had to recover.
But he feels
like I betrayed him
and it's very serious for him,
when he feels hurt.
So I'm not sure I
can move forward with him.
I'm lost,
are you with me or not?
I'm a bit lost too, because...
It was confusing, all that.
I never changed my vote.
When I say...
Hey, Joe. I'm trying to clarify
the situation between us.
I listen.
We exchange.
Aubry, you know that better than anyone.
You and me, we talk.
I am reasonable.
I listen to everything.
I told Tai that people felt
they had no voice.
Fine, I understand.
You make me look unreasonable.
Me, am I making you look
unreasonable?
I'm not. Do you know me.
I'm not like that.
I felt completely alone,
I don't know who to trust.
My biggest worry
is Aubry and Joe.
I put all my eggs
in their basket
and I don't know
which direction to take now.
Over here, everyone!
You are only five.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
you will run through the jungle
to a large wooden ladder
which you will climb
to retrieve sandbags.
You will come back and attempt to send
these bags into targets.
The first to send a bag
into each of the five targets
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yes.
The winner will go
to Survivor's spa.
Did you see ?
First,
you can take a bath,
wash your body and hair,
being clean.
Then, a massage.
Then you will eat:
chicken, beef,
your cheesecake.
Oh, the cheesecake!
And you will spend the night there.
For the first time in 33 days,
you will sleep in a real bed.
You will wake up
and return to camp refreshed,
with everything you will need
to overcome
these very last days.
I know it's worth it, we draw
the places and we start.
Well, on and go.
For the reward,
Survivors, ready?
First you have
to run through the jungle,
uphill, to collect
the first bag of sandbags.
Then you have to come back.
You have three saddlebags each.
You have to bring them back one by one.
Cydney is back
with her first satchel.
You were quick!
That's Michele, Aubry
and Tai with their first bag!
You have to empty them
then throw the sandbags
one by one.
Cydney throws, it's a little short.
Michele, a bit short too.
Aubry just misses.
Tai just misses.
Aubry leaves.
Michele goes back to get some.
Tai throws his last bag.
Nope ! Tai misses.
He returns to the jungle.
Joe is back.
The last to return.
He has five bags,
he could put it all on at once.
Joe takes his time,
it's his first pitch.
You have to hit your targets
for it to count.
Joe just misses.
that's all !
Joe's latest bag.
It's not good !
Joe returns to the jungle.
Cydney returns with her second bag.
Aubry, just behind.
That's Michele and Tai.
All come back to throw.
Cydney hits the same target,
it only counts as one.
Aubry scores a 2nd point.
Tai just misses.
Aubry and Cydney just miss.
Everyone is not far,
but it is missed.
Cydney scores a second point!
Aubry scores his third!
Still nothing for Michele.
Still nothing for Tai.
Tai leaves.
Michele scores her first point!
Aubry returns with her 3rd bag.
She's the one leading.
Aubry has 3 points, more than 2 targets.
These need to be insured!
Aubry throws.
She just misses.
Cydney returns
with her 3rd and final satchel.
Aubry throws very far and scores!
Aubry has four!
More than one, this one perhaps?
Not far, but no.
Aubry only has two bags left,
after that it's over.
Last bag for Aubry.
That's all.
We must succeed now.
Aubry misses, she has no more bag.
She must wait
and hope that the others
use all their bags,
and then we'll get back to it.
Third bag for Michele.
She just misses.
Cydney just misses.
Cydney is out of a bag.
Here's Joe with his second satchel.
First point for Joe!
Nice throw from Joe.
Second point for Joe.
Joe sticks back to the group.
New throw from Michele.
She just misses.
Tai no longer has a bag.
Michele has no bag left.
Nobody has a bag anymore, except Joe.
Another nice throw.
Good game,
Joe has three.
Joe still has a satchel.
He returns to the jungle.
Very interesting situation.
Aubry, Cydney, Michele and Tai
went much faster than Joe,
rode in the lead,
but failed to finish,
and now
Joe has time for himself.
No need to run,
he can take his time.
He could win now.
Alright, Joe, come on!
Joe returns with his third
and final satchel.
Joe, you have 3 points,
you have 2 targets left.
Nobody else has a bag.
Victory is reaching out to you.
The two targets
are the furthest apart.
You'll have to throw away
to reach them.
It won't count.
Just missed.
Almost, but no!
Two more bags for Joe.
You have to put both.
He's the oldest here,
will he succeed now?
The fourth !
More than a target!
The farthest.
He can win now.
The others can't do anything anymore,
they don't have a bag anymore.
Joe succeeds!
At 71,
he wins the individual award!
- Cheer !
- Good job !
I'm so happy for you!
You succeed ! Finally !
Joe, come closer!
Good job.
Good. Joe, you have
to make a decision.
Because a spa is great,
and sometimes
we want time for ourselves.
At Survivor, we want
you to have company.
Choose a person
to accompany you
on this reward.
Bath, massage, food
and a good night's sleep.
I'll choose my Intelligence partner
from the start,
we started together. Aubrey.
Aubry, come!
Aubry will join you.
Joe, you have
to make another decision.
Cydney, Michelle, Thailand.
- Cydney.
- Who are you going to choose?
And already Aubry, you are chatting.
- I'll let you say it.
- Cydney.
Cydney will join Joe and Aubry.
I chose Cydney for the reward
because everything is up in the air
with Tai.
It forces me to evaluate
my other options for the finale.
Good. Nice job, Joe.
Joe, Cydney, Aubry,
get your things and go.
- Have a good afternoon.
- Thanks.
Michele, Tai, I have nothing for you.
Take your things, return to camp.
As I left
the place of trial,
everything i thought about,
it was: well, Cydney, Aubry and Joe,
it is perhaps the final trio.
So I have to take a risk
to try to change
the hierarchy of departures.
- Thanks !
Wow, friends!
Look at this ! It is serious ?!
It's fantastic.
I'll try that first, I think.
I love this chicken, huh?
The chicken is delicious!
We land
on this beautiful beach
and we stuff ourselves,
we devour
all this fabulous food.
We are like in paradise.
The meat is so tender.
I eat little meat,
I'm not very steak,
but it's amazing.
That's all I needed.
This is the best event
I could have won.
I was out of juice, friends.
I can't believe
I won today.
I was delighted.
Eat something substantial
meat and all
this is a big advantage for me.
I love these proteins!
With just six days to go,
to be strengthened like this,
it is beyond my hopes.
The reward
couldn't have been better.
Just beef.
Joe is beef.
Joe is stuffing himself
with beef, beef, beef.
And from experience,
I knew he wouldn't feel
very well later.
I won it.
You won, Joe!
Great.
As long as we're here
what would you like to do, now
that we are in a position of strength?
I would like us to get there,
all three.
Me too.
So we're going to vote against Tai?
We can't, he has an idol.
Ah, that's right,
so it will be the next time.
Are you okay with that,
getting rid of Tai?
- How are you?
- If it's okay with me?
He is an adversary.
Cydney and me
- we are not adversaries.
- We follow the movement.
Aubry, Joe and I
could be the final trio,
but I try to be
as discreet as possible.
Now,
I just nod my head,
smile,
let me lead,
and I'll be happy
to win the million when we get there.
Aubry thinks
she got a lot of enemies and stuff,
but everyone
knows how hard you played,
how upright you are.
Just being sociable, like me,
it does nothing.
Cyd, she's been silent and all,
she was just there.
We are not threats.
No way.
- You're kidding ?
- Everyone plays the game in their own way.
There are other threats in the game
for me, in other forms.
Joe basically says I'm
the only threat in the game,
that Cydney is content
to be in the final trio.
Balivernes!
It made me realize:
"Oh my God,
Cydney is a menace!"
She had a key role
in some surprise hits,
she won a race
and, to a certain extent,
it is more appreciated.
So maybe I don't want to
be in the final three with Cydney.
Tai is maybe
a better option for me.
Exactly what I needed
to get my head around.
- Good for Joe!
- Yeah.
I figured it would be the three
of them anyway.
To go there? Yeah, I thought
Aubry would take... Yeah.
They have a
closer relationship too.
You know ?
We lost the race today,
so Joe took Aubry and Cydney.
It's obvious,
it's the final trio for them.
It really hurts me
from Aubry,
because I don't know
where his feelings go.
I don't know if you're open to that,
But sometimes,
I just like to speak frankly,
- and open up to others.
- Do you want to talk now?
Let's go in the water
, sit down and talk.
Sounds good.
When I got back to camp,
I said to myself: “Oh no!
How am I going to spend
the next 24 hours
with Michele,
who I just had a fight with?”
The only thing I can do
is straighten things out with her.
Last night everything went
so ugly.
You see,
yesterday, it hurt me,
but it's a game.
And for the jury...
I did not want to hurt you.
I knew you wanted to kill me.
I do not know why
I am attracted to some people
and not to others.
But it seems that there is no
chemistry between us.
maybe you are a beautiful girl
and that I'm not comfortable
or what.
Not only you, with certain people,
I let my guard down automatically.
With others, I warn myself.
- I understand.
- I can not explain it.
It runs through my whole life.
That's it
that he bases all his relationships
in this life
on the affinities
he has with people.
I understand, we have more affinity
with some than with others.
But in a game like this,
you have to play on all fronts.
I never closed the door to you.
It's like you choose
who you want to be close to
and then pushed the others away.
Ultimately,
Tai and I are very different,
we perceive the game very differently.
We're just going to take it easy.
This is going to be our
spa and relaxation day.
I will massage you.
- Oh my God !
- I am gifted. We'll see.
I believe that Michele and I
are at the bottom of the scale.
But we were in the Beauty tribe,
before the merger.
Maybe she's not fake.
Maybe
I missed something.
And I have an opportunity
to get to know her a little better.
It is true that you are gifted.
I hear cracking.
It feels good.
Looks like a Thai massage.
It's a Tai massage!
On the spa program,
there was a Tai massage.
It's a Tai massage
because it's a Thai method
and that it's Tai the masseur.
Oh, Mark is joining us.
Hey, Mark!
We miss him.
Honestly, it's way better
than their massage.
And later, I'll even
feed you mango.
We have our poor man's spa
when they have the real version.
Who would've believed that ?
We had a fight last night...
I still remember
all the words you said.
It still stings funny.
- You know ?
- Sorry.
Who would have thought that Michele and Tai
would be reconciled with a massage
and a one-on-one meal?
It's like...
I do not know.
Where is the world going?
I thought...
If we can do something together
in the game, but I...
Looks like we're both
out of it.
I feel like
that if I lose, it's done.
And if you lose the next one,
you're done.
I hesitate to say or do
anything with Tai
after what happened
last time,
but it looks like Tai and I
are out of the picture.
You know,
my door is always open.
We are only 2, they are 3.
We should develop scenarios.
We could
find a solution, right?
Yes I think.
We would do a great job
and that would be surprising,
because no one imagines
that Tai and I
can move forward together.
I have an idol.
And then it's the two of us.
Who do we choose?
Cyd is the only obvious choice.
Do you think that would be
the one swinging at us?
It's risky.
The idea of ​​working with Michele
never crossed my mind.
But I feel
completely betrayed by Aubry.
So I'm open
to working with Michele,
because Aubry won't see us coming.
I have nothing to lose.
It's certain.
And neither do I, I guess.
Survivor is the
hardest thing I've done.
Not the physical side,
I like the harshness
of everyday life,
but the hardest
thing is to trust
or not to people.
It really has a big effect
on my emotions.
It is, for sure,
the hardest thing
what I have done in my life.
It was amazing.
Thank you for this good time
in good company.
The decor, the food...
It was probably my favorite,
it was perfect.
Health !
It was awesome.
Full of great food,
and we were able to take a bath
in a large jacuzzi.
You look
clean and refreshed.
My God,
why are you coming home so early?
I wanted you to stay longer
and have some breakfast!
After the reward,
returning to the camp,
I know Cydney is a threat,
and my ideal final trio
is Tai and Joe.
Did you drink wine last night?
This gentleman, yes.
- Actually, we drank champagne.
- We drank champagne.
Oh, my God, in the hot tub?
But I'm afraid Tai
needs love and support so badly
that if he thinks
he has been betrayed or wronged
he makes completely different choices .
- Come, welcome home.
- Thanks !
I kept the fire going.
I thought to myself, if the fire dies,
Joe is going to kill me.
Today I have to talk to Tai,
I have to fix everything.
In the end, I know
Joe will go my way.
How is it going ?
How are you.
I collect my thoughts.
I don't know how you feel,
a lot has happened,
but we must have another option
for the end, in case something goes wrong.
Let's walk there.
I don't know how you feel,
but I had time alone
to think about things
and I don't know where you are.
I do not know.
I need
Tai to trust me
and know
that the only road to the end
must be done together, him and me.
you know that Joe, I believe,
will follow what I think is
the right decision.
And I know you're the one...
You... There's no doubt about it.
We had hard times,
but together,
we have a better chance
of reaching the final trio.
Tai must feel
he can trust me.
Because we are only five,
I have to be in a threesome.
If I have Joe and Tai,
it's 3 to 2.
Gives me hopefully
the little power I need
to pass the next elimination
and I cross my fingers
for Tai to go with me in the end.
You have to forgive a lot
in Survivor
and move forward step by step.
One.
I say.
This game is so crazy.
Aubry really opened up and told me that
we needed each other.
We are almost there.
It comforts me so much.
It relieved me of a great weight.
It had a big effect
on my emotions
and I cracked up for a moment.
You also need to
take time for yourself.
Don't do so much
on the camp.
So far
I've been playing with my heart,
and it looks good to me
to be on Aubry's side.
I had a soft spot for her
from the start.
- Go on.
As soon as we arrived,
we started eating. It was good.
I ate satay skewers
until we went swimming.
- There was a lot ?
- Oh yes, I must have eaten eight!
- Or six.
- A lot.
You haven't eaten it, have you?
One, just one.
Didn't you like it?
Yes, it was excellent.
Finally. There was
a beautiful sunset,
the sky, the clouds and everything...
Very pretty.
Here they are coming back.
I'm all lined up
with Joe and Aubry
so when I saw Aubry and Tai
come back from the well,
their conversation
sounded too pleasant,
the kind you have with an ally.
Here is the water!
Tai, I thought that was
the one we wanted out.
But I can
read situations very well.
and I didn't like it,
it looked very suspicious.
We can no longer think
piecemeal.
We must be two steps ahead.
And it's stressful.
You and me, we know we're tight.
So no matter
who wins immunity,
we have to convince the other person
to come with us.
- I see.
- You understand ?
Michele has always remained
trustworthy.
So I prefer to keep
it to make strategies,
but I want to keep
playing it discreet
hoping
not to screw up my game
trying to improve it.
We will have to
take a hit.
We're so close
now, Cyd,
everything we do
should have a purpose.
It's crazy
how things change here.
I thought I was out of it,
but Cydney and I have had
a great relationship for a long time
and Tai and I have our plan.
So it looks like
we can choose who to eliminate,
Joe or Aubry.
It would be a crazy reversal.
I mean,
no need to worry today.
It's cool.
I'm a little screwed up today.
I have stomach problems.
I ate all that meat yesterday.
I feel bloated.
I can't urinate.
I have a stomach ache.
I hope it's not serious.
Oh, my God, wow!
We should have a dance duel,
you and me, you're good.
You manage
not to look stupid at all.
- Hi.
- Hi !
How are you ?
- Not very well.
- What is it ?
I have bladder problems.
Really ?
Yeah.
You want some water ? Help ?
No, I think my prostate
relies on the bladder
and urine can no longer
pass through the urethra.
It's really unpleasant.
What's going on ?
There, it's fine,
but if it still fills up...
You do not feel well ?
How are you.
Here we are.
- Here we are !
- This time, that's it.
I worry about Joe.
Joe is a constant asset to me.
- Listen, would you give me some water?
- Yes.
Joe is my second vote,
Joe is my confidant,
Joe has been my anchor from the start.
I want him to be okay.
He has to be fine.
I need him to be okay.
I will be back.
What's going on ?
I think he's having trouble urinating.
He says it's the prostate.
I'm afraid he's hurting
even more than he says.
If he can't evacuate,
it's painful,
very painful.
It could cause his evacuation,
and when we're that far away,
with five people,
it's the last thing
we want to see happen.
But at the same time, if Joe leaves,
it helps my game.
So I'm sad for him,
but it is also positive.
So...
It's weird.
There, I have a stomach ache,
because I'm still constipated.
And there's pressure on the bladder.
It hurts like hell.
So the doctor will examine me,
take a first exam
and make
sure everything is working fine.
How is it going ?
This is what happens to me.
Yesterday we got the reward,
and this morning I'm a little constipated.
I no longer urinate.
Can we fix this quickly?
This is one of the things
that precipitates the problem,
probably constipation,
probably due to yesterday's meal.
We can do two things.
I'll give you medicine
to try to fix it,
hope it relieves
the pressure on the bladder
and allow you to empty it,
to eliminate pain.
My concern,
if this constipation remains,
that the tube is paralyzed
and you are not urinating,
I'm afraid that eventually
it will damage your kidneys.
Joe wasn't well,
so he consulted the doctor.
If Joe left,
it would screw up all our plans
for the final trio.
I'm very, very nervous.
After seeing the doctor
and took medicine,
it got a little better
I was able to drink and pee a little better.
I love this dress!
But I'm always in pain,
and not just a little.
To the point that I'm nauseous.
Oh my God !
The friends,
the doc said
that if I stop urinating,
it's not good,
it could mean
everything is blocked.
Joe has been very strong here.
See him with a medical problem
shows how crazy this game can be.
We hope it will go.
Fight, Joe, fight.
He said, "If you don't pee anymore,
it's no good."
We tried drugs,
to see,
but that does nothing.
- I will be back.
- I know you fight, so...
It seems to be getting worse every hour.
He was bent in two,
and I think he concealed a little
the intensity of his pain.
A Chinese lucky charm.
It's crazy.
It's not fair.
It'll be fine, Tai.
It'll be OK.
Everyone was in tears.
I was in tears, Cydney too,
because it is very dear to us.
And it happened so fast.
He and I
are the oldest in the tribe.
It creates links.
Thanks for being so [???].
And Tai, I know you don't like...
No, I... No, no.
Thanks for the kiss.
Lord, I feel special!
Can you make my sore disappear?
Monsieur Joe was like
my surrogate grandfather.
He said what my grandfather
would have said:
"Don't cry, go ahead,
don't cry for me!"
So he reminds me even more
of my grandfather now.
What a magnificent sunset!
I hope to be
as strong as you at 72.
You will be.
The pain becomes unbearable
and if I do nothing,
as I no longer urinate,
it will degenerate
and affect my kidneys.
It wasn't improving
as I had hoped,
so
I had to see the doctor again.
- Hello everyone !
- Hey, Jeff.
Joe, come here, let's have you re-examined.
I'm torn,
it's very painful.
- Is it visible?
- I'm all bloated, Jeff, see.
I was concave, yesterday,
and now I'm all bloated.
I suffer a lot.
Doctor Joe, explain to me.
What's going on ?
With someone Joe's age,
alas, we also have an aged prostate,
whether you like it or not.
It can block
the emptying of the bladder
and it becomes very painful.
Age clearly plays a role here.
His problem stems
from a combination of factors.
Ironically, you're
the last to get a reward,
and apparently
part of that reward,
probably all that food,
is one of those factors.
I'll tell you, Jeff.
I do not eat meat,
and yesterday we had some kind
of steak skewers,
a meter of skewers.
I couldn't stop
eating it, it was awesome.
And now I feel the impact.
Joe, you who have known
many trials in your life,
give me an idea
of ​​the level of pain.
I tolerate pain well,
I've had sores and bumps,
but here it is rough.
At this point, I need
something to help me.
Is a situation
where it's painful, but it'll be fine,
or is it actually
a potential medical emergency?
It is something
that can be cured.
If it's not, it can cause
long-term problems.
There, you can't just
wait for it to pass.
If you can take the pain,
the main problem,
is that when the urine is blocked,
the pressure rises to the kidneys,
which can cause them
long-term damage.
And so, Dr. Joe,
you extract Joe from the game?
With the risk to the kidneys,
it's the only safe thing to do.
Joe, you
probably expected that.
At my age...
You are not surprised
that he extracts you.
No, Jeff.
I couldn't last tonight.
It would be horrible.
How does it
feel to be so close to the end
and being extracted for, ironically,
a reason unrelated to your efforts,
but just
because you're 71?
Jeff, this is extremely disappointing.
But it's physical, it happens here.
And I don't want to endanger...
My future.
- You have a lot to live for.
- I hope.
I have gone far.
I would have preferred further
but other challenges await me.
I still don't know which ones.
but I always go forward.
You have just summed up
what you have given me.
Continue to search
what exalts you,
listen to the restlessness of your soul
that pushes you
towards the next adventure.
Never stop living
and get the most out of life.
I think you will
greatly inspire people.
I remember the phrase
"getting there at 71".
“Achieving it at 71”, yes.
That's what you've been doing
for 34 days.
It was a pleasure
to see you play,
to see you get
along with people
of more than 50 years your juniors,
but this adventure
in Survivor comes to an end.
Thank you, Jeff, for this opportunity.
Glad you got it.
Joe leaving the game,
it was like seeing a sick relative.
It's your worst nightmare,
but we are also relieved,
because Joe will be treated and will be better.
Do not Cry.
If you make him cry,
I won't hold on!
You laugh ?
Be well, everyone.
Play well.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you for making me
make decisions
and helped
to put one foot in front of the other.
And you'll continue
when you're done here.
Be well.
- Thanks a lot.
- Thanks, Joe.
- See you soon.
- Thanks.
Goodbye.
We'll burn this forest to ashes
for you.
There have never been
so many evacuations
in a single season of Survivor.
Three.
This has been the recurring theme
of this season:
when you think you are safe,
or when you fear
not to be,
something changes,
and it just happened again.
Your quest for the million dollars
is in sight.
But now, more than ever,
you will have to trick
and dominate
if you want to last.
Like a sense of déjà vu.
My biggest ally, Neal,
leaves right after the merge.
And now my other
biggest ally, Joe, is gone.
I am sad for him.
But that changes everything.
I had a very good plan.
Now everything is falling apart.
I wonder
what will happen.
Everything is possible.
Traduction: lshomie, Jack Bauer
Relecture: Jack Bauer, lshomie, Lény
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
After 35 of the toughest days
in Survivor history,
They are only four.
And with shifting alliances,
everyone can win.
I realized last night
that the game had become individual.
Aubry lost his closest ally
for the second time this season.
It's sad that Joe is gone.
Joe gone, my options are limited.
And she's scheming
to find a new one.
Your best choice
would be to stay with me.
I played
making tough decisions.
I won't ruin it
with an emotion-driven decision
at the last moment.
Michele played a
loyalty-centered game.
I will not write your name.
But she is now struggling to
find someone to trust.
If Tai wins,
I think I'm screwed.
She will have to fight
to get to the end.
I walk on eggshells
but I will fight to the fullest,
until my torch goes out.
Cydney is playing with fire,
with rival alliances.
Aubry clearly wants to
go all the way with you.
But I'm also
close to you, though.
Will this lead her to the end
or backfire on her?
To stay in the middle,
there is a trick.
You have to play,
otherwise you are being played.
Especially at the end.
This is the most important part.
And Tai no longer has any benefits or idols.
For the first time,
he is vulnerable.
I'm at the bottom of the ladder, huh?
Girls, are you together?
Without a solid alliance,
Tai might have to
show new resources.
I make all my decisions
by following my heart,
but I have to take a step back,
because at the end of the day,
I want that million dollars.
At all costs.
Everything is played
out in a captivating conclusion,
as the four face off
for the million dollars
and the title of Ultimate Survivor.
Don't miss the
Survivor season finale:
Explode in flight and the decision
rests with Doctor Joe,
taking me out of the game was tough.
But especially
at this point in my life,
I need challenges.
And it was a big one.
Suffer in the heat,
in the rain...
I wanted to prove myself:
"You say you can do it,
but can you?"
And I did.
So it was
a great satisfaction.