translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
This season...
Doctor !
...was a test of will.
Jeff made that...
It's not easy.
With perseverance, Neal...
The idol!
... It is
and Jason have each found an idol.
But Scot knew
about Tai's...
I have the idol.
...and Jason.
If we put them together,
it becomes a super-idol.
In the Chan Loh tribe,
Beauty was allied with Intelligence...
Debbie is my best option.
...and Muscles.
I like you.
But they were divided
on the way forward.
- Debbie wants us.
- We shouldn't trust her.
At the last immunity test...
Debbie made it!
... Gondol perdit.
Approaching the board,
Tai, Julia and Scot
had a plan to get Peter out.
They tried to convince Aubry
to follow them.
Peter is using you.
But Aubry hesitated.
If we take Peter out,
they'll come after us next.
Whatever I do,
it will fall on my face.
On the advice...
- The original blueprint.
- OK.
...Aubry was still so uncertain
about the vote...
- Is that Julia?
- Yeah.
...that she changed hers
at the last moment.
Sixth person eliminated...
Peter, the tribe has spoken.
And now everything is open.
There are 11 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Suddenly, you said:
"the original plan".
It bothered me that you said that.
Why ?
This is the original plan.
This is the problem.
You don't stick to
the decisions made.
I was just clearing
things up for Julia,
to make sure
she votes correctly.
But you didn't.
I will definitely
liquidate Intelligence now,
because of this, this indecision,
because I can't trust them.
You still voted for Julia,
and Joe too.
- Funny way to build trust.
- I didn't vote for Julia.
- You wrote his name down.
- I crossed it out.
Peter is gone,
that's what was planned.
But I wrote "Julia",
I crossed it out and I wrote "Peter"
and I stuck a target
on my back, and the same for Joe.
The future of Intelligence?
We are cooked. It's bent.
It's every man for himself.
You took an unexpected direction
by voting for her.
If I have to go back to the council, I will
write clearly:
Then I'll steer until I decide
which one goes first.
Well, he wants something!
Chicken, chicken!
He wants this food.
Aubry, when you're done,
we can...
Oh my God !
It's human food!
You will have your share afterwards.
Stopped ! Nope !
He wants it!
Don't, don't, don't.
Do not !
The low !
Go over there ! Eat this!
You can peck that.
He wants the crumbs.
Tai has a father/son relationship
with the chicken.
He does not leave this bird.
He must prefer it to us.
After the council, Aubry and I
are in danger.
And now Tai, Scot and Julia
form a trio
and they have two Intelligence.
Bye-bye, Intelligence!
Aubry clearly changed his vote,
so boom-boom, Joe is screwed,
because I broke ranks.
At this point in the game,
this chicken is doing better than me.
- He doesn't miss one.
- He likes coconut.
- Yeah.
Neal walks around
with a big bump in his pocket
and I'm like, "Mmh,
I know what the idol looks like."
So having seen
the shape of Neal's pocket,
I said to Jason:
"We need to blow
this crap."
- What pocket?
- Left.
- In his shorts?
- Mmm.
Have you seen the height of the tide?
- Yeah.
- She's tall as ever.
Yeah, she climbs.
Wow, more crab!
There will always be crab.
What's in your pocket?
Neal has a bump
in his shorts pocket
and if I think it
really looks like an idol,
it's because I have the same.
Now the target is on him.
Because that makes it dangerous
for everyone.
But I have to wait.
I have to sow
and wait for the perfect time
to harvest.
I'm happy as a king
at this point.
I hold all the power.
Friends,
it looks like someone is coming to us!
What is... ?
I was cushy on Chan Loh beach,
happy with myself,
ready to surprise Neal,
and this boat shows up.
What is this bronx?
"Chan Loh, you have five minutes
to ship whatever you want.
You are leaving for your new home,
Camp Gondol."
Five minutes is not long!
I reached the fusion, it's crazy!
It's my childhood dream!
But unfortunately,
I was in a good position at Chan Loh.
Now everything has changed.
I don't know what's going
on on the other side, it's scary.
I have it, I have it.
This season
has been particularly tough.
So achieving fusion
is huge.
I succeeded.
But I never doubted it.
The game has changed again.
It's going to be crazy out there.
I love change,
redistributing the cards.
I'll take the offensive,
recruit people,
that's what they want.
Everyone is waiting.
I will bring them to me.
They won't move.
Ohé !
- What ?
- Oh my God !
- It's fusion.
We are saved!
I have achieved fusion!
I achieved fusion
in Survivor!
It's awesome !
It is enormous !
And as soon as I saw Jason and Cydney,
I thought,
"Damn, here we are!"
It's like the playoffs.
You have to start over, refocus,
hoping my team is strong
and ready to win the championship.
I have returned!
And all of a sudden,
Joe and I were saved.
After the last tip,
I felt terrible,
to the point where I thought to myself:
"I'm a free agent,
parting ways with Joe. It's settled."
And then, seeing Neal and Debbie...
I was so relieved!
It was like reuniting with his
wacky family after a separation.
- There's goat cheese here!
- I'll take it !
Who has the cookies?
- That's crazy.
- Too good, the wine!
- Well done, fusion!
- Congratulations to all !
- We all deserved it!
- Bottoms up!
When Intelligence, Beauty and Muscles
finally come together,
I think effective.
Four Beauty,
four Intelligence, three Muscles.
How's it going to turn out?
It's Survivor,
I have to trust someone.
Scot is therefore my only ally
for the moment.
And it is the most logical,
because he knows about my idol.
Okay, Nick, I have to confess.
No, not now !
I just wanted
to give you a hug, just once.
I'm happy married,
but you're very handsome!
Too much wine !
This?
Hands off !
- I take it !
- Nope !
I will save you from the evil pirate.
Argh, I'll get it!
During the fusion feast,
people are a bit tipsy.
Me, I listen attentively,
I see who gets on well,
what information I can collect.
The Muscles
are clearly going to be arrogant,
as if they were in command
and no one could stop them.
Cydney and I
wake up in the middle of the night.
Scot is sound asleep
and he has a rat on his shoulder!
And we say to ourselves:
"We're not even going to tell him!"
The Intelligences
won't want to work with them.
They are their exact opposite.
They want to be in the shadows.
I stop.
I can't eat anymore.
Eat that damn cookie!
For now,
my real ally is Michele.
We have an excellent position
between these two tribes.
But I learned: take it easy,
analyze people,
let them bring you information.
And only then
do shavings.
Peter freaked out.
- I only have you.
- You are one of us.
I've got your back.
- Neal and you, are you still going?
- Absolutely.
More united than ever.
The two fingers of the hand.
Ass and shirt.
Papier Q and WC.
Aubry is concerned
about the turn of events.
She feels guilty.
She should not.
The four Intelligences:
Aubry, Neal, Joe and me,
we stay united.
Muscles seem super tight,
that's three.
- Just ?
- Clearly.
And you?
Probably all ready
to stick together.
Muscles are going to be
permanent physical hazards.
And they're a bit of a bully.
A Beauty/Intelligence alliance
therefore makes sense.
Will the Beauties stay together,
support you?
The Beauties?
I do not think so.
I feel like
that Tai is super close to Scot
and I have a feeling Julia
was saved by Scot last night.
And Michelle? Looks like...
I think she will stay with me.
I hope.
Neal and Aubry said,
"We just need two Beauties.
Nick, can you recruit Michele?"
"Yeah, I can probably
recruit Michele."
They want it to be
Brains versus Brawn.
As I thought.
- How many votes do we need?
- Six to win.
Six to win this vote.
Directed against one of the three Muscles.
Who matters?
Preferably one that doesn't have an idol.
Makes sense
to go with Intelligence,
but to corner oneself,
put your own back against the wall,
this is not good Survivor.
Make stars!
I start writing the names.
- Do you do red?
- Yeah.
- Isn't that cute?
- That's wonderful.
- Wonderful.
- Owl.
Who would have thought we'd be here?
I'm so happy.
Did you get along well?
Tai and me...
...it sticks.
Julia, I think we have her loyalty,
because we saved her last night.
Oh yeah,
she owes you.
So we are in a good position.
It's time to merge.
And the muscles,
we have to get back on track,
so we were open with Nick,
because we want him to feel comfortable.
There, we need him
for the majority.
And I believe Neal has an idol.
It is therefore
the main center of interest.
What do you think ?
That Nick has an idol.
So how do you get it out first?
We divide the votes, okay.
Did Scot and Jason
drink too much rum at the feast?
Scot immediately approached me.
Jason says Neal has an idol.
Thank you for including me
in your alliance!
You two are adorable!
It's between the three of us,
not even Cydney. OK ?
Tai found an idol.
He showed it to me.
For God Sake !
It's unreal!
Tai has an immunity idol,
it's awesome.
For with two separate idols,
mine and for example his,
we combine them
and we have a super-idol
that can be played
after the votes have been read.
We are therefore
literally unstoppable.
Only you and Tai
know about Tai's idol?
And now you two.
Let it stay that way.
You do not know...
I
just told you that because I know we are close together.
I don't like the smugness
of Scot and Jason.
It's like: "Fuck the others,
the game is ours!"
But even if it annoys me,
it's great for me, really.
Because they will never think they
can be taken out by surprise.
They will never see it coming.
Wanna see something gross?
Looks like I'm going to die!
- My firefighters!
- Hello.
You?
I really like you.
I want us to ally.
- OK.
- We would be in the majority.
- Would we be in the majority?
- Yeah.
OK.
I seem to be one of the few here
to play attack.
I need six people
to dominate Muscles numerically.
It's a battle for power
and I play to win.
Good. It's certain ?
Bargain.
It's really a shock.
What is your strategy
now that the game is individual?
First, ally me with someone...
You just did.
This morning I wake up
I sit down, Debbie arrives
two seconds later
and said,
"Hey, I really like you!
You must come into our alliance."
It was quite aggressive.
He's leaving.
We have it.
I don't buy his story.
I'm not stupid.
I see clearly in his game.
So Nick...
Are you with us?
Neal and you?
And probably Michele, too.
Debbie thinks she has Michele?
Don't be afraid to leave,
you will stay.
She's not very subtle
on this one.
And in motion.
It must.
Debbie needs to calm down.
She does too much.
suffocate people
is not the right way
to create a majority.
You have to be confident.
And there, we are desperate.
Eh, uh...
If Muscles and Beauty come together...
- There are so many of us!
- 7 against 4.
We create a family
and then we will advise.
Beauties always turn
to sportsmen.
Still.
This is how.
Beauties don't come out
with big heads.
They are at the ball with us
and we stuff the nerds
in the lockers.
Sorry, Intelligence!
Neal has an idol.
So we're gonna fire Aubry,
because they won't see it coming.
We want to attack Neal,
but we think he found the idol.
So we take out someone
they'll never see coming.
They'll think
it's Neal, then Joe,
- then Deb.
- One of those, they will think.
Jason probably thinks he's
on top.
He is the one who constantly says:
"This is what is happening,
this is what so and so said,
here's how we're going to do it."
Looks
like Muscles and Beauty are together.
But Muscles dominates far too much.
Oh, damn it!
I never ruled out
working with Muscles.
I feel like
I never spoke to you.
Yeah, huh!
Most...
Not one-on-one.
Okay for Intelligence to
stay together,
but someone's gonna have
to shake their ass and talk to people,
like normal humans.
Debbie freaked out a bit.
She's suffocating people!
Yeah,
she needs to take the pressure off.
It's pretty clear
that Debbie irritates people.
And if the Beauties
don't join us,
we are doomed.
I want to work with you.
I know, me too.
But the thing is Debbie,
she's horrible.
I still hope to
work with Intelligence,
but Debbie pisses me off at this point.
She almost monopolizes
the strategy of Intelligence.
And I want no one
to have more power than me.
Everyone
is so sick of Debbie.
Because of that,
I feel like we're screwed.
Nick is going to drop us, do you think?
I spoke with him
and I believe that... Yes.
For him, instinctively,
maybe that's more seductive
than having to deal with Deb.
It's really not good.
We know we have to recruit
at least two Beauty.
But Debbie
turns people off so much...
This is not good. We are badly off.
Do you have an idol?
I have one from the first camp.
I didn't tell anyone.
How can we use it
to our advantage?
Someone has to tell us
who will be eliminated tomorrow
and we use it.
Survivor
is a roller coaster!
I thought we were screwed.
But it turns out
Neal has the immunity idol.
That's what we needed
to start taking action.
The game is launched. Let's go!
Over here, everyone!
Good. I was talking
with the medical team,
they told me
you were pretty messed up.
Tai, how is this band doing
physically?
We had a lot of cuts
fairly quickly, the first 2 weeks.
I know Neal has two infections.
Two infections?
A kind of small volcano
appeared on my knee.
I baptized it "Mont-Saint-Neal
which-never-stops".
He's been coughing up pus
for four or five days.
But it's fine.
Scot, is the band aware
that an infection here
can be fatal?
That despite the jokes,
baptisms, it's serious?
Yeah, I have one too.
I have one too.
- Where is yours, Aubry?
- Inside the leg.
Another mountain!
Someone else ?
- I have 2 big ones since the 3rd day.
- Your scratches.
Yes, when I climbed the mango tree.
It's starting to heal.
It was raw, it was burning.
But I feel much better.
Jason, we're almost reaching
critical mass:
if you don't have one,
you're not good enough!
It's true. The elements
did not spare us.
But we all persevered, made do with it,
embraced the annoyances
and carried on.
So, ready to continue?
It's time to arrive
at your first
individual immunity test.
First of all, Debbie,
I'm taking back tribal immunity.
We're done with that.
The game moves on to its individual phase.
And this is what you covet.
Individual immunity.
To ensure your safety,
you need this.
Let's go. Today,
you will be standing on studs
with a ball
balanced on a disc.
Regularly,
we will add balls,
increasing the difficulty.
If you fall off your support
or a ball falls,
you are eliminated.
The last person to hold
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers: on the council,
someone will be eliminated
after 19 very hard days.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Everyone get on their support!
Find balance,
decide where to put your feet,
where you feel most assured.
Well, everyone
grab their first ball.
Place it on your disk.
Well, on and go.
Three,
two one,
take your hands off.
This test is on.
Our first
individual immunity test.
If, at any time,
your hand touches your ball,
you are eliminated.
If your ball touches the ground,
If you drop off your support,
you are eliminated.
Joe is the first down.
Joe is eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
You are only ten.
Debbie falls.
Take a seat on the bench.
More than nine.
Nice recovery from Scot,
who had quickly wavered.
Big feet to balance
on this little stud.
Sometimes being tall is an advantage,
sometimes not.
Everyone seems to be off to a good start.
It doesn't matter if it moves a little,
as long as you are in control.
This first phase
will last five minutes.
Two have passed.
Only 30 seconds left
in this round.
Continue like that.
No excitement.
fails to maintain itself.
There are ten seconds left.
Jason is the third eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
Five,
four,
three,
of them,
and,
it's all good.
Get ready
for round two!
It's time
to add a second ball.
Let everyone place two balls
on their disc!
And here we go. Three,
of them,
and,
spread your hands,
Here we go again.
And now
it's much more difficult.
Immediately, a
lot of movement.
Michele is quickly eliminated.
Neal is eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
And suddenly,
Scot falls,
you are only five.
In the space of 20 seconds
in this round,
three people eliminated.
Cydney is eliminated.
More than four.
Aubry is eliminated.
Everything will be played
between three Original Beauty.
A lot of things change
with the merger!
Often the game
is completely open.
You want to be safe tonight.
A little movement.
Tai's balls collide.
It's never good.
It moves a lot at Nick.
His balls
dance in all directions.
It is stable again.
Julia is perfectly still,
like a statue.
Everyone seems very stable.
Two minutes elapsed
in this round.
After five minutes
we will add another scoop.
Only ten seconds left
in this round.
Five, four,
three two,
and,
this round is over,
good for you all.
Well done, friends!
Well, on and go.
It's time
to add a third ball
and we will continue until the end.
Stabilize yourself.
Five,
four,
three,
two one,
take your hands off.
This test resumes.
Everyone has three balls.
From the outset, it moves a lot
at Nick, but good recovery.
He recovers immediately.
Things are moving a bit at Julia's.
Julia, the most stable
in this ordeal, falls,
offering us a face-to-face
between Nick and Tai.
For immunity.
You were 11 at the start,
9 fell.
It moves a lot at Nick.
Things are moving a lot at Tai.
Can he recover?
Nope ! Tai loses a ball!
Nick wins
the first individual immunity!
Safe at tonight's council!
I wish I could see you.
I wanted to watch.
- Cheer !
- Congratulations, friends!
Nick, come here!
First individual victory.
Protected at tonight's council.
As for you guys,
after 19 clearly tough days,
someone will leave tonight.
It won't be you. Congratulation.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Tonight, it will be the 4 Intelligence
against the brutes, the Muscles.
Fortunately, I have the idol.
If I think I have to play it,
I will play it.
I could run away
or pass it on to Aubry.
And with any luck,
we'll take control.
Cool, the necklace!
Tonight is the first board
after the merger.
Everything will be played there,
the orientation of the sequel
will be decided there.
Anyway, I believe in it.
It's Muscle
against Intelligence,
and I'm in the middle,
with Beauty, for the most part.
We're like the pretty girl at the ball.
You come in either with the quarterback,
or with the valedictorian.
It's a fun position.
It's fun to be the pretty girl.
I had never felt
like a pretty girl before.
But now, yes!
It's very nice.
So, what do you think ?
Everyone votes Aubry.
An obvious alliance of 7, against 4.
The Intelligences are screwed.
We'll take them out one by one.
In the best of cases,
Neal, paranoid, plays an idol,
but Aubry comes out anyway.
We fake them from the flank
and take out Aubry.
They'll never see it coming
that we're aiming for her.
I have confidence between our
Beauty/Muscles alliance,
because everyone seems comfortable
and thinks: "Why not?
We just have to take out the Intelligence.
And when there are
only seven left, we will advise."
Even though Jason and I
have already been notified.
And we will have gained four places
within a week.
Yeah, we take them out one by one.
For now,
I'm leaning towards Muscles,
towards the elimination of an Intelligence.
But Scot and Jason
will always be too sure of themselves.
And it's when someone feels
safe that you have to attack.
The thing,
is that these three
will clearly dominate
physically.
Oh yeah, the Three Muscles, yeah.
So they gon' use the girls
for the votes,
then get rid of them
and form the final trio.
Yeah, that's a solid trio.
With our group,
the chances of winning events
are better.
If there are six of us, it's all good.
So I just have to recruit Michele?
Seven is better,
but six is ​​good.
I believe
Nick wants to come with us.
So we have to convince Michele
to join us.
We must be six.
But in a desperate moment,
I'll just have to reach out
for the family jewels
and catch the idol.
Michele is our best bet.
Alright, I'll talk to him.
Do you have any idea what's going on?
No one approached me
for a decision.
So let's take one of all three
and act.
We have to play.
I think that...
I do not know.
What do you think ?
Jason or Scotus.
We have to.
We need to take out Scot or Jason.
I agree.
To gain power,
Intelligence needs
Nick and Michele.
I want a Muscles out.
We have to take action.
If we don't recruit Nick and Michele,
Neal and I will play the idol.
They are too tight.
It's the only way to separate them.
And they want
control at all costs.
And the options abound
to create links
between Beauty and Intelligence,
because we are less rigid than them.
Yeah, I agree.
I would love to work
with Aubry and Debbie,
but is it my best option,
strategically?
I'm going to have to
assess the relationships more.
I can go any direction
I want at this point.
I'm trying to figure out
what's best for me.
It's a good time
to talk about the future.
What do you want to do ?
Jason pissed off a lot of people
which I doubt
they would vote for him.
Scot, I also doubt
that people will vote for him,
because he is rich.
So...
That's what I think.
We go with Muscles.
Alright, it's rolling. And so ?
Makes sense to go with Muscles,
because I think I can handle
them very easily.
And beat them on puzzles
very easily.
They are idiots.
I like Aubry.
I prefer her
to all the girls here.
But alas, at the council tonight,
Aubry will leave.
So we say to Intelligence:
"Okay, we thought about it."
And we will surprise them at the council,
we will say:
"We're going to eliminate one of you."
So we're going to have to lie to them.
But we are in a pivotal position.
We do not have a choice.
I know
it's a big decision.
I'm thinking of taking the right one.
I'll see if that's the case.
It's all good.
Have you seen this before?
No. What's this ?
Jeff is there?
We were preparing for the council
and here comes Jeff,
the doctor comes to us.
Immediately, it was the alarm.
Jeff doesn't do that.
Doctors don't do that.
At least one of us
is in serious enough condition
for them to come to us.
This season of Survivor is rough.
- Do you consult at home?!
- Well...
Many of you
seemed sick.
After seeing everyone,
today, to the test,
I was a bit concerned.
So I came with Dr Rupert
to assess the situation.
We just want to review
those of you
who showed us their infections,
to see what it is.
Because everyone here
knows it's serious business.
Hopefully
the damage will be limited.
Who do you want to start with?
By Tai and her thighs.
I believe... I climbed the mango tree
to pick mangoes.
- I couldn't do it and...
- Did you scratch your skin?
Wow, damn it!
It was painful.
That's why I wear
my underwear to proofs.
Let Rupert take a look.
I have to say,
it heals quite well.
- So it's positive.
- It's positive, Jeff.
You are not worried,
because crusts form.
Yeah, absolutely.
And there is no redness
or swelling.
I think it's okay, he's recovering.
- Okay, Tai, everything is fine.
- I feel good.
Scott! You had one.
I have two.
Damn it !
It's painful ?
A little.
It's badly infected.
Here, the small cuts
degenerate quite quickly.
Do you have to deal with it or...?
We'll keep an eye on it.
We'll examine Aubry.
You had a nice one.
Let's see.
- Oh, lovely!
- Wow !
Damn it !
I feel it below,
it's firm so far.
Are you saying that underneath
it looks that big?
It's violent, very violent here.
Small things
take on huge proportions.
If I lose Aubry to injury,
it changes the whole game.
Explain me.
It seems to be getting worse.
I have two options here.
give him antibiotics
or incise the wound,
open it,
empty it, clean the dirt.
If I incise,
it opens a way
to evacuate the pus,
but it also opens the way
to infection.
So
what is your assessment?
My gut tells me
to give him antibiotics.
We will therefore adopt
the cautious approach
and if it gets worse,
you will always have option 2.
Exactly.
OK. Alright, Aubry.
So we're going to prescribe
antibiotics to Aubry.
The summit of Mont-Saint-Neal
exploded this afternoon, in fact.
A big lump of pus came out,
revealing this giant cavity.
It's more or less open
now.
It's not very pleasant.
And I have worse in the back.
It doesn't hurt, though.
Let's see.
When did you discover
the one behind your back?
Two days ago.
What if we found
a clean place?
That he can sit
in a clean environment.
The infection in my back
is really ugly.
But I think it will be fine.
If the doctor
tries to pull me out of the game,
he will have to drag me.
Alright, let's sum it up.
He has two infections
in two different places.
- Explain the concerns to us.
- Absolutely.
I feel good, that said.
I slept eight hours that night.
We had a feast recently
and I will win an award tomorrow.
I'm trying to see
how it might evolve.
This is in the skin,
but there is nothing underneath
that could be damaged.
So, what's your take
on this?
It's a beautiful piece of crap,
but I don't think
his life is in danger.
- I think he's going out.
- You think ?
- Nope.
- That's my impression.
Provided that you are wrong!
So this does not worry you
immediately.
This worries me less.
let's go back,
and tell me about the knee, let's
see what it is.
Near a joint,
such as the knee,
- is it more serious?
- In effect.
If the infection
passes into the joint,
it can destroy it
in a few hours.
Hours ?!
Yes. Very dangerous.
I really believe it will be fine
in a few days.
I believe you believe it.
The problem is: if it gets worse
and goes into the joint...
It's for life.
You could have
it for years to come.
I want you to be able to run
and do that
when you're Joe's age.
I won't let this pass.
It could get worse.
I love this game, Jeff.
Neal, I see you already moved...
...by understanding what he is saying.
So, Dr. Rupert, let's be clear:
you extract Neal from the game.
I think I have to.
You fought well.
You haven't done anything wrong.
You have tried so hard.
What do you feel ?
Because you are a fan.
It was something to be here.
It's been a hell
of a job, coming here.
I watched the show, summer 2000,
I worked in open space,
it was pointless,
I didn't like my life.
I've come a long way,
like you, over the past 15 years.
And all of a sudden, not only
could I go into Survivor,
but also be a real competitor.
Most...
It's been a great 19 days.
We will take you
to a good hospital,
fix that,
you will come back,
you will be a member of the jury.
You won't be able to win,
but you will have a vote
to decide who will win.
So... I imagine you'll want
to say goodbye to everyone.
You should consider yourself lucky.
Because they take me out of the game.
So...
It was an honor and a privilege
to play with each of you.
I know you don't want to leave.
I'm sorry.
Neal had to take a lot on himself
not to crack,
because he wants to play so much,
and he told us
how lucky we were to be here.
And he's right.
But really ?
My number 1 ally!
Party!
Be well.
So, Neal leaves,
and I refrain from saying:
"And the idol?"
And I hope he will give it to me.
And so, the bad news from Neal
is good news for you.
No advice tonight.
No one will leave this group.
One in ten chance of winning.
After 19 days, once again
the game has changed.
My poor.
Aubry was going to leave,
and by the grace
of a medical evacuation,
she may survive
another day or two.
Try to stay healthy,
clean your wounds,
and see you.
OK ? Good.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
I didn't expect to
cry so much in Survivor,
but there have been ups and downs,
And just when I thought
we were finally going to restart the machine,
my greatest ally comes out,
I have a swelling on my leg
that everyone could see,
and I say to myself:
"Neal gone, Beauty
will never go with Intelligence,
and the idol left with Neal."
The bastard!
Really ?!
Neal left me hanging.
But Survivor is a path
you pave yourself.
It's like
following the Oregon trail.
You have to cross every river,
caulk each cart,
up and down the hills,
and sometimes you get dysentery
and you die.
We have to pave our own way.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: lshomie, Lény
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Go to cbs.com
to see Neal at Ponderosa!
Next time in Survivor...
Marginalized, the Intelligence
hope for a miracle.
Sportsmen and cannons
will not cannonate forever.
But while everything seems written...
- I want us to be careful.
- I'm asking a question.
Paranoia will eventually set in.
...everything starts to fall apart.
Don't watch me!
Pissed off, Cydney will blow everything up!
I am one of those who truly believe
that the journey is the reward,
and it was an amazing experience
that I will cherish,
and which I will think back
to laughing and smiling,
maybe crying a little,
for the rest of my life.
But that's the game.
It's not enough to
dominate and outwit,
it must also last.