translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Tai, Jason and Scot
thought they had full powers.
From now on, we are unstoppable.
Julia was their mole.
Want to know their plan?
They had an advantage...
"You have won
an extra vote."
...and two immunity idols
that could be paired
to form a super-idol.
If something happens, play it.
What's great about the super-idol
,
it can be played
after the votes have been read.
But Aubry wanted to turn the game around
and schemed
behind Michele and Julia's back
for Tai to turn
against Jason and Scot...
Cydney, Joe and I:
you have three people with you.
Tai has all the cards in hand.
...leaving Tai
with a big decision.
I do not know what to do.
At the council,
Scott received the majority of votes.
Ninth person eliminated
and fourth member of the jury:
He then turned to Tai for
the other half of the super-idol.
But Tai betrays Scot and Jason...
You don't?
Wow.
...sending Scot to the jury
with Jason's idol...
Scotus, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Michele and Julia
out of the picture
and Jason alone.
There are seven left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
It's a game, friends.
We eliminated Scot by surprise.
It's a big hit.
The smallest
knocked out the biggest of the season.
It was excellent,
really excellent.
It was good.
- So happy for you.
- I'm happy for us!
I'm so happy for you.
And me for you!
Scott and Jason
weren't listening to me.
Tonight, I took control
of my own game.
We got the power now
and it's me who has the most,
because I have the idol
and the extra vote.
You won't be able
to eliminate it now.
You won't be able to
eliminate Tai now.
But hey, well done.
Well done, Cyd.
Yeah...
Great shot. As a fan,
I tell you, a great shot.
But as an
opponent of the alliance...
Grrrr!
Tai betrayed.
I didn't see it coming.
The only thing
that could go wrong went wrong.
Tai played the shot,
Scotus had my idol, and alas,
he was eliminated
and therefore could no longer return it to me.
So I don't have any more.
I lost an ally and an idol.
All this in a single instant.
Now
I will have to hold on.
I'm all alone now,
you know that.
If you want to try something crazy,
you know I'm crazy about it.
I won't forget, I promise.
Julia, you look
completely shocked.
Yes I am.
Like Michele, I'm upset that I was
n't warned.
I voted Nick with you,
I voted Debbie with you,
and tonight
I voted for who I said.
You voted against me.
It happened, and I'm upset,
But it is okay. No matter.
I was playing on both counts.
But Aubry, Joe, Tai and Cydney
have formed an unbeknownst alliance
and eliminated Scot.
You want to know why
I voted against Scot?
Honestly,
I don't really care.
Now Michele and I
have lost a few notches
after this vote.
We are at the bottom of the scale.
It's like that...
- It's like that.
- We're done.
Friends, we made it!
Final square assured.
- Jason no longer has an idol?
- Nope.
OK.
No idol. I don't think
there is another one.
I can't stop smiling anymore.
We eliminated Scot
and it feels crazy!
It completely changed
the dynamic of the game.
From now on,
no more surprises.
We know what we have to do
and we don't change.
We have the majority,
we have to release Jason.
We have the majority
and Jason no longer has an idol.
Let's hope Jason loses,
we take him down,
and let's continue on
our merry way.
I force myself to keep reminding myself
that Survivor is just a game,
that I made a big blow,
but this is the very first time
i've done this to someone,
lie so much.
It's a big betrayal.
I want to talk to Jason,
because he trusted me
and I betrayed him.
It's painful.
I feel guilty.
Listen to me.
I'm here.
It's the hardest thing
I've ever done.
Betray someone.
You and Scot
grew closer and closer
and that worried me.
You could have let me down.
I don't know,
maybe you wouldn't have done it,
but I had to act first.
I understand what you did
and why you did it.
I did it out of respect for the game.
In this game, you can do everything well
and still lose.
Hey, Mark!
I was afraid that on returning
you wring his neck in anger.
I wouldn't have done that
to the little chicken.
Mark and I are still allies.
Hey, boy?
thank you for listening to me
and understand why
I screwed up your game.
It's not funny, but...
- It's a game.
- It's just ironic.
Tai apologized well this morning,
half-baked excuses,
but I can't let see
how much it pissed me off.
- Where are they all? Gone ?
- I do not know.
I just want my revenge.
It enraged me
to remain without an idol or an ally
and that Tai
still has all his assets.
For someone
with such a big heart,
he turns his jacket around,
scam full of people.
He fucked me up, me,
and he will meet the same fate
because of it.
And he deserves it.
Where do I sneak?
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
you will run
through a series of obstacles
while collecting rings.
When you have the three rings,
you will throw them
on a moving hook.
The first ones will win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
A helicopter will pick you up.
Oh my God !
You will have an aerial view
of the island you live on
for 28 days.
You will land on a sandy island
in the middle of the ocean
where you will have a good picnic.
You chicken free,
corn cobs,
Apple pie,
sodas, wine.
- Did you say "wine"?
- Yes, wine.
He said "wine"!
- Is it worth it ?
- Absolutely !
Another thing:
you will not run alone,
you will be tied in pairs.
We will draw lots
and therefore, a person
will not participate.
We draw lots and we start.
Our draw
resulted in three pairs.
Joe and Tai,
Julia and Aubry,
Jason lost in the draw,
he will not participate.
Here we go, for the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go over
this first obstacle.
Julia and Aubry pass it quickly.
Tai and Joe.
It is necessary to detach this first ring.
You need three rings
to complete this trial.
Michele and Cydney quickly finish
this first part.
Tai and Joe have their first ring.
Julia and Aubry, just behind.
And already, they are falling heavily.
Cydney and Michele,
over then under!
Above.
Go over the first
and under the next.
Below.
Above.
Michele and Cydney still in the lead,
undoing the second ring.
Julia and Aubry just behind.
Tai and Joe try to catch up with them.
Prepare to climb.
Michele and Cydney
go for the third ring.
For my part !
Aubry and Julia arrive.
You have to climb that ladder.
Hop, I pass and I arrive at the top.
Tai and Joe have their second ring.
Michele tries to take it off.
Aubry also tries.
Tai's turn!
Everyone
is more or less equal.
Aubry and Julia have theirs!
They take the lead!
Try you!
Cydney will try,
can she make it?
It's Cydney versus Tai!
Tai a le temple!
Cydney at her temple!
Everyone has the three rings!
Now we have to hang them.
Give them to me.
Tai and Joe are right behind.
It's difficult.
Everybody
throw the rings now.
Cydney sends one.
Cydney grabs one!
Cydney and Michele
have their first ring.
We go back !
A big reward!
A chance to get away from the game
or even change the game.
Let me try a little.
Joe grabs one!
Tied, 1 - 1.
Michele and Cydney have one.
Cydney grabs a second one!
Attractive !
Joe grabs a second one!
Tie, 2 - 2!
Julia and Aubry
are still trying to get into it.
Why can't we get there?
More than a ring
for Cydney and Michele,
Joe and Tai!
Here we are !
For victory !
Just missed!
Cydney, for the win!
Cydney rolls and wins!
Cydney and Michele
win the reward!
I want that chicken, Jeff!
Michele and Cydney, come here.
Just there.
Congratulation.
Your first victory.
- She wanted fried chicken, so...
- For a while!
This is how it goes:
the helicopter will land,
take you for a ride,
and drop you in the middle of the ocean
where you will have your picnic.
Well, like the last 28 days,
there were
only surprise eliminations,
that means alliances
are constantly changing.
So this decision
should be interesting.
You can choose a person
to accompany you.
Anyone, even Jason,
who didn't participate.
You must agree
on the person chosen.
It was quick!
Michele, does it surprise you,
this consensus, so fast?
No. Someone has not eaten,
and that person must.
Alright, who do you choose?
Aubry, come!
Enjoy your afternoon,
the helicopter is coming.
Here it is.
I'm glad we decided to have
Aubry split the reward,
because last night,
I did not vote with the majority,
and at some point, I have to say to myself:
"Okay, this is my game."
It's a great chance
to make sure I'm with them,
that they trust me,
that they want to move forward with me.
We needed this!
Day 28, girls!
Good. Joe, Tai, Julia, Jason,
I have nothing for you.
Pack your things, head back to camp.
The horizon is dark there, really.
But I'm not giving up yet.
I can't.
For my family, I can't.
I have to keep trying.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to try to manipulate these people,
to find a flaw somewhere.
Oh my God !
It's incredible !
We are free !
That feeling of flying!
It was the foot.
It's too good.
It is an unforgettable experience.
Look, united!
- Beauty, Intelligence and Muscles!
- Perfect !
I'm in a helicopter,
down to a beautiful beach,
She is only for us.
Survivor
is about unique experiences.
It's a great pick-me-up
to get back on your feet
and readjust
for the next 11 days.
It's chicken time!
White or rosé?
That's good.
- The coleslaw is super good.
- The coleslaw?
- Treat yourself, my dear.
- It's the best day.
The best day.
I get by in life
thanks to my social skills.
I build links
and that's what got me this
far in the game.
Julia and I are close,
and even though I trust her
and enjoy working with her,
we are only two.
To rejoin the group,
they will have
to trust me.
So I want to be sure that even if
I was out of the vote,
I'm not
out of the covenant.
Well, it's obvious
that Julia and I are close,
but I've been super loyal.
I don't want
you to doubt me.
I think everyone
wants to work with you.
That's what I want.
I want it to work.
I told you, I trust you.
- Me too.
- It's true, I trust you.
Michele proved her loyalty,
every time she voted with us,
except for the time
we had to leave it in the dark.
So I trust him.
It's too good.
It's clear,
it's the best test.
I feel reintegrated into the group.
That says a lot about my ability
to inspire confidence,
staying happy,
while remaining humble and poised.
I hope my loyalty
will make them keep me a little longer.
Well, what do you think?
I think we are fine.
Michele is a good option.
This is also my opinion.
I don't want to say we're on top,
because I don't want to think that.
The same.
But I think we're going like this,
rather than like this.
Exactly.
But at the same time,
we can't go to the final
with that damn Tai.
It wouldn't be
our best choice.
If we go with Joe or Michele,
we would have a better chance.
You have to think about it.
It's good to start thinking about it,
but right now,
we have to get Jason and Julia out.
For now, we have to keep
our alliance with Tai super strong,
because it can help us move forward.
As Tai has an immunity idol
and an advantage,
it would be better to eliminate
it as soon as possible.
And we can use Michele
to make it happen.
This is what I need
to go all the way.
When to make that big shot,
that's the question.
- We'll figure out what to do.
- Yeah.
We have to win immunity.
- We have to keep fighting.
- Yes.
They will surely vote against me.
We have to be able to get out of this, Julia.
You and me.
I am at the bottom of the scale.
It sucks.
I will not give up,
you have to try.
There is always room.
There is a way to stay.
You just have to figure out how
before it's too late.
I can't believe
I'm so close.
But I want to get even closer.
I just have to figure out how.
Getting rid of Tai
would leave us free.
Absolutely.
But if they keep it on purpose...
- That's stupid.
- Really stupid.
But we don't have the majority.
What would be the ideal scenario?
There are four voices against him,
either he plays his idol
and someone else is eliminated
or he goes home with his idol.
You, me, Michele, we have to try.
But I don't know
who would be our fourth.
A fourth is needed.
Tai is a huge threat
in the game.
He has an immunity idol,
he has an advantage,
and he will win if he goes to the final.
Gotta find someone
who realizes it's stupid
not to use Jason, Michele
and me to eliminate him today.
As a good doggie, Joe will stay at the foot.
Yeah, I know.
Aubry told him not to move
while he was gone.
We could probably
convince Cydney.
Yeah, we need to talk to Cyd.
We can't do anything
before she comes back.
We have a plan for Tai.
There is a real possibility
with Julia and Michele,
but we need a fourth.
The only possibility left
is Cydney.
Cydney likes surprise votes,
that's obvious.
Maybe she wants
to do another big hit.
- Hi !
- Hello !
We got along well at first.
Maybe she'll switch sides.
I have to sell, sell,
sell my plan.
Thinking about
doing something crazy then, Cyd?
What's your plan?
It all depends on
whether you want to release Tai or not.
If you would like to listen to us...
I am always open
to proposals.
When we're on the council,
we will write TAI.
With Michele, we vote Tai.
Everyone else
will vote for one of us,
since you are not going to
eliminate each other.
Tai plays his idol,
remains, and one of us is eliminated,
or Tai gets caught
and all the idols are gone.
And you will still have the majority.
It holds up, that's for sure.
I put myself
in a great position,
my options are open.
Now I have to see
what's best for me.
It's a solo game,
not a team game.
If staying with my alliance
is better for me,
that's what I have to do.
If I have to turn tail
and vote Tai to advance,
I'll do that instead.
It's a win/win,
either way.
At least you know where our votes will go,
and uh...
Do your thing, girl.
That's to say ?
The real fans of this game
know it's designed
to be vicious.
You won't win
if you're just loyal.
You have to cheat, steal
and knock things over
and this surprise vote against Tai
could really change the game.
As soon as Tai leaves,
we eat Mark.
I'm not even kidding,
I can't wait.
What do you want ?
Over here, everyone!
Ready for the immunity test?
First, Jason,
I have to take the necklace back.
Sorry to hear that.
Win it again!
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will run
to a platform,
where you will memorize symbols
and their corresponding numbers .
Then you'll come back
and use these numbers
to find the combination
that will release a key.
If you just do,
the key will open a box
containing puzzle pieces.
The first person
to find the mystery word
will win immunity
and will ensure a one in six chance
of winning this game.
The losers will go to the council,
where after 29 days,
someone will become
the fifth member of the jury.
You don't want it to be you.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
OK, let's go !
For immunity, Survivors, ready?
Jason leads quickly,
raising the legs
to reach the obstacle.
You have to get
over this platform.
Finally, we will test your memory,
and after 29 days
in this environment,
who knows
how many symbols and numbers
you can memorize at once.
Match
numbers with symbols.
When you've had your fill,
you can leave.
There is no logical connection
between the number and its symbol.
You have to make the connection.
You have to find a way,
in your head,
to link each symbol
and not forget.
You don't know which one you will need
when you return to departure.
It is unlikely to
memorize them all at once.
You have to memorize
what you can and start again.
Cydney has had enough and leaves.
Jason, following in his footsteps, leaves too.
This is Michele and Julia,
and Aubrey.
Cydney drove off
and everyone followed.
There, it is the race to return.
Here is Tai.
Even a tiny obstacle
can be exhausting
after 29 days of Survivor.
And as you move forward,
you try
to remember the symbols
and numbers,
over and over again, in your head.
Joe shifts into another gear.
71 years old. Not bad.
Cydney and Jason
return first.
With Michele,
here is Aubry accelerating again!
Julia follows her closely!
Now you have to remember
which number goes with which symbol.
This will tell you how many squares to
turn the wheel.
Michele writes the numbers
in the sand to remember them.
Tai does the same now.
There are 12 symbols,
but you only need 5.
The question is:
have you memorized the good ones?
Do you have the right numbers
to find the combination?
Otherwise, you will have to leave.
Aubry has a little,
but she has to go again.
Cydney leaves as Joe arrives.
Tai leaves, he doesn't have enough.
Julia and Michele try again
after only seeing the numbers
once.
Jason pulls out a key.
There are eight keys
and only one opens the box.
Julia unties a key.
The question is: are you right?
Did you memorize
the correct numbers?
Jason thinks so and he will try.
It would be an impressive victory
to get there without having to leave.
It's up to Julia to try.
If it's good,
the padlock will open.
If it's wrong,
you will have to go back
to the platform,
so it better be good!
Jason made a mistake, he has to go back.
It's good for Julia!
She opened her box!
Start searching for
the mystery word!
Michele will try.
- Joe, are you giving up?
- Yes, I'm out of juice.
Joe gives up.
Michele found it!
It's between Julia and Michele,
both very advanced
while the others
check numbers and symbols.
An incredible performance!
Julia and Michele
found it very quickly!
You must find the word.
What is this mystery word?
Shit !
Jason and Aubry return.
Julia tries to move on.
Michele hurries forward.
You have to find the right order.
What word do you need to find?
Michele is moving fast now.
She thinks she has it.
If she is right,
it will be a big win!
-Jeff?
- Say it!
"Eliminated by surprise"!
Michele wins
individual immunity,
she won't be
eliminated by surprise tonight,
to the council!
Michele, come closer!
- Congratulation !
- Thanks !
I have to ask you,
how many numbers
did you memorize at once?
All.
You finished so quickly!
nice job,
you are guaranteed
to have a one in six chance of winning.
As for the rest of you,
someone will be eliminated tonight
and will become
the fifth member of the jury.
It won't be you.
Congratulation.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
I needed this victory
and I got nothing.
I could barely try.
We need to be sure
that Cydney and Michele are okay
to eliminate Tai,
or
I'm exhausted.
Well done, Michele.
It was impressive.
I can't believe you
memorized all those numbers.
My family is going crazy!
Since the reward,
we are four plus Michele.
Jason and Julia are on the sidelines.
Jason is a ticking time bomb,
so tonight's vote
looks super easy,
but I'm not sure
that's the best option.
So, what do we do, my beauties?
Me, I'm leaning towards Jason,
because if there is another test
in the water, he will beat us all.
Julia finished
right behind you today?
Yes, she is very strong.
She is good at puzzles.
She is very fast,
she has a great memory.
If it's balance,
she'll deliver.
I said "Jason"
before you knew
she was so close to you,
I didn't know.
Jason is a physical threat ,
but he's also
a very polarizing character.
In the jury
there will be people who like it
and people who hate him.
So I don't think
he can win.
The thing with Julia,
is that his physical game
is complete
and that in addition,
she has no blood on her hands.
She proved
she could be quite strategic
to dodge and scheme
to get to stay in the game.
Julia must leave.
So, have you decided?
What is the instruction?
- I believe so, dear.
- It will be Julia.
The group agrees?
Basically, I was okay
with voting Jason
and there, we decide to take Julia out.
It seriously sucks.
In a perfect world,
I would love to continue with Julia:
I trust him completely,
she proved her loyalty to me
many times
and we've been together
since day one.
So I don't want to write the name
of my closest ally.
We all know
she's coming to ask me.
So I tell him it's Jason?
If they ask you and me,
we say we're doing the thing against Tai.
I don't wanna hear my name,
it's never good in Survivor.
I don't trust them
and I don't feel Michele and Cydney.
- Wooden cross, iron cross.
- If I lie...
It's Survivor
and I want to
dot the T's
and the bars on the I's,
I don't know how to say it anymore.
Tonight, I will take
my idol and my advantage.
I won't leave
with an idol in his pocket.
So what's the plan?
We're back to the wall
with this Tai idol thing.
If Tai goes to the final, he wins.
So you, me,
Jason and Cydney are voting Tai.
Earlier I told the others
that I would vote Julia
so that everyone is happy,
to assure them
that I am fully with them.
But if Jason and Julia
really have Cydney's vote,
the vote against Tai might work
and it would also save Julia,
that would be great.
because it kills me
to imagine having to vote against it.
Getting rid of Tai is crucial.
Yes, I will vote Tai.
Good me too.
Hope Cydney is with us.
What's new ?
Are we good?
So we're doing the plan against Tai
you were talking about?
It's logic.
At least one idol is leaving tonight.
Exactly.
I hope we have the majority
to get rid of Tai,
but that doesn't mean
it's safe.
If Tai plays his idol,
he will stay and one of us will leave.
Julia and I make two.
If you and Michele are with us,
it doesn't matter what they do.
It should be interesting.
We agree ?
Tonight, Michele and I
have two options.
We can either go
with Julia and Jason
and eliminate Tai by surprise,
or follow the original plan
of our alliance
and eliminate Julia by surprise.
What do you think ?
It's good for us to have the choice.
For sure.
But everything we do
must have a purpose.
Absolutely.
So are they voting Tai
or are they trying to get me?
Michele says she will vote Tai.
Sydney too.
If it works, Tai will leave
with his idol in his pocket.
And we will still be here.
And then we will go to the final.
If I leave,
maybe at least
he'll lose all his goddamn idols.
Like he made
my fucking idol disappear.
I have a lot at stake
on the board tonight.
I have to make a decision
about my relationship with Julia
and with my alliance.
I don't want to betray either of them.
I'm having a hard time choosing what to do.
It can really affect your game
mentally and emotionally.
All I can do
is try to play my game.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Scot, eliminated at the last council.
Julia, where are we in the game
now?
I believe we are
at a crucial moment.
Every decision we make,
every person we eliminate,
every conversation we have
can make or break your game.
The only person who can feel
100% safe tonight,
it's Michelle.
you think the same,
that everything you do
from now will have an impact
on the gain of the million?
It's certain.
Every thing we do,
every word we say,
everyone remembers it.
Sometimes people want to listen,
other times they don't.
But you have to weigh
all the options,
because anyone among these five
is the fifth.
Julia, who do you think is at the bottom of the scale
?
I think of the five,
Michele and Cydney are downstairs.
Aubry holds Joe's hand
to take him to the final.
Tai is a great competitor
and he has the potential
to win the game.
We must be wary of that
and try to change it.
Tai, it must be a little stressful
to hear Julia call out your name.
Yes, because I have the idol
and I also have the secret advantage.
I am fully aware of that.
It's scary.
I want to remind my allies,
why sink the boat?
Why jump on a sinking boat and row with them,
when do you have a guaranteed place?
Aubry, we also
mentioned your name.
Is it also scary for you
that it seems to be for Tai?
It's true that it's a little scary,
but you have to base yourself on the relationships
you have built with people
and trust that.
At the same time,
I trusted my allies,
and what happened?
Scott? Goodbye !
Tai flipped
over more times than a pancake.
He's done it twice already!
To his strong allies!
What makes you think
there won't be a 3rd time around?
The bond between Scot and you
was so strong,
you two were in control.
It made me feel uncomfortable,
I had to break that.
So you left my wedding ring,
because Scot and I were close.
And you left for an alliance
where Aubry and Joe
are even more so!
Jason argues that Tai cannot
be trusted.
That's what makes
alliances so complicated.
Are you
constantly assessing the situation?
"Are the five united?"
"Should I do a hit?"
"Is this the right move?"
Yes, I'm constantly thinking
and you have to anticipate, in this game.
You have to make a move
at one time or another
if we want his game to be respected.
When you are present at the end,
you have to have something to say.
Cydney, Michele brings up
an interesting point:
it's difficult
to eliminate a person,
to crush his dream
of making a million,
then turn around and say,
"Give it to me!"
You want the jury
to respect your game.
They'll give the million
to someone who played the game
rather than someone
who only betrayed people
and only advanced like that.
Jason, you have a common interest,
it overlaps.
You want to stay,
the five want to make a hit
to plead their case in the end.
There may be a marriage of interest
where one helps the other.
Couldn't have said it better, Jeff.
Every person in this clique
must be able to justify themselves
to those on the benches.
"Why me?
What did I do?
How did I dominate,
how did I foil,
how did I last longer?"
We're two castaways
looking for a home.
The ideal people to ask to
do something crazy.
Everyone knows from the tips
that I love doing crazy stuff.
So Michele,
if the right situation arises,
are you the type to say,
"Yeah, I'm willing to have a shot." ?
You have to follow your instincts
in the game
and you have to feel sure
of your decisions.
If you're not comfortable,
maybe that's telling.
Intuition counts a lot
in this game,
and I try to follow mine.
Cydney, are you open
to big shots?
Downright.
If an idea arises,
you have to think about it and listen to it.
Every decision at this stage
will make or break your game.
You have to determine
what you want to see happen.
Tai, you were very careful.
How are you feeling
right now,
just before the vote?
Not comfortable at all.
I'm going...
I'm not comfortable at all.
Wow, once again
we come to the votes
with many doubts.
It's time to vote.
Jason, over to you.
Sorry, I'm not crossing it
this time.
I will count the votes.
Should I play my idol?
I don't think so,
but it's up to you.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
That is.
Tai.
That's two Tai votes.
Julia.
That's two Tai votes,
two votes Julia.
Julia.
That's three votes Julia,
two Tai votes.
Tenth person eliminated
and sixth member of the jury...
Julia, that's four,
that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
Good luck.
Julia, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
For the first time perhaps,
no one came confident
to the council.
Fear came into play
and when fear controls you,
everything can happen.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: lshomie
Relecture: Jack Bauer, Lény
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
scenes from the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Jason is down.
Nobody wants
to play games with me.
It annoys me too much!
Until the majority
cracks from within.
I think it's Michele.
It's a bigger threat.
Are you trying to lead the dance?
I say no.
If it comes to that,
will you vote with me or with them?
It's super hard.
I'm disgusted,
but proud of how I played.
Being one of the youngest
to ever participate,
I had the opportunity to grow up here.
I learned a lot about myself.
I played big shots
and contributed
to some awesome surprise kills.
I didn't go out
without trying,
I did not go out
after being passive.
At least I played.