>> Jeff: THESE 18 STRANGERS
HAVE VOLUNTEERED TO BE MAROONED
AND LEFT TO FEND FOR THEMSELVES
FOR THE NEXT 39 DAYS.
THEY'RE CRUISING THROUGH THE
WATERS OF KAOH RONG IN SOUTHEAST
ASIA, A BEAUTIFUL BUT FORMID
IBLG PART OF THE WORLD.
SCORCHING TEMPERATURES AND
STIFLING HUMIDITY PUNISH THE
BODY.
DEHYDRATION AND HEATSTROKE CAN
BRING DOWN EVEN THE STRONGEST.
THE SMALLEST CUT CAN LEAD TO A
LIFE-THREATENING INFECTION.
AND IF THEY LAST LONG ENOUGH,
MERELY EXERTING ENERGY WILL
BECOME THEIR BIGGEST OBSTACLE.
THIS WILL BE THE MOST GRUELING
39 DAYS IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
THEY'VE ALREADY BEEN DIVIDED
INTO THREE TRIBES BASED ON THE
QUALITIES THEY MOST RELY ON IN
THEIR DAILY LIVES.
THE BRAIN TRIBE:
>> BEING AN E.R. DOCTOR, IT'S
GOING TO BE DIFFICULT FOR ME TO
NOT SHOW HOW SMART I AM, TO
EXPRESS HUMILITY, BUT I CAN'T
DEAL WITH IGNORANT PEOPLE
BECAUSE THEY THINK THEY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> THIS GAME IS LARGELY A BRAIN
GAME, AND IN THESE CHALLENGES, I
AM GOING TO KICK ASS, BECAUSE
PUZZLES LAY DOWN FOR ME LIKE
LOVERS.
>> Jeff: THE BRAWN TRIBE:
>> I AM A FORMER PROFESSIONAL
BASKETBALL PLAYER.
I WAS THE GUY THAT DID ALL THE
THINGS NOBODY ELSE WANTED TO DO.
I'D GO KNOCK PEOPLE ON THE
GROUND.
I'D PUSH PEOPLE OUT OF THE WAY.
DIIT BETTER THAN MOST GUYS.
PEOPLE I'M GOING TO GET ALONG
WITH ARE GUYS THAT ARE STRONG
AND YOU SHOW A WEAKNESS,
BYE-BYE.
>> MY BREAD AND BUTTER HAS
ALWAYS BEEN BOUNTY HUNTING.
YOU KICK IN THE DOOR, YOU RAID
THE HOUSE, YOU SNATCH THE GUY
UP, HOG TIE HIM LIKE A PIG,
THROW HIM IN THE BACK OF YOUR
TRUCK AND TAKE OFF.
I DON'T CARE.
I JUST NEED TO GET MY PAYCHECK,
AND YOU'RE MY PAYCHICK.
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTY TRIBE:
>> I DO TRY AND USE MY LOOKS TO
MY ADVANTAGE IN POKER.
AND IF I FEEL LIKE A MALE IS
STARING AT MY BOOBS, I MIGHT
PUSH THEM UP A LITTLE MORE.
>> MY LIFE HAS DEFINITELY BEEN
EASIER BECAUSE I'M BETTER
LOOKING THAN MOST PEOPLE.
AND THAT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
IT SOUNDS AWFUL.
BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
MY LOOKS WILL DEFINITELY HELP
ME.
39 DAYS AND A MILLION BUCKS IN
MY POCKET AT THE END.
>> YEAH, BABY!
WOOO!
>> GET THE FISH TRAP.
GET THE FISH TRAP.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE WITNESSING 18
AMERICANS BEGIN AN ADVENTURE
THAT WILL FOREVER CHANGE THEIR
LIVES.
THEY'VE BEEN GIVEN TWO MINUTES
TO SALVAGE WHATEVER THEY CAN OFF
THIS BOAT.
>> WATCH OUT!
COMING DOWN!
>> Jeff: THERE ARE CHICKENS.
THERE IS FRUIT.
THERE ARE FISH TRAPS.
BUT THERE IS NOT ENOUGH TO GO
AROUND.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: YOU GOT A LOOSE
CHICKEN.
>> PEOPLE WILL PROBABLY
RECOGNIZE ME FROM "BIG BROTHER,"
BUT BEING AN OUTDOORSMAN, THIS
GAME IS TOTALLY FOR ME.
I DON'T MIND GETTING DIRTY AT
ALL.
>> Jeff: YOU NEED TO WORK
TOGETHER!
>> WATCH OUT.
>> YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
>> OH!
OUCH!
>> Jeff: YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYBODY'S NAME.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF YOU LIKE THEM!
AND YET YOU'RE ALREADY RELYING
ON THEM.
>> THROW STUFF OVER.
COME ON.
IT'S VERY HECTIC DOWN HERE.
I'M A RETIRED F.B.I. AGENTS AND,
OF COURSE, THERE HAVE BEEN TIMES
IN THE F.B.I. WHEN WE HAD THOSE
KINDS OF CASE WHERE'S
EVERYTHING'S GONE A MILE A
MINUTE.
BUT THIS TO ME IS GOING TO BE
THE ULTIMATE CHALLENGE.
SO I'M PUMPED FOR THIS.
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL FOR ME.
>> Jeff: 30 SECONDS LEFT!
YOU NEED ON START GETTING
SUPPLIES OVERBOARD AND THEN GET
YOURSELVES OVERBOARD.
>> I'M RUNNING AROUND LIKE
CRAZY.
I'M PROTECTING THE CHICKEN
BECAUSE I LOVE ALL LIVING
CREATURE.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER CHICKEN IS ON
THE LOOSE!
SOMEBODY BETTER GET IT!
>> COME HERE, CHICKEN.
>.>> Jeff: THAT IS FRIEND OR
FOOD.
15 SECONDS.
START GETTING OVER!
BRAIN TRIBE, GET IN THE WATER!
>> WHOA!
>> Jeff: BEAUTY TRIBE, GET
OVER.
>> WATCH YOUR HEAD.
WATCH YOUR HEAD.
>> Jeff: LET'S GO!
BRAWN TRIBE, YOU GOTTA GET OVER.
>> JUMP.
>> WE'RE HAVING FUN NOW, KIDS!
>> Jeff: IT IS THE ULTIMATE
CHALLENGE.
18 STRANGERS FORCED TO WORK
TOGETHER.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEY'LL BE VOTED OUT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHO'S A GOOD SWIMMER, BECAUSE
I'M AN EXCELLENT SWIMMER.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, ONLY ONE
WILL REMAIN TO CLAIM THE
MILLION-DOLLAR PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR!
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> WELL, KIDS, THIS MIGHT BE THE
GREATEST DAY OF OUR LIVES.
>> PADDLING IN AND LOOKING
AROUND AT MY BRAWN TRIBE, IT
FEELS LIKE HOME.
THE MAJORITY OF MY LIFE IS ABOUT
BEING STRONG, WHETHER IT'S
PHYSICALLY OR MENTALLY, IT'S
ABOUT BEING STRONG.
>> ON THE BRAWN TRIBE, IT'S
GOING TO BE A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
THINK THEY'RE THE GREATEST I DID
SIX YEARS IN THE ARMY.
I DON'T NEED TO PROVE TO YOU I'M
A BAD-ASS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE FIND ME
INTIMIDATING.
THEY JUDGE ME BECAUSE OF HOW I
LOOK.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> THEY DON'T REALIZE THAT I'VE
GOT TWO DAUGHTERS AND MY
YOUNGEST HAS AUTISM.
>> DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
>> LIKE, I'LL BE THE GIRLIE-GIRL
DAD, AND THEN I ALSO TEACH THEM
HOW TO BE A BAD-ASS.
>> THAT'S A GOOD START.
>> WHAT DOES EVERYBODY DO?
>> PROFESSIONAL BODYBUILDER.
>> DAMN!
>> SHOCKING!
SHUT THE FRONT DOOR!
>> WHAT!
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> POSTAL WORKER AND A STUDENT.
>> OH, NICE.
>> I DO REAL ESTATE.
I LEASE, LIKE, CONDOS AND
APARTMENTS AND STUFF.
>> OH, FANCY.
>> PEOPLE MIGHT LIKE AT ME AND
BE LIKE MALIBU BARBIE.
SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE IN HERE
LONG, BUT I'M A LOT TOUGHER THAN
THEY WOULD THINK.
I'VE BEEN BUNGEE JUMPING IN
BAIL, FACE-TO-FACE SHARK DIVING
IN AUSTRALIA.
WITH CAGED TIGERS IN THAILAND.
I'M FEARLESS, I'M OPINIONATED.
THIS IS SOMETHING I KNOW I CAN
DO.
>> I'M A CONSTRUCTION WORKER.
I BUILD HOMES, SOMETIMES
COMMERCIAL BUILDINGS.
>> I'M RETIRED.
I PLAYED IN THE N.B.A.
>> YEAH, THAT WAY WE'VE GOT
DOUBLE SHADE.
EVERYBODY OKAY WITH THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK ALL OF US HAVE A VERY
SIMILAR MINDSET PROFESSIONAL
BODY BUILDER, CAN YOU KNOCK
TREES DOWN FOR US?
>> I CAN.
>> WE'RE NOT BEAUTIFUL.
WE'RE NOT SMART.
BUT WE ARE STRONG.
AND I FEEL LUCKY RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW THINGS CHANGE IN THIS
GAME REALLY QUICKLY.
THE SAME THING THAT MAKES YOU
LAUGH MAKES YOU CRY BUT RIGHT
NOW, I THINK WE'VE GOT A GREAT
GROUP.
>> IF IT'S LONG ENOUGH FOR YOU
TO LAY I THINK IT WILL BE LONG
ENOUGH FOR US TO LAY.
>> I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT
COUNTING.
I'M THE BRAWN TRIBE.
>> SO WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> IN CALIFORNIA ORIGINALLY, I
LIVE IN NEW YORK CITY NOW.
I WORK FOR THE GOVERNMENT DOING
DATA ANALYSIS.
>> WELL, WHAT'S YOUR REGRESSION
ANALYSIS OF "SURVIVOR" RIGHT
NOW?
>> I HAVEN'T DONE SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
I THINK I WOULD NEED A LOT MORE
TIME.
THE BRAIN TRIBE IS DEFINITELY MY
TRIBE.
THAT'S THE ATTRIBUTE THAT I
ACTUALLY THINK IS VALUABLE
BECAUSE WE ARE ABLE TO LOOK FOR
NEW APPROACHES AND SLIGHTLY
DIFFERENT WAYS OF THINKING
THROUGH THE PROBLEMS.
SO WE'RE OFF TO AN IMMEDIATE
ADVANTAGE.
>> OKAY, I GET TO SAY IT-- I'M
STARING AT THIS GUY.
I'M THINKING, WHAT IS THE
PRESIDENT DOING HERE?
>> BEING CALLED OBAMA IS PART OF
MY DAILY LIFE.
IT'S BEEN LIKE THAT FOR THE LAST
SEVEN YEARS.
IF DEBBIE CALLS ME OBAMA, I
GUARANTEE YOU, EVERYONE ELSE IS
CALLING ME OBAMA.
>> WHEN YOU'RE COMING IT'S GOING
TO BE LIKE IN MY HEAD.
>> WE'LL PROTECT YOU, BARRY.
>> THAT BEING SAID, IF THEY FEEL
BETTER GETTING CRUSHED BY OBAMA,
SO BE IT.
>> I'M A CAPTAIN, CIVIL AIR
PATROL, U.S. AIR FORCE
AUXILIARY.
I CAN GET A FIRE STARTED WITHOUT
FLINT.
I HAVE EXTENSIVE TRAINING IN
SHELTER BUILDING, WINTER
SURVIVAL, SUMMER SURVIVAL,
REPELLING.
I'M A CHEMIST BUT I HAVE BEEN A
PROTONICS ENGINEERING
SUPERVISOR.
A BARTENDER, CARETAKE TORE NONE,
AND BETWEEN JOBS I FILL IN AT
RED LOBSTER AS A STERVER.
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO DO A QUICK
ASSESSMENT AND UNLOAD.
AT 49 I BRING A LOT OF WORLDLY
EXPERIENCE WITH ME.
>> I'LL ACTUALLY SHOW YOU A
TRICK RIGHT NOW.
YOU ACTUALLY WANT FRICTION.
>> YUP.
>> AND WE'LL SHAVE THIS OFF A
LITTLE BIT.
>> I HAVE MY OWN ICE CREAM
BUSINESS, AND I THINK PEOPLE
THINK THAT I'M A DANDY IN ICE
CREAM HAT.
I THINK THEY DON'T KNOW QUITE
WHAT TO MAKE OF ME.
I'M INCORRIGIBLE AND ECCENTRIC.
BUT DEBBIE HAS A WHOLE DIFFERENT
LEVEL OF CRAZINESS.
>> LOOK, HE'S GOT IT.
>> TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
>> ONCE IT'S REALLY SMOKING, YOU
PICK IT UP, AND YOU'RE GOING TO
BLOW IN THE LITTLE HOLE.
>> I DON'T HAVE A HOLE YET.
>> OKAY, THEM KEEP DOING IT.
>> KEEP GOING.
YOU'VE GOT SMOKE GOING.
>> SHOULD WE PUT A LITTLE HOLE
IN IT.
>> NO THE HOLE IS GOING TO COME
FROM YOU AND FRICTION.
>> YOU DID THE HOLE?
>> YES.
>> THERE'S NO HOLE YET.
THERE'S JUST A NOTCH.
>> I KNOW HOW EXHAUSTING T, SO
IF YOU WANT ME TO DO IT.
>> SUPPOSEDLY, DEBBIE HAS
STARTED FIRE THIS WAY MANY
TIMES.
NOBODY ELSE MADE ANY WARRANTS
ABOUT THEIR ABILITY TO BE THE
SAVIOR OF THIS TRIBE.
SOMEBODY WHO SAYS SHE'S A FIRE
EXPERT AND THEN COMES ON TO THE
BEACH AND WHEN IT'S REALLY
CLUTCH TIME AND NEEDS TO MAKE
FIRE FOR THEIR TRIBE CAN'T DO
IT, IS A BIG CONCERN.
>> WE CANNOT SHOW UP IN FRONT OF
THE OTHER TRIBES AS THE BRAINS
WITHOUT FIRE.
JUST FROM AN EVOLUTIONARY
STANDPOINT.
>> NO ONE HAS CONCEDED DEFEAT,
SIR.
>> LOOKING BACK AT PAST SEASONS,
IT SEEMS LIKE THE REALLY SMART
FOLKS ALWAYS HAVE SOME FORM OF
KRYPTONITE, SO I'M A LITTLE
CONCERNED ABOUT BEING ON THE
BRAIN TRIBE.
IT MIGHT BE COMPLETE AND UTTER
MADNESS.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS!
>> WHO-HOO.
>> LIFE WITHOUT A DOUBT IS
BEAUTIFUL.
OUR TRIBE IS BEAUTIFUL.
WE'RE FEELING BEAUTIFUL.
THE ISLAND IS BEAUTIFUL.
I MEAN, WE'RE ALL EXCITED, WE'RE
ALL HAPPY, WE'RE ALL SMILES.
AND WE WORK WELL TOGETHER.
AROUND CAMP, RIGHT NOW, NOTHING
CAN GO WRONG.
>> OH, MY GOSH, YOU'RE GOING TO
GIVE ME A FREAKING HEART ATTACK
DOING THAT.
>> OH, THERE'S COCONUTS, TOO.
WHY AM I HERE?
LOOK AT ME, I'M BALD, BIG HAT,
BALD, BIG EERKZ SKINNY LITTLE
BODY.
I DON'T BELONG HERE.
I JUST THINK, MY GOD, WHEN I GO
HOME, PEOPLE SAY HA!
THEY SAY WHY ARE THEY PUTTING
YOU ON THE BEAUTY TRIBE,
ESPECIALLY MY BOYFRIEND OR
SOMEBODY.
BUT I THINK MY PERSONALITY CAN
COME OUT.
WE ALL HAVE BEAUTIFUL INSIDE AND
OUTSIDE.
>> THAT LOOKS GOOD!
>> IT DOES LOOK GOOD.
>> IT REALLY DOES LOOK GOOD.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
DEFINITELY, LIKE, A MODEL OR--
>> YEAH.
>> HE SHAVES HIS ARMS AND LEGS.
I NOTICED THAT.
>> BEING A BARTENDER IS AN
EXTREMELY SOCIAL JOB.
YOU LEARN THAT PERSONALITY TYPES
WANT CERTAIN THINGS FROM YOU, SO
I WAS LIKE, OKAY, WHO LOOKS LIKE
I WOULD GET ALONG WITH THEM?
THERE'S T TAI.
HE'S FREAKING ALWAYS MOVING.
HE'S LIKE A WHIRLWIND.
CALEB IS SUPER STRONG.
AND NICK, THE TALL, DREAMY GUY,
OF COURSE, I WAS LIKE OH!
HE'S ON MY TRIBE.
I GET TO SPEND A LOT OF TIME
WITH HIM AND HE GET TO SEE ME
DISGUSTINGLY DIRTY.
WONDERFUL.
>> THIS IS SO, LIKE,
STEREOTYPAL.
>> I'M NOT SURE I CAN HANDLE ALL
THAT TESTOSTERONE OVER THERE
ANYWAY.
SO I DECIDED TO BUILD THE
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE GIRLS.
YOU'RE INCLINED TO GO WITH THE
GIRLS, BRAID EACH OTHER'S HAIR,
WHATEVER.
GIRLS KIND OF GO WITH GIRLS SO
THAT ALLIANCE FELT REALLY
NATURAL TO ME.
>> DO YOU THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
PAIR UP, THE THREE OF THEM?
>> PART OF ME THINKS THEY WON'T
BECAUSE THEY'RE SO DIFFERENT.
>> I THINK THERE'S PROBABLY A
LOT OF EGO OVER THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> ONE OF THE GIRLS SHE SAID SHE
WAS IN SCHOOL TO BE A BIOLOGIST.
>> WHICH ONE IS THAT?
>> THE ONE CLOSEST TO US?
>> MICHELE?
>> WHICH ONE IS THAT?
>> THE YELLOW.
>> THE ONE IN THE YELLOW?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M LOOK AROUND AT MY BEAUT
TRIBE AND I'M SITTING HERE KIND
OF WONDERING TO MYSELF, WHY IN
THE WORLD IS TAI ON THIS TRIBE.
50, 60-YEAR-OLD ASIAN GUY THAT
HAS EYEBROWS, LIKE, TWO OR THREE
INCHES LONG.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LIKE, MAYBE THERE'S A LOT MORE
THAN WHAT PEOPLE REALLY SEE.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TO DO-- YOU'RE
GOING TO MAKE A NOTCH.
>> YEAH, MAKE A NOTCH.
>> THIS WAY.
>> HOW HIGH, DO YOU THINK ABOUT
RIGHT HERE?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> DON'T KILL THE TREE?
>> DON'T KILL IT.
>> I HAVE A SOFT SPOT FOR TREES
BECAUSE I'M A GARDENER.
>> ARE YOU?
I HATE TO TELL YOU, BUT I'M
MURDALIZING THIS TREE RIGHT NOW.
>> IT'S A LIVING BEING.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT IF SOMEONE
CAME OVER AND STARTING CUTTING
AWAY PART OF YOUR SKIN?
>> THE GOOD THING IS IT DOESN'T
HAVE ARMS AND CAN'T HIT ME BACK.
>> I LOVE ALL LIVING CREATURES,
ESPECIALLY THE PLANT.
AS A GARDNER, IT HURTS ME WHEN I
SEE PEOPLE CUT OFF BRANCHES.
IT'S JUST LIKE AN ARM.
YOU CUT IT OFF, IT CANNOT GROW
BACK THE SAME WAY.
AND SOMETIMES I COULD BE REALLY
STRONG ABOUT IT.
BUT THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
I'VE GOT TO BE SMART ABOUT HOW I
SAY IT.
>> YOU'RE A GARDENER, TAI?
>> YEAH.
>> UP IN SAN FRANCISCO?
>> AND I'M FROM VIETNAM.
THIS IS, LIKE, MY HOOD, SO I
KNOW A LOT OF STUFF.
>> HOW LONG YOU HAVE BEEN IN SAN
FRANCISCO?
>> I HAVE TO GO GET IN THE YOUNG
EXPEL GET FOOD FOR US.
I'M FROM VIETNAM.
I LIVED THROUGH THE WAR AND I
SURVIVED.
AND IN 1979, 262 PEOPLE WERE ON
A 26-METER BOAT.
WE'RE JUST SITTING THERE LIKE
THIS FOR, LIKE, FOR 11 DAYS.
WE HAVE NO FOOD.
NO FOOD.
JUST A LITTLE BIT OF WATER.
AND WE JUST FLOAT AND FLOAT AND
FLOAT.
AND WE END UP ON THIS REFUGEE
CAMP REALLY CLOSE TO HERE.
A WHOLE YEAR, AND THEN WE COME
TO AMERICA.
SO THROUGHOUT A LOT OF MY LIFE,
THAT'S A LOT OF THINGS I
SURVIVED THROUGH AND I THINK I
HAVE AN ADVANTAGE.
ADVENTURE JUST EXCITES ME.
I CAN'T SIT STILL.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS ONCE IN A LIFETIME.
I'M LOVING IT.
>> OH!
>> IT'S A HARSH SUN.
MY SHOULDERS ARE FRIED.
MY SHINS ARE FRIED.
SUNBURN HURTS, YOU KNOW, BUT I
GIVE IT MY ALL, WORK PHYSICALLY
HARD FIRST AND START THINKING
ABOUT IT AS YOU'RE GOING ALONG.
IT'S JUST THE TYPE OF PERSON I
AM.
>> I GOT IT.
>> WE NEED ONE OF THE GUYS TO DO
THIS.
>> THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT WELL.
>> BLONDIE, I HAVEN'T EVEN
LEARNED HER NAME, CALL HER
BLONDIE.
I HAVE ZERO FAITH IN THAT GIRL.
>> I REMEMBER THE DIRECTIONS,
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO IT.
>> SHE DOESN'T DOING WITH.
>> WE NEED MORE BAMBOO DON'T WE.
>> I THINK THERE'S MORE OVER
THERE.
>> I'LL GO.
>> YOU WANT TO HEAD OUT THERE?
>> TO ME, SHE'S AT THE BOTTOM.
I HAVE NO SYMPATHY FOR HER.
I GOT MY OWN WIFE AND KIDS TO
WORRY ABOUT.
BLONDIE, LITTLE GIRL REAL ESTATE
AGENT?
>> WE'VE GOT STRONG PEOPLE AND
ALL OF A SUDDEN WE'VE GOT THE
CALIFORNIA GIRL.
>> WORST COMES TO WORST, HER,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
THE PLAN IS YOU, JENNY, AND ME.
>> JENNY'S THE CONSTRUCTION
WORKER, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M IN WITH YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THE TRUTH SI WANT AS MANY
ALLIANCES AS POSSIBLE.
>> ARE WE GOING GOOD?
>> YEAH.
>> IN MY EYES, THESE ALLIANCES
ARE ONLY TRUTHFUL WHEN I NEED
THEM.
>> YOU, ME, AND SCOT.
>> YEAH.
>> POTENTIALLY, THEY COULD ALL
BE TRUTHFUL IN A WAY.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM COULD
BE FALSE.
I'LL MAKE THAT DECISION AS I
NEED TO MAKE IT.
>> YOU AIN'T GOT ANY MATCHES ON
YOU, DO YOU?
NO?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
IF I LAYER THEM, IT WILL BE ALL
RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE IT WILL BE A LITTLE
HOLY.
>> I GET WHAT YOU'RE DOING NOW.
GROWING UP IN CHICAGO, IT'S
PRETTY TOUGH.
THERE WAS A LOT OF STUFF THEY
LEARNED, AND I'M GOING TO BRING
THOSE INSTINCTS INTO THIS GAME.
I'M GOING TO USE MY GUT.
I GOT YOUR BACK.
OKAY, WELL, WE'RE GOOD THEN.
I KIND OF LIKE ALECIA?
>> YOU DON'T LIKE HER.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO ALIGN WITH?
>> I'M THINKING THE GUYS, I LIKE
THEM MORE.
I'M THINKING WE NEED TO GET THE
GIRLS OUT FIRST.
>> I MOST DEFINITELY TRUST
CYDNEY.
THIS GUT DON'T LIE TO ME.
>> I MINUTE I FIND OUT SOMETHING
I'M GOING TO LET YOU KNOW.
AND RIGHT NOW, MY GUT TELLS ME
DON'T USE THE BATHROOM.
>> IS DARNELL GOING TO THE POOP
ROCKS?
>> HE IS.
>> I'D GO A LITTLE FURTHER.
>> OH!
( LAUGHTER ).
>> WATCH OUT FOR THE BROWN
TROUT!
>> I JUST HEARD, "DARNELL, ARE
YOU TAKING A DUMP?"
SERIOUSLY.
I CAN'T BE AT PEACE FOR TWO
SECONDS?
I NEED SOME READING MATERIAL.
>> SO, WHERE IS EVERYONE FROM?
>> I LIVE IN REDONDO BEACH,
CALIFORNIA, BUT I'M FROM NEW
JERSEY.
>> WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> I'M FROM KENTUCKY.
>> OH, MY GOD, THE CHICKENS!
>> I WONDER IF WE'RE BURNING
MORE CALORIES THAN WHAT WE'RE
GONNA GET OUT OF THIS CHICKEN.
IT WASN'T THE BEST OF STARTS FOR
THE BEAUTY TRIBE WHATSOEVER.
WHILE WE'RE BUILDING THE
SHELTER, THE CHICKENS GET OUT.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, REALLY, THIS,
RIGHT NOW?
>> YOU KNOW, THIS IS GOING TO
MAKE US A REALLY GOOD--
>> WAIT, WAIT!
>> GUYS, DO YOU SEE IT?
>> WE ARE RUNNING AROUND LIKE
CHICKENS WITH OUR HEADS CUT OFF,
AND WE'RE WASTING CALORIES BUT
YOU DESPERATELY WANT THOSE
CHICKENS.
>> YEAH!
>> WE NEED TO MAKE A BETTER
CHICKEN TRAP.
>> WE GOT TWO OF THEM BACK, AND
66%, I'LL TAKE IT.
BUT IT WASN'T THE BEST START.
>> I HAVE AN IDEA.
WE'LL TIE ONE CHICKEN TO THE
NEXT CHICKEN, ALL RIGHT.
AND BETWEEN THEM, WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A LONG LINE.
>> OKAY.
>> THEY CAN ROAM AROUND.
THEY'LL BE HAPPIER THAT WAY.
YEAH.
I THINK THAT WILL BE GOOD.
>> I LOVE TAI'S APPROACH ON
LIFE.
HE TAKES HIS TIME WITH ALL OF
US, AND WHEN THERE'S SOMETHING
NEW, HE TRIES TO TEACH ALL OF
US.
AND I ABSOLUTELY LOVE THAT ABOUT
HIM.
>> IT'S A LITTLE PET.
>> DON'T LET GO.
>> I'M NOT.
HE TAUGHT US HOW TO TIE A LITTLE
ROPE ON THE CHICKEN AND HOW TO
RUN AROUND.
I RESPECT THAT.
HE RESPECTS ALL THE CREATUREES
AND CHICKENS THAT LIVE HERE.
IS THAT ATTACHED?
>> HOW CUTE IS THAT?
>> THEY SEEM SO MUCH HAPPIER.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO BE DEAD IN A
FEW DAYS.
>> THEY'RE TWO LITTLE LITTLE
BUDDIES.
>> I THINK THIS ONE MIGHT BE A
ROOSTER.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING,
TOO.
>> TAI IS SOMEONE I CAN
DEFINITELY WORK WITH.
THE THREE GIRLS WE'RE PRETTY
TIGHT BUT IN ORDER TO HAVE THE
NUMBERS AND PROPEL OURSELVES IN
THE GAME, WE NEED A GUY, AND TAI
IS PERFECT TO TAKE ALONG WITH
US.
WE CAN USE HIM, FOR SURE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE
ASIAN GUY?
>> YEAH, HONESTLY, I LOVED HIM
FROM FIRST SIGHT.
>> YOU, TOO.
>> YOU ARE, LIKE AIR, SWEETHEART
ME AND YOU?
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF A
CONNOTATION THAT COMES FROM
BEING IN A SORORITY.
PEOPLE UNDERESTIMATE YOU.
THEY THINK THAT'S ALL YOU DO AND
THAT'S HOW YOU GET THROUGH LIFE,
THE WAY YOU LOOK.
BUT I'M REALLY NOT LIKE AT THAT
ALL.
I CAN PULL MY OWN WEIGHT AND
WILL MAKE CONNECTIONS WITH THESE
PEOPLE INSTANTLY.
I WANT TO STICK WITH ANNA AND
MICHELE, I THINK THE THREE OF US
COULD DO VERY WELL.
>> YOU, I TRUST.
I AM LIKE 99% SURE THAT THE
OTHER GUY WAS ON "BIG BROTHER."
>> WHICH ONE?
>> CALEB.
>> JULIA CAME UP TO ME AND SAID,
LISTEN, CALEB WAS ON "BIG
BROTHER."
I TRUST HER.
IT GIVES US A LOT OF INFORMATION
THAT HE WAS ON "BIG BROTHER."
HE WAS IN AN ALLIANCE OF NINE ON
"BIG BROTHER" AND HE KEPT IT ALL
THE WAY, WHICH SHOWS ME HE'S
VERY LOYAL.
SO THAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR
US.
>> I WAS AFRAID YOU GUYS
WOULDN'T KNOW WHO I WAS.
NICK KNOWS.
>> YOU MEAN "BIG BROTHER"?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I WOULDN'T AT THE PRESENT TIME
TO I GUESS HURT MY GAME.
>> WE'RE NOT JUST THE BEAUTY
TRIBE.
WE HAVE BRAINS, TOO.
>> I'M BEAST MODE COWBOY FROM
"BIG BROTHER," BUT I'M MORE THAN
THAT AND I WANT TO SHOW
EVERYBODY WHAT I'M MADE OF.
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> ALMOST.
>> YOU DEFINITELY BELONG ON THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
YOU LOOK GREAT UP IN THAT TREE.
>> I WAS IN THE MILITARY RIGHT
OUT OF HOLLY.
I WAS A PRISON GUARD IN BAGDAD,
IRAQ.
IF I'M IN A COMPETITION STANDING
ON MY TIPPY TOES FOR THREE
HOURS, I'M GOING TO STAND ON MY
TIPPY TOES FOR THREE HOURS UNTIL
LAST PERSON GIVES UP.
>> CALEB!
>> BLOW, BLOW, BLOW, BLOW.
>> LIVING MY DAIFL LIFE ON A
FARM AND BEING AN OUTDOORSMAN,
THIS IS HOME TO ME.
I KNOW WHAT IT TAKES TO MAKE A
FIRE.
>> HERE WE GO, BABY.
>> WE'VE GOT FIRE!
>> I'LL DO WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO
TO GET WHAT I WANT.
I BELIEVE I'M PROBABLY MEBT
MENTALLY STRONGER THAN ANYBODY
IN THIS GAME.
>> FIRE!
>> GETS EXCITING WHEN YOU GET TO
THE END.
>> YEAH!
COOL.
THAT WAS A GOOD RHYTHM.
>> I'M 71 YEARS OLD, AND I WAS A
HOSTAGE NEGOTIATOR IN THE F.B.I.
WE WERE ON SOME DANGEROUS
ASSIGNMENTS AT TIMES, BUT I HAVE
STREET SENSE.
I TEND TO SEE THINGS BEFORE THEY
ACTUALLY HAPPEN KIND OF AND HAVE
INTUITIVENESS ABOUT THINGS.
SO I THINK I CAN BE ABLE TO MAKE
IT THROUGH THAT GAUNTLET TO BE
THE SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'LL TAKE TURNS.
IT'S EXHAUSTING.
I'M NOT USING THE SAW.
ANYBODY WANTS TO USE THE SAW,
FEEL FREE, BUT I'M NOT USING THE
SAW.
>> YEAH, I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
NEEDED SAW.
>> JOE AND I ARE WORK HORSES.
WE'VE GOT THE WISDOM TO KNOW.
BEFORE WE GO STRATEGIZING ABOUT
WINNING THE GAME, WE HAVE TO
STAY ALIVE!
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE TO SURVIVE
HERE.
>> STOP, STOP!
WE'RE COMING DOWN THE WHOLE
THING HERE.
>> YEAH.
SO I'M GOING TO MAKE THIS CAMP
AS COMFORTABLE AS I CAN.
MOSTLY FOR ME AND JOE.
BECAUSE JOE AND I PLAN ON
STICKING AROUND A VERY LONG
TIME.
>> HOW ARE YOU LIKING THE GROUP?
>> GOOD.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE PEOPLE KIND OF LIKE WHAT
YOU EXPECTED?
>> YEAH WELL, YOU KNOW, WHEN WE
FIRST MET DEBBIE, SHE WAS
REALLY, LIKE, CHATTY, CHATTY,
CHATTY.
I WAS LIKE OH, MY GOD.
I HOPE SHE SHUTS UP.
>> WHEN I FIRST SAW HER I WAS
LIKE SHE COULD BE SUPER TOUGH
AND COOL TO WORK WITH AND WHEN
SHE FIRST OPENED HER MOUTH I WAS
LIKE OH, MAYBE NOT.
DEBBIE TALKS, TALKS, TALKS, AND
TALKS SO HIGHLY OF HERSELF THAT
I START TO THINK THAT SHE MIGHT
JUST ANNOY EVERYBODY TO DEATH.
>> WE HAVE THAT GERIATRIC TINGE
THAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GET
RID OF.
THEY'RE JUST GOING TO BE TOO
SLOW.
OLD JOE, A 72-YEAR-OLD RUNNING
THROUGH A GROUP CHALLENGE?
>> HE DOES SEEM LIKE THE MOST
LIKELY TO BE MEDEVACED.
>> DO YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT THE
FOUR OF US, THE CHILDREN?
>> I DO.
I FEEL LIKE THE FOUR OF US WOULD
REALLY HOLD TOGETHER WELL.
LIKE, I DON'T SEE ANYBODY, LIKE,
FLIPPING OUT OVER SOME STUPID
THING.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE SIX PEOPLE ON A
TRIBE, AND YOU KNOW THAT FOUR OF
US ARE GOING TO BE QUICKER, BOTH
PHYSICALLY AS WELL AS MENTALLY,
IT MAKES A HELL OF A LOT OF
SENSE TO TRY TO KEEP THE FOUR
YOUNGER ONES TOGETHER.
I THINK WE GET THE FOUR YOUNG
BUCKS AND GO TO THE MERGE.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE BEST PLAN
EVER.
I THINK WE'RE ALL EASY-GOING.
>> DON'T TALK TOO LOUDLY.
SOUND CARRIES IN THE WATER.
>> IN OUR GROUP WE'VE GOT FOUR
YOUNG PEOPLE AND TWO OLD PEOPLE.
THE FACT THEY SAY THEY'RE OLD
PEOPLE MEANS THEY ALREADY STICK
OUT.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO TAKE OUT
FIRST, GRANDMA OR GRASMS?
>> LET'S SEE HOW THEY DO IN THE
CHALLENGE.
>> JOE AND DEBBIE ARE
LOW-HANGING FRUIT SO THEY'RE
GOING TO BE EATEN FIRST.
>> I'M JUST GONNA DRAG THESE TWO
BACK WITH ME.
>> I'M GONNA LOOK AROUND TRY TO
SEE IF I CAN FIND SOME SIGNS FOR
THE IDOL.
THIS MORNING, WE WERE WALKING
AND EVERYBODY TURNED AROUND TO
TAKE THE BAMBOO BACK, SO I SAY I
HAVE TO LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
I HAVE NO CLUE.
BUT THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
THERE'S GOT TO BE AN IDOL
SOMEWHERE NEAR HERE.
THIS IS UNUSUAL THAT SOMEONE
WOULD HAVE THAT TREE HERE IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE TRAIL.
THIS MIGHT BE A SIGN.
IT'S GOTTA BE ONE OF THESE
TREES.
IT'S GOTTA BE IT.
I SHOULD KNOW BECAUSE I'M THE
TREE GUY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE?
>> I HAVE A FEELING, LIKE, TAI'S
LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
>> YEAH, I HAD THAT FEELING AS
WELL.
>> WHEN WE ALL WALKED OFF, HE
WALKED RIGHT BACK TO WHERE THE
TREE MAIL THING WAS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> SHOULD WE GO OVER THERE?
>> YOU WANT TO?
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> OKAY, NOT THIS ONE.
GOTTA BE ONE OF THESE GUYS.
I HOPE I DON'T MISS IT.
OKAY.
I GOTTA LOOK CAREFULLY.
ALL THIS WORK.
ANYBODY COMING?
I HEARD THEM.
>> NO ONE NEEDS IT YET.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN HAD A CHALLENGE.
LIKE, WE HAVE TIME.
>> IT DEFINITELY PAINTS A TARGET
ON YOUR BACK.
>> YEAH, IT DOES.
>> SORRY, TREE, I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING THAT I WANT.
>> I'M LOOKING AROUND, AND THEN
I SAW TAI, AND AS SOON AS I WALK
UP, HE KNEELS DOWN.
OOIK LIKE THAT'S REALLY WEIRD.
AND I SEE HIM PATTING THE FLOOR,
AND I'M, LIKE, OKAY, WELL, THIS
GUY'S LOOKING FOR THE IDOL, AND
I'M JUST RIGHT AWAY SKETCH.
>> DID YOU GET A LITTLE LUCKY
OVER THERE?
CALEB WAS LIKE TAI'S LOOKING.
I WAS LIKE, "OKAY, WELL, WE'LL
SEE, BUT WE DON'T KNOW."
>> I'M LOOK HERE.
>> IS IT UNDER IT OR SOMETHING?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE THE NEW CLOOU.
>> NO, I DON'T HAVE THE CLUE.
I SMAWT IT MUST BE SOMEWHERE
NEAR THE TREE MAIL SO WE HAVE TO
LOOK FOR SIGNS.
>> YESTERDAY I FELT COMFORTABLE
WITH HIM BUT NOW I DON'T TRUST
YOU FOR A FREAKING SECOND.
>> I SCREWED EVERYTHING UP.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ME AT PULL.
THE FACT THAT I WENT AWAY FOR
HALF AN HOUR TO LOOK FOR THE
IDOL, AND I GOT CAUGHT.
>> IT'S CERTAINLY SUSPICIOUS.
>> HE COULD VERY WELL WITH IT.
>> YEAH, I THOUGHT I SAW HIM PUT
IT IN HIS POCKET OR SOMETHING.
>> HE DID?
WE'LL PRETEND HE DOESN'T HAVE
IT.
>> SHOULD WE TRY, US FIVE?
>> I JUST DON'T TRUST TAI.
HE'S BRINGING A LOT OF ANXIOUS
ENERGY.
HE MADE HIS BED, AND RIGHT NOW,
TAI IS NUMBER ONE FOR ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOOD.
>> YEAH, WE'RE GOOD.
>> SHOULD I START UP HERE AND GO
DOWN?
>> I FIND IT EASIER TO START--
>> YOU'RE GOING IN THE OPPOSITE
DIRECTION.
YEAH.
>> IT'S SO HOT OUT HERE THAT I
DON'T THINK YOU EVEN REALIZE IN
THE MOMENT HOW HOT IT IS.
YOU REALIZE WHEN YOU START
MOVING SLOWER.
IT KIND OF SCRAMBLES YOUR BRAIN.
IT SLOWS YOU DOWN.
AND YOU CAN'T ESCAPE IT.
I THINK THIS HEAT MIGHT BE ONE
OF THE PIGGEST FACTORS IN THIS
GAME.
>> I NEED SOME SHADE.
>> OH, YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU WORKING IN THE SUN.
>> I AM DEHYDRATED.
>> I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
I WENT TO A PREP SCHOOL, AND I
WORK IN SOCIAL MEDIA.
SO COMING FROM BOSTON IN THE
MIDDLE OF WINTER TO BEING
MAROONED HERE, IT'S LIKE GOING
FROM BLACK TO WHITE.
IT'S INTENSE.
I STARTED FEELING A LITTLE
WOBBLY AND DISCOMBOBALATED, AND
YOUR THOUGHTS STOP MOVING IN A
LIRN PATTERN.
I JUST DON'T HAVE MY FACULTIES
ABOUT ME TO EVEN, LIKE SIT STILL
AND TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
>> WELL THEN YOU DO WHAT YOU
THINK YOU NEED TO DO.
>> CAN YOU GUYS JUST HELP ME.
>> SURE.
>> JUST, WITH, LIKE, FRUIT AND
WATER.
>> UH-HUH.
LAY DOWN.
>> YEAH, NEIL'S RIGHT.
COME UP HERE AND LAY DOWN AND
RELAX.
>> AUBRY COMES TO ME AND
IMMEDIATELY I KNEW SHE WAS
DEHYDRATED, HEAT EXHAUSTION, AND
ANXIETY-RIDDEN.
>> IT'S TOUGH.
>> MY MIND IT'S JUST SHOT.
>> SHE WAS ALSO ABSOLUTELY
OVERWHELMED WITH BEING THROWN
INTO A JUNGLE WITH FIVE
STRANGERS.
>> SEE HOW HOT YOU ARE?
>> YEAH.
I KNOW... THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE FOR ME.
>> NO PROBLEM.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> THANK YOU, DEBBIE.
>> YES.
>> I CARE ABOUT THIS GAME.
I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT IT, AND
MAYBE I WORKED IT UP TOO MUCH IN
MY OWN HEAD.
THIS SITUATION I'M IN ISN'T EVEN
ABOUT THE ENVIRONMENT.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT MY OWN HEAD.
I'M A THINKER.
I GET STUCK IN MY OWN HEAD.
I KNOW THAT I BROUGHT THIS UPON
MYSELF.
IT'S THAT FEELING OF YOU CAN'T
EVEN MAKE THE CHOICE OF WHAT YOU
NEED TO DO FOR YOURSELF.
TO MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION OF,
LIKE, I NEED TO DO THIS, THIS,
AND THIS, TO FEEL BETTER, TO
MAKE MYSELF FEEL BETTER.
>> AUBRY WASN'T, LIKE, ILL
DEHYDRATED.
SHE HADN'T EVEN GOTTEN TO THE
POINT OF, LIKE, CHAPPED LIPS.
SO FOR HER IT WAS REALLY MORE OF
AN ANXIETY ATTACK.
SHE WAS JUST FREAKING OUT ABOUT
FREAKING OUT.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO BE OKAY.
ONCE YOUR HYDRATED, ONCE WE HAVE
A FIRE, YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL
AWESOME AGAIN.
>> YOU'RE JUST GOING TO COOL
OFF.
>> I JUST WISH YOU GUYS GOT TO
MEET ME.
>> WHATEVER IMPRESSION SHE'S
GIVING OFF ON DAY TWO, I DO
THINK THERE'S A SIGNIFICANT RISK
SHE CRACKS AGAIN NEXT TIME
SOMETHING DOESN'T GO WELL.
>> WITH AUBRY BEING WEIRD AND
FREAKING OUT--
>> KEEP DRINKING.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE A REPEAT OF
THE FIRST BRAINS, BEAUTY, AND
BRAWN WHERE BRAINS WERE NUTS AND
JUST GOT SHELLACKED.
>> I'M ACTUALLY WORRIED.
I'M NOT SURE, BUT I THINK I GOT
A BUG IN MY EAR, AND I THOUGHT,
IT'S FINE.
IT WILL CRAWL OUT.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
BUT INSTEAD OF CRAWLING OUT, IT
IS GETTING DEEPER IN MY EAR.
I CAN'T SLEEP.
I CAN'T GET COMFORTABLE.
IT'S JUST DISGUSTING HEARING
THESE LITTLE LEGS CRAWL AROUND
IN YOUR HEAD.
LIKE, IT'S DIGGING DEEPER INTO
MY EAR CANAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT DOES TO A
PERSON.
EMOTIONALLY IT DOES A LOT, BUT
PHYSICALLY, WHAT KIND OF DAMAGE
IS IT DOING?
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S BLOOD COMING
OUT OF MY EAR.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S DOING TO
ME.
IT'S SO PAINFUL.
I PREPARED TO FACE A LOT OUT
HERE, BUT I DIDN'T PREPARE FOR
SOME BUG TO MUNCH ME FROM THE
INSIDE.
>> MY EAR'S BLEEDING,
SWEETHEART, SEE.
>> UGH.
>> YEAH.
>> TREE MAIL!
>> ALL NIGHT, I HAVEN'T SLEPT,
LIKE, NOT EVEN A MINUTE.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHAT IS INSIDE
ME THAT IS CAUSING MY EAR TO
BLEED.
IT IS SO PAINFUL, LIKE, IT HURTS
SO BAD.
LIKE, IT WILL GO FOR 30 SECONDS
AND HE'LL STOP FOR A MINUTE AND
HE STOPS.
I CAN HEAR HIM LITERALLY
DIGGING.
AH!
THAT'S WHAT IT SOUND LIKE.
HE'S GETTING FURTHER IN.
I THOUGHT HE WOULD CRAWL OUT,
BUT HE'S GOING FURTHER INSIDE MY
EAR, AND IT-- GOD, IT JUST HURTS
SO BAD.
>> WHAT IF SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH HER?
SHE GETS PULLED.
>> WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
>> IT CHANGES THINGS.
>> I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
WE NEED TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE
AND I DON'T WANT TO SEE HER, YOU
KNOW,... NOT BE ABLE TO
PARTICIPATE AND THEY PULL HER,
THEN WE'RE A MAN DOWN.
WE'LL SEE HOW THIS GOES.
>> IT IS A CONCERN GOING INTO A
CHALLENGE, THINKING THAT WE
MIGHT LOSE ONE OF OUR TRIBE
MATES BECAUSE SHE HAS A BUG IN
HER EAR.
I DO THINK I COULD BE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK BECAUSE THEY WANT
A STRONGER TEAM, SO HOPEFULLY
JEN IS OKAY FOR THE CHALLENGE
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT US GOING
INTO THE CHALLENGE FOR FIVE
PEOPLE.
>> AH!
>> DO YOU WANT TO USE MY JACKET
FOR A PILLOW?
DO YOU WANT ME TO GET YOU SOME
WATER OR ANYTHING.
>> POOR JENNY.
SHE'S BLEEDING AND IN SOME PAIN,
BUT SELFISHLY, I'M A LITTLE
WORRIED ABOUT THE CHALLENGE
TODAY.
IF WE DON'T WIN, THIS IT'S GOING
TO HURT ALL OF US.
SO, QUITE LITERALLY, FAILURE IS
NOT AN OPTION.
>> DO YOU SEE ANYTHING?
>> NO.
JUST--
>> I SEE IT!
EWWWW!
>> REALLY?
>> LOOK AT IT!
THERE'S A TAIL.
IT'S WIGGLING.
>> OH!
>> THERE IT IS!
>> GET IT!
>> IT'S GOING BACK IN.
HOLD ON,.
>> IT'S COMEOUTH, IT'S COMING
OUT.
THERE IT IS, THERE IT IS.
>> I'M GOING TO GET IT AS SOON
AS IT GETS OUT OF YOUR EAR.
>> EWWWW!
THAT LITTLE CRITTER WAS CLEAN,
CLEAR-- GOT YOUR BLOOD IN THERE
AND EVERYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
>> EWW"P" THAT WAS JUST AMAZING.
>> KILL IT!
>> AT FIRST I WASN'T SURE HOW
LONG WAS IT WAS AND IT ENDS UP
BEING ABOUT YA BIG, IT'S PRETTY
LONG FOR AN EAR CANAL.
SO I COULD SEE HOW SHE WAS IN
PAIN UPON.
>> DOES IT FEEL BETTER?
>> I FEEL LIKE MYSELF AGAIN.
WE'RE GOING TO KILL THIS
CHALLENGE BECAUSE I'M SO PISSED
OFF.
>> YEAH!
JENNY'S BACK.
I FEEL AMAZING, BACK TO WHAT I
WAS BEFORE, READY TO TAKE ON ALL
THESE CHALLENGES.
I GOT THIS, 39 DAYS, NO PROBLEM.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELCOME TO
THE FIRST CHALLENGE OF
"SURVIVOR: KOAH RONG"!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO SWIM
OUT TO A BOAT.
ONCE EVERYBODY'S ON BOARD, ONE
PERSON WILL DIVE DOWN TO
RETRIEVE A PADDLE.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL FOUR PADDLES,
YOU'LL THEN RACE TO SHORE WHERE
YOU WILL CONVERT YOUR BOAT INTO
A CART.
YOU'LL THEN PUSH IT TO THE TOP.
ONCE YOU'RE AT THE TOP, YOU HAVE
A DECISION TO MAKE.
YOU CAN EITHER CHOOSE TO
ASSEMBLE A PUZZLE OR TEST YOUR
DEXTERITY BY STACKING BALLS
WHILE STANDING ON A WOBBLY BEAM.
BOTH AVERAGE THE SAME AMOUNT OF
TIME TO FINISH, BUT IF YOU
CHOOSE THE RIGHT ONE FOR YOUR
TRIBE, YOU CAN FINISH MUCH
FASTER.
THE FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH
WIN IMMUNITY, ARE SAFE FROM THE
VOTE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT IN THIS
GAME.
EITHER ONE OF THESE PIECES OF
THEIDE DOES THE SAME THING-- IT
KEEPS YOU IN THIS GAME ANOTHER
DAY.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH, A MASSIVE FIRE-MAKING
KIT.
EVERYTHING YOU NEED-- DRY WOOD,
A TARP TO KEEP IT DRY, LIGHTER
FLUID, MATCHES, A FLINT, EVEN
CHARCOAL.
YOU WILL HAVE FIRE ALL THE TIME.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH, NOT AS
IMPRESSIVE, BUT GETS THE JOB
DONE, A FLINT.
FOR THE LOSERS, NOTHING.
BUT A DATE WITH ME AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
THAT IS A DISTINCTION NOBODY
EVER WANTS.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
>> I'LL PADDLE.
>> WE'RE DOING PUZZLE.
DO YOU WANT TO DO PUZZLES?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE DIVING.
>> I'M DIVING.
>> YOU'RE SURE.
>> I'M SURE, POSITIVE.
>> I'M NOT GOOD AT PUZZLES.
>> STOP TALKING ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE NOT GOOD AT.
ALL POSITIVE.
>> I'LL BE ONE OF THE ROWERS.
>> YOU'RE PRIMARY CIEFER.
>> THIS HASN'T BEEN EASY FOR ME.
I'VE BEEN HAVING A BIT OF A HARD
TIME.
I MIGHT BE GOING HOME TONIGHT
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO GO HOME
WITHOUT GIVING THIS ONE
EVERYTHING I HAVE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO THIS.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET IN THE
BOAT BEFORE YOU CAN DO ANYTHING
ELSE.
BEAUTY INTO THE BOAT QUICKLY.
BRAINS RIGHT BEHIND.
DARNELL STRUGGLING TO GET IN FOR
BRAIN BRAUN.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
>> Jeff: GETTING SOME HELP.
EVERYBODY'S IN FOR BEAUTY!
GO!
MICHELE MET WATER LOOKING FOR
THAT FIRST PADDLE.
GO, BRAINS!
IT'S AUBRY IN THE WATER.
DARNELL IN THE WATER FOR BRAWN.
>> WHERE DID THE GOGGLES GO?
>> THEY CAME OFF WHEN I DOVE IN.
>> Jeff: DARNELL LOST THE
MASK.
ONLY SECONDS INTO THE CHALLENGE,
THAT WAS AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER
FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE.
JENNY JUMPS IN NOW WITHOUT A
MASK.
MICHELE HAS THE FIRST PADDLE FOR
THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
GET IT IN THE BOAT!
YOU GOTTA PUT THE PADDLE IN THE
BOAT!
AUBRY HAS THE FIRST PADDLE FOR
THE BRAIN TRIBE.
BRAWN HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
WITHOUT A MASK.
CALEB HAS WANT SECOND PADDLE FOR
THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
AUBRY HAS THEIR SECOND PADDLE.
>> AWESOME JOB!
>> Jeff: JENNY FINALLY HAS THE
FIRST PADDLE FOR BRAWN.
TAI NOW IN THE WATER FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
THERE ARE FOUR PADDLES TOTAL.
THEY GET DEEPER WITH EACH ONE.
TAI HAS THE THIRD PADDLE FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
>> YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT, NICE
JOB.
>> Jeff: AUBRY HAS THE THIRD
PADDLE FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE.
>> JENNY HAS THEIR SECOND
PADDLE.
BEAUTY HAS THEIR FOURTH PADDLE.
START PADDLING, BEAUTY.
JENNY COMING OUT.
JAISON DIVES IN NOW WITHOUT A
MASK.
BEAUTY DOING A GREAT JOB WITH A
NICE EARLY LEAD.
JAISON WITH THE THIRD PADDLE FOR
THE BRAWN TRIBE.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE!
AUBRY WENT FOURTH PADDLE FOR THE
BRAIN TRIBE DID IT ALL HERSELF.
BEAUTY TRIBE IS BACK.
NOW YOU GOTTA PUSH THIS HUGE
BOAT UP INTO ITS CRADLE AND CLIP
IN.
BEAUTY WORKING TOGETHER NICE LE.
THIS TAKES A LOT OF STRENGTH TO
GET THIS BOAT UP INTO THAT
CRADLE.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE EVERYBODY.
HERE COMES THE BRAIN TRIBE
GETTING CLOSER.
BEAUTY STRUGGLING TO GET IN THAT
CRADLE.
YOU'RE GETTING THERE, BEAUTY!
BRAIN TRIBE IS BACK.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET YOURS IN THE
CRADLE.
CLIP IN.
BRAWN TRIBE STILL IN THE WATER.
BRAWN TRIBE HAS THEIR FOURTH AND
FINAL PADDLE WITHOUT A MASK.
HERE COMES THE BRAIN TRIBE.
THEY'RE HALFWAY.
HERE COMES THE BRAWN TRIBE.
AND, AMAZINGLY, STILL IN THIS
CHALLENGE BECAUSE BOTH THE
BEAUTY AND BRAIN TRIBE CANNOT
GET THEIR BOAT IN THE CRADLE.
>> PADDLE!
>> Jeff: NOBODY GIVING UP
HERE.
BEAUTY TRIBE MADE A LOT OF
PROGRESS RIGHT THERE.
THAT IS TEAM WORK!
BEAUTY TRIBE IS INCHING CLOSER
AND CLOSER.
AND HERE COMES THE BRAWN TRIBE.
WE'VE GOT A CHALLENGE!
COULD THE BRAWN TRIBE MAKE A
COMEBACK RIEMENT HERE?
BRAWN TRIBE DIGGING.
BEAUTY TRIBE DIGGING.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: BEAUTY HAS IT!
CLIP IN!
START PUTTING ON YOUR WHEELS.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: BRAINS YOU'RE IN!
LET'S GO.
CLIP IN, CLIP IN!
BRAWN TRIBE WITH A BIG EFFORT!
BRAWN HAS IT.
CLIP IN!
>> PUT IT ON.
>> Jeff: IT IS THE BRAIN TRIBE
NOW IN THE LEAD.
THEY ARE CLIPPED IN AND PUTTING
ON THEIR WHEELS.
THERE GOES AUBRY AND DEBBIE,
GOING TO GO UP AND PULL THAT
ROPE.
BEAUTY TRIBE HAS SLID OFF THE
TRACK, WHICH MAKES PUTTING ON
THESE WHEELS TOUGHER.
KEEP FIGHTING!
TWO TRIBES ARE GOING TO FINISH
THIS CHALLENGE.
BRAIN TRIBE HAS ALL FOUR WHEELS
ON.
THEY ARE IN THE LEAD NOW!
BRAWN HAS THEIR FOUR WHEELS.
START MOVING!
BEAUTY NOW GOING TO BE IN DEAD
LAST.
THE BRAIN TRIBE IS THERE.
>> PUZZLE.
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE UNTYING
THE PUZZLE BOX.
BRAWN STILL WORK THEIR WAY UP.
BEAUTY SLOWLY WORKING THEIR WAY
UP.
THIS HAIB A TAXING CHALLENGE FOR
EVERYBODY.
BUT EVERYBODY IS STILL IN IT.
THAT IS WHY YOU NEVER GIVE UP IN
THIS GAME!
IT IS LIZ AND AUBRY DOING THE
PUZZLE FOR THE BRAIN TRIBE WITH
A BIG LEAD RIGHT NOW.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: HERE COMES THE BRAWN
TRIBE.
THEY WERE IN DEAD LAST FOR MOST
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
THEY ARE NOW IN SECOND PLACE,
DESPITE TAKING FOREVER TO GET
THEIR PADDLES.
BEAUTY HAS BLOWN A HUGE LEAD BUT
IS QUICKLY GAINING ON BRAWN.
YOU'RE GOOD.
HOOK IT IN, BRAWN.
MAKE YOUR CHOICE.
WHICH BOX?
>> PUZZLE.
>> Jeff: RON UNTYING THE
PUZZLE BOX.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE
THE SURE THING.
JENNY AND ALECIA HAVE SOME WORK
TO DO TO CATCH UP.
>> GET THE ( BLEEP ) PIECES!
>> Jeff: WHAT YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE IS DEAD LAST AND RIGHT NOW
THAT LOOKS LIKE IT COULD BE
BEAUT WHOA HAS BLOWN A MASSIVE
LEAD.
KEEP DIGGING, BEAUTY!
HOOK IT IN!
GPUZZLE OR DEXITATOR!
>> PUZZLE EXPWHR BEAUTY WILL GO
FOR PUZZLE, TOO.
NOBODY WILL GO FOR THE HAIL MARY
AND TRY THE DEXTERITY.
IT IS JENNY AND ALECIA SOLVING
THE PUZZLE FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE,
AND LIZ AND AUBRY FOR THE BRAIN
TRIBE.
BRAINS STILL IN THE LEAD.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: LIZ AND AUBRY DOING A
NICE JOB WORKING TOGETHER.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: JENNY DOING ALL THE
WORK FOR THE BRAWN TRIBE.
>> ALECIA, YOU WANT TO TAG?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALECIA IS OUT.
SCOT IT COMING IN.
ALECIA CANNOT COME BACK IN.
SHE IS OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
BRAIN, PIECE BY PIECE GETTING
CLOSE TO WINNING THIS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT CLUES
CAN I FIND TO HELP ME SOLVE IT
BECAUSE THE OTHER TRIBES HAVE
HAD A BIG HEAD START.
AUBRY MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS
FOR THE BRAINS.
>> JEFF, JEFF!
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE HAS IT!
BRAIN TRIBE WINS IMMUNITY AND
REWARD!
FIRST CHALLENGE OF "SURVIVOR:
KOAH RONG"!
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
IT'S GOING TO BE BRAWN OR
BEAUTY.
ONE WILL GO BACK TO CAMP, ONE
WILL GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BRAIN HAS ALREADY WON IMMUNITY
AND A MASSIVE FIRE-MAKING KIT.
THIS IS A RACE.
IT IS JULIA AND ANNA WITH
ANOTHER PIECE FOR BEAUTY.
ANNA WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> LET'S GO, SCOT.
>> THERE WE GO, THERE WE GO.
>> GEN WEANOTHER PIECE FOR
BRAWN.
IT IS BACK AND FORTH.
PIECE VERSUS PIECE, EACH TRIBE
GETTING CLOSER.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: SCOT AND JENNY
FIGURING IT OUT.
AND ANOTHER PIECE.
>> LET'S GO!
KEEP GOING!
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE!
>> Jeff: THIS IS NECK AND NECK
RIGHT NOW.
>> YES, YES, YES.
>> COME ON, Y'ALL, WE'RE IN
THIS!
WE'RE IN THIS!
>> YES, YES!
>> Jeff: BEAUTY WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: JENNY WITH ANOTHER
PIECE FOR BRAWN.
BEAUT YOU DOWN TO THREE PIECES
IF THEY FIT.
>> SOMETHING IS NOT IN THE RIGHT
PLACE.
>> COME ON, BRAWN.
WE'RE IN THIS.
LET'S GET IT!
>> Jeff: BRAWN IS VERY CLOSE.
>> LET'S GO, SCOT.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: BOTH TRIBES DOWN TO
THEIR LAST PIECE!
BEAUTY HAS IT!
BEAUTY WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
SENDING THE BRAWN TRIBE TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE FIRST PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
BRAIN TRIBE, CONGRATULATIONS.
FIRST WIN OF THE SEASON.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, A MASSIVE
FIRE-MAKING KIT.
COME GRAB IT.
TAKE IT BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
BEAUTY TRIBE, IMMUNITY FOR YOU
AS WELL.
NOBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
( APPLAUSE )
IN ADDITION, NOT A BIG
FIRE-MAKING KIT BUT FLINT.
HERE IT IS.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, BEAUTY,
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
ALL RIGHT, BRAWN TRIBE, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> IT IS RISKATE TRIBAL BECAUSE
I'M NOT A PUZZLE WIDDARD!
BUT DARNELL DROPPED THE GLASSES
AND TOTALLY SCREWED UP THE
CHALLENGE.
SO THE ONLY WAY FOR ME TO STAY
IN THIS GAME RIGHT NOW IS TO TRY
TO GET THEM TO VOTE OFF DARNELL.
>> NO, THAT WAS MY FAULT.
>> I'M SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT IT.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I MEAN, I LOST THE GOGGLES.
AND THAT PUT US WAY BEHIND.
GROWING UP IN CHICAGO, I WAS A
LIFEGUARD, BUT I NEVER KNEW THAT
SEA WATER WAS THAT MURKY.
LIKE, YOU COULDN'T SEE NOTHING.
THAT WAS A HARD-ASS CHALLENGE,
PUSHING THAT BOAT.
>> WHEN PEOPLE IN THIS GAME ARE
NOT TALKING TO YOU, THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
WE HAVE TRIBAL TONIGHT.
I'M A GOOD CANDIDATE TO GO HOME.
SO I'M GOING TO DO WHAT I GOTTA
DO.
YOU ALL SAVE ME TONIGHT, I
PROMISE YOU'LL HAVE MY LOYALTY--
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT NO
MERGE, LIKE.
>> WE'RE VOTING BLONDIE.
>> BLONDIE, IT'S DONE.
>> I'M JUST LETTING YOU ALL
KNOW.
>> WE CAN ONLY TAKE SO MUCH
STUPID TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
>> WE HAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT, AND THE TWO PEOPLE THAT
ARE ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK, IT'S
DARN EXPEL ALECIA.
BUT REALLY THERE'S JUST ONE IN
MY OPINION.
DARNELL LOSES THE MASK.
HE APOLOGIZED, BUT THE DEAD
WEIGHT IN THE CHALLENGE, IT WAS
JUST UNACCEPTABLE.
>> HE'S GOING HOME.
WE'RE NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT,
ALL RIGHT?
>> I MEAN, IT JUST MAKES ME
QUESTION, THOUGH, HOW DO I KNOW?
>> LET IT HAPPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA LET THE
WORLD COME TO YOU.
YOU CAN'T FORCE EVERYTHING.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> TAKE IT ON FAITH.
WE'RE DEALING STRAIGHT.
AND I'M TELLING YOU--
>> I DON'T THINK I CAN TRUST
SCOT, BUT IF I CAN JUST TRY AND
BE A MASTER MANIPULATOR AND THEN
VOTE DARNELL, THAT'S THE ONLY
OPTION RIGHT NOW I REALLY HAVE.
I KNOW I'M AT THE BOTTOM RIGHT
NOW.
>> YOU'RE NOT.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD VOTE
DARNELL OUT.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU SOME FREE
ADVICE.
>> OKAY.
>> THE ONLY THING I HAVE AGAINST
YOU RIGHT NOW IS THE CONSTANT
SCHEMING.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU'RE GOOD.
>> AND DOES HE HAVE AN IDOL?
I KNOW HE'S BEEN LOOKING.
>> NO, HE DOESN'T HAVE ONE.
>> DO YOU HAVE ONE?
>> NEVER SAID I DID, NEVER SAID
I DIDN'T.
BUT HERE'S THE THING, LISTEN.
>> THAT JUST BLEW MY MIND.
I THREW HER A FREAKING BONE.
YOU'RE PUSHING YOURSELF OUT OF
THIS GAME.
IT'S OVER FOR ME.
I'M DONE.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE TRYING TO GIVE HER
BLATANT HINT TO JUST CALM DOWN
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING YOU'RE
DOING RIGHT NOW IS KILLING
YOURSELF.
>> WE ARE VOTING FOR DARNELL.
>> OKAY.
>> BLONDIE, SHE'S PISSING ME
OFF.
THE ONLY REASON I SAY DARNELL HE
JUMPED IN THE WATER, AND LOST
OUR GOGGLES.
YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
>> I'M NOT REALLY TO PRESSED.
I DON'T JUST-- WHATEVER.
>> SO WE'RE SET.
>> YUP.
>> THEY WANT TO VOTE DARNELL
OUT, BUT I DO PREFER ALECIA TO
GO JUST BASED ON THE SIMPLE FACT
THAT SHE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
I'D PREFER FOR DARNELL TO STICK
AROUND BECAUSE OF OUR INITIAL
ALLIANCE.
THE MEMBER NUMBERS I HAVE, THE
BETTER IT IS FOR ME.
SO WHEN I GET TO TRIBAL, I'M
GOING TO MAKE SURE PEOPLE KNOW
WHO NEEDS TO GO HOME.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GET A TORCH, DIP IT
IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE FIRE
REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE, AND WHEN
YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE YOU,
AND, SADLY, THAT WILL BE THE
CASE FOR SOMEBODY TONIGHT
BECAUSE WE'RE ABOUT TO VOTE OUT
THE FIRST PERSON FROM THIS GAME.
SO, JAISON, LET'S TALK ABOUT
FIRST IMPRESSIONS.
WHEN YOU GET A CHANCE TO REALLY
SEE WHO'S ON YOUR TRIBE, WHAT
WAS YOUR REACTION?
>> I WAS SATISFIED.
GOT A FORMER BASKETBALL PLAYER.
WE GOT THE NINTH TOUGHEST WOMAN
IN THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW, I SIT WITH SOME PEOPLE
I BELIEVE CAN STAND UP TO MY
HIGH STANDARDS.
>> Jeff: SOME PEOPLE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SOME PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: NOT EVERYBODY.
>> NOT EVERYBODY.
NOT EVEN CLOSE TO EVERYBODY.
>> Jeff: WHO STANDS OUT,
JAISON, AS SOMEBODY WHO MAYBE
CAN'T MEET YOUR EXPECTATION?
>> THERE ARE TWO PEOPLE ON OUR
TRIBE AND I HAVE NO PROBLEM
SAYING THE NAME, BLONDIE AND
DASCHLE.
>> Jeff: BLONDIE DOESN'T EVEN
GET A NAME.
>> WE CAN JUST GO WITH ALECIA.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT'S THAT FEEL
LIKE TO HAVE ONE OF YOUR TRIBE
MEMBERS SAY YOU'RE NOT GETTING
IT DONE?
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL GOOD, JEFF.
IT DOESN'T FEEL GOOD.
I MEAN, I KNOW RIGHT NOW THEY DO
SEE ME AS ONE OF THE WEAKER ONES
BUT I DO HAVE GOOD INTENTIONS
WITH THIS TRIBE AND HONESTLY, I
DON'T SEE MYSELF AS THE WEAKEST
LINK IN THIS TRIBE.
>> Jeff: DARNELL, YOUR NAME
MENTIONED AS SOMEBODY WHO ISN'T
GETTING IT DONE AS OF NOW.
>> I'LL BE HONEST, JEFF.
I WAS ONE OF THE KEY REASONES
YES WE LOST TODAY.
I STEPPED UP.
I SAID I WANT THAT OPPORTUNITY.
SO I DOVE IN FIRST, LOST THE
GOGGLES, AND THAT PUT US WAY
BEHIND.
BUT YOU KNOW, I WENT OUT THERE
AND I TRIED MY BEST.
>> JEFF, HE FLAT OUT OFFERED
IT-- "I CAN DIVE."
WE DIDN'T QUESTION.
OKAY, YOU'RE THE DIVE.
I'VE BEEN SNORKELING SINCE I WAS
12 YEARS OLD, AND EVERYBODY
KNOWS THE FIRST RULE OF DIVING
IS YOU HOLD ON BECAUSE IT COMES
OFF.
>> Jeff: DARNELL, YOU'RE
TAKING A LOT OF HEAT.
>> I KNOW I AM.
AND I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE ANY
EXCUSE.
I'M ONLY IT.
>> Jeff: ALECIA, DARNELL SAYS
THAT'S RIGHT.
I EARNED THIS.
>> WE DO HAVE TO KEEP THIS TRIBE
STRONG, JEFF.
AND I'M A MENTAL GIANT.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE STRUGGLES,
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO BREAK DOWN
OUT HERE.
I'M NOT GOING TO QUIT FIGHTING
FOR OUR TRIBE.
I'M GOING TO WORK MY BUTT OFF IN
CHALLENGES AND I WILL STEP UP
AND I REALLY WANT TO BE HERE AND
I THINK THEY KNOW THAT.
>> Jeff: SIDNEY, IT'S ALMOST
LIKE YOU'RE CONTAINED NAY BOX
AND YOU'RE TRYING TO GET OUT
WHILE LISTENING TO ALANDMARK'S
ANSWERS, BANGING OFF THE SIDE.
>> I AM, JEFF, I THINK SHE'S
SAYING THAT FOR SHOW THAN
BELIEVING SHE IS MENTAL STRONG.
>> I AM HONEST WITH YOU GUYS.
I AM NOT GOING TO SAY I CAN DO
SOMETHING WHEN I CAN'T.
LIKE THE CHALLENGE.
I TRIED TO DO THE PUZZLE AND WE
SWITCHED OUT.
>> WHAT IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN I'LL
BUST MY ASS TO TRY AND DO IT.
THE MINUTE YOU SAY YOU CAN'T,
YOU LOST BEFORE YOU START.
>> I DO AGREE WITH THAT.
I'LL GO OUT AND TRY MY BEST AND
WON'T QUIT FIGHTING FOR IT.
TODAY, DARNELL DIDN'T GO DOWN
AND TRY AND FIGHT AND GET THE
MASK.
HE CAME BACK UP.
I WOULDN'T HAVE GIVEN UP.
>> I ALSO PADDLED THE BOAT AND
PUSHED THE BOAT UP.
YOU DID ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
YOU DIDN'T ROW.
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT'S EASY TO SAY, "I DID A
PUZZLE.
I KNOW I MEASED UP, BUT I
GUARANTEE YOU, I'M GOING TO GO
OUT THERE AND I'M GOING TO MAKE
IT HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: DARNELL, IT FEELS
LIKE THERE IS A REALLY HEAVY
WEIGHT ON YOU RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT I WENT THROUGH TODAY WAS
ONE OF THE BIGGEST CHALLENGES OF
MY LIFE, A HEAVY WEIGHT, JEFF.
I REALLY FEEL BAD.
>> Jeff: COMPARE THIS TO LIFE
BACK HOME.
HAVE YOU HAD SIMILAR EXPERIENCES
IN TERMS OF BEING CHALLENGED
THAT WOULD RIVAL THIS?
>> THINGS WASN'T ALWAYS EASY FOR
ME SO, YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS HAD TO
FIGHT FOR EVERYTHING.
AND TO JUST LOSE, IT HURTS.
I DO NOT WANT TO DISAPPOINT NO
ONE UP HERE AT ALL.
LIKE, I LET ALL THESE PEOPLE
DOWN AND IT HURTS.
IT HURTS BAD.
>> Jeff: JENNY, CAN YOU RELATE
OR EMPATHIZE TO BEING IN
DARNELL'S SITUATION?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHEN HE SAID HE HASN'T HAD IT
EASY IN LIFE, WOW, AS SOON AS HE
SAID, THAT I WAS LIKE OH!
EMPATHY STRINGS JUST GOT PULLED
A MILE.
I'VE LOST A LOT AS WELL.
AND YOU GET TIRED OF LOSING.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK HE'S GETTING
AT.
>> Jeff: SO, JAISON, FIRST
VOTE, OBVIOUSLY IT'S AN
IMPORTANT ONE.
IT SETS A TONE.
DIFFICULT DECISION IN YOUR MIND
RIGHT NOW?
>> I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU,
SITTING HERE I DID THINK AND SAY
ARE WE MAKING THE WRONG CHOICE?
>> Jeff: SCOT, THERE'S A LOT
GOING ON AT TRIBAL RIGHT NOW.
IT'S ONLY SIX PEOPLE.
IT'S AMAZING HOW MANY LAYERS
THERE CAN BE.
>> BUT THAT'S WHAT TRIBAL'S
ABOUT.
THERE ARE PEOPLE WITH THEIR
BACKS AGAINST THE WALL.
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO MAKE SURE
IT'S NOT THEIR BACK AGAINST THE
WALL.
>> Jeff: AS THEY SHOULD.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE DOING WHAT
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
SO, YEAH, THERE'S A LITTLE
PING-PONG MATCH GOING ON.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TIME TO
FIND OUT WHICH ONE OF YOU IS
GOING HOME.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DARNELL, YOU'RE
UP.
>> YOU'RE REALLY STARTING TO IRK
MY SOUL, A LOT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ALECIA.
DARNELL.
ALECIA.
TWO VOTES ALECIA, TWO VOTES
DARNELL.
ALECIA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ALECIA, TWO
VOTES DARNELL, ONE VOTE LEFT.
DARNELL.
WE HAVE A TIE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE A
TIE.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
WE'RE GOING TO REVOTE.
DARNELL AND ALECIA, YOU WON'T
VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE, YOU WILL ONLY
VOTE FOR DARNELL OR ALECIA.
CYDNEY, IF YOU'LL COME GRAB THE
URN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
DARNELL.
THAT'S TWO VOTES DARNELL.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
KO"SURVIVOR: KOAH RONG - BRAINS
VS. BRAWN VS. BEAUTY," DARNELL.
THAT'S THREE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DARNELL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> BYE, DARNELL.
>> Jeff: WELL, THERE WAS A
THEME TO TONIGHT'S TRIBAL-- IF
YOU'RE GOING TO TALK THE TALK,
YOU BETTER BE ABLE TO WALK THE
WALK.
THE ONLY GOOD NEWS ABOUT COMING
TO TRIBAL TONIGHT, YOU WILL GO
HOME WITH FIRE.
FRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
"SURVIVOR."
>> WE HAVE THE BIGGEST FRONTAL
LOBES.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE MAY HAVE THE
BRAINS BUT SHE'S NOT FITTING IN.
>> DOES SHE HAVE 30 CATS OR 40
CATS?
>> Jeff: WHILE TAI MAKES A BIG
MOVE.
>> YOU TRIED TO KISS ME.
>> NO, I DID NOT.
I WAS TOTALLY GOING FOR THE
KISS.
>> THIS WAS VERY HARD BEING
VOTED OUT NUMBER ONE.
BUT I ENJOYED EVERY MOMENT OF
IT.
THIS WAS A LIFE LESSON PIWHAT I
LEARNED WAS FIGHT HARD.
THEY CAN VOTE ME OUT AND DO WHAT
THEY WANT BUT I WON'T LET
ANYBODY BRING ME DOWN.
YEAH, I'M OUT NUMBER ONE.
BUT I WENT OUT THERE AND PLAYED
HARD AND I'M SATISFIED WITH
THAT.