translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Muscles and Beauty
formed the dominant alliance
and aimed at Intelligence.
It is more or less established
that the Intelligences will leave.
But Cydney was fed up
with men controlling the game.
Don't watch me,
you're not my father!
Pissed off Cydney will blow it all up!
So she rallied the women
to get a man out.
Are you up
for voting Nick tonight?
If it sucks, well,
I will be the first to react.
On the advice...
We also heard about
a super-idol.
...Tai made a big mistake.
I thought everyone knew.
But for Cydney,
everything went according to plan .
when the women
sent Nick to the jury...
Nick, the tribe has spoken.
...Scot, Jason and Tai reuniting
to wonder what to do,
at the bottom of the scale.
There are nine left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Good game !
Girl power, huh?
Nice shot, girls.
The girls did a great job
and took us by surprise.
The Muscles alliance
is clearly over.
Now it's Jason and me.
And Tai.
Are the girls together?
- It's clear.
- With Joe.
At the council, I said,
"Jeff, there's a super-idol.", and...
Oh no !
I have spoken too much again!
So, who did you vote for?
So I freaked out
and voted for Jason,
but I dreaded
having to explain this vote.
Because I don't lie very well.
So I said, "I voted Debbie."
We should have saved Nick tonight.
Yeah, but we can still use it.
They don't know I have it.
- So you really have one?
- Yes.
I have one.
You have one.
The super-idol is real.
On the next board,
when they try something,
we'll be like,
"Guess what, bunch of bitches!"
We are only three,
but we have two idols.
And together,
they form a super-idol.
How about
taking their food?
We don't give them anything?
After bedtime,
the machete and ax disappear.
Yeah. Far far away.
Very far.
We'll take
the machete and the ax,
take away their ability
to do things,
just to demoralize them a bit.
It's psychological warfare.
I did it in the military
and as a bounty hunter.
We cut their relations,
we confuse their heads,
we maintain their weakness,
we look for the fault, their weaknesses,
we read between the lines
and we try to hit.
I love psychological warfare.
We make life in the camp miserable,
we don't bring anything to eat.
Do we agree on that?
It's a game,
I have to follow the strategy.
But the
Jason and Scot way
is really extreme.
When we talk about taking food and equipment away from the girls ,
this makes me uneasy.
It's not my approach to life
or problem solving.
I'm not proud of it
but I cannot
control their actions.
It's time to sow chaos.
Hello, Joe.
- Tai is up?
- Nope.
I've been lighting the fire for two days .
Sabotage
is above all to weaken them.
'Cause it might
freak someone out
and I hope
that will change things.
I found the machete.
- Where is she ?
- Just there.
It's time I tried
to ruin everyone else's life.
Let's put that somewhere.
It's a good path.
We took the machete and the ax,
we went a little deeper
into the jungle...
It's a needle in a
haystack, how would they know?
...and we hid the tools.
They will never find them.
I'm not going to lie down and say,
"Hey, well done!"
All we can do
is fight, and that's what we will do.
And if that means
ruining the lives of others along the way,
that's what I will do.
Jason, will you...?
If you want, I pour.
The advice was wonderful.
People who thought they
had total control
discovered
that it was an illusion.
It's good.
And now they are angry.
So the atmosphere is unpleasant.
- You want some ?
- Yeah.
It shows their character
the bad losers that they are.
They are not gentlemen.
Do you know where the machete is?
She was there.
You opened cocos
last night.
And the axe?
Ax and machete, missing.
- No machete?
- No axe.
Where have they gone?
This morning, upon awakening,
one of the girls,
Michele, I believe,
was looking for the machete and the ax...
Disappeared.
Could it be sabotage?
I think that's
the right term, sir.
I believe that's it.
Muscles took them.
It's ridiculous.
We don't hide tools
essential for the whole tribe.
It's really immature.
We'll find a way to eat
without a machete or an ax.
We fuck them.
The boys
think they can break us
by doing that,
but we'll use our brains
to find another way.
We're going to grill them,
like we used to.
Oh ! Missed !
It's going to work.
No big guys needed.
We'll find a way.
We do with what we have.
In 20 minutes,
we found a new way.
Wow, it opens!
You won't stop us!
Attractive ! It suddenly opened!
It's fun, actually.
I quite like this method.
I listen to their:
"Everything is fine! We're in control!
We'll heat the coconuts,
like before!
Everything will be alright !"
And... I was already upset.
Attractive !
But that was the last straw.
Alright, are you showing off again?
Now I'm drunk,
and I'm going to do something stupid.
It wasn't that long.
Let's end the speculation.
Why do you do that ?
- Why are you sabotaging us?
- Why did you sabotage us?
- What ? That's the game.
- Exactly.
Pour water on the fire?
- Come on, that's petty.
- It's part of the game.
You are the fire starter.
Light a fire.
I am speechless.
You show your true face.
I do not tolerate this kind
of behavior in my normal life.
I won't tolerate it here either.
Good. Let's turn it back on.
They can
fuel the power struggle,
but we will not back down.
We will always find a way.
Let's go.
Well done, my dear.
They turned it back on.
I knew they would get there.
Not serious. We'll turn it back on.
But we have to make life difficult for them.
Can't be too extreme.
- Why not ?
- They'll fire us anyway.
It will be hard for me to watch.
But I have to take a step back.
Picking on us last night
didn't bother them.
Exactly.
Let's find another
fun thing to do.
Over here, everyone!
At the last tip,
it was clearly
a surprise elimination.
Did it have an impact
on the camp?
Or does
the game just continue?
I feel
like the cold war is over
and the missiles are going
all over the place, frankly.
- In other words ?
- There is sabotage on the camp.
When I woke up,
the hatchet was gone,
machete,
and Scot poured
20 liters of water on our fire
to turn it off.
Scot, what is the reasoning
behind this action?
I just sent a message:
it is I who will fetch the water.
There are mangoes on the camp,
because I help Tai to climb
the tree and he picks them.
I can climb that damn tree!
Good luck.
We'll see.
It's clearly animated.
It should be interesting.
- Ready for the reward test?
- Yes.
Good. Today,
you will be divided
into two teams of four.
Each team
will be tied to a long rope.
At my signal,
you will work together to distress her.
When she
's completely unwound,
you will detach
and use sandbags
to knock blocks off
their support.
The first team
to free support from any block
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
It's something
you could do,
on a Friday night,
your house.
Chinese meals to take away,
delivered to the camp.
- Oh my God !
- So, I have a question.
We were going to form the teams
like a schoolyard.
But if you can
agree,
do it now,
otherwise we'll draw lots.
But be careful:
one person will be excluded.
This person may choose
to support a team.
If she chooses well,
she will enjoy the reward.
I do not participate.
You are not participating.
Well, that simplifies things.
Now there are eight people.
Do we have two quartets?
There is animosity, let
it be expressed!
Any of the girls
want to join us?
We have Tai, Jason and Scot
looking for a girl.
I will go.
Julia rushes in front
and says she will go with the guys,
fast enough.
I thought, "Wait,
what's really going on?"
I decided to go with the boys,
because at this point
I know that attracting Scot and Jason
can be of great benefit to me.
It's time for me
to start acting and playing my game.
Julia joins Tai, Jason and Scot.
Which leaves Michele,
Joe chose not to participate.
Which team will you support?
Girls.
- Joe chooses the girls. Easy.
- It's good.
Good.
Take a seat, let's get started.
Let's go.
For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Michele, below.
I pass over it.
No better test
for a group that does not get along.
Below? Above !
Lots of rope to distress.
The better you communicate,
the sooner you will be free
and can start
throwing your sandbags.
And I go over it.
- The women are doing well.
- Go girls !
Jason and Tai are tangled.
If you get tangled up, you'll fall
behind quickly.
I can't go under.
It makes knots.
Julia, go over the two.
The Yellows are accelerating.
I passed.
Julia chose
to join the men.
So far it works.
Women slow down.
Aubry, Michele, Cydney, Debbie
are all tangled up.
Scot, Jason, Tai and Julia
are very close to the goal.
- Below.
- Yeah, that's it.
Now you have to turn around
to free yourself
and bring back
the four separate strings.
I'm free.
The women are detached.
They try to turn
and release the rope.
Julia is free.
Its good ! Free yourself !
Start throwing your bags!
Tai, Scott, Jason and Julia.
You have to knock down
all these blocks from the support.
Aubry, the last woman,
has to go around.
There should be no more rope
on top of the log.
Good !
Jason hits the mark again.
Come on, girl!
The women are done!
Detach yourself!
Women need to step up.
Jason continues to shoot.
It will take more than that to get back up.
Jason is exhausted.
Here is Scott.
He throws with force.
Very big blow for Scot.
Who knows how to throw hard?
Cydney misses again.
This is Debbie.
Debbie takes down two more.
Debbie takes down three more.
Debbie drops another one.
The women are coming back!
Debbie has one hell of an arm.
Debbie takes down two more.
Scot tries his hand at delicacy.
You need to release the media.
All those blocks still count.
Scot shoots down another.
Again a hotly contested race.
Debbie shoots two.
Debbie drops another one.
It's very tight.
Scot shoots down another.
More than three for the men.
More than two for men.
There are six left for the women.
Five for women.
More than one for Jason.
One more hit for Jason
and it's over.
Like in baseball!
And There you go !
Jason, Scott, Tai and Julia
win the reward!
Huge effort.
Neck and neck again,
with teams chosen by you.
Jason, Scot, Thailand, Julia,
a great reward
awaits you on the camp.
Take-out Chinese
will be delivered to you.
Pack your things,
head back to camp, enjoy!
Cydney, Michele, Aubry, Joe, Debbie.
I have nothing for you.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Julia and the boys
won the award.
And as soon as I saw her
go with the boys,
I knew she was trying
to improve her position.
She plays both ways.
But I see clearly in his game.
I can't
trust him at all.
Noble effort.
I am happy for you.
Enjoy.
Tai, you're going to have your noodles!
I'm happy for you.
In today's race, we won.
Everything changes in the blink of an eye.
That's what makes this game
so wonderful.
- You're going to have your noodles, Tai!
- Yeah, you're going to have your noodles.
We are again
on the upward slope.
We're not at the top,
but Julia has restarted the machine.
We have a chance.
Ah, noodles!
- Good job guys !
- Owl !
Julia, Tai, Jason, me
and Marc the chicken,
we ate Chinese
and drank a few beers.
Everything was spot on.
Oh, horoscope cookies!
But the best in it,
it's having the opportunity to speak
with Julia, to see what she thinks.
If you had the choice,
what would you do ?
And don't worry
if you see it without us, I get it.
No, I see that with you,
for now.
Eliminating you
would be stupid of me.
Because then I would be at the end
from the chain
of Cydney, Joe, Debbie and Aubry.
At this stage,
you have to think long term.
I have my other allies,
in whom I trust,
but to take people
like Scot and Jason to the end,
who betrayed people,
wreaked havoc on the camp,
might be a good idea.
Because at this point,
no juror would vote for them.
You should do
what's best for you.
Whatever you do, please
communicate with us.
I will, from now on.
It's easier to be a villain.
When there are only five of us left,
it will be exceptional.
Here they are.
Who is that ?
Behind us.
Are they already finished?
She went to the dark side.
You know, she's very smart.
She plays with them.
On will come.
Some think that Julia
has it both ways,
but i have no
worries
as to a betrayal by Julia.
They tried to lure you out?
A little.
No chance.
Tomorrow, I hope it's Scot.
I don't believe Jason
is the mastermind. It's Scotus.
Is that where we split the votes?
We'll see who wins and we'll discuss.
- OK.
- OK ?
My canard radar was doing this
when Julia was talking to Miss Debbie.
You find it strategic
to come from this group
and start by asking:
"What strategy for the next
board?" I do not trust.
She thinks she's clever,
but it doesn't work with me.
I see it coming
as big as a house.
What I think...
Give me your opinion.
- Exactly.
- That's what I think.
- It's the most dangerous.
- She goes back and forth.
Exactly. She makes sense
and socially intelligent.
Julia doesn't want wedding rings.
She wants to stay in the center
until the end.
She plays both ways.
But sometimes the person in the middle
of the road gets knocked down.
And I hope it will be her.
I woke up
in the middle of the night.
I thought, "You know what?
I am engaged with the boys.
I was upset
when Scot put out the big fire.
My heart feels it.
But I have to take a step back
compared to my sympathy.
I like them,
but if it's war, we have to
complicate the life of the other side.
So I decided to put out the fire.
For now, it's them or us.
my evil side
rarely emerges, but it does happen.
What is the situation ?
- Dead.
- Completely off?
Yes, completely.
Maybe
we poured water on it again.
- Any embers left?
- No, it's dead.
This sabotage
is partly childishness.
But today, Scot and Jason
knew what they were doing.
It was to mislead us,
to vote for them,
because they probably have idols.
My instinct tells me,
flashing furiously,
that Julia must go.
Scot really pissed me off
with the fire today.
Now
it compromises our diet.
And our survival.
I want him to go.
- OK. Do you want my opinion ?
- Sure.
Scot didn't do it out of anger,
that's for sure.
He's smart, it was deliberate.
He tries to agitate us
so that we target him and Jason.
I really think, Deb,
that we would blow up all the idols
by voting Julia.
OK. That's the thing.
We have to fire all the guys first.
It kills me
let Debbie follow her emotions.
Scot poured this water on the fire
to provoke a reaction.
I want to say to Debbie:
"You are getting emotional.
But right now,
you have to be logical."
My instinct,
and I respect your instinct,
tells me Scot or Jason has to go.
But I ask you
if it's less risky
- and it would blow up the idols...
- I won't vote for Julia.
- I will not do it.
- OK.
Debbie doesn't budge.
I followed her
on many things,
but I firmly believe
that Julia has to leave.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First, Tai,
I'm taking the necklace back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will place
a series of blocks on a rail
avoiding tripping
over the obstacle.
If you hit the obstacle,
your blocks will fall
and you will have to replace them.
The goal: to place the blocks
so that they fall
like dominoes
and hit
a gong at the end.
The first person
to strike the gong wins immunity,
is sheltered from the council,
one in eight chance
to win this game.
The losers: on the council,
someone will be eliminated
and will become
the third member of the jury.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
One block at a time
and you must have
both feet inside
before placing the first.
It is speed or accuracy.
The faster you go,
the more risk you take.
You have to space them out so that they fall
like dominoes.
Not too close
nor too far.
Just the right distance.
Tai loses coins,
he has to go again.
As soon as a block falls,
you must start again
and then return to the obstacle.
Michele took the lead.
Jason is right behind her.
Aubry is in on it.
Scot tries to keep up.
Joe and Cydney are losing ground.
Julia, slowly but surely.
Jason loses everything.
First total disaster.
Jason does it again.
Scott loses everything...
It's okay, Michele!
...giving Michele
a great chance to win.
Tai goes back to Michelle.
It all depends on Tai.
Can he catch Michele?
Tai loses everything.
He is no longer in the game.
It's between Michele, Debbie and Aubry.
- As long as it's you or me!
- It's very tight.
Julia progressed slowly
but surely throughout.
To have a chance,
she is going to have to work harder
or hope for a mistake from Michele.
Aubry runs.
Aubry takes a big hit
and loses it all.
It's between Michele,
and Julia.
Cydney loses everything.
She's out of it.
Michele returns
with potentially her last block.
Only Julia and Debbie
have a chance of catching her.
This may be the end.
Is the spacing good?
It's good, my daughter!
Here we go, for victory!
So far so good.
But no ! Michele fails!
Michele has to replace almost everything!
It gives
Debbie and Julia an opportunity.
And Julia loses blocks.
- Debbie can win.
- Come on, Debbie!
She can win with this block.
Jason does not wait to be fixed.
He is still working, block by block.
Debbie is going to give it a shot.
For victory.
Let's go.
Debbie fails!
She will have to replace the blocks.
New opportunity!
It is now Julia who tries
to place her missing blocks.
And suddenly, Scot and Jason
are in on it again.
Without warning.
Jason had lost everything...
- I have to space them out.
- ...earlier in the test,
but he did not give up.
He kept fighting
and he's in on it.
Julia hurries
to replace her blocks.
She still has her chances.
Scot reverses everything again.
Jason takes the time
to put everything back from the end
to reduce the distance,
but he gives Julia a chance to
come back, it's risky.
But he is decided.
Julia places another block.
He only seems to be missing one.
It will be played on the wire.
Debbie replaces her blocks,
she doesn't give up.
Jason replaced everything.
Will it work?
It was swollen.
Jason, for the win.
Jason fails!
New opportunity!
Julia places her last block.
Michele goes back up,
only missing a few blocks.
I'm done, Jeff!
Debbie, without warning, has finished.
Debbie gives it a shot.
No, Debbie fails!
Julia, for the win.
And she succeeds!
Julia wins individual immunity!
Well done Julia!
It was awesome.
Julia, come here.
The youngest in this game,
and still going strong.
A one in eight chance
of winning this game.
As for you, after 24 days,
someone will be eliminated tonight
and become the 3rd juror.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council. Congratulation.
Thanks, Jeff.
The worst has happened.
Julia won.
And the plan I believed in
fell apart.
Just collapsed.
What to do now ?
The trick
was to use them all.
- You used them all. Good game.
- I was missing one.
Alright, I know we're gonna talk fast.
I just want to suggest this
while we're all here.
- [???]
- Alright.
I say we split the votes
between Tai and Scot.
Jason will expect
it to be him.
No chance
that the three have an idol.
If it's 3 - 3 - 3,
we vote again for Scot.
Oh no.
Deb says, "Here's the plan."
Right in front of Julia.
And that really scares me.
For this to go well,
we all have to agree.
Aubry, you, Joe and I are voting Scot.
They will vote Tai.
In this scenario,
the vote would be three for Scot,
three for Tai and three...
...decided by the boys.
I will look for Tai.
Let him take care of his damn bird.
But Julia played
the double agent pretty well,
and if only one person deviates,
everything explodes,
and a person
you wanted to keep leaves.
Want to know the plan?
What's this ?
They split the votes
between you and Tai.
So, vote Cydney and it's over.
OK.
If Julia decides
to be our little guardian angel,
and
hopefully she votes for Cydney,
it will be 4 - 2 - 3.
But if Julia
decides to follow her group,
we pull out all the stops,
we say we have idols,
we'll do whatever we can imagine
to make sure you stay.
We have no other option.
Good then...
But why is Miss Debbie
sharing the info like that?!
Don't say anything to Julia!
To believe that she wants
to screw everything up.
she worries me a lot.
Debbie is deaf to all logic.
She fully trusts
Julia.
And so far in Survivor,
i need a logical person
and which I know
will not deviate.
Should I give up on Debbie,
is that what you think?
And you know what ?
I am not against.
I don't think
Joe would be against it.
It's incredibly difficult
for me.
I don't want Debbie gone.
But when people
show me who they are,
I'll base it on that.
I still have Michele,
you still have Joe.
I have Joe, that's for sure.
As long as you're sure you have Michele...
- I have to make sure.
- OK.
Aubry and I agree:
Debbie would cause our downfall
before Scot and Jason did.
We'll have them later.
Aubry submitted the idea to me
that you, me, Joe and Aubry
vote Debbie.
I say to myself... Shit!
I didn't expect to see the light of day
where the four of us would attack Debbie.
Can we discuss honestly?
Debbie worries me a little.
She said a few
emotional things.
She trusts Julia,
why?
The girl who just spent 5 minutes
chatting with Scot!
- She probably told him everything.
- We have to vote Debbie.
No. Absolutely not.
Aubry offers to take Debbie out.
But it's useless
because we have a force
that holds up well.
We have to stick
with this idea: Debbie.
I don't know if there are enough of us.
If we convince Julia,
there are always four of us.
I trust you, Cydney,
and your instincts.
Let's talk about it with her, hoping
she doesn't screw us.
- Are you telling him or is it me?
- I will tell him.
Now, we need to talk to Julia.
And it's scary, because now,
The person I wanted to date
is the one I need.
- So ?
- Good.
Are you with us for real?
She is with us for real.
Alright, so we trust you
on this one.
If you fuck us, I explode.
- No, I know.
- Period. But really.
We vote for Debbie.
- Aubry up for it?
- Yeah.
I walk.
Let's shake hands.
It's Debbie. We will do it.
We will do it.
Oh my God !
Have a foot
in several alliances
gave me a lot of power.
- Welcome back !
- Thanks !
I have the power
to take out Debbie or Cydney.
Jason, Scot, and Tai
really want Cydney out.
She is very dangerous
because she talks to everyone.
But I want Debbie gone sometime
.
So my choice will decide.
Now here are
the members of our jury.
and Nick, eliminated at the last council.
Good. Let 's go back
to the reward test,
where a lot of information
was revealed.
Debbie, this tribe
is clearly divided.
I do not remember having seen
such a marked division.
And it was very hard,
because we don't eat.
We have no hatchet or machete.
So our lives
not figuratively,
our lives, literally,
are in danger.
Is this the purpose
of the actions of Scot, Jason and Tai?
To try to generate chaos?
So that, perhaps,
the game fractures?
It's possible.
Water on fire, it was epic.
Like ordering fajitas
at a Mexican restaurant.
Everything squirted out, and it was kind
of like a symbol of...
I love it.
Julia, there's a lot going on
and we still haven't talked
about the reward trial,
where you went
with Tai, Scot and Jason.
What was the reaction of others
when did you
volunteer?
The alliance
that decided to eliminate Nick
was okay with me going
with Tai, Jason and Scot.
Someone had to do it
and I volunteered.
Debbie, you nod.
Yeah, no worries, I'm glad
she ate well.
She deserved to eat,
and that was brave of her
to propose like this,
because one could believe this or that.
I just thought
you wanted to eat Chinese!
And, Michele, result:
big meal
for Jason, Scot, Tai and Julia.
And see
who is wearing the necklace today!
Yes, she is protected tonight
and it's a great opportunity
to show where his loyalty lies.
She can be quiet
and vote according to the direction
she wants to take
and the people she wants to play with.
And I think I know which camp it will be.
Tai, at the last tip,
we talked about idols.
Are there any? Is there a super-idol?
What is that ?
Maybe someone is lying!
Do you
think idols will appear?
Based
on this conversation, yes.
I think idols
will appear.
If there has.
We could simply
say what is going to happen.
Excellent idea !
Okay, Jason and Scot,
what's going to happen?
Well, Tai has an idol.
Tai isn't going anywhere tonight.
- He's safe.
- He stays here.
He's not moving.
I have an idol.
He's an idol.
- Can I see her ?
- Yes.
A moment !
The idol has a little sister!
There are two !
Yeah !
- They should combine them, right?
- Oh yeah.
- The same vote, huh?
- Yes.
Let's see if I understand correctly.
Tai, you say,
"I have an idol and I'm going to play it."
Clearly.
- We're 6 to 3.
- They're 6 to 3.
It's 100%,
or 30%, at least 35%.
And, Jason,
- you have another idol.
- Exact.
And guess what?
We're all going to vote.
When you ask,
"Is there an idol to play?",
we will get up,
we will do paper-pebble-scissors.
The winner will be able to play the idol,
the loser will be in danger.
Oh no.
I'll let fate decide
if I stay in the game,
thanks to this idol, or if it's Scot.
Original plan.
- And, Jason, it's debatable.
- In effect.
Right in front of you.
In effect.
You know they say
Tai won't let go of his idol,
but he could give it,
and then both would have one.
We must therefore place
our six votes wisely,
because we only have one chance.
It doesn't stop!
Julia, isn't it great
to have this necklace?
I love it !
I really love it!
Good. Are we ready to vote?
Wait. Its good ?
- Its good ?
- Yes it's good.
Good. Without a doubt,
one of the craziest councils
I have ever had the pleasure of attending.
It's time to vote.
Cydney, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
One second, Jeff.
Shit !
Or maybe we should
give it to Tai.
Yeah, let's do that.
We give away my idol
in Tai.
I accept the idol.
And I sit down.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
It's not written like that.
Scot.
Cydney. Two votes Scot,
two votes Cydney.
Cydney.
That's three Cydney votes.
Oh my God.
Debbie.
That's two Debbie votes.
Debbie. Equality.
Three votes Cydney,
three votes Debbie,
two Scot votes, one vote remains.
Eighth person eliminated
and third member of the jury...
Debbie.
Bring me your torch.
They are quiet for a moment.
Debbie, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
There is rarely a theme
as evident as in this season,
and it is very clear.
Even if it seems hopeless,
nothing is ever lost.
And even if you feel
safe,
you are not necessarily.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: lshomie, Lny
Synchro: Lny
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
With the power of the super-idol...
We have a super-idol.
We stay.
...Jason, Scot and Tai
feel invincible.
We are unstoppable.
But Aubry tries to snatch Tai
from the dark side.
Tai is not like Jason and Scot.
They are despicable.
I do not know what to do.
The big surprise was
that the girls decide
to eliminate a girl.
It amazes me,
and it will make it harder for them
to defeat Scot, Jason and Tai.
And it really sucks
that these three wankers
go further than me.
But they played better.