translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
In the Intelligence tribe,
Debbie's eccentricity...
We have the biggest frontal lobes!
...designated it as a pawn
to be used in the game.
This is exactly what is needed,
an Intelligent who has no game.
In the Beauty tribe,
the women's alliance was growing stronger.
An alliance of girls
seemed natural to me.
While
Tai's idol hunt...
First, you will need a key
to open this box.
This tool will help you.
...became desperate.
I can't have the idol.
I will have to come back another day.
At the last immunity test,
the Muscles tribe lost again.
...Returning Muscles to the Council!
Approaching the board,
Alecia seemed like
the obvious choice.
Blondie is useless.
But Jenny hesitated.
Jason is starting to piss me off.
On the advice...
There were hesitations,
"What do we do?"
...Jenny revealed her indecision.
Now I wonder.
And she paid dearly for it,
saving Alecia
for the second tip in a row.
Jenny, the tribe has spoken.
There are 16 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Alecia, just so you know,
I am the 2nd person
who voted against you.
But I already knew
there would be three votes against Jenny.
I had promised him
not to write his name, that's all.
OK.
- That's all. Without resentment.
- Great.
I just don't get
why you would write...
...my name, if Jenny
leaves anyway.
I don't get it. But...
- I have just told you.
- Its good.
I am loyal.
Scotus said, "I only wrote your name
only because I knew
Jenny was leaving."
I don't think I've ever
heard anything so stupid.
We go to the well.
"I can't believe you
wrote my name anyway."
If you betray my trust once,
you won't get it back.
Scott must go.
He is a millionaire,
he played ten years for the NBA.
- You know ?
- Yeah.
Alecia constantly baffles me.
She thinks we're allies
and it's "us against them."
But she doesn't know how
close I am to guys.
I just do:
"Mmh, that sounds good, I'm walking, whatever
you want, I'm walking."
I really think
we made a mistake tonight.
That's why.
How to win the next event
with 3 1/2 people?
All I can say
is that with this vote,
I believe that she trusts me more,
which is good for all of us.
- She clearly wants me gone.
- In effect.
Things have changed a lot
tonight at the council.
I lost a third
of my original alliance.
And here, Alecia feels reinforced
and could get me in trouble.
So many changes in one day!
Breakfast is ready.
Tai will eat the rest.
He is crazy.
He eats fish heads,
he eats everything.
People watch each
other like hawks.
But I'm going to get the idol
now. It is time.
A chance.
My only one, I think.
I think the tribe
really appreciates me, on a human level.
But only the idol
will give me a sense of security.
I know where she is
I just have to get the key out.
Gotta take a stick,
tie the tool to it
and poke through the container
to push the key.
No that's not true !
Where is the tool?
It's too stupid.
Don't tell me
I left it somewhere else.
I don't know how,
I lost the tool.
I want myself to death.
I don't get anything easily
in life.
Including this idol.
I see you.
Hi !
All my life I have known challenges.
In Vietnam, in the refugee camp,
when I came to the USA
and had to reinvent myself...
And that is another big challenge.
So I had to make myself
another tool for my stick.
You are going to be tough
for me, my friend.
It will happen,
please, please!
Please !
Go back... with me!
We're made for each other.
Get in there!
Yes ! Yes !
Oh my God !
“Congratulations, you have found the key
to the Immunity Idol.
Follow the map
to free your treasure."
Merci !
Thank you, tree!
It's been way too long.
Come see dad.
Here we are.
Oh, here it is!
Oh, my God, this is going to save my life.
It'll save my life.
I found the idol.
I worked so hard for this!
Jeff made it so...
It's not easy!
But I never give up.
Because the idol and I
are made for each other.
"Immunity Idol Rules."
"If you want to use the idol,
say so after the vote..."
Yes, I know this rule well.
"There is a surprise.
If you match
two immunity idols,
they form a super-idol.
A super-idol can be played
after the votes are read."
It is serious ?!
After reading the votes!
Two idols that come together
form a super-idol
who can save a person.
It's fantastic !
It's quite a surprise
for this season!
I'm going to wear it a little bit.
Here we are, planning
our victory strategy,
and we have a guy
working his chocolate bars.
It's the Intelligence tribe!
I have a central alliance with Liz,
but we manage
two separate groups of two.
Debbie and Joe,
and Aubry and Neal.
But we have control.
It would be a mistake
to take out Debbie or Joe.
They are puppets.
I would love to have them at the end,
for the ultimate immunity test.
It would be a guarantee, for me.
Peter and I are looking
for a tight-knit herd of loyal players
to guide towards the mixture of tribes
and fusion.
Debbie seems ideal.
She doesn't seem to have the motivation
to make a big move.
She's the king's jester.
Joe will probably be
a loyal soldier.
Aubry doesn't want to talk too much about the game
or stuff like that.
Neal, on the other hand, is very smart
and could very well eliminate
one of us by surprise
after mixing or merging.
So we just need
to split the votes.
We're not telling Deb or Joe
yet.
So we tell them to vote for...
We vote for Aubry.
We have to see it from an
analytical point of view, think about what we have
and all the time that remains.
It's only been seven days.
Let's put these elements together
to come up with a good plan.
We have things well in hand.
We play like bosses.
My position in this tribe
is to settle down, observe,
close it and gather information.
Peter really feels superior
and Liz is our diva princess.
Their goal is to eliminate us all,
while we do all the work.
For now,
Peter is an asset in the trials.
So the one who has to go
is Liz.
I see it clearly.
If we recruit Aubry and Neal,
we have a solid quartet,
we take Liz out by surprise,
this damn diva
who groans about everything.
We agree ?
We need to form this foursome
before Liz and Peter do.
To separate Liz and Peter,
we have to be subversive,
set up counterintelligence,
we have to act with a purpose, Joe!
And we have to do it now!
I'm asking you outright.
What do you think of Neal?
That he is frank with me.
Good. Me too.
- What are you thinking about ?
- I like it.
- I felt like it.
- Good.
Good, very good. Very well.
If you face me,
expect
superior and smarter tactics from me.
The bomb bay is open.
Prepare to fire!
I fully trust you
and I hope
we have a solid quartet.
What is beautiful in what I do,
it's that nobody
pays attention to me.
And that's exactly
what I want to do:
fly under the radar.
During this time, I relax
and collect information.
'Cause that's how
we play this game, honey!
- Do you enjoy eating a chicken?
- Mmm.
The one with fewer feathers
would be best, I think.
He is bigger.
We'll kill that one, then.
Killing a chicken
is best for our tribe.
We are all hungry.
But some
get attached to animals,
like Tai.
It shows his sensitivity.
We'll make sure to be by his side,
because it's hard for him.
Do you see that sound?
- I hear it.
- They're pretty happy.
They look good.
Maybe they will escape!
- Don't think about it...
- No, I can't do that.
If they disappear...
Tai is guilty!
To me, we don't need
to kill that chicken.
But boys need protein to
be strong in the tests.
It is the cycle of life.
We have to eat something,
which eats something else...
You know, the cycle of life.
As long as we are aware
of the whole... And no waste.
Above all, no waste.
I have to catch it somehow,
you're gonna have to hold it.
Sorry, buddy.
Come back for a better life!
- It'll be OK ?
- Yeah.
Just to see
life slip away into my hand...
I feel like...
...to have done wrong.
Very bad.
His feet are already cold.
Yeah, he's dead.
It's just the nerves moving.
You know, it had to be done.
But it's still very hard to live with.
It's still a life you took.
He is sad.
I don't like
when people cry.
Who that, Tai?
Oh, yeah, he was shaken.
think of tai trop
he has all these feelings,
these emotions that need to come out,
and that's not the way
to play.
My friends would compare me to a robot,
a cold-blooded being.
But we don't need
emotions here.
We just have to seem to have some.
He is in pain, it shows.
I sympathize.
It'll be fine for Tai.
Animals
eat other animals.
They're here for that.
Something about Nick
doesn't inspire confidence.
It's hard to talk to him.
He's just a big smile,
he irritates me.
I trust Caleb and Tai.
We are three girls and three boys,
we must recruit one of the boys.
That's the thing.
The girls want to stay together,
and these girls and I
are super loyal.
And never... Anyway, it's a game,
I could bamboozle you,
but I would
never betray you like that.
But here's the thing:
I don't trust Nick.
Truly not.
The girls
form a very solid trio.
Anna offered me
to join the girls
and we'd eliminate Nick.
This is not a bad thing,
because in case of defeat,
that means I'm not leaving.
I really don't want to lose.
If we lose, it will be...
...drama in shambles.
More litter and leaves.
Like everywhere I looked.
I try to find the idol,
because I don't trust Alecia.
But there are plenty of places to
hide an idol!
If there is a clue or an idol,
we
obviously don't want Alecia to find her.
Brothel!
"The idol is buried
at the foot of this tree."
Let's dig!
A priori,
I am at the bottom of the scale.
And I see a clue
to find the idol.
That's power, in this game.
With the idol, it's like, you're at the bottom
of the ladder, you take it out and...
You are at the top.
I walk,
and here's Alecia and Cydney,
digging.
I'm not stupid.
They are looking for the idol.
- Jason is looking at us.
- Where ? Where ? Where ?
Was he there long?
I have not seen it.
- One moment.
- Shut up.
They'll think it's here.
We have to find her.
But we have to find the hoe.
I stay here.
More, Alecia! Alecia!
Act normal !
And so, I found the idol!
I'll wait until
she's gone...
I let Alecia go,
because I found
a small tool with a clue
and I'm like, "Oh, seriously?"
So I start to dig deep,
and I scratch with my fingers,
and it says "idol" on it.
But the box is padlocked!
How the hell
am I going to open this box?
And without warning,
she was already back,
so I covered it.
I couldn't find it anywhere.
The hoe?
We need the hoe.
Are you going back there?
- Yes.
- OK.
I'm going to rinse my hair.
She found a clue.
Did she find a clue?
What's he saying ?
"The idol is buried
at the foot of this tree."
What tree?
- Where you saw us.
- Is that where she found the clue?
Of course, Jason having seen us,
I had to tell him.
It's so
that they don't wonder,
that they don't think I'm
allied with her.
I may be
one of the best bounty hunters
of southwestern Michigan.
The tree was there.
- This tree?
- No, I caught them there.
Here they are.
In my job,
if we give you a tip,
you have a few seconds,
minutes, hours maybe.
So you get active!
I try to approach this game
as I approach my job.
I got it !
Did you find a clue?
What's he saying ?
I found it pretty quickly.
I found the clue,
the box, locked.
And the clue has a map.
I had to act.
Is it the idol or the clue?
My God !
I took off like a rocket.
You keep the rhythm or I lose you.
“Congratulations,
you have found the Immunity Idol.
But first, you will need a key
to open this box."
The map was quite telling.
Then it's a matter of looking,
to be attentive to details,
to differences, to what is missing.
Here it is !
I found the key.
To get it out, you have to push
into a hole underneath.
But the tool is gone.
We don't know where he is.
It was dumped somewhere,
the girls didn't know what it was...
Who knows ?
- You told her ?
- Nope. He saw us. That's all.
- We're taken.
- What are you doing ?
Scot and I
made a makeshift tool
to get the key.
Obviously, Blondie stands there
to try to sting him.
And... I can't allow it.
It will get warmer.
Just there.
Hold on !
Get out of there !
Got it, Scott!
In this game, if you want something,
you have to go get it.
And it was good to have an
NBA player on my side.
Especially a swivel!
You know, with his size!
It paid off!
The buried treasure!
The buried treasure...
Coolest thing
I've seen all week.
I found the clue.
But alas, Jason has the idol.
It was all very disturbing,
it happened so quickly.
Honestly, at this point,
I don't trust anyone.
It's the roller coaster.
First I'm on top,
and there, I think I'm back
at the bottom of the ladder.
"There is a surprise. If you combine
two immunity idols,
they form a super-idol.
A super-idol can be played
after the votes are read."
Yin et yang.
If we find the other,
it doesn't matter if they vote against us!
"Twin Idol Power
Activated!"
We will stay, in fact!
It's idol time!
She is in good hands.
I bind mine,
but I trust,
Jason will protect me.
We just want to make sure
Alecia doesn't get it,
because unless there is a very easy test,
I doubt that we will win.
Now she is in the minority
and she will come out.
Over here, everyone!
Intelligence, Beauty,
discover the new Muscles tribe.
Jenny was eliminated
at the last council.
Amazing.
Ready for today's immunity test
?
Glad to hear that!
First of all, I take back the idols.
Thank you, Julia.
Thank you, Liz.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will jump from a platform
and swim to a boat
where you will collect
three bags of rice.
Together you will push
and pull these bags through a hole.
Then you will cross a plank
and return to the beach.
There you will rip open the sacks,
looking for three balls.
Then, one team member at a time,
balancing on a board,
will take a ball through
a maze of holes
to the top.
The first two tribes
to bring their three balls to the top
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers will go to the board
where someone will be
the 3rd person eliminated from the game.
You are also playing for a reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
The first tribe to finish
will have a choice.
You can choose between...
Comfort material.
Or, if you want...
Your emotional objects,
to remind you of the inspiration
that brought you here.
The first tribe to finish
will have a choice.
The second tribe
will have what is left.
The third tribe: nothing.
A date with me at the council,
someone leaving.
Beauty, two people
will not participate. Who ?
Anna and Michele.
- Intelligence, who in your house?
- Joe and I.
Aubrey and Joe.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, one minute
to get organized and we'll start.
Well, on and go.
For reward and immunity.
Survivors, ready?
One person
must board the boat
and pass the three bags
to your teammates.
Neal is on board for Intelligence.
Caleb is on board for Beauty.
Scot is on board for Muscles.
Put this rice
in the hands of your teammates.
- Go on !
- On the shoulder !
These bags are heavy.
The three tribes have their rice.
Now you have to pass it
through a very small hole,
one bag at a time.
You can send someone
to the other side to help you.
Caleb goes there for Beauty,
The three tribes
try to find the trick.
That's a lot of rice
to pass
through a very small hole.
Here, here!
Beauty brought her first bag.
Cydney has a first bag for Muscles.
When wet, the bags
are even heavier.
Beauty is doing a good job,
they have their second bag.
Peter and Neal
are on the second sack.
Jason and Cydney
Beauty has her third bag!
Nick needs to get over it
and they can move on.
Intelligence has its second bag.
Second bag for the Muscles,
they move on to the third.
You have to cross the plank
with the bags
and bring them to the beach.
Third bag for Muscles,
they are gone!
Peter and Neal are now last,
for Intelligence.
Tai passed for the Beauty tribe.
Forward, Beauty!
Come on !
Beauty has a nice lead.
Neal passed for Intelligence.
Peter gets on the board.
Tear those bags open!
There are three balls, one per bag!
That's great !
Nice team work!
Jason runs and succeeds.
Peter went for Intelligence.
Beauty has two balls.
More than one. They got it !
In the labyrinth, Beauty!
And here comes Intelligence!
The key is to avoid the holes
in the maze
and get to the top.
Intelligence has its third bag.
We're looking for the third ball
in the Muscles.
They still haven't
won a race.
They have the third ball.
Take your time, Julia!
Julia is halfway through.
She is looking for the right path.
If you fall off the board,
you have to start over.
If your ball falls,
Cydney becomes feverish.
Julia comes closer.
Go slow, you're there!
Julia scores a first point
for Beauty!
It's Tai's turn for Beauty.
Intelligence
finally has its three bullets.
Liz steps forward.
Cydney loses her ball again.
- Do you want to trade?
- Yeah, okay.
Jason comes in for Muscles.
Muscles still hasn't won
an event in this game.
But Beauty is doing very well.
Tai is close
with the second ball.
Take it easy, honey, you're there!
Tai places the second
beauty tribe ball!
More than one!
Caleb steps forward for Beauty.
Liz is very close.
Well done, Liz, great!
And There you go !
First ball for Intelligence!
One point for Intelligence.
Beauty leads with two.
One more time,
Muscles is far behind
in an event.
Caleb flew over that part of the wall.
It's good, that's it!
He made it all the way
without firing a shot.
And a new victory
for the Beauty tribe.
For victory !
Caleb, Beauty Tribe!
Immunity and a reward!
Come on Jason!
Jason is close.
Come on, let's change!
Jason scores a first point
for Muscles.
are vying for second place.
Tied, 1 - 1.
Peter for Intelligence.
Scot for Muscles.
Peter is close.
Peter places the second ball
for Intelligence.
More than one for Intelligence.
Debbie steps forward.
Scot is close for Muscles
with their second ball.
And it's done, equality!
2 - 2!
It's all happening now.
Debbie versus Cydney.
Intelligence
did not go to the council.
They don't want to go tonight.
Cydney wasn't very lucky
the first time around.
Jason helps her a lot.
Come on, Debbie!
Debbie is right in front of Cydney.
Intelligence
is just ahead of Muscles.
- Debbie, it's okay!
- At the top ! At the top !
Nice shot from Cydney.
It's neck and neck,
perfect equality!
Go left. You hold it!
The 2 women
are in the last section.
At the top ! To the left !
which now leads to Muscles!
Muscles has never been so close!
Sydney is close!
Debbie is losing ground!
Is this the end?
She's not there yet!
Debbie is getting closer,
she is just below!
It's neck and neck,
the last seconds!
She is there!
Sydney, close!
Debbie, close!
Muscles succeeds!
A few seconds before Intelligence,
sending Intelligence to the council,
where someone will be
the third person eliminated from the game.
Three bloody seconds!
It was time
for something to work for us!
Beauty, once again!
Unvoted.
Muscles is a
new experience for you.
Beauty, the choice is yours.
It is very clear: comfort or love.
Comfort !
Come get it, go back to camp.
No advice tonight.
come get your emotional items
and rejoice that you
don't see me in the council.
For the first time !
Jason and his teddy!
I have a teddy!
Intelligence,
for the 1st time: advice,
where someone will be
the 3rd person eliminated from the game
and the first person
eliminated from your tribe.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
We lost the race,
but no worries.
Now Liz and I are going to
take out the mafia-style intruders.
And the first will be Neal.
Gambling is gambling,
money is money.
Survivor is Survivor.
All in all, guys,
great job.
I was three seconds away from her.
Yes, it came to nothing.
We didn't explode mid-flight.
At the long-term level,
this defeat serves us,
Peter and me,
because we can eliminate Neal.
Neal is the one who would cause
trouble later on.
We're gonna have to tell Aubry and Neal
that Joe is leaving tonight.
But the real plan
is that the remaining four
will split their votes
between Neal and Aubry,
in case Neal has an idol.
The idea is to simplify the process
for Joe and Debbie.
They just have to write "Neal",
remember that Neal is the target.
They will have nothing complicated
to consider.
Our plan will work
if you and joe vote for neal
and Peter and I for Aubry.
So if Neal doesn't have the idol,
we will have a tie 2 - 2 - 2.
And in the vote, we vote Neal.
I'm confident everything will work out
as expected.
Losing this trial
will actually prove beneficial.
Well !
Liz approaches me.
She wants me and Joe
to vote for Neal
and followed orders,
like good soldiers.
It will not arrive.
I'm glad we're
on the same wavelength.
Let's not discuss it too much.
For me, it's settled.
- It is all good.
- Yes, we know...
When they take me on a boat,
I can reciprocate the
power of ten.
The fact is
that she is totally oblivious
of the reality of what is happening.
They vote for Aubry.
They think you have the idol.
I now know that Liz and Peter
whisper little lies
to pretend that I have an idol.
Accordingly,
they must be punished.
We agree,
all four, to vote Joe?
- We have to keep our strength.
- Yeah, I know.
Let's do what needs to be done.
Liz and I are beautiful and smiling,
but we'll be merciless.
The others
are clay in our hands.
They are unable to decide
you have to guide them, like a father.
And I'm the father
who will guide their vote
in the direction I want.
It's a great position.
But Neal and you,
you need to communicate better
with Liz and me.
This is new to me, I guess.
Peter wants to control everything.
I can't trust
someone who reveals himself to me,
every day,
as soon as he opens his mouth.
He has no
emotional intelligence
and I don't think
we can move forward with him.
Debbie basically
decided to target Liz.
But for me,
Peter is more dangerous.
I want to talk to Debbie about it
and make a decision.
Peter said something like:
Stop trying to control me!
Does he have a problem with women?
- Nope. He's egotistical...
- Or is it with everyone?
...arrogant and narcissistic. Yeah.
I don't like bullies.
My biggest regret
would be if we took Peter too far
and fuck us.
Do we get rid of Peter?
That's the question.
We still have a target: Liz.
But Peter plays
with too much exuberance.
He is narcissistic
egotistical
and ultimately a real problem
for the Intelligence tribe.
Liz and Peter will slit anyone's throat
without the slightest hesitation.
So it's a big decision.
But tonight's elimination
will be a total surprise
and it won't be pretty
when we get home, kids!
Total surprise.
Behind you, torches.
Take one
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because the fire represents your life.
If he disappears
you too.
In a group that does not know each other,
some get along,
others maybe not.
Have you seen friendships
formed quickly?
Absolutely. From the start,
things stuck between Liz and me.
Aubry and Neal
also got along well.
There's an age difference
between Debbie and Joe,
but as the days go by,
we all got along well.
Does this mean that three duos
will vote the same way tonight?
Yes, I see that
as three voting units.
Is it fair to consider,
for the Intelligence tribe,
that everything is mathematical,
pragmatic?
- Debbie, you're already nodding.
- Absolutely.
We are excessively analytical.
We know it's better to get
the facts,
examine them without panicking,
reassess, reanalyze,
and that emotions are
just a waste of time and energy.
Or else, everyone thinks
they are the smartest and quiet.
Aubry,
which is truer?
You are all very analytical
and leave emotions aside
or do you all think you
have it all figured out?
We are in troubled waters.
You can have the majority
and feel fully confident,
but there are comments
or silences,
and you should also know
what they mean,
even if they are not numbers.
Aubry talks about capturing the subtleties
social interactions.
All done.
As an emergency physician,
I am a pro
at social interactions.
Liz, let's talk about paranoia.
She settles in every tribe
at some point.
Does it already exist
in the Intelligence tribe?
"Paranoia" is a bit strong.
But whoever here doesn't fear
a plot to eliminate him
probably doesn't think
enough about the game.
To pick up on what Liz said,
that there is a degree of paranoia:
does your past career come
into play?
I am always suspicious.
I'm always suspicious
of people's motives
and that kind of stuff.
Often,
people are smiling,
looking good,
seem believable,
but are not.
That could be the case here.
Peter, that's a
pretty interesting statement.
You can't trust
appearances here.
But I trust appearances.
Joe is a policeman.
He spent 25 years at the FBI.
So whatever he tells me,
I believe him.
I would just mention
that the 1st Intelligence/Muscles/Beauty
was won by Tony,
also a policeman,
who lied every half hour.
I agree.
And I think Joe
is from another generation.
His word carries more weight to me
than that of a Tony.
Peter, what was the atmosphere
on the camp after the defeat?
We were very bad.
But I reassured myself
telling me
that the plan was in motion.
Neal, when a team member says:
"The plan is in place.",
unless you're part of the plan,
that must make you...
The question is:
what plan is he talking about?
Well, that's not your plan.
- To fart.
- Let's be clear.
The guy with the "ice cream" cap
could be a cap snake.
Is not it ?
So that's the plan.
If we want to take out Neal or Aubry,
one can split the votes and move
forward as an Intelligence.
Debbie. Peter, bluntly,
dictates what he wants to see happen.
It does him good to
expose everything like this.
Do you think tonight's vote
will go according to plan?
I don't think the person who leaves
will be totally shocked.
Neal, how about you?
What do you think will be
the outcome of the vote?
What are you hoping for?
I think the tribe
will come out stronger.
What "reinforced" means...
will be interpreted later.
Peter, this self-awareness
is essential.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
One thing I know
is that I love all these people.
I respect
some of their strategies.
But at this key moment in the game,
there are three duets.
So what do you want?
Liz and I are smart.
We have thought of everything.
Wow.
I just want to take this parchment
and write names on it.
- Shall we go to the vote?
- We are ready.
- Fine, let's go.
It's time to vote.
Aubrey, over to you.
The world doesn't revolve around you.
But good luck.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Aubry.
To fart. Equality.
Two votes Aubry, two votes Peter.
Liz. Upvote Liz.
Two votes Peter,
two Aubry votes,
one vote remains.
Liz.
We have a three-way tie.
So we're going to vote again.
Aubry, Liz, Peter,
you won't vote.
The others, you can only vote
for one of these three.
Joe, come get the ballot box.
I'll get the votes.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Third person eliminated
from Intelligence vs. Muscles vs. Beauty.
Liz, that's two, that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
- Really sorry.
- Do not worry. Hang on.
You, then!
Liz, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck to everyone !
With all the talk tonight
about the intelligence of this tribe,
the vote illustrates
that Survivor still rests
on emotional intelligence,
your ability to pick
up on social cues.
That's what brings you to the end.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: Lény, flosm92
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Survivor's most grueling season ...
The exhaustion shows.
Doctor !
...continues to do damage.
- We need water! Some water !
- Oh my God !
Physiological serum,
in the refrigerated box!
We will evacuate it!
Call the helicopter!
I was pretty sure that,
whether we win or lose,
I'll be calm.
I really don't know what happened
so that my tribe wants to eliminate me.
I don't think
the numbers lied to me.
These are the people who lied to me.
And when we add
up fictitious promises,
we obtain a fictitious total.