translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
After the merger...
Congratulations, everyone!
...Intelligence and Muscles
tried to charm Beauty.
It's great to have options.
Debbie wasted no time...
I want us to ally.
...aggressively trying
to secure a majority.
Bargain.
I seem to be one of the few here
to play attack.
But it backfired on her.
So, Nick, are you with us?
Debbie nearly takes over
Intelligence's strategy.
She got Intelligence on her back...
Everyone's sick of Debbie.
Because of that, we're screwed.
...facilitating
Beauty's decision...
- We're going with Muscles.
- OK.
...to unite with Muscles.
- There are so many of us!
- 7 against 4.
We stuff the nerds
in the lockers.
For Intelligence,
everything went from bad to worse...
...when Neal
fell victim to the elements.
- You pull Neal out of the game.
- I think I have to.
My poor.
My number 1 ally! Left !
And the idol with him.
The bastard!
Once again, the game has changed.
There are ten left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Previously on Survivor...
You can very well be happy
and sad at the same time!
- In the meantime, we're still here!
- We are here !
It makes me want
to clean my cuts thoroughly.
Today, Neal gone,
I don't feel in a strong position.
His departure blows our calculations.
The Intelligences are three,
Debbie, Aubry and myself.
I do not know what to say anymore.
Survivor
is like a box of chocolates.
You never know
what you're going to stumble upon.
We are at the bottom of the totem
and things are fluctuating.
I want to see if there are other options,
that's the main thing now.
I have to make
my neurons work.
As long as there is life,
there is hope.
We'll decide
who goes first and...
We stick to the plan.
It doesn't matter now.
We're pretty tight,
Beauty and Muscles.
It is more or less established
that the Intelligences will leave.
As far as I know,
Neal left with an idol.
But if he left her in the game,
the plan now is
to split the votes each time,
so that if there is an idol,
it is played without harming us.
Because we are 7 against 3.
Beauty votes for Debbie
until she comes out.
Muscles votes for Aubry.
- An objection?
- Nope.
Quiet, we do our thing.
Aubry returns.
I feel what is happening.
It's like in high school.
Our camp is divided
by the tough.
Around them are the girls,
those who are pretty
and get along with these people.
And the shyest, the intellectuals,
are on the sidelines.
They are all happy with his departure.
But sportsmen and cannons
will not cannonate forever.
They age and decay.
And they will disappear.
In the end,
the marginalized will have their revenge.
If I find a flaw
or play the troublemaker,
I may find an opening.
Do you let your daughter do your
hair sometimes?
- All the time.
She does my makeup "when I sleep".
She is awesome.
Chloe is...
She is Chloe.
Some of you already know it, might
as well say it, she is autistic.
His case is quite severe.
She goes to kindergarten.
We take care of her.
We go to therapy
three mornings a week.
We go to therapy after school.
Occupational therapy,
speech therapy, physiotherapy...
Basically,
I didn't want to use my daughter
to advance in the game.
But if I'm asked
about my children,
I tell the truth.
Cause I didn't really know
what autism was.
Until we figured it out
and my daughter was diagnosed.
Basically,
every penny that I earn
is used to pay the hospital, the doctors.
Because of this, we are very poor,
but happy,
because we see his big progress.
At least,
people will realize
that there are families
with autistic children.
And it is very expensive.
And it's much more common
than you think.
It wasn't supposed to serve me.
But I believe they realized
that I'm not just
this big deviant and dominant,
but that I am also human.
But she is perfect.
That's how it's supposed to be,
I'm not complaining.
I just wish I
could help her more.
Jason took a great opportunity
to talk about his life.
He is rather seen as a strong man,
hot-tempered and loud-mouthed.
At this point,
I saw all its facets.
It was nice, but at the same time,
it shows
that he might be hard to beat,
now towards the end.
I
would give him money too!
It's a beautiful thing.
At this point, it's my own game
that I have to determine.
Who do I trust? Who to go with?
Who will take me further?
I have to take a step back.
Who could you beat?
There is the question.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
- Yes !
- Yeah !
Today you will be divided
into two teams of five.
At my signal, you will rush
and use poles
to pass a team member
from one large platform to another.
Then you will all swim
towards a very narrow tower.
The first full team on
top of this tower,
with the feet on
or above the top,
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yeah.
Ice cream.
I'll whet your appetite.
Inspire your motivation.
It's too good.
I let you share.
A bowl.
Oh, a bowl, yeah!
It's nice !
Ice cream
will be delivered to you at the camp
and you will feast
until satiety.
Oh no !
We form the teams
like a schoolyard.
We draw the captains
and we start.
Good,
we have two
very different teams.
Julia was captain.
She chose the two larger ones
and the two smaller ones.
Nick, Debbie, Scot et Tai.
Aubry was captain.
His choices were more homogeneous,
with Cydney, Michele, Joe and Jason.
It's time to find out
who made the best choice.
Let's go. For the reward,
Survivors, ready?
You have to transfer someone
using these poles.
Only one person
must therefore climb on this platform.
It will be Julia and Aubry.
The two captains will also be
the people transported.
This is where teamwork
will make the difference.
- Closer.
- Go ahead !
Stay fixed. Good.
Aubry passes on the 2nd pole.
Julia tries to reach the 2nd.
Aubry falls, she will try again.
There is clearly
a learning phase.
A little bit closer. Sorry.
Aubry tries again.
Aubry falters.
Aubry falls again.
Julia progresses on the course.
When we've taken the hit,
we go faster,
so persevere!
Aubry tries again.
She seems much more stable
this time.
It's good, it's good.
Aubry falls again.
This is where we see the advantage,
for Julia's team,
of the great strength of Scot and Nick.
This same force, and this size,
will be obstacles in the end.
For the Blues, Aubry tries again.
Aubry falls again.
I'm going to try.
They exchange.
Michele is going to give it a shot.
Julia really took the hit.
Nice balance
and great teamwork
of Nick, Tai, Scot and Debbie.
- Its good ?
- I've got you.
Julia is halfway there.
Michele is going to give it a shot.
You just need a bit of rhythm!
Michele, undeterred,
tries to pick up the pace.
Joe and Cydney
try to hold her down.
Jason and Aubry bypass her.
Closer !
Another step for Michele.
She does not hold.
She has to start over.
- Wait, wait.
- Julia approaches the platform.
Fall now
and you'll have to start from the beginning!
No precipitation.
Julia is in trouble
for the first time.
Julia struggles to maintain herself,
but she succeeds.
Nice recovery!
Michele falls again.
Cydney will give it a shot.
Its good ?
Your stability
depends on that of the poles.
Julia, again
a stone's throw from falling.
Julia, not close enough to jump,
she still needs one.
- Its good ?
- Yes !
That will be enough!
Julia has passed!
Everyone get on the platform!
My legs are shaking!
Go for it !
They are Julia,
Debbie, Nick, Tai et Scot.
They have completed the first stage,
while Cydney falls headfirst
.
They just have to hold
on top of a very narrow tower.
Scot's feet
are bigger than the base!
That is to say
if it will be difficult for them.
Michelle is back.
And back in the water.
Tai is the last.
You just have to get up
and stand on your feet.
A real correction
is taking shape!
Absolute disaster for the Blues!
Here we are !
Three, two, one...
That's it !
Reward for Scot,
Nick, Debbie, Julia and Tai!
I'm sorry.
Julia, you clearly
made the right choices.
Ice cream will be delivered
on your camp, for your pleasure.
Grab your things, swim back
and wait for the reward!
When we say that in Survivor,
a bad choice snowballs,
shit, I feel the avalanche, there!
I can't
get my head above water.
First Neal left the game,
then I picked the team,
and apparently
it was a mess.
It sucks.
I wanted so much more than that!
And I'm not giving up.
I just feel
like I'm making bad decisions.
Ice cream !
Back on the camp,
after the test,
the five winners
were able to go see
the ice cream vendor.
can i have a chocolate ball
and one of coffee?
Mmm, cherries!
And whipped cream.
I wish we could share.
But we can not.
The other five
had to land in purgatory
and listen to us
eat ice cream,
five, six meters away.
Trim !
I mix ice and soda.
And make me a big
chocolate waffle cone!
The ice cream
was a wonderful treat.
It was fantastic
to have a moment of satiety,
to know that you are full of glucose
for the next day,
and I was not at all sorry
for the losers!
It's a little strange sitting here,
but we make a nice community.
You can make noise, do
n't worry! You have won.
No need to be so quiet.
Jason thinks he's in charge
of a lot of things here.
He is very sure of himself.
He screams :
"You can make more noise
if you want!"
And honestly, I respected
their way of doing things.
So long without talking
to my parents is a record.
I need to call my relatives
once a week.
How about you, Scott? Where does your mother live?
My mom is in Utah,
in a nursing home.
She has health problems.
She is only 75 years old.
She has a rare disease.
Basically, it's the reverse
of Charcot's disease.
Is your father alive?
He died when I was 16.
Are you a believer?
I haven't been to church
since childhood, 17, 18.
My universe is my family.
And that is the basis
of the Mormon religion.
It's amazing.
It was one of the advantages,
that's why
I watch over my family.
We were all poor.
My brother chose
religion and family
and I chose the NBA.
They're struggling,
financially, so...
And would you like to help them
even more?
That's why I'm here.
- That's what I do.
- It's very noble.
We were a somewhat random group,
so we didn't really
talk about strategy.
But it was a perfect opportunity
to bond.
And I think Scot and I
could make a good team.
I love having him on my team.
It is awesome.
Everything is fine.
We left ! We left !
- Julia, don't do anything!
- OK !
- I'll guide you.
- I would suck at rowing!
I don't think
he can hear us.
The to a sonotone.
- Really ?
- Yeah.
He left it at home.
Do you think
they will try to do
a female alliance
with Aubry and Debbie?
That's why we need
a majority. A fourth.
Scott and Jason
worry about a female alliance.
Me, not so much.
I do not believe it.
But whatever.
Guys have to stay in the majority.
- So it must be a girl.
- Fire a girl and not a guy.
Yeah, it has to
be one of them.
How was it ?
Meager peach?
Just a handful like that.
When the girls return
I wanted to check in with Julia.
We are on the same wavelength,
strategically.
- Any news on the boat?
- No nothing.
Jason and Scotus
fear a female alliance.
Yeah, there's no such thing.
Something, with Nick,
it is that he is the least discreet
on this island.
He takes 50 steps and turns around,
where I can see him talking.
Can we do more stupid?
I had tics in my face,
I said to myself:
"My God, I'm going to freak out!"
Nothing. Everything is fine.
Nick came back,
he looked at Scot and Jason, like,
"Oh, she didn't say anything!"
And me, I was...
You sent Nick
to find out about me?
When we came back,
Nick went to talk with Julia.
Really ? If you send someone
to inquire about us,
find better than Nick
in terms of facial expressions!
When we got back, Nick said,
"They didn't say anything."
I find that suspicious.
You should have asked me.
I'm not plotting against you.
We sent nobody
to inquire about anybody.
We know. We sent nobody
It is not you.
Hmm, you were
looking at me weirdly.
Shall we fetch water?
Sure.
Scott, Nick and I,
it was hoped that there would be no
female alliance.
Then Nick took the initiative
to ask a girl the question.
But it pissed off Cydney.
Paranoia will eventually set in.
It may have happened
earlier than expected.
What the fuck was this?
It was legit.
I don't know what you said.
- I will tell you.
- What ?
We sat down and Nick said:
"Are they talking
about a female alliance?"
And Scott said:
"I don't know,
we'll see when Cydney comes back."
Nick wasn't asked to
say or do anything.
And then you freaked out.
No, I asked a question.
I wanted to be clear,
because I said to myself:
"Who does he think he is?"
I had to clarify:
"Don't watch me,
you're not my father!"
It's like, the boys
talk to whoever they want,
and if I talk to someone,
"Oh, is there a girl's alliance?"
And me: "Oh no, no, no!
You don't know
Angry Cydney.
She'll blow it all away!"
I'll talk about the idol,
nothing to polish!
You know I got you covered.
Let him know who I am.
Nothing to do with the other girls.
Don't watch me, mate.
The current plan
is to split the votes
between Aubry and Miss Debbie
until the departure
of all Intelligence.
But if the boys have to leave,
they will leave.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all Nick...
It didn't help, but you know
you can win!
Yeah. Marvellous.
Oh, come on, Nick!
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will be balancing
on a very narrow support,
hanging from handles
behind your heads.
If you let go of the handle
or a foot leaves the support,
it's lost.
The last person standing
wins immunity.
The losers: on the council,
someone will be eliminated
after 22 hard days
in this game.
Good.
Take a seat, let's get started.
Well, on and go.
hands behind head,
hands on the back of the handle,
both feet
must remain on the support.
Good.
Everyone is in position.
This test is on.
Everyone looks good.
There are ten people left in the game.
Someone will win immunity.
A guaranteed place
in the last nine.
It's going to be painful, and fast.
You will feel it quickly.
Tai, you are struggling.
The first signs of pain.
A beautiful day,
warm and sunny.
Elapsed Time: 5 Minutes
Someone to acknowledge
that he's already hurting?
Let's get comfortable!
Debbie, is this what you imagined
when you signed up for Survivor?
It's a bit worse.
Good. You've been up there
long enough
to get an idea of ​​what's next.
Oh, my back!
A very uncomfortable position,
very hot sun.
And it will only get worse.
But some of you
feel safe for tonight.
You are not going to leave.
You may not admit
it on the camp,
then i will try you
for you to admit it now.
I will bring food.
Oh my God !
But beware :
this will be your one and only opportunity
to indulge yourself.
So you have to ask yourself,
while I'm going
to get the food:
"Will I come down
and give up immunity to eat,
or could it be
a million dollar mistake?"
Don't come down
until I suggest it.
I can't !
I say. I could not.
Oh, Julia, I'm sorry I
missed that!
I say...
And sorry for you,
it just happened too soon.
You will not take part in this.
Oh, it's a buffet!
- Four pizzas.
- Oh my God !
Brownies.
Chicken drumsticks.
And you have to get that through.
Cool drinks.
- I take.
- That works.
You will have ten seconds.
I will count.
After that, no more temptations.
Oh, Jeff, quick!
Let's go. Ten,
new...
- I take.
- ...eight,
Five...
Five seconds left.
Four,
three,
of them,
and...
I'm staying.
And There you go.
Jason came down.
Scotus is down.
Joe came down.
Michele came down.
That's a lot of food
for four people.
It remains :
who are still vying for immunity.
- Tai.
- Yes ?
Have you considered going down?
I want to go all the way, see how far
I can push my body.
And I don't want
an Intelligence to win.
Wow ! Nick, that's
a bold statement.
Yeah, that's obvious at this point.
What ?
That the Intelligences
are in the minority.
That it is one of the three,
and Debbie,
who is in danger.
I can't.
Debbie can't take it anymore.
Debbie is eliminated
and you are down to four.
Debbie joins Julia,
eliminated, but without the possibility
of eating or drinking.
How's it going, Jason?
Perfectly.
Four people
can still gain immunity.
Aubry, it shows on your face.
It's painful.
Without warning, Aubry descends,
and just behind Aubry,
Suddenly,
you are only two.
Nick, how are you feeling
about tonight?
Considering that as you approach
your first council,
you decide to go down
and waive immunity.
Yeah, I've thought
all along that it's in the pocket for Cydney.
It's a decision to make:
get off
or ensure that all Intelligence
is eliminated.
I will have to wait.
But I'm also excited
to finally go after 22 days.
Hoping
it's not bittersweet.
It won't be, mate.
No, I know.
That's Cydney.
Competing for immunity.
Are n't you feeling
a little numb, Cydney?
No, it's going tip-top.
How it is possible ?
I don't know, she's so...
ELAPSED TIME: 30 Minutes
Tai, the Intelligences
are all gone.
More than Cydney and you.
Do you think you can beat her
or is it a personal challenge?
I want to see
how far I can push.
But... She can't
be that strong.
Sometimes strong people
remain strong and suddenly crack.
I am like a bamboo.
The wind blows, blows...
I am resistant.
I knew the war,
the refugee camp.
It is not comparable.
She's a sturdy redwood,
but she might crack.
Not soon, Tai, not soon!
That's Cydney.
Very different sizes.
But both seem to share
the same frame of mind.
Oh no, not now!
ELAPSED TIME: 40 Minutes
It's been 40 minutes now.
- It's crazy !
- What resistance!
Tai, despite your visible pain,
you are still in on it.
At this point,
it's one second after another.
I invoke Buddha.
What's he saying ?
No, I'm just chanting.
"Faith in Buddha."
You suffer.
I saw it on your face.
Without warning,
the most unlikely happens!
Tai wins individual immunity!
Congratulations to you !
Incredible turn of events!
Oh, my back!
I have never seen anything like it.
- Tai, can you come here?
- Yes.
And even run!
- Tai.
- Thank you, Jeff.
You wanted it.
I don't know if you really thought you
could achieve this,
but you never gave up.
Tai is protected.
Individual immunity.
As for you, someone will leave
after 22 days.
But Tai showed it:
keep fighting,
until the end, until the vote.
Congratulation.
You are safe tonight.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Tonight,
the Beauties are voting for Debbie.
The Muscles vote for Aubry.
I'm safe tonight,
but who knows?
I won the
individual immunity test.
I earned it.
It was quite an ordeal.
Tai was amazing.
I saw ultra-marathoners,
people running in the Sahara...
It was excellent, sir!
What stamina!
You were like a statue
and I will... cook you some food.
You had a good day ?
The plan for tonight
is to split the votes
between Debbie and Aubry.
If an idol is played,
We'll get her out of the way,
but Debbie should go.
And Aubry
is in a weak position.
Someone has to take advantage of it.
That should be me.
That's my opinion anyway.
What have you got planned
with Debbie and Joe?
I'm just waiting to
be told what's going on,
because we were clearly...
public enemy number one.
Yes, that's obvious.
So... We're going to split the votes.
All Muscles and Beauty.
And we divide 4 - 3.
Between you
and the other two Intelligences.
So you have to make
the right decision
by voting for Debbie or Joe.
I would suggest voting Debbie,
but I didn't tell you.
I know
you're in this position,
but I have to take advantage of it.
I think you understand.
I know
I'm being arrogant, but...
- But at least you admit it.
- No, I know.
No, yeah.
It's not my habit
to reveal myself like this.
But hey, if nobody
wants to take advantage of Aubry, I will.
When you're down,
I'm here for you !
And... she knows it.
But she can't do anything about it.
Not immediately.
I wanted to discuss...
With Aubry and you,
before Nick comes back.
On trial, Nick's arrogance
really pissed me off.
Such confidence
is ridiculous.
Nick has the melon
and he gets on my nerves.
What do you have in mind for the vote?
We are tied for now.
5 - 5, women and men.
We must strike now.
- Do you want to go out Nick?
- Exactly.
- I knew it. I suspected it.
- He must go.
I like the idea of ​​it being Nick.
Here comes Cydney approaching us,
Aubry and I,
and said, "Let's get out Nick!"
I still hoped
that Nick would come to us
and we could take out
Jason or Scot,
but, Nick,
first come, first served!
I am 100% ready, decided.
- Aubry, how about you?
- Leaving.
Bargain.
My interest, for the future,
is to make sure the girls
stay as close as possible.
It makes more sense to me
to play with only girls.
If it does, well,
I'll be the first to react.
How do you feel about it tonight?
Are you comfortable
with the division of votes?
Are you close to Nick?
We come from the same tribe.
But he likes watching me.
He always says, "Are you following the plan?"
And me: "Yeah!
I'm following the plan, Nick,
nothing's changed!"
Are you up
for voting Nick tonight?
- Nick?
- Yes.
He is the person who is the most
in Jason and Scot's pocket.
Do we talk to Aubry and...?
It's already done.
Cydney would like to take Nick out.
She thinks it dangerous
and I agree.
But he's also my ally
and I think I can collaborate
a little more with him.
So I don't know if it suits me right now
.
Between girls,
we should stick together.
Absolutely.
The original plan
was to take Debbie out.
So there are many choices
at this point.
It's about figuring out the right
one for Julia and me.
Do you agree with the plan?
Yeah.
I want to make sure you're comfortable.
Jason will have us in the crosshairs.
You can feel the electricity in the air,
before the advice.
A power struggle unfolds.
It is obvious on the camp.
Lots of egos and personalities.
At some point
we gotta do something
that allows us
to take power.
I want to be able to take a hit
who consolidates my image
of someone deserving.
You have to find the right timing.
Nick and Michele, grab a torch
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears, so do you.
Here is now
the first member of our jury.
which was extracted from the game
by the medical team,
recovered enough to be
with us this evening at the council.
So Michele.
Escape the council for 22 days
is the best you can
hope for.
And yet,
something about coming here
fuels Survivor fever.
Yes, going 22 days
without advice is great,
but you don't show
how you play, who you are,
before being here,
to the council.
Debbie, what did you notice
when this band finally came together?
Initially, it was not clear.
Now the ancient tribes
seem to have remained distinct,
but Muscles and Beauty
actually merged.
Nick, we heard
this comment today:
"An Intelligence will go away."
Hey! The Intelligences are on the sidelines.
We're going to split the votes
and move on from there.
Aubry, who's together?
and Julia.
I turned on today,
like Cochran's dream girl,
horribly distressed,
because I am helpless
to make them move.
And yet, Julia,
it would be a great time
to make a move.
For in these seven,
someone is at the bottom of the scale.
People feel confident right
now.
It is always possible
to branch off later.
Jason, that's fear,
isn't it?
You have a great plan.
As long as everyone sticks to it.
I've been repeating it for three days:
"We stay united.
We are sure to get to seven,
and then we will face each other."
And everyone in the covenant said to me:
Scot, how to insure
that the seven stay together?
By not having six days
between two councils.
So that really changed the game.
Yes, it was tough.
Many ideas were considered.
But the game started again today.
We are here tonight.
And honestly,
I think the seven very close-knit.
Tai, were there discussions
about idols,
whether there is or not?
Yeah, we didn't
think there were until...
fusion.
We found
out that Neal might have one.
And we also heard about
a super-idol.
When two idols merge,
they form a super-idol
which can be played after the vote.
You say "we"
and Julia didn't know.
She twisted her neck
turning back to you.
I thought everyone knew.
Aubry, why
this big reaction?
She was not in the confidence.
This may be an indicator
of his true position.
Jeff. Someone
is at the bottom of the ladder.
And this super-idol,
and your ignorance about it,
if it doesn't show
you that you're clearly down,
and if you want to act,
it's still possible tonight.
Tai, you shake your head.
What troubles you?
I was told about the super-idol.
Now I say to myself:
"Maybe that person
didn't tell me about it
only to make me doubt
what is going on."
So, sitting here, I'm like, "Wow!
Are you playing me?"
Debbie, hearing
all that is being said tonight,
a hope ?
Oh, I still have hope.
Absolutely.
Very often,
more things are hidden
than hidden here.
Aubrey, and you?
Do you expect
votes tonight?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Scot, will it be
a surprise elimination tonight?
Or... as expected?
I can't imagine it going
any other way than planned.
Good. It's time to vote.
Tai, over to you.
Sorry, my daughter.
It is division.
See you later, Debbie!
It was nice.
Overconfidence
is a weakness.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Aubrey. Two Aubry votes.
Nick. Two votes Nick,
two Aubry votes, one Debbie vote,
one Jason vote.
Nick. That's three Nick votes.
- Nick. That's four votes Nick...
- Oh, damn it!
...two Aubry votes,
one Debbie vote, one Jason vote.
Seventh person eliminated
and second member of the jury:
Nick, that's five and that's enough.
Bring me your torch.
Nick, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
This is one of the hallmarks of
this game.
As long as you keep
fighting,
everything can happen.
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Proofreading: lshomie, Lény
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
After a surprise elimination,
the men want revenge.
We took the ax and the machete.
We want to starve them.
Do you want to shoot us down?
We will shoot you!
It's psychological warfare.
And it tears women apart.
Julia has it both ways.
But sometimes the guy in the middle
of the road gets run over.
First and last tip.
Obviously, it turns out bittersweet.
And I deserve it.
I was way too confident tonight.
It's a surprise, that's for sure.
I didn't see what was going on,
and I take my hat off to them.
I will remain too confident,
smug and arrogant,
but I should have struck before them,
and I didn't, that's all.