translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Kaôh Rông provided
the most violent conditions.
My poor, these sunburns!
Extreme temperatures brought
dehydration and exhaustion...
This heat could play
a central role in this game.
...leading some to wonder
how much more they can bear.
I am physically very weak there.
In the Beauty tribe,
the women found safety
with each other.
Girls, we are very close.
But Tai found an idol.
And a friend in Caleb.
I was clearly aiming for the kiss!
In the Muscles tribe,
Alecia came across the clue
leading to the idol.
If I find the idol, I lead the game.
But his luck ran out
when Jason found the idol first.
Got it, Scott!
First I'm at the top,
and then I'm back at the bottom.
At the last immunity test...
To the left !
...Muscles finally won.
Muscles succeeds,
sending Intelligence to the council!
On the camp...
We play like bosses.
...Peter and Liz were sure
to control the Intelligence tribe.
I'm confident
everything will work out as expected.
Well !
But Debbie was tired
of following orders
and led a revolt
against Liz and Peter.
It won't be pretty
when we get home, kids!
At the council,
Debbie's plan worked,
sending Liz home...
Liz, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Peter alone,
at the bottom of the ladder.
There are 15 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Well, that was something!
This advice went
exactly as I expected.
I gathered information,
I observed,
then set goals.
I knew how to reach them.
You could say I was the mastermind.
It was between her and you,
but I didn't want it to be you.
I'm just gonna have to
take a step back and relax.
Peter's position in the tribe
gave him a good blow to his ego.
He's totally narcissistic,
but he knows
let it stay on the periphery.
I'm not disappointed, just shocked.
I thought I was leaving.
- Hang on.
- Thanks. Thank you for coming.
The council tonight
was a complete surprise.
I'm still...
my stomach is in knots.
We're the Debility tribe,
not Intelligence.
We are doomed.
We no longer have a strong tribe,
physically or strategically.
I'm sidelined,
but happy to still be here.
And after the merger,
or a mixture of teams,
I will eliminate them one by one.
I need a beer!
Over here, everyone!
We're really going to enjoy ourselves.
Beauty and Muscle Tribes,
discover
the new Intelligence tribe.
Liz was eliminated
at the last council.
I did not expect that.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
you will cross a series of obstacles
until you reach a trunk
under which
you will have to dig and pass.
You will then reach
a sand pit
where you will have to dig up
three bags of bullets.
When you have the balls,
you will attempt to roll them
into targets.
The first two tribes to finish
win a reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
For the first,
Coffee !
Cups, spices, coffee.
It will give a different flavor
to everything on the camp.
For the second:
not as complete
but even salt and pepper
will make the coconut taste better.
For the latter:
nothing.
Beauty, you are two more,
two will not participate.
Remember, it can't
be the same two events in a row.
Who does not participate here,
will participate in the immunity test.
Julia and Anna do not participate.
Intelligence, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we get started.
Alright, here we go.
For a reward.
Survivors, ready?
Under this first obstacle,
very hot sand.
We forget how quickly
the sand heats up.
Above the next two
are Beauty and Muscles
who go strong,
then Intelligence.
Forward, Intelligence!
Start digging!
Come on, it's good!
Intelligence must wait
until all have passed.
Joe speeds up.
Go ahead, Intelligence!
You have to dig
and go under the trunk.
Wow, Cydney quickly passed
for Muscles!
No one had ever
passed so quickly!
Meet Debbie for Intelligence.
Like a turtle
emerging from its egg!
This is Tai for Beauty.
Once passed, you can
dig on the other side.
This is Aubry for Intelligence.
The biggest, Scot, has passed!
Jason too!
Carry on, Muscles!
Muscles took the lead.
Dig up those bags now!
Intelligence has passed.
Dig up your bags!
Beauty is now last.
Nick has a great body to push through.
Beauty is gone.
Start digging!
You are looking for three bags of bullets.
You don't know where they are.
When you have them,
you can continue.
Scot has the first Bag of Muscles.
I have a bag!
Beauty has her first bag.
One bag for Muscles, one for Beauty.
- They are there. One, then two.
- Scot has a 2nd bag for Muscles.
Two for Muscles,
one for Intelligence and Beauty.
- I will die !
- Die.
Just looking at you
is hard!
It's clearly not easy,
after nine days of the toughest game
you will ever play.
Oh my God !
ELAPSED TIME: 45 Minutes
Who knew it would be so hard
to find three small bags
in a pile of sand?
Complete exhaustion.
Muscles has had two bags
for quite a while.
No way to find the third.
One for Intelligence, one for Beauty.
Debbie has a second bag
for Intelligence!
It's good, it's good!
Go on !
And suddenly,
Intelligence has its third bag!
Come on, get those bullets out!
Huge advance for Intelligence.
The two tribes
digging in the sand,
are exhausted.
Good, Aubry!
Aubry throws the balls
for Intelligence.
You have to place the six balls
in the targets.
Aubry scores a first point
for Intelligence.
Second point for Intelligence.
But dig. Dig.
Considerable advance
for intelligence.
Peter takes over
for Intelligence.
He scores.
Three points for Intelligence.
The exhaustion shows.
Hold on, Caleb.
- To fart !
- Come on, Peter, it's good!
Fourth point for Peter.
- With the feet, it's easier.
- I'm digging here.
Intelligence placed 4 out of 6 balls.
Debbie steps forward.
It's a fix, at this point.
Debbie scores a fifth point
for Intelligence.
More than a bullet for Intelligence.
Peter takes over
for Intelligence.
- More than one! Can it get there?
- Come on, Peter! Get us this!
Peter scores the sixth
and final point for Intelligence!
What a correction,
the other tribes are far behind!
Big reward for Intelligence.
Now
it's for second place.
Muscles and Beauty.
This race has been going on
for a long time.
Keep digging!
Yeah, my hen!
Caleb has found Beauty a second bag .
Got it, got it!
And suddenly, Nick has the third bag!
Beauty has her three bags.
Start throwing!
Everyone is well ?
I burn inside.
This is Caleb.
First ball for Beauty.
- Shall I call the doctor?
- Nope.
- I'll call him.
- No do not do that.
Deb, you're gonna push too hard
and get heatstroke.
Second ball for Beauty.
She's got heat stroke, I think.
She weighs only 45 pounds.
- How are you feeling, Deb?
- It's heat stroke.
Doctor !
Over here, go!
Oh my God !
- Stay calm.
- Oh, Lord!
- How are you ?
- I have heatstroke.
- Stay calm.
- Oh my God !
Sweet Jesus !
We'll refresh you, okay?
Here's some water for you.
We have three different stories
at the same time!
Muscles always dig,
while Beauty
tries to finish second
and the doctor takes care of Debbie.
Sweet Jesus !
Joe, tell me everything.
What's going on ?
She is very hot at the moment,
she is suffering from the heat.
Its temperature is high,
we must lower it.
You pour cold water over it
to lower its temperature.
That's right, we have to refresh it.
OK.
Much better !
- Are you feeling okay, Debbie?
- Yes sir !
In my Ranger training
at Hawk Mountain,
I learned first aid.
Because of this, I knew I
had heat stroke.
It's like being roasted alive.
We have the head which turns,
we are exhausted
and we are hot.
And after a few seconds
of shade and water,
I
immediately felt better.
I knew that I would not be evacuated.
- Debbie, are you feeling better?
- Yes, much better.
You are in good hands.
Besides, you won the test.
Relax, no pressure.
Let's see what happens
with the other two tribes.
Keep it in the shade, Joe.
Beauty and Muscles
are vying for second place.
Beauty has placed five balls
since the medical incident.
More than one.
Muscles is always looking for
the third bag.
The only thing they haven't done
is give up.
Come on, teamwork!
Come on, we'll get there!
Keep cheering us on,
it's what you do best.
What matters
is being a team.
I had two bags. And you?
We had to dig more than 30 cm!
Dig. Shut up and dig,
please.
I don't want to be rude,
just that we find him.
Beauty revolves around the 6th target
without managing to conclude.
Caleb is going to give it a shot.
Got it, got it!
And suddenly, Jason
has the third bag for Muscles!
Forward, Muscles!
You are back in the race!
Go-y, Caleb!
Caleb is under pressure now.
Beauty has 5 out of 6 bullets.
Only one is missing,
can he make it?
Failed again!
It's a carnival game,
you can win in an instant!
Jason comes forward for Muscles.
You can throw as many balls
as you want at once.
Jason throws as fast as he can.
A first for Jason.
Caleb can win now!
Scott takes over.
Scot places a second ball
for Muscles.
Scot places a third ball
There are now 5 - 3,
Muscles goes up!
Is it good ?
Yes ! Beauty wins!
The 2nd place award
is for Beauty!
Reward for Intelligence,
nothing for Muscles,
otherwise an empty and lonely afternoon
on camp.
Oh, my God, friends!
Come, sweetie.
I can not move.
Joe, where are we?
How is she ?
She is doing much better.
Already, she is no longer so hot.
Jeff! I have the banana.
Cool.
Good.
His heart rate is quite high.
We managed
to lower his temperature.
Caleb, water?
Whore.
They know how hot it is.
They fight.
But they cannot land
to regain strength.
With the efforts they provide,
with this heat,
the body has difficulty maintaining
a normal temperature.
Doctor ?
I would like to keep an eye...
Yes, he needs the doctor.
Doctor !
Go see Caleb too!
Warning warning !
Get away, get away!
Tai, step aside, please.
Water is coming, okay?
Come on, we need some water!
Water, water!
It's okay, Caleb.
We are here. The doctor is there.
Come on, pour it on him!
We are here with you, my friend.
You are in very good hands.
Inhale deeply.
Deep, okay?
You have to move forward.
We need something to fan him,
anything.
Bring the reflector,
and someone fan it with it!
Tell me everything, Joe.
Caleb has heat stroke.
He has
a hard time withstanding the temperature.
Stay calm.
Breathe regularly.
Stay with us, champ!
How do you feel ?
Cydney, you'll be fine, do
n't worry.
Breathe deeply.
The whole medical team is here,
okay?
It'll be fine, Cydney.
Hey, everyone on the team
needs to get involved!
I continue this.
Umbrellas, coolers, water!
Make yourself useful!
- Thank you sir.
- You're welcome.
Caleb, I'm going to put a mask on you.
You will breathe better.
Continue with the water on both sides,
continue to refresh them.
Well, be still, my friend.
Caleb?
You're still with us, huh?
You are in good hands,
my friend.
Caleb, can you hear me?
Caleb, are you with us?
-Caleb?
- Oh my God !
Caleb, how are you?
Caleb, are you with us?
More ice cream!
Alright, let's turn it off.
Caleb, can you hear me?
- Caleb, can you hear me?
- Oh my God !
We're here with you, okay?
Stay with us!
I see you nodding.
Take a deep breath,
Caleb, okay?
You hear me ?
Bring me the saline,
in the refrigerated box!
I go.
Keep showering Cydney.
Joe, you give him
something to rehydrate, so what?
He is receiving cold fluid
intravenously
to lower its temperature.
And it will help rehydrate him.
- And you monitor his temperature.
- Yes.
Pass me the water, please.
Thanks.
His pulse is 112, Joe.
Blood pressure
below 46/94.
Monitor his vital signs
and add ice.
- Cydney, can you hear me?
- Yes.
Good. How are you ?
Jason takes good care of you.
The medical team is right there,
taking care of Caleb.
We need a helicopter
to evacuate him.
We will evacuate it!
Call the helicopter!
As fast as possible, the chopper!
Bring the big stretcher!
She's there !
Damn, they lost
two people?
Cydney is down too.
Breathe slowly
and deeply. OK ?
To get your breathing
under control.
Stay calm.
Breathe.
So, Joe, where's Cydney?
She seems to be doing better.
How are you feeling, Cydney?
How are you.
His temperature returned to normal.
But we have to keep watering it.
Everything will be fine, okay?
Cydney?
Everything is fine now, okay?
You do not risk
being removed from the game.
We are right next to it.
We have to leave shortly, Joe.
As you know, there are only 2 ways
to leave the game without being eliminated:
by giving up,
and this is clearly not the case,
or when the doctor
is too worried about you
to let you continue.
You don't want to be checked out.
My friend, you have no choice.
It's the doctor's decision.
You gave it your all,
with all your might.
You pay dearly for it.
You won't go any further.
We have to take care of you.
You are a warrior.
I'm glad you're here.
It'll be fine, darling.
Good then...
Crazy day.
Are you doing well ?
I don't know, I'm knocked out.
Good. Well,
here's the good news.
Cydney is doing well, Debbie is doing well.
We're going to evacuate Caleb.
- Are you kicking him out of the game now?
- Now ?
- Caleb is out.
- For real ?
Caleb is out of the game.
- Seriously, is he leaving?
- Yes.
This chopper is coming to pick up Caleb.
I wish it were otherwise.
Give them a second!
- Eh, my pot!
- Eh, Caleb!
We love you !
Its good.
We'll get through this.
- I thought he was invincible.
- Me too.
- Well done, my daughter.
- There, against the tree.
I'll summarize the situation for you.
It is unprecedented.
Three people down
on a single event,
simply because
of extreme heat
combined with dehydration
and heavy exertion.
Nobody went there halfway.
Everyone was
giving their all and fighting.
So where are we, Tai?
You are very touched.
I do not know.
We lose one of our own.
We worked so hard,
and Caleb, to give 100%.
He sacrificed himself
so that we could do this test.
We come from very different...
But the first night,
I snuggled up to him.
I will miss him so much!
Jason, is it possible,
for you, in this game,
after taking care of Cydney,
can you still eliminate it?
I have a military background.
If someone is injured,
the mission no longer counts.
It is this person who counts.
Your partner.
Here we live together.
Yeah, we don't all like each other.
But at the end of the day,
we are a family.
That's what we have, the cards
we got. We have to deal with it.
We stay together until the end.
Good.
Intelligence, your reward
will be waiting for you on your camp.
Beauty, your reward
Beauty has lost a limb.
After nine days, the game continues.
Return to camp,
get shade, hydrate.
Good luck.
Without Caleb, it's very sad.
He will stay in my heart for a long time.
I will see him again, that's for sure.
I still want that kiss!
Before his departure,
3 boys against 3 girls.
But now just Nick and me.
Now the girls
can choose who to date.
So the idol is more important,
because if we go to the council,
there's a one in two chance
that I'll leave.
But I will not leave
with an idol in my pocket.
Caleb has fully recovered,
he is in perfect health...
and hope to play again.
Damn, what a day!
It was crazy!
I just remember
Joe looking at me
and I'm incredibly hot.
He asks me whether to call
the doctor, and I: "No, no!",
because it was embarrassing,
I was going to make it on my own,
but he said, "I'm calling him.",
and luckily he did!
I was not only afraid
of appearing weak in front of my tribe,
but also to appear weak
in front of my daughters at home.
I like to see myself
as an example for my daughters.
They often tell me...
They often tell me
how proud they are of me.
I've done a lot
of silly stuff in my life.
Crystal always tells me,
"You are the best mother.",
They were very proud
that I came here.
I just don't want to disappoint them.
Beyond this game,
we are friends for life.
You really took care of me.
I just want to say...
I may not be
as tall and strong as you,
But the NBA should have taught you
that when we all hold on,
and that I try to encourage you,
look me in the face and say to myself:
"Keep cheering,
that's all you're good for.",
it's not working as a team.
What would the players say
if you said that on a pitch?
First, in an NBA game,
I'm with the best in the world.
There is no comparison.
I didn't want
to argue with Scot,
but I wanted to explain
the situation.
I did my best,
I never gave up.
During the race, I repeated:
"Come on, we'll get there!"
And Scott says:
"Let her take care of the encouragement,
she's only good at that."
On the one hand, I thought: "Shut up!"
But on the other: "Well, she helps,
she stays positive."
I meant it when I said,
"Keep cheering!"
I was doing my best,
I was trying so hard...
But I don't have your big hands.
I know it.
Whether he's bigger or stronger than me
doesn't impress me.
I will tell him how I feel.
I want us to be more of a team,
that we don't lower ourselves.
And with me, that's what they do.
So it's okay for you to push me
in the middle of the test, your teammate?
I wasn't pushing you, I was telling you
to shut up and dig in.
No, you said:
"Encourage us,
you're only good at that."
You've never been
on a team
and you give lessons
to a champion?
Just because
you were in the NBA doesn't mean...
What team
have you been part of before?
I played soccer.
But it's not that.
You played. When ?
Whether it's an NBA game
or football between kids,
the moral of the story,
is: acting as a team,
working as a team.
- We work together.
- So why don't you fit in?
On the camp, after my little discomfort,
I just wanted to stay cool.
And now it starts to yell,
and I: "Oh dear!
You're disrupting my recovery!"
The teams could be
mixed tomorrow. And I hope so.
- Me too !
- You're lucky to still be here!
Because on the next tip,
bye-bye!
OK.
In the Muscles tribe,
we do everything intensely, and...
I don't think Alecia
is aware of...
Anything.
"Come on, my daughter,
listen and be attentive!"
You said cheering you
on was wrong.
It was not the moment.
It's wrong.
We already know what we are doing.
- Once again, you're not listening...
- Then I should... Then...
You can't stop for a second
and say to yourself:
"Maybe
that they are right."
Always an excuse
always something,
always "I know",
always "I don't think so",
always...
Assume, once in your life!
I clearly don't believe
that Alecia truly understands
the world around her.
But I overdid it a bit.
I am getting angry.
You know, I'm raising two girls.
They are everything to me.
I want them to be strong,
highly educated and independent,
women who will
manage on their own, without a dad.
And I'm obsessed
with seeing a girl like Alecia
who can't even
hold a conversation.
You are one of those people
who love contradiction.
Alecia is so
low on the scale,
we're just waiting for advice.
Packed, it is weighed.
Over here, everyone!
How are you all ?
Are you taking care of yourself,
given what we just went through?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
Tai, did it increase
the seriousness of the game
and the importance of staying hydrated?
Self-care is crucial.
The way is still long.
- Ready for the immunity test?
- Yes.
First, I collect them.
Cydney, I know
you're going to hate giving it back.
And I know
you don't want to give it back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today, two people per tribe
will rush into the jungle,
will climb a wooden ladder,
will collect puzzle pieces
and bring them back.
Two other people
will then dive into the ocean
to get more coins.
Once all the pieces are together,
you will solve with them
a puzzle in the shape of a snake.
The first two tribes to finish
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
Losers go to the council
where someone will be eliminated.
Beauty, you are one more,
someone will not participate.
You cannot withdraw
from two events in a row.
Julia and Anna must participate.
Who will it be?
- Me.
- Tai won't participate.
Intelligence, one more person.
It will be Joe.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization.
And we'll start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
First, you have to rush into the jungle,
collect the first 3 coins.
Muscles is in the lead.
Beauty arrives, then Intelligence.
Three pieces.
Untie them, get back down, go again!
Everybody is on the same foot of equality.
Debbie unties 3rd
for Intelligence.
- Cydney's on 3rd.
- Go ahead, take the one below.
Julia has the third for Beauty.
Everyone has all three.
Pick them up, and let's go!
- Deb, do you have two?
- I have one. You have two.
Intelligence forgot a coin!
We must come back!
They are wasting precious time!
Muscles comes first.
Scot and Jason rush towards the water.
Beauty is back.
Michele and Nick rush off.
Scot and Jason
are the first in the water.
Beauty is just behind.
Intelligence struggled
to figure out who was wearing what.
Come on, let's move!
Intelligence soars.
There are three more puzzle pieces under
there.
You have to untie the knots
to free them.
This is Neal and Aubry.
It's Nick and Michele for Beauty.
You're running out of air.
You have to hold your breath
while undoing the knots.
Aubry dives.
Jason and Scot return.
Nick and Michele return.
Intelligence
has a significant delay to redo.
Come on, Beauty!
It's the final sprint,
Nick is back at a run.
It's a bit longer
for Jason and Scot.
Neal and Aubry have their three pieces.
They come back.
Come on, Michelle!
Forward, Beauty!
Anna and Julia
will take care of the puzzle.
Forward, Muscles!
It will be Cydney and Alecia
for Muscles.
Neal and Aubry
are still in the water.
Julia and Anna are progressing well,
if that's fair.
The kid goes here.
There is only one possible solution,
but it will be misleading, parts
will fit in the wrong place.
Alright, that doesn't work.
Come on, darling!
Go ahead, honey, you're there!
Aubry is back.
These are Neal and Debbie
for Intelligence.
It's all
about your ability to collaborate
and try many options
without losing sight of the big picture.
Like that ? No.
- Deb, can I come?
- Peter is dying to participate.
- Come on, Peter!
- Thanks.
Deb and Peter pass the baton.
Hippocampus, tonsils,
frontal lobes, go!
Muscles seeks to understand
what is wrong.
- So we take it off.
- Things are bad for Beauty.
Alright, this one next.
Intelligence
has regained a lot of time.
Your neurons are at full speed.
Come on, boys!
We found it, Jeff!
Intelligence thinks it has found.
And that's the case !
Intelligence gains immunity
and is immune to the vote!
Peter arrived and it was over!
We are fighting for 2nd place now.
We exchange ?
Yeah, we trade.
Beauty makes a change.
Will Nick do for Beauty
what Peter did for Intelligence?
Don't want to try?
Alexia, concentrate.
Nick is well launched,
he has new ideas.
Beauty has progressed well.
We have to get out of it.
It's always laborious
for Muscles.
Another adjustment for Beauty.
Is it over?
It seems like.
Eh yes ! Beauty wins!
Avoid the council
for the fourth time in a row!
Referring Muscles to the Board
where someone will be eliminated from the game.
It is the general reduction.
- How are you feeling, Alecia?
- Not very well.
I tried.
- We tried.
- We tried, yeah.
Scot, does this exchange sum it all up?
Alecia says, "I tried,"
and Cydney says, "we tried."
Alecia still thinks
she should talk about herself
to be valued in his eyes.
- I think that's wrong.
- "I tried."
- The advice will be funny.
- In effect.
Jeff asks Alecia a question
and Alecia responds
with her famous words:
"I did my best."
It's her, her, her, her.
Intelligence Tribe, congratulations!
Thanks, Jeff.
Immunity again.
Nobody is leaving.
Beauty Tribe!
You still avoid
coming to see me at the council!
Beauty, safe from the vote.
Intelligence, get your things,
go back to camp.
Beauty, get your things,
Which brings us back
to a familiar story.
The Muscles Tribe.
So, Muscles.
Body language alone
says it all.
This tribe is not happy.
Not at this time.
Alecia, do you feel like
you get picked on a lot?
Yes. And when I answered
"I tried",
I didn't want to say
that I had tried and she hadn't.
I assume our failure on the puzzle.
It was my fault.
What are your chances
of surviving tonight's vote?
- Scot, you're forming a zero.
- Zero.
- Alecia is leaving tonight.
- If I have my say.
We will not make this mistake again.
We can vote now.
- We can do the counseling now.
- I am on it.
But Alecia has to agree.
I will not do
the advice now.
It would be giving up.
Absolutely not.
All right, get your things.
We'll see you tonight,
advice,
whether long or very short.
Has anything changed
since the ordeal?
Not that I know.
Scott, do you think the same?
- Yes.
- Cydney?
So, Alecia, you have
three people saying the same thing.
You are in a
very interesting situation.
Because you are not at Muscles
because of your physique.
Come on, Jeff!
You are there, because you do not
let yourself count, ever.
- Do you agree ?
- Yes.
In other words, I'm stubborn.
But moreover,
I never felt
good contact with Scot and Jason,
so often when they talk to me,
I choose not to listen.
I don't have much respect for them.
Scot, Alecia dit
that you have to earn her respect
to get her to listen to you.
And you didn't earn it.
So no one can.
She finds something
she did well once
and she puts it back on the mat
until someone freaks out.
And I saw her do it,
and I saw Jason freak out.
It shows me
that she needs attention.
Positive or negative, it doesn't matter.
I pity her.
I think you're going to be
eliminated tonight.
I don't think there's
a chance another will come out.
I don't think I've ever seen
such obvious advice.
And yet,
I still support you.
Of course I want to stay.
I believe I have what it takes
to go all the way.
If I leave tonight
I could take it negatively
or retain what I learned,
that I am grateful
to have what I have.
Sometimes such an experience
is worth more than money.
Did I miss something,
before we vote?
Well, it's time to vote.
Cydney, over to you.
I hope you watch this
on repeat
and understand
that we were really trying to help you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Alexia.
That's two votes Alecia,
one Scot vote, one vote remains.
Fourth person eliminated:
Alexia.
Bring me your torch.
Alecia, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck, Cydney!
Thank you darling.
If one thing has been constant
in this tribe,
it's your threesome.
Is this link enough
to get you to the end?
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
I had never been like this
in nature,
to have to live
without shelter or food.
It changed me profoundly.
In the end, I'm proud of myself.
I don't think I gave up.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Relecture: Creature, flosm92
Synchro: Creature
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
This season, the lines of power
have been drawn.
I pull the strings behind the scenes.
We are in a very good position.
We have all the power.
But they are about
to be erased.
Everyone throw down their bandana!
We change things.
My Survivor experience
was unlike anything I've ever experienced.
To those who think it's easy,
I say, "Try it!"
This is serious.
I didn't
think it would be so rough.
It was fun, it pushed my body
to its limits,
the doctors were great.
It's an experience I would do again.