PREVIOUSLY ON: "SURVIVOR,"
AFTER A SURPRISE
SWITCH -- DROP YOUR BUFFS --
"SURVIVOR: KAOH RONG" WENT FROM
THREE TRIBES TO TWO TRIBES, AND
JULIA WAS FORCED TO GO TO BRAWN
BEACH ALONE TO FEND FOR HERSELF
UNTIL SHE COULD JOIN THE TRIBE
THAT LOST IMMUNITY.
OVER AT THE NEW CHAN LOH TRIBE,
IT WAS AN EVEN SPLIT.
>> TWO BEAUTY, TWO BRAIN, TWO
BRAWN.
>> Jeff: AND DEBBIE DIDN'T
WASTE ANY TIME FORMING
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> I WANT TO SEE A WOMAN WIN
THIS.
I'M ON THE OFFENSE, NOT THE
DEFENSE.
>> Jeff: AT THE NEW GONDOL
TRIBE, THE SWITCH LEFT THE
BEAUTIES WITH NUMBERS AND THE
BEAUTY WITH GOOD REASON TO
WORRY.
>> IT'S EITHER TAI OR I.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE --
>> WE GOT IT, JEFF, WE GOT IT.
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY FOR GONDOL
LOST.
BACK AT CAMP, THE FATE OF THE
BEAUTIES WAS LEFT IN THE BRAIN'S
HAND.
>> THE OBJECTIVE IS TO GET ONE
BEAUTY OUT.
>> Jeff: SENSING TROUBLE, TAI
CONSIDERED SAVING HIS IDOL.
>> SAVE THE IDOL AS LONG AS YOU.
CAN.
>> I'M SO WORRIED.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
TAI KEPT HIS IDOL.
AND THE BRAINS TRIBE FOUND ANNA
TO BE THEIR BIGGEST THREAT.
>> ANNA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: 12 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL
BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> LET'S GET A FIRE GOING HERE.
>> YOU'RE SO USEFUL AROUND THIS
CAMP AND YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD GUY.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS, FOR KEEPING
ME HERE.
>> YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD GUY.
COME ON.
>> AT TRIBAL ANNA WAS COMPLETELY
IN SHOCK.
I COULDN'T LOOK AT HER.
I FEEL BAD.
BUT I'M GLAD SCOT TOLD ME, DON'T
PLAY YOU IDOL, BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT TO SHOW ANYBODY MY IDOL.
THE MORE PEOPLE KNOW, THE LESS
POWER YOU HAVE.
NOW I HAVE TO FIGHT AND SEE HOW
IT UNFOLDS.
I DEFINITELY NEED SOME LUCK.
>> LET'S JUST NOT GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL AGAIN.
>> WE DON'T WANT TO DO THAT
AGAIN.
>> CAN WE KILL THE CHICKEN
TOMORROW?
>> SINCE THE TRIBE SWAPPED,
EVERYTHING IS UP IN THE AIR.
THERE'S A LOT OF UNCERTAINTY AS
FAR AS ALLIANCES GO.
IT'S GOT ME THINKING ABOUT MY
NEXT STEP, SO IN THE OLD BRAIN
TRIBE, I WAS ON THE BOTTOM RUNG,
SO BELIEVE IT OR NOT, I MIGHT
ACTUALLY DISBAND THIS BRAIN
TRIBE.
>> I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING I WAS THINKING ABOUT.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS GAME IS EVOLVING.
I'M NOT JUST A BRAIN.
>> YEAH.
>> ON THE BRAIN, I WAS AT THE
BOTTOM RUNG BECAUSE THEY VOTED
OUT MY ALLIANCE.
I WAS NEXT.
SO I HAVE NO ALLEGIANCE TO THEM.
>> OH.
I WANT TO GET JOE OUT.
HE'S NOT HELPING US OUT WITH
ANYTHING.
BY LYING TO ME, AUBRY AND JOE
PISSED ME OFF.
A GAME IS A GAME.
IF I WAS STILL IN THEIR BRAIN
TRIBE, I WOULD BE ON THE BOTTOM
RUNG, SO I'M ACTUALLY
POSITIONING MYSELF BETTER.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET THEM GET IN
FRONT OF ME AND $1 MILLION.
I'M STARTING TO THINK IF I'M
GOING TO MAKE A MOVE, NOW IS THE
TIME.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> WE'RE ALL HAPPY AT CAMP,
SMILING.
WHAT'S GOING ON INSIDE IS JUST
THINKING, NON-STOP.
IT'S A NERVOUS ENERGY, LIKE
RIGHT BEFORE YOU'RE ABOUT TO
TAKE THE FIELD AS AN ATHLETE.
SO FROM HERE ON OUT I'LL BE
BONDING AND MAKING
RELATIONSHIPS.
TIME TO PLAY.
PLAY OR GO HOME.
>> YOU NOW, NICK, I'VE ALWAYS
FOUND, AND IT HASN'T MATTERED IF
I WAS GIRL SCOUTS, A SOCCER
TEAM, YOU KNOW, THE ANIMAL
RESCUE, I ALWAYS STEP UP TO THE
PLATE AND WILL LEAD WHEN NOBODY
ELSE DOES.
>> THAT'S WHAT IT SEEMS LIKE,
YEAH, YOU KNOW HOW TO LEAD.
>> DEBBIE IS EASY THE READ.
SHE JUST NEEDS TO TALK, SHE
NEEDS TO BE HEARD, LISTENED TO.
>> I'M ALWAYS ON THE SCAN FOR
THE COCONUTS.
>> SHE WANTS PEOPLE TO STEP UP
TO THE PLATE, SO I JUST HAVE TO
REMEMBER, BE THAT PERSON FOR
DEBBIE.
WHATEVER PERSON SHE ADMIRES,
WHICH IS HERSELF, JUST BE HER.
>> GIVE YOU THE HONOR.
>> I THINK NICK LOOKS LIKE A
GREEK GOD.
HE'S GOT FINELY CHISELED BONE,
ABSOLUTELY RIPPED, AND THE
ANGULAR FEATURES OF HIS FACE
JUST MAKE FOR GREAT PHOTOGRAPHY,
AND I KNOW THAT BECAUSE I EACH
MODELED OFF AND ON FOR YEARS AND
YEARS.
I BET ANYTHING HE GETS A REAL
MODELING CONTRACT.
BUT IT'S GOING TO HAVE NO EFFECT
ON MY STRATEGY TO MAKE IT TO THE
MERGE, AND THAT'S STILL MY
NUMBER-ONE PRIORITY.
I CAN START A FIRE WITH ONE
MATCH.
>> RIGHT.
>> DEBBIE MIGHT HAVE A CRUSH ON
ME.
SHE PROBABLY DOES.
MAYBE SHE'S BUTTERING ME UP,
THOUGH.
MAYBE SHE'S BLOWING SMOKE UP MY
REAR END.
BUT I DOUBT IT.
>> WE HAVE TREE MAIL.
HERE WE GO.
>> IN THIS CHALLENGE THE TRIBES
WE LEASE BUT WEES FROM THE FLOOR
OF THE OCEAN AND THROW THEM INTO
BASKETS.
>> I HAVE THE FEELING.
SURE ENOUGH, WE HAVE REWARD
CHALLENGE, WHICH INVOLVES SOME
FORM OF BASKETBALL.
OUR OPPONENTS HAVE A
PROFESSIONAL BASKETBALL PLAYER,
BUT WE HAVE OUR OWN SECRET
WEAPON, ADONIS, A.K.A. NICK.
>> I WAS A POINT GUARD IN HIGH
SCHOOL, SO I -- GOING UP AGAINST
AN NBA PLAYER, I'M NOT EXPECTED
TO WIN, BUT I WILL NOT GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
CHAN LOH GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW GONDOL TRIBE.
ANNA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN JULIA,
RETURNING FROM BRAWN BEACH.
JULIA GETTING HER FIRST LOOK AT
HER NEW TRIBE.
YOU WILL JOIN GONDOL, REPLACING
ANNA.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE A BUFF FOR
YOU.
>> HI, JULIA.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN DROP THAT
OVER BUFF.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: SHALL WE GET TO
TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, ONE MEMBER OF EACH
TRIBE DIVES DOWN TO RELEASE A
GROUP OF BUOYS.
YOU MUST THEN WORK TOGETHER TO
GET ALL THE BUT WEES BACK TO
SHORE WHERE THE TWO REMAINING
TRIBE MEMBERS WILL ATTEMPT TO
SHOOT THE BUOYS INTO A BASKET.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET TEN BUOYS IN
THEIR BASKET WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" PICNIC,
BREAD, MEAT, CHEESE, INDIVIDUAL
TACKLE, TUNA SALAD, ASSORTED
BEVERAGES.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO IT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
TAKE A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND
WE'LL GET IT ON.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, "SURVIVOR" READY?
GO!
>> GET 'EM, MICHELE.
>> Jeff: IT IS AUBRY FOR
GONDOL, MICHELE FOR CHAN LOH.
YOU GOT TO SWIM OUT, DIVE DOWN,
UNTIE THE KNOT.
>> LET'S GO, BLUE.
>> Jeff: 30 BUOYS WILL POP TO
THE SURFACE.
THERE GOES MICHELE.
SHE'S HEADING DOWN.
AUBRY RIGHT BEHIND HER.
MICHELE, NO, HEADING BACK DOWN
AGAIN.
AUBRY GOING BACK DOWN AGAIN.
AUBRY HAS THEM FOR GONDOL.
THE BUOYS ARE UP.
GO, GONDOL!
>> YEAH, AUBRY.
>> Jeff: JEWELBACK PETER, TAI
AND AUBRY WORKING THOSE BUOYS
BACK TOWARD THE SHORE.
BIG SETBACK FOR CHAN LOH.
MICHELE CAN NOT GET IT DONE.
GONDOL WITH A HUGE LEAD IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
>> STAY RELAXED.
>> Jeff: MICHELE STILL TRYING
TO GET IT.
>> YOU GOT IT.
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
>> Jeff: MICHELE STILL
WORKING.
>> COME ON, MICHELE.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS!
GO, CHAN LOH.
MICHELE DID IT.
CHAN LOH HAS THEIR BUOYS.
NOW YOU GOT TO GET THEM ALL TO
THE SHORE.
GONDOL NOW WITH A NICE LEAD.
THIS PART OF THE CHALLENGE COMES
DOWN TO HOW WELL YOU CAN CORRAL
THOSE BUOYS TOGETHER AS A TRIBE.
THE FASTER YOU GET BACK, THE
SOONER YOUR SHOOTERS CAN START
SHOOTING, AND THAT WILL BE THE
ADVANTAGE.
>> HEADS UP.
WE'RE ALMOST HERE.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO GET ALL
THOSE BUOYS BACK THE SHORE AND
THEN START SHOOTING.
>> THERE YOU GO.
TO THE BEACH, TO THE BEACH.
>> Jeff: GONDOL DOING A NICE
JOB MOVING MORE BUOYS.
THEY GOT THEM ALL OUT OF THE
WATER.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET THEM IN THE
RACK.
THERE IT IS.
YOU'RE DONE.
YOU CAN START SHOOTING.
GONDOL WITH A BIG LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
SCOT JUST MISSES.
CHAN LOH STILL WORKING.
SCOT VERY CLOSE AGAIN.
THERE YOU GO.
CHAN LOH HAS ALL THEIR BUOYS
BACK.
GO, NICK.
IT'S NOW NICK VERSUS SCOT.
>> YEAH, ONE.
>> Jeff: SCOT WITH THE FIRST
ONE FOR GONZALEZ.
GONDOL LEADS 1-0.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR TEN.
NICK IN AND OUT.
>> RELAX, RELAX.
>> Jeff: SCOT WITH HIS SECOND.
IT IS GONDOL WITH 2.
NICK WITH HIS FIRST FOR CHAN
LOH.
>> YOU GOT IT, NICK.
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: THERE'S THREE FOR
SCOT.
AND GONDOL.
NICK RETURNS FIRE WITH HIS
SECOND.
IN AND OUT FOR SCOT.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: YOU GOT TO HIT IT
JUST RIGHT, AND NICK DOES.
WE'RE TIED 3-3.
JUST LIKE THAT WE GOT A
CHALLENGE.
NICK CAN PUT CHAN LOH IN THE
LEAD AND HE DOES.
CHAN LOH WITH FOUR.
>> NICE JOB.
>> Jeff: GONDOL WITH THREE.
OH, AGAIN IN AND OUT, SCOT.
SO MANY SO CLOSE BUT NOT
STICKING.
NICK WITH NUMBER FIVE.
IT IS NOW CHAN LOH WITH FIVE,
GONDOL WITH THREE.
THERE'S FOUR.
SO GOOD HE SPLITS THE BUOY.
IT IS 5-4.
MAKE IT 6-4.
SCOT RETURNS FIRE.
>> GET IN THERE!
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
CHAN LOH LEADS 6-4 OVER GONDOL.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
MAKE IT SEVEN FOR CHAN LOH.
>> GREAT JOB, NICK.
>> Jeff: THAT'S FIVE.
WE'RE 7-5.
NICK JUST MISSES.
SCOT SCORES.
IT IS 7-6.
GONDOL CLOSING THE GAP.
MAKE IT 8-6.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: SCOT HAS GOT TO PICK
IT UP.
AND HE DOES.
IT IS 8-7.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK STILL.
NICK JUST MISSES.
WE ARE TIED.
IT IS 8-8.
TWO LEFT.
NICK JUST MISSES.
>> RELAX.
>> Jeff: SCOT SCORES.
GONDOL BACK IN THE LEAD.
9-8.
GONE GONE'S GOT ONE LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: NICK WITH ANOTHER
SHOT.
NICK JUST MISSES.
SCOT COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
>> SCOT, WHAT YOU DOING?
>> Jeff: AND HE DOES.
GONDOL WINS REWARD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> MY FAULT.
>> Jeff: HUGE REWARD.
GONDOL, COME GRAB IT.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP AND ENJOY YOUR
AFTERNOON OF FEASTING.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NICE SHOOTING, NICK.
YOU PUT THE PRESSURE ON HIM.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHAN LOH.
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> I SCREWED UP THE REWARD
CHALLENGE.
I FAILED OUR TEAM, YOU KNOW, AND
IT'S NERVE-RACKING FOR ME.
I GOT TO GO BACK THE CAMP AND
KEEP FIGHTING AND HOPEFULLY I
CAN TURN THINGS AROUND.
♪
>> BOOM.
>> TUNA SALAD.
>> THAT WAS THE BEST WAY TO COME
BACK IN.
>> YEAH, WELCOME.
>> WALKING INTO MY OLD CAMP WITH
A TON OF FOOD RIGHT AFTER BEING
ALONE WAS REALLY KIND OF
AWESOME, AND IT WAS A GOOD WAY
TO KIND OF ENTER THE TRIBE,
ENTERING ON GOOD VIBES IS
DEFINITELY A LOT BETTER THAN
ENTERING LOSING.
>> SO GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I WAS DEFINITELY TRYING TO GET A
READ ON THIS TRIBE BECAUSE I
AUTOMATICALLY WAS LIKE, CRAP,
I'M NEXT, I'M THE NEXT TO GO,
THERE'S NO QUESTION.
THEY GOT ANNA OUT, I HAVE THE
START FROM SCRATCH.
>> RIGHT, SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS
ALL DO?
CAN WE GO AROUND AND DO THIS?
>> YOU'RE A BOMB U. STUDENT?
>> I'M A B.U. STUDENT.
>> WHAT YEAR?
>> I AM A JUNIOR.
>> WHAT'S YOUR MAJOR.
>> I'M STUDYING COMMUNECATIONS.
>> I'M AN E.R. DOCTOR.
>> REALLY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> I WAS HAPPY JULIA CAME IN FOR
ANNA.
SHE WASN'T FROM MY INITIAL
IMPRESSION SOMEONE THAT'S
CONNIVING.
THAT'S SOMEONE I WANT TO WORK
WITH.
>> IT'S HARD JUST COMING IN.
AWESOME.
>> JOE HAS BEEN PISSING ME OFF
LATELY.
NO, THINK ABOUT IT.
THEY GOT RID OF MY ALLIANCE.
I'LL BE HONEST.
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT A TIME
TO GET OUT JOE AND AUBRY.
AUBRY IS MORE IMPORTANT TO GET
OUT BECAUSE SHE'S BIG TIME.
>> THAT'S WHAT I ASSUMED.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF NOW IS TOO
EARLY.
>> I'M DOWN.
I'M DOWN.
IT'S FUNNY.
PETER IMMEDIATELY LATCHED ON TO
ME AND WAS LIKE, LET'S WORK
TOGETHER AND GET AUBRY OUT.
I WAS LIKE, I'M TOTALLY ON BOARD
WITH THAT.
SOUNDS GOOD.
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT MY NAME, I
WILL GO WITH IT BECAUSE I GOT TO
SAVE MYSELF.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND THE MAN,
BRIGHT, SHARP, VERY INTELLIGENT,
STRONG.
>> THE BRAINS HAVE CONTROL OF
THIS TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
AND I WOULD PREFER THAT WE GET
OUT JULIA FIRST.
THAT'S THE EASY VOTE.
THE BRAINS KEEP THE NUMBERS, BUT
PETER DECIDES TO KIND OF ISOLATE
WITH HER, AND I'M A LITTLE BIT
SUSPICIOUS ABOUT THAT.
>> EVEN JULIA COMING BACK, YOU
SHE SHE'D SAY, WHAT CAN I DO?
>> SHE'S CALCULATING.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> PETER IS A LITTLE ROGUE AND
DESPERATE RIGHT NOW, WHICH MAKES
ME FEEL LIKE I NEED TO SERIOUSLY
CONSIDER WHETHER NOW IS THE TIME
FOR PETER TO GO.
>> NOBLE EFFORT, EVERYBODY.
VALIANT.
>> 100% MY FAULT.
>> YOU HELD YOUR OWN.
IT WAS AMAZING.
>> WE WERE BEHIND WITH THE BALLS
COMING UP, SO HE STARTED AHEAD
OF YOU AND FINISHED AHEAD OF
YOU, BUT YOU DID GREAT.
>> I WAS ANGRY WITH MYSELF.
I SHOULD HAVE WON THAT.
OF COURSE, EVERYBODY GOES, NO,
NO, NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
YOU WERE GOING AGAINST AN NBAF
PLAYER.
I SHOULD HAVE CLOSED A DEAL, BUT
MICHELE COULDN'T UNTIE THE KNOT
AT THE VERY BEGINNING.
WELL, ANNA'S GONE.
>> TODAY WAS NOT THE BEST DAY
FOR MY "SURVIVOR" GAME.
A GIRL WHO IS IN MY TOP-TWO
ALLIANCE GOT VOTED OUT.
BESIDES THAT I JUST PUT MY HEAD
ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK BY BLOWING
THAT CHALLENGE.
AND IT FREAKING SUCKS.
>> MICHELE, DON'T BEAT YOURSELF
UP.
SHE MIGHT GO DROWN HERSELF.
YOU GUYS MIGHT WANT THE KEEP AN
EYE ON HER.
>> DAMN, DEBBIE.
>> EVERYTHING THAT'S BEEN UP TO
THIS POINT, IT FEELS LIKE IT'S
TEETERING, BUT I'M NOT ONE TO
GIVE UP.
IT DOES SEEM LIKE I HAVE THE
START OVER, SO I'M JUST GOING TO
TRY AND USE MY SOCIAL SKILLS TO
BUILD ME BACK UP.
THERE ARE TIMES THAT YOU NEED TO
STEP UP, AND I DEFINITELY NEEDED
TO STEP UP AND I DIDN'T.
I WAS REALLY BUMMED OBVIOUSLY.
>> I KNOW YOU WERE.
>> WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO
SOMETHING THAT CLOSE, YOU
SHOULDER THE RESPONSIBILITY, AND
IT SUCKS.
I LIKE DEBBIE A LOT.
SHE'S REALLY QUIRKY, AND I THINK
SHE'S PRETTY HONEST AND UPFRONT
ABOUT WHAT SHE THINKS AND WHAT
SHE RESPECTS.
SO MAYBE DEBBIE'S MY BEST
OPTION.
I'M HOPING WE DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO TRIBAL, IF WE DO, WHO ARE YOU
THINKING?
>> I'M THINKING I DON'T CARE FOR
JASON ALL THAT MUCH BECAUSE HE
DOESN'T DO ANYTHING AROUND CAMP.
AND I'D RATHER HAVE A WOMAN WIN.
THIS I'D RATHER THE GIRLS BATTLE
IT OUT.
WE'RE OUTNUMBERED RIGHT NOW.
>> BIG TIME.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO
THINK YOU HAVE NO OPTIONS.
SHE WANTS US TO WORK WITH HER TO
GET JASON OUT.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING THAT WAY.
HERE'S THE THING.
EVERYONE'S GOING TO BE FRIENDLY
TOWARD YOU.
THIS IS THE PEP TALK DEBBIE GAVE
YOU.
SHE WANTS YOUR SPIRITS TO BE UP
SO YOU'RE NOT NERVOUS, BUT YOU
ARE DEFINITELY THE TARGET.
>> THE WAY THAT NICK SPEAKS TO
ME IS NOT IN A WAY THAT I WOULD
EVER TOLERATE MAN SPEAKING TO ME
IN MY REGULAR LIFE, AND I JUST
WANT TO BE LIKE, BRO, I KNOW,
BUT THAT'S HIS EGO.
>> WE HAVE TO TRUST SOMEBODY,
AND I DON'T THINK WE TRUST
DEBBIE.
I DON'T THINK WE TRUST NEAL.
I HAVE TO ALMOST COACH MICHELE
IN THIS GAME.
SHE'S YOUNG AND SHE DOESN'T
REALLY KNOW HOW TO MANIPULATE.
SO THAT'S GOING TO BE MY JOB
FROM HERE ON OUT.
MAKING SURE MICHELE IS UNDER MY
WING AND MAKING SURE SHE SAYS
THE RIGHT THINGS AND COMES
ACROSS THE RIGHT WAY.
SO THE PLAN IS WE'LL STICK WITH
BRAWN AND THEN WE'LL FIGURE IT
OUT WHEN WE GET OVER ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
>> RIGHT NOW WHAT I'M GOING TO
DO IS JUST LET NICK BABY ME AND
MAKE HIM BELIEVE THAT I NEED ALL
THE HELP THAT HE CAN OFFER.
LIKE THE INNOCENT LITTLE GIRL,
LIKE I'M STUPID, BUT ACTUALLY
I'M A STRONG, INDEPENDENT WOMAN,
AND WHEN IT COMES TIME TO MAKE A
MOVE, THEN I WILL.
I DON'T NEED TO BE CARRIED, BRO.
>> WE HAVEN'T SPOKEN MUCH.
>> I KNOW.
BUT I TALKED TO JULIA, AND WE
WANT TO GET AUBRY OUT.
>> YOU WANT TO GET AUBRY OUT?
>> AND I WESTBOUND -- WANT TO
GET JOE OFF OUR TEAM BECAUSE
HE'S BOSSY.
I'M A FREE AGENT.
EVER SINCE THEY TOOK OUT MY
ALLIANCE MEMBER, I'VE BEEN OUT
THE GET THEM.
>> EVERY TIME I TURN AROUND,
THERE'S PETER WALKING AWAY WITH
THOSE GUYS AND IT MAKES ME
NERVOUS BECAUSE PETE'S BEEN
AFTER MY BUTT FROM THE GET GO.
>> HE'S WORKING THEM ALL OVER
RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M GOING TO APPROACH HIM.
AND IF HE LICE TO ME, THAT'S IT.
THE PROBLEM WITH PETER IS HE
PLAYS BOTH SIDES.
AND HE'S SO TRANSPARENT, YOU CAN
SEE RIGHT THROUGH HIM.
FORTUNATELY I'M RETIRED F.B.I.,
AND I'M TRAINED TO DEAL WITH
SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
I'M GOING TO ASK ONE QUESTION
AND YOU TELL ME STRAIGHT UP:ARE
YOU TRYING TO TAKE ME OUT?
>> DON'T LIE.
>> WHAT WAS THE QUESTION?
>> ARE YOU TELLING PEOPLE TO
TAKE JOE OUT, AND IF YOU LIE
RIGHT NOW, I'M TELLING YOU...
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH.
TELL ME THE TRUTH, PETE, DON'T
DANCE AROUND.
DON'T [BLEEPED] ME.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SAY YES OR
NO.
>> JOE STARTS ACCUSING ME OF
WANTING TO VOTE HIM OUT THERE.
IS A SERB ELEMENT OF TRUTH TO
THAT.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING AS HARD AS
POSSIBLE.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT JUST BLEW UP
ON ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> ANSWER THE QUESTION.
IT'S NOT A TOUGH QUESTION.
ARE YOU TELLING PEOPLE, JOE'S
GOT TO GO.
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> NEVER MIND.
WHEN YOU CORNER SOMEBODY LIKE
THAT AND THEY DON'T WANT TO TELL
THE TRUTH, THEY START DANCING,
WHICH IS WHAT HAPPENED.
HE'S KIND OF LIKE THE CANCER.
I DON'T KNOW, HE'S JUST NOT
TRUST WORTHY.
SO I'M DONE WITH THAT.
AND IF WE LOSE THE NEXT
CHALLENGE, WE GOT THE -- TO TAKE
HIM OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
CYDNEY, I MUST TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, BOTH
TRIBES WILL WORK TOGETHER TO GET
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
THEN TWO TRIBE MEMBERS WILL USE
POLES TO KNOCK BLOCKS OUT OF AN
OVERHEAD NET.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE BLOCKS,
YOU MUST STACK THEM ONE ON TOP
OF THE OTHER.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
THIS CHALLENGE WILL COME DOWN TO
ONE THING AND ONE THING ONLY:
TEAMWORK.
THE TRIBE WITH THE BEST TEAMWORK
WILL WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
TAKE A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS A RACE OVER THIS FIRST
OBSTACLE.
YOU NEED TO ATTACK IT.
DO NOT WASTE ANY TIME RIGHT
HERE.
>> EVERYBODY GOOD?
EVERYBODY GOOD?
>> Jeff: PRETTY EVEN OUT OF
THE GATE.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: NICK AND JASON HOP
OVER.
SCOT IS OVER.
SCOT HELPING TIE, WHO IS
STRUGGLING.
>> ON THE MAT.
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH IS OVER
FIRST.
GOOD TEAMWORK.
HEAD ON.
THIS WILL BE THE TOUGHEST PART
RIGHT HERE.
YOU GOT TO GET UP AND OVER AND
YOU CANNOT USE THE STRUCTURE.
JOE GOING UP AND OVER.
>> NICE, NICE, NICE.
>> Jeff: GONDOL HAS TO PICK IT
UP.
>> READY?
>> EVERYBODY GOOD?
>> Jeff: NICK IS UP AND OVER
ON HIS OWN.
NICK PULLING UP DEBBIE.
CHAN LOH STILL IN THE LEAD.
HERE COMES SCOT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE GOING TO RELY ON
SCOT.
SCOT GETS JOE OVER.
SCOT GETS TAI OVER.
THIS IS LIKE A DAD WITH A KID.
JULIA GOING UP AND OVER.
GONDOL CAUGHT UP NOW.
CYDNEY'S NOW UP FOR CHAN LOH.
HERE COMES NEAL.
PETER USING HIS BACK FOR A HUGE
DUDE, AND THIS IS WHERE GONDOL
IS STARTING TO FALL BEHIND.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: SCOT IS FINALLY OVER.
>> LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH, START
UNTYING.
>> QUICK, QUICK, QUICK.
>> Jeff: HERE GOES PETER.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
>> GO, GO.
GO!
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH WITH A NICE
LEAD.
GOT TO UNTIE BOTH POLES.
IT IS JASON AND NICK FOR CHAN
LOH.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff: IT IS SCOT AND PETER
FOR GONDOL.
>> YOU GUYS GOT IT.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE 20 BLOCKS.
YOU HAVE TO GET ALL 20 OUT OF
THIS NET BEFORE YOU CAN MOVE ON.
>> KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING, KEEP
GOING.
>> Jeff: FIRST BLOCK OUT FOR
GONDOL.
THERE'S ONE OUT FOR CHAN LOH.
ANOTHER FOR GONDOL.
GONDOL NOW IN THE LEAD WITH
ANOTHER BLOCK AND TWO MORE.
NICK AND JASON STRUGGLING.
GONDOL WITH A BIG LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GO.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: GONDOL WORKING ON TO
THE FINAL STAGE OF THIS
CHALLENGE WHILE CHAN LOH IS
STILL WORKING ON THEIR BLOCKS.
YOU HAVE 20 BLOCKS.
YOU HAVE TO STACK THEM ONE ON
TOP OF EACH OTHER.
THIS STACK IS GOING TO GET VERY
HIGH.
YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT A SYSTEM
FOR WORKING TOGETHER.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD TRY, SCOT
WILL HOLD THE LITTLE ONES AND WE
PUT BIG BLOCKS BELOW IT.
>> HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
>> YOU GOT THREE MORE?
>> Jeff: NICK AND JASON TRYING
TO CATCH UP.
>> GET IT, GET IT, GET IT.
>> Jeff: NICK WITH THE LAST
ONE.
LET'S GO, CHAN LOH!
PICK IT UP.
THEY HAD THE LEAD FOR MOST OF
THE CHALLENGE, BUT NOT ANYMORE.
GONDOL IS MAKING QUICK WORK OF
THIS.
THREE AT A TIME?
>> ONE AT A TIME.
>> STACK THE TWO, STACK THE
THREE, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: SCOT AND PETER
LIFTING THE STACK, VERY RISKY
APPROACH.
THEY'RE STACKING FROM THE
MIDDLE.
SCOT TRYING TO HOLD IT STEADY
ALONG WITH PETER, BUT IT IS
REALLY WOBBLY AT THE TOP.
>> ARE WE GOOD HERE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE ON THE
SHOULDERS OF NICK.
A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT STRATEGY.
DEBBIE STACKING THREE MORE.
>> HOLE ON, HOLD ON.
>> Jeff: GONDOL DOWN TO THEIR
LAST ONE.
THEY CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
GONDOL TAKING THEIR TIME.
THEY'RE GOING THE LOSE IT.
NO, THEY'RE NOT.
IT'S WOBBLING.
IT'S TIPPING.
WATCH OUT.
BLOCKS HIT JOE IN THE HEAD.
THOSE ARE BIG, HEAVY BLOCKS.
OPENS THE DOOR FOR CHAN LOH NOW.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> I GOT A HARD HEAD.
>> Jeff: IT IS NEAL, DEBBIE,
NICK, MICHELE, JASON AND CYDNEY.
IS THIS IT?
BLOCKS FALLING NOW FOR CHAN LOH.
THE DOOR BACK OPEN FOR GONDOL.
JOE TOOK A BIG HIT TO THE HEAD,
BLOOD STREAMING DOWN HIS FACE.
TAI NOW ON SCOT'S SHOULDERS.
DEBBIE STANDING ON NICK'S
SHOULDERS WHOM WILL GET THERE
FIRST?
CHAN LOH DOWN TO THEIR LAST
THREE.
TAI LITERALLY STANDING ON SCOT'S
SHOULDERS.
THIS IS TEAMWORK RIGHT HERE.
CHAN LOH OR GONDOL?
>> COME ON, BUDDY.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH DOWN TO
THEIR LAST BLOCK.
GONDOL DOWN TO THEIR LAST BLOCK.
DEBBIE HAS IT.
GET ON YOUR MAT.
>> COME ON.
>> Jeff: ONE, TWO, THREE.
CHAN LOH WINS!
LITERALLY BY SECONDS.
CHAN LOH, DRAMATIC FINISH.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER WIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GONDOL, TROOBL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ON THE WAY OUT, JOE, HAVE A LOOK
AT THAT.
>> KEEPING PETERS NUMBERS-WISE
WOULD MAKE SENSE IF HE WAS A
STRAIGHT SHOOTER, BUT YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO.
BEFORE YOU GET IN A POSITION
WHERE, OH, MY GOD, I'M IN
TROUBLE, YOU TAKE THE TROUBLE
OUT.
>> SO CLOSE.
>> VERY CLOSE.
>> WE DID NOTHING WRONG.
JUST ONE SECOND AWAY.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE PUT THE BIG
BLOCKS AND THEN THE LITTLE.
I'M SORRY.
>> I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS THAT
HIGH.
>> YEAH, IT WAS REALLY, REALLY
>> TODAY PETER HAD A STRATEGY
FOR HOW TO STACK THE BLOCKS, BUT
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT SO WELL.
AND NOW WE GOT TO GO TO TRIBAL.
EVEN THOUGH I DON'T TRUT HIM, I
FEEL LIKE IT'S NOT THE RIGHT
THING RIGHT NOW TO GET RID OF
PETER, BECAUSE IF WE DO THAT,
TAI, SCOT AND JULIA WILL HAVE
THE NUMBERS, 3-2.
AND THAT REALLY SCARES ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> RIGHT NOW, THAT ARGUMENT...
>> IT'S A BIG DEAL.
>> HE WIGGED OUT.
>> SO WE WANT THE KEEP THE TRIBE
TOGETHER, IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
>> HERE'S THE DEAL: IF WE TAKE
OUT PETER, THEY'RE GOING TO COME
AFTER US NEXT.
>> I'M SICK OF PETER, BUT AUBRY
DOES MAKE SENSE BECAUSE IF WE
VOTE HIM OUT, WE'RE GOING TO BE
DOWN ONE, AND THAT'S REALLY
DANGEROUS.
SO WE MIGHT HAVE TO KEEP HIM
SHORT TERM, EVEN THOUGH HE'S A
BIG PAIN IN THE BUTT.
>> TALK TO PETER AND WORK IT OUT
AS GUYS, YOU KNOW?
>> I WANT THE MAKE AMENDS WITH
YOU.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> I WANT THE KEEP THIS TEAM
TOGETHER.
>> I DO, TOO.
THERE'S NO REASON I WOULD VOTE
YOU OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I KNOW...
>> I'M GOING TO BELIEVE YOU.
>> IT'S A TRUST THING.
>> IT IS A TRUST THING, PETE.
YOU SAID, YES, I DID, JOE, THAT
WOULD HAVE BEEN IT.
>> I REALLY WANTED TO BLINDSIDE
EITHER AUBRY OR JOE, BUT THAT
BLEW UP, SO YOU HAVE TO ROLL
WITH THE PUNCHES AND TAKE IT DAY
BY DAY.
AT THIS POINT I FEEL LIKE IT'S
BETTER TO GO WITH THE BRAINS,
TAKE OUT JULIA AND NOT STIR THE
WATERS.
>> WE HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
IT'S GOING TO BE JULIA.
>> I CAN ASSURE AUBRY, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT'S THE PLAN, DOCTOR?
>> I'M JUST WATCHING ALL THIS GO
DOWN.
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TALK OR NO?
>> I'M SCRATCHING MY PLAN.
MY MUTINY FELL THROUGH BECAUSE
JOE IS ON EDGE NOW.
I WANT THE KEEP TAI AROUND
BECAUSE I WANT THE CHICKEN.
WE'RE VOTING JEWELA.
>> PETEER IS VOTING WITH THE
BRAIN, SO EVERYTHING HE TOLD ME
IS A LOT OF B.S.
HE IS A SNAKE, AND I THINK
EVERYBODY SEES RIGHT THROUGH HIS
EVEN NEAR, BUT STILL, THEY'RE
GOING TO STICK TOGETHER, AND
THAT DOESN'T GIVE THE REST OF US
A LOT OF OPTIONS.
>> PETER SAID THEY'RE VOTING
TOGETHER.
>> JOE AND AUBRY ARE STUPID.
HE'S GOING TO TAKE THEM OUT.
>> THE REASON THEY WANT TO KEEP
HIM IS BECAUSE THEY THINK WE'LL
TAKE THEM OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WE'RE AT A STALEMATE.
>> I'M DEFINITELY CONCERNED
ABOUT TRIBAL TONIGHT.
I KNOW I'M ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK, COMING IN LATE TO THE
GAME, SO IF WE DON'T DO
SOMETHING, I'M PRETTY MUCH GOING
HOME.
>> IF WE... HE'S A SMART GUY.
>> HE'S SO ARROGANT.
JOE AND PETER.
>> JOE'S LOYAL.
WE NEED TO TALK TO AUBRY.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT TRYING THE BREAK YOU
GUYS UP, BUT TELL AUBRY WHAT
PETER TOLD YOU.
>> PETER WAS TALKING TO ME AND
HE SAID I ORIGINALLY TALKED TO
TAI ABOUT GETTING OUT JOE, BUT
I'M THINKING NOW INSTEAD OF JOE
WE SHOULD GO WITH AUBRY.
SO PETEER IS USING YOU RIGHT NOW
AS LIKE A PAWN TO SAVE HIMSELF.
>> I WASN'T SURPRISED TO HEAR
THAT PETER HAS BEEN TRYING "THE
BLIND SIDE" JOE, APPARENTLY HE
ALSO THREW ME UNDER THE BUS.
I WAS GOING BY THE MANTRA IT'S
BETTER TO STAY WITH THE DEVIL
YOU KNOW, BUT AT THIS POINT,
PETER IS SUCH A WILD CARD, I'M
LIKE, ARE WE REALLY GOING TO
KEEP SOMEONE YOU'RE AFRAID IS
GOING TO BLIND SIDE YOU WERE YOU
BLIND SIDE HIM.
>> WE DON'T NEED HIM, SO I WOULD
BE HAPPY IF WE TOOK PETER OUT.
>> OKAY.
WELL, THANK FOR THE HEADS UP.
>> AUBRY DIDN'T SAY MUCH AT ALL.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S
THINKING.
BUT THEY GOT THE NUMBERS.
WHY WOULD THEY DO ANYTHING ELSE
THAN THE MOST OBVIOUS THING,
WHICH IS VOTING OUT JULIA?
>> I DON'T THINK SHE BELIEVED
ME.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A TIE.
>> OUR ORIGINAL PLAN WAS TO
CONVINCE AUBRY TO COME WITH US
AND TAKE OUT PETER.
BUT THE REALITY IS WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S GOING TO DO, SO WE
MAY HAVE TO JUST VOTE OUT JULIA
AND LIVE TO FIGHT ANOTHER DAY.
>> I DON'T HAVE AN AFFINITY OF
JULIA, IF SHE HAS TO GO, SHE HAS
TO GO.
I'M WITH YOU, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
>> PETER IS TELLING EVERYONE ME.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GET RID OF HIM.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS, COW COME
BACK WITH THAT?
I JUST WENT ALONG WITH WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO AND NOW YOU'RE
CHANGING.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
SERIOUSLY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
AND IT PUTS ME IN A BAD
SITUATION.
DO I STICK WITH THESE BRAINS OR
DO I SLIP, TAKE OUT PETER, AND
POTENTIALLY LOSE JOE'S TRUST?
>> I'M NOT SWITCHING.
I'M STAYING WITH THE PLAN.
YOU START DOING THAT LAST MINUTE
AND YOU GET YOURSELF CAUGHT UP.
I'M GOING TO VOTE JULIA.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S IT THEN.
>> I HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION,
AND I FEEL LIKE NO MATTER WHAT I
DO, IT'S GOING TO BLOW BACK AND
BITE ME IN THE ASS.
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB IT.
DIP IT IN THE FLAME AND GET
FIRE.
IT'S PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
SO, JULIA, YOU'RE THE NEWEST
MEMBER TO THIS TRIBE.
WHAT IS THE VIBE OF THIS GROUP?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE THREE
BRAINS, THAT DEFINITELY HAS KIND
OF CREATED THIS VERY INTERESTING
DYNAMIC.
I THINK RIGHT NOW WE'RE VERY
SPLIT.
SO IT'S GOING TO BE INTERESTING
TO SEE WHAT COMES OUT TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, ANY CONCERN
THAT A NEW PERSON LOOKS AND
SAYS, I SEE A SPLINTER HERE, A
FACTION THERE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THERE WERE TRIBES WE WERE ON
BEFORE, AND SOME OF THAT LEGACY
CARRIES OVER, AN YOU ALSO FORM
NEW RELATIONSHIPS, AND IT GETS
VERY COMPLEX.
>> Jeff: SCOT, SOUNDS LIKE
SHE'S TALKING ABOUT DO THE THREE
BRAINS STICK TOGETHER OR IS THIS
TRIBE OF SIX THE NEW TRIBE AND
YOU FIND DIVISIONS WITHIN IT?
>> I THINK THAT'S THE GROWING
PAINS WE'RE STILL GOING THROUGH
RIGHT NOW.
AND JULIA PICKED UP ON THAT.
IF WE'RE GOING TO MAINTAIN OLD
ALLIANCES OR FORGE NEW ONES AND
BE CONFIDENT IN THOSE.
>> Jeff: PETER, TALK ABOUT THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
WHEN YOU GOT BACK THE CAMP, WAS
THERE ANY FINGER POINTING?
>> IF THERE'S ANY FINGER POINT,
IT SHOULD BE MY DIRECTION.
I HAD THE IDEA OF ELEVATING THE
TOWER VERSUS BUILDING IT ON TOP.
WE WERE VERY CLOSE, ONE BLOCK
AWAY.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, WITH PETER
SAYING, I'LL TAKE IT, I MADE THE
DECISION AND I WAS WRONG, IS
THAT ALONE ENOUGH TO VOTE HIM
OUT.
>> SURE, BUT WE'VE ALSO BEEN
SEEING A LOT OF OTHER SIDES OF
PETER OVER THE LAST FEW DAY,
TOO, ONES THAT PEOPLE ARE
QUESTIONING AND THEY'RE IN THE
ALWAYS SURE WHERE HE STANDS, SO
THERE ARE THINGS TO TAKE INTO
CONSIDERATION TOO.
>> Jeff: JULIA, AS THE NEWEST
PERSON, ANY ATTENTION ON
SOMEBODY ELSE IS GREAT NEWS, BUT
THE PROBLEM FOR YOU RIGHT NOW IS
YOU CAN'T TRUST WHAT ANYONE IS
SAYING.
>> EXACTLY.
AND THE FIRST PERSON TO TALK
GAME TO ME AS SOON AS I GOT TO
CAMP WAS PETER.
YES, I'M STILL IN THIS.
OF COURSE, EVERYONE HAS
SOMETHING ELSE TO SAY.
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO GRASP WHAT'S
ACTUALLY HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: PETER, DID YOU MAKE A
CASE, LOOK, JULIA'S THE NEWEST,
WE'RE A FIGHT FIVE, LET'S STAY
THAT WAY?
>> WELL, THIS GONDOL TRIBE IS
COMPLEX, SO IT COMES DOWN THE
TRUST.
THAT'S WHERE IT GETS SCARY,
BECAUSE IF THERE ARE ANY
FISSURES, THEY'LL BE SHOWING
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: SCOT, IS THAT WHERE
THIS GAME IS, A CONSTANT
JUGGLING ACT OF WHAT SHOULD WE
DO?
>> I BELIEVE SO BECAUSE THERE
ARE CERTAIN MEMBERS OF THE TRIBE
THAT MAKE A DECISION AND TEN
MINUTES LATER THEY NEED TO GO
OFF AND TALK ABOUT IT AGAIN.
THAT CREATES DISSENSION, THAT
CREATES DISTRUST, AND THAT
WORRIES PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: SO AUBRY, YOU HAVE
ALL THIS INFORMATION, FROM HERER
FROM THERE, FROM THERE, FROM
EVERYWHERE.
HOW DO YOU PROCESS IT?
>> I TRY TO BE AS LOGICAL AS
POSSIBLE WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO
NUMBERS, BUT AT THE END OF THE
DAY SHE'S SHADED BY THE GUT
FEELING I GET ABOUT WHAT PEOPLE
ARE SAYING TO ME.
>> Jeff: SO, JOE, IS THERE A
PLAN IN PLACE AND REGARDLESS OF
WHAT'S HAPPENED TONIGHT, IT
SHOULD GET PLAYED OUT?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, JEFF, YOU
DREW OUT SOME INTERESTING
ANSWERS THAT PEOPLE ARE
UNWILLING TO ELABORATE ON, BUT I
HAVE NO IDEA HOW THIS VOTE IS
GOING TO GO.
>> REALLY?
>> I THOUGHT I DID, BUT NOW A
LOT OF STUFF HAS BEEN BROUGHT UP
AND IT'S INTERESTING TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> Jeff: PETER, THERE'S A LOT
OF TALKING GOING ON.
I'M ASKING QUESTIONS, AND
THERE'S THREE OR FOUR
CONVERSATIONS.
>> BUT I CAN'T READ LIPS.
IT LOOKS LIKE PIRANHAS JUST
GOING AT IT.
THEY'RE MAKING A DECISION REALLY
FAST, AND I'M GOING TO TRY TOO3
GET ON.
>> Jeff: DO YOU FEEL AS SOLID
NOW AS YOU DID WHEN TRIBAL
STARTED?
>> IT'S COMPLETELY ALIVE.
IT'S DYNAMIC.
THAT'S WHERE IT GETS SCARY.
>> JULIA, ORIGINAL PLAN.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: SCOT, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> ORIGINAL PLAN.
>> Jeff: WOW.
SO IT REALLY IS ALIVE.
JOE IS NOW LOOKING AT AUBRY
GOING, WHAT'S ORIGINAL PLAN
MEAN.
JEWELBACK OUT OF THE BLUE, ONE
COMMENT, THIS GAME IS ALIVE.
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: IS THERE ANYTHING
ELSE WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT OR
SHOULD WE VOTE AND SETTLE THIS?
>> WE SHOULD VOTE.
>> JUST VOTE.
>> Jeff: AUBRY AND JOE ARE
STILL TALKING.
YOU READY TO VOTE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JULIA, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IS THE PLAN AS FAR AS I
KNOW.
AS LONG AS MY NAME IS NOT
WRITTEN DOWN I'M COOL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL BE ASKED TO LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, PETER.
JULIA.
PETER.
TWO VOTES PETER.
JULIA.
TWO VOTES PETER, TWO VOTES
PETER.
THAT'S THREE VOTES PETER, TWO
VOTES JULIA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT, PETER.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
PETER, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, THERE WAS CLEARLY A LOT OF
UNCERTAINTY ABOUT TONIGHT'S
VOTE.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS TO
YOU GUYS, YOU SURVIVE AND WILL
LIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY IN WHICH
THE UNCERTAINTY OF THIS GAME
WILL MOST CERTAINLY RETURN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR"...
>> IT'S THE MERGE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THE MERGE HAS EVERYONE
SCRAMBLING FOR POWER.
>> EVERYBODY IS DANGLING.
>>.
>> Jeff: BUT WHO WILL RISE TO
THE TOP IN.
>> SCREW EVERYBODY ELSE.
THIS IS OUR GAME.
WE ARE UNSTOPPABLE.
>> WE'RE JUST SHOVING GEEKS IN
LOCKERS RIGHT NOW.
>> IT SUCKS.
IT'S HEARTBREAKING BEING VOTED
OFF.
I UNDERSTAND WHERE THEY'RE
COMING FROM.
LIFE GOES ON.
I'M DISAPPOINTED IN JOE AND
AUBRY.
$1 MILLION IS NOT WORTH MY
DIGNITY OR WORD.
OF COURSE I'M MAD, BUT NO ONE IS
GOING DEEP ON THAT TEAM NOW AND
I LOOK FORWARD IN SEEING THEM IN
THE NEXT FEW DAYS.
IF THIS IS OVER STACKING BOXES,
I'LL NEVER HEAR THE END OF IT.