translated from Addic7ed.com french, translatesubtitles.com
Previously on Survivor...
Everything seemed to be going well
for Tai.
I have power now.
He had an idol
an advantage in the game...
"You have won
an extra vote."
...and a covenant of five.
It's Julia.
But Jason and Julia saw
that Tai was the most dangerous.
It's stupid not to eliminate Tai.
They tried to convince
Cydney and Michele to release Tai...
Getting rid of Tai is crucial.
...which left
Cydney and Michele with a heavy decision.
It's good for us to have the choice.
Exit the most dangerous
or eliminate one of Michele's closest
allies.
At the council,
Jason pleaded
for Tai's elimination.
I trusted my allies
and Tai flipped
over more times than a pancake.
He's done it twice already!
What makes you think
there won't be a 3rd time around?
But Michele and Cydney
stayed with the majority
and sent Julia to the jury...
Julia, the tribe has spoken.
...Jason must now
fend for himself.
There are six left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
You are incredibly persuasive.
I was afraid.
I almost played my idol.
I leaned over to her,
I said, "What should I do?"
It scared me.
The board was a bit hot.
People know now
that I can preach.
I can speak.
I do it every day
in my job.
I would convince a mother
to report her child to me.
We all got there.
- We made it.
More than six.
You have to seize the opportunities
that present themselves.
It's time
to make changes.
Tai will be tough to beat.
And Aubry will be tough to beat.
Having me on your side
wouldn't be bad for you.
I have no allegiance to anyone.
But it's better to have me,
me, in the final trio
rather than one of them.
It's time
to set up a scheme,
to play for oneself,
to go all the way.
Jason frankly went there
with Cyd and me.
And it would be smart
to go all the way with him.
But I don't want
to doubt my allies.
That's why I voted Julia,
'Cause there's no better way
to show my loyalty
than to eliminate my main ally.
If the three of us stick together...
We will stay united.
Everyone knows now
that we stay united.
I have an extra vote.
We will use it next time.
And we will have four votes.
Suddenly
Tai reveals that he has an advantage,
an extra vote,
and an immunity idol.
And next,
I'll use my idol.
- We're quiet.
- We're not moving from here.
We stay at least
until the last square.
It's a little scary.
Tai has so many levels of control
and I must stay by his side.
They don't know
about the extra vote.
Only the three of us know.
For now, my alliance
is Aubry and Joe.
It's already a close-knit group of three.
And Cydney is number four.
Which leaves Michele and Jason.
If we stay true
to each other,
nobody can do anything.
So on the next vote,
it's either Jason,
that is...
He may be
less dangerous than Michele.
Michele is a
more complete player.
So...
I have an extra vote
for one of them.
Come see this crazy thing!
What's this ?
It's a big larva.
We may have to eat it
in a trial.
Tai, would you eat it?
It's a larva.
I dug and saw this larva.
She is big.
A little gross.
I said,
"Maybe Mark will like it."
Let's see.
- Oh my God !
- Here he goes!
Yeah, he wanted her, that's for sure!
Oh, my God, look at the chicken!
Wow, that's brutal!
- Oh my God !
- He swallowed it!
Swallowed whole!
Like: "It's mine,
nobody eats it!"
He ate it all.
It was funny.
I gave up eating that chicken
days ago.
Everyone loves that chicken jerk.
Mark is sure to see the 39th day,
for now.
Watch out, Tai, here come the chickens!
They will steal your feathers!
I am clearly
between a rock and a hard place.
I'm frustrated.
They don't let me play
nobody wants to
discuss strategy with me,
their course is fixed,
it's like talking to walls.
What do you do ? You are thinking ?
I'm hanging out with Mark.
I see it.
What are you thinking about ?
We're spoiling the concept of the game
at this point.
Just hanging out?
No, by not playing anymore.
It's time to act,
but no one is playing anymore,
everyone accepted their position.
It's frustrating.
It pisses me off.
Jason has little respect
for what goes wrong with him.
And here I am
away, and I still want to play.
I always imagine
some very crazy shots,
and everyone goes,
"Huh! I don't really want to."
When it doesn't go his way,
he's vulgar
and tries to force it.
But people are not fooled.
And if I should be excluded,
reduced to just watching,
with no choice,
then I won't help anymore.
At this point,
I only have one card to play,
the "feigning" card.
I do nothing
and I eat their food.
I don't help with wood
or anything.
Why help
those who want me dead?
That's how it is, so...
Doing that makes them think:
"He won't get any votes.
Let's keep it."
- I don't know what else to say.
- Let's stay there.
Yeah.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
you will be divided
into two teams of three.
At my signal,
one by one you will overcome
a series of obstacles
up to a floating maze.
When you three are there,
you will collaborate
to evolve three balls there.
The first team to finish
win the reward.
- Do you want to know what's at stake?
- Yeah !
This reward is quite intense.
You will go to a place called
The wildlife alliance.
It is an organization,
here in Cambodia,
who saves animals from poachers
and traffickers
and brings them to this refuge
so that they may have a better life.
Great.
You can visit
their facilities
and interact with animals.
You will also be entitled
to an afternoon picnic.
- Is it worth it ?
- Yes !
I know it well. We draw
the teams and we start.
We have our two teams.
face Tai, Michele and Jason.
For the reward, here we go.
Survivors, ready?
Jason goes first.
Joe goes first.
Jason quickly jumps
over these obstacles,
leaving Joe
at the first platform.
You have to go all the way
before the next one can go.
Joe is still progressing
for the Yellows.
It takes him a while, but he's going.
Go, the Blues!
Michele is in the water
for the Blues.
Joe is still progressing
for the Yellows.
Michele is at obstacles
for the Blues.
Joe se his se.
His body is tired,
but he hasn't given up.
Michele arrived.
Go, the Blues!
Tai is in the water for the Blues.
Joe crawls to his mat.
Go, the Yellows!
Cydney is in the water
for the Yellows.
Cydney needs to buy some time.
The Blues have a big lead.
Tai will take the first ball
for the Blues.
Tai has the first ball
Aubry is in the water for the Yellows.
Alright, you can start.
The Blues have their first ball.
Now we need to work together
to move this ball
through the maze.
Aubry takes the first ball
for the Yellows.
- Quick ! Over there ! On each side !
- Big lead for the Blues.
Come left!
It's teamwork.
Go in this direction!
The Yellows have their first ball,
they can start.
- You! This way !
- Tai, Michele, Jason.
Lots of communication
to understand
how the balance is made,
how this labyrinth rocks.
Aubry, Cydney, Joe,
back in the running.
Jason, Tai, and Michele
are making progress.
They are at the center of the maze
now.
We have to take him there.
Jason directs perfectly.
It's one thing to move
to get the ball moving.
It must be controlled
so that it crosses the passages.
This way.
A little more, girls.
Nice work by the Blues.
They approach the center
with their ball.
This way !
Joe, Aubry and Cydney
make little progress.
You have to come here,
she has to lean on this side.
You don't listen.
Now you have to put it
in a hole.
The Blues place one!
Go get the second one!
They lead 1 - 0.
Jason detaches the second ball
for the Blues.
Joe, Aubry and Cydney
are still at the same point.
Jason has the 2nd ball,
he's back.
Cydney, Aubry and Joe
are making progress now.
Jason, Michele and Tai
took the hit.
They collaborate very well.
Huge in-game reward.
Come on !
Separate!
Jason, very confident,
fully in control.
Michele, Jason and Tai are nearby
to bring this 2nd ball to the center.
They go, will it work?
Yes, they are in the center and that's it!
Two for the Blues!
Jason will look for the 3rd
and last ball for the Blues.
Come to me, come to me!
finally brought
their first ball to the center.
You have to put it in a hole.
So ! Go, Aubry!
On the way to the second ball
for the Yellows.
Michele, Jason and Tai
are on the 3rd and final ball
while Aubry releases the 2nd.
Go left!
Left, left!
The Yellows are on their 2nd ball.
They will have to act fast
and rely on luck,
because Tai, Michele and Jason
understood this ordeal.
They approach the center,
Jason tries to get her in.
- Come on, jump!
- Can he reach the 3rd hole?
She's in!
Tai, Michele and Jason
win the reward!
We needed it.
A visit to The wildlife alliance
and an afternoon picnic.
It'll be nice !
Stupid ball!
Good. Michele, Tai, Jason,
great job.
Return to shore,
take your things,
have a good afternoon.
Joe, Aubry, Cydney,
I got nothing for you.
Get back to shore, get your things,
go back to camp.
It's very exciting
to have this award,
and I love animals
but I'm worried, I'm too scared
that in my absence,
the team collapses on the camp.
Valiant effort, ladies.
We tried.
Now, let's see if we can...
If there's anything left.
Oh, I see a little smoke.
Do you see an ember?
No, but I hope there is.
We lost the event,
Aubry, me and Cydney.
When you've finished the mangoes,
take your time,
but we need wood,
because it's ok...
Do you want us to take care
of the food or the wood?
Let's start with the wood,
make a nice fire,
then we can go and leave him.
My performance
was worthy of an infant.
I'm ashamed, but hey, what can I do?
Cyd, go get
more wood, honey!
A few more bites and I'll be there.
I'm laid down, I'm
trying to make "a meal",
namely to
swallow five pieces of coconut,
and apparently, it took too long,
I had to move
and bring wood.
I did...
No no no ! Are you having problems, are
you tired? I do not care.
Keep that for you.
I hate being told
what to do when I eat.
I won't take this
all day.
There's little chance.
I won't last.
I have trouble with orders.
It was demonstrated
throughout the game,
that's how it goes
with the Muscles tribe.
It should take a while.
I don't think I've received
so many orders in my entire life.
I don't know if Joe understands it,
but fire does not need
great flames to last.
We are in the middle of Kaôh Rông,
we don't need more heat!
It's starting to boil.
Tell me if I can help.
- There, put that under.
- I'm trying to help.
On this side of the fire.
This side ?
No no. Slide this under
while I lift.
- Slip what?
- Yes, right there, below!
Sorry, just to be sure.
Yes, there is nothing else.
Yeah, that's it.
It's been a long day
for all of us.
I don't know
what Joe's problem is.
He wants to burn everything here,
I don't know.
And it's hard too
'cause Cydney doesn't like
being bullied
and tell him what to do.
And above all, she must not
blow up everything,
because then we'd be screwed.
Oh my God !
It's a feast!
Look at this !
Jason, Tai and I
went to the shelter
and this beautiful picnic
was prepared.
It was paradise.
Too good.
I'm not supposed to
eat meat,
but I'm here and I'm too hungry.
Cheers ! Cheer !
- We made sure.
- To teamwork!
It's an elephant!
But he's coming this way!
Oh my God !
He is huge !
We were in this beautiful hut,
we were having a great time
and we see this elephant coming.
Oh my God !
Who is this ?
I am Nick.
- Hello !
- And she's Lucky.
Nick, director
of Wildlife Alliance,
brought this elephant, Lucky.
She is 16 years old
and she was wonderful.
How did you get it?
She was found alone,
in Kaoh Kong,
the forest in the southwest of the country,
wandering alone,
without his mother.
All our animals
have been saved from traffickers.
You want some ?
Is it me you want?
Lucky, you are so beautiful!
My daughter is crazy about animals.
She won't believe it.
My daughter, being autistic,
for some reason,
she has always loved animals.
It's visible, it brings him
calm and sweetness,
it stimulates her
and makes her feel
like she's needed.
It was cool to know
that I was doing something
that my little baby would love so much.
Thanks to you, I am fulfilled, Lucky!
She will hallucinate to see
that Dad hangs out with animals.
Who has a father who does this?
Come quickly.
Vites, vites!
Slowly and calmly.
Speak softly, be calm
and sit down, don't startle them.
Little monkey !
It was good that Jason was there.
He has an autistic daughter
and she'll see
him hanging out with that monkey,
touch an elephant...
A little affection, the monkey!
I appreciate it more and more.
I just want a little affection!
Although Jason
is very persuasive on the board,
Michele has no enemies
in the jury.
At the moment, I think Michele
should come out next.
Where did the little baby go?
- He is down there.
- He's right there.
Health !
Jason wants us to see
him softer than he is.
I want to believe he likes animals
and do this for his kid,
but with the story
of the machete and the ax,
I saw his evil side.
- Hey, don't be silly!
- Brawler!
So if Jason
doesn't win immunity,
the best case scenario for me
would be to release it now.
Over here, everyone!
Are we attacking
the immunity test of the day?
First of all, Michelle...
You're not going to help me at all!
I'm half way there.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will be holding a rope
balancing an unstable plateau.
At my signal, you will
fetch wooden blocks,
bring them back one by one
and stack them on top of each other,
forming the word "immunity".
If your board wobbles,
your stack falls,
you have to start over.
The first person to finish
gain immunity,
ensures a one in five chance
of winning this game.
The losers: after 32 days,
someone will be eliminated
and become the 6th member of the jury.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity
and a guaranteed place
in the final quintet,
Survivors, ready?
There will clearly be
a learning phase
in this test.
It's a question of balance,
patience
and, when necessary,
the right amount of speed.
You form the word "immunity",
but you have to do it
one block at a time
while keeping
the blocks balanced
on a very unstable plateau.
Joe comes to get his 2nd block.
Joe, 71 years old,
still in play,
takes the lead in this event.
There were 18 people
at the start of the game.
There are six left.
Five will still be there tomorrow.
Joe places his second block.
Joe plays aggressively.
Michele places her second block.
Tai places his second, he leaves.
Aubry places his second.
Jason places his second.
Cydney is dead last.
She moves like
she can't walk.
Joe places his third block.
Michele is second.
Third block for Tai.
Jason places his third.
Aubry places his third block.
Joe has his fourth block.
Even grabbing hold of the block is difficult,
because you always have to
maintain the balance.
Joe, back with his 4th block.
Joe is halfway through,
followed by Michele, then Tai.
Everyone else
is struggling to get back up.
Cydney is always dead last.
She returns with her third,
totally out of the way
at the moment.
This is Joe, with his fifth.
You have to be careful.
The higher the stack,
the more careful you have to be.
Tai nearly loses his stack.
Nice recovery.
Jason, who was on the bottom
rung, would love to have immunity tonight.
But you have to do it
one block at a time.
One mistake and the battery drops.
Joe loses everything!
After leading all the way.
Pick them up, bring them back
and do it again!
Michele is leading now.
Tai is on his heels.
Michele loses everything!
Tai leads!
See how quickly
everything can change!
Aubry loses everything!
It's contagious !
Tai leads now,
with Jason on his heels.
Cydney, still out of it.
And suddenly,
Tai loses everything!
Jason leads now.
Everything changed.
Cydney is now second.
Damn, that's the wrong letter!
It's an "I"!
Joe got the letter wrong!
Not only must they be
stacked in balance,
but we must also remember
how to write "immunity"!
Jason, who has a big lead
over Cydney,
returns with his sixth.
Jason loses everything!
And now Cydney is leading!
Incredible turnaround
!
Cydney was totally out of it
and she is now in the lead.
Say what you want
about Cydney's method,
but she didn't lose anything
from the whole ordeal.
Everyone is running after Cydney.
Last throughout the race,
she could now win it.
Taking care of your mount,
is that the answer?
- Shit !
- Joe is doing it again!
Cydney extends her lead.
Cydney is at five.
Aubry is on three.
Michele is at three.
Tai is at three.
Jason is two.
The good news is that Cydney
continues to evolve very slowly.
In other words,
it can be caught up.
Michele comes back
to place her fourth.
Aubry has her fifth block.
Jason places his third,
he tries to get back in the race.
He moves faster.
Tai has his fifth block.
He got back into the race.
Whore !
I keep getting it wrong.
Joe brings back the wrong letter!
It's fun, until
you get to the board.
Aubry returns with his sixth.
She could take the lead.
Michele has her fifth.
Michele loses everything!
Tai loses everything!
He's out of it.
Aubry loses everything!
The only one who rivaled Cydney
has just lost everything!
Cydney now places
her sixth block.
It's going to be played out between Jason and Cydney.
Can Jason accelerate enough
to come back up?
Jason returns with his sixth block.
Cydney is two blocks
from certainty,
tonight at the council.
Jason places his sixth block.
He's only missing two.
Cydney speed up a bit now,
she feels pressure from Jason.
Cydney places her seventh block.
He's only missing one.
Jason returns with his seventh
while Cydney leaves,
very slowly,
pick up his eighth.
Jason, on his heels,
places his seventh.
Jason almost caught up with Cydney.
Cydney is moving very slowly.
Jason, extremely aggressive.
It's neck and neck
between Cydney and Jason.
Cydney reaches for her 8th block,
she can't find it.
You can't take your
eyes off the board!
Jason has his eighth block.
Jason takes the lead.
New change
at the head of the race.
It's between Jason and Cydney,
who both return
with their 8th and final boulder.
Cydney tries to pick up the pace.
Jason places his eighth block.
He's going back.
Cydney places her eighth block.
She leaves.
It's gonna be racing
to get back to the start
without dropping everything.
It could all be there.
Jason always has a
few centimeters...
And Jason loses everything!
Cydney is
just a few steps away from immunity.
Cydney put one foot down.
And two!
Cydney wins
individual immunity!
She secures a place
in the final quintet.
Oh my God !
It was crazy !
Cydney, come here!
- Good game.
- Thanks.
You are safe,
you will not be eliminated.
A guaranteed place
in the final quintet.
Advice tonight.
Someone will be eliminated
and become the 6th member of the jury.
It won't be you.
Congratulation.
Take your things,
return to camp. Good job.
- My favorite event so far.
- Me too.
Yeah, that was good.
Just you against the block.
For tonight's advice,
I decided that Michele
was the most dangerous,
in front of Jason.
I will therefore try
to convince the group
to vote Michele.
Hold on. Joe, sit down.
Michele is not here yet.
Let's talk.
For me, it's Michele.
I would not prefer.
It's up to you.
But I'd rather take Jason out.
I say: Michele.
Here it is.
So, sirens?
Unfortunately,
Michele joined us,
the four of us,
and the group has not decided yet,
but it will probably be Michele.
We remain five welded.
Jason gave up.
- It's pretty obvious, isn't it?
- It's very obvious.
No need
to take the lead this time.
Michele thinks
Jason is next.
But tonight I'll use
my extra vote
to vote Michele.
So we might have,
I don't know,
four or five votes,
and we'll see what happens.
Please I think...
- ...that she's more dangerous.
- Oh, I'm with you.
I vote for Michele.
Are you voting for Michele?
Yeah.
I want you to vote Michele.
I push in this direction.
But we haven't decided.
But I will talk to them.
Tai's like, "Vote Michele!"
But I can't trust Tai.
He's already betrayed me once.
I want to vote for Joe.
So I don't know what I'm going to do.
At this point, I improvise.
How do you feel ?
I would like to take it out.
I'm sick of his face.
Me too, we agree.
But Tai has his own plans,
his reasons for voting Michele.
Jason should have been out
a long time ago,
so i hope i
can convince people
that Jason has to get out before Michele.
I will do what others want.
I'm not going to oppose
the majority, it's not worth it.
Tai wants to impose his choices.
And I say, "No.
You try to impose your choices
through intimidation."
Joe feels intimidated.
It makes me suspicious.
I don't like it too much.
Tai is thoroughly anti-Michele.
He's pushing
for us all to be anti-you.
So Aubry is coming after me
now?
It's Tai.
He tries to push us
in this direction.
To my surprise,
Tai has me in the crosshairs
and explains to them
that he wants me out.
I will do my best
to make them let go of you,
I'll do everything I can,
but know that I've got you covered
as much as I can.
But I was tight, time wise,
to talk to people
I haven't talked to.
So tonight, at the council,
I'll try to limit the damage,
hoping Jason leaves
and that I'm still here tomorrow.
Ce foutu Tai !
I have a concern.
my concern,
it's that once again,
someone is imposing their choices on us.
And Tai pushes hard.
Absolutely not.
I have already experienced this.
You won't decide who I vote for.
Tai has more or less decided
that we will take out Michele.
And actually, I agree.
Michele didn't upset anyone,
everyone
gets on well with her.
But I have known
more democratic decisions.
And Cydney thinks it's a mistake
and she refuses
to be told what to do.
For me, personally,
we are not going to control my game.
But Tai
is in my core alliance.
So it's a tricky position.
I'm in a funny situation.
- I hope you'll respect that...
- Yes.
...That I have another opinion
on that one.
If you had to choose
between voting with me
or voting with them?
I am mentally exhausted.
This time around, it's rough.
It's like Sophie's Choice.
I have no idea
who I'm going to vote for tonight.
I will decide at the time.
The council is likely to be hectic
and it could well
be my doing too.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Julia,
eliminated at the last council.
Let's talk about today's test.
I don't remember seeing
so many changes at the front of the race
in the same ordeal, never.
Jason, is this a good summary of the game?
It's all over the place
and anything can happen.
In effect.
It's unpredictable. Every time
you think it's good,
it escapes you.
Everyone here almost won,
but the blocks remained
in place only for her.
With that around your neck,
in addition to security,
immunity can give you
a little more influence.
Did you feel it today?
For me, everyone played their game.
But some were
more sure of themselves than others,
seeking to impose their choices
or to decide for you.
I can clarify who it is.
We all know it's Tai.
Tai said over and over
that he has two idols
or that he has the super-idol.
The other is an advantage.
Whether he's an idol or not,
I don't know.
It's up to me to decide whether
to show it to you or not.
Whether you believe me or not
is up to you.
Coming back to the discussion,
I think our alliance came together
and that everyone could speak,
everyone expressed their opinion.
Cydney, why this reaction?
It's Tai's choice or nothing
at this point.
I had that feeling
today.
We expressed different ideas,
but it fell
on deaf ears.
I wanted to have
a moment with Cydney, alone.
To talk.
We didn't have time.
Aubry, what a face you made!
I thought he could talk
and have a good chat with Cydney.
So you wonder
why he wanted more time?
Yeah, I guess, a little.
I thought everything was clear
for the group.
It's telling enough,
when we are allies
and that we all decided
who we would vote for,
whether you need
private conversations.
It doesn't make sense to me.
But OK.
Well, Jeff.
There is a large group
and a smaller group in it.
Tai means
there is a starting order
and I'm down.
So I can't be included,
because there's a smaller group
and he thinks he can
impose everything
because he has "two idols".
Even if we don't have the same idea
of ​​what should happen tonight...
I thought we had the same idea!
We were
on the same wavelength.
I think
our opinions differ, but...
And there is a consensus
on who should leave tonight.
But Tai goes beyond
different opinions.
You said there is a group
and a smaller group.
Are you aware
of how Michele may be feeling,
not being
high enough in the hierarchy
for that level?
Yes. In his place, that's exactly
how I would see him.
So, Michele, you know
where you fit in this group.
I know where Tai thinks
I fit in this group,
and if that's what my other allies think ,
so it's a pity,
because Tai betrayed
all the allies he had
and I proved my loyalty,
again and again.
Madness is doing
the same thing over and over again
hoping for a different result.
If they want to be crazy,
let them follow Tai!
And they will be had.
At the last vote, I did not betray.
- A vote where you did not betray!
- And nobody...
And then you try
to generate more chaos!
Honestly, I don't know how
you failed in this alliance.
You weren't there originally.
and I don't know how,
after the vote...
I was in this alliance
before you!
We formed
a brand new alliance,
and I said, "Why do we have
one more person?"
Wow ! You're downstairs, and besides,
we don't really want you.
Well...
It's a piece of crap,
but hey, whatever.
Aubrey. There 's a
lot going on.
Do you feel like you're
in chaos?
Yeah. Looks like Cydney
and Michele are suspicious of Tai.
It was discussed a lot,
and if it goes into a spin,
that I can't control
what Tai says,
Tai can assume his words.
My playing style is different
from Tai's.
Hello, Jeff!
Jason, you seem to
be on the low end, aloof,
for a while, and yet,
the discussion does not revolve
around you.
Yes, that's why
I keep quiet.
When you hear Michele and Tai
settle their accounts,
does that excite you?
Of course that excites me.
We get here and these cracks
in the concrete appear.
So this may not be
my last trip here.
Or else I'm leaving anyway tonight,
and then I know who will follow me.
Well, it's time to vote.
Jason, over to you.
You have to go first.
I will count the votes.
Wait, Jeff.
I want to use my advantage.
Tell us what it is.
My advantage,
I can add another vote
to any advice.
Tai's advantage
is an extra vote.
It counts
like any other vote.
Tai, go vote a second time.
It's number 2.
You must go.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote:
Michele.
Jason.
Tied: two votes Michele,
two votes Jason.
A vote Joe.
Jason.
That's three votes Jason,
two votes Michele,
a joe vote,
one vote remains.
Eleventh person eliminated
and sixth member of the jury...
Jason.
Bring me your torch.
Jason, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
It seems that by eliminating Jason,
you have eliminated
the only person still isolated.
Which leaves you five
and not enough room
for everyone on the raft.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Translation: Jack Bauer
Relecture: lshomie, Lény
Synchro: Lény
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Like I was the easy vote.
Tai's plan to take Michele out
backfires.
Aubry tricked me.
But an unlikely alliance
could change everything.
I have an idol.
Who do we choose?
If he feels betrayed, he could
take a completely different direction.
Who knew
Tai and I would collaborate?
I've been watching Survivor for 15 years.
I love the show
as much as the first day.
I didn't give up, didn't give up,
even kept away,
alone against all,
I was still trying
to go back and fight.
I'm proud of how I played,
proud of my game,
and I think my family
will be too.
I love you girls.