>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... SINCE DAY ONE THE
GAME HAS BEEN A FIGHT AND
NOTHING HAS COME EASY.
>> I'M NOT GETTING DIRTY AT ALL.
>> Jeff: IDOLS WERE FOUND BY
TAI AND JASON.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: ALLIANCES WERE MADE.
>> WE'RE PRETTY TIGHT.
>> Jeff: AND BROKEN.
>> I'M JUST SHOCKED.
>> HE'S A TOTAL NARCISSIST,
STILL ON THE PERIPHERY.
>> Jeff: BUT NOTHING COMPARED
TO THE BATTLE WITH MOTHER
NATURE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE AN
EVACUATION.
AND CALEB WAS HER FIRST VICTIM.
>> NOW IT'S ONLY NICK AND I.
NOW THE GIRLS HAVE THE CHOICE
WHO TO KICK OUT.
>> Jeff: AT THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, THE BRAWN TRIBE LOST
FOR THE THIRD TIME.
SENDING BRAWN BACK THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AND AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, SCOT,
JASON AND CYDNEY DIDN'T LET
ALECIA ESCAPE ANOTHER VOTE.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
13 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> HOW'S YOUR FINGER?
>> I'VE BEEN SOAKING IT IN SALT
WATER.
I'M HEATING UP ANOTHER BATCH.
I TRIED TO LANCE IT.
IT KIND OF HEALED UP IN THE
SUMMER.
SINCE THE LAST VOTE WHERE I FEEL
IN THIS PACK IS AT THE BOTTOM.
I FEEL LIKE A NEUTERED DOG RIGHT
NOW BECAUSE I HAVE NO PLAY.
>> DR. PETER TO THE E.R.
DR. PETER TO THE E.R.
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE HIM, LOOKING
LIKE THIS?
IT'S STRATEGICALLY CRUCIAL THAT
I START PANDERING TO THESE
PEOPLE.
SO I GO INTO DOCTOR MODE.
>> A LITTLE REDNESS RIGHT THERE,
BUT THAT'S IT.
>> YOU CAN'T BEND IT BECAUSE
IT'S SO SWOLLEN, THAT'S BAD.
YOU'RE NOT THERE.
RIGHT NOW IT'S DR. PETER'S
CLINIC, BUT IT'S AN ATTEMPT TO
MAKE THEM FEEL AS IF THEY NEED
ME.
>> HE'S SO GENTLE.
>> RETURN TO THE TRAUMA CENTER
HERE.
>> THANK GOD WE HAVE YOU, PETER.
>> IF THEY SEE ME AS SOMEONE WHO
IS FUNCTIONAL AND USEFUL, I'M
GOING TO EXPLOIT THAT AND TRY TO
GET MYSELF OUT OF THIS MESS I
GOT MYSELF IN.
>> DOCTOR, WHAT'S THE PROGNOSIS?
WILL THE PATIENT LIVE?
>> YES, THE PATIENT WILL LIVE.
>> $475, PLEASE.
>> WE HAVE A TRIBE OF FIVE.
IF FOUR PEOPLE ARE ALIGNED AND
ONE CANCER NAMED
I BRUSHED SOME LEAVES AND
THERE'S A BOX BURIED IN THE
EARTH.
BUT THE BOX HAS A PADLOCK ON IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU FIND THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
FIRST YOU WILL NEED A KEY TO
OPEN THE BOX.
FOLLOW THE MAP TO THE TREE AND
LOOK UP.
THIS WILL HELP PUSH THE KEY OUT
OF THE CANISTER.
I KNOW I'M GOING TO GET IT.
I'M CONFIDENT I'VE GOTTEN HERE.
I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
I'M GOING TO GO FIND THAT.
BUT WILL I GET CAUGHT IN THAT
PROCESS?
SO I HAVE TO MOVE VERY, VERY
FAST.
I SCAMPER ACROSS THE ISLAND
LOOKING UP AT EVERY COCONUT
TREE, AND SURE ENOUGH, RIGHT
BEHIND ONE, IS A CYLINDER WITH A
LITTLE HOLE RIGHT AT THE BOTTOM
TO PUSH THAT TOOL THROUGH.
THE KEY TO THE IDOL.
THE IDOL.
THE KING HAS HIS IDOL.
THERE'S A TWIST TO THE IDOL.
IF YOU PAIR ONE IMMUNITY IDOL
WITH ANOTHER IMMUNITY IDOL, THEY
FIT TOGETHER TO FORM ONE SUPER
IDOL.
THE SUPER IDOL CAN BE PLAYED
AFTER THE VOTES HAVE BEEN READ.
THE LAST RULE IS A TWIST IN THE
GAME THAT IF YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE
TWO IDOLS, THEY CAN BE COMBINED
INTO ONE SUPER IDOL.
SO NOW THE GOAL IS TO FIND
ANOTHER IDOL.
OR SOMEBODY THAT HAS AN IDOL.
ONE OF MY PHILOSOPHIES IN LIFE
IS YOU MAKE YOUR OWN LUCK.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'M DOING.
IF SOMEBODY IS BETTING IN VEGAS,
I'M THE FRONT-RUNNER.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
BRAIN TRIBE, BEAUTY TRIBE
GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE
NEW BRAWN TRIBE.
ALECIA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU ARE ALSO GETTING YOUR LAST
LOOK AT THE BRAWN TRIBE.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> OH, NO.
>> Jeff: WE'RE SWITCHING
THINGS UP.
>> WOW.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING THINGS UP.
>> OH.
>> WOW.
>> MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ORIGINALLY WE WERE
PLANNING ON SPLITTING THE TRIBES
TODAY WITH 14 PEOPLE INTO TWO
TRIBES OF SEVEN.
CALEB'S UNFORTUNATE EVACUATION
CHANGED THE NUMBERS AND LEFT US
WITH AN UNEVEN NUMBER AT 13.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: SO HERE'S WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN: THERE ARE 13
BUFFS.
THERE ARE SIX BLUE, SIX YELLOW,
ONE RED.
WHOEVER DRAWS THE RED BUFF WILL
GO BACK TO BRAWN BEACH ALONE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: WHERE YOU WILL HAVE
TO FEND FOR YOURSELF, FOOD,
FIRE, WATER, THE WORKS.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WHILE YOU'RE ON
BRAWN BEACH, YOU WILL NOT
PARTICIPATE IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, THEREFORE YOU WON'T
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU CAN'T BE VOTED OUT.
THE BAD NEWS: WHILE YOU ARE ON
BRAWN BEACH, YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO STRATEGIZE AND MAKE NEW
ALLIANCES.
YOU WILL HAVE TO RELY ON YOUR
CURRENT ALLIANCES TO KEEP YOU
TIGHT UNTIL YOU CAN GET BACK IN
THE GAME.
YOU WILL RETURN, JOINING THE
TRIBE THAT LOSES THE PERSON AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SHALL WE DRAW?
>> YES.
>> YES, SIR.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: TAKE ONE.
PLEASE DON'T OPEN IT YET.
>> WHICH ONE DO YOU RECOMMEND,
JEFF?
>> Jeff: FOLLOW YOUR GUT.
>> OH, MY GOD, THIS IS SO NERVE
RACKING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S END THE SUSPENSE.
EVERYBODY OPEN YOUR NEW BUFFS.
>> YELLOW.
>> I'M BLUE.
>> BLUE.
>> YELLOW.
>> MY GOD.
>> Jeff: JULIA.
>> I HAD LIKE A GUT FEELING.
>> Jeff: IF YOU HAVE BLUE,
MOVE OVER TO THE BLUE MATT.
IF YOU HAVE YELLOW, MOVE OVER TO
THE YELLOW MAT.
AND IF YOU HAVE RED, JULIA, FIND
YOUR SPOT ALONE.
>> HI.
I'M MICHELE.
>> DEBBIE.
>> SCOT.
MICHELE, NICE TO MEET YOU.
PETER, NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> Jeff: REALLY INTERESTING
REDIVISION OF TRIBES.
THE BLUE TRIBE, YOUR NEW NAME IS
CHAN LOH.
WE HAVE TWO BRAINS, TWO BEAUTY,
TWO BRAWN.
CAN'T GET ANY MORE EVEN THAN
THAT.
NEAL, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THIS
TRIBE?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE SOME
STRENGTH.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE SOME
SMARTS AND IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
SOME BEAUTY, SO I'LL TAKE IT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT MYSELF MOSTLY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YELLOW
TRIBE, YOUR NEW NAME IS GONDOL.
WE HAVE THREE BRAINS, TWO
BEAUTY, ONE BRAWN.
ANOTHER PRETTY EVEN
DISTRIBUTION.
JULIA.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: HERE YOU ARE ON
EITHER SIDE.
THE NEW TRIBES ARE EXCITED,
READY TO GO BACK THE CAMP TO SEE
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE ALONE.
>> I'M ALONE.
>> Jeff: YOU WILL HAVE TO
SURVIVE ON YOUR OWN.
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO BE OKAY.
I'M GOING TO LOOK AT IT IN A
POSITIVE WAY.
I WOULD SAY THE ONE DOWN SIDE IS
NOT BEING ABLE TO GET TO KNOW
EVERYONE.
I'M GOING TO COME IN KIND OF THE
ODD ONE OUT, ESPECIALLY IF
BEAUTY GETS VOTED OFF AT THIS
NEXT IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JULIA.
HEAD OUT AND GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, CHAN LOH,
GONDOL, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO YOUR NEW CAMP.
THE GAME HAS JUST CHANGED.
>> WHAT THE HECK.
THE GIRL'S ALLIANCE GOT CLEAN
DIVIDED.
TO HAVE THE PEOPLE YOU TRUST
MOST OUT HERE GO THREE DIFFERENT
WAYS, IT'S CRUSHING.
>> WELCOME, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> WE HAVE FRUIT.
WE HAVE ONE CHICKEN LEFT OUT OF
THREE.
>> WHAT?
>> WE HAVE MANGOES.
>> WE HAVE A MANGO TREE.
WE DISCOVER MANGDO TREE.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE DONE WELL FOR
YOURSELF.
>> THIS SWAP IS EXACTLY WHAT I
NEEDED BECAUSE IF THAT DIDN'T
HAPPEN, I WAS DEAD.
MY ALLIANCE MEMBER WAS VOTED OUT
BEFORE ME AND I WAS THE NEXT
LOWEST-HANGING FRUIT.
NOW IT'S IN OUR BEST INTEREST TO
GO FORWARD TOGETHER.
>> I'M PETER AGAIN.
>> ANNA.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> PETER, HI.
>> ON THIS TRIBE THERE ARE THREE
BRAINS, TWO BEAUTY, ONE BRAWN.
WE'RE THE MAJORITY.
I'M SET UP RIGHT NOW TO EASILY
MAKE IT INTO THE MERGE WITHOUT
EVEN HAVING ANY CONCERN OR EVEN
A BEAD OF SWEAT DOWN MY EYEBROW.
>> SEE THAT TREE, THAT'S A
MANNINGO.
I CAN CLIMB THAT TREE.
I NEED A BOOST UP, A BOOST UP.
>> SOME OF THOSE I CAN REACH
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD FOR SOMETHING.
I'M THE SOLE BROWN, AND I'M
THINKING, ALL RIGHT, I'M ON THE
BOTTOM OF THE TOTEM POLE.
>> HE CAN RUN AROUND AND EAT
WHATEVER HE WANTS.
>> IT'S FAMILIAR FEELING FOR ME.
I PLAYED FOR FIVE DIFFERENT
TEAMS IN THE NBA, AND EACH TIME
YOU'RE JOINING A GROUP OF PEOPLE
YOU USED TO PLAY AGAINST AND YOU
USED TO FIGHT AGAINST.
>> THIS IS A PALM.
>> I CAN HANDLE IT.
I JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT IF I
CAN TRUST ANYBODY, WHO IT IS,
AND IF IT'S GOING TO DO ME ANY
GOOD.
>> WINNER, WINNER, CHICKEN
DINNER.
>> WE WILL HAVE A CHICKEN
DINNER, TOO.
>> CRAZY.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> I SAY WE LOSE THE CHALLENGE,
WHOEVER WE ELIMINATE WE'LL BE
REPLACED BY BEAUTY.
THE LOGICAL THING IS TO TAKE OUT
A BEAUTY.
>> I MIGHT HAVE THREE BRAINS IN
NUMBER, BUT WITH PETER, THAT
MIGHT ONLY BE TWO.
I DON'T TRUST PETER AS FAR AS I
CAN THROW HIM.
LOGICALLY IN NUMBERS, DOES IT
MAKE SENSE TO GO WITH PETER,
YEAH, IT DOES, ESPECIALLY IF
THERE'S POTENTIAL A BEAUTY COULD
COME BACK TO THIS TRIBE.
>> PUT YOUR HEAD ON THE PILLOW.
>> IF JULIA COMES BACK FROM THE
BRAWN TRIBE, SHE'S GOING TO BE
ANOTHER BEAUTY AND WE'LL LOSE
THE NUMBERS.
IT WILL BE 3-3.
>> WHAT DO WE DO IF WE LOSE A
CHALLENGE?
IT'S A BEAUTY.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT MANY BEAUTIES
AROUND.
>> I'D RATHER DO THAT BECAUSE
ANYTHING COULD HAPPEN.
ONE THING IS GOING TO HAPPEN,
ALL OF A SUDDEN, WHAT?
I'M ABSOLUTELY ALONE.
BUT BRAIN TRIBE SEEMINGLY HAS
ALREADY MADE THE DECISION.
EVERYBODY IS ON BOARD TO TAKE
OUT A BEAUTY.
>> COMFORTABLE?
>> BUT PEOPLE SAY ONE THING, AND
THEN THEY TURN AROUND FIVE
MINUTES LATER AND SAY SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> HOW IT IS?
COMFORTABLE?
WE CAN ACTUALLY ALL FIT.
>> WHO KNOWS?
IT MIGHT SWITCH ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> WELCOME TO OUR VERY HUMBLE
ABODE.
IT'S NICE TO HAVE YOU ALL.
I.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY
EXPECTED THE SWITCH TODAY.
I WAS STUNNED.
ON BEAUTY THE GIRLS' ALLIANCE IS
REALLY, REALLY TIGHT.
WE'RE ALL I CAN VOIDED NOW, US
TREE GIRLS, AND IT'S
NERVE-RACKING.
>> LET ME FIND OUT.
>> YES.
>> HOW'S IT GOING?
>> THE ONLY THING IS TO GO DOWN
ALL THE WAY, DEBBIE.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK,
HONESTLY?
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME, KIDS.
IT'S YOUR HOME.
>> ON MY TRIBE I FIND MYSELF
WITH TWO BEAUTY, TWO BRAIN, TWO
BRAWN.
>> WE'RE ALL BLEEDING BLUE RIGHT
NOW.
>> SO THERE'S A LOT TO THINK
ABOUT.
IT'S GOING TO BE A ROUGH
ADJUSTMENT, BUT YOU HAVE TO KEEP
YOUR HEAD UP AND READ PEOPLE
UNTIL IT COMES TIME WHERE I'VE
GOT TO MAKE AN ALLIANCE.
>> NEAL AND I ARE PROPOSING ONCE
WE GET SOME FOOD IN US, GO
SCROUNGING AND WE GET PROBABLY
THE LAST CUP OF COFFEE AND WE
WATCH THE SUNSET GO DOWN
TOGETHER.
THE NEW CHAN LOH TRIBE IS A GOOD
TRIBE.
IT WAS A WARM WELCOME TO OUR
HUMBLE ABODE, BUT IMMEDIATELY
I'M JUST LOOKING FOR AN OPENING
BECAUSE MY GAME PLAY IS I'M ON
THE OFFENSE, NOT THE DEFENSE.
AND FROM THE GET-GO, I WANTED TO
WORK WITH BRAWN BECAUSE THE
BRAWN TRIBE DEFINITELY IS THE
POWER HOUSE.
>> AND I THOUGHT I WORK OUT HARD
AND TRAIN HARD THAT.
GIRL MAKES ME LOOK LIKE CHICKEN
LITTLE.
I WAS REALLY RIPPED TWO WEEKS
AGO.
>> UH-HUH.
>> SO WE'RE ON A WALK LOOKING
FOR COCONUTS AND DEBBIE HAS A
VERY MOTHERLY VIBE AND IT
DEFINITELY COULD BE GOOD FOR ME
TO HAVE LIKE A MOTHERLY FIGURE
AROUND, TOO.
SO I THINK IT COULD BE A GOOD
DUO.
>> I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE
REALLY THE TRIPLE THREAT, JUST
THE WAY I COULD HEAR YOU
BRIEFLY, I SAID, AND SHE'S
REALLY SMART.
YOU HAVE TO BE SMART.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE DISCIPLINE TO
BE BUILT LIKE YOU ARE.
>> I'VE BEEN PLAYING THE DUMB
JOCK ROLE, BUT I HAVEN'T TOLD
ANYBODY THAT I WENT TO ONE OF
THE TOP SCHOOLS IN THE NATION.
YOU WOULDN'T WITH LIKE, SHE'S SO
SMART.
NO.
THAT'S JUST NOT WHAT I GIVE OFF.
BUT I DID GO TO AN IVY LEAGUE
SCHOOL.
IT TOOK A LOT TO GET THERE,
ESPECIALLY GROWING UP IN THE
ATLANTA PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM.
>> YOU ANDRY CLOSE.
>> OKAY.
>> WE DON'T APPEAR CLOSE AND WE
ABSOLUTELY KNOW HOW TO ZIP IT.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S THE KEY THING.
>> KEEP IN MIND, EVENTUALLY I
WANT TO SEE A WOMAN WIN THIS.
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
I'M WITH YOU ON THAT ONE.
>> I SPOKE WITH CYDNEY ABOUT MY
PLAN OF THE TWO BRAWNS HOOKING
UP WITH THE TWO BRAINS.
NOW I NEED TO SPEAK TO JASON AND
MAKE IT A FOURSOME.
>> YOU TALKED TO CYDNEY?
>> YES.
>> FIRST TIME I SAW HER, I JUST
LIKED HER, THE ATHLETICISM AND
SO WE KIND OF WANTED TO TAKE OUT
A BEAUTY IF IT CAME TO IT.
AND LET THEM KNOW WHAT IT'S
LIKE.
I ALL RIGHT WENT TO CYDNEY.
I ALREADY WENT TO JASON.
WE HAVE A FOURSOME.
DING, KA-CHING, KA-CHING.
WE GOT A CYANIDE TRIPLE BOND
CARBON NITROGEN.
YOU'RE NOT BREAKING IT BETWEEN
US BECAUSE IN THIS GAME YOU HAVE
TO HAVE FLEXIBILITY, AND YOU
HAVE TO HAVE STRENGTH.
ONCE AGAIN I'M THE MASTERMIND
BEHIND THE SCENE, AND THEY JUST
DON'T SEE ME COMING.
>> YEAH, THE OUTSIDE OF IT, IT'S
A THICK MEAT COCONUT.
I'LL OPEN IT.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
WITH CALEB BEING GONE, I THINK
ABOUT A DEAR FRIEND, BUT THE
SWITCH HAPPENED AND WE COME
TOGETHER AS A NEW TRIBE, SO
THERE'S A LOT OF OPPORTUNITY TO
MAKE NEW FRIENDS.
>> YOU'RE VERY GRACIOUS WITH
YOUR FOOD.
THANK YOU.
>> WE'RE GOING TO REPAY YOU BY
WINNING.
>> TAI IS GREAT.
IT'S ALWAYS GREAT TO HAVE A GUY
IN YOUR TRIBE THAT KEEPS THINGS
JOVIAL.
HE KNOWS HOW TO DO EVERYTHING.
THAT'S COOL.
I LIKE PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
>> SCOT, WANT TO GO PICK MANGO?
I NEED A BOOST.
SCOT IS GIGANTIC.
HE'S 6'11".
HE'S SO TALL.
370 POUNDS.
I THINK ALMOST THREE OF ME TO
MAKE ONE OF HIM, AND HE WEARS
SIZE 18 SHOES.
THAT'S AMAZING.
I NEED A BOOST.
I'VE DIDN'T DYING TO DO THIS.
>> GOOD?
>> TAI IS LIGHT AS A FEATHER.
I TOSSED HIM UP THE TREE AND
THAT LITTLE DUDE JUST RAN AROUND
THAT TREE PICKING MANGOES LIKE
CRAZY.
>> THIS IS FUN FOR ME.
I DON'T FEEL SCARED OR ANYTHING.
>> I HAVE MAN CRUSH ON TAI
ALREADY.
IN MY OPINION, HE'S NUMBER ONE
MOST VALUABLE MEMBER OF THE
TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
>> ONE MORE BRANCH.
STRAIGHT AHEAD.
RIGHT THERE.
>> IT'S AN EASY PICK.
>> OH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>> IT'S EXCITING TO DO SOMETHING
NEW.
>> IT IS.
IT'S FUN NOW BECAUSE HONESTLY IT
WAS NICE TO BOND, BUT IT WAS
LIKE, OKAY, WHEN ARE WE GOING TO
PLAY?
I'M IN THE WORST SPOT EVER WITH
THIS EXTRA DYNAMIC OF JULIA
COMING BACK INTO THE MIX,
THERE'S NO WAY THAT BRAINS ARE
GOING TO KEEP BOTH BEAUTY, SO
IT'S EITHER TAI OR I.
>> TAI, HE'S THE ONE THAT WAS
RUNNING AROUND WITH THE IDO.
TWICE WE CAUGHT HIM.
WE'RE LIKE, THIS GUY NEEDS TO
GO.
>> I'M A PROFESSIONAL POKER
PLAYER.
I PLAY A STRATEGY GAME FOR A
LIVING.
I KNOW HOW TO ADJUST.
I KNOW HOW TO HUSTLE.
I SAW HIM PATTING THE GROUND
WHERE THE TREES ARE.
I SAW HIM FIND THE ID.L. AND DIG
IT UP.
>> I'M NOT AFRAID TO THROW TAI
UNDER THE BUS TO PROTECT MYSELF
AND GET AS FAR AS I CAN IN THE
GAME.
>> I CAUGHT TAI TWICE LOOKING
FOR THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
AN I THOUGHT, CAN WE STICK
TOGETHER?
IT'S AN UPHILL BATTLE, BUT I'M
NOT GOING TO GO OUT WITHOUT A
FIGHT.
>> WHAT DAY DO YOU GUY THINK IT
IS, 13?
>> THE TRIBE SWAP IS A REBIRTH
FOR ME.
THIS MIX OF BEAUTY, BRAIN AND
BRAWN, IT KIND OF MAKES THINGS
MORE SIMPLE.
IT'S TWO, TWO AND TWO.
SO IT'S GOING TO BE THE BATTLE
OF THE PAIRS.
I'M WITH MICHELE RIGHT NOW, AND
I'M TRYING TO MAKE SOME BONDS TO
GET TWO MORE WITH US.
>> I LIKE EVERYBODY HERE, OR AT
LEAST... I MEAN, FIRST
IMPRESSION, RIGHT.
CYDNEY SEEMS COOL AS HELL.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> PRETTY MUCH RIGHT WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, MICHELE SEEMS REALLY
NICE.
I LIKE YOU.
>> YEAH, SAME.
>> YOU SEEM LIKE A SOLID PERSON.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO BEING
MANIPULATIVE, I THINK I'M THE
MOST INTELLIGENT PERSON OUT
HERE, SO COMING INTO THIS TRIBE,
I GET TO START FRESH AND COME UP
WITH NEW LIES OR NEW STORIES,
AND I'M HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> I CAN PROBABLY GET MICHELE TO
BE ON BOARD.
IF YOU'RE ON BOARD WITH ME,
YOU'D BE GOOD WITH CYDNEY.
SHE'LL BE GOOD.
>> RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT NOW.
>> AND MICHELE WILL BE FOUR.
WE MAKE UP OUR OWN NEW BRAWN
TRIBE PRETTY MUCH.
>> RIGHT.
I AGREE WITH THAT.
>> COMING TO THE NEW CHAN LOH
TRIBE, I WAS PUT IN A GOOD SPOT.
BEAUTY ARE GOING TO STICK
TOGETHER.
THE BRAINS ARE GOING TO STICK
TOGETHER, AND THEY'RE BOTH
REACHING FOR CYDNEY AND I.
BOTH SIDES LOOK AT US AS THAT
TIEBREAKER.
SO IT'S A GREAT SPOT TO BE IN.
BEAUTY ON THE RIGHT, BRAINS ON
THE LEFT.
WHO DO YOU SIDE WITH?
WE KIND OF HOLD ALL THE POWER.
SO I'M FEELING REALLY GOOD.
AND I LIKE FELT MY BODY SHUTTING
DOWN.
I HAD NEVER FELT LIKE THAT
BEFORE.
IT WAS A COMBINATION OF
DEHYDRATION, BEING OUT HERE
ALONE AND PARANOIA.
AT THIS POINT THERE IS NO CHANCE
OF ME RECONNECTING WITH MY
ENTIRE ALLIANCE, SO IT'S GOING
TO BE HARD.
I WOULD SAY THAT RIGHT NOW BEING
OUT HERE ALONE IS THE HARDEST
PART OF MY GAME SO FAR.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THAT I'M
ACTUALLY A TEEN, AND I THINK
IT'S EASIER FOR STRONGER PEOPLE,
BIGGER PEOPLE THAN ME, PEOPLE
WITH MORE LIFE EXPERIENCE THAN
ME TO HELP GET YOU THROUGH THIS.
ALL DAY ALL I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT IS WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE
GOING ON BACK AT CAMP.
THE LONGER I'M OUT HERE, THE
MORE PARANOID I'M GOING TO GET.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
OLD HABIT.
>> I KNOW.
DIE HARD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AS NEW
TRIBES?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, I'LL TAKE
BACK THE IDOLS.
THANK YOU, MICHELE.
THANK YOU, JOE.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, TWO
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE SWIM OUT
AND RETRIEVE A NET OF FISH
PUZZLE PIECES.
ONCE YOU GET IT BACK TO SHORE,
TWO OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS WILL
UNTIE THOSE FISH, HOOK THEM ON
TO A POLE.
YOU'LL CARRY THAT UP TO THE
PUZZLE PLATFORM, WHERE THE
REMAINING TWO TRIBE MEMBERS WILL
USE THOSE PIECES TO COMPLETE A
FISH PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT RIGHT WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL OR
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE
AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS NICK AND JASON AND SCOT
AND AUBRY HEADING OUT INTO THE
WATER.
YOU CAN'T DIVE DOWN UNTIL BOTH
OF YOU ARE AT THE BUOY, SO YOU
ARE ONLY AS FAST AS YOUR SLOWEST
SWIMMER.
>> GO, NICK.
LET'S GO, JASON.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: JASON AND NICK ARE
THERE FIRST.
THEY BOTH DIVE DOWN.
THERE'S AUBRY.
SCOT GOES DOWN NOW.
SCOT HAS THE FIRST SET OF KNOTS
UNDONE.
HE'S GOING TO DO IT ALL HIMSELF
SCOT WORKING ON THAT SECOND SET.
NICK STILL WORKING ON THE FIRST.
SCOT HAS THE SECOND SET.
JASON HAS THE SECOND SET.
NOW IT'S GOING TO BE A RACE BACK
TO THE BEACH.
>> LET'S GO, SCOT!
>> Jeff: THERE ARE 14 PUZZLE
PIECES THAT WEIGH ABOUT 100
POUNDS, SO WITH THAT AND THE
WATER, IT'S A LOT OF RESISTANCE.
>> ALL RIGHT, GONDOL.
>> Jeff: SCOT HAS BEEN A
WORKHORSE IN THIS CHALLENGE FOR
HIS TRIBE, BASICALLY DOING THIS
FIRST STAGE ALL BY HIMSELF.
AND HE'S NOW GOT A PRETTY DECENT
LEAD OVER JASON AND NICK.
>> NICK AND JASON GET CLOSER,
LESS RESISTANCE.
>> CLOSER TOGETHER, GUYS.
>> Jeff: THERE'S A LOT OF DRAG
ON THAT WATER.
THESE PIECES WEIGH A LOT.
>> PUSH IT, PUSH IT.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN SEE HOW MUCH
EFFORT IT TAKES TO DRAG THESE
UP.
ONCE YOU GET TO THE MAT, YOU CAN
START UNTYING THEM.
GO, GONDOL.
IT'S NOW JOE AND TAI WORKING TO
UNTIE THESE.
HERE COMES JASON AND NICK.
>> COME ON, NICK!
>> Jeff: GO, CHAN LOH.
NOW MICHELE AND CYDNEY JOIN SCOT
AND TAI.
THIS IS THE SECOND STAGE OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
HOW QUICKLY CAN YOU GET THOSE
PIECES UNTIED AND ON THEIR HOOK?
TAI AND JOE DOING A NICE JOB.
TAI WITH ANOTHER PUZZLE PIECE.
MICHELE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: CYDNEY AND MICHELE
HAVE ALL OF THEM UNTIED.
TAI STILL UNTYING FOR GONDOL.
THE GIRLS DOING A NICE JOB FOR
CHAN LOH.
THEY HAVE MADE UP SOME TIME.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: TAI HAS THEM ALL
UNTIED.
HE'S NOW GOING TO GET INVOLVED
IN PUTTING THEM ON THE HOOKS.
WE'RE VERY CLOSE.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL FOUR TEAM,
CARRY THEM UP.
THE GIRLS HAVE IT FOR CHAN LOH.
THEY ARE NOW IN THE LEAD.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT.
RIGHT BEHIND THEM, THERE'S JOE
AND TAI.
THE GIRLS ARE DRAGGING THEM.
IT'S SO MUCH HEAVIER THAN YOU
CAN ANTICIPATE.
NOW IT'S GONDOL BACK IN THE
LEAD.
>> ALL THE WAY UP, ALL THE WAY
UP, ALL THE WAY UP.
>> AND ON ONE, TWO, THREE,
GIRLS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIRL,
YOU'RE OUT.
NOW WE'RE TO THE FINAL STAGE.
IT IS DEBBIE AND NEAL AND IT IS
ANNA AND PETER.
14 PUZZLE PIECES.
GET THEM ALL ON THAT TABLE
BEFORE YOU START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLES.
BOTH GROUPS HAVE ALL THEIR
PIECES.
NOW YOU CAN START WORKING ON
THAT PUZZLE.
THIS IS IT.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> WE HAVE A BIG ONE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: PETER'S HAD A LOT OF
SUCCESS ON PUZZLES.
SO HAS ANNA.
IT COULD BE A TIGHT DUO.
NEAL AND DEBBIE HAVE DONE A LOT
OF WORK ON PUZZLES.
>> NO.
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH HAS A LOT OF
PIECES DOWN.
THAT COULD BE A VERY GOOD THING
OR ABSOLUTELY MEANINGLESS.
YOU DON'T KNOW UNTIL YOU GET TO
THE END OF THE "SURVIVOR" PUZZLE
IF IT'S RIGHT OR NOT.
IT CAN FOOL YOU.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: NEAL AND DEBBIE
MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
ANNA AND PETER ARE TAKING A LONG
TIME TO MAKE ANY PROGRESS AT
ALL.
>> GOOD COMMUNICATION.
GOOD COMMUNICATION.
>> Jeff: IS THAT IT?
>> WE GOT IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: NEAL AND DEBBIE THINK
THEY HAVE IT.
IMMUNITY FOR CHAN LOH!
SENDING GONDOL TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE THE FIFTH PERSON WILL BE
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
>> THAT WAS FAST.
>> Jeff: CHAN LOH,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NOBODY GOING HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, GONDOL.
FOR ONE OF YOU, THIS IS IT.
TONIGHT SOMEBODY GOING HOME FROM
THIS TRIBE, AND AT THE NEXT
REWARD CHALLENGE, JULIA WILL
JOIN YOUR TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> AS SOON AS WE LOST THE
CHALLENGE, MY HEART SANK.
WE ARE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND IT'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE A
BEAUTY PERSON.
>> IT'S A BATTLE OF ANNA VERSUS
TAI.
GUYS.
SORRY.
>> WE HAD A STRATEGY OF JUST
TAKING OUR TIME, FOCUS, GET IT
TOGETHER.
WE LOOK OVER AND THEY'RE DONE.
>> THEY WERE SO GOOD.
>> RIGHT NOW IT DEFINITELY COMES
DOWN TO ME AND ANNA TONIGHT.
>> I THOUGHT WE HAD A REALLY
GOOD CHANCE.
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
I KNOW IF I PLAY THE IDOL, I
KNOW I WILL LAST ANOTHER DAY,
BUT I DON'T WANT THE PLAY THE
IDOL.
IF I DON'T PLAY IT, THEY MIGHT
BE ALL VOTING FOR ME.
MORE THAN ONCE.
MANY SURVIVORS GO HOME WITH THE
IDOL IN THEIR POCKET.
>> SO, GUYS AND GALS, WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
>> I THINK WE VOTE TAI TONIGHT.
>> YOU WANT THE PRIMARY PROVIDER
OUT?
>> THE OBJECTIVE IS TO GET ONE
BEAUTY OUT.
I PREFER ANNA BECAUSE SHE'S MORE
DIVISIVE.
THAT'S A GOOD ARGUMENT.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW HOW THAT GOES.
>> SURE.
I DON'T CARE.
>> I THINK THE ARGUMENT FOR ANNA
TO GO NOW IS BECAUSE SHE'S TOO
GOOD OF A PLAYER.
SHE'S A SCHEMER.
SHE'S INTELLIGENT, AND SHE'S A
VERY ATTRACTIVE WOMAN.
SHE CAN WIN PEOPLE OVER NOT ONLY
WITH HER BRAIN BUT WITH HER
LOOKS.
>> IF WE BASICALLY BLINDSIDE
ANNA, BECAUSE TAI IS REALLY GOOD
AT CAMP.
HE DOES EVERYTHING.
>> I SEE THE ARGUMENT BOTH WAYS.
>> DO WE WANT TO PROTECT THE
BRAINS OR NOT?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
>> WELL, IF WE DO, WE STILL HAVE
THREE AND TWO ON THE OTHER SIDE,
AND I KNOW SHE'S SWEET AND
EVERYTHING, BUT IF WE WANT TO
GET TO THE END, WE HAVE TO PLAY
THE GAME SMART.
>> OKAY.
>> I CAN COUNT ON YOU THEN?
>> I'M GOING TO GO ON YOU WITH
THIS ONE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
TONIGHT NOW THAT WE LOST?
>> WELL, THEY'RE TALKING GET ONE
OF THE BEAUTY OUT FOR NUMBERS.
>> I FIGURED.
>> IT'S PART OF THE GAME.
>> I DO NOT LIKE PETER.
THERE IS SOMETHING AR GABT ABOUT
PETER.
WE COULD TAKE PETER OUT.
I CAN DO IT BECAUSE I HAVE THE
IDOL.
>> SCOT?
>> YEAH.
DO YOU REALLY WANT PETER OUT?
THERE MIGHT BE A WAY.
>> HOW?
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
I CAN PLAY IT.
>> YOU HAVE THE IDOL.
>> I HAVE THE IDOL.
WANT TO SEE IT?
>> YES.
>> I LOVE THIS.
>> WE CAN DO IT.
DO YOU WANT TO?
>> DONE.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> I LOVE "SURVIVOR."
I LOVE BLIND SIDES AND I LOVE
IMMUNITY IDOL, ESPECIALLY HIDDEN
ONES.
>> I'LL USE IT AND WE'LL ALL
VOTE FOR PETER.
I WANT THE TAKE PETER OUT AND WE
HAVE NUMBERS.
>> I WAS PETRIFIED, BUT TAI WILL
BE USING THE IDOL, SO WHOEVER IS
THE NEXT PERSON WHO HAS THE
HIGHER VOTE GOES HOME.
WHO IS THAT GOING TO BE?
IT'S GOING TO BE PETER.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> ONE OF US IS GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> THEY WANT TO GO ANNA.
THAT'S WHAT THEY WANT.
>> OKAY.
>> AUBRY CAME UP TO ME AND SAID,
TAI IS SAFE.
>> I'M GOING TO GO GET SOME
WATER.
>> SO WITH JASON, I HAVE TWO
GUYS THAT HAVE IDOLS, AND IF YOU
PUT THEM TOGETHER, IT BECOMES
SUPER IDOL, AND I THOUGHT, WOW,
WE COULD BLIND SIDE ANNA AND
KEEP THE IDOL HIDDEN, THAT WOULD
MAKE ME THE ONLY PERSON IN THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR" THAT KNOWS
WHERE THERE ARE TWO IDOLS.
THAT PUTS ME IN, IN A GOOD SPOT
PROVIDED I GET TO THE MERGE.
>> WHAT IS THE BEST THING?
>> THEY ARE VOTING ANNA OUT.
I LIKE YOU.
THEY LIKE YOU.
NOBODY WANTS YOU TO GO.
YOU'RE ASKING ME WHAT'S BEST FOR
YOU.
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU, I THINK, IS
TO SAVE THE IDOL.
AS LONG AS YOU CAN.
>> YES, OF COURSE.
>> THEY'RE NOT VOTING YOU OUT
TONIGHT, SO DON'T USE IT.
>> SCOT SAID, MAYBE THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO VOTE FOR ME AND I CAN
USE THE IDOL AS A TOOL, BUT I'M
SO WORRIED THAT IF I DON'T PLAY
THE IDOL, I MIGHT GO HOME WITH
THE IDOL IN MY POCKET, IN MY
SHOE.
THAT WOULD BE A TERRIBLE THING.
>> YOU KNOW, TRIBAL COUNCIL IS
LIKE HIGH SCHOOL PROM.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO GET OUT OF IT, BUT YOU'RE
GOING TO FEEL SOMETHING.
>> I CAN KEEP IT FOR MYSELF,
SHARE WITH AN NARCOTIC I DON'T
KNOW.
I GUESS I'M BRINGING MY IDOL
TONIGHT, AND I WANT TO SEE HOW
IT PLAYS OUT.
I THINK A LOT OF STUFF WILL
PROBABLY COME UP AT TRIBAL, AND
FROM THERELY DECIDE WHETHER TO
PLAY IT OR NOT.
>> Jeff: ANNA AND TAI, AS IT
IS YOUR FIRST TIME AT TRIBAL,
THERE ARE TWO TORCHES BACK
THERE, GRAB ONE, DIP IT IN AND
GET FIRE.
PART OF THE RITUAL OF TRIBAL
COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS GAME,
FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOU FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
SO AUBRY, LOOKING AT THE TRIBE
DIVISION, IS IT FAIR TO SAY WITH
THREE WRAINS, YOU, PETER AND JOE
ARE STICKING TOGETHER IN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE WE KNOW,
THE DEVILS WE KNOW, BUT WHEN YOU
GO INTO A TRIBE SWAP, YOU WANT
TO STICK TO THE NUMBERS.
>> Jeff: SO, SCOT, THAT PUTS
YOU IN AN INTERESTING SPOT.
IT COULD BE GOOD.
IT COULD BE TERRIBLE BECAUSE YOU
HAVE NO BUDDY.
>> I'M LITERALLY ALONE ON AN
ISLAND, IF YOU WANT TO GO THERE,
BUT PEOPLE HAVE TALKED TO ME AND
THEY'VE MADE ME PART OF THEIR
GROUP FOR NOW, AND WE'LL SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Jeff: ANNA, WHAT WAS YOUR
FEELING, KNOWING I'M NOT ON THE
BOTTOM BUT I'M CERTAINLY NOT IN
THE POWER SPOT.
>> AUTOMATICALLY MY HEART
DROPPED.
I DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS.
MY FIRST THOUGHT IS THERE IS A
GOOD CHANCE IF WE LOSE IMMUNITY,
IT WILL BE TAI OR I.
THAT'S WHAT I FEEL LIKE NOW.
>> Jeff: TAI, DO YOU FEEL THE
SAME WAY?
DO YOU THINK IT'S YOU OR AN IN?
>> I AGREE COMPLETELY.
THESE ARE THE BRAINS.
THESE ARE THE SMART PEOPLE.
THEY HAVE THREE.
WE HAVE TWO.
OBVIOUSLY THEY'RE GOING TO KEEP
SCOT BECAUSE HE'S MASSIVE, A
HUGE ASSET TO THE CHALLENGES.
>> Jeff: ANNA, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I CAN READ BETWEEN THE LINES,
IT'S WHATEVER THE BRAINS AND
SCOT DECIDE.
IT'S 50/50.
I THINK IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO
KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG.
I MIGHT NOT HAVE BIG GUN, BUT MY
LEGS ARE STRONG.
YOU KNOW, I'M COMPETITIVE.
SO HOPEFULLY THEY SEE ME AS AN
ASSET AND KEEP MY AROUND A
LITTLE LONGER.
>> AND I HATE THAT WE'RE
DISCUSSING ABOUT THIS BECAUSE WE
HAVE A GREAT CONNECTION.
AND I'M PLAYING EVERYTHING VERY
STRAIGHTFORWARD WITH YOU GUYS,
YOU KNOW, AND I ALWAYS WORK.
I'M THE ONE THAT WORKS.
I'M THE ONE THAT DISCOVERS
EDIBLE FOOD.
THE REASON I SCRAPE UP TREE, I
CLIMB MANGO TREES TO GET MANGOES
FOR THE TRIBE.
YOU CAN SEE IT.
IT'S FORMING A SCAB ALREADY.
>> Jeff: I BELIEVE YOU.
>> I'M NOT HURT.
EVEN WITH THIS THING... EVEN
WITH THIS THING, I HAVE A LOT OF
SKILLS, A LOT OF RESOURCES, AND
I NEVER EVER COMPLAIN ABOUT
WORK, NEVER.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, DO YOU
APPRECIATE THE FACT YOU HAVE TWO
VERY DIFFERENT PEOPLE, AND
THEY'RE BOTH MAKING THEIR CASE
FROM THEIR OWN PERSONALITY?
>> QUITE HONESTLY, IT'S HARD TO
HEAR BECAUSE THEY'RE PUTTING IT
ALL ON THE TABLE, AND I
APPRECIATE IT, BUT WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO MAKE A TOUGH
DECISION.
>> Jeff: JOE, HAS THE TOPIC OF
IDOLS COME UP.
>> WELL, MY PERSONAL BELIEF, YOU
ALWAYS SAY THERE IS A TWIST.
I THINK THE TWIST IS THERE WAS
NO TWIST ABOUT AN IDOL.
>> Jeff: MEANING THERE ISN'T
ONE?
>> THERE IS NOT ONE.
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT BY NOW
THERE WOULD BE A CUE.
THAT HAS NOT HAPPENED AND WE'RE
MOVING ON IN THE GAME.
PI PERSONAL BELIEF IS THERE IS
NOT ONE.
>> Jeff: TAI, DO YOU BELIEVE
IT'S POSSIBLE THERE ARE ACTUALLY
NO IDOLS OUT HERE?
>> I DON'T THINK SO EITHER
BECAUSE I LOOKED AND I GOT IN
TROUBLE FROM THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
AND ACTUALLY I'M TERRIBLE ABOUT
LOOKING FOR STUFF.
I HAVE A BAD SENSE OF DIRECTION,
SO I NEVER FIND IT, AND THERE'S
IN CLUE.
SO I DON'T THINK THERE'S AN IDOL
OUT THERE.
>> Jeff: SO SCOT, IF IT'S TRUE
THAT IT'S PETER, AUBRY AND JOE
VERSUS ANNA AND TAI, YOU HAVE
OPTIONS.
>> WELL, POSSIBLY.
BUT IT ALL DEPENDS ON HOW TIGHT
THE BRAINS ARE.
>> Jeff: PETER, SCOT BRINGS UP
AN INTERESTING POINT.
DID YOU SEE PEOPLE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT IF THERE ARE CRACKS
BETWEEN YOU AND AUBRY AND JOE?
>> NOT TODAY.
BUT TO BE HONEST, JEFF, I'M NOT
CONCERNED BECAUSE I'M IN A
POSITION OF POWER.
THE BRAINS AND SCOT, WE'RE IN
THE POWER POSITION.
WE CAN DO WHAT WE WANT RIGHT NOW
AND WE'RE GOING TO.
>> Jeff: BUT PETER, THE
HARDEST THING ABOUT TRIBAL IS
YOU CAN'T EVER TRUST A SINGLE
THING YOU'RE HEARING FROM ANYONE
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
STORY IT IS THEY WANT YOU TO
BELIEVE IS ACTUALLY HAPPENING.
>> THAT'S THE IRONY.
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS ITS OWN LITTLE
UNIVERSE.
THE WORDS OUT OF OUR MOUTHS
AREN'T NECESSARILY THE TRUTH.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT'S THE
LIKELIHOOD THAT ANNA, TAI AND
SCOT DECIDE WE'RE DEAD IF WE
DON'T TAKE THESE THREE BRAINS ON
RIGHT NOW TONIGHT?
>> LIKELIHOOD LOW, VERY LOW.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, THE REASON I
ASK IS, IF YOU'RE SITTING WHERE
I AM, THE THREE OF YOU ARE
THREE.
THERE'S TWO AND THERE'S ONE.
SO IT'S NOT A BAD IDEA TO MAKE
ANOTHER THREE AND SAY, LET'S
JUST GO FOR BROKE.
>> THAT COULD DEFINITELY BE A
POSSIBILITY.
YOU SEE THREE.
YOU FEEL LIKE THESE PEOPLE ARE
TIGHT.
IF YOU'RE IN A DESPERATE
SITUATION, SOME PEOPLE WOULD GO
FOR IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ANNA.
YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE PETER.
ANNA.
TWO VOTES ANNA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ANNA, ONE
VOTE PETER.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT, ANNA.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ANNA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, EVERYONE.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, "SURVIVOR" IS A GAME ABOUT
DECISIONS.
TONIGHT YOU DECIDED TO KEEP TAI
OVER ANNA, AND THE QUESTION
YOU'RE GOING TO BE WRESTLING
WITH UNTIL THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, DID WE MAKE THE RIGHT
DECISION?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," DEBBIE IS COURTING A
NEW ALLEY.
>> ONE OF MY STRATEGIES IS NOT
TO BE A FLIRT, BUT I THINK NICK
LOOKS LIKE A GREEK GOD.
>> Jeff: WHILE JOE
INVESTIGATES ONE OF HIS OWN.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE ME OUT?
DON'T LIE.
I'M RETIRED F.B.I.
I'M TRAINED TO DEAL WITH
SOMEBODY LIKE THAT.
>> OH, MY GOD, THIS HURTS SO
MUCH.
I DID NOT EXPECT TO BE OUT THIS
EARLY.
I THOUGHT I WAS POLITICIAN A
PRETTY GOOD GAME, BUT MAYBE I
WAS PLAYING A LITTLE TOO HARD.
BUT THAT WAS MY STRATEGY.
I WAS GOING TO GO ALL IN.
I WAS GOING TO GO WITH MY GUT.
WHEN TAI SHOWED ME THE IDOL, I
THOUGHT, OH, MY GOD, WE'RE GOING
TO BLIND SIDE PETER, BUT HE
BLIND SIDED ME.