>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... AFTER A MEETING,
JASON, SCOT AND TAI WERE ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> IT'S TIME TO COME OUT.
>> Meaghan: JULIA SAW IT AS A
PERFECT OPPORTUNITY TO GET
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> GETTING RID OF YOU GUYS WOULD
BE A DUMB MOVE ON MY PART.
>> Jeff: BUT EVERYONE NOTICED
JULIA WAS PLAYING BOTH SIDES.
>> JULIA WANTS TO RIDE THE
MIDDLE TO THE END.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
DEBBIE EXPOSED THE PLAN IN FRONT
OF JULIA.
>> DEBBIE COMPLETELY TRUSTS
JEWELA.
THAT SCARES ME.
>> Jeff: AND IT PUT A TARGET
ON DEBBIE'S BACK.
>> DO I HAVE TO CUT DEBBIE
LOOSE?
I'M READY.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL...
>> I'VE GOT AN IDOL.
THE IDOL'S GOT A BROTHER.
>> Jeff: JASON, SCOT AND TAI
SHOWED OFF THEIR IDOLS.
>> I'M GIVING MY IDOL TO TAI.
>> Jeff: AND WERE PREPARED TO
PLAY THE SUPER IDOL, WHICH GAVE
THE MAJORITY MORE REASON TO VOTE
OUT ONE OF THEIR OWN.
DEBBIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
THE ONLY WAY IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BETTER IF CYDNEY HAD GONE HOME,
BUT THEY ATE ONE OF THEIR OWN.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
TRIBAL WAS EXCITING.
THE BOYS ARE HAPPY BECAUSE NONE
OF US WENT HOME, NONE OF US USED
OUR IDOLS, SO WE THINK TRIBAL
WENT VERY WELL.
>> I AM GIVING YOUR IDOL BACK.
>> I WILL ACCEPT IT AND I THANK
YOU SO MUCH.
>> PSYCHOLOGICAL OPERATION.
IT WORKED.
AND ALL WE DID WAS HIDE A
MACHETE AND AN AX AND PUT A FIRE
OUT.
AND THEY COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
WE CAUSED CHAOS.
IT FRACTURED THEM, AND IT MADE
THEM GET RAID OF THEIR OWN.
WE MAY NOT HAVE GOTTEN THE
PERSON HOME THAT WE WANTED, BUT
ALL THREE OF US STAYED.
WE GOT JULIA ON OUR SIDE, AND WE
STILL HAVE THE SUPER IDOL.
THAT'S A WIN IN MY BOOK.
>> I'M BEYOND GOOD.
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER.
THAT'S A START.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO GET CAMP LIFE
BACK TOGETHER.
IT'S ALL ABOUT MENDING
RELATIONSHIPS AGAIN.
I THINK WE NEED TO SAY, YOU
KNOW, OLIVE BRANCH IS THERE.
YOU GOT TO START SOMEWHERE.
>> WE HAVE TO TALK TO AUBRY AND
SEE WHAT HER... I WANT
ASSURANCES.
>>
I CAME INTO THIS
GAME NOT WANTING TO BE THE GRUFF
MAN KICKING OVER THE RICE AND
POURING WATER ON THE FIRE LIKE I
DID, BUT I HAD TO MAKE A POINT
THAT WE WERE THE PROVIDERS AND
THEY WEREN'T GOING TO EAT AND
SUCCEED WITHOUT US.
>> WE ENJOY GETTING WOOD,
GETTING THE WATER, GETTING ALL
THIS STUFF.
I WANT... MY REAL BEEF IS WITH
CYDNEY.
SHE BETRAYED US FOR NO REASON,
SO WE WANT CYDNEY GONE.
IF WE FEEL LIKE YOU'RE ON BOARD
WITH THAT IDEA, EVERYTHING WILL
GO AS NORMAL.
>> NOW WE'RE BEING THE BIGGER
PEOPLE.
WE'RE SHOWING OUR MATURITY.
WE'RE SHOWING THAT WE CAN COME
BACK IN AND BE LIKE NOTHING
HAPPENED.
HOPEFULLY CYDNEY CONTINUES TO
SHOW EVERYBODY WHO SHE REALLY
IS, WHICH IS BROODING, PETTY,
SMALL.
>> WE WANT A HAPPY CAMP.
>> OKAY.
IT'S A LOT FIRST THING IN THE
MORNING.
SCOT WAS TELLING ME CAMP LIFE
WILL BE NORMAL IF HE GETS WHAT
HE WANTS.
IT WAS A SOFT, CONTROLLING MOVE.
IT WAS HIM TELLING ME WHAT HE
WANTS, AND WHAT I WILL GET IN
RETURN, BUT IT WAS SERVED UP
WITH A BIRTHDAY CAKE THAT WAS
VERY SUGARY TO MAKE IT SEEM A
LITTLE LESS COME NEARING.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO DEMAND
ANYTHING FROM YOU RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T NEED A PROMISE.
I NEED YOU TO THINK ABOUT IT.
>> NEW YORK IT'S DEFINITE.
THERE WAS IN THE A SHOT IN HELL
I'M GOING TO WORK WITH THEM, BUT
I'M WILLING TO LET THEM THINK
I'LL PLAY ALONG, AND WHEN IT
COMES TIME TO GET OUT SCOT, I'M
READY THE FIGHT, BUT IT'S A BIG,
SCARY MOVE.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: VERY SIMPLE: FOR
TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'LL PLACE
ONE FOOT AT THE END OF A
BALANCING BEAM.
AT THE OTHER END, CERAMIC POTS.
WHEN THE POTS DROP, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEP.
>> Jeff: TODAY IT'S SOMETHING
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
YOU HAVE A CHOICE.
YOU CAN CHOOSE TO PLAY FOR FOOD
IN THE FORM OF A BACON
CHEESEBURGER, FRENCH FRIES, COLD
BEER AND CHOCOLATE CHIP COOKIES
FOR DESSERT.
OR IF YOU WANT TO NOURISH YOUR
SOUL, YOU CAN CHOOSE TO PLAY FOR
LOVE.
THESE ARE THE LETTERS WRITTEN BY
THE VERY PEOPLE YOU ARE OUT HERE
PLAYING FOR.
THIS COULD BE JUST WHAT YOU NEED
TO GET YOU THROUGH THESE LAST
FEW DAYS.
OR IF YOU FEEL YOU'RE IN
TROUBLE, YOU CAN CHOOSE TO PLAY
FOR ADVANTAGE.
THE SPECIFICS OF THE ADVANTAGE
WILL REMAIN A MYSTERY.
ALL YOU KNOW IS THIS WILL HELP
YOU IN THE GAME.
HERE'S THE TWIST: SO YOU ARE ALL
COMPETING IN THE SAME CHALLENGE.
YOU ARE ONLY COMPETING AGAINST
THE PEOPLE WHO CHOOSE THE SAME
REWARD.
SO IT BECOMES A CASE OF WHAT DO
I NEED VERSUS WHAT DO I WANT
VERSUS WHAT DO I THINK EVERYBODY
ELSE IS GOING TO CHOOSE.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO CHOOSE YOUR
REWARD IN SECRET AND GET
STARTED.
WE HAVE OUR MATCHUPS.
GOING FOR ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME,
IT IS TAI, CYDNEY AND AUBRY.
CHOOSING FOOD, IT IS SCOT VERSUS
JASON VERSUS MICHELE.
AND CHOOSING LOVE, IT IS JULIA
VERSUS JOE.
SO ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS BEAT
THE PEOPLE IN YOUR CATEGORY.
SO WE WILL HAVE THREE WINNERS IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY PLACE YOUR FOOT ON
YOUR BEAM.
GENTLY.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
YOU CAN'T TOUCH THE STRUCTURE.
IT'S ALL ABOUT BALANCE, STAYING
FOCUSED.
JOE, A LITTLE TROUBLE OUT OF THE
GATE.
>> I'M SHAKY.
I'M SHAKY.
>> Jeff: ALL JULIA HAS TO DO
IS BEAT JOE TO GET THOSE LETTERS
FROM HOME, AND THAT'S IT.
JOE IS OUT.
JOE, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
JULIA, YOU'RE DONE.
JULIA THE FIRST WINNER IN THIS
CHALLENGE, THE LOVE LETTER.
YOU MIGHT WANT THE WAIT UNTIL
YOU GET BACK TO CAMP.
NOW IT IS DOWN TO ADVANTAGE
BETWEEN TAI, CYDNEY AND AUBRY,
AND FOOD BETWEEN SCOT, JASON AND
MICHELE.
LOTS OF STRATEGY IN THE CHOICES
EVERYBODY MADE.
IF YOU DON'T THINK YOU CAN BEAT
SOMEBODY, THEN GO FOR SOMETHING
THAT YOU THINK NOBODY ELSE WILL
CHOOSE.
JASON STRUGGLING BUT GETS IT
BACK UNDER CONTROL.
A LITTLE BIT OF MOVEMENT IS
OKAY, AS LONG AS YOU'RE IN
CRIMINAL OF IT.
SCOT, A LITTLE BIT OF
HESITATION.
HE'S OUT.
NO SHOT AT FOOD.
IT'S NOW DOWN TO JASON VERSUS
MICHELE FOR FOOD.
DON'T START DAYDREAMING.
STAY FOCUSED.
IF YOU LOSE YOUR CONCENTRATION
FOR ONE MOMENT, YOU'RE OUT.
THOSE POTS WILL DROP.
HERE COMES THE WIND NOW.
BIG BREEZE.
AUBRY WITH SOME MOVEMENT.
JASON ALL OVER THE PLACE NOW,
BUT HE'S STILL IN IT.
BUT HE CAN'T DO IT.
JASON IS OUT.
MICHELE WINS FOOD.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> Jeff: HAVE A SEAT, MICHELE.
I'LL BRING IT TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WE ARE DOWN TO OUR
LAST THREE.
OUR LAST WINNER WILL BE EITHER
TAI, CYDNEY OR AUBRY GOING FOR
ADVANTAGE.
>> ENJOY.
>> I THINK I'M GOING WITH THE
COOKIE FIRST.
>> GOOD JOB, MICHELE.
>> Jeff: JULIA HAS WON LETTERS
FROM HOME.
MICHELE HAS WON FOOD.
BUT THIS MAY BE THE REWARD WITH
THE MOST LONG-TERM VALUE.
TAI, CYDNEY LOOKING VERY GOOD.
AUBRY WAVERING AGAIN.
THIS COULD BE WHAT YOU NEED TO
GET TO THE END.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
A SILLY LITTLE CHALLENGE THAT
COULD BE WORTH $1 MILLION.
CYDNEY GETTING A LITTLE HIGHER.
AUBRY WITH A LOT OF MOVEMENT.
OUT OF NOWHERE CYDNEY DROPS.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: CYDNEY HAS NO SHOT AT
ADVANTAGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO TAI AND
AUBRY.
>> GOOD JOB, CYDNEY.
>> Jeff: THE LAST TWO PEOPLE
IN THIS CHALLENGE GOING FOR
ADVANTAGE.
>> JEFF, I JUST WANT THE PROVE
IT TO MYSELF.
>> Jeff: SO THIS IS NOT ABOUT
THE ADVANTAGE?
>> THIS IS ABOUT PROVING MYSELF
THAT THIS IS A HARD-ASS GAME AND
I CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: DO NOT LOSE YOUR
CONCENTRATION.
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING TO KEEP
CONTROL OVER YOUR BODY, KEEP
DOING IT.
PROBABLY SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
OUT HERE FOR A LONG TIME.
IT HAS ONLY BEEN TEN MINUTES.
TAI WITH A LITTLE BIT OF
MOVEMENT.
AUBRY WITH A LITTLE MOVEMENT.
THOSE THIGHS HAVE TO BE BURNING.
THE WHOLE IDEA OF DIG DEEP.
NOW IS THE TIME TO DO IT.
TAI WITH A LITTLE MOVEMENT.
YOU HAVE TO STAY ALERT.
STAY ALERT.
ANOTHER NICE SAVE BY AUBRY.
TAI STRUGGLING MORE.
HERE COMES THAT BREEZE AGAIN.
AUBRY FIGHTING TO STAY IN IT.
AUBRY IS OUT.
TAI WINS INDIVIDUAL REWARD IN
THE FORM OF ADVANTAGE.
>> GOOD JOB, AUBRY.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER BIG SHOWDOWN
THIS SEASON.
TAI, YOUR ADVANTAGE.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: TAKE IT BACK TO CAMP.
FIND A PRIVATE SPOT, OPEN IT AND
READ IT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> SO TAI WINS THE ADVANTAGE.
THAT'S THE BEST THING THAT COULD
HAVE HAPPENED FOR OUR LITTLE
ALLIANCE, BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY,
CYDNEY DIDN'T WIN ADVANTAGE.
CYDNEY DIDN'T EAT, AND CYDNEY
GOES HOME.
>> WOW.
>> THAT WAS A HUGE BURGER.
>> I WAS TRYING TO SHOVE THE
FOOD IN MY MOUTH, BUT I DIDN'T
WANT THE MAKE ANYONE WAIT, SO I
WAS LIKE, ALL RIGHT.
IT FELT SO GOOD TO BEAT SCOT AND
JASON, BECAUSE I KNOW THEY
WANTED THAT BURGER MORE THAN
ANYTHING.
>> YOU GUYS NEED ANYTHING ELSE
WHILE WE'RE OUT?
>> I'M DYING OF THIRST, BUT I'LL
EAT THIS FIRST.
>> IT'S A LITTLE NERVE-RACKING
THAT TAI WON AN ADVANTAGE,
BECAUSE EVERYBODY KNOWS HE HAS
AN IDOL.
AND IT'S SCARY.
>> THE MOAT SAY GO THE TREE
MAIL.
MY IDOL RIGHT NOW IS KIND OF OUT
IN THE OPEN.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE THAT WAS LIKE HIDDEN
AND NO ONE WOULD KNOW I HAVE IT.
JUST LIKE ANYTHING, THE MORE
PEOPLE KNOW, THE LESS POWER IT
HAS.
OH, CONGRATULATIONS, YOU WON
YOURSELF AN EXTRA VOTE.
WOW.
I OPEN UP THE BOX, AND THE BOX
SAY YOU HAVE AN EXTRA VOTE.
FANTASTIC.
AN EXTRA VOTE.
THAT'S A LOT OF POWER, AND I CAN
PLAY IT ANY TIME UNTIL UP TO
FIVE PEOPLE ARE LEFT.
YEAH.
I FOUND AN IDOL.
I HAVE AN EXTRA VOTE.
AND I'M SCARED OF WHAT'S THE
RIGHT THING TO DO.
IT'S A RICH MAN'S PROBLEM, BUT I
HAVE TO TRUST MYSELF.
OTHERWISE I MIGHT GO HOME WITH
BOTH OF THEM IN MY POCKET.
>> THAT WAS FUNNY.
>> I'VE KIND OF GONE ON THIS
ROLLER COASTER THROUGHOUT THIS
GAME.
I'M KIND OF FIGURING OUT HOW TO
GET POWER, TO GETTING POWER TO
LOSING POWER WHEN I WENT TO
BRAWN BEACH, COMING BACK AND
HAVING A LOVE LETTER GIVES YOU
THAT BOOST THE KEEP GOING
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT'S WHO
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR.
EVERY DAY KNOW THAT YOU ARE IN
OUR HEARTS, SO HANG TIGHT AND BE
FIERCE BECAUSE YOU KNOW OUR LOVE
RUNS SO DEEP AND IT GROWS EVERY
DAY.
AND HAVE THE GREATEST
SOUL-SEARCHING EXPERIENCE OF A
LIFETIME.
OH, MY GOD, I'M GOING THE CRY.
TRY NOT THE CRY.
BUT IT KEEPS YOU GOING.
AND IT WAS KIND OF A MOMENT FOR
ME TO STEP BACK AND REALIZE THAT
I'M HERE THE PLAY AND THE GOAL
IS TO WIN.
AND TO DO THAT, I HAVE TO MAKE
BIG MOVES.
COMING OUT AND SAYING THAT THEY
HAVE THE IDOLS WAS SO DUMB.
>> NOT THE SMARTEST THING.
>> THOSE IDOLS CANNOT BE AROUND.
AND TAI GOT AN ADVANTAGE TODAY.
>> THAT SCARES ME.
>> THAT SCARES ME, TOO.
>> TAI IS DEFINITELY A THREAT AT
THIS POINT.
SO WHAT I WANT TO DO IS FLUSH
OUT THESE IDOL, BUT ALSO STAY
LOYAL TO MY ALLIANCE WITH JASON
AND SCOT.
>> THIS IS THE THING, IF WE ALL
VOTE TAI AND TAI DOESN'T MY AN
IDOL, TAI IS OUT.
IF HE PLAYS AN IDOL, CYDNEY IS
GONE BECAUSE THE THREE OF THEM
ARE GOING TO VOTE FOR CYDNEY.
AND THEN WE HAVE AN IDOL FLUSHED
OUT.
>> GET THAT DAMN IDOL OUT.
I THINK THAT'S...
>> I THINK IT'S A GOOD PLAN,
BECAUSE HE'LL GET NERVOUS AND
PLAY IT.
>> THE THREE GUYS HAVE TWO
IDOLS.
THAT'S A HUGE PROBLEM.
AND WE GOT TO FLUSH OUT THE
IDOLS AND WE GOT TO GET RID OF
THE GUYS, ONE OR THE OTHER.
>> WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE TAI DOES
NOT WIN IMMUNITY.
>> THAT SEEMS LIKE A GOOD WAY TO
GET THEM ALL OUT OF THE GAME.
>> JULIA WANTS TO THROW ALL THE
VOTES AT TAI AT NEXT TRIBAL AND
MAKE HOUR THE IDOL GOES.
JULIA IS DUE POLICE US THE, BUT
AT THE SAME TIME, SHE'S PLAYING
A GOOD GAME.
I CAN RESPECT THAT.
BUT I DON'T KNOW THAT I WANT HER
NEXT TO ME.
SHE'S SUPER SHADY, AND PEOPLE
LIKE MICHELE DON'T SEE THROUGH
IT.
I THINK JULIA IS GOING TO WAIT
UNTIL THE NUMBERS ARE PERFECT
AND SHE'LL TAKE OUT THE GIRLS.
IF I HAVE TO TURN ON HER, I'M
NOT AFRAID TO GET MY HANDS
DIRTY.
>> YEAH.
>> I SAT CRYING IN THE GRASS
HERE SAYING, I DON'T KNOW IF I
COULD STILL PLAY THIS GAME.
>> I THINK THAT EVERY NIGHT WHEN
I GO TO SLEEP.
EVERYBODY IS PLAYING BETTER THAN
ME.
WHAT AM I DOING.
>> OUT HERE, I REALLY STRUGGLE
WITH PEOPLE TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
OTHER PEOPLE, ALL THE LYING, ALL
THE CHEATING.
I KEEP TELLING MYSELF, IT'S A
GAME.
BUT IT SEEMS REALLY DIFFICULT
FOR ME TO DO THAT.
>> IT'S THE HEART AND THE BRAIN
CONSTANTLY FIGHTING, ALL DAY
LONG, IN THIS GAME.
AND SOMETIMES IT'S HARD TO KNOW
WHEN TO TRUST THE BRAIN AND WHEN
TO TRUST THE HEART AND WHEN TO
STOP THINKING.
>> MY HEART SAY, I LIKE THAT
GIRL AUBRY A LOT.
OUT HERE, MOST PEOPLE I DON'T
HAVE MUCH IN COMMON WITH, BUT
SHE HAS A CERTAIN ENERGY THAT I
REALLY LIKE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TALK
AT SOME POINT BECAUSE CERTAIN
GIRLS WANT TO PUSH THE VOTE TO
TRY TO GET IDOLS OUT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I WANT TO WORK WITH YOU, AND
I WANT TO SHOW YOU THAT YOU CAN
TRUST ME.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT I COULD HAVE YOUR BACK
ON THIS.
>> I WENT OUT ON A LIMB TALKING
TO TAI.
BUT I WANTED TAI TO KNOW THAT
JULIA'S GUNNING FOR HIM, AND I
AM ABALTERNATIVE TO THE WAY
JASON AND SCOT AND JULIA ARE
PLAYING THIS GAME.
SO MAYBE WE CAN MAKE IT WORK AND
I CAN TELL YOU WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> I'M EXCITED AUBRY IS ON MY
SIDE.
I THINK SHE'S A GOOD
CONTRIBUTION TO THE ALLIANCE.
TOGETHER WE COULD BE A GREAT
PARTNERSHIP.
I THINK SCOT AND JASON ARE GOING
THE LIKE IT.
IF THAT'S THE CASE, THEN
EVERYTHING IS BEAUTIFUL.
SO THIS MORNING AUBRY SAY SOME
GIRLS WANT YOUR IDOL GONE, AND
SHE THINKS SHE'S OPEN IF WE WANT
TO JOIN FORCES.
AND SHE SAID, WELL, I AM A FREE
AGENT.
I'M FREE, OPEN TO ANY
SUGGESTIONS IF YOU WANT TO TALK.
>> HOW ABOUT THIS IDEA: AT NEXT
TRIBAL WE TAKE AUBRY OUT.
>> THIS ONE?
>> THE NEXT ONE.
>> SEEMS LIKE I HAVE NO SAY IN
OUR ALLIANCE.
I'M NOT PART OF THE DISCUSSION.
I ALWAYS PARTICIPATE, BUT SEEMS
LIKE THEY'RE SO FORCEFUL.
>> THE SMARTEST OPTION IS TO GET
AUBRY OUT.
>> I SAY WE DO IT.
>> BREAK HER AND JOE UP.
THEN WE HAVE ALL THE POWER.
THE DOWNSIDE IS WE HAVE TO KEEP
CYDNEY AROUND, WHICH I HATE
DOING.
AS MUCH AS I HATE IT, IT'S THE
LAST THING THEY'LL EXPECT
BECAUSE THEY KNOW WE WANT CYDNEY
OUT SO BAD.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> THOSE TWO BOYS ARE RUNNING
THE SHOW.
THAT'S WHY I'M FEELING A BIT
LIKE AN OUTSIDER.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO?
>> SHE WON'T SUSPECT IT.
WE BLINDSIDE HER, BAM, AUBRY
GOES HOME.
THIS PLAN WORKS SO MUCH BETTER
THAN JUST GOING BLINDLY AT
CYDNEY BECAUSE IT WAS AN
EMOTIONAL DECISION.
AS LONG AS TAI AND JASON AND
MYSELF REMAIN FAITHFUL, WHICH I
DON'T SEE WHY WE WOULDN'T, WE
HAVE A PRETTY GOOD PATH TO GET
TO THE FINAL THREE, SO WE JUST
NEED TO MAKE SURE AUBRY DOESN'T
WIN IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
JULIA, TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO STRETCH YOUR ARMS OUT
AND USE YOUR FINGERTIPS TO PRESS
AGAINST TWO WOODEN DISKS.
ATTACHED TO THE DISKS, CERAMIC
POTS.
THE POTS DROP, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
SEVEN SHOT AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
AFTER 27 DAYS SOMEBODY WILL
BECOME THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY IS IN POSITION.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
IT IS DESIGNED TO MAKE YOUR
FINGERS FEEL NUMB FAIRLY
QUICKLY.
YOU HAVE JUST ENOUGH THAT YOU
CAN KEEP PRESSURE ON THE DISKS
BUT NOT SO MUCH THAT YOU CAN
JUST PUT YOUR ENTIRE PALM OR
YOUR FIST UP AGAINST THERE.
WHEN YOUR SHOULDERS AND YOUR
ARMS START THE WEAR OUT, YOU'LL
DROP.
JOE STANDING STRAIGHT, TRYING
THE HOLD STRONG.
YOU CAN FEEL THE PAIN.
JOE DROPS.
JOE IS THE FIRST PERSON OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
SPOT ON THE BENCH.
VULNERABLE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO SEVEN.
ONE OF THE GREATEST FEELINGS IN
THIS GAME IS TO WALK INTO TRIBAL
KNOWING, I CAN'T BE VOTED OUT.
THIS COULD BE THE CHALLENGE THAT
SAVES YOU OR DOOMS YOU.
BY NOW YOU'RE DEFINITELY FEELING
IT IN YOUR SHOULDERS.
YOUR FINGERTIPS ARE STARTING TO
GO NUMB IF THEY HAVEN'T ALREADY.
PEOPLE CHANGING POSITIONS,
STANDING UP STRAIGHT, BENDING
OVER, LEAKINGED TO RIGHT.
AUBRY DOING SOME SORT OF 50s
DANCE CRAZE.
WHATEVER IT TAKES TO KEEP THAT
BODY ALIVE AND THAT BLOOD
MOVING, THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO.
JULIA SLIPS BUT A NICE RECOVERY.
SHE GETS IT BACK IN PLAY.
SCOT DROPS.
SCOT IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE,
AND WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
JULIA'S NOW OUT.
>> MY THUMBS.
>> Jeff: WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE.
EVERYBODY STARTING TO LOOK AT
EVERYBODY ELSE NOW.
A SURE SIGN THAT THE PAIN IS
THERE.
WONDERING, IS ANYBODY ELSE
HURTING.
YEAH, THEY ARE.
TAI SLIPPING WITH HIS LEFT DISK
A LITTLE BIT.
NOW TAI SLIPPING ON THE OTHER
SIDE.
TAI DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO LOSING
ONE OR BOTH POTS.
HE'S ON THE EDGE RIGHT NOW.
CAN HE GET IT BACK.
TAI IS OUT.
TAI HAS NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
MICHELE FIGHTING TO STAY IN
THIS.
MICHELE CANNOT HANG ON ANY
LONGER.
MICHELE IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE.
ONE BRAIN, TWO BRAWN, ONE
NECKLACE.
EVERYBODY'S FINGERTIPS ARE
SUFFICIENTLY GONE AT THIS POINT.
ANOTHER HOT, MUGGY DAY.
JASON CONTINUES TO FIGHT.
YOU CAN FEEL YOUR MUSCLES
STARTING TO GIVE OUT.
CYDNEY CAN'T HANG ON.
CYDNEY IS OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS NOW AUBRY, AN ORIGINAL
BRAIN MEMBER, VERSUS JASON, AN
ORIGINAL BRAWN MEMBER.
>> I'M NOT BACKING DOWN.
>> NEITHER AM I, PAL.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT GET YOU A
LITTLE, AUBRY, WHEN JASON SAYS,
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE?
>> NOT AT ALL.
WHERE ELSE WOULD I EXPECT HIM TO
GO?
THIS GUY'S BEEN THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
WHY WOULD HE NOT GET THROUGH
THIS?
>> Jeff:
SUPER IMPRESSED.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN DIGGING FOR A
LONG TIME.
AUBRY WITH A LITTLE SLIP.
AUBRY WITH A NICE RECOVERY.
BUT HER HANDS ARE NOW IN A TOUGH
SPOT.
CAN SHE GET IT BACK UP?
SHE DOES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER NICE SAVE BY
AUBRY.
>> DAMN, AUBRY.
>> Jeff: THIS HAS BEEN A
BATTLE.
YOU'VE GOT TO DIG DEEP RIGHT
NOW.
THIS IS IT.
27 DAYS.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO HOME
TONIGHT BECAUSE YOU COULDN'T
KEEP YOUR ARMS UP JUST ONE MORE
SECOND.
AUBRY SLIPPING.
BOTH DISKS MOVING.
NOW IT'S JASON THAT'S MOVING.
KEEP FIGHTING!
YOU GOT TO DIG!
AND MORE SLIPPING.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: AUBRY DROPS.
JASON WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WILL LIVE TO SEE DAY 28 IN A
HUGE CHALLENGE.
>> NICE JOB BOTH OF YOU.
>> GOOD JOB, JASON.
>> NICE.
>> Jeff: JASON, COME ON OVER.
JASON, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER
27, AND I KNOW HOW TOUGH THESE
DAYS HAVE BEEN, SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT TONIGHT AND BECOME THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
IT WILL NOT BE YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> THANKFULLY WE BEAT AUBRY, AND
WINNING IMMUNITY, IT LETS US
PLAY OUR IDOL AS A SUPER IDOL,
SO SCOT, TAI AND I, NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS, US THREE ARE SAFE.
AND FROM HERE ON OUT WE'RE
UNSTOPPABLE.
>> THAT WAS AMAZING.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> YOU WERE SO STABLE.
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
>> IT WAS AMAZING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
I COULD NOT MOVE THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
WE GOT IT.
>> WE GOT IT.
>> THE WHOLE THING, ONE OF US
HAD TO.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
SHE WAS A HELL OF AN OPPONENT ON
THAT ONE.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S GONE.
>> IT WENT BETTER THAN I EVER
COULD HAVE DREAMED.
WE WENT THERE KNOWING WE
COULDN'T LET AUBRY WIN IMMUNITY.
FINALLY CYDNEY WENT DOWN AND IT
WAS BETWEEN AUBRY AND I, AND I
WON.
AND THAT'S HUGE.
>> YOU AND SCOT WILL NOT LEAVE
TONIGHT AND I AM NOT EITHER.
WE HAVE A SUPER IDOL.
WE'RE STAYING.
>> YEAH.
>> I HAVE THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE
AND WE HAVE TWO HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOLS, WHICH COMBINE BECOME THE
SUPER IDOL.
WHAT'S SO GREAT ABOUT THE SUPER
IDOL IS WE CAN PLAY IT AFTER THE
VOTE IS READ.
AND NO ONE BUT THE THREE OF US
KNOWS THAT.
SO AUBRY'S GOING HOME, AND
THERE'S NOTHING SHE CAN DO.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING?
>> WELSH -- WELL, EVERYONE WANTS
TO GET RID OF TAI'S IDOL.
>> JEWELBACK OUR LITTLE DOUBLE
AGENT, IS COMING OVER AND
TELLING US THE GIRLS ARE VOTING
FOR TAI, AND THAT'S FINE.
WE'LL JUST PLAY THE SUPER ID.L.
AND SAVE HIM, BUT WHAT THEY
DON'T KNOW IS WE'RE GOING AFTER
AUBRY.
THAT'S A STRATEGIC MOVE, BECAUSE
SHE'S VERY SMART, SHE'S VERY
SAVVY, PLUS SHE'S TOUGH.
AND THAT'S ANOTHER REASON FOR
HER TO GO, BECAUSE SHE IS SUCH A
THREAT IN THE CHALLENGES.
>> YOU'RE KIND OF PLAYING BOTH
SIDES, WHICH WE UNDERSTAND, BUT
YOU COME WITH US AND THEN WE
HAVE THE NUMBERS, WE KNOW WE
CAN'T BEAT TAI EITHER, SO WE
EVENTUALLY HAVE TO BLINDSIDE
HIM.
>> WHEN HE DOESN'T WIN AN
IMMUNITY.
>> AND THEN ONCE THAT HAPPEN,
WE'RE GOING FINAL THREE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M STOKED RIGHT NOW.
THE GIRLS AND MYSELF ARE GOING
TO VOTE FOR TAI AND FLUSH HIS
IDOL.
AND SCOT AND JASON ARE AREN'T
REALLY TOO WORRIED ABOUT THAT
BECAUSE AT SOME POINT THEY WANT
TAI GONE ANYWAY.
THEY'D RATHER GO TO THE FINAL
THREE WITH ME, AND THAT WOULD BE
AWESOME BECAUSE THEY HAVE RUINED
RELATIONSHIPS WITH ALMOST EVERY
SINGLE PERSON OUT HERE, AND
THAT'S THE KIND OF PEOPLE YOU
WANT TO STICK WITH AT THE END OF
THIS GAME.
>> WE NEED TO SPLIT UP SCOT AND
JASON, WHICH ARE THE POWER
PLAYERS RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M DOWN FOR IT.
>> I'M DEFINITELY THINKING SCOT.
>> WITH THE GIRL, THE GUYS ARE
JUST TOO DAMN POWERFUL.
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY THE GET
ONE OF THEM OUT.
I THINK WE SHOULD TRY THE BLIND
SIDE SCOT BECAUSE HE'S JUST SO
CONFIDENT IT'S RIDICULOUS.
HE'S DEFINITELY GOTTEN A LOT
COCKER SINCE HE FOUND THE IDOL
WITH JASON.
I'M LIKE, SIMMER DOWN, YOU WOULD
NOT HAVE THAT WITHOUT ME, SO
SHUT UP.
>> WE NEED TO FIND A CRACK
SOMEHOW.
>> HE AND I HAVE BEEN LIKE
PEOPLE ON CONNECTIONS IN
CRAIGSLIST ALL GAME.
>> AT THIS POINT THE GUYS ARE IN
A REALLY STRONG POSITION, BUT I
FEEL LIKE I HAVE SOME KIND OF
CONNECTION WITH TAI.
I THINK TAI IS SOMEONE WHO WANTS
TO BE TRUE TO HIMSELF.
AND TAI'S NATURAL STATE IS NOT
WITH JASON AND SCOT.
AND I THINK HE'S SMART ENOUGH TO
KNOW THAT HE CAN'T BE THAT
INCONGRUENT AT THE END OF THE
DAY.
>> WHATEVER YOU SAY I'M DOWN
FOR.
>> OKAY.
>> THEY DON'T WANT ME TO TALK TO
YOU AT ALL BECAUSE THEY WANT US
TO VOTE FIVE AT YOU, BUT I DON'T
WANT YOU TO GO.
I WANT TO TAKE OUT SCOT.
I KNOW CYDNEY IS FULLY ON BOARD.
I KNOW THAT JOE WOULD BE FULLY
ON BOARD.
I'M WORKING.
>> I'M VERY TORN ABOUT THIS
VOTE.
THE BIG THING IS WHERE IT'S
GOING TO PUT ME AT THE END.
>> CYDNEY THINKS WE SHOULD STICK
WITH OUR PEOPLE.
>> BUT SCOT AND JASON, I'M GOING
TO BREAK UP THAT DUO.
>> WHO DO YOU WANT IT TO BE?
WHAT'S BETTER FOR YOU?
>> MY HEART SAYS, YOU KNOW, I'D
LIKE TO WORK WITH AUBRY, AND MY
INSTINCT IS TO TRUST HER, BUT MY
BRAIN IS TELLING ME THE STAY
WITH THE BOYS BECAUSE THEY'VE
PISSED OFF A LOT OF PEOPLE, AND
IF THE THREE OF US GO TO THE
FINAL THREE, MAYBE I HAVE A GOOD
CHANCE AT BEATING THEM.
>> I'M RELYING ON YOU PUTTING
YOURSELF OUT THERE.
I WANT YOU TO BE COMFORTABLE.
THIS IS YOUR GAME.
YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MOVE.
AND I'M TELLING YOU, YOU HAVE
THREE PEOPLE BEHIND YOU.
I'M POSITIVE.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
IF I FIGURE SOMETHING OUT, I
WILL LET YOU KNOW.
>> THIS IS A HUGE VOTE.
AND TAI HOLDS ALL OF THE KEYS IN
THIS GAME.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT HE'S
GOING TO DO.
>> WE'RE VOTING FOR SCOT?
>> I'M GOOD.
I'M VOTING FOR SCOT.
>> WE KNOW WHO WE'RE VOTING FOR.
>> NO QUESTION.
AUBRY.
>> THEY'RE PROBABLY GOING TO
VOTE YOU.
WAIT UNTIL THE VOTE IS READ, AND
THEN WHOEVER IS VOTED OUT, BAM,
SUPER IDOL.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> HERE YOU GO, BUD.
>> IF ANYTHING HAPPENS YOU PLAY
IT, IF NOT WE GIVE IT BACK.
>> AT THIS POINT I TRULY DON'T
KNOW WHICH WAY I'M LEANING, BUT
I'M IN THE HERE THE MAKE GOOD
FRIENDS.
I'M HERE TO WIN THAT $1 MILLION.
SO I JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME, AND I HAVE
TO COMMIT TO IT, BECAUSE AFTER
THAT THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
>> Sarah: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
NEAL, NICK.
AND DEBBIE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
MICHELE, A LOT WENT DOWN LAST
TRIBAL.
IT WAS A PRETTY BIG DISPLAY OF
IDOL POWER FROM JASON, TAI AND
SCOT.
>> YEAH, THEY MADE A BIG SHOW OF
IT, AND YOU NEVER KNOW WHOSE
HAND THOSE IDOLS ARE GOING THE
LIE INCH IT'S NERVE-RACKING.
>> Jeff: SCOT, YOU'RE A FORMER
ATHLETE.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
MAKE A STATEMENT IN THE PRESS,
YOU ARE ENCOURAGING YOUR
TEAMMATES, BUT YOU'RE ALSO
SAYING TO THE OPPONENT, BRING
IT.
>> IT WAS ALMOST A LITTLE BIT OF
TRASH TALKING.
AND WE'RE PRETTY MUCH DOING THE
SAME THING TONIGHT.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> Jeff: JASON, YOU'RE
NODDING.
JUST LOVING THIS.
>> I LOVE IT.
YOU KNOW, WE PUT UP SOME
PSYCHOLOGICAL WARFARE.
IT WORKED.
IT BROKE DEBBIE UNFORTUNATELY,
AND NEW THEY HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHICH ONE OF THEIR TONE CUT
AGAIN BECAUSE THEY CAN'T CUT US.
IT'S EITHER THEY DECIDE OR WE
DECIDE.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, IT'S GOT TO BE
A LITTLE FRUSTRATING TO HEAR,
THAT EVEN THOUGH YOU HIGH
APPRECIATE IT AS FAN.
>> I MEAN, WITH THESE THREE IT'S
LIKE YOU KEEP RUNNING INTO A
WALL, TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THE HECK IS GOING TO HAPPEN, AND
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW.
>> WE TRIED TO TELL YOU WHAT WAS
HAPPENING.
WE DIDN'T GET A RESPONSE.
WE ASKED YOU FOR A DEAL, AND
YOU...
>> EVERYONE HERE SHOULD KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE DOING,
BECAUSE WE'VE NEVER HID
ANYTHING.
>> NO, WE SAY WE'RE GOING TO DO
SOMETHING, AND WE DO IT.
>> Jeff: JILLIAN, A LITTLE
UNNERVING WHEN THE THREE OF THEM
SAY, I'M TELLING YOU, IT'S ONE
OF THE FIVE OF YOU.
>> OF COURSE.
THE ONLY PERSON WHO IS TRULY
SAFE HERE IS JASON, BUT THE FACT
THAT ALL THESE IDOLS WERE
BROUGHT TO EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
HAS MADE EVERYONE REALLY, REALLY
WANT THE PLAY.
>> Jeff: CYDNEY, A LITTLE
NERVOUS COULD BE YOU?
>> TONIGHT I'M DEFINITELY
NERVOUS.
JASON AND SCOT ARE A LITTLE
SALTY THAT I LEFT THEM AND WENT
TO ANOTHER SHIP.
>> Jeff: SO CYDNEY, WHAT DO
YOU DO TODAY?
YOU DON'T WANT IT TO BE YOU.
YOU'RE 27 DAYS.
YOU'RE CLOSE.
>> YEAH.
SINCE WE ARE THIS CLOSE,
EVERYBODY NEEDS TO TAKE INTO
ACCOUNT, WHO IS THEIR WEST --
BEST BET TO GO IN CHALLENGES.
I HAVEN'T MADE ANY CHALLENGES.
>> SHE MAKES A VALID POINT, BUT
SHE'S ALSO FORGOT, THE PEOPLE
THAT HAVE BEEN WOMEN IN THE
CHALLENGES AREN'T GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
YOU AND TAI.
>> BING YORK AND NEITHER IS
SCOT.
>> Jeff: TAI, WHAT'S GOING ON
IN YOUR MIND, BECAUSE YOU SEEM
LESS TALKATIVE TONIGHT.
ARE YOU UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THE
BOASTING?
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I DO IN MY
PERSONAL LIFE, BUT THIS IS WAR.
AND I'M COMMITTED TO THESE GUYS.
AND I GOT TO DO EVERYTHING TO
ADVANCE MY GAME.
>> HE HAS STEPPED UP FOR OUR
ALLIANCE TIME AND TIME AGAIN.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, TALK ABOUT THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
YOU PUT UP A MASSIVE EFFORT
AGAINST JASON.
WAS THAT A WAY OF SAYING, I'M
NOT JUST A BRAIN?
>> I THINK IT WAS, JEFF.
LIKE WHEN AGAIN IN MY LIFE AM I
GOING TO HAVE AN NBA PLAYER ON
ONE SIDE, A KICK-AS VETERAN ON
THE OTHER WHO IS STARING ME DOWN
AND SPITTING AND I'M SPITTING
BACK AT HIM LIKE A DERANGED
LLAMA.
IT'S NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN
AGAIN.
WE WERE PUT ENTER A GROUP,
BRAINS, BRAWN AND BEAUTY, BUT I
THINK THAT ONLY SCRATCHES THE
SURFACE OF WHO ALL OF THESE
PEOPLE ARE.
AND IT WAS JUST A MOMENT TODAY
TO BE STANDING UP THERE WITH A
BRAWN AND THEN THERE WAS JUST
THAT... IT'S OVER.
>> BUT TODAY WASN'T NEW.
SHE'S BEEN GIVING GREAT EFFORT
IN EVERY FACET OF THE GAME THUS
FAR.
>> SHE'S BEEN KICKING BUTT THE
ENTIRE TIME SHE'S BEEN HERE.
THIS THERE'S AS MUCH BRAWN IN
HER AS THERE IS IN ME.
>> Jeff: MICHELE, IT'S AMAZING
HOW MANY OF THESE CHALLENGES ARE
A METAPHOR FOR THE GAME.
YOU HAD IT AND THEN IT'S OVER.
>> YEAH.
EVERYTHING IN THIS GAME CAN
HAPPEN IN A MOMENT, AND YOU
NEVER KNOW WHEN THAT MOMENT IS,
BUT YOU BETTER BE ON THE RIGHT
SIDE OF THE MOMENT WHEN IT
HAPPENS.
>> THEM SAYING SINCE WE WALKED
IN HERE, IF YOU CAUGHT WIND OF
WHAT'S GOING ON, IT'S SMARTER TO
BE ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THIS.
SO MIGHT AS WELL JUMP ON BOARD
THE TRAIN, OTHERWISE THE WORLD'S
GOING TO BE DICTATED FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MICHELE, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IS ONLY BECAUSE YOU ARE
SUCH A GREAT COMPETITOR.
>> PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL BE ASKED THE LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TAI.
AUBRY.
SCOT.
TAI.
TWO VOTES TAI.
AUBRY.
TWO VOTES TAI, TWO VOTES AUBRY.
ONE VOTE SCOT.
SCOT.
TWO VOTES SCOT.
THAT'S THREE VOALTS SCOT, TWO
VOTES TAI, TWO VOTES AUBRY.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
NINTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, SCOT.
>> NO?
WOW.
SCOTT, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, ONCE AGAIN, JUST WHEN YOU
THINK YOU'RE SAFE, OOP, THERE
GOES ANOTHER BLIND SIDE.
12 DAYS LEFT, SHOULD MAKE FOR A
VERY INTERESTING FINISH.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," AFTER BETRAYING
JASON, TAI'S ON TOP OF THE
WORLD.
>> I HAVE POWER NOW.
>> BUT JASON AND JULIA ARE OUT
FOR BLOOD.
>> THIS GAME IS DESIGNED TO BE
VICIOUS.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT NUMBERS.
>> TAI MADE ME ANGRY.
>> REALLY I JUST WANT REVENGE
RIGHT NOW.
>> JASON WON IMMUNITY AND HE
SAID, HERE, TAKE THIS.
I TRUST YOU.
OBVIOUSLY WE COULDN'T TRUST TAI
SO THE PLAN DIDN'T WORK, SO
THAT'S A BAD FEELING FOR ME
BECAUSE I'VE GOT AN IDOL IN MY
POCKET THAT BELONGS TO JASON AND
IT SHOULD BE WITH HIM, BUT IT'S
A GOOD PLAY BY TAI.
AND I GOT BLINDSIDED.
AND I'M OUT.