>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... YOU HAVE TWO
MINUTES TO SALVAGE WHATEVER YOU
CAN OFF THIS BOAT.
18 NEW CASTAWAYS DIVIDED INTO
THREE TRIBES.
THE BRAINS TRIBE HAS A TON OF
KNOWLEDGE.
>> I WORKED FOR THE GOVERNMENT
DOING DATA ANALYSIS.
>> Jeff: NO ONE'S RESUME WAS
LONGER THAN DEBBIE'S.
>> I'M A CAPTAIN, CIVIL AIR
PATROL.
I HAVE EXTENSIVE TRAINING.
>> BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
>> Jeff: BUT IT DIDN'T IMPRESS
HER TRIBE.
>> SHE ANNOYS EVERYBODY TO
DEATH.
>> Jeff: THE BEAUTY TRIBE, THE
WOMEN THOUGHT THEY COULD USE TY.
>> TY'S PERFECT TO TAKE ALONG
WITH US.
>> BY TAI GOT CAUGHT LOOKING FOR
A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, MAKING
HIMSELF THE ODD MAN OUT.
>> I DON'T FIT IN, SO I FEEL
LIKE I'M IN TROUBLE.
>> Anchor: THE BRAWN TRIBE WAS
FLECKING THEIR MUSCLE, BUT
ALECIA COULDN'T KEEP UP.
>> SHE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> HARD SUN.
MY SHOULDERS ARE FRIED.
>> IT'S SO HOT OUT HERE, IT
SCRAMBLES YOUR BRAIN.
>> Jeff: BUT AUBRY WASN'T THE
ONLY ONE LOSING HER MIND.
>> I HAVE A BUG IN MY EAR.
>> IT HURTS SO BAD.
>> I SEE IT.
EW!
>> Jeff: AT FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, DARNELL AND ALECIA
WERE A MESS, EXPOSING BRAWN'S
WEAKNESS.
THE BRAWN TRIBE GOES TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, ALECIA FOUGHT
TO STAY IN THE GAME.
>> I'LL WORK MY BUTT OFF IN
CHALLENGES, AND I WILL STEP UP.
>> Jeff: HER TRIBE GAVE HER
ANOTHER CHANCE, SENDING DARNELL
HOME.
DARNELL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
THERE WAS A THEME TO TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO TALK THE
TALK, YOU BETTER BE ABLE TO WALK
THE WALK.
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> LET'S NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, I'M
REALLY GOING TO STEP IT UP.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE STILL HERE,
SWEETHEART.
>> ALECIA, NOW DO YOU TRUST US?
>> YES.
>> NOW WE CAN TRUST YOU?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I WAS A LITTLE NERVOUS THERE
FOR A MINUTE.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE GOING TO TRY
AND VOTE ME OUT TONIGHT.
FORTUNATELY DARNELL ENDED UP
GOING HOME.
BUT WHAT THREW ME OFF, IS IF YOU
GUYS WANT ME HERE, WHY ARE YOU
TALKING SO MUCH CRAP TO ME IN
TROUBLE.
I ALMOST WONDER, I COULD BE
WRONG, BUT I SAW JENNY AND JASON
WHISPERING DURING TRIBAL.
AT ONE POINT I THOUGHT I HEARD
SOMEONE SAY, "I CHANGED MY
MIND."
MAYBE THEY WERE GOING TO VOTE ME
OUT.
>> I'M JUST REALLY CONFUSED AT
THIS POINT.
>> I AM GOING TO CHOP MY FINGER
OFF.
>> I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA.
>> THE TRUTH IS BLONDE WAS THIS
CLOSE TO GOING HOME TONIGHT, SO
SHE SHOULD BE THANKING HER LUCKY
STARS SHE HAS TO SPEND THREE
MORE DAYS HERE OR HOWEVER LONG,
BECAUSE I'LL BE HONEST, SHE'S
DRIVING ME NUTS.
>> TO BE HONEST, WE STARTED TO
RECONSIDER OUR VOTE.
SCOT AND I ARE LIKE, ARE WE
DOING THE RIGHT THING?
>> WE ALMOST GOT IT, GUYS.
WE HAD AN.
BER AND IT WENT OUT, BUT WE
ALMOST GOT IT.
>> EMBRYO?
>> ME AND MY WORDS.
>> SHE'S JUST SO DUMB.
I MEAN, END OF THE DAY, SHE'S
NEXT.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
IT IS.
>> WOW.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT MY
STANDING IS WITH THE TRIBE.
SO I WANT DESPERATELY TO GO OUT
AND LOOK FOR THAT ADOLL, BUT I
GOT CAUGHT THE FIRST DAY, AND I
DON'T WANT TO PUT A TARGET ON MY
BACK.
I SAY I WENT TO GET WATER.
I'M GOING TO GO.
I'LL GO REALLY FAST.
I WANT TO GO BACK TO WHERE I WAS
LOOKING THE FIRST TIME BECAUSE I
THINK THAT'S NOSE OBVIOUS PLACE.
WHAT DID I MISS?
DID I PICK OUT THIS ONE?
YEAH, I DID PICK OUT THIS ONE.
IT'S GOT TO BE SOMEWHERE HERE.
RED ANTS, RED ANT, RED ANTS.
OH, NO FREAKING WAY.
NO FREAKING WAY.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNEW IT!
THE IDOL IS BURIED AT THE FOOT
OF THIS TREE.
IN WAY.
IT'S THE IDOL.
WHAT IS THIS?
CONGRATULATION, YOU HAVE FOUND
THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
FIRST YOU WILL NEED A KEY TO
OPEN THIS BOX.
FOLLOW THE MAP TO THE TREE ON
THE MAP.
THE KEY IS JUST OUTSIDE OF YOUR
REACH.
FIRST YOU HAVE TO GET HIGH
ENOUGH.
DAMN, THAT'S A TRICK THEY'RE
GIVING ME.
I THOUGHT I GOT THE IDOL.
I LOOK UP AND IT'S A CLUE.
OH, NO.
OH, MY GOD, THAT'S A LOT OF
WORK.
I SAID, I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR
ANYTHING.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME I
SPENT ALREADY.
HOPEFULLY THEY'RE STILL AT THE
BEACH.
WHAT IS A BLACK PALM?
DOES IT LOOK DIFFERENTLY?
I SEE IT OVER HERE.
IT'S HIGH.
IT'S WAY ON TOP OF THE PALM
TREE.
SO I'M GOING TO HAVE TO BITE THE
BULLET AND JUST GO FOR IT.
SLOWLY.
DON'T GO DOWN WHATEVER YOU DO.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS SO HIGH UP.
CAN I DOAIT?
OH, DEFINITELY TESTING ME.
OH, ALMOST THERE.
I CAN DO IT.
OH, NO.
I'M NOT DOING SO WELL.
THE PALM TREE IS LIKE SAND PAPER
SANDING BOTH MY THIGHS.
MY WHOLE CHEST IS BURNING.
THE BOTTOM OF MY FOOT IS
BLEEDING.
I'M THINKING, I CANNOT GET THE
IDOL.
I HAVE TO GET BACK BECAUSE I'VE
BEEN GONE TOO LONG NOW.
I HAVE TO GET BACK ANOTHER DAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED THAT WE WON
KEROSENE.
WANT TO DO THE HONORS?
>> SURE.
I WAS A BIT OF A PYROMANIAC AS A
KID.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> YEAH.
>> WHOA.
[CLAPPING]
>> OKAY, NEXT TIME A LITTLE LESS
KEROSENE.
>> IT FEELS SO AMAZING THAT THE
BRAINS TRIBE WON THE VERY FIRST
CHALLENGE OF THIS GAME.
WE'VE BEEN FEELING REALLY
COHESIVE AND TIGHT, AND THIS
VICTORY REALLY HAS SOLIDIFIED US
EVEN BETTER.
>> I'M THINKING WE SHOULD PUT ON
ANOTHER POT OF WATER.
>> AGREED.
ELISABETH IS A SMART GIRL,
HOWEVER, THE CHANCES OF THERE
BEING ORGANIC CHEMICALS HERE
THAT WE HAVE TO BOIL TO FITTER
THE WATER ARE VIRTUALLY SLIM TO
NONE.
I DON'T WANT TO TOUCH HER BOILED
WATER.
I'VE BEEN DRINKING THIS FROM THE
GET-GO.
IT'S IN MY REALM OF EXPERIENCE
TO BE ABLE TO JUDGE WATER JUST
BY LOOKING AT IT.
KEEP IN MIND I HAVE 20 YEARS
EXPERIENCE ANALYZING WATER.
>> I UNDERSTAND IT'S NOT CRUCIAL
BECAUSE YOU'RE STILL ALIVE AND
YOU'RE NOT DRINKING ANY TREATED
WATER.
>> NONE, NONE.
>> IT DOESN'T PROVE YOU HAVEN'T
PICKED UP ANY PAIR SITES.
>> JUST BECAUSE I HAVE AN IMMUNE
SYSTEM LIKE A HORSE DOESN'T MEAN
YOU DO.
>> I DON'T.
>> I DO.
I GREW UP AROUND PIGS, HORSE,
CATTLE, EVERYTHING.
>> DEBBIE MARCHES TO THE BEAT OF
HER OWN DRUM.
WHEN I FIRST SAW HER, DOES SHE
HAVE 30 CATS OR 40 CATS?
AND THE QUESTION, THE ANSWER IS
PROBABLY 40 CATS AT HER HOUSE
RIGHT NOW.
>> I ALWAYS TELL PEOPLE, WHEN I
PERSONAL TRAIN THEM, I SAY,
LOOK, JUST BECAUSE I CAN RUN TEN
MILES DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN OR
YOU SHOULD.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT NEED TO
LOSE A LOT OF WEIGHT SHOULD JUST
WALK, DON'T YOU AGREE?
>> OH, YEAH, STAY ACTIVE.
JOGGING AND ALSO WOMEN WITH
BOOBS SHOULD NOT BE RUNNING.
>> NUMBER ONE PERSONAL TRAINER.
NUMBER TWO, CHEMIST.
WHAT ELSE?
>> SHE RAISES TURTLES.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S A JOB,
THOUGH.
THAT'S A HOBBY.
I THINK DEBBIE WANTS TO PROVE
HOW STRONG AND COMPETENT AND
CAPABLE SHE IS.
>> WOW.
>> BUT SHE DOESN'T REALIZE THAT
ALL TALK, IF IT'S NOT BACKED UP
WITH ANYTHING, ISN'T GOING TO
GET HER ANYWHERE.
>> SO I THINK IT'S JUST YOU'VE
GOT GOOD HAND-EYE COORDINATION
OR YOU DON'T.
>> YEAH.
YOU APPARENTLY HAVE AMAZING
HAND-EYE COORDINATION.
>> I THINK I HAVE FAIRLY GOOD.
>> DEBBIE IS NOT EXHIBITING MUCH
GAME PLAY WHATSOEVER, SO SHE'S
THE PERSON YOU WANT ON YOUR
TEAM.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT, A BRAIN TO
HAVE NO GAME.
I'M KEEPING DEBBIE AROUND AS
LONG AS I CAN.
>> THIS IS BREAKFAST SUGAR.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE EATING
CINNAMON TOAST CRUNCH.
>> YOU REALLY HAVE THE APPETITE
OF A CHILD.
>> CUTE.
>> YOU LIKE THAT?
>> VERY CHILD-LIKE.
LOOK AT THE MAN HOLDING THAT.
I'M PAYING THEM A COMPLIMENT.
TRUST ME, IT IS.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE SWEET, NEXT TO
YOU.
>> IF I WANT TO GET THE IDOL, I
HAVE A HUGE AMOUNT OF WORK, BUT
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GO ABOUT
DOING IT.
SO I THINK I'M GOING TO LAY LOW
BECAUSE I THINK MAYBE MY CHARM,
MY PERSONALITY WILL HELP ME
CONNECT WITH THE PEOPLE IN MY
TRIBE.
>>I MISSED YOU LAST NIGHT.
MY BOYFRIEND LIKES THAT.
>> HE'S LIKE, HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> WHERE I'M FROM YOU DON'T SEE
TAI.
HE'S NOT THE AVERAGE COUNTRY
GUY.
FIRST NIGHT I WAS HERE, TAI,
HEY, MAN, I'M COLD, CAN I CUDDLE
YOU TO WARM UP.
YEAH, MAN, YOU CAN HOLD ME THE
WARM UP.
THERE IS NO SUCH THING IN
HOMOPHOBE IN THIS GUY RIGHT
HERE.
I LIKE HANGING OUT WITH HIM
BECAUSE HE'S ONE OF A KIND FOR
SURE.
>> IT'S A HORNET.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
HE'S JUST LOOKING FOR FOOD.
>> WELL, HE'S GOING TO LOOK FOR
FOOD ON MY FOOT.
>> NO REASON TO KILL ANYTHING.
>> IT'S A FRICKEN BEE, DUBAI.
>> CALEB AND TAI ARE THE MOST
DIFFERENT PEOPLE I'VE MET IN MY
LIFE.
CALEB IS A COUNTRY BOY, A
HUNTER.
>> YOU'D GET MAD AT ME IF I KILL
A BEE?
>> YEAH.
>> TAI IS A GARDENER WHO IS SO
CONCERNED ABOUT ANIMALS AND THE
ENVIRONMENT.
>> IT WAS HERE BEFORE YOU MOVED.
YOU MOVED.
>> IT'S MY HOUSE
HE NEEDS TO GO SOMEWHERE.
>> THEY ARE TWO TOTALLY
DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES THAT YOU
WOULDN'T THINK CONNECT, BUT
SOMEHOW THEY GET EACH OTHER.
>> CALEB, I DARE YOU.
>> OH, YOU DARED ME.
>> OH, BOY.
>> YOU HAVE TO USE YOUR MOUTH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THERE'S THE BALL.
NO, NOT FOR YOU?
IT'S PROTEIN, MY FRIEND.
>> PROTEIN MY FOOT.
>> THE BROMANCE IS REAL OUT
HERE.
THEY BICKER LIKE A MARRY COUPLE
AND THEN THEY KISS AND MAKE UP.
>> TAKE THE WHOLE THING.
GET SOME.
>> YOU TRIED TO KISS ME.
>> NO, I DID NOT.
I TRIED TO BITE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I DID THAT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY I DID THAT.
>> I WAS TOTALLY GOING FOR THE
KISS, JUST TO SHOCK HIM AND
TEASE HIM.
I KNOW HE CAN TAKE IT.
I THINK HE LIKES IT A LITTLE
BIT.
I HOPE I DON'T GET YOU IN
TROUBLE.
>> NEXT TIME JUST ASK.
>> OKAY.
>> NO.
>> WE NEED TO KEEP THIS STUFF
COVERED SO IT WILL DRY OUT.
LET ME SEE HOW MUCH FUEL IS
LEFT.
>> WHERE THE HELL DID IT GO?
>> THE RUBBER SEAL?
>> THE SEAL'S GONE.
>> IT'S BEEN LEAKING.
>> WE REALLY NEED THAT.
>> THE KEROSENE IS FRUSTRATING
BECAUSE WE STARTED WITH THIS
LITTLE VERY VALUABLE JAR.
JOE PUT ONE-THIRD OF IT ON THE
FIRE AND THEN LET IT TIP ON ITS
SIDE, AND WE LOST MOST OF IT.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN IF WE
DON'T HAVE OUR FIRE IS WE'RE
GOING TO DRINK FROM THE WELL AND
PEOPLE COULD GET SICK.
>> I KEEP THROWING THINGS DOWN
FOR THESE GUYS TO TRIP OVER.
IT'S WHAT I LOVED ABOUT YOU.
I SAID, GIVE ME THE DISCIPLINED
GUY.
>> THERE IS PRACTICALITY IN
BEING HERE.
I WOULD SAY THE TWO MOST
PRACTICAL PEOPLE ARE DEBBIE AND
ME.
THIS IS WHAT WE HAVE LEFT.
I HAVE A LOT OF SURVIVAL SKILLS
HAVING A MILITARY BACKGROUND,
AND THE REST OF THE PEOPLE, I
THINK THEY HAVE BOOK KNOWLEDGE,
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME THING.
THESE ARE WET.
THESE GUYS ARE SHOT.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME?
>> I WAS PRETTY UPSET ABOUT THE
FIRE BECAUSE I WAS DYING FOR
SOME FRESHLY BOILED WATER, AND
JOE WASTED A LOT OF KEROSENE AND
DESTROYED MOST OF THE REST.
>> MAYBE IF WE DROP A SMOKING
EMBER INTO SOME KINDLE.
>> I'M TAKING CARE OF IT, LIZ,
OKAY.
LIZ IS BECOMING KIND OF A PAIN
IN A BUTT.
SHE KNOWS EVERYTHING ABOUT
EVERYTHING.
IT'S LIKE, COME ON ALREADY,
PLEASE.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO KILL ANY
BACTERIA.
>> THERE'S PATHOGENS IN IT.
PATHOGENS MIGHT BITE.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
EVERYTHING LIZ KNOWS IS BOOK
KNOWLEDGE FROM STRINGING
TOGETHER A ROD TO GET COCONUTS
TO SPRINKLING ANT DUST TO
PREVENT ANT ATTACKS TO MAKING
WATER FILTER THINGS THAT DON'T
WORK.
IT'S LIKE I'M AT KINDERGARTEN
CAMP AND IT'S JUST IRRITATING.
>> I'M FEELING EMOTIONAL JUST
BECAUSE I'M PHYSICALLY VERY WEAK
RIGHT NOW.
AND JOE DOESN'T SEEM TO CARE OR
APPRECIATE THAT I REALLY NEED A
FIRE GOING.
I HATE BEING EMOTIONAL.
I HATE ALLOWING MYSELF TO NOT DO
THE LOGICAL THING AT EVERY GIVEN
POINT.
I KNOW THAT I'M CAPABLE OF BEING
PATIENT AND CALM UNTIL I CAN GET
SOME WATER IN ME.
SO I JUST NEED TO LIKE HIDE
MYSELF FOR A LITTLE BIT UNTIL
THE FIRE IS GOING.
>> I'M TIRED.
I JUST HAVE NO ENERGY BECAUSE I
HAVE NO FUEL.
>> I'M SUCKING ALL THE WAY
AROUND.
>> EVERYTHING IS GOING WRONG FOR
THE BRAWN TRIBE.
WE CAN'T MAKE A FIRE.
WE DON'T HAVE FRESH WIRE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
EFFECT.
WE MIGHT LOOK BRAWNY.
WE ARE WEAKLINGS AT THIS POINT,
WEAKLINGS.
>> DAMN, YOU GOT BLISTERS.
>> BUBBLES.
I THOUGHT IT WAS SWEAT.
REALLY BAD.
>> MY SHOULDERS ARE FRIED.
MY SHINS ARE FRIED.
MY THIGHS ARE FRIED.
BUT I WAS IN IRAQ AND
AFGHANISTAN, SO I CAN LIVE WITH
IT.
I CAN EMBRACE THE SUCK OF.
THIS I'M USED TO THE SUCK.
I JUST KEEP CHALKING IT UP TO
ANOTHER HORRIBLE DAY.
LET'S MOVE ON.
BUT FOR NOW I NEED THE STAY IN
THE SHADE.
>> AT THIS POINT I KIND OF FEEL
LIKE I'M AT THE BOTTOM, BUT I
DON'T BELIEVE IN QUITTING.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN GIVING UP.
SO I NEED TO SHOW THEM WHY THEY
SHOULD KEEP ME IN THE GAME.
AND I'M GOING TO KEEP TRYING
UNTIL I SEE FLAMES.
>> WHY IS SHE TRYING TO DO THAT?
>> I THINK SHE'S JUST WORRIED.
>> DON'T DOUBT HER RIGHT NOW.
>> NOT ONE THING HAS GONE RIGHT.
WE'RE HERE IN MISERY LAUGHING
OUR ASSES OFF.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I'VE BEEN OVER THERE BY
MYSELF TRYING TO MAKE THE FIRE
ALL DAY.
AND I LOOK OVER, AND THE HIT MAN
AND THE NBA PLAYER ARE HAVING
NAP TIME.
AND IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING.
GOT FIRE.
I GOT FIRE!
IT'S GOING OUT.
>> KEEP BLOWING, KEEP BLOWING,
KEEP BLOWING.
>> THIS IS GOING.
THIS IS GOING.
>> WE NEED BABY STICKS.
THAT'S WHAT WE NEED, BABY
STICKS.
>> GOOD GIRL.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> ONE THING I LOVE ABOUT
ALICIA, SHE'S NOT A QUITTER.
SHE'S TOUGH.
THAT BOOSTED HER SELF-ESTEEM SO
MUCH.
SHE JUST SO BADLY WANTED TO
CONTRIBUTE IN SUCH A HUGE WAY.
WE NEED PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
>> HEAT TONIGHT!
>> THIS FIRE HAS SAVED US.
SCOTT, HERE'S YOUR PIECE.
HERE YOU GO.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> NOW WE HAVE FOOD AND CLEAN
WATER, AND I JUST FEEL LIKE
WE'RE JUST GOING TO GET STRONGER
AND STRONGER, AND THAT'S HUGE.
BECAUSE WE DEFINITELY NEED TO
START WINNING CHALLENGES.
>> WE NAILED IT!
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
BRAIN TRIBE, BEAUTY TRIBE
GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT THE
NEW BRAWN TRIBE.
DARNELL VOTED OUT AT FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES, PLEASE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
GIVE IT UP, LIZ.
>> SORRY TO SEE IT GO.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE CHANCE TO
GET IT BACK.
CALEB.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU WILL
RACE DOWN THE RIVER TO RETRIEVE
A VERY HEAVY LOG.
YOU'LL THEN CARRY IT THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
ONCE YOU REACH THE CRADLE,
YOU'LL UNTIE A BALL AND USE IT
TO KNOCK DOWN TWO TARGETS.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH...
>> OH, FISHING GEAR.
>> Jeff: THE ULTIMATE SURVIVOR
FISHING KIT.
WITH THIS KIT, THAT OCEAN, YOU
SHOULD BE ABLE TO FEED
YOURSELVES.
THERE WILL ALSO BE A BOAT
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH, SMALLER KIT, STILL GETS
THE JOB DONE.
LOSERS, NOTHING BUT A DATE WITH
ME AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
BRAIN TRIBE, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
MEMBER.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT SOMEBODY
OUT.
WHO WILL IT BE?
>> ME.
>> DEBBIE.
>> Jeff: BEAUTY TRIBE, SITTING
SOMEBODY OUT, WHO IS IT GOING TO
BE?
>> ME.
>> Jeff: JULIA.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TAKE A SEAT ON THE
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH
THAT THICK MUD TO YOUR LOG.
CAN'T START UNTYING UNTIL
EVERYBODY IS THERE.
>> JEN, GO.
CALEB, GO.
>> Jeff: BEAUTY OFF TO FAST
START.
THEY'RE UNTYING THE KNOTS TO
RELEASE THAT LOG.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
YOU'RE DOING AWESOME.
>> Jeff: GO!
ONCE YOU HAVE THAT LOG UNTIED,
START MOVING.
>> GOOD JOB, BEAUTY!
>> Jeff: BRAWN OUT, BEAUTY
OUT.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES BRAINS.
>> WAY TO GO, BRAINS.
>> Jeff: THESE LOGS WEIGH
ABOUT 300 POUNDS.
YOU CAN GO OVER, UNDER, FLOAT
IT, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
BRAWN WENT TO THE FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THEY DO NOT WANT TO GO BACK.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DOING SO
AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IT IS BRAWN AND
BEAUTY RIGHT NOW WITH BRAINS
FALLING BEHIND.
>> YOU'VE GOT THIS, GUYS.
GO, BRAINS, GO!
>> Jeff: IT'S A LISTENING
CHALLENGE AND IT IS GOING TO
PUNISH YOU.
>> GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
>> Jeff: NOW YOU GOT TO LIFT
THIS LOG, 300 POUNDS, ON YOUR
SHOULDERS AND CONTINUE ON.
>> BRAINS, GO, BRAINS, MOVE THAT
GRAY MATTER.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER PHYSICALLY
EXHAUSTING CHALLENGE.
IT IS BEAUTY AND BRAWN SIDE BY
SIDE.
BRAINS TRYING TO STAY IN THIS.
GO, BEAUTY.
BEAUTY NOW WORKING ON THAT
SECOND OBSTACLE.
BRAWN NOW HEADING THROUGH THAT
HERE COMES BRAINS.
YOU GOT TO GET THAT LOG THROUGH
THE OBSTACLE.
>> READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE, HEAVE.
>> PULL BACK.
NOW PUSH UP.
LET'S GO.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, HEAVE.
>> Jeff: CALEB TAKES A BIG
FALL.
TAI TAKES A FALL.
BEAUTY FIRST OUT.
BRAWN HUNG UP A LITTLE BIT.
IT IS BEAUTY NOW IN THE LEAD.
NOW YOU HAVE TO UNTIE THAT BALL
THAT YOU NEED TO LAUNCH YOUR
TARGET.
BRAINS NOW CLOSING THE GAP.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS!
>> GO.
GO, GO, GO GO,.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES THE BRAWN
TRIBE.
EVERYBODY IS IN IT NOW.
BEAUTY HAS THEIR BALL.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT TO THE
SLINGSHOT.
GO, BEAUTY!
GOT TO GET THAT ROPE INTO YOUR
SLINGSHOT.
IF YOUR ROPE IS TANGLED, IT WILL
NOT MAKE IT TO THE TARGET.
BRAWN HAS THEIR ROPE FREE.
THEY'RE HEADING OUT.
BRAINS STILL UNTYING THAT ROPE.
BRAWN NOW TO THE PLATFORM.
THE BEAUTY TRIBE IS ALL KNOTTED
UP.
THEY HAD A BIG LEAD, AND THEY
HAVE GIVEN IT AWAY.
BRAINS TRIBE NOW HAS COME BACK.
>> YEAH, BRAIN, YEAH.
GO, GO!
>> Jeff: BEAUTY TRIBE STILL
KNOTTED UP.
THERE GOES A SHOT FOR THE BRAWN
TRIBE. 3
FALLS SHORT.
THERE'S A LEARNING CURVE TO
THIS.
>> CALEB, YOU'RE GOOD.
CALEB, YOU'RE GOOD.
>> Jeff: YOU GOT TO PULL THAT
ROPE BACK IN.
>> HERE WE GO.
NO THERE GOES CALEB.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: THERE'S ONE FOR THE
BEAUTY TRIBE.
ONE MORE.
>> WE GOT TO GET THE ROPE UP.
COME ON.
UP HERE.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: BRAINS TRIBE HAS MADE
UP A LOT OF TIME.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: CALEB LAUNCHES AND
HITS FOR THE BRAINS TRIBE.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
HERE GOES SCOT FOR THE BRAWN
TRIBE.
SCOTT CONNECTS FOR THE BRAWN
ONE TARGET LEFT FOR EACH TRIBE.
EITHER COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
THE BRAIN TRIBE FALLS SHORT.
>> OH, BABY.
>> Jeff: OPENS THE DOOR FOR
THE BEAUTY TRIBE.
CALEB FOR THE WIN.
YES!
BEAUTY WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
IT'S NOW DOWN TO BRAWN AND
BRAINS FOR SECOND PLACE.
IF YOU FUMBLE, IT WILL COST YOU.
I WILL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL.
>> GO.
GET IT.
PUT IT BACK DOWN.
IT'S TANGLED UP.
>> Jeff: THIS SHOT COULD WIN
IT RIGHT HERE FOR THE BRAWN
TRIBE.
JUST MISSES.
BRAWN IS HUSTLING TO GET ANOTHER
SHOT IN.
>> YES!
CALEB!
>> Jeff: BRAIN TRIBE WINS
IMMUNITY AND REWARD, SENDING
BRAWN BACK THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
FOR THE SECOND TIME IN A ROW.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS.
FANTASTIC, BABY.
>> WE TRIED.
>> Jeff: BEAUTY TRIBE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BRAIN TRIBE, SAME RESULT,
IMMUNITY, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BEAUTY, IN ADDITION, THE
ULTIMATE FISHING KIT, THIS
SHOULD CHANGE YOUR LIFE.
COME GET IT, HEAD BACK TO CAMP,
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
BRAIN TRIBE, GOOD WORK FOR YOU,
AS WELL.
COME GET IT.
IT'S A SMALLER FISHING KIT, BUT
IT WILL GET THE JOB DONE.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: GOOD EFFORT.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
NOBODY GOING HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
BRAWN TRIBE, TRIBAL COUNCIL
AGAIN TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY ELSE WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO GO DOWN AS
THE WORST TRIBE IN HISTORY.
LET ME TELL YOU, OUR SHIP IS
SINKING AND WE'RE ON OUR WAY TO
THAT RECORD.
>> I MISSED.
IT HAPPENS.
>> I DON'T CHALK THAT UP TO YOU.
>> I'M IN THE SAYING I'M TAKING
ALL THE BLAME, BUT IF WE
CONNECTED...
>> AND WE DIDN'T.
WE LOST THE CHALLENGE.
WE'RE GOING TO TRIBAL... AGAIN.
FORTUNATELY JASON, CYDNEY, JENNY
AND MICE, WE'RE STRONG.
WE GENUINELY LIKE EACH OTHER.
I WOULD BE SHOCKED IF ONE OF US
TURNED.
THAT LEAVES ALECIA.
>> WE ARE SO WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
ALECIA DOES AND WHAT WE ALLOWED
HER TO DO WAS UNTIE A KNOT.
WE KNOW WHAT SHE BRINGS TO THE
TABLE.
>> BLONDIE, SHE'S A DITZ AND A
HALF, A DITZ.
I'M SURE SHE'S GOT A GOOD HEART,
BUT SHE'S JUST DUMB.
SHE'S ALWAYS CONFUSED.
SHE'S LIKE AN OSTRICH.
SHE'S A BIRD, BUT SHE CAN'T FLY,
SO SHE'S USELESS.
SO YOU GOT TO GET RID OF HER.
>> THERE SHEZ XI GOES.
SHE LOOKED BACK FIVE TIMES.
IT MAKES EVERYBODY ELSE GO,
OKAY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING FOR
SURE.
>> SHE'LL NEVER FIND IT.
>> IT'S LIKE LOOKING FOR A
NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
I'M GETTING A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT TRIBAL TONIGHT BECAUSE NOT
ONCE DID ANY OF THEM ASK ME TO
BE IN AN ALLIANCE WITH THEM, SO
I GUESS THAT'S TELLING ME
SOMETHING.
THERE'S STILL A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL OUT THERE, BUT WHERE IT IS,
NOBODY KNOWS.
>> SHE'S STILL OUT SEARCHING?
>> YEP.
>> SHE'S JUST SO STUPID.
EVERY DAY SHE BLOWS MY MIND A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> OH, BOY.
>> I HAD AN ALLIANCE IN THE
BEGINNING, BUT IT'S FUNNY WHAT
SIX DAYS OUT HERE DOES TO YOU.
YOU REALLY GET TO KNOW PEOPLE
FOR WHO THEY ARE AND WHAT THEY
ARE, AND TO BE HONEST, JASON IS
STARTING TO PISS ME OFF.
I DON'T LIKE HIS ATTITUDE.
HE JUST SITS AROUND AND DOESN'T
DO ANYTHING EXCEPT TALK ABOUT
ALECIA, AND I'M TIRED OF IT.
>> OKAY, BLONDIE.
>> BLONDIE.
>> JENNY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> THAT'S REALLY CLOSE.
>> IT LOOK LIKE IT LANDED IN
THERE.
>> BALLOONDY.
>> ALECIA, WHAT'S THE BEST THING
WE CAN DO?
>> THAT'S NOT THE BEST THING YOU
CAN DO.
WIN A CHALLENGE?
>> NO.
THAT'S NOT IT EITHER.
>> I WAS THINKING, YOU GUYS CAN
DO IT EASY AND HELP ME OUT,
RIGHT?
WE CAN VOTE OUT ONE OF THE GUYS.
>> YES.
>> US GIRLS WILL STAY STRONG.
WE'LL MAKE THE MERGE.
WHEN WE MAKE THE MERGE, THEY GO
AFTER GUYS LIKE THEM, AND
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE AN
ALLIANCE.
SO IF YOU GO US WITH, WE HAVE A
BETTER CHANCE OF NOT GETTING
PICKED OFF.
>> VERY GOOD POINT.
>> IT'S FUNNY HOW QUICK THINGS
CHANGE BECAUSE I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING HOME, AND THEN JEN'S LIKE,
HEY, LET'S DO AN ALL-GIRLS
ALLIANCE.
>> MY GUT HAS BEEN TELLING ME TO
DO THIS ALL ALONG.
I'VE BEEN IGNORING MY GUT
BECAUSE I GAVE MY WORD.
NOW JASON IS JUST PISSING ME
OFF.
>> HE'S ANNOYING.
WE THINK WE NEED THE GUYS, WHICH
WE DO.
WE CAN KNOCK OFF JASON AND WE'LL
HAVE SCOTT FOR THE NEXT TWO
CHALLENGES.
>> LISTEN, YOU'RE ABSENT MINDED
AND YOU DRIVE ME CRAZY, BUT I
LIKE YOU.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT BIG MOVES.
IF THIS WORKS AND JASON GOES
HOME TONIGHT INSTEAD OF ME, I
WOULD BE REALLY EXCITED.
I MIGHT EVEN THIS A LITTLE HAPPY
DANCE.
I'M GOING TO BE STOKED.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT THEY'RE
TOGETHER.
>> THERE'S IN BREAKING UP OUR
FOUR.
>> I WORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> 100%.
100%.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE GOOD, RIGHT?
>> OF COURSE.
>> HE'S A LITTLE SUSPICIOUS.
THE LAST THING I WANT IS HIM
QUESTIONING...
>> I HAVE THIS THING, THEY CALL
IT LOW-IMPULSE CONTROL.
I CHASE SHINY OBJECTS.
SOMETIMES WHEN I HEAR IDEAS, I
THINK, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
LET'S DO THAT.
THEN I REALIZE BLINDSIDING JASON
IS ALSO ME BLINDSIDING SCOT, AND
I ACTUALLY LIKE SCOT, AND HE
TRUSTS ME.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> I'M CONFUSED.
>> I'M ASKING YOU.
I CAN GO EITHER WAY RIGHT NOW.
LET'S THINK ABOUT IT.
MY GUT WAS TO GO ALL GIRL, BUT
NOW I DON'T KNOW.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME TO...
>> I WAS GETTING AHEAD OF
MYSELF.
WE CAN DO THAT LATER.
I'M LIKE, WHAT IS GOING ON?
LIKE WHEN DID THIS TIDE TURN?
THE GIRLS ARE ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
>> I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE WISHY-WASHY.
>> SHE'S GOT SOME BALLS GOING
BACK AND FORTH LIKE THAT.
EVERY TIME I TURN AROUND
SOMETHING IS GOING ON, BUT ALL I
KNOW IT'S UP IN THE AIR AT THIS
POINT.
AND THAT'S A VERY, VERY
DANGEROUS WAY TO GO TO TRIBAL.
>> Jeff: ALECIA, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL IT WAS YOUR OR DARNELL.
DID YOU FEEL HEAT, OH, GREAT,
NOW IT'S ME.
>> THEY DID SAY I WAS WEAK IN
THE CHALLENGE, BUT SINCE THEN
I'VE DONE WELL AND PULLED MY
WEIGHT AROUND CAMP, SO HOPEFULLY
IT WILL NOT BE ME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: JENNY, SIX DAYS IN,
THERE ARE A LOT OF WAYS TRIBAL
COULD GO TONIGHT.
YOU COULD BE PLAYING THE LONG
GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: OR ALLIANCES TAKE
OVER, OR YOU COULD EASILY SAY
THREE WOMEN, PICK OFF ONE OF THE
THREE GUYS, LET'S STICK
TOGETHER.
>> IT WAS DEFINITELY UP IN THE
AIR AFTER YOU HEAR A COUPLE
DIFFERENT STORIES, YOU HAVE TO
THINK, WOW, THAT MIGHT MAKE
SENSE.
OH, DAMN, THIS ISN'T AS SOLID AS
I THOUGHT.
SO THERE WAS DEFINITELY SOME
BACK AND FORTH, WHAT DO WE DO.
>> Jeff: SCOTT, WHY THE BIG
REACTION?
>> TO HEAR JENNY SAY I WAS UP IN
THE AIR AT CAMP, MY EYEBROWS ARE
UP.
NOW I'M WONDERING.
EN.
>> Jeff: WOW.
JUST LIKE THAT, JASON, THE GAME
TURNS.
>> THAT'S PART OF THIS GAME IS
THAT IT TURNS ON THE DROP OF A
DIME.
IT'S A CLASSIC WHAT HAPPENS
AFTER YOU LOSE CHALLENGE, AND
YOU'RE GETTING READY TO GO THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE QUESTION IS HOW MUCH OF THAT
GETS OUT AND WHO FINDS OUT WHAT
YOU JUST SAID AND THEN YOU COME
TO TRIBAL AND THINGS GET
CONFIRMED.
>> THINGS YOU THINK GET
BUT THE TRUTH IS, YES, IDEAS
WERE THROWN AROUND, BUT YOU GUYS
ALL ASSUME BECAUSE ANOTHER IDEA
WAS DISCUSSED THAT THE PLAN WAS
CHANGED.
>> I DIDN'T THINK ANYTHING HAD
CHANGED UNTIL I JUST HEARD YOU
RIGHT HERE SAY, YEAH, BACK AT
CAMP EVERYTHING WAS UP IN THE
AIR.
AS FAR AS YOU TOLD ME AT CAMP
THIS AFTERNOON, THE PLAN WAS IN.
IT WAS DONE.
>> AT THAT POINT IT WAS.
>> WOW.
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS GOING TO
TURN THAT QUICKLY BECAUSE I
ADMITTED IDEAS WERE DISCUSSED.
>> YOU HAVE AN ALLIANCE, YOU GO
SOMEPLACE TOGETHER AND YOU NEVER
WAIVER.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE'VE
DONE UP TO THIS POINT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ALECIA, WHAT DO YOU TAKE FROM
THAT?
>> THAT SOUNDED LIKE THEY HAD
SOMETHING LOCKED IN AND JENNY
SAID IT'S UP IN THE AIR THAT.
RAISES A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
>> SO WHY NOT LET THIS BE
COMPLETELY HONEST.
ALECIA CAME TO ME AND SAID,
LET'S DO AN ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE.
>> THAT WAS JEN'S IDEA.
>> YOU SAID, JEN...
>> SHE WAS THE ONE TRYING TO GET
US TO HAVE AN ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE.
>> NEW YORK I WAS NOT.
NO I WAS NOT.
>> WHO DID YOU SAY TO THROW ON
THAT CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> JASON.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: THAT'S EVERYTHING
BUSTED RIGHT THERE.
>> AGAIN, IT WAS ALICIA'S IDEA.
>> WHATEVER YOU SAY, JENNY.
>> BUT WHERE IS THAT GOING TO
GET ME?
VOTE ME OUT AND LET'S KEEP
LOSING CHALLENGES.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GREAT IDEA.
VOTE OUT ONE OF THE STRONGER
MEMBERS OF THE TEAM.
>> Jeff: CYD, WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF THIS?
>> I THINK IT'S ABOUT BEING IN
THE WRONG PLACE AT THE WRONG
TIME AND SAYING THE WRONG THING
AT THE WRONG TIME TO THE WRONG
PEOPLE.
I THINK THAT'S WHERE LOYALTY
COMES IN.
THERE IS NO PLACE THE HIDE.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW...
>> IF I BROKE YOUR TRUST, THAT'S
MY BAD.
BUT WHAT I'M ASKING FOR IS A
TRIBE THAT WANTS TO WIN AND NOT
HAVE TO COME BACK HERE.
IF YOU STICK WITH HER, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE BACK HERE.
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG IN
THE CHALLENGE THAT MADE US LOSE,
NOT ONE THING.
>> LET ME ADDRESS SOMETHING.
NEVER IN THIS GAME HAS SOMEONE
WALKED UP TO THEIR ALLIANCE AND
WENT, GUYS, JUST WANT YOU TO
KNOW, I'M CONSIDERING A FLIP.
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU, LET YOU
KNOW HOW THINGS WORK OUT.
IF IT DOESN'T, HEY, WE'RE STILL
GOOD, RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
COOL.
AND THEN GO AWAY.
>> Jeff: JENNY, IS THIS AN
ABSOLUTE...
>> NIGHTMARE?
>> Jeff: NIGHTMARE, YEAH?
>> JEFF, THE PAIN IS THEM NOT
TRUSTING ME.
THAT'S THE PAIN.
BECAUSE FOR THE LAST SIX DAYS I
HAVE GIVEN THEM NO REASON NOT TO
TRUST ME.
ALL OF A SUDDEN ONE PERSON, WHO
BY THE WAY IS AT THE BOTTOM, IS
DOING ALL THIS SCRAMBLING AND
TELLING THEM LIES.
>> I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: HONESTLY I HAVEN'T
LISTENED TO A WORD ALECIA HAS
SAID.
I'VE JUST BEEN LISTENING TO YOU.
FIRST WORDS OUT OF YOUR MOUTH
WERE, YEAH, EVERYTHING'S UP IN
THE AIR, I DON'T KNOW.
MAKE ME GET OVER THAT.
>> OKAY.
MY INTENTIONS WERE NOTHING BUT
GOOD.
I ACTUALLY LIKE ALECIA.
IT WAS TO GIVE HER A GOOD LAST
DAY AND NOT THINK SHE'S GOING
HOME THE MAKE HER COMFORTABLE, I
DIDN'T SEE...
>> LYING TO ME IS NOT GIVING ME
A GOOD LAST DAY.
>> I'M NOT SAYING IT'S THE BEST
DECISION OR RIGHT DECISION.
THAT'S WHO I AM AT A PERSON.
I CARE ABOUT PEOPLE'S FEELINGS.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING I COULD
TAKE BACK, THAT WOULD BE IT.
>> Jeff: SCOTT, WHAT'S YOUR
REACTION WHEN YOU HEAR JENNY
SAY, I'D DO ANYTHING TO TAKE IT
BACK.
I'D DO ANYTHING TO CHANGE IT.
I WISH I COULD.
YOU SEE THAT EMOTION.
DO YOU HAVE EMPATHY AT THAT
POINT?
>> YEAH, I UNDERSTAND
MISSPEAKING.
I'VE DONE IT MYSELF ONCE OR
TWICE.
I REALLY DO THINK THAT IN THE
LONG RUN JENNY WOULD BE BETTER
FOR US PHYSICALLY, MENTALLY,
SO...
>> GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE,
PLEASE.
I'M NOT PERFECT, SCOTT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
OKAY.
PLEASE TRUST THE ORIGINAL
ALLIANCE WE HAD.
NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
I THINK THE FOUR OF US CAN GO
FAR, RIDICULOUSLY FAR.
SO PLEASE BELIEVE ME.
>> Jeff: I DON'T KNOW IF I'VE
EVER SEEN A TRIBAL COUNCIL LIKE
THIS.
>> THAT'S HOW BRAWN DOES IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ALECIA, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JENNY.
ALECIA.
TWO VOTES ALECIA.
JENNY.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES ALECIA,
TWO VOTES JENNY, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
BRAINS VERSUS BRAWN VERSUS
BEAUTY, JENNY.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
GENERALLY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> HEY, GUYS, HOPE YOU WIN LOTS
MORE CHALLENGES.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS A DRAMATIC
EXAMPLE OF HOW QUICKLY THE GAME
CAN CHANGE.
ONE WRONG WORD AND IT GOES FROM
GOOD TO BAD, WHICH MEANS IT CAN
ALSO GO FROM BAD TO GOOD.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," DEBBIE ENLIST A
SOLDIER AND PLANS AN ATTACK.
>> WE NEED TO MOVE WITH A
PURPOSE, JOE, AND WE NEED TO DO
IT NOW.
>> Jeff: WHILE AT THE BRAWN
TRIBE...
>> IDOL TIME, BABY.
>> Jeff: IT'S ALL-OUT WAR FOR
THE IDOL.
>> I TOOK OFF LIKE A BAT OUT OF
HELL.
YOU'RE EITHER GOING TO KEEP UP
OR GET LEFT BEHIND.
>> I AM SHOCKED.
I THOUGHT THE TRIBE WOULD WANT
TO STAY STRONG.
WE CAN WORK OUT OUR PERSONAL
FEELINGS LATER.
AS FAR AS BEING VOTED OUT OF THE
GAME, IT HURTS.
THIS ISN'T WHAT I ENVISIONED.
THIS ISN'T WHAT I CAME OUT HERE
TO DO, BUT I PUSHED MYSELF AND
DONE THINGS I NEVER EXPERIENCED
BEFORE, SO I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO
REGRETS.