Previously on Survivor.
At the last tribal council, there was a rock draw.
Reveal.
Jessica was sent to the jury and willed her legacy advantage to Ken.
Nine are left. Who will be voted out tonight?
That was the worst.
We're still here. I'm still here. We're all still here.
Oh my God.
Tonight was just very emotional to have people pick a rock rather than vote me out of this game.
And then to have Jessica pick the black rock, it's an awful feeling.
I feel guilty and I feel thankful and I just feel awful.
I just watch someone get, everything get ripped because of a rock.
Don't put this all on yourself.
No, we all took the gamble.
We all took, we all made a choice.
I'm really angry at myself.
I burned my idol at tribal for no reason.
And now I find myself in a minority with Hannah, Ken and Adam.
So I need to find some crack somewhere.
Otherwise, the five is just going to pick us off one by one.
Starting with me.
I don't know that I ever had friends who did something as nice as what you did for me tonight.
Bro, I told you.
I told you.
Hey, when I'm with people, I'm with people.
The tribal council was amazing.
I loved it.
Man, I felt like a warrior.
David should freaking go home, bro, because that piss me off.
That piss me off too.
We all know why he did that because he figured it was a 50-50 shot that we'd be screwed.
And now he's screwed.
This vote was all about David and I going to war together.
I definitely won the battle.
We're all five together.
This is my thought.
I'm trying very hard not to be too excited,
but I'm feeling like I'm going to the final five.
Five strong.
Sounds good to me.
10%.
And let's take them all out one by one.
Oh, yeah.
I think I can win this game, and I'm just as happy I can win this game
because I am that David is going to lose it.
I received a gift this morning in my bag.
I got this.
Congratulations, you have found the legacy advantage.
If you are in possession of this note on day 36, you will receive an advantage in the game.
Jess, you are amazing.
Jess told me that she'd give me the advantage if she got voted out.
God, I love that girl.
And she did?
It's big.
There is something to be said about the power of being authentic
and genuine relationships in this game.
Day 36, if I'm still here, I'm going to open this up and see what it brings me,
because I feel like I got a really good shot to give my daughter and I a new life
and a better life and maybe walk in with a million dollars.
Come on, guys.
All right, so we are 31 days into this game.
I think it sounds like a perfect time for love.
No way, dude.
Sunday, say hello to your husband, Jeff.
Jeff, come on out.
No way.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe you're here.
Take it in, Sunday.
What does that feel like?
Like you're with people all the time, but you're, like, alone.
And then to see someone that makes you not alone.
All right, give her a hug.
Take a spot.
Brett, you ready for some love?
Yep.
Here comes your dad, Don.
Don, come on out.
Oh, boy.
Try not to trip.
I'm doing all right.
Look at you.
You're looking great.
Oh, my God.
It's great to see you.
He's going to cry.
I told him I wouldn't cry.
Look at you.
You're a hunk.
This guy is the best guy in the world.
He's been a great friend.
There it is.
Just to see him here, you'll do anything for him.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks, Tess.
I'm going to, I can't believe I'm crying.
I told you guys I wouldn't cry.
You'll lose them.
All right, take your spot back.
Don.
Jay, say hello to your sister, Melanie.
Come on out, Melanie.
Hey, Jaybird.
Don't make fun of me, OK?
You always make fun of me.
You can cry this time.
Oh, my God, what they do to you.
I know.
I'm going to chonch in.
Jay, you can't let go of her.
You keep grabbing her back in close.
I got two halves to my heart, Jeff.
And one is standing right here and one's at home.
And because my mom can't come, so that's my fuel.
That's my heart, Jeff.
My heart.
I'll give me up before I give her up.
Melanie, that's pretty powerful.
Not every brother sister has this relationship.
Well, he just has to know that we love him back home,
and he's not alone.
Not even on this island.
We're all there for him.
All right, Melanie, give him a last hug.
I love you.
Hannah, you ready for some love?
I want to see my mom.
Mom, come on out.
Here comes Liz.
I'm okay.
Wow, you're now comforting your mom.
Wait a minute, this is backwards.
I'm good.
Tell me what's going on, because this is a pretty unique situation
in that the daughter started comforting the mom.
My mom is my hero.
She's the bravest person I know.
She beats cancer.
I know she's... she beats cancer.
So, like, the strength is this woman.
All right, give her one last hug.
I love you so much.
I'm good.
Okay.
Bye.
Adam, you ready for some love?
Yeah.
You have no idea, Jeff.
Evan, come on out.
Here comes Adam's brother, Evan.
Hi.
My mom has stage four lung cancer,
and I don't know what's going on with my mom.
I don't know what's going on at home.
I love you so much.
She's okay.
I'm here.
I'm so proud of you.
Okay.
I love you.
Adam, does it strike you how fast the game can fall away,
and all you're doing right now is feeling love
of someone you know you can trust?
Yeah, I mean, I needed to be here right now.
I needed my brother to come out today,
and if I didn't get that,
it would have been absolutely devastating.
I want you guys all to know, and Evan, they already know this,
but I actually have an advantage in this game
that allows me to steal a reward,
but I can't use it.
Okay?
We're going to win it anyway.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because I can't take you guys away from your loved ones.
I can't do it, you know?
You're a good dude, bro.
You are.
Thank you, Adam.
Give him a hug.
I love you.
David, you ready for some love?
Yeah.
Let's get your dad out here.
Doug, come on out.
I miss you so much.
I'm so sorry to be such a sad.
I swear, I've been crying so much out here.
David, why is it important for you
to have your dad see you out here
in one of the toughest situations anyone will ever find themselves in?
I just want to make him proud.
Oh, you already have.
Thank you.
He has such a joy for life, a passion for life,
and he lives a fearless life,
and I came into this game as this fearful, neurotic oddball,
and when I walk out, I want to walk out as the man my father is.
He's my hero.
And I love you. I love you.
Thanks for coming out, man.
Thanks. Love you.
Ken, let's get your brother out here.
Yeah, buddy.
William, come on out.
Here, little brother.
Wow.
Oh, my God, they're both so handsome.
Ken, can you describe that feeling of security you get
when you put your arm around blood,
somebody you know in this moment will not betray you?
You know, I was asked in second grade to draw a picture
of what you want to be when you grow up,
and it was him in his football uniform.
Wow.
I wanted to be him.
He was my idol, my role model, a father figure,
and now a best friend all rolled into one.
It's...he's my rock.
All right, last love.
Zeke, let's get your dad out here.
Sam, come on out.
Yeah!
Hop on!
Hey, buddy.
Good to see you, man.
I'm so glad to see you, Dad.
It's wonderful.
I love you too, buddy.
Oh, and to your dad.
You're looking great. You're looking strong.
Tell me about this relationship, Dad.
Well, this is my hero.
This is the strong person here.
This is who I look up to and who I model my behavior after.
Wow.
Zeke, that has got to feel great to have your dad say that.
Yeah, I mean, oh, God, I said I wasn't going to cry.
You know, my dad and I, you know, we've not always been super close,
and, you know, it's been in the past couple of years
that we've really made an effort to get to know one another,
and this adventure is about, like,
becoming the person I want to be for the rest of my life,
and it's about forging this relationship
that we're going to have for the rest of our lives.
Hugs.
It's so nice.
Strong like bull.
I'm with you.
Will, let's get your mom out here.
Irene, come on out.
Come on out.
Young William.
High school.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Whoo.
You are so amazing.
God is good.
Whoo.
I remember when you were little,
and I said I'd go anywhere for your smile, even 10 bucks, too.
Well, here I am, 10 bucks, too.
Oh, huh.
I love you, Mom.
All right, so we know the stakes.
The stakes are love.
Let's get to the challenge.
For today's challenge, you're going to be attached to a rope
that is woven through a series of obstacles.
On my go, you are going to race through those obstacles
to the end toward love.
First to finish wins.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Yes.
First person to finish will take their loved one
back to camp with them,
and instead of treating them to your normal day of rice
and maybe a couple of fish,
we're going to do a good old American barbecue.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
I know it's worth playing for.
We're going to draw for spots.
We'll get started.
You're going to watch.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Here we go for reward in the form of love.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Go, Adam!
Get him, Brett!
You have to launch yourself over these obstacles
while threading that rope, giving yourself slack
where you need it,
but making sure you don't get tangled up in the slack.
Ow!
Adam all tied up.
Sunday having a lot of trouble,
Will having a lot of trouble.
It is Ken in the lead.
Jay, right behind.
You got it.
You can do it.
Go, Brett!
Go!
Wow, Jay launches himself.
Here comes Zeke.
He's trying to get in this now.
Yeah, Zeke!
Here comes Hannah out of nowhere.
Hannah's now in it.
Kevin and Jay have moved on to the next obstacle.
Go, Hannah!
Right behind Hannah is Brett, and then Adam.
We got a lot of people in this now.
Yeah!
Zeke makes quick time of that second obstacle.
Zeke now at the third obstacle.
David moving on to the next obstacle.
It is still Sunday, who cannot figure out this challenge,
and Will, who is struggling.
Adam through the second obstacle, moving on to the third.
It is now Ken in the lead.
You've got to dig under that beam.
David back in it.
Good job.
Ken stuck underneath that post.
He had a big lead.
First with your feet!
Jay trying to catch Ken.
Adam is stuck.
He's got half his body through, but just like Ken, it's that booty.
Got this, Adam!
Jay is through now.
Jay in the lead now.
I can't breathe.
Jay is at the final obstacle.
Come on, brother! Come on!
Come on, bud!
Zeke is now going to give Jay a run for his money.
Can he catch him?
We're in there, Zeke!
Keep going, buddy!
Go, go, go, go!
Ken is now in it.
Go, Ken!
Come on, Hannah!
Here comes Hannah!
It's the final thing, Hannah!
David is now at the final obstacle.
Adam is literally stuck and cannot move.
His shot at love is falling away.
Can anybody catch Jay for the win?
I'm sorry, Evan.
I know you're trying, Adam.
It is David, Zeke, Jay, and Ken...
Keep going, brother! I love you!
...who will get to the end first.
Keep going, great-brother!
Zeke throwing himself through the ropes.
Come on, buddy! Come on, Zeke!
Jay, catch him, Zeke!
Jay wins the award...
Damn it!
...in the form of love in a massive challenge.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Jay!
Jay, come on over.
Nice work, Jay.
Thank you, guys.
Melanie, come on over and join Jay.
You are going back to camp with your survivor experience
along with a nice barbecue.
Pick another survivor and their loved one to join you.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I respect each and every one of you as warriors,
but I made a promise in the beginning
that I would never let you down.
I'm going to make sure that I get to the top.
I'm going to be a warrior, but I made a promise
in the beginning of the game to take Will,
so I'll take Will.
Will, come on over.
Mom, come join him.
Oh, I'm liking it.
Jay, pick one more survivor and their loved one.
This is the same reason.
They made a promise to me first before every one of you,
and I have to pick Sunday.
Sunday, come on over.
Jeff, join your woman.
I'm sorry, guys. I truly am.
No, hey.
This is looking like a nice gathering for a barbecue.
I think to even it out, it would be nice to have
one more survivor...
You're not even kidding me, dear.
...and one more loved one.
Jay, please.
You got to.
Oh, my God.
Look at that.
Jay, every single person...
I love you guys, man, but this guy didn't do it.
He could have done it.
And me and Adam have been brawling this whole damn time, man.
Hey.
Come on, man.
Thank you, didn't do it, dude. Thank you.
Adam and your brother, Evan, come on over.
Thank you, you did it.
Thank you.
All right, guys, everybody's going back to camp together.
The only people who will share in the reward part of this
are you guys.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp, enjoy the afternoon.
Loved ones, I'm sorry, you got to go.
No last hugs.
Love you, man.
Love you, David.
I love you, Dad. I'll see you soon.
All right.
Tell everyone back home I love them too,
and I miss everyone.
Love you.
MUSIC
Jay, thank you.
Hey, cheers.
Adam, I expect you for not playing to your advantage.
This whole time Adam has had an advantage to take away a reward,
but when he walked out there and he's like,
listen, I'm not stealing a family visit because that's not right.
For five seconds we saw the soft side of Adam,
so I was like, yo, sometimes I hate you, sometimes I love you,
but at this moment I truly respect you and you're a cool dude.
Should we just sit here?
MUSIC
I've been thinking about you guys every single day.
We've been thinking about you too.
What's going on?
She started having some bad reactions to the chemo pill.
The MEK inhibitor.
Yeah.
Eventually they decided that the side effects that she was having
just weren't worth the potential gain that she might be getting,
so we stopped that pill.
And a couple weeks later they said that infusion wasn't really doing its job.
LAUGHS
Again?
Why is this happening?
So we had her take a break from that.
That's so sad.
And she's doing nothing now?
She's regaining a lot of strength.
OK.
We stopped that about two weeks ago.
Damn it.
Since then she's been so much better.
So much she's been getting better.
She's not getting any treatment.
Not right now.
Nothing can really lighten the load back at home.
It's a very serious situation,
but me and my parents love Survivor as much as Adam does,
and having him out here is such a boon for us.
It drives me and my parents forward, especially my mom.
She's getting so much strength from knowing that he's out here living his dream.
The most important thing she wanted me to let you know is
that she's getting so much of her strength from you.
I know.
She feels you out here.
I know. I feel her.
I'm here to bring joy to my family, to make them proud,
and to give them as much to look forward to as humanly possible.
And the better I do in this game, the longer I last,
and the more that I make my mom happy,
the better I have to stay focused,
and I have to use this as inspiration to continue fighting out here.
So what's up, brother?
We just wanted to say thank you so much.
Hey, man. Don't worry, bro.
You don't know how important this was.
It really, really meant a lot.
True that.
And I'll never forget it.
I don't know if there's ever going to be a way that I can repay you totally,
but I'm giving you the advantage, dude.
Damn, bro.
You for real?
Yeah. No strings attached, nothing.
I just want you to have it.
Yeah, man. Thank you.
We want it out of the board.
Thank you.
I'm playing for so much more than a million dollars in the title of Soul Survivor.
The stakes for me are maybe higher than for anyone who's played this game.
What's the meaning going on on the beach?
Who?
Seeing my mom made me realize that I need to start playing this game,
because despite the moves I made, despite the things that I've done in this game,
people still don't give me the credit I deserve,
and that could ruin my shot at winning this game.
Here's the thing. I think Zeke beats all of us.
He does. He absolutely does.
And by the way, I know I'm a target and everything, but right now, use me for this vote.
Dude, I'm tired of losing people. I want more.
Okay, good. Yeah, great.
Zeke needs to go. Tonight's the night.
It's time to flip the script.
The biggest threat out here is Zeke, and if he gets to the end, he will be any one of us.
It is very risky, but I didn't come here to be dragged as a goat. I came here to play.
So we're going for it, you see?
All right, I love it.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Will telling me that he wants to swing over to our side.
It was like music to my ears, because right now, you know, I'm an endangered species,
but I think Will's telling the truth.
So there's a really good chance that Zeke is going home tonight.
Devil's in the mud!
Fish and fire!
Come on in, guys.
You guys ready to get to today's immunity challenge?
Yeah.
Jay, you know what has to happen first.
I know.
I must take it back.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you will each have two handles that you will use to keep tension on a steel bar.
If at any point you release that tension, the bar will drop, the tile will break, you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing wins immunity, guaranteed a one in eight shot at winning this game.
Losers, tribal council, somebody will become the fifth member of our jury.
Drop your spots, we'll get started.
All right, everybody grab your handles.
Get some tension on that bar.
Let's go.
Three, two, one.
And this challenge is on.
There is absolutely no wiggle room in this challenge.
The slightest slip and you're done.
It could happen quickly.
You start to feel your hands shake a little.
David is the first to drop.
David's out.
Take a spot on the bench, no shot at immunity.
We are down to eight.
That's how fast it can happen.
It looks so easy watching it.
Hannah slips, but a nice save.
Hannah drops.
Hannah's out of the challenge.
Will drops out of nowhere, you just let up for a moment.
That tension released and that's what happened to Brett.
Four people quickly out of this challenge.
Strength, concentration and touch.
That is the key, the right finesse.
Sunday drops, no shot at immunity and we are down to four.
Jay, Ken, Adam and Zeke.
Zeke with a little wobble, but a nice recovery.
Zeke struggling to stay in it.
Zeke dropped.
Zeke is out of the challenge.
No shot at immunity and we are down to three.
Jay, Ken and Adam fighting for immunity.
Jay with his first movement, but a nice recovery.
This is another challenge.
There is no finish line.
It's just outlasting the others.
Don't let this hot sun start to bake your mind.
You have been out here only four minutes and I know it seems like a lot longer.
Adam's still solid.
Ken, the big slip.
Jay slips again in another recovery.
Ken slips a little more.
If you lose your concentration, you will drop.
Ken drops and we are down to two.
It is Jay and Adam in a showdown of millennials for immunity on day 33.
This is survival right here.
Who wants it more?
Jay trying to keep tension on his bar.
Adam slips, but a nice save.
Both guys feeling it.
Jay drops.
Adam wins.
Individual immunity.
We will live to see day 34.
Adam, come on over.
I'm going to soak this in.
Soak it in.
Individual immunity is yours.
It's a dream come true.
Safe tonight.
We will live to see day 34.
Massive accomplishment as for the rest of you.
After 33 days, your quest to win Survivor and the million dollars that goes with it will come to a crashing halt.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Zeke lost the challenge.
So this is my moment.
This is my time to make a big move so that people realize that hey, this 18-year-old kid from Jersey, he's here to play.
Congratulations, Adam.
Thank you.
Hell of a win there.
You earned it.
Thank you.
The immunity challenge was awesome.
I'm making my Survivor dreams come true.
I only have one check box left, and that's winning this game.
And you know what?
It might actually happen because I'm safe at tribal council tonight.
I have a hidden immunity idol in my pocket, and Will wants to make a move and blindside Zeke.
We have a solid five.
Vote Zeke no matter what anybody says.
Vote Zeke.
Yeah, no matter what anyone says.
That's it.
And we pray that Will is...
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't work without Will.
I no longer have a hidden immunity idol, so I'm incredibly vulnerable.
And it's like Will just got his driver's license, and we're all sitting in the back terrified because this is the first time he's going to take us for a drive.
But I think it's going to work.
Does he have that he's so calm?
Something's up.
I have the numbers, so I should be feeling great.
However, there's something amiss at the Vinaka camp.
It does not make sense that the four should be as calm as they are.
He has an idol.
Just burgers and margaritas for me tonight.
I know David's coming for me, so we need to get rid of him.
But David has a nose for idols, and I'm so close to the end.
I can't take the risk, so we need to throw someone else under the bus.
What are we doing?
Camp.
Let's do that.
Yeah.
Camp.
How you feeling, brother?
You got two sides tugging at you, man, and it's tough.
Well, I mean, I feel like there's a group that respects me
and a group that doesn't respect me.
Hey, you got to just tell me where to go if they don't take my input.
Exactly.
If I don't just start talking strategy with just anyone...
Yeah, I know.
Not until I have an idea of who they are.
I had a pretty good feeling about Will, but it wasn't 100%.
And I don't just have a five-minute conversation and then hop in bed with somebody.
I've got to know the core of a person, their integrity, their value,
because I'm trying to win for my little girl, and I want to make sure that I'm safe.
Is your motive to work with a better group? Is your motive to...
I am willing to vote Zeke because he could beat anybody in this game.
OK.
I give people one chance to be honest with me, and if that breaks, then I...
It's done.
Working with Ken is like getting your finger and toenails ripped out at the same time.
It's excruciating, but I want to make a big move, so I have to deal with that crap.
You're one of the few people I've found in this game that I feel is as authentic as myself.
Yeah.
And I respect that more than you can possibly know.
I'm definitely in with you guys, and they're right in your name down there.
Really?
That's what they just told me. They're voting for you.
I understand that.
Apparently, Zeke and his group are voting for me, and I'm like, why?
I'm not ready to go home.
Can you help me get a big piece of gilfoo drink?
Thanks to it.
I'm thinking we're good to go.
Then Ken walks back up into camp, gets Jay, and says we need to talk.
And at this moment, I know we're about to have a rumble.
I went and had a talk with Will, and he said, you guys were saying my name.
Will said that?
Yeah.
Is that what Will said? Look at me. I mean...
One minute, the solid five is good to go, like, yo, we're doing Ken.
Next minute, I have Ken come up to me and say, Will told me that you were voting my name.
And I'm like, what the f...
I was testing you earlier to see where you were at, because I...
I get it. You're blowing up my game at this point.
What's up, guys?
Ken comes to me and he goes, yo, Will just told me that you're all throwing my name out there.
This is my issue, guys.
Every time I make a move, other people take credit for it.
How am I supposed to win at the end if I don't have a resume?
I'd rather be playing hard than taking to the end as a goat.
We all knew something was up.
It's just a young kid trying to prove himself to the whole world.
But I still need him.
I wanted credit for this one big move.
Tell me the name. I'll freaking go with you and we'll figure out how to do it.
And I've told you since we've been with you since day one.
Okay.
We love you, dude. Let's get to the five with this.
And then we can battle it out. Okay?
Okay.
I had to test Will to see where he was at, because I didn't feel 110% comfortable with him.
No, no, no, no, no, no, where he was at.
They don't value him by seeing where he stood, asking where he was at,
and then going to those guys and saying, hey, Will's saying this. What the f—
Oh, jeez.
We have this plan, and Ken tests Will, revealing Will's plan.
That's not a test. That's a betrayal.
Ken walked up to me literally two seconds after.
He screwed you.
Can I just put you in that spot?
You know what? Screw it, because we got five here and I'm done with this.
I want him gone right now, tonight.
This guy preaches about honor and integrity and how he's this great and noble human being
with his arrogance and his extreme ego, and then he has the audacity to pull this crap on me.
I don't know why Ken did that.
Now Will has no incentive to vote with us.
Ken just screwed up everything, because if we don't have Will,
whoever that alliance led by mobster Zeke wants to vote out, they're going home.
What if David plays the idol for Ken?
So who do we vote?
Do we want to consider Hannah because they wouldn't be expecting that?
Should we vote for Hannah or vote for Ken?
I already know it's me, but that's okay.
No, I think it's going to be me.
Are you sure?
Everybody knows I'm in the middle. Now I have to make a decision.
The logical side of me is telling me this is my time to make a big move,
but I am so angry with Ken.
I would love to blow up his game.
Either way, I'm in control, and there is nothing anyone can do about it.
We'll now bring in the members of our jury.
Michelle, Taylor, Chris, and Jessica voted out at the last Tribal Council.
So David, coming off of one of the craziest Tribals ever, the Survivor,
has much changed or are we still locked into this two sides, only one side is down a member?
You know, there's no reason not to just put everything out in the open,
because basically there are two sides vying for a single swing vote right now.
Sunday, what are the divisions? Who are they?
Brett, Jay, Zeke, myself, and Ken, David, Adam, and Hannah.
Will is appropriately sitting in between.
Will, how did you end up in the middle?
Well, my original plan was to flip on Zeke, but Ken today revealed to the entire Tribe this plan.
So everybody knows basically what's going on.
So Sunday, the youngest kid out here is making the biggest decision of the night, and it is a massive swing vote.
You know, Will came to play hard, and I feel like he doesn't want to sit on the sidelines
and feel like all the big kids did all the work.
I think he was swayed a little bit today, but we're hoping he sticks with us.
Hold on here, I wasn't swayed at all today. I was the one who came to them with the decision to try to flip.
And that's part of the issue. Everybody treats me like the 18-year-old high school kid.
I don't want to be treated like that. I want to be treated like an adult,
because I am here to win and play just as hard as the rest of you.
Is it insulting a little?
It is very insulting, you know. It's insane that this crazy swing vote with me in the middle
is what it takes for people to realize that I am a serious contender.
So Zeke, everybody agrees they need Will's vote. So what's your pitch?
Well, Will, I've always wanted to play with you in this game.
We have aligned many times, and when Taylor and Jay were under heat,
you weren't under heat because I was protecting you.
But even the way that he talks about it, it's all about, I've been protecting you. I did this for you.
No, I don't think I was saying that in the least. He saved my ass last tribal council.
And if I'm here at the next tribal council, I will again owe my life to Will.
Jay, why should he come with this side?
Well, honestly, Jeff, I've never looked down on Will.
I've always talked to Will as if he was equal to me,
and I've never once tried to take credit for anything that we've done together
because we've made moves together. We took out Michaela together.
David, the topic of big moves is vital to the game.
Yeah. Will feels like he really has to have something on his resume
to show at final tribal should he get there.
And right now, Jay's trying to make Will feel like he already has that.
But I'll say if he votes with us, his name will be on this vote in big, bold letters.
And that's something to put on your resume.
Rep, David clearly just made a case to Will about going with those four.
Jeff, I'll tell Will right now. They'll build you up, and then they'll vote you out in the hot beat.
They've done it several times, so I'm sorry. I don't buy it.
Adam, you're shaking your head.
Yeah, I mean, our side has an equal partnership in terms of decision-making and the moves that are made.
And Will is already a part of that.
Will, do you buy that you could have five people and everyone has an equal say?
I don't buy it. When you have five people, everybody's going to be fighting to get their own voice heard,
and five people can't take credit for one move.
Hannah, what's the mistake Will will make if he goes with this four?
You know, I think there's been a lot of fluffing Will up on that side,
telling him that they'll work with him and that he gets credit for all the moves.
You know what, Will? I'm not here to fluff you.
All I want to tell you, dude, is honestly just go with your gut, bro. Simple as that.
And if that's what you feel is right, then do that.
Thank you, man.
Will, you're nodding your head.
Well, if there was one person here who has shown me respect throughout the entire game, that would be Jay. Yeah.
Well, I could sit here all night with you guys, but it is time to vote.
Ken, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
Sorry, Jeff. It was the only place I could keep it tonight.
What?
I didn't have a bag with me.
What? Whoa.
Oh, this will be fun.
You don't have to touch it if you don't want to. I'm playing this for Hannah.
What?
This is a hidden immunity idol. Any votes cast for Hannah will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Hannah does not count.
Zeke. One vote Zeke.
Zeke. That's two votes Zeke.
Twelfth person voted out and the fifth member of our jury.
Zeke. That's three. That's enough. You need to bring me your torch.
It's been an honor to play with you all. Keep fighting.
Thank you, Zeke.
Thanks, Zeke.
See you, Zeke.
Zeke. The tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, here's the thing about big moves. They're great until you're the one that gets punched.
With only eight people left, there are a lot of knockouts still to come.
Everybody needs to have their gloves up.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor, Will tries to take charge.
I think we just go for David.
Now I'm the one calling the shots.
The most insecure I've ever felt is right now.
But Adam has other ideas.
Will is going to flip back and forth.
I do not want Will controlling my fate in this game.
It's possible I went after David and his side too early.
I think maybe I was excited to play a little hard, but I didn't come here to ride coattails.
I came here to throw some punches, and I wasn't going to go down without a fight.
Because I think when you play at this high level with this caliber of players, it just makes you want to play better.
And maybe one day I will.