Previously on Survivor...
In the Ikabula tribe,
Sunday and Bret were
numerically dominated by Gen Ys.
See you, Gen X!
In the Vanua tribe,
Zeke was getting closer to Gen X.
I might have to give up
the Gen Y tribe.
In the Takali tribe,
Adam had control
and he had to decide
if he voted with the Gen Y couple...
- Shall we take Ken out?
- Yes.
...or trusted Gen X.
I will never vote for you.
The question is, which camp
will be the best for my future?
At the council,
Adam and Gen X
eliminated Taylor's girlfriend.
Figgy, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck, Taylor.
There are 14 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Taylor, if you and is disposé...
I would love
to talk to you face to face.
Yeah, I'd love to hear
your grand plan of...
How do you plan to do now.
Lord!
The advice was rubbish.
No one from no one.
I can't trust them
like Figg.
The simple comfort of his presence.
The smiles,
just the good mood on the camp.
For me, Figg was the light.
Our camp is greyish now.
For me, it was lose-lose.
It seemed the least bad to me.
I may have screwed up.
- Yeah. And it affects me too.
- Sure.
Yes, I fucked you.
I lied to you and I screwed you.
Clearly.
I admit it.
I blame myself for ending
their island romance,
but i did
what i had to do.
I put myself
in a position to progress
with a group of Gen X,
and Figgy was
ultimately
the necessary sacrifice.
Your position has worsened.
And it's my fault.
I admit it.
I'm beyond pissed off
with Adam.
Now
it's about revenge.
For now, I'll keep it cool,
but when the time comes...
I will destroy you!
- Can I take this place?
- I thought you were sitting here.
The rice is excellent this morning.
Very well cooked, as always.
It's easy to put rice
in the pot.
Sitting on the beach of Vanua,
I reflect.
If we lose the next immunity,
it is clearly Michelle
that we would eliminate.
But I do not exclude
that Chris tries a bad move
to eliminate me rather than Michelle.
But I believe I have a stronger bond
with Zeke than with Chris. Frankly,
we are made of the same wood.
I'm paranoid, so tell me
if anyone's coming up behind.
- No it's OK.
- Good.
I tell myself that I could
show him my idol.
It would build a lot of trust.
But I hate to
share this information.
It's a very risky move
or it's a super move.
You can never know.
Zeke,
I have great faith in you.
Me too.
I'm going to tell you something
you don't have to repeat.
- Do you have the idol?
- I found her the next day.
It's excellent.
Great. OK.
- Don't tell anyone.
- It's not in my interest.
I want to go all the way with you,
hence this confidence.
- I appreciate.
- This is my proof.
David told me
that he had an immunity idol.
I was glad to hear it.
Because if you don't have one,
it's good that a close person
has one.
You are literally the only one
besides myself who knows this.
Your secret is safe.
David and I could have
a future together in this game.
He put his life in my hands.
And I will take good care of it.
For now.
Over here, everyone!
Sick stuff!
Vanua and Ikabula,
discover the new Takali tribe.
Figgy was eliminated
at the last council.
Oh my God!
So many different reactions!
Michaela,
at the final immunity challenge,
you looked at this tribe
and said,
"You're three Gen Ys.
Get by or never mind."
Sometimes we say what we have to say,
not what we want to say.
This was the case.
In other words?
Figgy's hour had come
a long time ago, so...
Taylor, surprised to hear that?
No comment.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
you will work together
to unroll and release three balloons.
Then you'll throw them in a basket
and push them
through a rope tunnel.
When you have the three,
you will try to place them
on a perch.
The first two tribes to finish
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
For the first to finish,
a leader will come to your camp
and will cook for you.
You will relax
while tasting chicken,
garlic prawns,
salads,
and finally, cheesecake.
My God!
Not possible!
For the second,
skewers.
You will have to cook them yourself.
- But it will fill your stomach.
- Hey, that's it!
For the third,
nothing.
Ikabula, you are two more.
Who will not take part
in this event?
- Bret and me.
- Bret and Sunday are not participating.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we're gonna start.
Alright, here we go.
For a reward.
Survivors, ready?
You have to work together
to release the balloons.
You cannot
climb on the structure.
Everyone left well.
It's like a spirobol!
Jay is now up
on the shoulders of his comrades,
and it works.
Adam begins to find the rhythm.
- Here!
- Like that!
You have to turn them,
it takes strength.
- Underneath!
- Come on, push!
Zeke, in trouble.
Big fall for Zeke.
Vanua tries something else.
David is coming up.
Jay is the first
to release the balloons.
Takali releases them.
David has as much trouble as Zeke.
They are rapidly losing ground.
Now you have to undo the knots
to release your balloons.
They are finally there!
Forward, David, give it your all!
Ikabula is in the lead
from the beginning.
Vanua arrives.
Go ahead, untie the knots,
free the balloons!
Jay tire pour Ikabula.
Ken shoots now.
Ken scores the first point
for Takali!
Now Jessica and Adam
get the ball across the net.
You can't shoot again
until the ball is passed.
Ikabula, still on the first.
Give me another!
Vanua released its balloons.
Chris shoots.
Chris scores for Vanua.
They close the gap.
Now
Zeke and Michelle are working
to release the ball.
It's up to Will and Hannah
to move the ball forward.
Michelle and Zeke
quickly regained ground.
Chris shoots again.
Its good.
It increases the advance
of Vanua.
Go, Takali!
Ken shoots again
and scores on the first shot.
Zeke and Michelle
found the system.
They progress very quickly.
Go, Chris!
Vanua leads once again.
And two!
Type in!
Go, Takali!
Ken, for the third.
Just too short.
Chris scores again.
This is the third ball for Vanua.
When it is released,
move on to the 3rd and final step.
Ken scores with the third
and final ball for Takali.
Go, Vanua!
What have Michelle and Zeke figured out
that no one else has figured out?
Because that is the difference
in this event.
Chris is going to shoot for Vanua.
You have to place all three balls
on the perch to win.
Ikabula is still
on the second ball.
Far behind.
Chris places first for Vanua.
There you go!
Go, Takali!
Will and Hannah passed
their second ball.
Chris places his second.
More than one!
Jay scores with the third
and final ball for Ikabula.
Chris, it's back.
Ken places his first.
Chris is close.
Chris could win now.
And he does!
Huge reward for Vanua!
A chef on the camp!
Ken tries to finish second
for Takali.
And Will and Hannah
are still on that ball.
This is Jay and Michaela.
Can they get back in the game?
Michaela shoots for Ikabula.
Ken tries to place his second.
Michaela is trying to catch up on
a huge backlog.
Michaela places her first, tie!
That would be a huge lift
for Ikabula if they succeeded
and won the skewers.
Ken places his second for Takali.
He only has one left.
Don't shoot the others!
Here, take your time.
Michaela places her second.
Equality, everything is at stake here!
More than a ball!
Ken versus Michaela.
Michaela succeeds
for Ikabula!
A huge comeback
to victory!
We have skewers!
We eat!
- Let's eat!
- Let's eat, friends!
Vanua.
Nice reward.
Full of prepared food,
fill your belly!
Enjoy! Take your things,
return to camp.
- Thanks!
- Good afternoon.
Michaela, once again,
a show of strength.
Nice victory for Ikabula.
Come get your skewers.
Good afternoon.
I hope you have a fire
to cook them.
Thanks, Jeff.
Takali, I have nothing for you.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Going from first to last
to first again,
and take second place...
On the one hand, I'm happy,
because we have skewers.
But on the other, I'm nervous
to have helped in the victory,
because I don't want
people to think
that I am the one to beat.
Open!
- Bula!
God's goodness!
Return to Camp
after winning and seeing
the chef with the barbecue,
the grills and all the trimmings,
it was a huge relief.
The prawns
have just been caught.
It's fantastic!
Jeff was off the mark.
This is the kind of food
I imagine in an LA restaurant.
- I do not stop.
- Cheer.
This game requires
change and adaptation.
I was on a diet
for most of my youth.
So I always watch
what I eat. But here,
I fill my plate,
I shove it in my mouth
and I don't stop.
Because the more calories I ingest,
the more it will benefit me.
And because
of the small fat that is in me,
I could stuff myself.
Zeke doesn't do things by halves.
I'm taking a break.
I have never eaten so much
so fast in my entire life.
The three guys
we have become animals,
scraping the food off the plate.
Michelle used her cutlery,
like a human.
It has to come out!
It frees up space for food.
Just hiccups, no worries.
At the end of the meal,
all I hear,
it's bodily functions
and noises coming from guys.
It got gross and annoying.
I don't eat like that.
My mother taught me manners.
But now
I'm a little nervous,
because being the only girl,
I could be an easy vote.
But I will not change
who I am for the game.
Everything in our daily life
is affected by the policy.
The policy is created
by those who govern,
whether they are elected or not.
I noticed that a lot of people
of my generation don't care.
I hate talking politics.
Whatever we do,
there will always be unhappy people.
Who will be president
does not interest me.
I don't want to pin my hopes
on politics.
I think my generation
will change things drastically.
Things we've done
that they are no longer useful,
like the electoral vote.
Taylor is the typical Gen Y.
He is completely honest
in his answers.
He is not always
bright with intelligence,
but we still love it,
because he will give you his true answer.
Let me ask you a question.
Did Adam promise
you and Figgy
- not to vote for you?
- Oh yeah.
I know you will do
what you have to do,
but when the fusion comes,
I will have no allegiance.
I can shake your hand
and swear not to vote for you.
- I will not do it.
- It's good to know!
I will never write "Jessica",
I won't write "Ken" anymore.
Thanks. I appreciate it,
it means a lot.
Taylor wouldn't understand the strategy
even if it was explained to him.
So his words are perhaps
more reliable than those of Adam,
who is more of a strategist.
Ken and I soak up all the info
we're given.
If we don't win,
it will be a very big decision.
And we have to take the right one.
Fireworks!
- On the 20th day, friends!
- The 20th day!
We've done half!
It was a bug party
tonight!
- Horrible.
- I just thought, "Michaela,
you don't feel anything crawling on you.
It's your imagination.
This fly buzzes,
but it does not sting.
Let it buzz, Michaela!"
I have been on this island
for 20 days.
I'm halfway there.
But I am strong,
the strongest of the tribe.
"It doesn't itch,
it's in your head, girl!"
I know I take things
very seriously.
Just like Steve Jobs was, so
is Michael Jordan.
Michaela Bradshaw
takes things to heart.
That's what makes us
winners.
If you can't keep up,
step aside!
How's yours, Sunday?
Pumped up for today?
Good.
We try to preserve
our sense of unity,
to keep winning.
Of course, it's a kind of mirage,
because there are four Gen Y
and two Gen X.
Sunday is super nice.
My aunt calls me "Sunny".
She alone has the right.
But Bret is suspect to me.
What is your job?
Owner of a
funeral home.
I strive
to comfort families.
I want to raise
doubts about Bret,
because i think he is lying
about funeral directors.
I help them choose a coffin,
all that.
Nothing in particular.
Was it moving at first?
Yes very.
But it's like everything, you get used to it.
It's a bit morbid, but...
I was calm, cushy, and Hannah
asks me about my business.
I gave her the answers
she seemed to expect.
Do you see one family at a time?
How it works?
We make an appointment, we see each other
and arrange the funeral.
I don't like lying to him,
but I know the story of Survivor.
The police
rarely do well.
So I won't give up.
Can I say something about Bret?
I'm 70% sure he's a cop.
He grew up in Boston.
I'm pretty sure he's a cop.
I think
I just interviewed a cop.
Bret talks like a cop,
walks like a cop.
But above all,
it's about getting
the other three Gen Y
are wary
of these two so sympathetic Gen X.
Because I want us to stay together,
all four of us.
For me, if you had to vote,
I'd be like, "Man,
I'm pretty sure you're a cop.
My vote is based
on trust and honesty."
If he's a cop, let him say
it when he wants.
Don't force his hand,
it would be unpleasant.
Funeral directors,
it's so specific
that one would not think to doubt it.
That's the thing.
I grew up in Boston.
He talks like all the cops
I've met. It's silly?
I also believe he is a cop.
Bret calls himself
a funeral director.
But the thing is, I know
the Florida cops.
And frankly,
if you take the accent away from him,
you put him in a uniform,
you put him in Florida,
that would be the guy i'm running from
when I make a bonfire
on the beach.
Continue your little investigation.
"But what are you doing exactly?"
He's too funny and good-natured
to run funeral parlors.
It's important
to know if he's a cop,
that would mean he's lying to me.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
- First, as you know...
- I know.
Thank you, David.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will throw coconuts
in a net.
When the net is heavy enough,
a flag will unfurl,
revealing numbers.
These numbers will release a key.
This key will unlock a slingshot.
You will then fire sandbags
to knock down targets.
The first two tribes to finish
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be the 7th person
eliminated from the game.
Ikabula, you are two more.
Two will not participate.
It was Bret and Sunday
last time. And today?
William and moi.
Hannah and Will are not participating.
Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we begin.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
First step, very simple,
throwing coconuts
into a net.
Ken misses.
Jay just misses.
Chris, right into it!
Michaela... hits the mark.
In rainbow.
Taylor takes a chance.
Taylor succeeds.
When you have put enough coconuts,
the flag will unfurl.
So far,
it's not as easy as it looks.
You have to take the hit.
Nice shot from Sunday.
David, a bit short.
Vanua is struggling a bit.
Chris just misses.
Adam sets one up for Takali.
Nice shot from Jessica.
Takali's net fills up.
Ikabula's net fills up.
Ikabula has
never lost an event yet.
They wouldn't want to
start today.
Michaela succeeds for Ikabula.
You should start
picking up the pace.
- There you have it!
- Come on, David!
- David finally succeeds.
- Nice shot.
Adam rocks!
Takali reaches the stadium
where one or two more coconuts
will suffice.
Where is the tipping point?
Everyone is close.
It's good for Takali!
Adam will use the numbers
to try to free the key.
He must find the correct combination
of number pairs.
What is the correct order?
It's not good.
A missed opportunity.
Jay shoots and scores.
Ikabula approaches.
Adam tries and finds.
Come on, forward!
Adam can now
unlock the slingshot.
Ikabula approaches.
Will it go down?
That's enough, and that's it!
It goes down!
Michaela has the numbers,
she steps forward.
Adam unlocked the slingshot.
Takali can start
shooting the bags at the targets.
Taylor gives it a shot.
Too left.
Michaela
is on number pairs.
You have to release this key.
She has it!
Forward, Ikabula!
she will unlock
the fronds.
- Shit!
- Taylor just misses.
Vanua is dead last.
Voici Zeke.
Will it be enough?
Yes, it goes down!
Can they get there?
Can they go up?
Michelle is on the numbers,
trying to free the key.
It's one of those events
where you can come back quickly.
Pushes you!
Ok, Go!
- Are you going?
- No, stick to your decision!
Michelle tries to find
the combination.
What is the correct order?
It's not that!
Just too short!
Ken shoots now.
He just misses.
Michelle tries another combination.
It's not that.
Try another!
There are six combinations.
You have to try them all
to find.
Ken tire
and knocks down a first target
for Takali.
Michaela fails
to hit a target,
which leaves a chance
in Vanua.
Want to change?
- Nope!
- OK.
Ken takes down a second target.
- Two for Takali.
- Alright, come on, someone!
- Go ahead, Jay!
- This is Jay.
I have tried everything!
I think she's cracking up.
Michelle finally succeeds
after a long time.
Taylor shoots down a third.
Three for Takali.
Ikabula ...
Always nothing.
Vanua tries to score.
...and hits a first target
for Vanua.
The Vanua were dead last
and here they are in the shot.
Jay scores for Ikabula.
Ken scores for Takali.
That's four for Takali,
one for Vanua and for Ikabula.
Let them fly, Chris!
More than a target for Takali,
for immunity.
Ken could do it
right now.
And he does!
Ken wins immunity for Takali.
No advice.
He remains in second place.
- Go on, Zeke!
Huge challenge.
Nobody wants to go to the council.
Zeke brand for Vanua.
That's two targets for Vanua,
one for Ikabula.
Here is Bret.
And he succeeds!
Both Ikabula and Vanua have
only three targets left.
This is Jay.
Jay just misses.
Chris is back for Vanua.
Right in the target!
Vanua took the lead,
more than two targets.
- We're changing, I'm exhausted.
- Come on, Michaela!
It's Michaela and Chris now.
Chris aims... and succeeds again!
Chris touches another.
Michaela knows no defeat
with this tribe.
It would be a bad time
to start.
- Completely failed.
- She was almost there.
Chris, for the win.
He would send Ikabula to the council.
It's okay, Chris!
Chris shoots deep.
And he succeeds!
Vanua wins immunity
and send Ikabula
to the board for the first time!
Takali.
Good game.
No one will leave this tribe.
Vanua.
Good job.
No one will leave Vanua.
Takali, congratulations,
enjoy your free evening.
This tribe remains intact.
Pack your things, head back to camp.
Thanks, Jeff!
Vanua, nice comeback.
No one will leave tonight.
- Take your things, go back to the camp.
- Thank you, Jeff!
Sunday you will return to camp.
Will it be
seconds or minutes
before the paranoia sets
in and the shenanigans begin?
I would say minutes,
because we will try to play it cool
for a few seconds,
and then
after a few minutes,
we will press the "parano" button.
Good, Ikabula.
Advice tonight. Someone
will be the 7th person eliminated.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Of course,
the Gen Y must meet
and decide if it will be Bret
or if it will be Sunday.
But as Bret continues to lie,
sorry, Bret,
but you have to go.
This defeat was
like a punch in the stomach.
We sat in silence
at least half an hour,
because we really
like each other.
Bret and I looked at each other.
"Damn, it's one of us."
I had to hold back my tears,
because I'm not used
to others deciding my fate.
But this is Survivor.
And we both know it.
Sorry.
You know what that means, right?
You will have to vote for me
and me for you.
- Unless we find another plan.
- I say.
Even if we don't want to.
Sunday and I said to each other,
"I won't vote for you."
But, tonight,
we'll have to break that promise.
And she agreed.
It sucks, 'cause if you vote
for someone else and survive,
- they will come after you.
- I know, yeah.
We must do so.
I hate this.
Me too.
It sucks not being in control
of your destiny. But that's the game.
There are times
when we are at the mercy of others.
But this is Survivor,
you never know what will happen.
I played out a scenario
in my head.
Here is our final square.
That's the other tribes.
Two Gen Y.
Two Gen X.
And that is the person
who will survive the vote.
I'll show you why,
it doesn't matter who we keep.
We still have four votes.
So one of those people is leaving.
I say, a Gen X.
And so, we meet again.
I gathered Gen Y
and I used pebbles and shells
to lay out a plan,
show that in fact, no matter
who stays and who goes
if we play correctly
with the numbers.
Who do you want to vote for tonight?
Bret might be a cop.
Maybe.
We could split the votes,
whenever an idol is played.
Alright, we split the first time
and we all vote Bret the second time around.
This plan to divide the votes,
this is in case
an idol is played.
So the girls will vote Bret
and the boys Sunday.
It will create a tie.
So we'll vote again,
for Bret if all goes well.
We are the four shells.
As long as they remain
shells...
- Everything is fine.
- ...we're quiet.
Michaela has seashells,
like a soccer game plan.
She said, "Well, after the merger,
that person is eliminated.
There will be four shells left.
It's us."
And... Michaela is intelligent.
This is the problem.
We need not fear the council.
Going there more often than others
is the only way to win.
We develop trust.
Yeah. That's why
I love this tribe.
Because I believe I can
trust you.
And I doubt there are three other
people I can trust.
She is very dangerous.
She is good in trials,
she is smart,
then I had a revelation,
"Michaela should go!
Before the merger!"
I'm starting to think about it.
How about we take out Michaela?
She's wickedly smart.
She will take people out
one after another.
I barely remember people,
and her, it's like,
"This person, and this one,
two Gen X, one Gen Y..."
And I'm like,
"You're seeing way too far!"
Michaela is super intelligent.
Every time
I chat with her
about the game,
she thinks about it methodically.
I just have to wait for the right moment
to eliminate it.
Because I really appreciate it.
It emits positive vibrations.
I don't think any of us
want her to leave.
I play devil's advocate.
She knows we have the idol.
It's scary too.
You are not wrong.
Bret and Sunday will vote Michaela.
If we tell her, she'll freak out.
If we don't tell her,
she'll freak out later.
I'd rather not tell him.
The thing
is, I trust her.
She never lied.
We are his only allies.
Damn, what a vote tonight!
I am nervous.
Michaela is a great ally
and I've been with her since the beginning.
And I still don't
trust Bret.
It's crazy,
when you make a big hit,
one wonders,
"Is this the logical thing to do?"
Survivor is no joke.
This decision could shape
the rest of my game,
to victory
or defeat.
I'm freaking out!
So, Ikabula.
First time on the board.
The other two tribes
came here,
and in both cases
the majority eliminated
one of his.
Michaela, seeing this,
how much do you trust Gen Y?
Tonight, I'm thinking of the people
I'm with.
The majorities of the other two tribes
were full of shady people.
Shady people are unreliable.
But what 's great
about Ikabula,
it's that all six of
us are pretty reliable.
Jay, were you surprised
that the majorities of the other tribes
eliminate one of their own?
Yeah, clear.
Seeing Gen Y release a Gen Y,
we say to ourselves, "What are you doing?"
And where Gen X were in the majority,
they did the same.
That's crazy.
Sunday, to the test, I said,
"How long
until the shenanigans?"
And you said,
"About two minutes."
- Did you get it right?
- Actually no.
We came home and sat down,
all aligned on a trunk,
without saying a word.
- Even Michaela?
- Even Michaela!
So, Michaela, the six of you were
sitting on a trunk.
What were you thinking?
To the fact that it sucks
that our six has to become five.
We really like each other.
They are Tonton Bret
and Maman Sunday.
We are near.
We would have taken control of the game
if you had let us
go to the merger together.
It's always my fault!
But yes!
We didn't ask for a slingshot!
Sunday, does
it play against you
that the four Gen Y can say,
"It's not that we don't trust
Sunday or Bret,
it's because they know people
we don't know.
These four
I can trust.
- We've been together since the beginning."
- Absolutely.
Bret and I know very well
that we are in the minority.
They did everything
so that we didn't feel left out,
but, you know...
It's still 4 - 2.
Bret, if there is any positive,
is that the other two tribes
had a majority
who eliminated one of his own.
You're probably thinking,
"I could cause this tonight!"
Hey, I'm open to anything,
Jeff, let's go!
But... They know who I am.
They know what kind of person
I am, that I'm honest with them.
So if anything can help me,
let's do it.
Will, when you watch
the evolution of the game,
since the time of your birth,
and the importance of trust,
Is it possible
that the strategy has surpassed it
and that it is only
temporary alliances and devoted blocs?
"And I don't care if I eliminate
anyone by surprise,
because I play as a sniper."
You're describing a game
à la Tony Vlachos.
It's dangerous.
People see
if you play crazy
full balloons.
And in a game where trust
is a precious rarity,
every time you find it,
you have to hang on to it.
Because that's what could
take you all the way.
Jay, is it played
on instinct,
Bret versus Sunday?
Yeah.
You have to follow your instincts.
If he tells you one thing,
trust him.
'Cause that's all you got,
frankly.
What is it based
on for you?
The merger is probably near.
It depends on who, in our opinion,
can go all the way to the final quintet
with us.
So, Will, predict the future.
After the vote,
you return to camp.
What kind of tribe will you have?
Five solid and reliable people
to progress in the game.
Jay, are you okay?
Will this vote
actually strengthen the tribe?
If I could predict the future,
Jeff, I believe it,
because then the bonds
will only get stronger.
Michaela. After this vote,
will this tribe
be broken or strengthened?
Clearly reinforced.
But I hope that tonight
no one feels like they're at the bottom of the ladder.
We hadn't planned that,
but it's part of the game.
Who would feel
at the bottom of the ladder?
The one of these two great people
who will remain.
But that's not what I want.
So based on what I'm hearing,
we have a group
that trusts each other,
or someone
will be taken out by surprise.
It's time to vote.
Hannah, over to you.
As always, I'm shaking.
I hope
people will keep their word.
I wish I
could have gone further with you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Breth.
Two Bret votes.
Michaela.
Two Bret votes, one Michaela vote.
Two votes Bret,
two votes Michaela.
- Michaela.
- What?!
That's three votes Michaela,
two votes Bret,
one vote remains.
- You did that?
- Yeah.
I did it.
- Sorry.
- I didn't do that.
Seventh person eliminated...
Michaela.
Bring me your torch.
You fucked up.
What...?
Michaela, the tribe has spoken.
You will feel good with.
My shoes.
Merde, Jay!
You screwed up a good thing, bro.
Well, it was going to be "trust"
or "surprise elimination."
It turns out that the one
who preached the most trust
is the one
that was eliminated by surprise.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The merger has arrived.
Fusion!
This is where I really start
destroying people's dreams and hopes.
And the Gen X are in the minority.
They are too close.
We have to get Gen Y out
or we're in trouble.
But Hannah wants revenge.
I can't trust Jay.
I hope to have my revenge.
I'm pretty pissed off.
It's a stupid decision.
I was focused on the end,
I don't even reach the fusion.
If Jay had known how to
control his paranoia,
this group of four
would have gone all the way.
We would have dominated the game together
and someone would have walked away
with the million.
But hey, too bad.
I will get rich otherwise.