It is one of the most amazing
places in the world.
Crystal clear waters,
a varied and dangerous fauna
and hundreds of
breathtaking islands.
This will be the battlefield
from a culture war
to the Survivor.
These 20 Americans don't know it yet,
but they are about
to be separated into two tribes.
Generation Y,
18 years old
at 31 years old.
For my generation,
what matters
is doing what you want.
And I did a lot.
Beekeeper, beer brewer,
snowboard teacher,
I went
to North Dakota...
I'm definitely the Peter Pan type.
I will never grow up.
I am like this.
I can not change.
I earn my living
by playing online video games.
To adults, we say all the time,
"Grow up, stop playing,
it's not a game.", but...
I want my whole life
to revolve around gaming.
Survivor is the ultimate game.
And I will win it.
The stereotype of young people is,
always on social networks,
always on Twitter.
But I don't like
being glued to my phone.
I really don't like
technology.
Twitter is the worst thing
ever invented.
Well, I'm on Twitter,
but it's still horrible.
Generation X,
aged 33
at 52 years old.
I am a lawyer,
I am 38 years old.
And I know the older ones
are actually listening to you.
They use their experiences.
If you've already been knocked down,
you know how to get up
and fight.
I have four children
and I'm surprised
by the 25-year-old kids
living with their parents,
always on video games.
I feel like
they're more like
"time will tell".
"It takes me seven years
to finish school? So what?
My parents pay."
I write for television.
It took me 14 years of purgatory
as an assistant
to finally become an author.
And I doubt the younger ones would
spend so much time
to their dream, whatever it may be.
They would find themselves another dream.
two generations
with two very different ways
of approaching life.
They will be abandoned
and left to fend for themselves.
They must learn to adapt
or they will be eliminated.
In the end, only one will take home
the million dollar prize.
39 days,
20 people,
a survivor.
Good ! Welcome
to the 33rd season of Survivor.
Take your name,
don't open it yet,
wait for me.
Very exciting time.
Which tribe will I be in?
All right, unpack all your bandanas.
Take a seat on your mat
and greet your new companions.
If you're purple,
go purple.
If you are orange,
go orange.
Put on all your bandanas.
It's not official
than when the bandana
is somewhere on your body.
I'm so happy
to have this thing on my head!
Well then.
Once again,
Survivor shakes things up.
This year it's Survivor,
Gen Y versus Gen X.
I thought, "Damn,
clearly,
it is a war of generations.
From the start, we tear each other apart.
That's crazy !
May the best generation win!
Gen X, born between 1963
Old !
Gen Y, born between 1984 and 1997.
This division
is deeper
than just "old versus young".
They are two very different philosophies of life .
What we will test this season
is which is better suited
in the game of Survivor.
Someone among Gen Y
does he want to assume he was born in 1997,
the youngest person?
Without hesitation !
What's your name ?
- Will.
- 1997. How old are you?
- Do you have your baccalaureate?
- No, still in high school.
I left high school
to play this game.
- I'm ready to play!
- Graduate first !
It's a first !
Our first high school student.
Good. And does anyone among Gen X
want to assume
being born in 1963,
which makes him the oldest?
What's your name ?
- Paul.
So, Paul, how does it feel
to live in this environment
where at one time, Generation X
tear down the walls
and rebuild the culture?
Now you are the oldest,
and the next generation is coming.
In our generation,
there was no trophy
without winning.
In our generation,
only the winners
had a trophy.
We had to do without an iPod,
an app for this, an app for that.
You had to go to the store
to buy milk.
It was not delivered by drone.
Madam, in front, what is your name?
- What what.
You nodded, "Yes, yes!"
Absolutely.
They do not work,
we give them everything.
You have to work
to get what you want.
This is how you can truly
know success.
- The guy in the middle, your name?
- Adam.
Good. Adam.
You see what I mean ?
So, you hear that, this is how
we sum up Generation Y.
"Participation trophies",
"We don't want to work"...
Does that seem true to you?
I do not think so.
When we win
the first immunity,
we'll see who has to work to win.
Good. You are about to pass
your first test.
Scattered in this piece of jungle
find
helpful articles for the next 39 days.
Some have
short-term value,
others a long-term value.
Moreover, each tribe
has two positions.
You will choose an item
at each position.
Leave the other where he is.
These will be your first
big decisions in the game.
Are you ready to go?
So, forward!
Quick !
Forward, Gen Y!
You have two minutes
to bring as many as possible
to your carpet.
If it's on your mat,
it's up to you.
The friends !
"Choose one."
We need that.
Gen X
make their first decision.
They take the pan
and the utensils
and leave the hammer where it is.
You make decisions
that will influence
the next 39 days.
There are things to find
in every corner!
- Hammer and nails?
- You can cook in bamboo.
Les Gen Y,
half the tribe
for a single decision!
Someone decide,
no need to all be there!
Some are already coming back.
Take all you can!
There are articles in the trees,
others at the foot of the trees.
Don't forget anything.
Quick quick !
On the ground, there was an envelope.
I caught her,
stashed behind my back
and I continued.
It was a moment where you said to yourself,
"My God! I have to continue!"
But my heart was pounding,
because it had to be a good thing.
- Take the gear.
- I'm taking care of it.
Gen X
take the fishing gear
and leave the chickens.
30 seconds left!
Bring what you want
on your mat!
Adam, let's go!
Come back and get
some if you've laid everything!
Hey, them Gén Y!
The chickens. The chickens.
15 seconds left!
Come back, that's it!
Gen Y took the chickens
and left the fishing gear.
Big difference right away.
Gen X think long term.
Gen Y think in the short term.
Latest post!
End of time!
It's finish ! Put down your items
and come back to your mat!
The chickens ? Good choice !
Let's recap the big picks.
You took
the fishing gear.
Paul, why prefer
him to chickens,
which are ready to be eaten?
Fishing gear is...
39 days.
This is the most important item
we took.
Taylor. You
guys took the chickens.
Why ?
They lay eggs, Jeff!
Good.
Let's go.
Gen X, the map
to reach your beach!
Les Gen Y,
the map to reach your beach!
Before I release you...
It's hurricane season.
Here in Fiji.
It was tough.
We are in a hollow here.
Another heavy storm is expected
soon.
It's not sham,
it's for real.
This season more than any other,
you must attack your shelter
immediately on the camp,
because you will need it.
Take your things, let's go!
Good luck !
Generation Y versus Generation X.
It's a war of generations.
I guarantee some
in this Gen X tribe
said exactly
the same thing as me,
"It's the best generation
ever."
Our sweet home!
Walk along this beach
and see the tribe's flag...
Everyone is super excited,
very happy to meet.
And we're going to make the clichés lie
on Generation Y.
We take a walk, everyone says their name?
My name is Figgy.
My real name is Jessica, but...
I am 23 years old
and I'm a bartender.
My name is Mari
and I make a living playing video games.
In good Gen Y,
we touch everything.
Nobody has an ordinary job.
I think it's great.
My name is Michelle, I'm 28 years old
and I do missionary work
for an organization
that translates the Bible.
Yeah !
I clearly think
that our tribe and our generation
see things
completely differently.
And as Gen Y,
that's a huge plus.
Let's take some bamboo stalks
to form the base.
You have to be above the ground.
Go to work !
- I like...
- Yeah, everyone here looks serious.
I have a great tribe.
I have a very good contact with Jay.
He has a very cool haircut
and he's a real friend, I can see that.
With him, I will get along easily.
We're putting a beam
between the trees around here.
I had thought of that earlier, but...
- But if...
- Oh, you're so smart!
You are so intelligent!
And I clearly get
along with Figgs,
because she is downright cute.
I will make the fire.
Do you have wires in your pockets?
It would take right away.
- Soggy.
- Yeah, we're all soaked.
Hair ?
It would take!
- One of your braids!
- The Jedi Braid!
Also, Michelle is cool.
And they are both pretty.
And I like pretty girls.
So I already have a connection
with those people.
- I'm so excited!
- That's crazy !
I am appalled.
I'm with a bunch of Gen Ys.
I'm 28, but to be honest,
I never referred to myself
as a "Gen Y". Never.
I'm not dressed
for the youth parade,
but for the "meetings" night
at the Miami retirement home.
Like, I'm actually 80 years old.
It's like tidying up my room!
Like, "Oh no!
Where's that going?"
I am in a tribe of children.
When I saw all these kids
around me,
I thought, "You know what those kids
never had?
A real job."
Let's go bowling!
They don't know how to do anything!
- To the youth!
- I love you all !
Our sweet home, friends!
Great job, everyone!
I expect Gen X
to be Gen X,
that they are people
of my caliber.
People my age work hard.
They have strong
family values.
strong opinions,
but based on a solid
decision-making process.
Hey, friends!
One moment, huh?
Being the oldest
I would just like to say...
When Jeff said how
the tribes would be made up,
it changed everything.
From top to bottom.
It went from,
"Wow, as long as it's not..."
to, "Damn, there are
thinking people here!
Who know how to build, who know..."
We are also a generation
that has been taught humility.
These kids shouldn't be underestimated . They are lively, gifted...
We grew up
working with our hands.
They work with their minds.
Don't underestimate them.
Underestimate your enemy
and you'll get your ass kicked.
- [???]
- Shall we get on the shelter?
Let's go!
Let's take advantage of the daylight.
I spent the last five years
away from it all, in the Maui jungle.
So when it comes to setting up camp,
getting to know the environment,
find food, all that...
Let me help you on that.
It's like it's my home.
I want to help, guide my team
in the direction that I consider necessary.
The beach is on this side.
But do this by supporting them
and putting them in a good mood,
and that they know they
can count on me.
Shall we form a group
to bring back all this gear?
- Let's go!
- We're making an A-frame for the shelter?
This area is nice.
Yes. If you could
take this debris
and pile them up...
Once dry, it can be used
as kindling.
When I was running
to collect items,
I found something
in a nice envelope.
Need more bamboo?
Yeah.
It's Survivor. It could be
a lot of wonderful things.
And I don't want to
be found with,
because I think
that would make me a target.
"Congratulations, you have found
The Heir's Advantage.
If you have this message
on the 36th day,
you will receive
an advantage in the game.
If you are eliminated,
you will have to bequeath it
to another player."
It's the first time in Survivor
that there is this Heir Advantage.
If I'm still here on the 36th day,
I will receive an advantage in the game.
This is a good thing.
And I will be there on the 36th day.
So no one but me
will have this.
I want to baptize one of the chickens.
I don't want to call him Tai,
otherwise I won't be able to kill him.
Can you help me with the chickens?
At home,
I am the center of attention.
I like to flirt.
And I'm good
at manipulating men.
I risk splitting my head!
People think
I'm just a pretty face,
they don't know
the brain behind it.
I might end up making
the million AND getting myself a husband.
Did you see
the cocos we brought back?
- There are other things to bring.
- On the beach ?
On and goes?
Where is everyone?
I do not like it.
- I do not like it. Where are they ?
- They're looking for idols.
Seriously !
But seriously, where are they?
I don't like separation.
I like to know where everyone is.
You, him and me,
it works between us, there.
Yeah, I know.
We need, like, three more,
but we're out of the question.
No, I know, me neither, but...
Join the discussion!
We three are welded.
Jay and I
had a connection from the start.
Then Taylor is my
blue-eyed hottie,
and I find it too crunchy.
I'm tired, my hands are shaking.
Biceps, buddy!
And I knew
that these two boys were close.
So of course, I want to be in it,
it's going to be solid.
We're invincible,
we're, like... The Triforce!
I love Taylor.
Taylor is my buddy.
I can tell
because he's like my friends
at home.
It's like, "Hey,
the waves are nice, let's go!"
Michelle is with us or what?
Because she...
- Who is Michelle?
- The one who travels and...
- Namaste?
- The Christian.
Yeah, she's with us.
Besides, Figgy is cool.
this is my band,
I really like them,
they're great.
Who do you feel good?
You me...
- Him, cool.
- Cool.
But you and me, that's for sure.
And then I have Namaste,
whose name is actually Michelle.
I know we're cool.
And she's super good too,
by the way. Super good.
You know ? I hate to hear,
"I slept like a baby.",
because I have known babies
and they don't sleep at all!
They sleep very badly!
I look around,
and it makes me nervous to see
all the beautiful faces
of "Kappa Kappa Survivor",
because I don't want to be
the obvious first eliminated.
But it's hard when
you don't fit in immediately.
I'm still trying
to remember all the names.
Me too.
- Michelle.
- Michelle, okay.
So you're doing missionary
for the Bible?
It's nice.
- It's cool.
- Actually, I'm a recruiter.
How do you approach people?
"Do you like Bibles? That's it!"
I'm just a Jewess
who doesn't know anything about the Bible!
I think I am seen
as a sincere person,
no doubt by my faith,
by my belief.
So people approach me.
I created a little bond with Jay.
And Hannah told me
she would trust me.
And in this game,
trust you,
to be seen as someone
who cares about others,
it is very beneficial.
You and me, we're doing fine.
- Do we dig and build from there?
- Alright, let's do this.
How deep
do you want this hole to be?
I think we should...
- How far do you want to dig?
- Not too deep.
Afterwards, I would like to put...
You can leave that.
What is "not too deep"?
I need two [???]
and small pieces of [???].
That's not 15 cm.
We have to dig some more.
You see ?
- We're in business here!
- In effect.
You like to play more than work.
You you you !
You like to laugh.
I have to keep him focused!
Really ?
Rachel wants too much.
She is too confrontational.
In a forming group,
it can bring
a lot of negativity.
And people don't like that.
Are you gonna do
what you were supposed to do,
namely to collect wood
for the fire?
I think you and me
should take the machete
and we build this damn thing,
because it's a lot of talk, but...
I know, I will.
We need four corners,
obviously.
And I think it takes one
in the middle of each side, that's six.
Honestly, I've never
built a shelter before.
But I'm good
at following orders and...
Welcome to the club !
I don't like sleeping outside,
bugs or the sun.
I don't like water or the ocean.
All of these things are horrible.
What I like is strategy, that's
what I'm here for.
- Do we just knock on it?
- Yeah, let's knock!
Wow, that hits well!
Just there ?
Yeah, right after the join.
Dave is afraid of his shadow.
I was cutting a bamboo
and he was jumping and covering
his ears, like, it's too loud!
Cover your ears!
Dave better toughen up.
The girls at camp
have more testosterone than him!
It's almost there.
Not complicated, right?
I believe
they have found the immunity idol.
Why ?
They had
something in their hands and...
I think they have it.
- Who is it ?
- It's... Ken and Paul.
- You think ?
- Yes.
We should intercept them.
What do you say ? Is it weird?
Better we all know
that than suspect it.
- I doubt. Why do you believe that?
- That thing in his left hand.
- He doesn't hide it.
- Clearly.
He plays the innocent,
he doesn't want it to show.
No, they would have fled
into the woods. I can not believe.
I don't want to be paranoid.
But that's downright suspicious.
Keep an eye on his hand, and if he comes back
with something that looks like [???]...
He will come back with nothing.
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
If he comes back with something...
If he comes back with nothing,
he has an idol.
Dave was very paranoid.
He is afraid.
He is also funny, sometimes,
and also quite charming.
I like you, I trust you,
I hope it's mutual.
If I hear your name mentioned,
I'll tell you.
Chris! Chris, Chris, Chris, Chris!
I believe in you. OK ?
I believe in you. If I hear
your name mentioned, I'm coming to see you.
Please do the same for me.
I'll try to find out what's going on.
Stay cool.
No. Everything is fine.
The paranoia started.
He does way too much.
He stirs things up
and talks strategy.
I think it's too early
to go all the way there.
It's funny, though.
- The game is started.
- I say !
He's a little paranoid,
it makes me a little nervous.
The wind picks up.
I don't know if that's a good sign.
It's not the moment.
- Should we pick him up?
- Yeah.
As the first night approaches,
I'm very nervous because...
Our shelter is disaster!
We don't really have a roof,
but everyone here thinks
that everything will be fine.
Do we get naked? Nope !
Oh my God !
Believe my experience,
not a good idea!
I say. I do not want...
But we are Gen Y, who cares!
Everyone is very excited,
very happy to get to know
the others.
Alright, let's have a blast, kids!
I look at the sky, it's darkening
and it will only get worse.
But no one seems to care.
Come on, team!
The difference
between Gen X and Gen Y,
is that Gen Xers believe
in spending time
to achieve its goals.
Gen Y don't believe it.
They think
if we set a goal
and that we are not afraid to dream,
we can realize it now.
I don't know what they are doing.
Mom says, "Come back now!"
Our projects are all half finished.
We were partying on the beach,
we realized it was getting darker.
We came back in a hurry,
because the shelter was not built.
Come on, guys,
I need some palm fronds!
Here is one.
We tried to install
palm fronds,
to keep us dry,
we thought the rain was coming.
We were rushing to build the shelter,
Jay and I trying to put the roof together.
It was clearly one of the worst shelters
in Survivor history.
Be careful !
We all went into the shelter,
but with the weight, it sank.
How are you ?
- Nope. Oh my God !
- [???]
Oh no ! Apparently
there is a weight limit.
And it ended up crashing.
I thought to myself, "No chance
that we finish the shelter in time."
I'm a little scared
that our shelter
is not yet one.
I know it's not finished, but...
It is a work in progress.
It will be fine.
We will survive this night.
We are doomed !
It's going to be horrible!
What's going on ?
We were terrified,
because it was the flood
and we had no shelter.
We were sitting in the rain,
freezing.
It's the worst thing I've ever known
the longest night of my life.
I was shaking.
You could feel people
breaking down mentally.
We believe it will never end.
We heard
rumblings,
thunder and lightning,
and we saw the storm,
in the distance on the water,
approaching us.
Like monsters
coming to catch us
and punish us
for not having built a shelter.
It doesn't seem to be stopping anytime soon.
We must continue.
- I think they should be cut.
- Yeah.
What a rotten day.
My hands are...
- I can't do anything about it.
- Look at mine!
Oh, damn it!
Do not say that.
We spent a night in hell.
It seems so easy, with you!
We didn't finish our shelter in time
and it started to rain.
Oh, my God, it's so cold!
And it never stopped.
And it never stopped!
And it never stopped
raining!
And it's still raining!
Oh yeah, that one is twisted.
This sheet
is not terrible either, sorry.
- The mail !
- And a package!
- Oh, Lord!
It's big! Is it a tarp?
It's probably four tarps.
The mail ! Come on all of you,
it's the first !
- Some mail !
- Is it a tarp?
Mail is cool,
but I want to see this.
"It's an unusually strong storm
and it will last.
I know you have
n't had time to build a shelter,
so as a gesture of goodwill,
receive the protection of this tarpaulin
until you can
protect yourselves.
When the rain stops,
bring me the tarp.
If I have to come and pick her up,
it'll cost you more than a tarp.
Good luck,
and try to stay dry.
I don't think they knew
what was coming.
Do we put it above the leaves?
I don't remember a tribe
has ever received a tarp.
We hang it here, like this?
We'll see
what some are made of.
It's going to be a tough season
of Survivor, in my opinion.
This time
will be something for which
none of us are ready.
"As a gesture of goodwill,
receive the protection of this tarpaulin
until you can
protect yourselves.
Good luck,
and try to stay dry.
Big hugs, Jeff."
He does not say "big kisses"!
You know it's bad
if Jeff gives you a tarp.
You don't even have to earn it,
it arrives in the mail.
That's also when we knew
the weather was going to get worse.
So we have a job.
Alright, you wanna
tear it all up on the shelter?
Put that up there.
Watch your head!
I would rank our camp
at the "pig barn" level.
It's just a puddle of mud
with bits of bamboo
planted haphazardly.
And I'm like, "Great.
We're building the base, we've got a tarp,
it will be less bad
than the time before."
But it's hard,
because the rain never stops.
And last night
was one of the worst of my life.
So I don't see
how it could get worse.
- That's not bad.
- OK. It holds... Almost.
Well tight !
Oh ! What is this...?!
Oh, my God, Probst!
We were there, in the mud
created by the storm,
and Jeff Probst shows up
quietly on the camp.
And I don't know what's gonna happen
but I'm a little nervous.
Are these the traces of last night?
- Nobody slept.
- We haven't slept at all.
The storm is getting worse.
We thought the tarp
would help you support it.
But in the last few hours,
she has been recategorized again.
It is now a cyclone.
And we predict that tonight
it will be much worse
than last night.
What does it mean ?
So for the first time
in 33 seasons of Survivor,
we will evacuate you.
Oh my God !
Is that a bad thing?
It means it's serious.
It's serious !
My jaw dropped.
It is unprecedented!
This is unheard of !
There have been nasty storms
in Survivor,
but that's never happened
in 33 seasons of Survivor.
This is what will happen.
You will gather
your personal belongings,
take your chickens,
we're not going to leave them here.
You wanted adventure?
You have some !
Good.
Where are you going?
We just arrived!
Everything will be completely destroyed.
It's no joke.
It's for real.
It's a real cyclone
and real lives are at stake.
If the storm returns, we're finished.
It's wide open.
If it crosses,
we will take it directly.
- Yeah, it's not good.
- Look !
- Jeff!
- What ?!
It's him !
- What's going on ?
- [???] The tarpaulin.
Seeing Jeff,
I stopped breathing.
What's up, Jeff?
I knew
something was wrong,
because Jeff very rarely comes
to the camp,
unless
it's a security issue.
Hi all !
- Thanks for the tarp.
- Thanks.
Yes. That's why I'm here.
The tropical storm
I told you about yesterday
gains in intensity.
She was again recategorized.
It's a hurricane.
So,
we will get you off
this beach,
take you to a safe place
until it passes.
Can we take our bags
before leaving?
Your personal affairs.
The rest...
We'll see what we have in the morning.
Good !
Do we put the food and the gear
in the shelter?
[???] bad idea.
Wow, the wind is coming.
A cyclone is going to hit today,
and I'm not surprised, actually.
The weather is going to be terrible tonight.
We will therefore be evacuated.
Lord God!
Welcome, rain!
Oh my God !
Go up, go up!
Oh shit.
- The biggest tree fell.
- Yeah, he broke everything.
We would have...
clearly been hurt.
On the 3rd day, we returned to the camp
after the passage of the cyclone.
Everything was overturned
and a tree had fallen
on our shelter.
We thought,
"Lord, this is scary!"
We talk about our lives.
A falling tree
could injure someone.
It was good that we were evacuated.
It was clearly a good thing
that Jeff decided to do this.
We have work.
Alright, let's start clearing!
- Well received, let's get started!
- Yeah, let's go!
The first few days in Survivor
are all about building a shelter.
And I suck at it.
And we had to do it twice.
No one perceives me
as physically strong.
- Dave, do you need help?
- Its good !
So they have no reason
to want to keep me.
So it all resonates with me,
this paranoia,
this nervousness, this anxiety,
that I am in danger.
I've always been neurotic.
I've been afraid of dying
since birth,
I think about it every day.
You mean, afraid of dying
on a plane, of drowning...?
- Die in general.
- In general.
I do not want to die.
Because, you know...
So here you are really
out of your element.
I came to broaden my horizons,
it's the best way.
Want something new?
Take this little guy!
Don't, don't!
It's just a stick insect,
it's harmless.
- Are you sure ?
- [???]
- Except walking around on you.
- It doesn't sting?
- Are you sure ?
- Yes.
There is little hope for me
in this Survivor game.
But I'm a Gen X,
I'm not giving up.
I will work hard
to make it work.
I will reverse
the situation for me.
I have
to start researching the immunity idol thoroughly.
It may be the only thing
that can save me.
Dave is looking for an idol.
Where ? On the beach ?
On the track there.
- He lost his mind.
- I want to know what he's doing.
He was looking up there.
We need to calm him down,
before it gets out of hand.
You must be really stupid.
Dave was madly looking for an idol
while we were building the shelter.
And that pissed off a lot of people.
If David has an idol,
That would probably complicate
things later on.
So if we lose, it will be David.
I have an idea for the roof.
You can take
bamboo strips
and tie them firmly.
OK.
We come back to camp
and it's a mess.
We have the base of the shelter,
but no roof.
So we had
to tinker with the shelter.
And I led the construction
of the second shelter.
It has to be
at the height of the roof.
I don't know how to build a shelter.
I live in Brooklyn!
Taking the metro is the limit
of my outdoor skills.
Keep putting them through.
But you know what ?
I took the plunge and did it.
And against all odds,
I became the boss.
I never see myself as the one
who will adapt to the outside.
Go on, go on, go on!
You and it is, you and it is!
I'm not like that.
But the idea of ​​proving
my toughness intrigues me.
You and it is, mec!
We are there, we are there!
So strangely,
Survivor helps me
reach my potential.
- Fire !
- Come on !
We have fire
and I made it!
I never imagined
that I would be the one
who would make a fire without flint!
We did it !
Yeah, my hen!
It is a moment in my life
to mark with a white stone.
I am a new man.
The master of fire!
They say Survivor changes people,
I feel changed already.
Dude, nothing will be the same!
I feel like I'm growing here.
I am affected by this experience,
in a very positive way.
I'm very proud of myself here.
- We are solid, do you think?
- But yes.
I adore you both.
- I say. Me too.
- We're a big threat.
I know I know.
- Honestly...
- Yo, we're solid!
- The Triforce!
- Damn, I love you!
By observing the group,
I started to notice
that there really is
a kind of division
between canon high school students
and weird nerds.
The cannons against the marginalized.
And it looks like the marginalized
are going to be in the minority.
So, what do you think
of the tribe so far?
Figgy and the boys are dangerous.
So I have to nip this in the bud.
I just want one person
in this game to trust.
And I don't want the
great-looking dorks to win.
You know what ? Remaining in the majority
is important, at the beginning.
It can take two directions.
That of the handsome
or that of the marginalized, us.
We can say so!
The group of cool hunks
isolates himself from the tribe.
So we have to break up this group.
I want to play with...
- Marginals.
- Outcasts.
My goal is to play
like I would play video games.
So at this point I gather
the marginalized, the excluded,
in a way.
They isolate themselves at four.
So I started to insinuate
than the four foppish ones
were inseparable.
Figgy is very aggressive.
She holds the reins.
And that is dangerous.
So while we have the majority,
this is our opportunity to strike.
Over here, everyone!
Good.
First, I'm glad to see
the two tribes bringing back their tarps.
Thanks a lot.
You can drop them off
and leave them there.
Ready for your first
immunity test?
This is what you covet
in this game.
The immunity idol.
In possession of this,
you are safe.
Without, you risk elimination.
Today
you will make choices
who will help you either at the beginning
or at the end of the event.
Here's how it works.
You will dash under an obstacle
and retrieve a war club.
Then comes a rope tunnel.
You can cross in the state
or use a shortcut
which will make it much easier.
You will then reach a beam.
You can cross as is
or use a shortcut
which will make it much easier.
You will then carry a crate
to the finish
and solve a puzzle
with the pieces it contains.
Here is the dilemma.
Every shortcut used
add ten pieces to the puzzle.
So if you think you're
good at puzzles,
you might want
to take the shortcut,
rush to the end
and attack him as soon as possible.
If you are unsure about
the puzzle,
you may have to cross
the course as it is,
knowing that you will be behind,
but that you can reassemble
with a smaller puzzle.
This test will be decided
according to the group which, in a few days,
will have learned
its strengths and weaknesses.
The first to finish
win immunity,
are safe from the vote, and in addition...
Fire, in the form of flint.
The losers will go to the board
where someone will be
the first person eliminated
of Survivor,
Generation Y versus Generation X.
One minute to get organized
and we'll get started.
Who will get the club?
- I will do it.
- The big one ?
- I'll take care of the big one.
- Are you sure ?
Who does the puzzle, at the end?
- Him and Rachel.
- Unless someone is very good.
The beam may be...
We have to take the shortcut
on the beam.
- Without even trying?
- Yeah.
Well, on and go.
For immunity and fire.
Survivors, ready?
First step, detach
all your clubs.
Two on each side.
There's already a fight down there.
Jay and Chris face off!
You must untie all your clubs.
These
and those along the pole.
Go to your mat,
wait for the others!
Everyone must be there,
with all your clubs.
- I'll hold his hands.
- I'm holding his hands.
Chris blocks two Gen Ys, alone.
They cannot reach their clubs.
You must all be gathered.
Do we have them all?
It's a fight!
Chris is out.
Two Gen Ys are missing!
Go ahead, Gen X!
On the eye!
Gen X
will take the first shortcut.
Rachel takes a long time.
Its good ! Go for it !
Gen Ys
don't take shortcuts.
From the outset, Gen X
greatly simplifies the obstacle.
A wise choice, given their size.
They opened it.
Gen Ys are much finer.
They cross
without taking the shortcut.
The Gen X are in the lead.
Here is Paul, the most imposing,
finishing the obstacle!
Go ahead, Gen X!
Gen X will take
the second shortcut.
Go for it !
Gen X
took both shortcuts.
Go for it!
Forward, forward!
Gen Y are always
on the first hurdle.
They may regret
not taking the shortcut.
Huge advance for Gen X.
They arrive at the last post
where they will work
on the most difficult puzzle.
Go ahead, Gen Y!
And There you go ! The Y Gens
are going to take the second shortcut.
Ahead !
Gen X
took both shortcuts.
They will work
on a 70 piece puzzle.
Take a handful!
Here are Gen Y,
who took advantage of a shortcut.
They will work
on a 60 piece puzzle.
They have ten coins less.
Gen X have ten more.
Their puzzle
is significantly more difficult.
They are far behind us,
they have many more coins!
It's David and Rachel
and it's Michelle and Figgy.
Everything will depend on how quickly you
solve this puzzle.
Gen Y
are starting to pick up the pace.
They see their puzzle taking shape.
David and Rachel squandered
the lead taken with the shortcuts.
If you see something,
tell me!
We can't see,
you want to exchange?
Yeah, go!
You go-y !
David and Rachel leave.
Jessica and Sunday replace them.
They try to make up for
all the lost time.
More progress among Gen Y.
Ignore it, you progress.
Gen Xers
are starting to make progress.
It starts to take shape.
It's good !
Only a few pieces
left for Gen Y.
Gen X
are desperately trying to come back up.
There are [???] on both sides.
Rachel offers a lot of help
from the side.
She was there first
and couldn't do anything.
Not nothing !
I did something !
This one goes sideways.
This one there.
Gen Y are getting closer to the goal.
More than the one in the middle!
Gen Ys
gain first immunity
and the reward!
Sending a signal to Gen X.
One, two, three, Gen Y!
Gen Y, congratulations!
The first immunity.
Who wants it?
Congratulation.
No one will leave
the Gen Y tribe.
Also, fire in the form of flint.
Not that we need it!
Take your things,
return to camp.
Gen X. For one of you,
that will be the end of the road.
Tonight,
someone will be eliminated from this game.
The first person eliminated.
Nobody wants to go through this.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
The test did not go
as expected.
It was a disaster.
Rachel was barking orders.
David, who claimed to be
the king of the puzzle, screwed up.
So these two are in danger.
I wanted so much to beat Gen Y,
and I really believed in it.
We have a lot of
strong and experienced people.
I really thought
that we would eclipse them today,
and I'm shocked that we lost.
Never do that again.
I approve.
They are fast. They are lively.
But we had a strategy
for the start of the event.
We got fucked on the puzzle.
In the immunity test,
Rachel tells everyone
she knows how to do puzzles,
that's his thing.
And she fucks us all.
I'm going to fetch water.
Anyone want some?
Let's go.
You want to come ? Great.
- Are you going in the water?
- Yeah, we have to go wash up.
We have to wash up.
We have to win races.
Physically,
we were there.
You two, sorry,
but you should have done the puzzle,
because you would have succeeded
with a little more time.
If you say, "I'm doing the puzzle!",
and then you fail,
then you disqualify yourself.
If a person does not insure
in an event,
it will always
shine the spotlight on her.
That's how things go here.
I think we're good with her.
So for now,
we're going to vote for Rachel.
But my fear is of course
that someone has an idol.
- We're in agreement, huh?
- Absolutely.
Everyone is strategizing
without including me.
I don't think anyone
trusts me at this point.
I know my position in the game.
My head is on the block.
I'm thinking of leaving tonight.
Hey, I'd like to talk to you
when you have a moment.
- I don't want to leave tonight.
- Yeah.
I'm ready to write
whatever name you like.
Good.
I want certainty
that you don't have an idol.
100% I don't.
And believe me, I would love to,
I would play it tonight.
- But no.
- We would have made an agreement, otherwise.
I don't have one,
so what, okay?
You seem to think I have one.
But no, really not.
Well, I know rumor
has it you have one.
I tell you everything, I explain to you.
That's exactly
what went through my head.
I got a little paranoid
I had the impression
not to be included
in the strategies and everything.
So what I did...
Yes, I came here,
I searched the area,
hoping to find something.
Of course, you can
write my name, it's your choice.
I hope not.
If you don't,
you'll have my loyalty.
I think David has an idol
despite his denials.
And that makes me very nervous.
So I want him to be comfortable.
Don't be paranoid and you'll be fine.
- I appreciate.
- Yes, it will be fine.
My decision is, Rachel or David.
It's interesting,
they talk to everyone except me.
Rachel is useless in trial.
For me, it's a handicap.
And I might vote David tonight,
because I believe he has an idol.
Its good ? Its good.
I appreciate.
But if I have six people,
that's enough to split the votes.
And I think we got me, Chris,
So, Cece, Ken, Rachel and Dave
will be excluded from the decision.
- It's Rachel or him.
- Yes, Rachel or him.
Let's divide the votes.
Pass the word to Sunday and then...
- Who do you think they are thinking about?
- I do not know.
I wonder if people think
I've given up on the puzzle.
- We sit together tonight, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
Something weird is going on, isn't it?
- Do you see alliances forming?
- Yes.
Say no more words.
I do not know.
I don't really know
what's going on.
I never imagined
feeling this so early in the game.
I believe Cece and I
are in danger.
What do you think ?
I do not know,
I haven't had time
to think about it.
- I do not believe it.
- Believe it!
It's not a good sign
when people tell you, "I don't know."
So I'm not too sure
where I stand.
- Relax, man!
- I appreciate.
I am at the mercy of my comrades.
I'm my own worst enemy
in the game, I've been paranoid.
I hope that the speech
that I made to them
will be enough
to reassure
them and save me.
I'm afraid not.
I'm almost sure not.
But I won't know until the council.
Behind you, torches.
Take one,
approach the fire,
immerse it and light it.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears
you too.
Alas,
one of you will be tonight.
But let's start at the beginning,
because those first days
were among the hardest
never experienced by Survivors.
Jessica, even looking at your eyes!
What's going on ?
When we had to be evacuated
because of the cyclone,
the winds
were deliriously strong,
raising a lot of sand.
I took sand in the right eye.
I now have
a bacterial infection in my eye,
which went into the other eye.
Bret, even when I approached
the beach,
the sand was bombarding me violently,
and the storm was not yet here.
I thought it was comparable
to a northeast storm in Boston,
but I think
it was ten times worse.
It was intense.
It felt
like it would never end.
- David.
- Oh, shit!
- Sorry ?
- I said, "Oh, shit!"
Why, "Oh, shit!" ?
Because he is afraid of everything!
He is afraid of everything.
Wow, David,
all nine say it in unison!
This is the first time I have camped
in 21 years.
The world where I feel
safe has shrunk.
But here, in nature,
I am stripped of everything
and I am transparent.
It's as if these four days
had lasted a year.
I am very happy
with this experience.
These are the words of someone
who wouldn't mind leaving.
"I am very happy
with this experience."
I don't want to leave tonight.
But I risk leaving.
My worst enemy in the game,
honestly, is myself.
That's what
I'm up against here.
Cece, do you sympathize
with David's pain?
No one wants to be eliminated,
but above all,
no one wants to be the first.
Of course, I sympathize.
You dreamed of being in Survivor
and you risk leaving...
I wouldn't wish that on anyone.
It's horrible.
Sunday, is it great
to hear someone say,
"It could be me." ?
Absolutely, because,
you know, I love David,
but we all want to stay.
And if someone gets attention,
it turns it away from you
and you may
be less likely to leave.
Among you ten,
who, in the last few days,
thought, "That could be me." ?
All of us !
Chris, is this
a real impression
or just this paranoia,
"Who knows
if they are frank with me?"
Probably just paranoia.
On the second day, I thought I was isolated.
I actually thought,
"My God, I'm going out on the first
and it's going to be hell when I get home.
But I thought,
"It's probably in my head.
I'm going to show them
that I can work hard."
And I feel much better today.
Rachel, how about you?
Tell me about the time you
thought, "Maybe I'm in trouble."
Today, in fact,
when everyone seemed undecided,
without reaction and approached.
These were very unusual behaviors .
So I don't feel comfortable.
Either it's paranoia
or I'll walk away.
Why would it be you?
I do not know.
I may have been very frank.
I say what I think
as I think.
It's not out of malice
or to intentionally injure.
I don't hurt
feelings on purpose.
Whether they vote for me or not,
I want to do my mea culpa.
I apologize to everyone
if I have offended you.
Good. Let's talk about idols.
Jessica, what do you think?
Are there any idols in play?
Could anyone here have some?
There are clearly idols
in this game.
And some
have had opportunities to look for it.
It must have played a part
in David's paranoia,
because that is one of the concerns
that have arisen about him.
And we come back to David!
Yeah, isn't that great?
You know,
I respect that answer.
I want to prove tonight
that you can trust me.
So it's a test.
Good. It's time to vote.
Paul, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
What what. A Cece vote,
one David vote, one Rachel vote.
Rachel.
That's two votes Rachel.
Cece.
That's two Cece votes.
Equality. Three votes Cece,
three votes Rachel,
a David vote.
Rachel.
Four votes Rachel,
three votes Cece,
one vote remains.
First person eliminated
from Survivor, Gen Y against Gen X...
Rachel.
Bring me your torch.
Rachel, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
One of the distinctive traits
of Generation X,
hard work doesn't scare you.
And you've clearly been
working hard these past few days.
The big question is,
how are you going to recover
from these Gen Y?
Good news,
fire, in the form of flint,
will be waiting for you at camp.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
There is romance in the air.
I have Chimene's eyes.
Man, couples don't last.
Sometimes women blind you.
Wake up !
And someone's stay
could be cut short.
Breathe, my friend.
He may have had
a heart attack.
It could be positive for me.
Survivor is...
one of the toughest and most brutal
social games on the planet.
But I'm happy
to have had this experience.
I hope to use it
to improve myself.
Surviving the elements
is much harder
as you might think on TV.
But for the most part,
I had a lot of fun.