Previously on Survivor.
At the Millennial Tribe, Viggy and Taylor couldn't hide their love.
At the Gen X Tribe, a blindsided Brett and Chris sought revenge on Jessica.
But David and Ken wanted to save her.
It's your one aim going down.
My mom says they're gunning for me, but it seems a little suspicious.
At Tribal Council, David played his idol for Jessica.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Saving her and sending Lucy home.
Lucy, the tribe has spoken.
Sixteen are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Y'all can let me have it now or not, it's up to you.
I'm not mad at you, David.
I'm not mad at you.
I ain't either.
I'm just curious why I like the dramatics.
I played an idol tonight, but I don't know that playing that idol was the right move
because I saved someone who nobody really wants to work with.
And now I don't have an idol and I'm incredibly vulnerable.
I owe Dave and you so much and I'm sorry I didn't listen.
I shouldn't have.
Can I tell you something I haven't told anybody?
I found a legacy advantage.
So if I'm still here on day 36, I will receive an advantage in the game.
If I had been voted out, I would have handed it to you because you were trying to help
me.
I told Ken about the legacy advantage because I wanted him to know that he can trust me.
So I'm hoping that that bought me some more goodwill.
I'm really, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry about it.
No, I am.
Jess says that she has a legacy and she's going to share it with me.
That means a lot.
I'm giving Jess my full trust again.
This game just messes with you so much.
You have those.
We're going to look everywhere.
Ain't no shame today.
Am I right, CeCe?
What?
Ain't no shame in looking for the idol today.
Ain't no shame in looking for the idol.
I'm telling you, man.
Since the immunity was flagged, the immunity idol is back up for grabs.
So we kind of like had an idol search party.
It's an interesting little area over here.
It is.
We openly were on the hunt for a hidden immunity idol.
I felt empowered by the fact that I was the only one that knew to look for a symbol of
our tribe.
But the one issue with an open idol hunt is that everybody is looking for the idol and
you might be seen having found it.
So frustrating.
Keep looking, Sunday.
So I'm wandering the jungle and then I just turn and I spot on the ground a log with our
tribe symbol on it.
Right nearby was Sunday and CeCe.
And I'm thinking, oh, this is the worst.
This is the worst.
A log.
You know what, you?
No.
Oh my God.
This is exhausting.
Eventually CeCe gets bored.
She goes back to camp.
So does Sunday.
Oh, yes.
Yep.
That's the sound of an idol inside.
All right.
I know you're in there.
Immunity Isle.
I found the other one.
Oh my God.
I can't believe that I was so fortunate to play an idol and then find it again the very
next day.
Congratulations.
You found the Hidden Immunity Isle.
The Hidden Immunity Isle will keep you safe from being voted off of tribal council.
To be able to do what I love and crave.
I've tasted no victory in my real life that compares to the victory that I feel right
now in Survivor.
It's just a shame that it took me till 42 years of age to get it.
But I want to be that guy because that's going to get me further in this game.
Here I go, guys.
Millennials, get in your face.
You're doing it.
I'm doing it.
get in your first look at the new Gen X tribe.
Lucy voted out at the last tribal council.
All right, shall we get to it?
Yes.
Well, there are so many elements to the game of Survivor.
Knots and puzzles you can practice in your backyard.
You can go to therapy, learn how to get along with people better.
But there are some elements that you have absolutely no control over,
and yet they can change your game just like that.
Everybody, drop your buffs.
We're switching things up.
To be a little more interesting,
not only going to mix up the tribes,
we're going to switch from two tribes to three tribes.
Oh, my God!
Expansion.
If you draw an orange buff,
you will return to what was the Millennial Beach.
Your new tribe name will be Vanua.
If you draw a purple buff,
you'll return to what was Gen X.
Your new tribe name is Tikali.
If you draw a green buff,
you will go to a new beach.
Your tribe name will be Icabula,
and you will have to start from scratch.
Oh, my God.
To help offset that work,
you will have one extra tribe member.
All right, shall we see what's going to happen?
Yeah. Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Get this over with.
Oh, and oh, and oh, and.
Don't open them yet.
Oh, my God.
The swap is random.
You have no idea what's going to happen,
especially, like, me and Figs
with this, like, little romance going on.
Iggy grabs.
My biggest fear right now is getting split up.
Give me something good, Jeff.
Moment of truth, baby.
Oh.
Let's do it. Everybody reveal.
Oh, my God.
If you're green, you go in the middle,
where there is no map.
Hold them up once you get it.
Put them on. Damn it.
Mikayla, green and not happy.
I'm purple.
Is that good? Purple, purple.
Brett is green.
Jay is green.
Hi. Hi, I'm Hannah.
Boy, Mikayla is wearing it on her face.
Hi, Hannah. Nice to meet you.
Hey, guys.
Give her a hug, buddy.
Hugs are good.
Nice to meet you.
All right, let's take a look at our new tribes.
To Kali, we have three millennials,
Taylor, Figgy, and Adam,
along with two Gen Xers,
Jessica and Ken.
Figgy, you're smiling big.
I'm just pumped up, man.
Honestly, like, I see success from here.
Rock on.
Big tales continue.
Like, I was so stoked
because I've got the numbers and I have Fig,
so it could not go any better for me.
The newa, we have three Gen Xers,
Cece, Chris, and Dave,
and two millennials, Zeke and Michelle.
Zeke, you were on the majority tribe.
With a winning streak, you're now in the minority
on a tribe of only five, not many places to hide.
Yeah, it's tricky.
The numbers are definitely not in my favor.
But, you know, I look around,
I see a strong tribe, I see a tribe
that I think can continue the winning streak.
And for Iqabula,
we have four millennials,
Makayla, Hannah, Jay, and Will,
and two Gen Xers, Sunday and Brett.
Makayla, you still seem unhappy right now.
You didn't do this right, Jeff. Just saying.
All right, fair enough. I'll take it.
I open up my buff and I see green.
Man, I was pissed.
You gonna send us to an empty beach
where we gotta make the shelter
and we don't have any food.
I just wanted to flick them off right there,
but I didn't.
Iqabula, map to your home.
Good luck building that shelter.
Thanks.
All right, head out.
Get to know your new tribes.
This was like the disaster scenario.
I'm on the one tribe where the millennials
are not in the numbers, and I'm with Michelle,
the one person from my tribe I have zero trust in.
And we're outnumbered, so we're in a bad spot.
MUSIC
Do you guys want an introduction?
Oh, yeah, let's do it.
Brett. Jay. Jay.
Will. Will.
Makayla. Makayla.
Sunday. Sunday and I are in serious trouble right now.
But Gen Xers, we have the drive to get through
tough times in life and not to quit.
All right, so we hit the well,
and then we'll get to the shelter.
Yeah.
So I need to prove to them that I'm worth keeping around,
because right now it's just all about surviving this game.
Let's do it.
MUSIC
On the millennial side of things,
everyone says we're just dreamers.
But the truth is, most of us are relentless.
So do you want to make indentation in that one?
You know what I'm saying? So it could sit on it?
I have no idea what you're saying.
Kind of like this?
The Gen Xers said, oh, we work hard,
and we do things the right way.
But the people that I have right now,
I got Brett and Sunday.
And it just sucks because they can't figure things out
for themselves, and they just sit back
and wait for you to say something.
We're going to put two like this.
OK. Kid knows how to do everything, huh?
Oh, that's cool, huh?
But even if I got to build a new shelter,
I'm happy, because we have the numbers.
Four millennials, two Gen Xers.
See you later, Gen Xers, because I'm chilling
even if I lose a challenge.
I don't care.
Boom, you're out of here.
This is now your home.
Yay!
Well done. Super cool.
So different than ours.
You guys want a tour?
Yeah.
Let's do it, man.
Coming back to camp was interesting.
The millennials definitely bring some high energy,
some goofy energy to the tribe.
Do you guys have a goat looser?
No.
We have a goat that's loose.
If I catch that thing, it is dead.
If you guys want a song...
Hopefully, Jess and I being more grounded
and more subtle with the way that we speak
and the way we do things can help us.
Oh, I'm so happy.
This is awesome.
You should not hug me.
So are we doing that?
Yeah.
Even though we have numbers?
Yeah, yeah.
Screw that.
It sucks, Vic.
You said no.
Oh, yeah.
I said no.
No contact.
Taylor thinks because we have the numbers
that we can be out in the open.
No.
Sorry, Taylor.
I love you to pieces,
but being with these new people,
that's gonna put a target on our back,
so it's not smart.
Does it really matter, though?
Yeah.
Like, that matters?
Fine.
Trust me.
I trust you.
I just think it's stupid.
Get over it.
But you know you're gonna do what she says.
I know.
Vic doesn't want anything to do with me.
She's like, stay away from me, stay away from me.
But I really think that us being a power couple
isn't any different than two people in an alliance
that really trust each other.
We'll do taro, eggplant, pepper, stir fry with some fish.
That's perfect.
I love it.
I was thinking boiling these separate,
just to soften them,
and then I'll stir fry the rest.
Sounds great to me.
Getting swapped into a tribe with only Taylor and Figgy
from my original millennial tribe,
it's my worst nightmare.
Figgy is very controlling.
She lies constantly,
and she's gonna go through this charade as long as she can
about how they are not a couple.
I don't know how long that will last,
but I think it's gonna be a great experience.
I think it's gonna be a great experience.
she decided that Gal way to be her friend
and today she and Fritz are not a couple.
I don't know how long that will last
because Taylor is ready to start canoodling again.
To me, that's a worthless partnership.
How did you feel over there?
Should feel like you were towards the top,
towards the bottom?
Right around down here.
But I'm third?
Was your name also up there?
No, but Figgies was.
And that was you?
Yeah.
Were you the only one that put Figgies' name down?
No, me and Mari and Zeke.
Adam's just like the nicest kid ever.
Kind of feel like I hit the jackpot.
He's super positive, he's respectful, he's polite,
and there's a little bit of a crack in the Millennials.
So hopefully Jess and I have got Adam.
I got your back, man. I think you seem cool.
Shake off all the dust.
Yep, yep.
Shake it off. It sucks.
Thanks, man.
Ken and Jessica, they seem to have a tight bond,
and I know that Figgie and Taylor won't turn on each other,
so I have pairs on both sides of me.
I'm the guy they need to come to,
I'm the guy they need to work with.
I get to decide which side moves forward.
Did you dream, Mr. Daisy?
I don't dream. I have no dreams.
Yeah, I very, very rarely remember a dream.
I mostly just sort of wake up and...
Good morning, Michelle.
Good morning.
Yeah, I'm going to go do your dream.
What about you, Dave? Did you dream?
This is the first time I think I had a dream since I got here.
Yeah, wow.
So you actually slept.
Yeah, exactly.
How'd you sleep?
Not too good.
Good, all right.
My whole game was turned upside down.
I happened to be on the only tribe with the minority Millennials,
just me and Zeke, and three Gen Xers.
Are you guys thinking we should slow cook the beans?
I'm not that hungry.
I'm a little worried if we have a challenge
that we won't have time to cook the beans.
That's true, that's a good thing.
My problem is that the Alliance might be stacked against me,
so I'm definitely scared.
You got it, Dave.
Oh, yeah.
I'm mixed. Where y'all are from?
Oklahoma.
Oklahoma?
I'm from Edmond.
I grew up here at 12 Springs Falls.
We're the Oakey Boys, man.
He's a Sooner Nation, too.
Okay.
Pennsylvania now, Ellen.
Did you play for the Sooners?
Yeah.
Who did you coach to play for?
Two years of Blake, two years of Stu.
Oh, so you were on the National Championships.
Yeah.
I see you didn't bring your ring out.
No, no ring out here.
Right, you can't lose a National Championship ring.
Yeah, you don't want to do that.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that was a good year.
Zeke's an Oklahoma boy, just like me.
Grew up in Oklahoma, probably an hour and a half from where I grew up.
He's a big Sooner fan, and of course I played on the last National Championship,
so we have that connection immediately.
I'm all broken down.
It hurts, man.
Oh, that cotton ball.
You ready?
I am feeling better on this new tribe than I did at the end of the Gen X,
because here I feel like I have a tad bit more control over my decisions
and how I'm going to play the game.
Hey, I want you to know right up front, y'all got a chance,
because I mean you need to talk before anything,
just because there's three of us doesn't mean anything.
Don't think you're just out, because I'm ready to make a move.
Chris played for my team, the University of Oklahoma Sooners.
Not only did he play for the Sooners, he was on the 2000 National Championship team.
These guys were my childhood heroes.
That National Championship was one of the biggest events of my childhood.
I got a game plan, and we can hash it out together and see what you think,
because right now I guarantee those two will want to just,
don't just want to hold you on out, and I got different plans.
Alright, who do I want to work with?
I want to work with the big ginger-haired football player,
who says, buddy, don't worry, things are not what they seem.
You are not on the bottom, and I want to work with you.
It's like the heavens open and the lights shine down,
and finally I catch a break in this game.
So we wake up this morning.
We don't have a fire yet, and I'm starving and I'm thirsty.
There you go.
Why doesn't that light, man?
I don't know. I don't understand.
I'm trying to use this flamethrower. I'm exhausted. I'm trying. I'm trying.
It just does not work for me, and I don't understand why,
and I'm just losing all hope, and I'm like, you know what, forget this.
How about it?
The fire got to a point where Jay gave up.
I was exhausted, but I was like, fire is necessary to our life in the game.
So I started trying deeper down.
There is this theme in my life that sometimes I get to a point
where I've given it all that I have, and I'm almost to the point of giving up,
and then I push a little further, and things pop.
I worked for things, working to put my own self through college,
working to pay off my own loans. I worked.
Good spot.
There it is.
There it is. Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Keep it going.
Oh, it works. Come on.
Michaela said, well, let me try, and she went berserk,
and all these sparks got coming out.
Next thing you know, boom, the whole thing ignited in the fire.
We were psyched, and I was psyched for her.
There you go. Keep it going.
Michaela, awesome.
Man, it really brought us all back to life, and it was a great moment,
because she saved us today, and it was really kind of emotional for her.
I'm normally not a person to cry, but sometimes you just need something so bad.
Sometimes when you have no other choice but to get something done, it happens.
It's just letting me know the life I'm trying to get by winning this thing is worth it.
I do want it badly for my family.
There's nobody in my family that's been able to have success and keep it.
It's like everybody has some type of problem,
and I just want to prove that you can have success, and you can have your family together.
Michaela, you're a hero.
You are the best. Look at that.
Is that awesome or what?
Are you crying?
Yeah, you should be crying, because you just saved us.
You're not a girl.
You should be proud. None of us could do that, and you got it done.
Michaela, my god, save the day.
All right, you guys ready to get to your first immunity challenge as new tribes?
Yeah.
First things first, Zeke, need it back.
Yep.
Wow, nice toss.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs, and today, two tribes will win immunity.
Here's how it works for today's challenge.
You're going to dive down, retrieve a buoy, and swim it to the platform.
Then the next person goes.
Once you've collected all five buoys, you have a choice.
You can immediately start throwing your buoys, attempting to land them in the basket,
or you can take the time to try to hook your basket, pulling it much closer, making it easier to score.
First two tribes to five win immunity, safe from the vote, losers, tribal council,
or somebody will be the fifth person voted out of this game.
If you're a bully, you have one extra member.
We're going to sit somebody out.
Who's it going to be?
Will is going to sit this one out.
Everybody else, get them in and strategize.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go for immunity.
First two tribes to finish, safe from tribal, losers, somebody will be voted out.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Looking for that first buoy.
Adam has it for Takali.
Cece has hers for Vanua.
Come on, Sunday.
Sunday's still working on that buoy for Ikeboola.
Cece is going to give up, and swimming in is going to cost her tribe a lot of time,
because somebody else will have to swim twice.
It is Adam and Cece in the lead.
Adam is back with the first buoy.
All right, wait till it's in there.
Go, Takali!
Sunday is back.
Go, Ikeboola!
Jay in the water for Ikeboola.
Jay making quick time of it.
Cece still working for Vanua.
Keep kicking.
Jay is back.
Go, Ikeboola!
Jessica back with the second buoy.
Go, Takali!
Kayla quickly with the buoy.
Come on, Cece, you got it.
Cece is taking forever to get out of the water.
Put it up there, Cece.
Just put it up there and get up.
Go!
David now in the water for Vanua.
Viggy making good time.
Good job, Viggy.
Makayla now coming back.
Go, Ikeboola!
Go, Takali!
David has a buoy for Vanua.
Now David's got to get out of the water.
Ken with a buoy.
Good job.
Hannah has hers for Ikeboola.
Ken is back.
In the back, you're nice and easy.
Go, Takali!
There we go.
David's struggling.
Come on, David, put it on the deck.
David cannot get out of the water with the buoy.
My God.
A huge setback for Vanua.
Get it, David!
Oh.
And now David loses the buoy.
Come on, David.
Oh my God.
He's got to get back in the water.
Disaster.
David, get it!
Hannah back now.
Go, Ikeboola!
Is he throwing this?
Takali has all five.
You can start shooting.
Ken now going to try to retrieve his basket and pull it closer.
David absolutely out of gas.
And he's lost the buoy again.
Go!
Fred is back.
Ikeboola still has another buoy in the water.
Jay is going to have to swim all the way back, get up on the platform and go again.
Ken going for it, but he's all knotted up.
We got it.
We got to leave.
Come on, Jay.
Come on, Jay, you got it.
That lead is evaporating.
Jay, a monster in the water.
Come on, Jay.
Michelle trying to get a buoy.
Go, go.
And she can't get a buoy.
Jay is now back with the fifth buoy.
Yes!
Ken with a great lasso.
He's got it, pulling it closer.
Mikaela now going to try to lasso that basket and pull it closer.
There you go.
No.
Ken is now shooting.
Right there.
Right there, Ken.
Chris is back with that third buoy.
Go, Z!
Zeke now in the water, slips off the platform.
Takali has had to leave the entire challenge, but Ken has not yet scored.
Woohoo!
Ken in and out.
Zeke is now back, but there's still one buoy short.
Got to go all the way back, then come back and get the buoy.
Can they make up the time they need to get in this?
Come on, Mikaela.
Ken misses again.
There you go.
Mikaela hooks it for Ikebula.
She's pulling it closer.
We've got a challenge.
Brett is in the water, Hannah in the water.
And Ken scores on her first shot.
It is now Ikebula in the lead.
Two for two.
Incredible.
In and out.
Got to get it back.
It is now Ikebula in the lead.
Ken now scores for Takali.
Way to go.
Chris is back.
Let's go.
What's the decision?
Manua going to just start shooting.
There goes Chris from a long ways away.
Can Chris find the distance?
Yeah, Mikaela, take your time.
Mikaela with the third for Ikebula.
There we go.
She has been on fire.
Mikaela with four for Ikebula.
You got it.
No, Chris short again.
Don't get nervous.
Just do it.
Mikaela for the win.
Yes.
Ikebula wins immunity.
We are looking for a second place.
Watch out pulling in, Zeke.
Michelle coming out of the water.
Zeke coming out of the water.
They're going to go back to trying to lasso their target
and bring it closer after being dead last the entire challenge.
Manua is still in it.
It is anybody's game right now for second.
Ken with the second point for Takali.
Okay.
Come on, keep swimming.
Just don't stop.
Ken with the third for Takali.
He's got a hot streak now.
Ken for four.
No.
It is a battle for the second immunity.
Chris lassoes in for Manua.
Their target is much closer.
Will it make a difference?
Frustration setting in for Manua.
Takali has had a gigantic lead.
Ken with the fourth.
Ken needs one more to secure immunity for the win.
Oh, yes.
There it is.
Takali wins immunity.
Manua sending Manua to tribal council.
Ikebula, congratulations.
Somebody swim over and get it.
Nice job.
Thank you, sir.
Takali sends somebody over to get it.
Nice entry.
Thanks, sir.
Nobody going home from Ikebula, nobody going home from Takali.
You will live to see another day in this game.
Grab your stuff, swim on out, enjoy it.
Get him, boy.
All right, guys, date with me tonight.
Tribal council, somebody from this five will be voted out.
Swim it in, see you tonight at tribal.
I'm frustrated because CC and David are just atrocious in challenges,
and they don't even seem to care because they think they have the numbers.
But thankfully, Chris is trying to make a move with us.
And if he does, a Gen-Xer goes home regardless.
That sucked.
I think that sucked tonight, guys.
He swam twice, so you retired, too.
He swam twice.
I just blew it on the basketball, man.
I mean, I'm sorry about the buoy.
That just wasn't our best day.
We all tried.
We gave it our best shot.
Yeah.
It was like a nightmare, a recurring nightmare.
It's like I go to sleep, I wake up, and I'm in this same nightmare,
back to tribal council.
The one positive is finally I'm not on the bottom.
This time we have the majority, three Gen-X against two Millennium,
so either Michelle or Zeke will be voted off.
Zeke could do puzzles, and he's still strong.
He's still pretty decent in the water.
Yeah.
No, he's pretty good.
I mean, he's strong in the water.
Yeah, he's strong.
Zeke's been pretty open about whatever you all want.
Here's the question.
Do we tell them we're voting for Michelle?
We could.
We could tell Zeke.
I think so.
All right, well, we tell him, then.
So we don't take any chances.
Huge night tonight.
This is a crucial decision, and quite honestly,
I've made a different decision.
Let's just do it.
Yeah.
CC and Dave backstabbed me, and one of them has to go today.
Dave bit me in the butt a couple times,
but he has at least some numbers that will survive this three
tribe situation that we're in.
I have to have a big alliance to protect me in a merge,
so we're going to vote CC off tonight.
Hey.
Me and you just set out in really big boo, isn't it?
Right.
We bumped up.
We can't get rid of Zeke.
Right.
I mean, I hate to say it, but we need to think this thing
through tonight.
This is a pivotal moment, and if we make the wrong move here...
You're thinking CC?
Well, I don't want to.
Right.
But we're kind of decimated here.
It sounds like Chris wants to vote off CC,
and I'm extremely nervous about that.
Chris has on his side Zeke and Michelle,
so I think I should just go along with the plan
and make him believe he can trust me.
So it's CC.
I mean...
I'll do it.
I swear to God, I'll do it.
I just want you to think it through.
I don't even need to.
If we can come together, we can benefit each other.
Now, whether Dave will stay to his word or not, I don't know.
I'm trusting a guy that's barked me twice.
Hey, uh...
Yeah?
Michelle, we just wanted to let you know
why CC's gone with this one.
It's Christmas.
You're safe tonight.
Both of you are safe tonight.
Yeah.
Both of you.
Thank you, guys.
Yeah, no, you guys are awesome.
David and Chris say, it's not you, we're voting CC.
But how do you trust it?
So no matter what is said at Tribal, you vote CC.
Okay.
And if it's not, I'm gonna be the first one
to ever, like, choke David in front of the whole nation.
And it all ain't pro-Chep Rho.
I know, I know, I know.
There's a thousand possibilities
that he's not telling the truth.
I'm not gonna sit back and let other people decide my fate
because that's not how I'm used to doing things.
Don't feel defeated.
You enjoying it?
Yeah, I'm enjoying it.
It's still tough, you know?
Yeah.
This game is just like...
You know that I know that, like,
either me or Zeke, probably me,
there's a lot of trying to do.
I know that.
Yeah.
Like, that just makes me, I see that.
Right.
But I know that I can do better than you.
I weigh more, I'm stronger.
I have great upper body strength.
I'm great with puzzles.
I just don't, I just don't see a benefit in carrying out a plan.
You definitely have a point.
And you know that since I know I'm on the bottom,
like, I'm willing to make a deal.
Oh, yeah.
I tried to talk strategy with her,
and I can't get anywhere.
So all I can do right now is hope that David and Chris
are telling me the truth and hope for the best.
She knows she's going home.
But she wants to vote you out.
Vote me out?
Why does she want to vote me out?
She said you're the weakest and you're clumsy.
That's what every girl says about me.
Chris and I had talked, and we decided that we would work
with the millennials to vote for Cece.
But I really don't trust Michelle.
She wanted to woo Cece over and target me.
Once Cece is gone, I would be the weakest person of our tribe.
And I worry that Chris, Michelle, and Zeke could form a voting
block and vote me out in the next tribal.
And it's got me thinking whether or not I should give my idol
to Cece and then vote off Michelle.
I play a lot of chess.
And the thing about chess, if you're going to play a good game,
is you have to look as many moves ahead as you can.
And if it means betraying an alliance or people that trust you, do it.
All right, so let's talk about the challenge today.
Zeke, this is your first challenge as a new tribe.
What were the stakes?
Well, I think for Michelle and I, we see that we're clearly on the bottom.
We know that the millennials are dominating the other two tribes.
We both felt if we ended up here, one of the two of us is going home.
David, when you have a three and a two, there's always one idea,
which is who's three on the three?
Who's the bottom?
Because we'll make you top over here.
That's always an option.
But I do feel that the Gen X3 sitting up here tonight are very strong.
And I don't think any of us have the insecurity that we're on the bottom,
though, of course, that can't possibly be true.
Zeke, there it is.
You talk about being the bottom.
You could become the top if you can just get one of these three to join you.
Yeah, that's the trick.
And look, I know it's intimidating.
I know you don't want to work with a millennial
because you see a massive millennial advantage.
But you're not going to move further in this game
without connections to millennials, and I provide that.
And I'm ready to make a move with the Gen Xers if that's what I need to do.
Chris, Survivor is a big game with a lot of moving parts
and the thought that all the millennials are going to stick together
while on three separate tribes right now could be foolish.
Well, yeah, I don't think they're going to stick together,
but we can't be unaware of the situation.
Gen X is down numbers, and we do need millennials to help going forward.
So did you feel Michelle or Zeke trying to work David, CeCe, and yourself?
You bet. You bet.
They haven't given up, that's for sure.
And I've talked a lot with Zeke.
We're both Oklahoma boys.
He's a big Sooner fan, and, of course, I've played,
so I have a lot in common with Zeke, and that may surprise people,
the big country boy and the New York kid.
CeCe, what level of concern do you have when you see one of your three Gen Xers,
Chris, talking with Zeke?
It definitely raises concern.
You know, going forward, Chris may be willing to vote out a Gen X to save Zeke.
So, Chris, it sounds like this is a question of when does the game play begin?
The last two Tribals I've been to, I've been blind-fited.
So this vote tonight is really a chance for us to build back a really strong bond
and be really close.
David, has there been talk about previous Tribals and what may or may not have happened?
Yes, there has been, and, you know, I do understand Chris' concerns
about whether or not he can trust me, and we actually talked about that today.
I mean, trust is paramount tonight, and I keep finding myself in the position
of having to prove my loyalty, and I own that, and tonight I'm going to do that.
Chris, the other specific thing David said was he needs to prove his trust.
Do you understand that?
Yeah, David, he got me a couple of times, and I don't like to be reckless or anything,
but sometimes you've got to take a risk, and I'm taking a risk on David and I,
but I specifically told him, if you're doing it again,
I better be sitting right up there tonight.
I think you said you were going to choke me.
I might have said that too, but I was kidding on that.
Michelle, that is the best thing you can hope to hear, is that there were problems in that group.
Yeah, I personally don't see how there could be very much trust there,
especially continuing forward.
I just wonder why would you want to try to work with someone who's blindsided you twice?
So who do you think should be voted out tonight?
I think I would put out David.
This is fun.
David, it can't surprise you, though.
If you're sitting in their seat, you've got to get that vote off your shoulder onto somebody else's.
Understandably, but I think that if the Gen X3 sitting up here tonight are truly united,
we have nothing to worry about.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Cece, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Michelle.
Cece, one vote Michelle, one vote Cece.
Cece, that's two votes Cece, one vote Michelle.
Fifth person voted out.
Cece, that's three, that's enough, you can bring me your torch.
Cece, tribe is spoken.
Good luck, guys.
Well, if there's one thing this group of four can take comfort in, it's knowing you can trust each other.
Unless, of course, you're the one being lied to.
Grab your torches, head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor, Figgy lets her guard down.
Taylor and I kind of have a thing.
You think?
It's obvious.
While a challenge leaves the survivors spinning.
Sunday, dizzy now.
She's spinning.
Hey, medical.
You're not going to let me die.
It's insane.
I was blindsided.
My two fellow Gen Xers voted against me and going forward, they're going to lose.
I think it was the dumbest mistake that they made.
I feel betrayed, you know, but I played as hard as I could.
I strategized, I snuck in, and I absolutely believe that my kids are going to be very proud how far I came in a game.
And that I did my best.