Previously on Survivor.
At the Gen X tribe, Paul was in charge of an alliance of six.
If I 100% want to be in control, that's where I have to be.
But the elements brought him down.
It was Pete exhaustion, which is now settled.
At the Millennial tribe, Zeke, Adam, Hannah, and Mari wanted to dismantle the power couple.
Biggie and Taylor are super close.
That's dangerous.
But Michelle had plans of her own.
I might have to pull strings at tribal council to make sure I have the numbers.
At tribal council, Michelle convinced Hannah and the majority of the tribe to vote out
Mari.
Mari, the tribe has spoken.
Leaving Zeke and Adam on the outside.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Dang, dude.
What a vote.
I've got to say, well played, everybody.
Yeah, that was nice.
Wow.
Taylor, Figgy, hats off to you guys.
No, hats off to Zeke and Adam are like, Taylor, Figgy, well done.
Like I commend you.
And it's like, it's not just us, buddy.
There's seven votes.
I don't see the first day that did not feel good.
No, no.
No, it didn't at all.
Yeah, because it's like random.
Adam and Zeke know they're at the bottom at this rate if we go back to tribal.
People that write down Figgy's name go home.
I know you're mad.
I'm going to try to be an adult about it and not play victim.
Can we just talk tomorrow?
I just want to say a few things.
I had no intention of doing that, but walking into tribal council.
Michelle told me at tribal council that they have the numbers and I didn't see the point
of voting at the bottom of the alliance.
Even walking into tribal, I thought Figgy was going home and then Michelle says, trust
me, we have the numbers.
And suddenly I couldn't think of anything else.
I did what I felt was best for my game and I had to and it sucked.
I'm not looking for you to feel sorry for me, dude.
I'm looking for you to like.
Okay.
I just would like to be alone right now.
So you know how like you're totally in control of the game and you're totally excited to
go to tribal council and then, oh wait, you get totally blindsided?
That's what happened to tribal council tonight.
I don't care if you yell at me or tell me I'm an asshole.
Hannah, I just don't want to talk to you right now.
Okay.
Can you just like give me some space?
I'm gonna be a six to four vote, dude.
Can you just give me some space right now?
That's all he's asking.
But like, think of me as a tribal.
I don't want to talk.
Can you respect that I don't want to talk to you right now?
And just like go up and make rice with everyone else and maybe we'll talk later.
I just want you to.
No, no, look, look, look.
He's not saying he doesn't want to talk to you.
I'm not saying I'm not going to consider your argument.
He's just saying he doesn't want to talk to you right now.
I'm saying I'm upset right now.
I'm particularly upset with you.
And please just like give me a sec to just like breathe.
I know, I know.
I'm just saying before you breathe, just meditate on this, okay?
No, Hannah, please.
He doesn't want to talk to you right now.
Just give me a second.
He's saying he will talk to you later.
He doesn't want to talk to you right now.
Just give me a second.
Just, alright.
It's only during tribal and the votes would have still been...
Oh my God, Hannah, you're...
Whatever.
He's not saying he doesn't want to talk to you.
Okay, fine.
He just doesn't want to talk right now.
Okay, okay guys.
Okay, you can say I'm the worst person ever.
He's not saying that.
He just doesn't want to talk right now.
What are you like?
I know that, Adam.
He needs space, that's it.
I know that.
Don't play the victim right now.
I'm not playing the victim.
Yes, you are.
I'm not the victim.
He just needs some space.
Just talk to him later.
Hopefully something can happen with Zeke and Adam.
Hopefully I can repair enough to the point where we can work together.
Or maybe even Adam and Zeke can make a move using me.
I want them to use me.
Use me.
I don't like everyone in this damn majority alliance.
I think we just got to be chill.
I'm glad we're sitting next to each other though.
Because at least I knew who was the other fool.
That's me, you and me on Dumbass Island.
It's been my dream since I was nine years old to play this game and have this experience.
And I did not expect my first tribal council to be my first hashtag blindside.
Now I'm going to have to play from the bottom and it's going to take a lot of work to get
back into a position of power.
But I wouldn't count me out.
I think I can get back up to the top again.
Nice.
Isn't that how beautiful that sky is right now?
Red sky at night, sailors delight.
Red sky in the morning, sailors take warning.
I have faith that things are going to go in our favor.
I trust God.
I trust God and I pray really hard.
On my tribe right now I have a pretty good handle of what's going on.
And it's definitely me, Ken and Cece on the bottom without question.
If you are next, I'm right after you.
And I know that.
But I found an idol already.
That was on my survivor bucket list.
So there's hope for me.
I am a Gen Xer and I don't think you should ever give up.
Feels good today.
Not too hot.
Nice little breeze.
I feel like I'm back from the dead, man.
I feel awesome today.
We want to talk about a guy who's come back from the dead.
I went from flat on my back to I feel like I just got here.
Like it's day one for me.
I'm going to try to get some fish.
All right.
Don't hurt yourself out there.
No.
Let us know if you catch something.
We'll come help.
We'll take it.
Well, I'm going to bring a stringer.
OK.
And hopefully no sharks or barracudas try to take it away from me.
Yep.
I hear you.
I'm going to let them have it.
And then we're going to do the victory at sea dance.
You know, I live in the Florida Keys.
For me to go shoot a nice, you know, yellowtail or something in the Keys is like I'll be back
in a minute and I go get a couple of fish.
Here it's like we'll have to see if I'm as good as I think I am because I think I'm really
good.
I hope we get something big.
I need to chow on like an octopus or a shark or something.
Shark.
How about a tuna?
The yellowfin tuna.
Why can't we catch that?
Something we could chomp on for like a week.
We'll get it done.
Boy, that current is strong this morning, buddy.
That's murked up really bad.
I saw a couple of nice big fish in there, but man, you can't get close to them.
Yeah.
But those yellowtails, I'd get up right up to them and in the waves, just pull me right
back.
Paul comes back.
There's this school of yellowtail, but you can't get them.
They're just, they're too fast.
And I look at these people and it's like, do you not see that time and time again he
says something and doesn't follow through?
Who do you want leading you into battle?
The current this morning, what my ass?
People talk about, you know, Cece, she's on the outs.
David's terrified of anything physical.
Whoa, he's got corncarnival.
What about Paul?
Like, what is he currently offering the tribe?
He's not providing food.
He's not providing shelter.
And I'm baffled that I'm on the bottom.
Gather round, gather round.
We've got tree mail.
Call it a summit or call it recon, but call on four to go.
You'll have the orange rock in your hand and you'll represent and return with inside info.
Wow.
Grab it.
Don't look at it.
So four.
And then we'll reveal all I want.
Adam comes back to camp with tree mail and he has this bag of rocks.
And whoever gets the orange rock will leave camp and go intermingle with the other tribe.
And I think a lot of people don't want to go, but me being a super fan, I want to be
a part of this twist.
You know, why not work with people from the other side if they're going to help you advance
in this game.
One, two, three.
Oh boy.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
Nice.
Remember your tribe is recon.
Yes.
So we're losing Will, Jay, and Taylor.
And Vicki.
No, I should be like, I'm the biggest boy in camp.
Yeah.
It's like just glorious of who got to go.
It's me.
It's Fig.
It's Will and it's Jay.
I'm just going the top people in my Alliance.
Thank you.
Guys, we got to go.
I'm fully excited, honestly, to go on this journey.
I get to feel out the Gen X generation of, oh, we work hard and we do things the right
way and I want to see, okay, what's the right way.
But I really hope Figgy and Tails don't start making out because then we're going to look
like a bunch of idiots.
And then they're really going to have this idea that millennials don't know what we're
doing because we're letting a power couple stay in the game.
On the boat, the word summit kept popping up in my head.
And for me, that is a meeting of, you know, like when different countries come and they
have a G8 summit from the Gen X tribe, it's CC, Dave, Paul, and myself.
I'm really excited to go do this.
This is the first time that the Gen X and the millennials are going to mix together.
And for my game, making some connections to them is a good thing.
I want a pizza and beer.
An old attorney once said to me, you have to look at the opposition with clear eyes
and a cold heart.
And that's how I'm trying to view this game.
So my strategy is to keep my mouth shut and just get information.
Oh, peanut butter.
Broken.
Oh my gosh.
Break bread with your rivals, a respite and a temporary truth.
Then take time for some one-on-one more friends you sure could use.
I'm a huge survivor super fan and being the one selected to go to a summit like this was
just fantastic.
Cheers, guys.
Cheers.
So far, I'm achieving all of my survivor dreams.
Who's missing from who went home last night?
Maury.
Maury?
Maury, yeah.
Did she know it was coming?
No.
No, she didn't.
That happens, right?
That happens.
So we got any boyfriend, girlfriends on the tribe?
Yeah.
No.
Anybody hooked up?
Yeah.
Anybody headed that way?
Most of us are old and boring.
I'm a lead singer in a rock band.
ZZ Top?
We do some ZZ Top.
We do a lot of songs.
I'm old if you hadn't noticed.
I play a lot of stuff you guys probably never heard of.
I think the millennials think a guy like me because I'm older and they haven't talked
to parents in a while and to have their dad sitting there that they can talk to, they
really do appreciate it.
I honestly can say Dave is one of the most incredible guys I've ever met.
Oh, Paul, back at you.
I mean, you want to talk about a guy that's brutally honest about everything.
Yeah.
I mean, a bug flies on him and he will scream.
I'm surprised you can't hear it and you can't hear it.
Paul wants an audience.
He's in a rock and roll band and he gets on stage and he doesn't ask the audience what
they think.
He tells them what he thinks.
That is not a guy I would ever imagine myself aligning with.
Those are the guys that annoy me.
I'm going right in the agua.
I'm not even slowing down.
Right now, I'm at the bottom with CeCe and Ken.
So I need to find a way to make new friends among the millennial tribe because once there
is a swap or a merge, I'm going to need their help to get rid of Paul.
How's Ken doll?
We call him Ken doll because he's like a Barbie doll.
No, I love Ken.
He's the opposite of what you think.
He's the most humblest.
He's totally not the Ken doll, totally opposite.
The boys went in the water and Taylor and I talked to CeCe and David.
We're trying to learn if they're on the outs, if there's any division in their tribe.
Do you have somebody on the bottom or do you guys feel like you're on the bottom?
We know, we don't think Paul's on the bottom.
Definitely.
Paul's not?
No.
Our tribe, there's like nobody trying to run around for any idols.
Yeah, same here.
Or to be like the boss man.
No, we're not trying to do any of that.
Well, we do got a couple boss men.
You guys do?
One.
Definitely Paul.
Paul definitely.
Yeah, he wears it on his sleeve.
You can tell.
Yeah.
Me and Dave let Taylor and Figgy know that Paul, he's the head person in charge.
He's the alpha male.
He's the one who's running things in camp.
So leaving us alone, it was the stupidest decision they could have did.
It may cost them a million dollars.
Hey, if I end up on a swap with you or a merge, let's work together.
Let's do it, dude.
Let's do it.
I trust you.
Yeah, dude.
Mike, we're so solid with our group.
Mike, there's Noah.
I will kick off my tribe if you want me to, okay?
I swear to God.
I got to have a very, very important 30 second conversation with Taylor.
And I mean it.
Come a swap, if it's three millennials and two Gen X, I'm getting rid of that other
Gen X.
Honey, we're home.
Paul, Chris, myself and Cici came back from the summit.
What was the meeting about?
We met at a real, it was like a real summit.
We met at a different beach.
And everybody wanted to know how it was, what happened.
I tried to win.
Jay, Taylor, Figgy and Will.
And the thing about talking to Taylor is that I felt like I had a ray of hope that it's
really been, other than finding the idol, it's really been missing for me this entire
game.
And all the girls want to know about Ken.
Yeah, they did.
They were asking about Ken.
They said they call you Ken Dow.
I said, no, Ken is the most humblest guy you ever want to meet.
But they call you Ken Dow.
That's a not a fun nickname for him.
You were called that before?
Half my childhood.
Oh my God, really?
Ken and Barbie.
Where's Barbie?
Ken Dow.
I never thought about that.
When you're a boy, like the last thing you want to be referred to is a plastic Barbie
with no penis.
So the millennials know me as Ken Dow.
They think of me as the pretty boy and all the things that come along with that.
But I have the strength and body and the strength in mind to make it far in this game.
I'm hungry and I want fish really badly.
I'm going to go fish a little bit.
The Gen X tribe, I think, would be hurting if they got rid of me as far as the challenges
goes and my work ethic.
We need food.
We need fish.
And what I say I do, I wind up doing.
90, 90% of the time.
When I say I'm going to do something, I know how to do something.
I do it and it works.
Paul, he's the greatest fisherman, but yet he comes back empty handed.
Put that guy across.
I would never go into a battle with a leader who is incompetent or incapable.
You pick the person who follows through.
You pick the person who does what they say they're going to do.
Coast Guard mister 40 years in the Keys, owning his own boat, fishing charters, all that.
Hasn't brought back anything to us.
Lots of talk.
Right.
He hasn't brought back one fish, has he?
Not a single one.
I would say you and Sunday probably threw the most humble people here.
And then we have our rock star lead singer.
We have the guy who not only thinks but acts like he's in charge.
Is he out for the tribe or is he out for him?
Yeah, no, I know.
Obviously you feel like you're on the outs and I don't want you to feel that way.
It's just when there's conversations going on, I'm not getting the nod to come.
And that sucks.
Ken feels like he's on the outs and I totally understand why he feels that way because he's
not part of the six.
It seems the only person in this camp that's rubbing people the wrong way, it's Paul.
Right.
Ken wants to vote at Paul, but I've committed myself to Chris and Paul and Brett and Sunday
and Lucy, who are my best bet moving forward to day 36.
And day 36, I will then get to read the legacy advantage that I found and then utilize that
to my advantage.
I can't wait until you guys, y'all will come and visit me in Nashville and we're going
to have the time of our lives.
That's the truth though.
Strategically, the millennial tribe is moving forward and it's really great for me.
Me and Figs are pretty good at the moment.
My girl's here.
She's happy and this could be a better position to be in really.
It's just nice to sit out here.
Not even have to worry about what's going on back there.
We already got rid of one.
We got rid of it.
Got to get rid of the other two.
Yeah.
I think Zeke should be the next to go.
Zeke is going to be next to go.
He's going to kick our ass up here if we take him.
It's got to be Zeke.
Yeah.
Ain't nothing to it.
The status quo of the tribe is not a good position for me.
I'm still flabbergasted by that vote because Figgy sucks at survival.
You can't make an obvious pair that is strong, good looking, talented in the challenges and
not be a threat in this game.
And so if Figgy goes home, there would be a shift and that's what I need to happen in
order to have some semblance of power here.
If you're Taylor and Figgy, who do you credit for saving Figgy's life in that vote?
Michelle, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
If you're Michelle and Jay and you know that Figgy and Taylor credit you for their lives,
you know those two are never going to vote you out.
So to me, that tells me those four are as tight as can be.
If they stick together, they can pick out any of us that they want.
And so all we need to do is vote out Figgy or Taylor and then this crew is back in the
middle in the power position of this tribe.
I see your point.
Adam gives me different things to think about even though I'm in the majority.
I still don't like Figgy.
She's sneaky.
I do not trust her.
But I'm not making any decisions right now.
I'm just watching and thinking and my gut will tell me something when the time comes.
Come on in, guys.
Gen X, getting your first look at the new Millennium.
Gen X, getting your first look at the new Millennial tribe.
Mari, vote it out at the last tribal council.
All right.
Shall we get to today's immunity challenge?
Yes.
First things first.
Thank you, Brett.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're going to carry heavy bags over and under an obstacle and
then across a balance beam.
You'll then separate the sandbags from the coconuts and use the sandbags to knock down
large puzzle pieces.
Once all the pieces are on the ground, you'll then race to reassemble the puzzle.
First to get it right wins immunity, safe from the vote.
In addition, you're playing for a reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Yes.
Be nice to have a little comfort.
Hammock, blankets, pillows, candles, and two custom survivor lounge chairs.
Losers go to tribal council where somebody will be the third person voted out of this
game.
Give me a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
All right.
Here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Bars ready.
Go.
First you got to get five people under and over all these obstacles with that bag with
you.
That is a heavy bag.
That's 40 plus pounds.
Up and over.
Go.
Come on.
You got it, kid.
Go, go, go.
Great.
Gen X is falling behind.
Come on, Paul.
Come on, Big.
Adam, let's go.
Millennials are there first.
Start up on the balance beam.
Go, Kail.
Yeah, Taylor.
Gen X is there.
Chris is going to take the balance beam first.
Good man, Chris.
Now you've got to get across the beam with the bag.
The beam is tough enough without 40 pounds.
Good job.
Good.
Take your time, Baba.
Now we are tied.
Go, Zach, go.
It is now Will and Brett.
Ninja focus.
Take it easy.
Will drops.
Got to go back.
All right, all right.
Brett's across.
Go.
It's Cece now up for Gen X.
Go, guys.
Go.
If you can, you can do it.
Go, Chris.
If you can't do it, somebody else from your tribe can.
Taylor, run back.
It just means they've got to go twice, and you've still got to get across.
Stay calm, Fig.
Stay calm.
You got it.
Good girl.
Figgy is across.
You're good.
Here comes Taylor.
He's now going to take Will's bag.
Will still has to get across, himself.
Cece taking a long time on that beam, which she could just let another tribe member take
which is what the Millennials are doing.
Come on, Cece.
Taylor across again.
Taylor's coming back.
Cece is taking forever.
It's gonna cost her tribe a lot of time.
Michaela now out on the beam.
You got it, Michaela. Take your time.
Millennials with a big lead right now
thanks to a great strategy.
You got this, Michaela.
Jump to it. Jump to it.
Michaela's across.
You got it, go, Lucy.
Cece finally gets it.
Lucy now on the course.
You got this, Luz.
Taylor has become a workhorse
with the fifth and final bag for the Millennials.
Millennials have all their bags.
Now they've just got to get their other two players across.
Yeah, Will, stay calm.
Will struggling to stay on it.
Keep going. You're doing great. Go.
Lucy falls. She's got to come back.
Lucy, you still got to get across the beam.
Go, Paul, go, go.
She has to get across the beam.
Calm down.
Jump, jump.
Yeah.
Will's across.
Adam, the last Millennial to get across.
Let's get Adam.
There you go, baby.
That's it, Luz. Take your time.
Yeah, buddy.
Adam.
Let's go.
Adam's across.
Good separating.
Sandbags from coconuts.
Lucy's across.
Here comes Paul with his bag.
Big lead for the Millennials.
You've got to get your sandbag.
You've got the corral.
I'll take your time.
Paul falls.
Yeah.
Go, go, go.
She's spent a lot of time on that beam and lost a lot of time.
Good job.
Chris, he's across.
You're good.
Keep going.
Paul now going across without a bag.
Let's go, guys.
Let's go.
Going across.
Go, Chris.
Chris with his third bag.
You got it.
Chris is across.
Start separating Gen X.
Throw it in.
It's a pop.
Jay's starting to throw now.
There you go.
Jay is winging it and not getting any love yet.
Yeah, yeah.
Jessica, Ken, trying to catch up.
They lost a lot of time getting across the beam.
You've got a rock and fire, dawg.
Big hit by Jay.
Now the puzzle's starting to come apart.
Another piece by Jay.
We're not out of it at all.
Go.
Gen X has all their bags.
Ken's going to start throwing.
Rock and fire, baby.
There you go.
Ken knocks out a piece.
Rock and fire, baby.
Go.
There you go.
Good boy.
I got it.
Ken knocks a few more pieces off.
Gen X starting to catch up now.
Come on, baby.
Come on, boy.
There you go, Jay.
Another nice hit by Jay.
And another.
Millennials down to two pieces left.
Dindit and Michelle will take over.
Jay knocks off the last piece for the Millennials.
Get all of them here on the mat.
Ken with another big hit for Gen X.
There it is, buddy.
Right there.
Another sweet one.
Zeke and Michelle now going to start solving the puzzle.
Good job.
Gen X is catching up there, closing that gap.
Ken knocks off two more.
Remember the middle.
E-N-B-S.
It is Michelle and Zeke trying to make sense of all these pieces.
You got middle one, Jay.
This goes underneath that one, though.
Okay.
We're still going to need one more though in the middle.
Oh, almost.
Ken's got one left.
David and Sunday head in.
Ken knocks off the last piece.
We got this.
We might have a challenge after all.
Come on, you guys got this.
It is Michelle and Zeke, Sunday and David, starting the bottom pieces.
They got it.
Look for the feet, Dave.
Look for the feet.
You've been staring at this puzzle during the entire challenge.
Now you have to reassemble it.
On the side.
Millennials still with a lead.
They've had the lead from the beginning.
There you go.
Iguana on the left.
First to solve it wins immunity and reward.
Losers back to tribal council.
No one's going home tonight.
Zeke, back corner.
Back corner.
Millennials getting a lot of help from the bench.
That goes on top.
Oh, that's it.
You're right.
Listen.
Yeah, don't even listen.
I'm not going to shut up.
I'm going to mess him up.
Just shut up.
There you go.
That's it.
Another piece by Millennials.
Iguana.
Another piece by Gen X.
Yes.
Millennials with another piece.
Come on, Dave.
Come on, Sunday.
Yes.
Do they have it?
Come on, Jeff.
Four!
Yeah!
Woo!
Ah!
Good job, guys.
Just couldn't catch him.
Oh my God, good job.
Woo!
Millennials, congratulations.
Yes!
Woo!
Yeah!
Oh my God.
Nobody going home from the Millennial Tribe.
In addition, nice reward.
Question, Jeff.
Yes.
Can I switch comfort for fishing gear, please?
Let me go fishing in Fiji.
Please.
Here's the only way this could work.
A, if GenX agreed to it,
and B, if the terms of what the trade were,
because I'm not sure this is enough for fishing gear,
we're all agreed to,
but I'm totally open to having this discussion.
We have sand to sit on, let them be hungry.
What do you think?
Let them be hungry.
It's pretty simple, you can just say no, too.
What about our beans?
They're gonna try to get out.
Sand?
As much as I enjoyed catching octopus and yellowtail
and grouper and everything else,
we as a group decided that they can keep the chairs
in the comfort.
All right, Millennials, grab your reward,
head back to camp.
Thank you.
Enjoy the night off.
All right, let's go.
GenX, they said no.
If they were our parents, they would have said yes,
but we're already beating them,
so they don't wanna make us stronger.
That makes sense.
All right, GenX, somebody from your tribe
will be the third person voted out of this game.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal.
CC, she wanted that personal victory
of inching across the balance beam.
Three and a half Millennials got across
in that amount of time, and it was the difference maker.
Yeah, tribal council, it's on tonight,
but I'm not sure how CC doesn't go home tonight.
I'm gonna do my...
Oh, that sucks.
It did suck.
It sucked.
Good try.
Big time.
Everybody's bopped.
So we move forward, right?
Let's go.
In my opinion, CC cost us the challenge.
There was no question who was going home after that.
All right, let's figure out what we're doing
the rest of our day.
But it's Survivor, and I've seen it happen before.
When you get too complacent, things happen.
But I think everybody's on board with voting out CC unanimously.
She can't do the swim challenge.
She can't do these challenges.
I mean, enough's enough.
Three and a half out of five people crossed on her.
I know.
That's huge.
Watching it was just like...
It was painful.
I mean, let's...
All right, so we're all agreeants, right?
Who's going home?
Yeah.
I know.
When I went to the well with Chris and Brett,
we basically talked about sticking to our alliance of six.
So what we have on the docket for tonight is to vote out CC.
We gotta keep the team strong.
Absolutely.
And it sucks.
It's gotta be hard, but it's gotta be hard.
It doesn't suck, then.
Well, I know.
I'm sorry.
Voting CC out to keep the tribe strong is a good thing to do.
She has not done well in challenges.
I can't argue it at all.
So it's time.
Yeah.
Do you girls have an idea of what the plan is?
I have no idea.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm clueless.
I think the boys are working out the details.
So...
Ugh.
I'm worried about tonight because I had three votes last time.
And, of course, no one ever comes up to me and says,
hey, let's do this.
You know, Paul never comes up to me.
Brett, Chris, Sunday, Jessica, and Lucy,
they never come up to me.
I'm 100% worried about that.
I just feel unsafe.
Ken, what do you think about us trying to put a target on Paul?
This has to happen.
CC, we're already on the bottom.
I don't think we...
Have anything on Lucy?
Yeah.
We have to get rid of Paul.
As soon as Paul goes away,
then some other connections and bonds can start forming.
I feel optimistic, but...
There's CC, myself, and Ken on the bottom.
I already retrieved my idol from its hiding spot,
but other people could absolutely take control of the game right now
if they wanted to and vote off Paul.
That's all we need.
I wish they could see that there's just no point
in keeping Paul on their side.
It seems too easy not to just hold and stay the course, right?
So we got the same people in mind, right?
We go CC, and we go right down the line.
Mm-hmm. Yep.
Okay. Yep. Perfect. Yep.
And we just placate everybody in the meantime.
Of course. Yeah.
And as long as you guys aren't doing a boy's thing...
Oh, no.
Well, this is a solid six point.
And you have my word, if that came up, I would tell you.
If they decided to do that, I would say,
ladies, you're on your own.
Paul said to me that if the boys came to me
and said they wanted to do an all-boys thing,
I'd say, good luck, girl.
And I went, what?
So at that moment, I knew that he was not...
He's not with me. He's with boys.
You're right.
We're on the bottom as far as a six-year-old.
Yeah.
It's the boys and then it's the girls.
Well, if we feel like he's the biggest threat right now,
then we need to get rid of Paul first.
Right.
I'm comfortable with it.
If you guys are.
Yeah, I don't know.
You think Dave would be on board with that?
We need Ken, Cece and Dave.
Yeah.
I'm sure Cece, Ken and Dave would vote off Paul.
So tonight we have a very big decision to make.
If we determine that voting off Paul
will be the best thing for our tribe,
I am going to be courting two individuals
that I've worked with, Brett and Chris.
You think we're good, right?
Yeah.
Oh, we're good.
We're on it.
She's over there too.
Who?
All the women are on this.
They're fine.
Oh, God, this is so horrible.
I'm fearful of what will happen if we don't vote off Paul,
but I'm fearful of what will happen if we do vote off Paul.
You don't know me.
David, let's talk about the summit.
Who went from your group?
It was myself, Chris, Paul and Cece.
So you mixed tribes, you meet each other.
What was your takeaway?
The thing that did strike me as odd
is that I actually saw the millennials as people and peers.
There was a mutual respect between all of us,
and I'm feeling like transformed in some way.
Well, what is it that's changed, David,
because you were very nervous at the first tribal,
and you do seem much more calm.
What's happened?
This experience actually is helping me cope with my anxiety.
So it's not that I feel like I'm any safer in the game right now.
It's actually like tearing down the walls
and the energy I have for the anxiety.
So it makes me more calm.
Cece, you were also very nervous.
Turned out, rightly so, you got votes.
Yeah, I got three votes.
You know, I didn't feel safe in the beginning anyways,
because it was like no one was talking to me,
no one was giving me a straight answer,
and I still feel the same way today.
I just feel like three people that's at the bottom
and everyone else is at the top.
Who's at the bottom?
I feel myself.
I think Dave and possibly Ken.
So, Chris, if there's an alliance of six,
how do you navigate keeping everybody together
when there's an opportunity to go with Cece and David and Ken
and say, let's make something else happen,
because I think I might be number five?
Way too early to be making those assumptions.
If you're going to try to stick to an alliance,
it's very dangerous to start making those assumptions
who's five and six right now.
Way too early.
Let's talk about the challenge today.
Just generally speaking, Cece,
did you feel good about getting over the balance beam?
Yeah, absolutely.
And it was very impressive that you finished.
It took a long time.
What you guys didn't see were the Millennials
who moved across that balance beam quickly
because they cooperated.
Brett, watching you guys, it looked like a lot of individuals.
Yeah, I think there might be some truth to that.
I mean, is it because of pride that we had to...
could be? I don't know.
Sundae, do you think there's something to that?
Because I was blown away by how efficiently
the Millennials worked together to figure it out.
Right, for Gen Xers, we think of everything
in terms of it's the right way or the wrong way.
Where it's not necessarily right or wrong,
it's just you may get there a different path.
And I feel like my kids that are Millennials,
they'll give anything a try, they'll try it with anybody,
and they'll try it 80 different ways.
I have a question, just curiosity.
Paul, do you text?
No, a little bit.
Sundae, do you text? Oh, yeah.
When you write the word you, as in see you later,
do you spell Y-O-U or do you use the letter U?
I spell Y-O-U.
I spell Y-O-U. Yeah.
Pretty interesting because the Millennials will tell you
the language is changing, and you can change with us
or you can just be an old fogie.
But it's more efficient.
There's something about efficiency,
but there's also something poetic about language,
and language is beautiful.
We lose that foundation of language that we have,
we lose something really beautiful.
Okay, let's be efficient, but don't lose sight of the past.
But Ken, how far away is that comment from being the guy
that says, vinyl's the only way to listen to music?
Gotta tell you.
There's something about vinyl over digital that I just, I dig.
You're asking the wrong guy. I like the texture.
So, before we go to the vote,
what's the level of paranoia right now, Paul?
I think the level of paranoia within the six is low,
and I think the level of paranoia for the three is high.
But people that are sitting in the six
made those other moves to get them in that six.
And I have just as much of a chance
to be sitting there as they do.
I'm sure I'll be sitting there one day,
and I won't feel good about it either.
But that's why we're here. We're not here to go camping.
We're here to play the game.
Ken, could you feel that level of paranoia as one of the three?
I think some people definitely feel more comfortable than others,
and there's been chatter,
but for me it comes down to my work ethic.
I want to be an asset, and I feel like it's helping,
but I could be an idiot.
Cece, what odds do you give yourself right now?
10%.
Really?
Jessica, what do you think's gonna be the result of tonight's vote?
I'm hoping that the result helps this tribe move forward as a tribe.
I understand that there's divisions,
but we also need to focus on winning the next challenge,
and that's not gonna take just six of us.
It's gonna take everyone who's left.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Brett, you're up.
Oh!
igent
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Okay once the votes are read the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Paul.
Cece.
Two votes Paul, two votes Cece.
Paul.
That's three votes Paul.
Cece.
We're tied again.
Three votes Paul, three votes Cece.
Paul.
That's four votes Paul, three votes Cece.
Third person voted out.
Paul.
That's five, that's enough.
You can bring me your torch.
Paul, the tribe is spoken.
Time for you to go.
Good luck guys.
Well whether you're a millennial or a Gen Xer, the blind side is the blind side.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
Tensions are high at the Gen X tribe.
Don't talk to anybody else.
We went from one dictator to another.
But the real battle is against the millennials.
Their guys are you.
Kayla now takes her top rock.
They're about to do some ta-tas today.
Blindsided 150 percent.
Apparently somebody played better than I did and I'm still kind of in shock on trying to
figure out who voted for me and what happened.
When I got sick it was pretty scary.
But Survivor has been a great experience for me.
At 52 years of age I've been through a lot in my life and I would say this rate's up
there with number one.