Previously on Survivor.
Zeke's Alliance had a numbers advantage.
This is my five.
Over David's coalition.
The five is just going to pick us off one by one.
But Will was ready to graduate from high school student to power player.
Zeke needs to go. Tonight's the night.
I came here to play.
At Tribal Council, Adam played his idol.
I'm playing this for Hannah.
What?
But his move proved unnecessary when Will flipped to David's side.
Zeke, the tribe has spoken.
Leaving Jay with the only idol left in the game.
Eight are left. Who will be voted out tonight?
You're playing great moves, Will.
I came into this game a kid, and I feel like I'm leaving this tribal the man.
Filled up your resume, young man.
I opened up every door possible for me.
Everybody needs me in this game.
And I believe I can start flip-flopping back and forth enough times to win this game.
Making big moves, huh?
That's what it is. Everyone's going to attack at big moves.
How about get to the three? It's a million dollar prize.
Get to the last three. Why would you vote Zeke before David?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm used to tribal council not going my way, and again it didn't go my way.
Will flipped and voted out Zeke.
He said, you know, I want to make some big moves in this game.
I want to check it off in my checklist.
I'm like, this kid wants everyone to think he's not just a high school kid,
but he's thinking like a high school kid.
Oh, I got to do all my homework. I got to check off all these boxes.
Give me a break.
They're all insane.
This is getting to be a crazy game, and there's a lot of people really playing it.
So there's got to be a way for me to stay alive in this game.
Listen, Zeke was a huge threat. You don't think we knew that?
Yeah.
We just knew it was a threat that was on our side.
Right.
Now there's a couple more threats left in this game.
Jay, I'm talking about Will, I'm talking about Dave.
Dave. Dave's a huge threat.
If those three people make it to the final three and not win it,
I might as well go back and eat cake right now.
That's right.
Brett and Sunday come up to me this morning,
and they say Dave, Jay, and Will are the three biggest threats in the game.
Those three need to be the next to go, and it's music to my ears.
The question is, who do you take out first?
I don't know. Who's more important to take out?
I don't know.
Us three are very equal. We could go five and get to the end.
If they want to put themselves in a position where they're left with myself,
Hannah and Ken, I love that.
You have our vote.
Okay.
Those two got to go.
Are we going over?
Those have to be the next three.
All right. Deal.
Deal.
Let's go.
Come on in, guys.
This looks involved.
All right. Shall we get to today's immunity challenge?
Yeah.
First things first, Adam.
Got to take it back.
Yep. You can grab it. I'm not going to give it up.
Fair enough.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're going to race out to a group of disks.
You'll stack them and then transport them over a balance beam and through a wire maze.
Once you have all 10 disks out to finish, you'll attempt to roll them into a target.
First to finish wins immunity.
Safe from the vote.
Guaranteed a one in seven shot.
You'll be the sixth member of the jury.
You'll be the second person to win this game.
Losers, tribal council, somebody will become the sixth member of our jury.
We're going to draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right. Here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Start that pull.
Start stacking your disks.
You can take one or 10.
The fewer trips, the better.
But if you drop, you got to come back and start again.
Brett quickly out of the gate.
David heading out.
Everybody heading out now.
Sunday immediately drops and got to come back.
Now you've got to get across the balance beam.
Takes a lot of coordination to balance on a beam, carrying that stack.
David quickly over the balance beam.
Brett is over the balance beam.
He's going to drop and head back for more.
Ken is over the balance beam.
Jay is clear.
Will drops. He's got to go back.
Add him back with his first four.
Sunday and Hannah moving slowly.
It's now David, Ken, Brett and Jay all with their remaining disks.
David whipping over that beam quickly.
Brett falls off.
He's got to go all the way back.
David is back.
Ken drops. He's good.
Now you're moving into the second phase where you will use a staff
and have to get through a wire maze.
How many can you put on each side and feel safe?
David heading out through the second phase.
Not only do you have to navigate the wires, you also have to step over the rope.
Very difficult to maintain your balance during this.
Adam is good. He can start on this second phase.
It is now Will, the only person who cannot get through that first phase.
Everybody else working on the second phase.
Nobody took all 10 disks at once, so everybody's going to have to make at least two runs.
Brett is the first one through. He's got four.
You're good. Get him on there and head back.
It is now Brett in the lead.
Here comes Jay with his first six.
David near the end of the wire maze.
Jay's good. He can head back for his last four.
It is now Brett and Jay in the lead.
David is back with his first six disks.
Ken is back.
Adam heading back.
Zunde and Hannah falling out of this quickly.
And Will still back at the beginning of this challenge.
Yeah, thanks, Jeff.
Jay is the first one through.
Here comes David. He's through now.
Jay has all 10 disks.
He's in the final phase, rolling them into a target.
He's got one. He's got to get all 10 in there.
David, he can start rolling.
Brett is finished. He can start rolling.
It is now Jay, Brett, and David.
David has one. David has another.
There's another one for Jay.
Jay getting hot. He's got four.
Brett gets one. Jay with another.
That's five for Jay. Make it six for Jay.
Just misses.
Jay, Brett, Jay, all rolling disks now.
There's another for Brett. It is six for Jay.
Two for Brett. Two for David.
There's a seven, eight, nine.
One left for Jay for the win right here.
And he does it. Jay wins.
Individual immunity. Safe from tribal council.
Huge effort.
Jay, come on over.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Jay, safe from the vote tonight, cannot be voted out of this game.
Will live to see day 35.
As for the rest of you, somebody going home tonight will become the sixth member of our jury.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp. See you tonight at tribal. Congrats.
Thank you, sir.
It felt phenomenal to win, you know?
I've already won two individual challenges, but anytime Jeff says, Jay wins immunity, I'm like, damn right I want immunity.
Put that thing around my neck. Let me go back to camp and I'll go spearfishing if I want to.
I don't even need to talk to any of these fools.
And plus, I still have my idol and I'm going to hold on to this baby until I really have to use it.
Good job, Jay.
Thank you.
That was fun. Nice job, Jay.
Thank you, thank you.
Good job.
Yeah.
Good fight.
Jay, again, you know, three of the last four challenges, he's won.
He got the immunity challenge today.
And we would have probably targeted Jay tonight had he not won.
But now we don't know what's going on.
That's how the game goes.
We're going to have to go through the whole process.
The whole process.
What's going on.
That's how this game is being played right now.
You never know from one day to the next.
So tonight's completely up in the air.
You see how, um, David's kind of like dying.
Basically, yep, he can't win a challenge.
Can, can.
But David is a weasel.
That'll be the salt at the end of Ken somehow gets to the end.
Not even a contest.
Okay.
I'm down.
So you want to take David out for Ken.
Yeah.
I have a working relationship with every single person left in the game.
People want my vote, people want my input.
It's David.
Yeah, that's what you told me.
I'm done being afraid, you know, let's just get the hell off the safe.
Oh, but you good?
Okay, I'm good with that.
So I have to talk to people and get people to realize that David's the kind of guy where
if he gets to the end, he will beat anybody, and that includes me.
Which means to me, I need him out of this game.
I think we just go for David.
I agree. Let's just cut the head off this thing, I'm on you.
Yeah.
I need them to feel like, hey, I'm an equal contributor here.
At the end of the day, they're not.
I'm the one calling the shots.
So many conversations are happening.
Unfortunately, because Jay is now safe tonight at Tribal,
there is so much scrambling going around, and the most insecurity I've ever felt is right now.
You know, dude, I just hope I survive tonight.
That's my goal too.
At the last Tribal, Will voted with us.
It was great.
But the thing is, Will is looking to pad his resume a little bit more.
So if Will is smart, the thing to do is to follow up a big move with yet another big move.
And there's this perception in the Tribe that I'm the biggest threat in the game.
And so, yeah, why wouldn't you want to get rid of me tonight?
Hannah just filled me in.
Yeah.
Oh, David.
Are you threatening somebody?
Yeah, we're threatening somebody.
Oh, David.
I'm with you guys.
I told you, last vote, I'm not voting your name.
This vote, I'm working with you.
Will's preference right off the bat is obviously to vote out Dave next.
Will thinks now he has a degree of power and he is in control.
And that makes him more dangerous.
So to me, Will is a bigger threat.
And I do not want to put myself in a position where Will is, you know, controlling my fate in this game.
Will, I think, genuinely wants to go far with me.
But I'm not interested in that.
And I don't want to work with someone who's going to flip back and forth.
So the plan is I'm voting Will tonight.
Okay.
I think Adam's been smart about how he's been playing this.
And we have some common goals that we're looking to make.
So me and Sunday agree.
We'll go with Adam and vote together.
Tommy, what's your name?
I'm voting off me.
Brett and Sunday, I think, are actually willing to vote out Will.
Do you feel like this is the right move against someone who just rescued us from a really bad situation?
Because we were screwed.
Like in his mob alliance, we're going to take us all out.
Yes.
And I was going home.
I get that Will did it for his own game.
But, you know.
I'm torn up as I always am emotionally because Will saved my butt in the game.
So it's like I do owe Will in a sense, but I also feel like I owe David in a sense.
I mean, David pulled a rock for me and we have always been allies.
So, you know, you end up owing more than one person.
Dave could flip because he knows that we're not going to want to sit next to him in the end.
Right.
Because he knows we're not.
He's going to have to keep moving in order to stay in this game.
Right.
You know what I mean?
So we may have to actually do David next.
So what do you want to do?
Right now, Hannah and I are in power positions.
We can decide who goes home next.
It's a really tough choice.
Brett and Sunday are in a weak position.
They're going to vote the way that I want them to vote.
So the question is, blindside Will and take out someone who I do believe is loyal to me at this point.
Or try to blindside Dave and take out potentially the biggest threat in this game.
So we have a huge decision to make tonight.
This is the moment where I start making the moves that I need to make to win this game.
Now bring in the members of our jury.
Michelle, Taylor, Chris, Jessica, and Zeke voted out at the Last Tribal Council.
So Will, Last Tribal Council, everything centered around you.
You were the swing vote.
You wanted to show your playing.
You made a big move, took out Zeke.
What was the reaction when you got back to camp?
Yeah, I wrote Zeke's name down.
And then Adam also played an idol when he didn't have to.
And that caused a lot of stir around camp, for sure.
Jay, how did Will's move shake out when you guys got back to camp?
I mean, I was proud of him as a fan, but as a player, it sucked.
So David, Will makes a big move.
It was 4-4.
What does it do to the game?
Well, I have deep concerns that it might be me.
Jay, should David be worried?
I mean, considering the last vote, Will went with that side of the two alliances.
So if they trust in Will, then Will should be sticking with them, shouldn't he?
Hannah, what was your takeaway from Will's move in terms of what it does to the game and the numbers and the alliances?
The fascinating thing to me is almost everyone up here has both worked with people up here and also worked against people up here.
And I think you want to play with people who want to play with you and take out those threats left in the game.
Adam, it's really tricky.
It all comes down to how do I get to the end and who do I take with me?
I mean, you think about who you want to sit next to at the end, but you also think about what's my best way to get there.
And a lot of the jury members made some really good moves in this game, and it probably contributed to them getting voted out.
So you have to weigh both options.
So the double-edged sword is you make a big move, great. Now you're a bigger threat. Watch out.
Yeah.
David, that does really sum up where this season is.
It's going to be very hard to win this game if you don't have a resume.
Just being a nice person will not get it done.
And yet every time you make a move, you also have everybody else going, yeah, that might be one too many.
It's a complicated game, and the thing is if you don't make big moves, then you're just a goat.
And then maybe you make it to final tribal, but you're not going to get the million dollars.
So it's really essential to make big moves as much as it does put a gigantic target on your back.
Jay, what do you think is going to happen tonight?
Because if I'm watching at home, I have no idea with this group who is going home tonight.
You know, considering, Jeff, everyone here is a player, I honestly am wondering who could it be?
They could go with an easy vote or someone could be trying to make a big move again.
All right, it is time to vote. Will, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
OK, once the votes are read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
David.
David. Two votes, David.
Will.
Will. We're tied. Two votes, David. Two votes, Will.
Will. That's three votes, Will. Two votes, David.
Will. That's four votes, Will. Two votes, David.
Thirteenth person voted out and the sixth member of our jury.
Will, that's five. That's enough. You need to bring me your torch.
Will, the tribe has spoken.
How to bless, guys. Good luck to all of you.
Well, with the game being played at this level, the natural instinct is to want to hide.
But in order to win this season, you must be seen.
Grab your torch, let's head back to camp. Good night.
Getting voted off as survivor is not something I wanted on my survivor resume,
but I am the youngest person to ever play survivor.
And to be able to experience this is the most amazing thing that has ever happened to me so far in my life.
Thanks a lot, guys. That worked.
Dude, anytime that someone tries to make a plan with me, they end up going home.
I'm like the black plague right now. You know what I'm saying?
I am all alone. I have no alliance.
But tribal council has been a complete chaotic mess every single time.
You never know what's going to happen. So it's time for the underdog to keep fighting because I'm not going down without a fight.
I still have an idol and there's still more immunities on the way and I'm not going down.
I'm sorry that I lied to you again. I respect you fully. You and I have been.
Like, it's like it's honestly crazy. It's like a yin-yang. You know what I'm saying? It's sick.
It's a sick relationship. Me and Adam have this. It's kind of like a yin-yang relationship where we love each other, but we hate each other.
And that's how it's been. What is your game, Adam? To take David to the end? Because he's going to take you out, dude.
Well, I hope not. He will. He's not taking you to the end. And you can't beat David.
I'm not planning on taking David to the end. I'm trying to make Jay feel as comfortable as possible with me.
And so I tell Jay that the next move is to get rid of Dave. But to me, Jay has to go home.
You have an idol. Yeah. I'm not going home. I know. I'll take you to the end if I win.
He has a hidden immunity idol and we have to take every opportunity we can to take a stab at the guy.
If he doesn't have immunity, he needs to go home.
Come on in, guys.
I like it. Oh, my goodness.
Guys, ready to get to today's immunity challenge? Yeah. Yeah.
First things first, Jay, it's becoming familiar. Yes, sir.
Take it back.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs for today's challenge. You're going to solve a block puzzle.
There's a twist. You will have a timer in the form of a survivor pinball table.
Here's how it works. You're going to roll your ball.
As long as the ball is making its way down the table, you can work on solving the puzzle.
When the ball reaches the bottom, you catch it, roll it again, go back to your puzzle.
If, however, the ball drops before you catch it, there is a time penalty as the ball slowly makes its way to the bottom, during which you cannot work on your puzzle.
Oh, my God. So it becomes a challenge of split focus.
You have to focus on the puzzle in order to solve it, but you also have to focus on where the ball is on the table.
First to finish their puzzle.
Wins immunity, guaranteed a one in six shot.
Winning this game, losers travel council where somebody will become the seventh member of our jury.
Big stakes, fun challenge. Let's do it. Drop the spots. Get started.
All right, here we go. Four immunity, one in six shot.
Survivors ready. Go.
You got to roll the ball. And while the ball is in play, you can start working on your puzzle.
Brett having trouble just getting the ball up there.
It's going to take a bit of a learning curve. Jay is the first to fill the time penalty.
He now cannot work on his puzzle until that ball stops.
Slowly makes its way to the bottom. And I mean slowly.
Just happened to David. He's got to wait.
A puzzle that would normally take a fair amount of time is going to take a lot of time because your focus is split.
So you can only think about this puzzle a little bit.
While part of your brain is thinking about where that ball is. Oh my God.
Hannah just misses her ball. It drops. She's got to wait.
If your ball drops, you got to make use of the time Adam just misses.
He can't get to his ball. Ken drops. He's got to wait.
Oh, it's so slow. How that ball makes its way down that track.
This is so hard.
All you can do while your ball is out of play is study your puzzle. See if you can figure out your next move.
David's starting to make some progress on his puzzle.
Hannah making some progress. Jay doing a nice job with his puzzle.
Jay drops again. Cannot work. Ken now back at it.
He's got something going. David with some nice work.
Hannah with a nice save. Ken is very close.
David working on his puzzle again. It's now David in the lead.
No, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not.
Ken out of nowhere. Ken thinks he has it.
Ken is wrong. Keep going.
What is wrong? We've been counting on you.
Ken is wrong. Keep going. What is wrong? We've been playing with this logo all season.
Ken now making a change. That opens the door for David and Jay.
Ken, I'm going to tell you when your ball is dropping. You've got to come back.
Everybody trying to catch Ken. David drops.
Keep working. Ken is still wrong. Ken going to try again to change it.
Ken, come back. Ken, come back. Ken, come back.
Whoa, nice save by Ken. Really, Adam?
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Does he have it this time?
Come on. Yes.
Ken wins. Individual immunity. Safe from the vote.
We'll make it to the final six.
That was fun, but that was crazy.
Good job.
Ken, come on over. Good job, Ken.
Apparently when you haven't eaten for 35 days, you can't spill.
You got it right the second time. Ken, safe from the vote.
You will make it to the final six. Live to see day 36. As for the rest of you,
after 35 very tough days in this game, it will come to an end for one of you.
Tribal council tonight, somebody going home. It won't be you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp. See you tonight at tribal. Congrats.
Jay is one of the strongest contenders in this game, and it's definitely a struggle to sit there
and watch someone who's a younger version of myself doing what I would have been doing
10 years ago. So I felt good about wearing the idol around my neck as opposed to Jay.
Great job, Ken. Nice job, Ken. Unbelievable. Good work, buddy.
I thought you weren't a puzzle guy. Simple puzzles like that, yeah.
Slide puzzles and all those, definitely not. My biggest fear going into the challenge
was that Jay or Dave would win immunity. Of course, I would have preferred to win
myself, but if I couldn't win, I was glad it was Ken. I need firewood so I can cook.
I'll go with you. Yeah.
He's so poor. Adam helped him. He didn't win that thing.
I didn't want Dave to win. He was right behind him.
Yeah, I wanted to do everything I could to help Ken, because the most important thing
about the challenge is Jay did not win and Dave did not win.
I swear to God, you guys, I'm voting David tonight. If you want to take me out later,
take me out later, but just let me stay over these two, please, God.
My plan tonight is in the case that Jay does play his idol, Dave would go home.
Look, I want Jay to go home tonight, but the safest thing to do, especially to keep me around...
Is to take Brett home. Yeah.
I don't feel great about the state of my game at all, especially since Jay will be afraid
that we're throwing votes towards his way, and if he does have an idol and he does play it,
I automatically go home. Can we just tell you our plan?
Can I really? Okay, tell me your plan. Okay, so, ostensibly, we are a voting block of four.
Okay. You, me, Ken, Adam. Yeah, that's true.
Okay, we throw three votes at Brett, one vote to Jay, and then Sunday, Brett and Jay will throw
three votes at me. Jay will, if he has an idol, will play it, he'll be safe. Yeah.
Then there's a tie between Brett and myself, and there'll be a re-vote, and then we flip all the votes
to a Brett vote, and Brett goes home. This is my only question. So, we're throwing three votes Brett.
Why not Sunday, and here's why. Sunday, at this point, is such an enticing goat, and the longer
she's in the game, the scarier I feel that someone like Adam, who's playing really hard,
will flip on one of us to try to go with Sunday. Okay. I mean, can you get behind that, Ken?
Okay. All right, all right, well, let's get with that.
It is important at some point to split up Brett and Sunday.
Sunday's extremely dangerous because she's sort of made herself into a tenting goat,
and people could want to sit next to her, and I'm very scared that someone who worked less hard
will get a spot that I've worked really hard for.
Let's talk about tonight. Yeah. Jay is two immunity wins away from winning this game.
Yeah. All I know is that I need to vote for Jay tonight.
He's gonna play his idol. And then if he does, who do the other three go to?
Dave. I definitely want to be walking back here after tribal council with David,
who has been my closest ally and my closest friend, but Adam's afraid of David,
doesn't want to play against David. We need to vote for Jay. We need to get rid of his idol.
I had a long conversation with Ken and Hannah, and throughout the entire conversation,
I knew what I wanted to do. We have to put enough votes on Jay that if he doesn't play his idol,
he goes home, and we have to put enough votes on Dave that if he does play his idol, Dave goes home.
The only way around it is if the four of us vote for Sunday, but that risks Jay moving forward
with an idol in his pocket. And if Jay were to win again, we'd be in big trouble.
If we vote for Sunday, it would leave both Jay and Dave in the game, and they're two strong strategic players,
so we have to make sure that one of them goes home.
Do you feel good? Yeah. I mean, as sad as it is, these are the two biggest risks.
If Jay goes home tonight, that's huge. He could win every immunity going.
There are so many moving parts to tonight's vote, and the worst thing that we can have is tomorrow morning,
Jay is still in this game with an idol in his pocket.
You're going to have to play your idol.
Why that big of a threat to you that you have to strip me of everything?
Yeah.
That's the only way that I'd beat you. I hate you.
It's Adam telling me, I know you have the idol, I'm going to force you to play it.
But Adam always lies to me, so in all honesty, my name might not even come up tonight,
and if I feel like not playing the idol, then I might just do it.
You're forcing my hand. I'm not forcing it.
Yes, you are. I'm not going home, Adam. It's me and you until the end.
Just get me there, man. Please. I need to.
I know. I know it means a lot to you.
It means a lot to me, too, that I'm in the same boat.
And that's why I came with it.
I can't waste my opportunity.
Can I tell you something that I haven't told anyone in this game?
What?
My mom has stage four lung cancer.
And she's already been through three treatments.
And I found out when my brother came in the third one, it isn't working either.
That's why this has been so much to me, I'm doing it for her.
She wants to watch me get to the end.
That's why I can't waste this opportunity.
I've been scared for the past nine years, and my mom's going to die, bro.
I'm so scared.
I love my mom just like he does.
And it's crazy because, like, my mom's got brain aneurysms.
Me and Adam are both out here for our families, for our moms.
He's not a Weasel in my book anymore. He's a good freaking dude. He's a warrior.
I think I might vote for Sunday.
Oh, I hate you.
Okay, here's why. Even if Jay gets through with an adult, if Sunday goes home, then we've just saved David's ass and we have a more loyal four.
I don't want to do that.
Why not?
Because I think one of the two of them has to go home tonight.
Why?
Because there are huge threats in this game.
Adam's reluctance to vote out Sunday is my reluctance, too, because it leaves a visible threat in the game, which is David.
The problem is, if Jay plays his idol and David goes home, I lose David, who I freaking love.
So I don't know the right choice.
But the kind of person that makes a decision and convinces other people of that decision is the kind of person that wins Survivor.
Now bring in the members of our jury.
Michelle, Taylor, Chris, Jessica, Zeke, and Will voted out at the last travel council.
So David, right now in the game, do friendships and alliances really matter or is it everybody for themselves and all bets are off?
I actually think you have to lean on friendships and bonds even more than at the beginning or middle of the game.
I think they're incredibly important.
Jay, do you agree with that? Do bonds have currency?
Yeah, you are relying on alliances, which, you know, I don't see any of mine sitting here anymore.
But Jay, is that where you feel a little pressure is that you're clearly a threat and tonight you don't have the protection of the necklace.
Honestly, Jeff, a challenge threat is a big deal. But if you have a challenge threat who's sitting up here with a necklace on his neck, who has an alliance, what's bigger?
The guy who's alone or the guy that has friends that have his back?
Brett, what is Jay saying?
Jay's saying he wishes he had that necklace around his neck because he's very scared tonight.
David, Jay's saying I'm just one guy, but that all depends on perspective.
Yeah, you know, another term you could use would be a free agent. And so if there are people looking to make a move, you can exploit someone like a free agent.
You've taken a lot of heat, David.
I have.
For several Tribals, people have said you're a legitimate threat to win this game and we've got to take you out. And yet, here you still sit.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I do. I don't know that that'll be true after tonight. But yes, I've relied heavily on friendships and alliances to still be sitting here.
Adam, you seem to have a reaction to that. Is David right or wrong?
Yeah, Dave's in the majority pretty much every vote, has impressed people with his work around camp, with his transformation, and that's what juries love to root for.
Hannah, we keep coming back to this whole conundrum. Who to get rid of, who to take, based on what we think the jury's going to think.
Yeah, a lot of discussion has been around who are the threats to win at the end, because I think every single person here has already written their final speech, and that's been a main point of discussion for all of us.
Sunday, what do you think is thought of you right now? Are you somebody that they should take to the end or are you a threat to get rid of tonight?
You know, obviously I'm not a physical threat, and so I think I'm a person that people are thinking, oh, I'll just take her to the end.
Meaning, you can't get any votes?
I think I can get votes, but I think there are people that think that I can't get votes, and so I think I'm a little bit underestimated.
Adam, if the perception of Sunday is true, it works to Sunday's advantage.
Suddenly it's like, maybe you should take me to the end, and maybe I can still beat you even though you clearly have no confidence in me.
Yeah, I mean the reality is everyone in this group right now has been playing their own game.
It's just a matter of what is the perception of the jury, and that's what you have to take into account when deciding who you want to sit next to at the end.
Alright, it is time to vote. Sunday, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity addle and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
Alright.
I'd rather be safe than sorry, Jeff.
You guys get to play with me some more.
This is a hidden immunity addle. Any votes cast for Jay will not count.
I read the votes.
First vote, Jay does not count.
David, one vote David.
David, two votes David.
Sunday, two votes David, one vote Sunday.
Sunday, two votes David, two votes Sunday.
Sunday, that's three votes Sunday, two votes David, one vote left.
I knew it, I didn't have to use it.
Fourteenth person voted out, the seventh member of our jury. Sunday, you need to bring me your torch.
Sunday, the chart was spoke.
Good luck guys, have fun. Thanks Sunday.
Take care.
Dang it.
Well, 35 days ago we began this season, Millennials versus Gen X.
So it is only fitting that there are three Millennials, three Gen X, as we begin the battle to the finish.
Grab your torches, head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survival, Six are Left, and the game is still up in the air.
If I have to do dirty tricks like this, then so be it.
An idol can screw everything up.
I have the legacy advantage that you got in store for me.
Who will outlast all the others?
Every person here is a legitimate threat to win this game.
And claim the title of sole survivor.
Join us for the finale.
Having to go home now this close to the end is just gut wrenching because you can see the finish line.
But I know my family is going to be beyond proud of how I played.
I slept in the dirt for 30 days. I did challenges I would have never done.
I jumped off things I never would have jumped off of.
I am honestly leaving feeling so proud of myself and I have zero regrets about it.