Previously on Survivor...
In the Ikabula tribe,
Sunday and Bret were in the minority.
I went from a quartet to a duo.
In the Takali tribe,
Figgy and Taylor
were trying to hide their romance.
Don't hug me!
And Adam found himself
in a position of strength
between two Gen X
and Gen Y lovers.
It is with me
that they must work.
In the Vanua tribe,
Gen X had control,
but there were cracks
between them.
So it's Cece.
- I mean...
- I will.
And Chris used his ties to Zeke
to enlist Gen Y.
I'm ready to take a hit.
Finally, I have an opening
in this game.
At the council,
the Gen X gave
up their numerical advantage
and to Cece.
Cece, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck to everyone.
There are 15 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The fight goes on!
It was really good.
The return of the council
was a complete relief.
Chris and I said goodbye
to Cece with these two Gen Ys.
Let's rekindle the fire!
Good boy! Good boy!
It was clearly the right thing to do
for the future.
It's no longer Gen Y against Gen X,
it's my trusted
people against your trusted people.
It was great
voting with you today.
It was a pleasure
voting with you and Michelle.
- It had to be done.
- And you kept your word.
The advice was a delight,
car ces idiots by Gen X
fired one of their own
in the only tribe
where they were in the majority!
Suddenly, I seem to be
in a strong position with Chris.
I'm so happy.
I'm a new man
in this game of Survivor.
I am really hungry.
It's horrible.
Everyone is hungry
and grumpy.
But I have to stay focused,
because I have this passion,
in me, who says,
"You have to watch over your family."
Do you want to go get
some dead buds?
Downright.
I have my mother, and my sister,
and I never had a father.
For me, it was, "I have to watch
over these two beautiful ladies."
Gen Ys are said to be selfish,
want to do everything their way
and do whatever they want.
But this is not true.
It's for my family.
I will win Survivor.
Do you see something?
Jeez, where are they hiding these idols?
I do not know.
The immunity idol
is the only comfort.
I have to find her.
And I look for her everywhere.
Here, that's weird.
It's the symbol of the tribe, huh?
There is a small green symbol
and I'm like,
"What the hell is this?"
Seeing the acronym,
I know she's around.
But I go,
"No, fuck, she's not here!"
I look in the tree and around,
and boom! I break the bamboo...
Hell, I knew it!
So what...
I hear the Survivor theme playing
in the background!
And I'm like,
"This is so awesome, this is awesome!"
Dude, open your eyes.
Brothel!
- I have an idol!
- Dude!
Oh my God!
- Lord!
This idol means,
"Mom, this is one step closer
to your house."
This is probably
my best day in Survivor.
I'm so happy.
- Man, it stays between us.
- Yeah.
What is that?
"Hey! What do you have there?"
- Where did you find her?
- On the ground.
I come across these two,
huddled together like Eskimos,
and appears this idol.
Now
we know they don't.
- So it's all good?
- Yeah.
Jay is one of my allies,
but do I think he would play
this idol for me?
Surely not!
- Bad timing.
- Horrible.
Damn Michaela!
For now, I won't tell anyone
that Jay has the idol.
But if I get wind
of something going on,
I will swing it.
Over here, everyone!
Discover the new Vanua tribe.
Cece was eliminated
at the last tip.
And lots of reactions.
Figgy, you were the first.
You cheered
as soon as it was Cece.
I love Michelle, so...
I love Zeke too,
but I was very, very worried.
Said like that,
it's horrible, sorry.
Michelle and I
are very close, I adore her.
Michelle. Does it concern you
that in such a game,
Figgy be so open?
No. I think
the truth actually works well in this game.
You must be
the first person to say that,
"Truth works well in this game."
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today,
one person will be your voice.
The others will be blindfolded.
By oral commands alone,
the voice will lead
his blindfolded comrades
to collect puzzle pieces.
When you have them all,
the voice will direct
a comrade always blindfolded
to solve the puzzle.
- Oh my God!
- My God!
The first two tribes to finish
win a reward.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Please!
For the first tribe to finish...
Apple pie,
iced tea,
cold milk.
- Milk!
- Apple pie!
For the 2nd tribe to finish, not bad,
chocolate chip cookies.
Good. Takali, you are one more.
- Who will not participate?
- I ss.
Jessica will not participate
for Takali.
Ikabula, you are two more.
Who will it be?
Bret and me.
Bret and Hannah
will not participate for Ikabula.
All three on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and here we go.
Here we go, for a nice reward.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
- To the right.
- Ahead. To the right!
Carry on, forward!
A little to the left! Carry on!
It's all about communication.
Ken, left!
Straight! To the left!
Are your instructions clear?
- All right, keep going!
- On your right, there you are!
Carry on!
Advance! Stop!
You are at this pole where we turn!
- Sunday is at an obstacle.
- Turn right!
Go to your left!
Keep it up, Zeke!
Attention! So!
Adam tries to reach
for puzzle pieces.
Undo it, Adam!
Sunday continues, his head is spinning!
She freed them!
She falls, that's what happens!
Sunday is confused.
Adam has puzzle pieces.
That's it, Zeke!
Zeke reached for coins.
There are four coin packs
per tribe.
Michaela, pull the rope!
Right in front of you! Here, shoot!
Michaela unwinds the rope
for Ikabula.
Adam brought the 1st pieces
to the table for Takali.
Turn to your left!
Turn... Yes!
Advance!
David, move on!
Taylor! Pull the rope!
Second package of coins
for Takali.
They are widening the gap!
Stop! Go to the touch,
on the thing!
Sunday, right.
The table is right there.
Sunday has the first package of coins
for Ikabula.
Yes, that's it, Chris!
Turn it!
To your right, David, to your right!
David, go right!
Stopped!
Taylor untied a bundle of parts.
Go to your left, Taylor, to the left!
Zeke brings back
the first parts of Vanua.
That's it?
Chris has the second package,
can he bring it back?
Will has the second pack of parts
for Ikabula.
This is the third for Takali.
More than a bundle of coins
for Takali.
Michaela, can you smell the table?
Put that on it.
Michaela has the third
pack of coins for Ikabula.
Ken and Taylor,
at the fourth station,
look for their last package.
To the right!
Faster, Ken!
- Where is it?
- Right in front of you.
Chris has the 2nd coin pack
for Vanua.
- David...
- Go through me, it'll go faster.
OK. "Go to your right."
David, go to your right!
David, right again!
Tell him!
- On your right!
- David, right!
David does not know where to go.
Right left,
North South?
No, David, no!
These are not the good ones!
Don't, David, don't!
God's goodness!
Ken takes a big fall!
The key, the key!
Who has the key?
Michaela, turn right!
Grab the rope! Untie it!
Open it and grab the coins!
Good!
Yes it's good! Straight!
David, come back!
- David, over here!
- Move!
David, over here!
Ken and Taylor return
with the final bundle of parts.
Its good!
They can attack the puzzle!
Distribute them well!
Figgy and Ken
will try to solve the puzzle,
Ken, blindfolded.
Yes! Follow the rope!
Here, turn left!
David finally has something to do!
David unrolls.
Here are my parts.
Michaela has the fourth
and final coin pack.
- Straight!
- Zeke, to your right!
Zeke, to your right!
David and Zeke attempt to retrieve
the final two for Vanua.
David has a pack of parts.
David, come back!
The table is there. Put them down.
Michaela has the fourth
and final package.
- Untie them!
- Attack the puzzle!
Yes that's it!
Big advantage for Takali,
they have a huge lead
for a huge reward.
David returns
with the third package for Vanua.
- I feel very weak.
- Really?
Hurry up, Zeke,
it's good, it's the last!
Zeke brought back
the fourth and final package.
They have plenty of time
to catch up.
Zeke will solve the puzzle.
The only problem,
it's that the jigsaw attendants
are blindfolded.
She feels weak.
So come over here.
Get in the shade.
- Tell me if you need the doctor.
- OK. Its good.
Do not hesitate to ask!
Take the one on the right. No, sorry,
leave it, but exchange them.
Michelle started long after,
that would be an impressive comeback.
Replace that.
Yeah, honey.
Figgy and Ken
had a huge lead.
Can they make it work?
We try, Jeff!
Michaela and Jay
are making some progress.
- Now lift that.
- Push that one!
The Vanua were dead last.
Michelle and Zeke
do their best to come back up.
Turn that one.
the one you have in hand,
put it on the top left.
Figgy tries to figure out
what's wrong.
- My whole face is tingling.
- Stay cool.
Michelle and Zeke
collaborate very well.
It could be an amazing comeback
if they are right.
Zeke tentacle of pleasure...
- Yes! That's it!
- And they are right!
What a comeback!
Vanua wins a huge reward!
He remains in second place.
- I can't feel my hands anymore.
- I'm here.
It's Jay and Michaela,
Figgy and Ken,
in search of chocolate cookies.
Return those two.
Another piece for Jay!
Ken moves another piece.
Michaela slips another coin.
- Jeff, I'm done.
- Jay thinks he found it.
Return this one!
Ikabula wins the reward!
Chocolate chip cookies.
They send Takali back to camp
empty-handed.
after having had
a gigantic lead.
Everything is fine. I'm here.
Are you doing well?
I don't know if I'm panicking
or dehydrated.
Doctor! Doctor Joe!
Could you review Hannah?
I have cramps in my arms.
Because you're breathing
a little fast, aren't you?
- What's wrong with Hannah?
- I do not know.
- Don't let me die!
- But no, everything will be fine.
It's just because
you're breathing a little fast, okay?
Breathe with me, okay?
Slow down. Exhale.
Slowly. That's it.
Well, it's getting better.
- Really?
- Yes everything is fine.
What's going on, Joe?
Hannah must have gotten a little excited
during the ordeal
and begin to breathe
a little too quickly.
And if we do this for no good reason,
physically,
it can reduce the acidity of the blood
and one of the symptoms,
it's spasms
in the wrist and hand.
But Hannah was able to calm down
and it already seems to be going away.
You seem to know it,
to be aware of what is going on.
I knew coming here
that panic attacks,
this is something that happens to me.
But I would have preferred without an audience.
If anything should reveal
your weaknesses, it's Survivor.
It's brave
to have come here despite that.
We'll take you back to your tribe
and give you more water.
Thanks. Thank you.
Good. How are you.
No need to applaud!
How are you, Hannah?
- Much better, thank you.
- It shows.
Thank you, Dr. Joe.
Yes, I feel better.
Good. Let's go to the result.
A spectacular comeback
led by Michelle.
Huge reward.
Come get her!
- Pie, cookies, brownies!
- Take the pie, man!
- Iced tea, milk!
- I'll take the cupcakes!
- Enjoy!
- Look at this pie!
Ikabula, it's not a feast,
but, Michaela...
I take!
You take?
Well, come and get them!
- I accept!
- Enjoy!
Thanks, Jeff!
So Figgy...
It's a "hero or zero" role,
when you say, "I'll be the voice."
What happened?
It's frustrating when you're so close,
that we are the voice, the leader,
we have a puzzle,
but guiding a blind man is hard.
We think we can get there
and we fail, it sucks.
It's hard.
Takali, I have nothing for you.
Pack your things, head back to camp.
Thank you all!
I'm so happy there!
It's funny.
Before, I thought to myself,
"You're all blocking my
way to the million."
You see? We think about it!
And now it's,
"Oh, my God, pie!"
We probably wouldn't have won
with Cece.
Michelle did everything,
solve the puzzle, lead us...
And of course,
Figgy seems to really like me!
- He missed it, I think.
- I say.
Michelle is a
very dangerous player.
For Figgy announced to the world,
to the test,
"I'm so happy
to see Michelle."
Then, after a moment,
"Oh, and Zeke too!"
It was, "Hi, Michelle!
Hey, Zeke!"
No, it was, "I love Michelle.
Oh, and Zeke!"
"Hi, good to see you too!"
I'm clearly
at the bottom of Gen Y.
My instinct therefore tells me that
eliminating Michelle
is not bad for me.
Because she plotted against me
and has ties to Taylor and Figgy.
Honestly,
Figgy owes me his life in this game.
I never thought I would say that.
But I believe that to progress,
I might have to give up
the Gen Y tribe.
Today
was a fascinating experience.
A panic attack is not
necessarily a lot of panic.
It's suppressed panic.
And in this game
one constantly puts one
's feelings aside.
Today I already know
some will laugh at me.
I can't help it
if I'm anxious.
Of course, it's embarrassing,
to collapse
without even being in the test.
I said to myself, in relation to the game,
"I must not seem weak."
That's the worst, "I mustn't
be so weak in front of my tribe."
Let's give up. I think
we've proven to ourselves that we can do it.
My brain is exhausted.
Not a moment ago
where you can breathe and...
I'm taking a break from Survivor
for five minutes."
And so, I must continue.
Perception is reality.
I have to repeat that I'm fine,
to let people
know that I'm fine,
so that it doesn't handicap my game.
I'm too co-happy
to have my coco!
- Thanks!
- Go on!
- It was on the cheek, not the lips.
- Too cute.
How about we make out in
front of you, Adam?
Disgusting!
My Survivor romance is
growing every day.
But Figgy tells me,
"Don't talk to Jess and Ken
of our history!"
Of this little romance we have.
But Gen Y are in the majority,
so we are well placed.
We are the dominant couple.
At this point, there
is no reason to hide.
Everyone knows except Ken and Jess.
It can't harm us.
- Adam is with us, so...
- I know, honey.
Should I tell Jess?
I would train with me,
quickly.
Are you going to do Jess?
Health!
So, Taylor and I,
there's something between us.
Oh, I knew it!
I knew it, darling!
There, we have the majority, with Adam.
But coming out
worries me.
God, isn't it gonna be weird?
Yes, it will be weird.
But will do it.
I don't know
what reaction to expect.
- Hey, my little lady!
- Hi!
I want to talk to you about something.
It's the scariest. Will the reaction
be good or bad?
I didn't tell you
nor to Ken, because I was nervous,
but there is something
between Taylor and me.
Serious?!
You are to die for!
Wait, really, did you know?
You're not very good
at keeping secrets.
Ken, I was telling Jessica...
There's some kind of thing
between me and Taylor.
No kidding?!
- I never would have guessed.
- Really?
Well, when I wake up in the morning
and see you
entwined, holding your hand...
Or when you're always
looking at yourself and looking for yourself...
You laugh?
I wasn't born yesterday, kid!
I
rolled my bump a lot more than you and...
It's obvious!
And she was shocked, convinced she was
hiding it wonderfully.
I who thought
I would reveal a secret to you!
I appreciate you bringing it up, but...
Not surprised.
These kids think they're in charge.
They think, "It's the holidays,
we're having fun, I'm in Survivor,
It's awesome!"
But this little couple,
they're less cool than they think.
I'm not going to sit idle
and hope everything goes well.
I will act to make sure.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First,
I have to take back the idols.
See you soon, Junior!
We'll trade it for the big one.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will cross
a series of floating beams,
collect bags of coconuts,
bring them back to the beach.
When you have them all,
open them to find three balls.
Two players
will then maneuver these balls
on a table-maze.
The first two tribes
to bring their three balls to the end
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers will go to the board
where someone will be the sixth person
eliminated from this game.
Takali, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
- Me.
- Adam won't participate.
Ikabula, you are two more.
- Who will it be?
- We.
All three on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization
and we start.
Good.
Let's go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Ken is in the water,
Jay is in the water
and David is in the water.
Ken moves fast,
but he falls.
Ken has to start over.
Jay quickly crossed.
Now you have to climb
and land three bags.
Jay unties.
David and Ken try to catch up with him.
Jay has his second.
Ken unties.
Ken has his third,
and a big fall!
David has his third.
Well done, David!
David, the big surprise
of this event!
It's Ken who's having trouble.
Jay brings the three bags at once.
David can only bring one,
but he retains the advantage over Ken.
Third bag for Ken.
Lord, what a fall!
Jay brought the three bags.
Bret is in the water for Ikabula.
Come on, Breth!
Ken brings the three bags at once,
catching up on time.
David is dragging two bags now.
Combined, they weigh more than him!
Go!
Chris is in the water for Vanua.
Taylor quickly crosses
the beams.
Takali now leads.
Give it your all, baby!
Chris arrives,
he tries to catch up with time
lost by David.
Taylor escalates fast
and fetch
the last three bags.
Bret is right behind.
Taylor quickly lands
all three sacks, in one fell swoop.
Bret has his third bag.
Give it your all, you're almost there!
Once Taylor arrives, it's good.
Hang them!
Takali has a huge lead.
Bret arrives
with the last three bags.
Third bag for Chris.
Chris is going to have to be quick
to stay in the game.
Ken and Taylor are fast,
here is the sixth and final bag.
Its good!
Over to you, ladies!
It's now Figgy
and Jessica.
You have to take out all the coconuts.
You are looking for three balls.
Sixth bag for Jay.
Go to the mat!
Over to you, ladies!
Chris is there with his three bags.
Michaela and Hannah
are doing a great job.
Go, Vanua!
Michelle and Zeke
are going to open the bags.
Takali pulled it all out.
You have to find three balls.
There in front.
have their three balls.
Attack the maze!
You have to maneuver
a very difficult table
while having the feet
on a very small perch.
We manage.
Jessica and Figgy
have a huge lead.
Michaela and Hannah
opened the last bag.
They have their three balls.
Ahead!
Zeke is on the last sack
trying to make up time.
And There you go!
Find the ball and come here!
- It's Figgy and Jessica...
- We have to go through this though.
- ...Michaela and Hannah...
- Stop making such moves!
...and Zeke and Michelle,
for immunity.
Michelle and Zeke know
they have some catching up to do.
From the outset, they go all out.
- Not as much, not as much!
- Sorry.
You hold on too much.
Just hold it.
Michaela continues
to bark orders at Hannah.
Don't move it,
I'm telling you to just hold it!
She makes sure Hannah
knows who's ordering.
Each duo tries to understand
the rhythm of the others.
Michaela and Hannah
at a difficult place.
You have to go through
a very narrow passage.
Michaela and Hannah,
closer than ever.
- Don't move at all!
- No, I'm just keeping it.
Can they do it?
Yes! Hannah and Michaela
took the lead!
Jessica and Figgy are nearby.
Oh my God!
Rushing will only get you
a date with me at the council.
- Don't be frustrated.
- I'm not.
I'm just trying to make you win.
To keep us all here.
Lowers and to the side!
Hannah and Michaela are two up,
huge lead!
Gently, Figg.
Figgy and Jessica are nearby.
- Yeah!
- Yes! Quick, the next one!
Figgy and Jessica
placed their first ball.
Michelle and Zeke get nowhere.
- Tell me if I should move.
- The farm!
Hannah and Michaela
may never go
on vacation together...
I love it! I just need
people to shut it up sometimes.
Stay fixed!
They are inches away
from immunity.
Lift slightly.
Oh my God!
And they succeed!
Hannah and Michaela
win immunity,
Ikabula is safe!
You can do anything!
He remains in second place.
It's Jessica and Figgy
against Michelle and Zeke
who know they have to
start something.
Zeke, Michelle, only one has to move
to pass the bar.
Now
Michaela helps Michelle and Zeke.
- Stop the ball!
- Michelle and Zeke...
...are close. Well saved!
Can they place it?
A few centimeters away...
There you go!
Tied, 1 - 1.
Now there is a game!
Jessica and Figgy, well saved!
And they place their 2nd!
Well, well!
One more bullet
and Jessica and Figgy win immunity.
The pressure is on Michelle and Zeke.
Nice touch.
Will she go down the hole?
Let her slide!
One centimeter, and voila!
Another tie, 2 - 2!
It's the race to the finish.
It all happens there.
Go! Go! Go!
If Vanua succeeds,
it would be a gigantic comeback.
Nobody wants to go to the council.
Jessica and Figgy arrive.
One more, baby.
All around.
Nice recovery
from Michelle and Zeke.
Jessica and Figgy,
can they save her?
Michelle and Zeke are well placed.
And it is successful, for immunity!
Vanua is safe
and sends Takali to the council!
Someone there will be eliminated from the game.
Ikabula.
Congratulation.
Immunity.
No one will leave your tribe.
Vanua.
Congratulation.
No one will leave your tribe.
I have to ask.
There was encouragement
from you, Michaela, for Vanua.
What's there behind?
We would like Gen Y to stay
and at 2 - 2, someone has to leave.
There are Gen Y here!
Yeah, but you are three.
If you can't cooperate,
you deserve to leave.
Ikabula, no one will leave,
no advice tonight.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Vanua. No advice tonight
for you either.
No one will leave.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Takali, tonight, advice.
Someone will be the sixth person
eliminated from the game.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Takali tribe go to council tonight
It's really too dumb.
But if Gen Y's smart,
we'll stay together
and we will release the Gen X.
Well done, everyone.
You worked well.
We tried.
We were so close...
That we lost
is very annoying for me,
because since we've been here,
I've been playing the double agent
and it looks like if I wanted
to go with Jessica and Ken,
I could do it.
And if I wanted to go
with Figgy and Taylor, I could.
But whatever I vote tonight,
someone will come back unhappy.
My position is very difficult.
I am with you.
- Taylor is with you.
- I say. I know it well.
- So it's Ken or Jessica.
- Sure.
Most...
- Who would you rather date?
- Ken, I guess.
I do not know.
It's hard, very hard.
I think we should vote Ken.
I think so too.
So the plan is to take Ken out.
He is a dangerous player
and at the merger, he will be a threat
in the trials.
I believe we are
on the same wavelength.
- We're taking Ken out.
- Yes.
Tonight, at the council,
we're going to eliminate Ken.
Damn, why did we lose?
I hate that.
But who knows?
Maybe Adam will double cross us,
He's a lot smarter
than you think.
But maybe!
What do you say?
- Do we really trust Adam?
- I only trust you.
I say.
It sucks!
Well, if you wanna
work with me, I got Ken.
It is 100% reliable.
One of the two is eliminated
and then it's you, me and Ken.
You see? Where does your heart take you
now?
I do not know.
Do you know if they're considering Ken?
Sure.
Figgy and Taylor vont vote Ken.
But that
clearly doesn't have to happen.
I need Ken to progress.
He covers me and I cover him.
And if Ken leaves,
I'll be next.
what you must do,
it is talking to Adam.
You have to convince
him that you are with him 150%.
Otherwise, he will vote for you.
You have to convince
him that you will never vote for him.
That's what we need to tell him,
that the three of us will control the game.
I could leave
but I never bow
without a fight.
So from here the advice,
I am going to fight.
I respect you. Jess too.
We don't want to move forward
with two sneaky people
and arrogant kids.
So Jess and I are voting Figgy.
Do you want to sit there with me,
David and Jess?
Or with Taylor, Figg
and popular kids,
knowing you're at the bottom of the ladder?
Basically, what you ask me,
it's trusting
people I don't know.
I'll cover you all the way
and never vote for you.
And I will fight for you.
So...
All you have to do is decide
who you want to ride with.
My mind is spinning.
Ken has a strong case.
The question is,
which side will be the best
for my future in the game?
The whole world is probably screaming,
"Get out the dominant couple!
What are you thinking about?!"
But at this point,
I don't know
if that makes sense to me.
Ken, give me a rundown.
' Cause on the surface
it's easy to say,
"Three Gen Y, two Gen X,
one of you is going."
Yes, it is obvious
that there are only two Gen X.
It clearly sets us apart.
Taylor, are you okay?
The Gen Ys will stay together.
Yes, that's what I would say.
If you can have such a link,
so many things are possible.
even if you started
with Taylor and Adam,
it doesn't imply
that you get along.
Yes, not everything is rosy
between Gen Y.
Friends of this guy
voted for me on the 1st tip!
But I don't blame them.
I passed that.
Adam, Figgy says she's forgiven you
for voting for her.
Let her look at you
like she looks at Taylor,
"We are in the same boat."
She clearly doesn't look at me
exactly like Taylor!
Let this be very clear!
Whether you call it
a "showmance" or a romance,
there is "mance" in the air.
So Taylor.
Are you in love?
I wouldn't say that.
This is going a bit far.
But we love each other very much.
The budding loves!
Ken. Did you notice
this relationship?
It was hilarious,
when they came,
"Surely you didn't notice it,
but know it,
- Actually, there's something between us."
- Did you say that?
It was obvious from the start.
Being an honorary pastor,
if I said to you,
"To hell with caution!
Let's get married immediately!"
Gen Ys do that kind of stuff.
We'll get you married right away,
I'll take care of the papers!
- Lord!
- A first! Let's go!
You are serious?
I can't tell.
I was just saying
it would be a first.
Taylor. When Figgy says,
"Let's do it!",
and you say,
"Are you serious?",
she's waiting for you...
Am I right, Ken?
...that you come forward and confirm
what she just said,
thus validating his feelings
and giving him
a sense of security
in this very deep relationship
born two weeks ago.
Oh my God!
So, Figgy.
You don't seem worried
- let it be public.
- Nope.
Me and Taylor, we got our thing,
but we're just two people
voting together.
As they both vote together.
Jessica and Ken.
Exactly.
But, Adam, there seems to be
a slight difference
between Ken and Jessica
voting together by strategy
and Figgy and Taylor
doing it because they like each other.
Sure.
Figgy, you act
like this is totally insane.
Yeah, man!
We didn't come here for that.
It just happened.
We remain very strategic,
at each stage.
Taylor. Is it easier
to be honest about your relationship
with the luxury
of a power play?
Yes, clearly.
With that edge, you can just say,
"You know what?
It's like that.
If you don't like it,
I can write your name."
But the majority can change sides
at any time.
It may not be
all black or white,
Gen X or Gen Y.
So Adam.
We have Taylor and Figgy
who are a couple,
Jessica and Ken,
who are a strategic duo,
which leaves you in the middle.
I think that's okay, Jeff.
So Taylor.
Either Adam remains among you three,
or he joins Jessica and Ken.
Yes, he could totally
turn his jacket around.
But at the merger,
Gen Y are already in the majority.
They might be like,
"Oh, what are you doing, man?",
and release it immediately.
So you're pretty clear,
if Adam betrays Gen Y,
you will untap him.
I think Gen Y
would, all together.
- Adam, you must have thought of that.
- Sure.
The issue goes beyond tonight.
I consider the future
and I hope
that whoever the four
who leave tonight,
they can be a quartet.
Jessica. If these three
remain faithful,
you can't do much.
I was surprised to notice
quarrels in the tribe.
And if you achieve fusion,
they will still be there.
- Figgy, it makes you react.
- Yes.
I feel like I'm
having an arm wrestling match.
To win Adam?
Yes almost. Finally...
You have to remember
where the majority is.
Jeff, I have one more thing to say.
The person I'm voting for tonight,
I really appreciate it.
It is going to be difficult.
Someone will leave angry
and someone
will return to camp angry.
Good. It's time to vote.
Taylor, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Ken.
Two votes Ken.
Figgy. Equality.
Two votes Ken,
two votes Figgy.
One vote remains.
Sixth person eliminated
from Survivor Gen Y against Gen X...
Figgy.
Bring me your torch.
I will explain myself, if I can.
Figgy, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Good luck, Taylor.
It was said tonight,
"Someone will be eliminated
and someone
will return to the camp dissatisfied."
The question becomes,
how are you going to handle it?
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Taylor, the disappointed lover...
I lied to you and I screwed you.
...seeks revenge.
I will destroy you!
But a powerful new duo...
Zeke, I trust you a lot.
...begins to form.
We are made of the same wood.
- Do you have the idol?
- I found it.
God's goodness!
He put his life in my hands!
I arrived fully launched,
ready to fight,
and I was clearly
a force to be reckoned with,
so I take my elimination
as a compliment,
because otherwise, I would
probably have taken them all out.
I am not at all
disappointed with my game.
But I'm upset that I'm
not with Taylor anymore.
We will probably be
reunited one day.
But not for a while.