>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THERE WAS A ROCK DRAW.
REVEAL.
>> JESSICA WAS SENT TO THE JURY.
AND WILLED HER LEGACY ADVANTAGE
TO KEN.
NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> TONIGHT WAS JUST VERY
EMOTIONAL.
TO HAVE PEOPLE PICK A ROCK
RATHER THAN VOTE ME OUT OF THIS
GAME AND THEN TO HAVE JESSICA
PICK THE BLACK ROCK, IT'S AN
AWFUL FEELING.
I FEEL GUILTY AND I FEEL
THANKFUL, AND I-- I JUST FEEL
AWFUL.
I JUST WATCHED SOMEONE--
EVERYTHING GET RIPPED BECAUSE OF
A ROCK.
>> DON'T PUT THIS ALL ON
YOURSELF.
>> WE ALL TOOK THE GAMBLE.
>> WE ALL MADE A CHOICE.
I'M REALLY ANGRY AT MYSELF.
I BURNED MY IDOL AT TRIBAL FOR
NO REASON.
AND NOW, I FIND MYSELF IN A
MINORITY WITH HANNAH, KEN, AND
ADAM.
SO I NEED TO FIND SOME CRACK
SOMEWHERE.
OTHERWISE, THE FIVE IS JUST
GOING TO PICK US OFF ONE BY ONE.
, STARTING WITH ME.
>> BRO, I TOLD YOU, I TOLD YOU.
>> THE TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
AMAZING!
I LOVED IT.
MAN, I FELT LIKE A WARRIOR.
>> THAT PISSED ME OFF, TOO.
>> THIS VOTE WAS ALL ABOUT DAVID
AND I GOING TO WAR TOGETHER.
AND I DEFINITELY WON UPON
BATTLE.
>> I'M TRYING VERY HARD NOT TO
BE TOO EXCITED, BUT I FEEL LIKE
I'M GOING TO THE FINAL FIVE.
>> OH, YEAH.
I THINK I CAN WIN THIS GAME.
AND I'M JUST AS HAPPY I COULD
WIN THIS GAME AS I AM THAT DAVID
IS GOING TO LOSE IT.
>> I RECEIVED A GIFT THIS
MORNING, IN MY BAG.
I GOT THIS.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND THE LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
IF YOU ARE IN POSSESSION OF SOME
NOTE ON DAY 36, YOU WILL RECEIVE
AN ADVANTAGE IN THE GAME."
JESS, YOU ARE AMAZING.
JESS TOLD ME THAT SHE'D GIVE ME
ADVANTAGE IF SHE GOT VOTED OUT.
GOD, I LOVE THAT GIRL.
AND SHE DID.
IT'S BIG.
THERE IS SOMETHING TO BE SAID
ABOUT THE POWER OF BEING
AUTHENTIC AND GENUINE
RELATIONSHIPS IN THIS GAME.
DAY 36 IF I'M STILL HERE I'M
GOING TO OPEN THIS UP AND SEE
WHAT IT BRINGS ME BECAUSE I FEEL
LIKE I'VE GOT A REALLY GOOD SHOT
TO GET MY DAUGHTER AND I A NEW
LIFE AND A BETTER LIFE AND MAYBE
WALKING AWAY WITH A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO WE ARE
31 DAYS INTO THIS GAME.
I THINK IT SOUNDS LIKE A PERFECT
TIME UNDE FOR LOVE.
>> NO WAY!
DUDE.
>> Jeff: SUNDAY, SAY HELLO TO
YOUR HUSBAND, JEFF!
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: JEFF, COME ON OUT!
>> NO WAY!
OH, MY GOD!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE HERE!
>> Jeff: TAKE IT IN, SUNDAY.
WHAT DOES THAT FEEL LIKE?
>> LIKE, YOU'RE WITH PEOPLE ALL
THE TIME BUT YOU'RE, LIKE,
ALONE.
THEN TO SEE SOMEONE THAT MAKES
YOU NOT ALONE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HER A
HUG.
TAKE A SPOT.
>> OH!
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: BRET, YOU READY FOR
SOME LOVE?
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES YOUR DAD,
DON.
DON, COME ON OUT!
>> OH, BOY.
>> TRY NOT TO TRIP.
LOOK AT YOU!
YOU'RE LOOKING GREAT!
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I TOLD HIM I WOULDN'T CRY.
>> LOOK AT YOU.
>> I KNOW.
THIS GUY IS THE BEST GUY IN THE
WORLD.
A GREAT FRIEND.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> TO SEE HIM HERE, HE'LL DO
ANYTHING FOR ME.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> THANKS, DAD.
I'M GOING TO-- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M CRYING.
I TOLD YOU GUYS I WOULDN'T CRY.
>> YOU LOSER!
YOU LOSER!
LOSER!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR
SPOT BACK.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, DAD.
>> Jeff: JAY, SAY HELLO TO
YOUR SISTER MELANIE.
COME ON OUT, MELANIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DID THEY DO TO YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: JAY, YOU CAN'T LET GO
OF HER.
YOU KEEP GRAK HER BACK IN CLOSE.
>> I HAVE TWO HALF TO MY HEART,
JEFF, AND ONE IS STANDING HERE,
AND ONE IS AT HOME BECAUSE MY
MOM CAN'T COME.
SO THAT'S MY FUEL.
THAT'S MY HEART, JEFF.
THAT'S MY HEART.
I'LL GIVE ME UP BEFORE I GIVE
HER UP.
>> Jeff: MELANIE, THAT'S
PRETTY POWERFUL.
NOT EVERY BROTHER-SISTER HAS
THIS RELATIONSHIP.
>> HE JUST HAPPENS TO KNOW WE
LOVE HIM BACK HOME AND HE'S NOT
ALONE, NOT EVEN ON THIS ISLAND.
WE'RE ON THERE FOR HIM.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MELANIE,
GIVE HIM A LAST HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: HANNAH, YOU READY FOR
SOME LOVE.
>> MY MOM, I'M GOING TO SEE MY
MOM.
>> Jeff: MOM, COME ON OUT.
HERE COMES LIZ!
( APPLAUSE )
>> I'M OKAY.
I'M OKAY.
>> Jeff: WOW, YOU'RE NOW
COMFORTING YOUR MOM.
>> Jeff: WAIT A MINUTE, THIS
IS BACKWARDS.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> Jeff: TELL ME WHAT'S GOING
ON, BECAUSE THIS IS A PRETTY
UNIQUE SITUATION IN THAT THE
DAUGHTER STARTED COMFORTING THE
MOM.
>> MY MOM IS MY HERO.
SHE'S THE BRAVEST PERSON I KNOW.
SHE'S-- SHE BEAT CANCER, SO,
LIKE, THE STRENGTH IS THIS
WOMAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HER
ONE LAST HUG.
>> I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD.
>> BYE.
>> Jeff: ADAM, YOU READY FOR
SOME ROF?
>> YEAH.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA, JEFF.
>> Jeff: EVAN, COME ON OUT.
HERE COMES ADAM'S BROTHER, EVAN.
>> HI!
>> MY MOM HAS STAGE FOUR LUNG
CANCER, AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH MY MOM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON AT
HOME.
>> Jeff: ADAM, DOES IT STRIKE
YOU HOW FAST THE GAME CAN FALL
AWAY AND ALL YOU'RE DOING RIGHT
NOW IS FEELING LOVE OF SOMEONE
YOU KNOW YOU CAN TRUST?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I NEEDED TO BE HERE
RIGHT NOW.
I NEEDED MY BROTHER TO COME OUT
TODAY.
AND IF I DIDN'T GET THAT, IT
WOULD HAVE BEEN ABSOLUTELY
DEVASTATING.
I-- I WANT YOU GUYS ALL TO KNOW,
AND EVAN -- THEY ALREADY KNOW
THIS-- BUT I ACTUALLY HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME.
THAT ALLOWS ME TO STEAL A
REWARD.
BUT I CAN'T USE IT.
OKAY?
>> YOU'RE GOING TO WIN IT
ANYWAY.
>> BECAUSE I CAN'T-- I CAN'T
TAKE YOU GUYS AWAY FROM YOUR
LOVED ONES.
I CAN'T DO IT.
YOU KNOW.
>> YOU'RE A GOOD DUDE, BRO.
>> , ARE.
THANK YOU, ADAM.
>> Jeff: GIVE HIM A HUG.
LAWYER.
>> I WILL.
>> Jeff: DAVID, ARE YOU READY
FOR SOME LOVE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET YOUR DAD
OUT HERE.
>> DOUG, COME ON OUT!
>> DAD!
>> I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I SWEAR I'VE BEEN CRYING SO MUCH
OUT HERE.
>> Jeff: DAVID, WHY IS IT
IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO HAVE YOUR
DAD SEE YOU OUT HERE IN ONE OF
THE TOUGHEST SITUATIONS ANYONE
WILL EVER FIND THEMSELVES?
N?
>> I JUST-- I WANT TO MAKE HIM
PROUD?
>> OH, YOU ALREADY HAVE.
>> THANK YOU.
AND HE HAS SUCH A JOY FOR LIFE,
A PASSION FOR LIFE.
AND HE LIVES A FEARLESS LIFE,
AND I CAME INTO THIS GAME AS
THIS FEARFUL, NEUROTIC ODDBALL,
AND WHEN I WALK OUT, I WANT TO
WALK OUT AS THE MAN MY FATHER
IS.
HE'S MY HERO.
AND I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
I MISSED YOU.
>> THANKS FOR COMING OUT, MAN.
>> Jeff: KEN, LET'S GET YOUR
BROTHER OUT HERE.
WILLIAM, COME ON OUT!
>> BROTHER!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: KEN, YOU CAN DESCRIBE
THAT FEELING OF SECURITY YOU GET
WHEN YOU PUT YOUR ARM AROUND
BLOOD, SOMEBODY YOU KNOW IN THIS
MOMENT WILL NOT BETRAY YOU?
>> I ALWAYS HAVE SINCE SECOND
GRADE.
I IT WAS WHAT WOULD YOU WANT TO
BE WHEN YOU GROW UP?
IT WAS HIM IN HIS FOOTBALL UNION
FORM.
MY ROLE MODEL, FATHER FIGURE,
AND NOW BEST FRIEND ALL ROLLED
INTO ONE.
HE'S MY ROCK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAST LOVE.
ZEKE, LET'S GET YOUR DAD OUT
HERE.
SAM, COME ON OUT!
>> YEAH!
>> PAPA!
>> HEY, BUDDY!
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I'M SO GLAD TO SEE YOU.
>> IT'S WONDERFUL!
>> I LOVE YOU, BUDDY.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> YOU'RE LOOK GREAT.
YOU'RE LOOKING STRONG.
>> Jeff: TELL ME ABOUT THIS
RELATIONSHIP, DAD?
>> WELL, THIS IS MY HERO.
THIS IS THE STRONG PERSON HERE.
THIS IS WHO I LOOK UP TO AND WHO
I MODEL MY BEHAVIOR AFTER.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ZEKE, THAT HAS GOT TO FEEL GREAT
TO HAVE YOUR DAD SAY THAT.
>> YEAH, I MEAN-- OH, GOD, I
SAID I WASN'T GOING TO CRY.
YOU KNOW, MY DAD AND I-- YOU
KNOW, WE'VE NOT ALWAYS BEEN
SUPER CLOSE.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN IN THE
PAST COUPLE OF YEARS THAT WE'VE
REALLY MADE AN EFFORT TO GET TO
KNOW ONE ANOTHER, AND THIS
ADVENTURE IS ABOUT, LIKE,
BECOMING THE PERSON I WANT TO BE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
AND IT'S ABOUT FORGING THIS
RELATIONSHIP THAT WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
>> Jeff: HUGS.
>> STRONG LIKE A BULL.
( APPLAUSE )
I'M WITH YOU.
>> Jeff: WILL, LET'S GET YOUR
MOM OUT HERE.
IRENE, COME ON OUT!
( APPLAUSE )
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU ARE SO AMAZING.
GOD IS GOOD.
I REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE,
AND I SAID I'D GO ANYWHERE FOR
YOUR SMILE, EVEN TIMBUKTU.
AND HERE I AM IN TIMBUKTU.
>> I LOVE YOU, MOM.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO, WE
KNOW THE STAKES.
THE STAKES ARE LOVE.
LET'S GET TO THE CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE ATTACHED TO A ROPE
THAT IS WOVEN THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES.
ON MY "GO," YOU ARE ANYTHING TO
RACE THROUGH THOSE OBSTACLES TO
THE END TOWARD LOVE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: FIRST PERSON TO
FINISH WILL TAKE THEIR LOVED ONE
BACK TO CAMP WITH THEM.
AND INSTEAD OF TREATING THEM TO
YOUR NORMAL DAY OF RICE AND
MAYBE A COUPLE OF FISH, WE'RE
GOING TO DO A GOOD-OLD AMERICAN
BARBECUE.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
WE'RE GOG DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
YOU'RE GOING TO WATCH.
HERE WE GO, FOR REWARD IN THE
FORM OF LOVE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> GO, ADAM.
>> GET THEM, BRET!
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO LAUNCH
YOURSELF OVER THESE OBSTACLES
WHILE THREADING THAT ROPE,
GIVING YOURSELF SLACK WHEN YOU
NEED IT, BUT MAKING SURE YOU
DON'T GET TANGLED UP IN THE
SLACK.
>> OW!
OW!
>> Jeff: ADAM ALL TIED UP.
SUNDAY HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE.
WILL HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE.
THERE'S KEN IN THE LEAD.
JAY RIGHT BEHIND.
>> YOU GOT IT!
YOU CAN DO IT!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: WOW, JAY LAUNCHES
HIMSELF.
HERE COMES ZEKE!
HE'S TRYING TO GET IN THIS NOW.
>> GO, ZEKE!
>> Jeff: HERE COMES HANNAH OUT
OF NOWHERE.
>> COME ON, HANNAH!
YOU CAN DO IT.
>> Jeff: KEN AND JAY HAVE
MOVED ON TO THE NEXT OBSTACLE.
RIGHT BEHIND HANNAH IS BRET AND
THEN ADAM.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE IN
THIS NOW.
ZEKE MAKES QUICK TIME OF THAT
SECOND OBSTACLE.
ZEKE NOW AT THE THIRD OBSTACLE.
DAVID MOVING ON TO THE NEXT
OBSTACLE.
IT IS STILL SUNDAY WHO CANNOT
FIGURE OUT THIS CHALLENGE, AND
WILL WHO IS STRUGGLING.
ADAM THROUGH WANT SECOND
OBSTACLE, MOVING ON TO THE
THIRD.
IT IS NOW KEN IN THE LEAD.
YOU'VE GOT TO DIG UNDER THAT
BEAM.
DAVID BACK IN IT.
>> GOOD JOB!
>> AAAHH!
>> Jeff: KEN, STUCK UNDERNEATH
THAT POST.
HE HAD A BIG LEAD.
>> PUSH WITH YOUR FEET!
>> Jeff: JAY TRYING TO CATCH
KEN.
ADAM IS STUCK.
HE'S GOT HALF HIS BODY THROUGH.
BUT JUST LIKE KEN, IT'S THAT
BOOTY.
>> YOU GOT THIS, ADAM.
>> Jeff: JAY IS THROUGH NOW.
JAY IN THE LEAD NOW.
>> I CAN'T MAKE IT.
AAAH!
>> Jeff: JAY IS AT THE FINAL
OBSTACLE.
>> COME ON, BROTHER, COME ON!
>> Jeff: ZEKE IS NOW GOING TO
GIVE JAY A RUN FOR HIS MONEY.
CAN HE CATCH HIM?
>> KEEP GOING!
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: KEN IS NOW IN IT.
>> GO, KEN.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES HANNAH!
>> AAAH!
>> Jeff: DAVID IS NOW AT THE
FINAL OBSTACLE.
ADAM IS LITERALLY STUCK AND
CANNOT MOVE.
HIS SHOT AT LOVE IS FALLING
AWAY.
>> NO!
>> Jeff: CAN ANYBODY CATCH JAY
FOR THE WIN?
>> I'M SORRY, EVAN!
>> I KNOW YOU'RE TRYING, ADAM.
>> Jeff: IT IS DAVID, ZEKE,
JAY, AND KEN.
WHOA WILL GET TO THE END FIRST?
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: ZEKE THROWING HIMSELF
THROUGH THE ROPES.
>> COME ON, BUDDY!
COME ON, ZEKE!
>>
>> Jeff: JAY WINS REWARD!
>> DAMN IT!
>> Jeff: IN THE FORM OF LOVE
IN A MASSIVE CHALLENGE.
>> THANK YOU!
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
( SPITTING )
>> Jeff: JAY, COME ON OVER.
>> NICE WORK JAY.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Jeff: MELANIE, COME ON OVER
AND JOIN JAY.
YOU ARE ANYTHING BACK TO CAMP, A
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE ALONG WAY
NICE BARBECUE.
PICK ANOTHER SURVIVOR AND THEIR
LOVED ONE TO JOIN YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OKAY, I RESPECT EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF YOU AS WARRIORS,
BUT I MADE A PROMISE IN THE
BEGINNING OF THE GAME TO TAKE
WILL.
SO I'LL TAKE WILL.
>> Jeff: WILL, COME ON OVER.
MOM, COME JOIN HIM.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> OH, I'M LIKING IT.
>> Jeff: JAY, PICK ONE MORE
SURVIVOR AND THEIR LOVED ONE.
>> FOR THE SAME REASON, THEY
MADE A PROMISE TO ME FIRST
BEFORE EVERYONE OF YOU.
AND I HAVE TO PICK SUNDAY.
>> WOW, YAY!
>> Jeff: SUNDAY, COME ON OVER.
JEFF, JOIN YOUR WOMAN.
>> I'M SORRY, GUYS.
I TRULY AM.
>> NO, HEY--
>> FORGET IT.
>> Jeff: THIS IS LOOKING LIKE
A NICE GATHERING FOR A BARBECUE,
I THINK TOW EVEN IT OUT, IT
WOULD BE NICE TO HAVE ONE MORE
SURVIVOR.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME,
DUDE.
>> Jeff: AND ONE MORE LOVED
ONE.
>> JAY, PLEASE.
YOU'VE GOT TO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: LOOK AT THAT.
JAY, EVERY SINGLE PERSON.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, I LOVE
YOU GUYS, MAN BUT THIS GUY
DIDN'T DO IT.
AND HE COULD HAVE DONE IT.
AND ME AND ADAM HAVE BEEN
BRAWLING THIS WHOLE DAMN TIME,
MAN.
YOU COME ON, MAN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU DIDN'T DO IT, DUDE.
>> Jeff: ADAM AND YOUR
BROTHER.
EVAN, COME ON OVER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
EVERYBODY'S GOING BACK TO CAMP
TOGETHER.
THE ONLY PEOPLE WHO WILL SHARE
IN THE REWARD PART OF THIS ARE
YOU GUYS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
LOVED ONES I'M SORRY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GO.
NO LAST HUGS.
>> I LOVE YOU, MAN.
>> I LOVE YOU, DAD, SEE YOU
SOON.
TELL EVERYONE BACK HOME I LOVE
THEM, TOO, AND I MISS EVERYONE.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> JAY, THANK YOU.
>> CHEERS.
>> ADAM, I RESPECT YOU FOR NOT
PLAYING YOUR ADVANTAGE.
THIS WHOLE TIME ADAM HAS HAD AN
ADVANTAGE TO TAKE AWAY A REWARD
BUT HE WALKED OUT AND THERE AND
SAID, "LISTEN, I'M NOT STEALING
A FAMILY VISIT BECAUSE THAT'S
NOT RIGHT."
FOR FIVE SECONDS WE SAW THE SOFT
SIDE OF ADAM.
SOMETIMES I HATE YOU, AND
SOMETIMES I LOVE YOU.
BUT AT THIS MOMENT, I RESPECT
YOU, AND YOU'RE A COOL DUDE.
>> I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT YOU
GUYS EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> WE'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
YOU, TOO.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> SHE STARTED HAVING SOME BAD
REACTIONS TO THE CHEMO PILL.
EVENTUALLY, THEY DECIDED THAT
THE SIDE EFFECTS SHE WAS HAVING
JUST WEREN'T WORTH THE POTENTIAL
GAIN THAT SHE MIGHT BE GETTING.
SO WE STOPPED THAT PILL AND A
COUPLE OF WEEKS LATER, THEY SAID
THAT THE INFUSION WASN'T REALLY
DOING ITS JOB.
>> SO WE HAD HER...
>> SHE'S REGAINING A LOT OF
STRENGTH.
>> DAMN IT.
>> NOTHING CAN REALLY LIGHTEN
THE LOAD BACK AT HOME.
IT'S A VERY SERIOUS SITUATION,
BUT ME AND MY PARENTS LOVE
"SURVIVOR" AS MUCH AS ADAM DOES,
AND HAVING HIM OUT HERE IS SUCH
A BOON FOR US.
IT DRIVES ME AND MY PARENTS
FORWARD.
ESPECIALLY MY MOM.
SHE'S GETTING SO MUCH STRENGTH
FROM KNOWING THAT HE'S OUT HERE
LIVING HIS DREAM.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING SHE
WANTED ME TO LET YOU KNOW IS
THAT SHE'S GETTING SO MUCH MORE
STRENGTH FROM YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> SHE FEELS YOU OUT HERE.
I'M HERE TO BRING JOY TO MY
FAMILY, TO MAKE THEM PROUD AND
TO GIVE THEM AS MUCH TO LOOK
FORWARD TO AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
AND THE BEST I DO IN THIS GAME,
THE LONGER I LAST, AND THE MORE
THAT I MAKE MY MOM HAPPY, I HAVE
TO STAY FOCUSED.
AND I HAVE TO USE THIS AS
INSPIRATION TO CONTINUE FIGHTING
OUT HERE.
>> SO WHAT'S UP, BROTHER?
>> WE JUST WANTED TO SAY THANK
YOU SO MUCH.
>> HEY, MAN!
DON'T WORRY, BRO.
>> LIKE, YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH-- HOW IMPORTANT THIS WAS.
IT REALLY, REALLY MEANT A LOT.
AND I'LL NEVER FORGET IT.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S EVER
GOING TO BE A WAY I CAN REPAY
YOU TOTALLY, BUT I'M GIVING YOU
THE ADVANTAGE, DUDE.
>> DAMN, BRO.
FOR REAL?
>> YEAH.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
NOTHING.
I JUST WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
>> YO, MAN, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> I'M PLAYING FOR SO MUCH MORE
THAN A MILLION DOLLARS AND THE
TITLE OF "SOLE SURVIVOR."
THE STAKES FOR ME ARE MAYBE
HIGHER THAN FOR ANYONE WHO'S
PLAYED THIS GAME.
>> SEEING MY MOM MADE ME REALIZE
THAT I NEED TO START PLAYING
THIS GAME BECAUSE DESPITE THE
MOVES I MADE, DESPITE THE THINGS
THAT I'VE DONE IN THIS GAME,
PEOPLE STILL DON'T GIVE ME THE
CREDIT I DESERVE.
AND THAT CAN RUIN MY SHOT AT
WINNING THIS GAME.
>> HE DOES.
HE ABSOLUTELY DOES.
AND, BY THE WAY, I KNOW, LIKE,
I'M A TARGET, AND EVERYTHING,
BUT RIGHT NOW, LIKE, USE ME FOR
THIS VOTE.
>> DUDE, I'M TIRED OF USING
PEOPLE.
I WANT TO WORK WITH PEOPLE.
>> OKAY, GOOD, YEAH, GREAT.
>> TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
IT'S TIME TO FLIP THE SCRIPT.
THE BIGGEST THREAT OUT HERE IS
ZEKE.
AND IF HE GETS TO THE END, HE
WILL BEAT ANY ONE OF US.
IT IS VERY RISKY, BUT I DIDN'T
COME HERE TO BE DRAGGED AS A
GOAT.
I CAME HERE TO PLAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, I LOVE IT.
BOOM.
WILL TELLING ME THAT HE WANTS TO
SWING OVER TO OUR SIDE, IT WAS
LIKE MUSIC TO MY EARS BECAUSE
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW, I'M AN
ENDANGERED SPECIES.
BUT I THINK WILL'S TELLING THE
TRUTH.
SO THERE'S A REALLY GOOD CHANCE
THAT ZEKE IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: JAY, YOU KNOW WHAT
HAS TO HAPPEN FIRST.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU WILL
EACH HAVE TWO HANDLES THAT YOU
WILL USE TO KEEP TENSION ON A
STEEL BAR.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU RELEASE THAT
TENSION, THE BAR WILL DROP, THE
TILE WILL BREAK, YOU'RE OUT OF
THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY.
GUARANTEED A ONE-IN-EIGHT SHOT
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE FIFTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
DRAW FOR SPOT, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR
HANDLES.
GET SOME TENSION ON THAT BAR.
LET'S GO.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO WIGGLE
ROOM IN THIS CHALLENGE.
THE SLIGHTEST SLIP, AND YOU'RE
DONE.
IT COULD HAPPEN QUICKLY.
YOU START TO FEEL YOUR HANDS
SHAKE A LITTLE.
DAVID IS THE FIRST TO DROP.
DAVID'S OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH, NO
SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE ARE DOWN TO EIGHT.
THAT'S HOW FAST IT CAN HAPPEN.
IT LOOKS SO EASY WATCHING IT.
HANNAH SLIPS, BUT A NICE SAVE.
HANNAH CROPS.
HANNAH'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WILL DROPS OUT OF NOWHERE.
YOU JUST LET IT UP FOR A MOMENT,
THAT TENSION RELEASE, AND THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENED TO BRET.
FOUR PEOPLE QUICKLY OUT OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
STRENGTH, CONCENTRATION, AND
TOUCH-- THAT IS THE KEY, THE
RIGHT FINESSE.
SUNDAY DROPS.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
JAY, KEN, ADAM, AND ZEKE.
ZEKE WITH A LITTLE WOBBLE, BUT A
NICE RECOVERY.
ZEKE STRUGGLING TO STAY IN IT.
ZEKE DROPS.
ZEKE IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY, AND WE ARE
DOWN TO THREE.
JAY, KEN, AND ADAM.
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
JAY WITH HIS FIRST MOVEMENT BUT
A NICE RECOVERY.
THIS IS ANOTHER CHALLENGE.
THERE IS NO FINISH LINE.
IT'S JUST OUTLASTING THE OTHERS.
DON'T LET THIS HOT SUN START TO
BAKE YOUR MIND.
YOU HAVE BEEN OUT HERE ONLY FOUR
MINUTES.
I KNOW IT SEEMS LIKE A LOT
LONGER.
ADAM STILL SOLID.
KEN, THE BIG SLIP.
JAY SLIPS AGAIN AND ANOTHER
RECOVERY.
KEN SLIPS A LITTLE MORE.
IF YOU LOSE YOUR CONCENTRATION,
YOU WILL DROP.
KEN DROPS AND WE'RE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS JAY AND ADAM IN A SHOWDOWN
OF MILLENNIALS FOR IMMUNITY ON
DAY 33.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR" RIGHT HERE.
WHO WANTS IT MORE?
JAY TRYING TO KEEP TENSION ON
HIS BAR.
ADAM SLIPS BUT A NICE SAVE.
BOTH GUYS FEELING IT.
JAY DROPS.
ADAM WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
WILL LIVE TO SAY DAY 34.
ADAM, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
>> I'M GOING TO SOAK THIS IN,
JEFF.
>> Jeff: SOAK IT IN.
>> OH, MAN.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS YOURS.
YOU WILL LIVE TO SEE DAY 34.
MASSIVE ACCOMPLISHMENT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 33
DAYS, YOUR QUEST TO WIN
"SURVIVOR" AND THE MILLION
DOLLARS THAT GOES WITH IT, WILL
COME TO A CRASHING HALT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> ZEKE LOST THE CHALLENGE, SO
THIS IS MY MOMENT.
THIS IS MY TIME TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
OF SO THAT PEOPLE REALIZE THAT,
HEY, THIS 18-YEAR-OLD KID FROM
JERSEY, HE'S HERE TO PLAY.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> CONGRATULATIONS, ADAM.
>> HELL OF A WIN THERE.
YOU EARNED IT.
>> THANK YOU.
THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WAS
AWESOME!
I'M MAKING MY "SURVIVOR" DREAMS
COME TRUE.
I ONLY HAVE ONE CHECK BOX LEFT,
AND THAT'S WINNING THIS GAME.
AND, YOU KNOW, WHAT?
IT MIGHT ACTUALLY HAPPEN BECAUSE
I'M SAFE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN
MY POCKET.
AND WILL WANTS TO MAKE A MOVE,
AND BLINDSIDE ZEKE.
>> WE HAVE A SOLID FIVE.
JUST VOTE ZEKE.
NO MATTER WHAT ANYONE SAYS, JUST
VOTE WEEK.
>> AND WE PRAY THAT WILL--
>> IT DOESN'T WORK WITHOUT WILL.
>> I NO LONGER HAVE A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, SO I'M INCREDIBLY
VULNERABLE.
AND IT'S LIKE WILL JUST GOT HIS
DRIVER'S LICENSE, AND WE'RE ALL
SITTING IN THE BACK TERRIFIED
BECAUSE THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
HE'S GOING TO TAKE US FOR A
DRIVE.
BUT I THINK IT'S GOING TO WORK.
>> SOMETHING'S UP.
I HAVE THE NUMBERS SO I SHOULD
BE FEELING GREAT.
HOWEVER, THERE'S SOMETHING AMISS
AT THE VINAKA CAMP.
IT DOES NOT MAKE SENSE THAT THE
FOUR SHOULD BE AS CALM AS THEY
ARE.
IF HE HAS AN IDOL, IT'S
MARGUERITE AS FOR ME TONIGHT.
I KNOW DAVID IS COMING FOR ME,
BUT H AND WE NEED TO GET RID OF
HIM.
DAVID HAS A NOSE FOR IDOLS, AND
WE'RE SO CLOSE TO THE END, I
CAN'T TAKE THE RISK.
SO WE NEED TO THROW SOMEBODY
ELSE UNDER THE BUS.
>> WHO?
>> KEN.
>> LET'S DO THAT, YEAH.
>> HOW YOU FEELING, BROTHER?
YOU GOT TWO SIDES TUGGING AT
YOU, MAN, AND IT'S TOUGH.
>> YEAH, WELL, I MEAN, I FEEL
LIKE THERE'S A GROUP THAT
RESPECTS ME AND A GROUP THAT
DOESN'T RESPECT ME.
AND THEY JUST TELL ME WHERE TO
VOTE.
THEY DON'T TAKE MY INPUT.
>> EXACTLY.
I DON'T JUST START TALKING
STRATEGY WITH ANYONE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> NOT UNTIL I HAVE AN IDEA OF
WHO THEY ARE.
>> I HAD A PRETTY GOOD FEELING
ABOUT WILL, BUT IT WASN'T 100%.
AND I DON'T JUST HAVE A
FIVE-MINUTE CONVERSATION, AND
THEN HOP IN BED WITH SOMEBODY.
I'VE GOT TO KNOW THE CORE OF A
PERSON, THEIR INTEGRITY, THEIR
VALUE BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO WIN
FOR MY LITTLE GIRL.
AND I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT I'M
SAFE.
IS YOUR MOAT TOIF WORK WITH A
BETTER GROUP OR IS YOUR MOTIVE
TO--
>> I AM WILLING TO VOTE ZEKE
BECAUSE HE CAN BEAT ANYBODY IN
THIS GAME.
>> OKAY.
>> I GIVE PEOPLE ONE CHANCE TO
BE HONEST WITH ME, AND IF THAT
BREAKS, THEN I-- IT'S DONE.
>> WORKING WITH KEN IS LIKE
GETTING YOUR FINGER AND TO NAILS
RIPPED OUT AT THE SAME TIME.
IT'S EXCRUCIATING, BUT I WANT TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE, SO I HAVE TO
DEAL WITH THAT ONE.
>> YOU'RE ONE OF THE FEW PEOPLE
I FOUND IN THIS GAME THEY FEEL
IS AS AUTHENTIC AS MYSELF.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I RESPECT THAT MORE THAN YOU CAN
POSSIBLY KNOW.
>> I'M DEFINITELY IN WITH YOU
GUYS, AND THEY'RE WRITING YOUR
NAME DOWN TONIGHT.
>> REALLY?
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY JUST TOLD
ME, THEY'RE VOTING FOR YOU.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
APPARENTLY, ZEKE AND HIS GROUP
ARE VOTING FOR ME.
I'M LIKE, "WHY?"
I'M NOT READY TO GO HOME.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> I'M THINKING WE'RE GOOD TO
GO, THEN KEN WALKS BACK UP INTO
CAMP, GETS JAY, AND SAYS, "WE
NEED TO TALK."
AND AT THIS MOMENT, I KNOW WE'RE
ABOUT TO HAVE A RUMBLE.
>> I WENT AND HAD A TALK WITH
WILL, AND HE SAID YOU GUYS WERE
SAYING MY NAME.
>> WILL SAID THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> IS THAT WHAT WAS SAID?
LOOK AT ME.
I MEAN--
>> ONE MINUTE THE SOLID FIVE IS
GOOD TO GO, LIKE, YO, WE'RE
DOING KEN.
THE NEXT MINUTE I HAVE KEN COME
UP TO ME AND SAY WILL TOLD ME
YOU ARE VOTING MY NAME.
>> I WAS TESTING YOU EARLIER TO
SEE WHERE YOU ARE AT--
>> I GET IT, YOU'RE BLOWING UP
MY GAME AT THIS POINT.
>> KEN COMES TO ME AND SAYS WILL
JUST TOLD ME YOU'RE THROWING MY
NAME OUT THERE.
>> THIS IS MY ISSUE, GUY, EVERY
TIME I MAKE A MOVE, OTHER PEOPLE
TAKE CREDIT FOR IT.
I WOULD RATHER BE PLAYING HARD
THAN BEING TAKEN TO THE END AS A
GOAT.
>> WE ALL KNEW SOMETHING WAS UP.
HE'S JUST A YOUNG KID TRYING TO
PROVE HIMSELF TO THE WHOLE
WORLD, BUT WE STILL NEED HIM.
>> I WANTED CREDIT FOR THIS ONE
BIG MOVE.
>> TELL ME THE NAME.
I'LL GO WITH YOU AND FIGURE OUT
HOW TO DO IT.
I HAVE BEEN WITH YOU SINCE DAY
ONE.
>> OKAY.
>> WE LOVE YOU, DUDE.
LET'S GET TO THE FIVE AND THEN
WE CAN BATTLE IT OUT.
OKAY?
>> I HAD TO TEST WILL TO SEE
WHERE HE WAS AT BECAUSE I DIDN'T
FEEL 110% COMFORTABLE WITH HIM.
>> OH, GEEZ.
>> HOW'D YOU TEST HIM?
>> BY SEEING WHERE HE STOOD,
ASKING WHERE HE WAS AT, AND
GOING TO THOSE GUYS AND SAY,
"WILL IS SAYING THIS."
>> WE HAVE THIS PLAN, AND KEN
TESTS WILL.
REVEALING WILL'S PLAN.
THAT'S NOT A TEST.
THAT'S A BETRAYAL!
>> KEN WALKED UP TO ME LITERALLY
TWO SECONDS AFTER--
>> HE SCREWED YOU.
>> IMAGINE PUTTING YOU IN THAT
SPOT?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
SCREW IT BECAUSE WE HAVE FIVE
HERE, AND I'M DONE WITH THIS.
I WANT HIM GONE RIGHT NOW
TONIGHT.
>> THIS GUY PREACHESESES ABOUT
HONOR AND INTEGRITY AND HOW HE'S
THIS GREAT AND NOBLE HUMAN BEING
WITH THIS ARROGANCE, EXTREME
EGO, AND HE HAS THE AUDACITY TO
PULL THIS CRAP ON ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY KEN CAN
THAT.
>> NOW WILL HAS NO INCENTIVE TO
VOTE WITH US.
>> KEN JUST SCREWED UP
EVERYTHING.
BECAUSE IF WE DON'T HAVE WILL,
WHOEVER THAT ALLIANCE LED BY
MOBSTER ZEKE WANTS TO VOTE OUT,
THEY'RE GOING HOME.
>> WHAT IF DAVID PLAYS THE IDOL
FOR KEN?
>> WHO DO WE VOTE?
>>
>> SHOULD WE VOTE FOR HANNAH OR
KEN?
>> I ALREADY KNOW IT'S ME, BUT
THAT'S OKAY.
>> NO, I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE
ME.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS I'M IN THE
MIDDLE.
NOW I HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION.
THE LOGICAL SIDE OF ME IS
TELLING ME THIS IS MY TIME TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
BUT I AM SO ANGRY WITH KEN.
I WOULD LOVE TO BLOW UP HIS
GAME.
EITHER WAY, I'M IN CONTROL, AND
THERE'S NOTHING ANYONE CAN DO
ABOUT IT OPINIO.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
MICHELLE, TAYLOR, CHRIS, AND
JESSICA, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, DAVID, COMING OFF OF ONE OF
THE CRAZIEST TRIBALS EVER ON
"SURVIVOR," HAS MUCH CHANGED?
OR ARE WE STILL LOCKED INTO THIS
TWO SIDES, ONLY ONE SIDE IS DOWN
A MEMBER.
MEMBER.
>>UN THERE'S NO REASON NOT TO
JUST PUT EVERYTHING OUT IN THE
OPEN BECAUSE BASICALLY, THERE
ARE TWO SIDES VYING FOR A SINGLE
SWING VOTE RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: SUNDAY, WHAT ARE THE
DIVISIONS?
WHO ARE THEY?
>> BRET, JAY, ZEKE, MYSELF, AND
KEN, DAVID, ADAM, AND HANNAH.
WILL IS APPROPRIATELY SITTING IN
BETWEEN.
>> Jeff: WILL, HOW DID YOU END
UP IN THE MIDDLE?
>> WELL, MY ORIGINAL PLAN WAS TO
FLIP ON ZEKE, BUT KEN TODAY
REVEALED TO THE ENTIRE TRIBE
THIS PLAN, SO EVERYBODY KNOWS
BASICALLY WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> Jeff: SO, SUNDAY, THE
YOUNGEST KID OUT HERE IS MAKING
THE BIGGEST DECISION OF THE
NIGHT, AND IT IS A MASSIVE SWING
VOTE.
>> YOU KNOW, WILL CAME TO PLAY
HARD.
AND I FEEL LIKE HE DOESN'T WANT
TO SIT ON THE SIDELINES AND FEEL
LIKE ALL THE BIG KIDS DO ALL THE
WORK.
I THINK HE WAS SUEDE A LITTLE
BIT TODAY BUT WE'RE HOPING HE
STICKS WITH US.
>> HOLD ON HERE.
I WASN'T SUEDE AT ALL TODAY.
I WAS THE ONE WHO CAME TO THEM
WITH THE DECISION DISIGZ TO TRY
TO FLIP.
AND THAT'S PART OF THE ISSUE.
EVERYBODY TREATS ME LIKE THE
18-YEAR-OLD HOLLY KID.
I DON'T WANT TO BE TREATED LIKE
THAT.
I WANT TO BE TREATED LIKE AN
ADULT BECAUSE I AM HERE TO WIN
AND PLAY JUST AS HARD AS THE
REST OF YOU.
>> Jeff: IT IS INSULTING A
LITTLE?
>> IT IS INSULTING.
THIS IS INSANE THIS CRAZY SWING
VOTE WITH ME IN THE MIDDLE IS
WHAT IT TAKES FOR PEOPLE TO
REALIZE I AM A SERIOUS
CONTENDER.
>> Jeff: SO, ZEKE, EVERYBODY
AGREES THEY NEED WILL'S VOTE.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PITCH?
>> WELL, WILL, I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO PLAY WITH YOU IN THIS
GAME.
WE HAVE ALIGNED MANY TIMES, AND
WHEN TAYLOR AND JAY WERE UNDER
HEAT, YOU WEREN'T UNDER HEAT
BECAUSE I WAS PROTECTING YOU.
>> BUT EVEN THE WAY HE TALKS
ABOUT IT IT'S ALL ABOUT, "I'VE
BEEN PROTECTING YOU.
I DID THIS FOR YOU."
>> NO, I DON'T, I WAS SAYING
THAT IN THE LEAST.
HE SAVED MY ASS AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND IF I AM HERE
AT THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL, I
WILL AGAIN OWE MY LIFE TO WELL.
>> Jeff: JAY, WHY SHOULD HE
COME TO THIS SIDE?
>> HONESTLY, JEFF, I HAVE NEVER
LOOKED DOWN ON WILL.
I HAVE ALWAYS TALKED TO WILL AS
EQUAL TO ME AND I HAVE NEVER
ONCE TRIED TO TAKE CREDIT FOR
ANYTHING WE'VE DONE TOGETHER.
WE MADE MOVES TOGETHER.
WE TOOK UP ON THE MICHAELA
TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: DAVID, THE TOPIC OF
BIG MOVES IS VITAL TO THE GAME.
>> WILL FEELS LIKE HE REALLY HAS
TO HAVE SOMETHING ON HIS RESUME
TO SHOW AT FINAL TRIBAL SHOULD
HE GET THERE, AND RIGHT NOW, JAY
IS TRYING TO MAKE WILL FEEL LIKE
HE ALREADY HAS THAT.
BUT I'LL SAY IF HE VOTES WITH
US, HIS NAME WILL BE ON THIS
VOTE IN BIG, BOLD LETTERS AND
THAT'S SOMETHING TO PUT ON YOUR
RESUME.
>> Jeff: BRET, DAVID CLEARLY
JUST MADE A CASE TO WILL ABOUT
GOING WITH THOSE FOUR.
>> JEFF, I'LL TELL WILL RIGHT
NOW, THEY'LL BUILD YOU UP AND
VOTE YOU OUT IN A HEARTBEAT.
THEY'VE DONE IT SEVERAL TIMES.
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T BUY IT.
>> Jeff: ADAM, YOU'RE SHAKING
YOUR HEAD.
>> YEAH, OUR SIDE HAS AN EQUAL
PARTNERSHIP IN TERMS OF DECISION
MAKING AND THE MOVES THAT ARE
MADE.
AND WILL IS ALREADY A PART OF
THAT.
>> Jeff: WILL, DO YOU BUY THAT
YOU COULD HAVE FIVE PEOPLE, AND
EVERYONE HAS AN EQUAL SAY?
>> I DON'T BUY IT.
WHEN YOU HAVE FIVE PEOPLE,
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO BE FIGHTING
TO GET THEIR OWN VOICE HEARD,
AND FIVE PEOPLE CAN'T TAKE
CREDIT FOR ONE MOVE.
>> Jeff: HANNAH, WHAT'S THE
MISTAKE WILL, WILL MAKE IF HE
GOES WITH THIS FOUR?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK THERE'S
BEEN A LOT OF FLUFFING WILL UP
ON THAT SIDE TELLING HIM THAT
THEY'LL WORK WITH HIM.
AND THAT HE GETS CREDIT FOR ALL
THE MOVES.
>>UN WHAT, WILL?
OOIK NOT HERE TO FLUFF YOU AWP
ALL I WANT TO TELL YOU, DUDE,
HONESTLY, IS JUST GO WITH YOUR
GUT, BRO, SIMPLE AS THAT, AND IF
THAT'S WHAT YOU FEEL IS RIGHT,
DO THAT.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
>> WILL, YOU'RE NODDING YOUR
HEAD.
>> WELL, IF THERE IS ONE PERSON
HERE WHO HAS SHOWED ME RESPECT
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE GAME, THAT
WOULD BE JAY, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WELL, I COULD SIT
HERE ALL NIGHT WITH YOU GUYS,
BUT IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KEN, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULDN'T TIME TO DO SO.
>> SORRY, JEFF, IT WAS THE ONLY
PLACE I COULD KEEP IT TONIGHT.
>> WHAT?
>> I DIDN'T HAVE A BAG WITH ME.
>> WHAT!
WHOA!
>> Jeff: OH, THIS WILL BE FUN.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO TOUCH IT,
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
I'M PLAYING THIS FOR HANNAH.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTE CAST FOR HANNAH WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, HANNAH.
DOES NOT COUNT.
HANNAH.
ZEKE.
ONE VOTE ZEKE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ZEKE.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ZEKE.
THAT'S THREE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> IT'S BEEN AN HONOR TO PLAY
WITH YOU ALL.
KEEP FIGHTING.
>> THANK YOU, ZEKE.
>> THANKS, ZEKE.
>> SEE YOU, ZEKE.
>> Jeff: SWREERK THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, HERE'S THE THING ABOUT BIG
MOVES-- THEY'RE GREAT, UNTIL
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT GETS
PUNCHED.
WITH ONLY EIGHT PEOPLE LEFT,
THERE ARE A LOT OF KNOCKOUTS
STILL TO COME.
EVERYBODY NEEDS TO HAVE THEIR
GLOVES UP.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": WILL TRIES TO TAKE
CHARGE.
>> NOW, I'M THE ONE CALLING THE
SHOTS.
>> THE MOST INSECURE I'VE EVER
FELT IS RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: BUT ADAM HAS OTHER
IDEAS.
>> I KNOW.
>> I DO NOT WANT WILL
CONTROLLING MY FATE IN THIS
GAME.
>> IT'S POSSIBLE I WENT AFTER
DAVID AND HIS SIDE TOO EARLY.
I THINK MAYBE I WAS EXCITED TO
PLAY A LITTLE HARD.
BUT I DIDN'T COME HERE TO RIDE
COATTAILS.
I CAME HERE TO THROW SOME
PUNCHES AND I WASN'T GOING TO GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT BECAUSE I
THINK WHEN YOU PLAY AT THIS HIGH
LEVEL WITH THIS CALIBER OF
PLAYERS IT JUST MAKES YOU WANT
TO PLAY IT BETTER AND MAYBE ONE
DAY I WILL.