...After a surprise elimination.
I'm angry here.
There, I will have to play
from the bottom of the ladder.
In the Gen X tribe,
David found an idol...
...and thought
maybe he should use it.
Clearly, Ken, Cece and I
are at the bottom of the ladder.
But Jessica wanted to turn
against the majority alliance.
Paul is not with us.
He's with the guys.
Eliminating Paul
would be best for our tribe.
At the council,
sunday and lucy
suivirent le plan de jessica
and eliminated Paul...
Paul, the tribe has spoken.
...taking Bret and Chris
by surprise.
There are 17 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I would like to speak.
I'm not talking to you tonight.
We'll see tomorrow morning.
Upon returning from the council,
I was downright pissed.
It was quite a surprise.
I was close to
throwing the rice in the ocean
and create
my own one person tribe.
What the hell happened?
He held the reins.
No one is speaking!
No more whispers! Come on, come on!
It has nothing to do with you two.
We want to know what's going on.
This is the problem
we were facing.
Straight in the eye, Paul said to me:
"If the guys
want an alliance of guys,
Good luck to you."
- He didn't promise me anything.
- Never anything like this.
Today,
some are very unhappy.
Especially Bret and Chris.
I don't know if they believe me.
For now,
there is too much anger.
It's painful, believe me,
it was not an easy decision
for anyone.
We would have said so.
I am very nervous.
I hope...
...that it wasn't
a bad idea.
Did we make a mistake?
Let's forget the past.
Moving forward.
This morning, I felt bad,
because Bret and Chris feel betrayed.
It's almost
like cheating on someone
and
that the relationship now needs to be repaired.
- We can patch things up, do you think?
- Yeah, you just have to...
- Give them time?
- Yeah.
The guys are furious
because they really trusted Jessica.
And honestly,
I don't have 100% confidence in her.
She the first
implanted in my head
the idea of ​​voting for Paul.
She didn't do it by accident.
It's like she's trying
to take control.
I feel like I
have to fix it.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
Sorry, you know, it's a game.
- No need to apologize.
- I know your worth.
But I can also tell you
that the power-hungry
had to pull out a power-hungry.
But now you know
who is trying to take over.
Lucy arrives and says:
"Jessica is
pulling the strings."
Jess plays it hard,
and I applaud him for it.
But now
you've played your cards.
I want you to know
that Ken and Dave
trust me completely.
So if you have plans...
- Can you make them?
- I can make them, yes.
I don't trust Jess.
Yes, but know that I can...
- Understood.
- You understand?
Lucy thinks she has Dave and Ken
in her pocket
and that maybe we could take
action against Jess.
I don't like Jess.
I can not stand her.
So if I can help
make her squirt, I will.
Next tip...
She needs to get out.
I'm losing my mind, I'm so hungry.
Go hunt that pig,
whatever it is, if necessary.
Do you really think
there's a pig on this island?
We saw pig tracks
on the beach.
The definition of a Gen Y would be:
a young man full of dreams,
ready to conquer the world.
Let's kill a pig!
And I like it,
because I'm a dreamer.
Gen X is like:
"Okay, high school, college,
subway, job,
build yourself a life!"
I don't want that.
Wait, did you hear?
- It's a goat.
- Where is she?
- The!
She's up there!
She is on the way.
Oh my God!
- Let's go to the hill side.
- Let's go catch it!
- Speak softly!
- I say!
There, up there!
Oh my God!
They don't really hunt, do they?
The search for the idol
has really slowed down on this camp.
But I feel like
she could still be there.
So I think I have
to dedicate myself to his research.
Because after the elimination of Mari,
I clearly have my
head on the block.
What if I could
get my hands on an idol,
I could save myself.
Oh my...
Oh my...!
Oh my God!
I knew it!
By the way, I knew it!
Oh my God!
I can't open it!
Too excited!
"Mother Nature hides your security.
Your tribe's crest
marks power.
The coveted prize is shelled."
Lord!
She couldn't be here?
I still have to search?
It's incredible.
For a super-hyper
Survivor fan like me,
it's absolutely a dream.
I found the clue.
All that remains is to decipher it.
Always nothing?
- Nope.
- No goat.
I don't know how long
I can lose looking for it.
So I have to go back to camp
and search another time.
Over here, everyone!
Gen Y, discover
the new Gen X tribe.
Paul was eliminated
at the last tip.
- Wow, I didn't see that coming!
- Neither do I.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today
you will collect a ring.
Then you'll come back
to your flag
while the other tribe
will try to stop you
in every possible way.
The first
to have a hand on the flag
and another on the ring
scores a point for his team.
The first to three points
win the reward.
- Want to know what's at stake?
- Yes!
I think you'll like it.
sausages,
- vegetables, spices.
- Spices!
A grill!
- Laugh.
- Any!
Is it worth it?
Okay, Gen Y,
you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Who will it be?
It will be Michelle.
The others, one minute
to get organized and we'll start.
Well, on and go.
Two men
against two men.
It will be Chris and David
against Jay and Adam.
From the outset,
an interesting confrontation.
Alright, round one.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
There are big waves.
You'll have to swim to the ring.
Jay goes straight for Chris.
He blocks it.
Chris tries to push him away
like an insect.
That leaves Adam
free to go to the ring.
Excellent Gen Y strategy.
Jay sacrifices his body.
Adam is in trouble now.
He sees a clumsy attacking him.
And very easily,
Adam gives up the ring.
There is no photo.
Chris holds Jay and Adam,
allowing David to return.
Come on, Dave!
Grab his fingers, Adam!
Chris is unstoppable.
He gives David
all the time he needs.
The first point goes to Gen X!
The women.
Sunday and Cece
against Figgy and Michaela.
On and go.
Survivors, ready?
Michaela and Figgy leave quickly.
Cece is going to stay back
and play defense.
Sunday also remains behind.
They let Gen Y
do the work and bring the ring back.
- Advance
- Sunday, advance!
This is where the game gets interesting.
Michaela throws to Figgy.
It's Figgy versus Cece.
Is Cece strong enough
to come back to her flag?
Now
the battle can begin.
Michaela shoots and gets closer.
Michaela and Figgy
approach the flag.
Cece and Sunday
try to hold them back, but to no avail.
Michaela has her sights set!
Can she get there?
Gen Y score, draw!
Next round:
Bret and Ken for Gen X,
an excited Taylor and Will
for Gen Y.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
Everyone rushes towards the ring.
No one stays behind.
Taylor intercepts Ken.
He knocks him out,
giving Will an opening.
Taylor, very aggressive, holds Bret back.
Now Ken is going after Will.
Ken snatched the ring from Will!
Taylor is now
restrained by Bret.
Taylor can't
get away from Bret,
Will rattrapper Ken.
Come on, Ken!
Taylor breaks free from Bret,
he's on it.
There, there is a battle!
Ken does the forcing.
Bret helps him shoot.
The Gen X are very close.
Come on, Bret!
Can they get there?
Taylor counterattacks.
Will shoots as well.
Ken scores for Gen X!
The Gen X take the lead.
Next round:
it will be Jessica and Lucy
against Michaela and Hannah.
Gen X leads 2-1.
We go to three points.
They can win now.
On and go.
Survivors, ready?
Jessica swims towards the ring.
Hannah attacks Lucy
and tries to restrain her.
Lucy escapes.
Jessica is all alone.
Lucy attempts to restrain
Michaela and Hannah.
Michaela takes her top off
so she can attack Jessica.
Michaela is now
facing Jessica.
She tries to grab the ring.
Gen Y must score,
they are trailing 2 - 1.
Huge in-game reward.
Lucy tries to pull them closer.
This way! This way!
Lucy tries to get rid of Hannah.
She has the flag in sight.
Michaela pulls her back
now.
Michaela pulls him away from the flag.
Michaela is on!
Michaela gives it her all!
All!
She can equalize for Gen Y!
It's epic!
Michaela succeeds!
Gen Y equalize! 2 - 2!
Huge effort from Michaela,
who lost her top in the operation
- without it stopping him.
- Oh my God!
That's what it takes
to win in Survivor!
Cheer!
You literally gave it your all!
We go to the test of strength.
It's quits or double.
It's David and Chris
versus Jay and Zeke.
Come on, Hulk!
Considerable pressure
is exerted on Jay and Zeke.
Let's go. For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Zeke, the smallest of the four,
attacks Chris,
just trying to annoy him,
to harass him.
And it works!
Jay has the ring.
Jay has an opening!
Zeke is doing a great job
with Chris!
Now
Chris takes the ring from Jay.
Come on, Jay!
We are close!
A huge battle!
Zeke makes things very difficult.
A big wave is coming!
She gets everyone on board.
Gen Y are closer than ever.
Zeke holds Chris back.
Chris escapes.
He has the ring.
Jay holds it again.
Chris pulls it now.
Chris approaches.
A big turnaround,
and another wave!
Who brings them together!
That's it!
Gen X earn the reward!
It was a colossal ordeal!
Gen X come out victorious.
A great reward,
who will be waiting for you at the camp.
- Enjoy it, it's deserved.
- Thank you, Jeff!
- Cheer.
- Thanks. Good luck.
Gen Y, I have nothing for you.
Take your things and leave.
Nice job, friends.
Michaela ripped it all up.
- There wasn't much to do.
- The girls tore everything up.
The last group, you, you,
you were the last, I believe,
it was so tight!
The reward event
was a nightmare from the start.
Their guys are huge.
Chris must be
three times my height.
- He lifted me up and threw me!
- Yeah, boom! With one hand!
We got demolished.
Michaela, on the other hand,
is like an Amazon.
Champion!
It was impressive!
Michaela, the champion!
I'm one of those who...
I like to win, you know?
And when stuff happens,
like my bathing suit
getting ripped off,
we can either lose,
or get the shirt ripped off
and win.
So I thought to myself...
"They're going to see boobs
today!"
- We lacked strategy.
- It's true.
- We learned our lesson.
- Better organized, we could have won.
I would have liked
to do a better performance.
But it was not
a test for me.
I'm not super comfortable
with physical clashes.
I'm going to wash these shoes.
I feel like I need
this idol more than ever.
But I have little time left,
'cause I have to make sure I find her
before we go back to the board
or get mixed up.
"The crest of your tribe
marks power."
This is the emblem of the tribe.
"The coveted prize is shelled."
"Encrusted". Shellfish.
The clue says to seek
the emblem of the tribe
somewhere in the indicated area
and look for a seashell.
If you open the seashell,
you will find the immunity idol.
No.
Back to the beach.
I search everywhere
and I don't see it.
He is not there.
So I walk along the beach,
hoping to spot something,
find something.
That's the emblem of the tribe!
That's what I wanted!
Come on, open up!
I have to go back to camp!
I no longer need you.
You can leave.
Yeah, that'll do.
Hey, Adam!
Oh, don't!
How
's your idol search going?
I'm working on it!
Good luck, friend!
I hope she didn't corner me.
Has she seen me with this?
Oh my God!
I'll put it
on, just for fun!
I found an immunity idol!
It's beyond my wildest dreams.
I finally started looking for
it today, and I found it!
Mom, this is for you.
I love you so.
The decision to come here
was very hard to make.
My mother was diagnosed,
seven months ago,
stage 4 lung cancer.
This disease wreaks such havoc!
It was such a nightmare!
It's the worst thing imaginable.
As my biggest dream
comes true
as
my worst nightmare arrives,
it's not... It seems unreal.
My mom is a huge super-fan.
She is my ultimate reason for being here.
I want to give my mother
something to look forward to.
That she can see me finding this,
that's why I came.
To bring
some joy back to my family.
Everyone kept their sausages.
Sausages for breakfast!
We
have peppers, onions left...
I had not been so happy here.
Anyone need some water?
It's good for me.
Have you spoken to anyone about...?
In case we lose?
I won't give you
a name right away.
- I don't want... to talk.
- Yes yes.
I took a walk with Lucy
today,
to try to get an idea
of ​​what she has in mind.
'Cause even though I survived
the last tip,
I'm afraid that Ken and I
remain at the bottom of the ladder.
So the smartest
thing for me to do, for now,
it is to go
in the direction of the majority.
You two have nothing to fear.
OK.
What do you have in mind?
Where Jessica came from.
You two don't have
to be paranoid.
Then I don't want to see you
talking to anyone else.
Otherwise, it will upset me.
- OK.
- That's all.
It suits you?
Everyone is in on it.
- Are you going to tell him?
- Nope.
Because if you do,
no one will trust you.
I say.
- OK?
- Thanks.
Lucy approached me and Dave
"We're going to eliminate Jess."
What really pissed me off,
is that Lucy
had a kind of list of rules
on what we had the right
to do or not.
"Don't talk to that person!"
"Don't sneak over there!"
"Don't go alone!"
And I say to myself:
"We went
from one dictator to another."
And it doesn't work for me.
Over here, everyone!
What is that?
Let's come to the
immunity test of the day.
First of all, Zeke,
I take back the idol.
See you soon!
"See you soon",
they say, Gen X!
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will go through a series of obstacles
until you reach a chair.
Your tribe
will then raise the chair,
allowing you to collect
ten numbered bags.
Then the next one goes.
Once the 30 bags have been collected,
you will form a sentence
with the letters they contain.
The first tribe to achieve this
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers will go to the council,
where someone will be eliminated from the game.
Gen Y, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Adam, on the bench. The others,
one minute to get organized
and we'll start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
First, the obstacles.
Chris makes
it look very easy.
Chris quickly crosses the obstacle.
Chris is in the chair.
Start shooting, Gen X!
The one, the one!
If you can lift Chris,
you can lift everyone!
Figgy is in the chair,
she goes to get the one.
You have to take them in order,
from 1 to 10, then come back.
Leftmost!
Chris must be
three times the weight of Figgy.
I'm almost there, shoot!
- At the top!
- To the left!
I got it!
Chris has two.
Figgy has two.
Perfect equality.
Chris has three.
Top, all right!
Gen X leads,
they have number four.
Figgy blocks on the three.
Chris has number five.
Gen Y are losing ground.
Chris rushes, he is at six.
More than one for Chris.
Come down! Chris has all ten!
You have to bring them to the table
before you come back.
Top right!
Go away!
Figgy has all ten!
This is Ken, for Gen X.
Figgy leaves.
Ken is in the chair.
Ken is aiming for the numbers 11 to 20.
This is Michelle.
Ken ale 14.
Michelle tries to catch up to him.
Ken ale 15.
Gen Y are fighting
to stay in the game.
Ken struggles
to catch number 20.
The tribe gives everything it has.
He has it!
So far, the Gen X strategy
is working well.
Michelle is 18.
Meet David for Gen X
and Michelle ale 20.
Gen Y
are in on the action again.
Like in football, in high school!
David is in the chair.
We back to the end!
This is Michaela.
She was unstoppable
in the reward test.
David but 24.
Michaela must take
numbers 21 through 30, in order.
Can she catch David?
David but 26.
27, and the 28, right there!
David is at 28.
Michaela quickly arrives at 24.
David but 29.
More than a room for David.
- And he has it! David comes back down.
- To your left!
You go-y, Dave, you go-y!
Michaela is at 29.
And David... They have all 30!
Forward, Gen X!
Michaela at 30.
Take it down!
Another hotly contested event!
Now you have to
reconstruct a sentence.
You have 30 letters.
You have to guess the sentence
to continue surviving
in this game.
This is where communication
is crucial.
Gen Ys count the letters.
Will it work?
No need to place the letters
if you know it won't work.
Gen Xers
have a different approach.
"I want to see him!"
Come on guys!
Shut up, shut up!
Gen Y think.
Are discussing.
It's the hare and the tortoise.
David has another idea.
Is it the right one?
There's only one "G"?
So many words can be written
with these letters!
What could it be?
Gen Ys spent a lot
of time talking and thinking.
Gen X are experimenting.
Two different approaches.
Which will turn out
fruitful?
- That's it! That's it!
- Gen X have another idea!
Gen Ys don't panic.
They don't even seem to realize
they're up against another tribe.
They do their thing
Gen Y way.
There is no "D".
45 Minutes
It's been going on for quite a while.
It's a real study in contrasts.
- There is only one "R".
- The Gen X proceed by attempts.
Gen Ys work from the mind,
but few letters move.
Girls! Girls!
And if ...
That's it, Dave, that's it!
It's something"...
"Someone loses"...
Gen Y are moving fast now.
Suddenly,
the two tribes are launched.
You can feel the energy rising.
Don't stop, Dave!
Gen Y think they have it,
all of a sudden.
Say it!
"Someone will lose their flame tonight."
It's just!
Gen Ys win immunity!
None of them
will lose their flame tonight.
Gen Y!
You wanted her back.
You have it.
Take your things,
return to camp.
Enjoy your free evening.
Okay, Gen X.
Advice.
Someone will be
the 4th person eliminated from this game.
Take your things, return to camp.
See you tonight at the council.
Alright, that sucks.
We have made so much effort!
It was hard, the puzzle was hard.
What are we going to do?
I will light the fire.
Losing immunity today
was tough, because on the board,
I'm not sure
what will happen.
Bret and I were
taken by surprise the day before yesterday,
so I don't feel
safe at all.
But we have a plan:
taking Jess out by surprise.
I'm counting on Lucy
to make it happen.
This puzzle was killing us.
Yeah.
But we did our best.
But you think
Dave is with us?
Yes, I recruited them.
- You are sure of it?
- Yes it is certain.
It's Ken, Dave,
Bret, you and me.
I'm like a "mother tigress",
because the scenario that I love
is me having control.
Often I displease
my husband and my children,
because I make all the decisions.
But somebody's got to do it,
so if it works at home,
it should work here.
What do you have in mind?
It's very, very simple.
This morning when you and I
were scolded and said
not to speak to anyone,
for me, that was settled.
It puts us, you, me and Cece back
at the bottom of the ladder.
What must happen, in my opinion,
is that you, me,
Cece and Jess,
It's only been four.
And Jess recruits Sunday.
Oh my God!
In real life,
Lucy must be used to deciding.
But here,
you have to be careful
what you say, and how.
Because you can really upset people.
And that's exactly
what happened, because there,
Ken wants to take her out.
And frankly,
that sounds like a great idea to me.
We vote for Lucy, okay?
She must not have wind
of our discussion.
On se verra là-bas, more...
Lucy, Lucy, Lucy!
Honey...
Lucy wants you out.
She and Chris and Bret
don't trust you.
No way.
Our only chance to stay,
it's for Lucy to leave.
What have you heard all day?
- Your name. On the block.
- Yes, who said my name?
Ever since Paul left,
Lucy has been putting everything on you.
She came to tell
David and me
not to trust you.
Your name will come out.
My name?
You need to talk to Sunday.
Otherwise, you're screwed.
I am dumbfounded.
know me this
that it's me they want out,
because I was the mastermind
behind Paul's elimination.
Which surprises me greatly.
Because I thought
we had the idea together.
So that seems a bit suspicious to me.
I think we all vote for Cece.
Yes, that's what I had imagined.
But Ken says
that you tell everyone
to vote for me
and he's trying to convince me
to vote for you.
There, things degenerate
at high speed.
Ken told Jess!
Frankly, I'm shocked.
It was the dumbest
stunt in the world.
It's stupid.
Jessica repeated everything to Lucy.
Why?
That does not make any sense.
I'm shocked.
I thought my connection with Jess
was genuine.
And I just found out
she betrayed me,
taking everything i told her
to serve it to Lucy
on a silver platter.
So who are you voting for?
I do not know.
I don't like being told what to do,
who I can talk to.
"Don't stray from the camp!"
- "Don't go and argue." Basically...
- So that you don't reveal everything.
Basically, you gave me rules,
which I, as an adult, shouldn't do.
Ken turns out to be a traitor.
My way of approaching him offended him.
I probably
could have been nicer,
but Ken is emotional as a girl.
Go on! Be serious!
We're just gonna fire Jessica.
Why worry now
about who we eliminate?
The important thing is:
"At least you stay in the game.", right?
- Dave!
- What do we do? What are you voting for?
What the hell is going on?
Do we do it or what?
I thought it was Jessica.
At this point it's such a mess
that the safest thing
might be to write "Jessica".
But if I do that,
I go back to the bottom of the ladder.
- You're not voting for me, are you?
- But no.
My other option
is that i could play my idol
for jessica
and save her.
But I lied to Lucy to her face.
And I think she knows it.
I'm sure.
Pack all your bags
because we have a cafeteria here.
I just want to have the idol,
just for safety.
I don't intend to play it,
most...
I have a lot to consider.
Let's talk about the last tip.
David. Did he unite this tribe
or did he rather express:
"The game is on."?
I don't think he united us.
It was the right move to play,
yes, the game is on.
Chris, how did you react
back to camp after the vote?
Bret and I
were angry with our allies.
We were totally
taken by surprise.
This tribe
is in complete chaos.
We gotta raise the bar
or we'll be in big trouble.
If Chris and Bret really believe
they were taken by surprise,
What does that mean
for the remaining five of the six?
I think we've all thought
why things
happened this way.
But unfortunately,
we can still see the ramifications,
and whether it happens or not
let the five re-form,
I hope that is the case.
Lucy, it seems
that the last advice
was a bomb that exploded,
and now
the game is on.
Yes. Everyone
starts to feel threatened.
We hear
a lot of different things,
we mention your name,
we mention another name...
Hence the chaos,
because no one knows
who will vote for whom.
What do you think?
Do you have an idea tonight?
I thought I was safe
until Jessica told me
Ken wanted me out.
And I don't know if he could muster
enough people for that.
Ken, you nod.
Yes, it refers to a discussion
we had today.
There are different ways
to ask for something.
"Do you mind...?"
"Are you okay with...?"
And then there's coming up and saying:
"You will do this."
Yes, but that's my way of speaking.
I may be too direct,
but in general, with men,
I guess
they support straight talk.
And many tell me
they appreciate it.
Thinking about it, instead,
"Lucy tell me
something that will help me
to move on to the next..."
Do you realize that you are reoffending?
No, no, I...
"Let's hurry,
here is your decision,
no explanation."
That was the whole idea,
what I was trying to do.
Ken, the result,
it's that Lucy now thinks
you want her out
and that you have
at least discussed it with Jessica.
What confidence do you have
in the fact that this vote
will go as you wish?
I hesitated all day.
This is what happens
when someone
I was loyal to
turns out not to be so loyal.
Jessica, you reacted strongly.
Was he talking about you?
Yes. I know he's talking about me.
But am I supposed to believe
what you told me,
100 %,
about what you told me others
said about me today?
That's the thing,
you never know who's telling the truth.
This is living advice!
"Alive" in the sense of
"not set in stone".
Exactly. We leave the beach
with an idea of ​​what we're going to do,
then she changes to the council.
Anything can happen to the board.
It's completely unpredictable.
Jessica,
watch your body language!
Have you
questioned your vote tonight?
Chris, how about you?
I do not
question my vote.
I may still
take a hit,
but no
doubts, so...
The only question to ask
is who is the pigeon at the table.
Everyone went all-in,
who's the idiot who shouldn't have?
This is the real question.
The time seems right
to find out.
It's time to vote.
Sunday, over to you.
This is for you, Paulie.
Torpedoes launched!
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Oh, damn it!
Can I say a few words,
real quick?
Yes, stand there.
Good. I want
you all to know:
it was a pleasure to meet you,
I enjoy your company.
And now for the part
that might upset some people.
I play this for Jessica.
Good.
This is an immunity idol.
Votes against Jessica
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Jessica.
Does not count.
What what.
A Cece vote.
Lucy.
A Cece vote,
one vote Lucy, one vote left.
Fourth person eliminated
from Survivor Gen Y vs Gen X...
Bring me your torch.
Wow.
Lucy, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
We were talking about living advice...
It doesn't get more alive than that!
Take your torches,
return to camp.
Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The Gen X idol is brought back into play.
A quest for the idol!
And a surprise mix...
Throw away your bandanas!
...threatens to separate two lovers.
I really love Taylor.
My biggest fear
is that we will be separated.
You have no idea
what will happen.
I was almost in control
and it almost worked.
I didn't expect
Dave to play the idol,
I was rather shocked.
I went all out,
I probably should have
gone more slowly.
This is one of the lessons
I learned.
But unfortunately,
a little too late.