Previously on Survivor.
At the old Gen X tribe, it was Chris, Brett and Sunday.
I don't trust Jessica as far as I can throw.
Against David, Ken and Jessica.
Sunday, Chris and Brett don't trust you.
But after the merge, the Gen Xers put their differences aside.
What needs to be broken up is the upper echelon of the Millennials.
Forming a majority alliance with Hannah, Zeke and Adam.
Michelle is the person to go after.
But Adam and Taylor began sharing secrets.
I cannot tell anyone about this.
I can steal someone's reward.
And the alliance started to question Adam's loyalty.
You don't think Adam would flip on us, do you?
Adam couldn't just play with the weirdos.
He had to sit at the cool kids table.
At tribal council, the majority decided to trust Adam.
Michelle, the tribe has spoken.
Leaving Taylor, Jay and Will out of the loop.
Twelve are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
I just lost one of my most trustworthy and loyal people.
And now I guess the big Gen X-S pool over there is gunning for the Millennials.
Good job, guys.
May it be on the bottom of the Gen X.
And even the Millennial flippers don't even know because they're so stupid,
like Zeke and Adam and Hannah.
Like, oh yeah, you three are really going to match up to the other six that are coming for you.
Freaking idiots.
Yeah, no problem.
I was happy to see the votes come down the way they did because that means that I'm gaining
some traction and some control in this majority group.
I feel comfortable enough with the solid people in our group, but people like Adam,
who were maybe floating in between and really lost on where they needed to go,
it just scares me.
I don't like it.
Hey, you good?
Stick around.
Ah, yeah, yeah, man.
How the hell did that happen?
You know, you only have so many people you can trust in this game.
Yeah.
And then when they're gone, freaking sucks, bro.
They trusted Adam.
Me and Jay have to work our way somehow into the alliance that was solid tonight.
So what, how many are there left, Jen?
Of us?
Three.
And they're, yeah.
I got to go pull Adam aside and kind of make sure we're still on good terms as far as legal warfare
because Adam could possibly spill the beans.
But I buried two things of food.
I know that tonight didn't work out how we wanted it to.
I understand that you decided that working with me wasn't in your best interest,
and that's totally fine.
Going into tribal council, Jay and Taylor blew up my spot, and then they gunned for me.
And when they gunned for me, all bets were off.
Even if I am at the bottom of Gen X, it certainly feels a lot better than being out of the game,
which is where you tried to put me.
As far as like me knowing that you have an advantage in the game, that's still, like, I respect that.
As long as you respect me.
And I have a secret of yours as well, and I will keep that as well.
Okay.
Back on, dude.
I feel like I hold a bigger secret of Adam's than he holds of mine.
Goodnight, dude.
And I'm going, if you rat me out about my food stash, then, you know, I'm going to rat you out
about your advantage in the game.
This is my best idea ever.
Stealing food.
I'm so sneaky that I stole, like, half of the food.
Oh, yeah.
And no one even noticed.
My pretzels are getting a little bit soggy from all the fruit in there.
So I'm trying to eat the pretzels first.
This looks like a date, maybe.
Can't really see it.
Super wild.
That's a peach.
I still have a whole nother mason jar.
I'm not even, like, halfway with this one.
The only person that knows is Adam, but I have more leverage on him than he has on me.
So, you know, it just works out great.
Hmm.
Great thing.
So shade?
Yeah.
All right, sounds good.
Last night, I got blindsided.
So now in my head, it's like, dude, Jay, you might be next, dude.
So try to find your way out of this hole, because even though I have the immunity out of my
back pocket, I'm in trouble.
There was a lot of feeling of these people want to take me somewhere and not play with me.
I felt like the way I had been playing in my relationship to you guys would have turned
me into a pretty decent goat.
And that's not what I wanted to be.
I wasn't sure how you'd feel about it.
So I decided to play independently last night.
That was cool.
I'm proud of you.
You did good.
I've taken my game into my own hands, and I want to do it well.
Like, I want to do it justice, because I've loved the show since I was 14.
And I'm coming out here and I'm actually playing with the intention of trying to win and build
a resume.
And it's so fun.
Like, damn, my homie didn't tell me.
I know, but I couldn't include you this time.
Well, include me on the next one, please.
Yeah.
It's like I'm finally getting to play.
And last night, I realized that I could do it.
And it's addicting.
It's like I want to be able to pull off another vote.
And now I finally get the chance to make some moves.
High five.
I don't want to low five.
Come on in, guys.
All right, you guys ready to get to today's reward challenge?
Yes.
For today's challenge, you'll be divided into two teams of six.
On my go, you'll race through a series of obstacles, attempting to retrieve a key.
You'll use the key to unlock a box.
You'll then drag the box underneath the net to the finish.
You'll open the box, retrieve the bolos inside, attempting to land them on a target.
First team to get all five bolos on their target wins reward.
I know you want to know what you're playing.
You're going to like it.
The winning team will be taken to a resort where you will lounge poolside.
While dining on cheeseburgers, fries, and cocktails.
And soft drinks for Will.
To make it more interesting, we're going to do a schoolyard pick.
So we'll pick for captains, and the question will be, who do you choose?
Members of your alliance or people who will help you win the food?
We'll draw for captains.
We'll get started.
Let's do it.
All right.
So we randomly chose for captains.
Chris was a captain and picked Brett, Ken, David, Sunday, and Taylor.
Hannah was a captain.
She chose Adam, Will, Zeke, and Jay, and Jessica.
Let's see who made the better choice.
Here we go.
Four rewards.
Ready?
Go.
Over and under.
Ken takes a big fall, but it doesn't slow him down.
Once you get everybody to the mat, you can start working on that key.
Go, go, go, go.
You guys got it.
Go.
Perfect.
Go on.
David being hoisted up, and Adam is going up.
Come on, Orange.
Come on, guys.
David working quickly for Purple.
He's got it.
Unlock that box.
Come on, guys.
Adam needs to get those knots undone.
He can feel the pressure.
Come on.
A quick early lead for Purple.
They have the box unlocked.
Let's go under the net now.
Orange still working on those knots.
A gigantic setback early into this challenge.
Now he's got it.
Unlock the box.
Go, Purple.
There you go.
Come on.
Ready?
Go.
This is going to be the toughest part.
Come on.
Push, guys.
You got four bodies and a very heavy big box.
You've got to get under it.
Get the dirt out of the way.
Orange has their box unlocked.
Let's go, Orange.
You've got to catch up.
Move the dirt.
Which force can get through here the quickest?
Adam, stay up there.
You will give a big lead to the Volo throwers.
Go, go, go.
Great teamwork by Purple.
You watch the net, huh?
Go.
Orange makes very little progress.
They're having a hard time pushing that thing.
Clearly right now, Chris made the better choice with tribe members.
So I'm not going to be a sports captain.
Go, let's go.
Purple out of the net.
Do it.
Here we go.
All right.
Three people on the mount.
One person on the net.
Let's go.
Come on.
Two people on the mount.
One person is using the machete.
It's going to be Kim now chopping the ropes.
Now he'll release the box.
There you go, buddy.
Orange still in the netting.
Guys, do a one, two, three, four.
Ready?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
We're almost there.
Ken has threw two.
Ken has threw all three.
Pull the ropes out.
You're out.
Now Taylor and Sunday taking over.
Come on, guys.
They have the five Volos.
Now you've got to hit the target.
Come on.
Come on, Taylor.
This is a massive blowout right now.
Orange is nowhere close to being through.
Taylor going to give it a go.
Taylor hooks the first Bolo.
Keep going, Taylor.
Taylor, keep going, bud.
Nice.
Taylor hooks the second Bolo.
Guys, don't give up.
Taylor with three Volos.
They are two away.
Oh, my God.
It would be the first blowout this season.
There is four.
While Will, six.
Adam and Jay continue to fight to try to get back in this.
Is it too little, too late?
Yeah.
Taylor hooks it.
For a war for Chris, Ken, Brett, David, Sundance, Taylor.
Nice.
Shooty.
Outside drinks, food.
What a blowout.
I defeated.
Chris, clearly you chose wisely.
Nice job.
Huge reward.
You'll be taken to a beautiful resort.
Cheeseburgers, fries, cocktails.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Enjoy the afternoon.
Thank you.
Good job, guys.
That was a tough one.
All right.
Adam, Z, Jay, Hannah, Will, Jessica.
Got a message?
I got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
Thank you, Jeff.
I was on such a high for pulling off my first blindside vote, and I knew I wanted to keep
Jay and Will closer to me because I know they feel on the bottom.
But I picked a horrible team, and to make such a glaring mistake, it takes you back
a step.
But if I want to stay in the game, I have to prove that I can handle this.
Oh my gosh.
This is beautiful.
Oh, you guys, look at this spread.
Are you kidding me right now?
Drinks.
Oh, oranges.
Oh, that cheese.
We walk in, and my senses were just overloaded.
The amount of food packed on that table, it was crazy.
Burger.
Luckily, my body's been a little bit more adapted to food than these other guys because
I've been sneaking food, so I'm a lot more capable of drinking more, eating more.
That's an advantage.
I could win next challenge from that.
Guys, some cocktails are coming.
Here it comes.
Woo.
Going into the reward, I says, there are going to be drinks, Brad.
Take it a little easy.
Don't go crazy.
Yes, sir, right here.
But come on now.
You get the others.
There's a pool looking out at the ocean.
There's food.
I was like, well, at least my belly will be filled so I can have more drinks.
Keep these coming until I drop, will you?
Yeah.
All right.
So I just kind of went all out.
I was like, I'm going to drink as much as I can while I'm here.
This is ridiculous.
Have you climbed that beach, Doug?
You're looking at this face right here.
Man, my man, Brett, started knocking back the drinks.
He was all in, man.
He had probably, I don't know, eight or nine drinks.
He was letting loose, but that's just Brett.
You know, he's a big, loud guy.
If I run off to the ocean to get fresh fish, can you mix it into a drink?
It's kind of an odd group that we have going on here.
I mean, for a solid alliance, we've got Chris, Brett, myself, but we don't 100% trust David,
Ken, or Jessica.
Good as new, Sunday.
Good as new.
We're just fractured as Gen-Xers because of the experience at the Gen-X tribe.
So moving forward, what I want to make is a proactive move because I definitely feel
like I need to take control of the game.
That was a pretty challenge for sure.
Dude, that was hell.
Right now I'm on a losing streak.
Michelle goes home from tribal council.
I just lost reward, so I try to regroup myself, and I'm like thinking to myself, the Gen-Xers
are gone.
I'll talk to Adam.
Maybe we can make something happen.
I know you have numbers obviously because I got blindsided yesterday.
I knew that I was screwed, that I got caught, and that it was going to be that my name was
going to come up.
Yeah.
And so at that point, I would have written your name down.
It was either be at the bottom of Gen-X as you like to call it, or go home.
So there was no choice.
I'm worried that I might be playing too aggressively, that I might be playing too hard, but I have
to prove my loyalty to my alliance because I have a much stronger bond with Gen-X than
I certainly ever will with Jay at this point.
Taylor is the reason that you and Will and Taylor are all on the bottom and that Michelle
is out of the game because, you know, he-
So I am on the bottom.
Of course.
You know from the vote last night, you're on the bottom.
I talked to Adam, and Adam was just a huge jerk.
He's basically like throwing it in my face that I'm on the wrong side of the line and
basically saying, you know, how does it feel to be on the bottom, Jay?
So what is it?
The Gen-Xers are all together again?
The people who voted last night clearly made some kind of, you know, you heard Chris.
He said tonight a line will be drawn.
So my back's up against the wall.
There's going to be immunity tomorrow.
Hopefully it's a challenge I can win, but if not, I'm in trouble because it looks like
they're gone in my way.
Adam basically just rubbed in my face that I'm on the bottom.
What did he actually say to you?
That we're on the bottom and we're next in line and that's it.
Why would Adam say that to you?
Because he's next.
Yep.
Yeah, pretty much.
So Zeke, you don't like working with him then?
I wanted to vote Adam out yesterday just to get Adam out of the game so I didn't have
to work with him.
I can confirm that Zeke said this.
Adam can't be smart like the rest of us are trying to bring Will and Jay back into the
fold.
Adam has to gloat and make Jay feel crappy.
And I'm just like, Adam, don't be an idiot and make people feel like they're on the
bottom because that's when they vote against you.
Oh, here it comes.
Oh wow.
Look at those rocks coming over.
Isn't that nice?
That looks cool.
It's freaking gorgeous.
Day 25.
14 days left.
Here comes the crazy game.
You all right?
Mm-hmm.
I'm in the position right now where Jessica and I are friendly hellos but something's underlying
there.
I don't trust it.
I'm sure it's me.
Why is she here?
Because I put her name in a rose-colored turtleneck.
She's nice.
We connect as moms.
But I just think because I voted for her, I feel like she really is going to want to
get me out.
Hello, Sunday.
Hello.
Are we up?
We were just like, well, it's nice knowing you boys.
We thought of us as going home now.
One of us is going to get each other first.
I can definitely use Jay because right now he's feeling like he's at the bottom.
We have a really good relationship from our time at Ikeboola.
So I just need to talk to Jay.
Who would be your pick?
I'm just wanting to see where you're at.
I'll write whatever name it's in there.
I told you I'm with you.
I'm with you too.
I trust you fully.
I do you too.
I mean, I really do.
I'll push for Jess today and I'm sure it'll be an easy.
So I just feel like she's going to be after me.
That's what I did with Michaela.
Yeah.
I'll write just tonight.
Unless I'm five minutes before you guys are like, write this.
Yeah.
If I don't say anything, then just plan that.
You and Taylor and Will.
Yeah.
As soon as Sunday says Jessica, I'm like, okay, sweet.
Say anyone's name but me and Taylor's and Will.
I'm cool.
I got to stay positive.
Got to give good energy.
And you know, the universe should be all right with giving it back.
Come on in, guys.
Oh no.
All right.
You guys ready to get to today's immunity challenge?
Yeah.
First things first, Will.
You got to take it back.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're going to stand on a narrow beam while balancing a ball on
a wooden bow.
At regular intervals, you will move farther down the beam, making it more difficult.
If at any point your ball drops or you fall off the beam, you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing wins immunity safe from the vote.
Losers go to tribal council where somebody will be the ninth person voted out of this
game, the second member of our jury.
There are moments in every season of Survivor that even without immunity, you feel pretty
safe.
If that is you today, I have an opportunity.
You can opt to sit out of the challenge, give up your shot at immunity and eat grilled ham
and cheese sandwiches, salty potato chips, ice cold beer and soft drinks.
Let's do it.
Go!
All right.
Zeke and Will are sitting out.
The only two people who feel safe enough to have no shot at immunity.
You can start eating.
Let's get this challenge on.
Everybody take your spot.
I'm going to count you in.
I opted to eat because I knew I wasn't going to win that challenge against surfer guys.
They're obviously going to beat me.
So I could lose and go back to camp with nothing or I could eat and go back to camp with a
full belly.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This challenge is on.
It is not easy to balance that ball on that bow while on a narrow beam.
We will go five minutes in this round and then we'll move to the next section.
Hannah in trouble but a nice save by Hannah.
Hannah, first out.
We'll join Will and Zeke but will not be able to eat or steal a chip or sip a beer or a
soft drink.
Will, you know you can't drink beer, right?
Yeah.
We are down to nine.
Very clear from the choices made that this game is absolutely up in the air.
Will and Zeke have perceived certainty.
The rest of you are fighting for actual certainty.
I'm going to count you down.
When I get to zero, you're safe.
Five, four, three, two, one.
You are safe.
We're going to move down now to the next section.
You must have one foot now in the second section of beam.
It's a little more narrow, going to be more difficult.
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
This challenge is back on Sunday in trouble quickly but a nice save.
Great recovery.
That wind can come up out of nowhere.
Brett's ball on the move now but quickly recovers.
On the move again, couldn't recover.
Brett is out of the challenge.
We are down to eight.
Chris with some movement now and a nice save.
Why didn't I opt out?
All right, we have five, four, three, two, one.
This round is over.
For this next section, you will now have one foot in the most narrow part of the beam.
This will be the trickiest part of the challenge.
We will stay here for 20 minutes.
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We are back on the third and final section.
Immediately Jessica's out, Sunday's out, David's out, three drop.
Chris is out.
We are quickly down to four.
It is Jay, Adam, Taylor, and Ken fighting for immunity that clearly everybody except
for Will and Zeke thinks they need.
Adam in trouble.
Jay now in trouble and a nice save.
Adam is out and we are down to three.
Can't do it.
Jay is out and we are now down to two.
It is Taylor and Ken fittingly side by side.
Taylor, a lot of movement and whistling.
Little movement by Taylor but a nice recovery.
Ken with a little movement.
Ken is going down.
Ken is out.
Taylor is out.
Ken wins individual immunity safe with tribal council.
Nice work guys, nice work.
Ken come on over.
Nice job.
The immunity is yours.
Ken is safe tonight at tribal council, cannot be voted out of this game.
As for the rest of you, after 25 days out here, somebody will be the ninth person voted
out, the second member of the jury.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp, see you tonight at tribal council.
So leaving the challenge, all I'm thinking to myself is it's either going to be me or
Taylor tonight but Sunday told me Jessica so my life is basically in Sunday's hands
at the moment.
The immunity challenge came down to a battle between Ken and Taylor but in the end, Ken
pulled out a win.
The play is hot.
Yeah, I'm down for a swim.
Yeah me too.
Now we have a choice between whether to vote out Jay or Taylor.
Will is safe because he's seen as less of a threat.
But an idol could come into play tonight and then whoever Taylor and Jay want to go home
goes home.
So it's the safest bet to split the votes.
So what's our best move guys?
Split them?
Yeah.
We're comfortable with that.
Let's get Sunday over here.
I think it's a logical plan.
There's Adam and Jess.
Should we just include them?
Yeah.
What do you think Jess?
We're scared of an idol.
I like the split.
Okay, I like that.
In this particular instance, we think it's the safest bet to split the votes between
Taylor and Jay.
Jay is the biggest schemer, the biggest plotter.
Taylor is the least trustworthy of the two.
Can you vote Jay?
Yeah, yeah.
So we're good.
Yeah, we're good.
Because we're splitting the votes, I feel very confident that one of them is going to
go home.
What's up?
I like it.
I'm gonna go with it.
I don't want to rate Jay.
If it were up to me, I would 100% like to see Jessica go home.
I'm worried about Jess.
We have to do Jess.
But because of the way the numbers are, I don't think there's any way that I would be
making the move.
I'll talk to her.
Okay.
Let's go get split.
I'm a little bit more calmer because I wanted to use Jay to make a move against Jessica.
The majority wants you as Taylor.
I can't do anything about it.
That's okay.
I got to do what I got to do.
This sucks.
Everything that we've planned is out the window.
And I hate being on the freaking bottom, man.
Yo, yo, yo.
Hello.
Hey, Dern.
You know.
Yeah.
Tonight, it's either me or Taylor.
But I'm still in the ring, still throwing punches.
I'm not going to give up.
So what's up?
Dude, we got to walk down to the raft.
You have a bunker full of food.
No, you don't.
Yeah, I do.
I know that it's either me and you tonight.
So let's have our feast together.
My closest friend out here was Taylor.
But I'm not going to tell Taylor that I have an idol.
You got to be kidding me, dude.
No, I'm not.
Look out.
New jars.
So let's just chill here.
The bunker of food, my friends.
I love you.
I got three options with my immunity.
Plan A, put it on my neck.
Be like, yo, forget your guys' plan.
I'm never going anywhere.
This is the last meal.
Option B, put it on Taylor's neck.
But if they're splitting the votes, that could just backfire.
And then the next thing you know, I'm gone.
Wow.
I got a good feeling it's me, bro.
Cheers, dude.
Cheers.
Or option C, just be quiet about it.
Hope for the best and just save it for a rainy day.
I don't know if this smart could bite me in the ass, but I have nothing to lose at this
point.
But one of us is going.
Yeah.
Adam has an advantage in the game.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
And this is what it is.
It's that he can steal someone's reward.
So loved one visit, he can switch it all up no matter who wins.
But here's the thing.
If Adam knows about my food bunker and then exchange, he wouldn't tell anyone about my
bunker for me not telling anyone about his advantage in the game.
If I state that Adam has an advantage in this game, that's going to put a massive target
on his back.
Dude, that will ruin his game.
Dude, do it.
He voted out Piggy.
Yeah.
In my mind, still holding a lot of animosity towards Adam.
Do it, dude.
I am an Avenger of Piggy at this point.
Crazy day though today.
Oh, I know.
If you steal the loved one's visit, those people hate you.
And I think that that's a lot more leverage against him than he has on me.
People already know I steal food.
Like, who cares?
Figs told me to fight as hard as I could get to the end of this.
So that's what I'm trying to do.
Now bring in the first member of our jury.
Michelle voted out at the last Tribal Council.
Jay, what happened when you got back to camp after last Tribal?
Oh man, Jeff.
You know, as a fan, damn, what a good play.
I wish I was on that side.
But being a player on the wrong side, hopefully I get some new info or somebody throws me
a bone because it felt pretty crappy being on the wrong side, honestly.
Welcome to the club.
You know, Jay is not the first person in this game to be blindsided.
It's happened to me.
It's happened to a lot of people that are sitting here.
Well, obviously that's the game survivor.
So Jay, you and Adam clearly are not voting together tonight.
I mean, I'd love to write his name down again.
Honestly, Jeff, I'll be real with it.
So do you, Taylor, and Will feel like you're in trouble tonight because of last Tribal?
Oh, for sure, Jeff.
All three of us, we were on the wrong side.
And you're like, oh man, my clock's ticking, you know?
Chris, could you feel that Taylor and Will and Jay believed they were on the wrong side
of that line that had been drawn?
Sure, I think they felt that the first night.
But I've been on the wrong side of the line and you just work yourself back in.
So play the game.
Get back in there.
There's cracks.
Huh?
Interesting.
Yeah.
That's it.
Thank you.
OK, here we go.
I'm going to do something.
So when I got caught eating banana chips, I wasn't trying to be sneaky.
But I did hide two jars full, packed full of food and buried them.
And Adam helped me do it.
They had three jars buried in the sand together.
And he said, look what I hid with Adam.
Let me just clear the air, Jeff, if I may.
Go ahead.
I did not help Taylor bury anything.
You ate the food.
I did not eat any of that food.
And you know that's a lie.
I watched you dig the hole.
So that's what you're upset about?
Yeah, because you're defaming my character.
I watched him do it.
I did not help him at all.
And I never ate that food.
Not once.
Why is Adam so upset about it?
Because you're lying that I helped you do it.
All I did was keep your secret, Taylor.
That's all I did.
Sure, man.
Wait, what specific food was in the jars?
Man, I smashed as much stuff in there as I could.
Where are they now?
It's gone.
You ate it?
Yeah, me and Jay ate it today because we thought you guys were voting us out.
But if you guys want a gun for me and Jay, the bigger threat is over there.
Because he told me a little secret.
Oh my God.
Adam has an advantage in this game.
That is the truth.
I have an advantage.
Wait, there really is an advantage?
Let me hear from Adam.
Adam, what's the advantage?
My advantage is that at any point, if I lose a reward, I can play the advantage and it's
as if I had won the reward.
So in other words, he can steal your loved one visit.
Not necessarily.
That means someone is going to get their loved one ripped from their hands even though you
won.
But it's an advantage that doesn't impact the game.
It's a reward.
I mean-
It does impact the game, man.
But it's a reward.
It's here and in here.
That impacts the game, bro.
Wait, how did they know about the advantage?
I told Taylor.
Clearly I made a mistake in who I could trust.
But I did not bury any food or eat any food that was buried.
And I thought it was wrong from the start.
And if the advantage that I got is so terrible, then vote me out.
Wow.
David, that was the equivalent of a survivor bomb.
Just being dropped.
Yeah.
Huge bomb.
I'm stunned.
I'm uncomfortable and I'm stunned.
I do feel admitting what you did is the nail in the coffin for one of you.
And no other choice.
The reason he had no other choice is because he knew that as soon as he revealed my secret,
I was of course going to reveal his.
If I know that I can get ahead by eating more food than these guys, I'm going to do it.
Jessica, do you think what Taylor is expressing is millennial?
That idea that you just say, well, yeah, I did it.
And you know, here's why, man.
And it's all good.
I think Taylor is looking for a pat on the back.
Like, it's okay.
You told us.
You came clean.
Here's a trophy.
You are absolutely correct.
And that's not the way I was raised.
And I'm sure that's not the way Chris was raised or Ken was raised or anyone else.
Why'd you skip me?
I didn't hide those jars.
You didn't hide it.
I mean, I'm not like that.
So that's not cool with me.
So I was pissed at Adam and Tails.
Tails is like one of my homies from home.
Like get drunk, have fun and go with the flow.
Me on the other hand, I have dreams and goals.
I'm not just a regular dumb surfer.
Like I'm here on Survivor trying to further my life.
No offense, dude.
No offense.
But when I found out from Taylor today that him and Adam buried it, if I was in Adam's
position, I would have been like, this isn't right, dude.
This isn't morally right.
Adam, he's bringing up a strong point, which is not saying something can often be seen
as just as bad.
First of all, this is coming from the guy who already admitted eating this food earlier
this afternoon.
There were only crumbs, but you ate it.
I did not eat any of that food.
But he said you did.
And just because this is a game of Survivor, I'm not going to drop my morals.
When everyone is starving, you do that.
You ate the food.
I did not.
What are you talking about?
Jay, you're accusing Adam of not saying anything, but you've got to own the other half, which
is you're admitting that I did go and eat some of it.
Oh, no, I'm going to admit.
Like I had some food, yeah.
He just said he would not take food from starving people and then admitted to eating it, which
I did not do.
And he thinks that-
So you say.
Oh my God.
So Hannah, where are we for the vote tonight?
Because on one hand, nobody's going to disagree with voting out Adam because he has an advantage.
On the other hand, you've got Taylor and Jay, who both admitted now to eating food.
The game is always more complicated than a simple disagreement.
It's about who you can trust.
It's about looking at future votes and future partnerships.
I mean, there might be an idol in play.
There are idols in play.
It complicates everything.
Survivor is not a simple game.
Brett, what's your take?
Well, I think what we have here is several different errors here.
And I think what we need to know is who's the most culpable.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Adam, you're up.
I'm in.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read, the decision is final.
The person voted out will be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jay.
Taylor.
Adam. One vote Jay, one vote Taylor, one vote Adam.
Jay. Two votes Jay.
Surprise, surprise.
Taylor. Two votes Taylor.
Jay. That's three votes Jay.
Taylor. We're tied. Three votes Taylor, three votes Jay, one vote Adam.
Jay. That's four votes Jay.
Taylor. Tied again. Four votes Taylor, four votes Jay, one vote Adam.
Taylor. Five votes Taylor, four votes Jay.
The second person voted out and the second member of our jury, Taylor.
That's six, that's enough. You need to bring me your torch.
Taylor, the tribe has spoken.
Good luck guys. Sorry for stealing food.
Well almost every single vote at tribal council is about strategy.
And every so often, it's just about consequences.
Grab your torch and head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
Three of us vote out Chris. The Gen Xers are imploding.
We're going after Jess. It's a Gen X civil war.
And Will puts his trust in Zeke.
Jay does have an eye on him. I don't want to tell too many people.
Jay does have an eye on him. That's good to know.
Jay does have an eye on him. Jay does have an eye on him.
But did you hear what Will told Zeke?
My Survivor adventure has been quite epic. I came out here, you know, running through the night and sneaking food.
I lived through a hurricane, made a new great friend. His name is Jay.
I got a girlfriend and hopefully we're going to buy a sailboat and go have some adventures together.
So I'm pretty stoked about that.