to help us. We're going to
help you. We're going to help
you. We're going to help you.
Previously on survivor at the
Tocali tried. Adam betrayed
Taylor. I lied to you and I
screwed you. Figgy was the
sacrifice that had to happen
at the venue a tribe. David
and Zeke were growing closer.
Zeke. I trust you a lot. I
think we're cut from the same
cloth at the Ikeboola tribe.
We're going to make a big
move. This decision could
honestly mold the rest of my
game. A tribal council, Jay
and Will voted with the Gen Xers.
Seventh person voted out.
Michaela sending Michaela home.
Michaela tribe spoken.
Leaving Hannah in the dark.
13 or less who will be voted
out tonight?
That was hard man. I know it
was really hard. Yep. She was
mad man. I told you dude. Yeah
I never seen anything like
that. I made a big ass move
tonight and I thought I was
going to get punched in the
face honestly. But Michaela is
the closer. She closed on
every single challenge. So I
needed to do this pre merge
just to be safe and pretty
proud of myself right now. I
appreciate you guys keeping us
around you know. Thank you
Hannah too. I want to thank you
Hannah. I know. You kept your
little girl out. We didn't want
her to be dirty. You know I
would have voted with you all
though. I know but I didn't
want you to do that. I know I
just wanted you to know that
I. Yeah. At this point I'm
clearly at the bottom of this
whole thing. I'm not going to
vote with you guys. I'm not
going to vote with you guys. I
can't trust any of these people
being completely excluded from
a vote is a sure fire way to
break trust and create enemies.
J thinks I'm just pathetic
idiot that can't see past his
pretty face and intense
gameplay. You have to trust
me. I promise you I will tell
you. You gotta tell me I don't
care about my hands getting
bloody. I just want to know
what the vote is. OK do. I
hope I can get my freaking
revenge. I'm ready to play.
I see it here. Watching or
waiting to see what it is. It's
coming in this direction. What
do they want. What is happening.
All right everybody settle down.
What's going on. What's going
on. Thank you sir. All right.
Let's go. Everyone gather
around. Gather you around. Gather
you around. He could pull a
tribe. You have five minutes to
gather all supplies you will
need to survive for the rest of
this game. Get on this boat.
That was music to my ears. I
went from terrified that I was
going home to now I'm at the
merge within 24 hours. I can't
tell you how awesome that feels.
Oh yeah. Hammer. Now the whole
game is just opening up for me.
Jay's word has been true so far
so maybe I could trust Will and
Jay. But yet I know I still have
Chris and I want to see what
he's been working on. We're not
staying here. Nope. We're going.
I made the merge. To get to this
point means so much. It really
means the world. But this is
when things start to get really
serious like this is the point
of the game where alliances and
loyalties are really tested and
the really great players get
separated from the mediocre
players. And I hope that I'm in
the former group.
Hey, hey, look. Oh my God.
I'm so stoked. You know, I was
down on the bottom for so many
days. I didn't know that I was
going to make the merge. And here
I am. Clouds have cleared and
I'm thrilled. I'm a little
nervous because who knows who
has made what connections at
their other beaches. But for now
I'm just excited to be here.
We're back together. Thank God.
It's the merge. This is
gigantic to be back with the
people that you originally
trusted and that you want to
work with is huge. And Jay and
Taylor, those are the
relationships that I could take
to the end. So I'm back in the
game.
This place, huh?
Fingers. I got a wrist.
Shall we? Yeah.
We shall.
Congratulations. You have made
the merge.
So let's eat.
What, someone?
Oh yes, cheers.
I'm super excited because I'm
back with Michelle and I got
Taylor's back. Oh my God. But
then I also got in my pocket, I
got Will and Hannah and I'm
pretty sure Bret and Sunday.
Besides that, I got an idol in
my back pocket. So I'm the
kingpin, but no one knows. And
I want to keep it that way.
Do we want to go around and
just say what we, where we come
from, our age, what we do?
My name's Taylor and I'm 24
years old and I'm a snowboard
instructor. Seeing everyone
together, I have no idea who I
can really trust and who I
cannot. I still truly trust
Chris and Sunday the most.
I'm Sunday. I'm older than all
of you. And then I thought I
might be able to trust Jay. But
I saw some millennials kind of
coming together laughing, all
joking and you know, it got me
a little nervous. So I don't
know, man. We'll see.
Good to see you, brother. Oh my
God, Bret.
David and I've been like,
how are we going to get Bret
and Sunday back over, man?
We'll get Bret and Sunday
rolling in good shape.
Oh yeah.
Of course, many things have
happened, but...
Yeah.
I haven't decided if the merge
is going to be a good thing or
a bad thing for me. Everything
was going really well at Vanua
and we were on a roll. But the
fact that there was two tribes
and then a swap and then now
we're back into this 13 and
trying to figure out their
relationships is extremely
difficult.
We need to think this through
though.
Dave, Zeke and myself are
meshing pretty well. That's a
pretty good core group right
there to work with. And then I
want to regroup with Bret
and Sunday and figure out what
the next move is.
Hey guys.
Congratulations on none of us
being voted out.
Yeah, exactly.
I am delighted to see my old
nerdy pals, Hannah and Adam.
You know, it's almost good that
we got split up, right?
Because I have intel from
Vanua, Adam has intel from
Takali and Hannah is tapped in
on the intel from Jay at
Ikebuluk.
So I go to travel council and I
write down Bret's name and
Makayla writes down Bret's
name. And then everyone flips
on the two of us.
Really?
Led by...
Jay?
Having my nerd voting block, I
should be feeling great. But
Jay worries me. He's the locus
of power right now because Jay
is very charming. He looks at
you with those deep brown eyes
and he smiles his surfer smile
and it's very enchanting.
Dude, I almost had you on that.
And it's making me nervous to
see all of like the dudes, you
know, Ken and Chris and Tay,
everyone sort of getting taken
in by this Jay charm.
How you doing?
Good, man. Good to meet you.
Good to meet you.
For real?
Yeah.
He sort of has this like mystique
about him that everyone is drawn
towards. He controls Will
outright. He probably controls
Michelle.
You surf?
Yeah. I used to live in Newport
Beach.
Beautiful man.
And I'm just like, if this bro
lions happens, I'm in trouble.
Dude, we got like a buried chest
of awesome things.
When we first got here, I was
nervous that there wouldn't be
enough food.
There we go.
And, uh...
Way more, I thought.
Yeah, way more.
My philosophy here is that
having a belly belly is
the best way to get
the most out of your body.
But it's not just about the
belly, it's about the
body and the body.
It's about the body.
My philosophy here is that
having a merge feast, it's
nice, it's fun, I like to eat,
but do I need it?
No.
And almost every merge in
Survivor, there's going to be
a merge idol out here
somewhere.
And I know this camp well.
I was the only person that's
been able to find an idol
here.
So if there is an idol out
here, I feel like I may have
a good chance to actually
find something.
I take a look at Tremail,
I look up, and there's a note.
I grab it, I open it up,
but there's no idol.
So I'm like, what's going on
here?
Oh!
Whoa.
Congratulations.
You have found an advantage
that allows you to steal a
reward after it has been won
by someone else.
But wow.
I know everything about this
game, and this is certainly
a first.
And it's exciting to be a part
of Survivor history, to have
a new power that nobody has
ever had in this game before.
Alert Jeff of your intention
to steal after he has presented
the reward to the winners and
before they leave the
challenge area.
I think I'm in one of the best
positions in this game, and I
have an idol.
And so I'm going to sit on
this and use this on something
that really matters.
music
I wake up in the middle of the
night and I get this idea.
I'm like, I'm pretty good with
mason jars and canning stuff.
So I pull a classic Survivor
move.
I grab a mason jar.
I put so much stuff in there.
I was just like, I'm going to
try to eat as much of that as I
possibly can.
That's my stash.
music
In the middle of the night, I
hear clanging.
I look out and the kids
grabbing dried bananas.
That's our food for the week.
This is 13 people living out
here.
You don't just jump in and
start divvying up food
for yourself.
Well, I don't want to be the
one to say anything, so I go
back to bed.
music
I wake up in the middle of
the night and I see Taylor
sneaking some food, so I
decided it's an opportunity to
build trust with them.
I'm going to have a midnight
bro down and talk some game.
music
You cannot tell anyone about
this, bro.
If I tell anyone about this,
just vote my ass out.
Okay.
I'm not even hungry, so you
go down.
Okay.
I know your history.
That figure is gone.
And that's like, mm-hmm,
totally understandable.
Taylor is an incredibly
unlikely ally for me.
I have voted against his
girlfriend twice and actually
voted her out.
But if I can convince him to
vote my way, then I've got
control of this game.
music
Jay is building an arm.
Yeah.
And Will has become Jay's
right hand man.
Yeah.
They're tighter, honestly,
than you and him have
maybe ever been.
I hate the idea of holding
out a millennial first.
Yeah, yeah.
But what if we voted
off someone like Will?
music
What if we voted out Will?
So if you take out Will,
then he has no choice but
to go back to you.
This is number one.
Holy crap.
Adam's trying to get Will out.
Are you dumb?
Like, I couldn't believe it.
I don't want to work with Adam.
He wrote my woman's name down,
but Adam thinks that we are
very buddy-buddy,
and I want to keep it that way.
Can I tell you a secret?
Sure.
I was looking for an idol today,
and I found an advantage.
Okay.
It's never been done before.
It says that at any point,
I can steal someone's reward.
Reward?
Yeah.
So if someone wins or
lost his or her money,
I say, bro,
I'm taking this reward.
I'm hilarious, dude.
The only reason I'm telling you this
is because I want you to know
that I'm serious about working with you.
I want to, like, run this thing.
That could not have been easier.
I get all this intel from Adam.
Like, I didn't really have to do anything.
I am a fan of the survivor revenge,
and so I want to blindside Adam
as best as possible.
That is gonna be epic, dude.
It's freaking epic.
Ha-ha-ha.
MUSIC
Yeah, we should.
That's if somebody needed it
in the middle of the night.
At night, we went to bed,
the mangoes had not been touched.
I woke up,
and there was maybe, like,
a quarter to a third back in the jar.
And it's tailing.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
That world is gonna be styling, you know?
I think we're getting bamboozled.
I do too.
They're too close, man.
I know.
Tick of thieves.
I'm starting to think that we've underestimated
the Millennials' hold on each other
and their actual bond.
I see a tight group over there,
so I'm thinking we have to get
one of them gone or we're in trouble.
We have no match.
We have all kinds of people.
Are you sure?
Well, let's think about it.
You, Sunday, me, David, Z,
which one?
Jesse, Ken, Seven.
Yeah, he's ready to bounce.
Nobody's pissed at David.
Yeah.
Maybe it's dumb.
MUSIC
The tightest bonds in this game
are J with David, J with Michelle,
and then Will.
Yeah, I agree.
Not only are they unbreakably tight,
but they're also dangerous players.
So you guys are good with Taylor, right?
Great.
That would be, like, sweet.
Already, people are floating around the name Taylor.
It seems like we're all on board with it,
but it's so early,
and we're at a point in the game
where everybody is trying to carve out
a path to Final Tribal,
so there's going to be a ton of scrambling.
People are going to start to get unsure,
and that is when the game gets crazy.
MUSIC
What's up?
I was thinking, to what extent, like,
will you vote out Millennials?
Me?
I said we keep them strong for right now.
OK.
Because the thing is,
is I know Gen Xers,
they're going to target me and you.
Yeah.
I want Gen Xers to flip one of their own,
so it's easy.
Yeah.
And we can get Adam to stay with us.
Like, where does Will stand at this point?
Will's good.
He's with us.
Yeah, yeah.
We're so solid, that group,
no one's trading on anyone.
Yeah, yeah.
MUSIC
How tight-lipped can you be?
Super.
OK.
Because if this gets back,
then it's going to blow up in our faces.
OK.
What happened?
Adam wants to gun for Will.
For Will?
For Will.
Don't tell Will this.
Adam wanted to get Will now?
Yeah, tonight.
Holy crap, dude.
No.
I'm chilling, just sitting back,
and Tails comes to me,
and he's like,
we need to talk.
And he's like,
dude, Adam's gunning for Will.
And I'm like,
what the hell is going on?
Why is he going for Will right now?
I said, dummy.
Because he's convinced
that he's your right-hand man.
Will's my right-hand man?
Yeah.
So that means he's gunning for me?
Eventually, yes.
And so then it makes me think, OK,
is it less of a risk
to just get out Adam right now?
That's going to come out of left field.
Yeah, it is, and it's going to surprise him.
LAUGHS
I just heard Jay and Taylor
discussing getting rid of Adam.
And I'm just like,
oh, my God, like, this is not good.
But if Adam gets spooked,
this is going to blow up.
Yeah.
We just need to get Will on board.
Right now, Jay and his quarterie
are the most dangerous.
So I was hoping to get this kind of, like,
nerd alliance together.
But if Adam gets voted out,
it'll throw a wrench into my beautifully laid plan.
It's going to get so crazy right now.
There's names being tossed out left and right.
Yeah. Have you heard mine?
Yes.
You have? From who?
Adam.
Because he knows that he's in the same position
as he was when we left this camp.
Yep.
Adam's the rat, and we need to get him out.
But now I'm freaking out because
if he can get the numbers, I'm screwed.
So I'm starting to think to myself,
I have to win immunity.
Come on and go.
All right, you guys ready to get to
your first individual immunity challenge?
Yes.
First things first, take back tribal immunity.
Thank you, David. Thank you, Zig.
Tribal immunity, no more.
Individual immunity is now what you covet.
Oh, yeah.
With this around your neck, you are safe at tribal.
Cannot be voted out.
Without it, you're in trouble.
For today's challenge, you're going to balance
on a narrow perch.
Your hands will be tethered to a bucket above you.
When your arms drop, you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing wins immunity.
Safe from the vote, losers, you know the drill.
Tribal council, somebody will be the eighth person
voted out of this game.
Take your spots. We'll get started.
All right, everybody in position.
This challenge is on.
It's a blast from the past that has been updated.
It's a survivor classic.
We used to do it with one arm.
That wasn't tough enough.
So we decided to make it a little tougher for you guys.
Both arms above your head.
There really is very little wiggle room.
If your arms drop just a little, that will be enough
to tip your bucket, and you'll be out of the challenge.
Sunday is the first move.
Sunday, first out of the challenge.
No shot at immunity.
Now you have an idea how sensitive it is.
Not much wiggle room, right?
Nothing.
Chris drops.
Chris is the second person out of the challenge.
Brett drops right behind Chris.
Brett is now out.
Your challenges are made to test.
How far can you dig right now to stay in this?
Come on, my shoulder.
Oh, my God.
Ow.
Okay.
You're a lot of grunting and groaning.
Oh, man.
You're not crazy.
You're not weak.
You're not a good designer.
God.
This was improved to make it very tough.
Come on.
Jay had been struggling for a while.
Groaning at the pain, Jay drops out.
Zeke falls off right behind Jay.
Zeke is out of the challenge.
We are down to eight.
David has been moving a lot, but his arms are staying steady.
Where are you feeling it, Adam?
Nowhere, Jeff.
Where are you feeling it, Jessica?
I'm good, Jeff.
I'll be honest where I'm feeling it.
No one else was honest to you.
I feel it in my arms and my back and my face and my legs and my toes.
You feel it in your face.
I feel it everywhere.
It's like pain everywhere.
Ken, the slightest bit of movement, and his bucket drops.
That's how fast it goes.
My palms are going numb.
You start daydreaming about something else, and you're drenched.
Hannah can't take it anymore.
Her bucket drops.
Hannah now will take a spot on the bench.
No shot at immunity.
We are down to Taylor, Adam, David, Jessica, Michelle, and Will.
Everybody trying to put on a big game face.
You don't want anybody to know that you're hurting, that you're close to falling,
because they might just be a little closer.
So whatever you have in that tank, you need it now.
Oh, Michelle.
Michelle is out of the challenge, and we are now down to five.
This is about proving to yourself what you can do.
Win push.
Taylor is now out, and we are down to four left.
David can't hold on any longer, and that leaves us with three.
Adam drops out.
We are down to two now.
Jessica and Will, one Gen Xer, one Millennial, fighting for immunity.
How are you feeling, Jessica?
I'm feeling fine.
How are you, Will?
I'm doing amazing.
It would be so nice to go to tribal with that necklace, certain that you aren't going home.
You've reached the one hour mark.
Good job, guys.
Nice work.
Jessica, what would your kids say right now?
My kids are going to be damn proud of their mom.
Yeah.
I've always told them they can do anything.
Anything.
My mom told me the same thing.
You have a good mom.
Yeah.
Now I'm here to prove it.
Oh, man.
I'm going to go another hour.
This is crazy.
Insane.
That's incredible.
Can't be much feeling left in your arms, hands, fingers.
And every time you try to loosen them or get some feeling back, you know you're risking
tipping that bucket.
But you've got to do it to get the feeling back.
Oh, well.
Whoa.
After an hour and 30 minutes, Jessica drops Will the high schooler wins first individual
immunity.
Whoa.
Nice job.
Wow.
What a performance.
Good job.
I knew I needed it, so I just kept pushing for it.
Will, come on over.
Nice job, Will.
First individual immunity goes to Will.
Congratulations.
I don't know what your friends back home in high school are doing right now, but it definitely
isn't this.
You are safe tonight as for the rest of you.
After 23 days, your quest for a million dollars for one of you, it will fall short.
Tribal council tonight, somebody will be the eighth person voted out of this game.
It will not be you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp, see you tonight at tribal.
Congrats.
Good job.
Unbelievable.
My plan totally just blew up in my face, and I got to give him credit.
Will needed to win today, and he did.
And so now I need to try to figure out another plan.
Well, you are unbelievable, man.
I don't know how you did that.
Incredible.
That was amazing to watch, dude.
It was incredible.
Nice job, man.
Thank you.
I can't believe that I, the youngest person to ever play this game, won the first immunity
challenge.
And what makes it even better is that I needed this one, because I know that Adam had planned
to try to vote me out of this game.
So he has to go.
I said we take out Adam.
I know it's all on you, but he was going for Will.
You was calling me out, but you was calling Jay.
Yeah, but he doesn't have numbers to do anything.
That's crazy.
Think about it.
And you still want him?
Whatever you want.
I vote Adam.
I know it's uncomfortable, but we have to do it.
We get back, and almost immediately, Jay turns around and says, we're voting Adam out tonight.
And my immediate reaction is, what?
That's stupid.
We have all these other people who would be great to go home.
I'm with you.
We've been since the beginning.
It seems like more of a personal move than a strategic move, and I'm really worried we're
making a huge mistake.
Hey, buddy.
I got some news for you.
Before we went to the challenge, Taylor told Jay that you had been planning to vote out
Will.
That's why Will knew.
Yeah.
Because I know I'm a target.
I knew it.
As soon as he was up there for like three hours, I was like, the kid knows what went wrong.
Yeah.
Damn it.
I'd laid the groundwork for what I thought was a solid plan, and then the day of tribal
council, it all unravels.
So you are now Jay's target, but I think we can pull the votes together to get out Taylor.
Taylor, why would you do that?
I had a feeling I might be playing too hard.
I was playing too hard, and now I have to scramble.
And at this point, I'm willing to work with anybody on this tribe if it'll keep me in
this game.
I'm sorry I'm coming to you like right before tribal council, but...
Well, we're saying Taylor.
Whatever name you want.
That's what I'm putting down.
But we're saying Taylor.
I'm a little wary he has an idol.
I think Jay has the idol.
Well, he could give it to Taylor.
Right.
What needs to be broken up is the upper echelon of the Millennials, and that's Jay, Michelle,
and Taylor.
It's just a question of getting everybody on the same page, because in the back of our
minds, we're thinking, well, there are idols out there, right?
Here's what I think.
Michelle is the safest person to go after, because she does not have an idol, and they
won't see it coming.
She definitely doesn't have one.
Exactly.
You hear that, Ken?
Are you all right with that?
We need to go after Taylor.
We've got to make a decision, guys.
I need Zeke and the Gen X-ers to get through this tribal council, but they're back and
forth on who to vote for, and if they can't get it together, then I need my plan B, which
is to see if I can get Taylor to target somebody else.
Jay won't look me in the eyes.
We shouldn't have done that, dude.
Because it was too soon, and then information leaks.
So what do I do?
I swear I'm with you.
At this point, Adam has a good idea that his name's been dropped, so he's scrambling,
but it's too late, man.
I will write anyone's name down at this point.
Tonight is 100% about revenge.
Adam's responsible for Figgy going home.
So now we're in the merge and I got my boys back.
We're coming to beat you up.
That's a weird scenario we play tonight.
He doesn't have an eye on us.
I know he does not know.
He's scrambling too much.
It's so odd.
It's like all these conversations that are happening.
Like when Adam walks off with Taylor.
You don't think Adam would flip on us, do you?
We were going to try to save Adam, but I don't know if we could trust him.
The paranoia sets in in the panic and that little seed of doubt can grow into a gigantic forest of doubt.
I'm really nervous.
Adam, if you freak out too much and pull too many people aside, the vote will get screwed up.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
I trust you.
I just don't know if I can trust them.
I will check in with those people, but if you keep pulling people aside, that's what's going to get you in trouble.
Okay.
Okay?
Adam's name is being thrown out there hardcore, and I knew this was going to happen because Adam decided
he couldn't just play with the weirdos.
He had to sit at the cool kids table.
I know Adam was on our team, but he's the worst teammate ever.
Yes, Adam needs to go very soon.
Adam is not trustworthy.
Adam is a bad alliance member.
I've been hoping to preserve my sort of like nerd voting block,
but Adam is the most frustrating person to work with because I don't know what he's up to.
So now I'm thinking we should just vote him out.
Hannah's telling me that I just need to relax and that everything is going to be okay.
But I know for a fact that my position in this game is very tenuous.
I don't think Adam's breathing.
I'm just happy he's awake.
I see his super-ass face change.
I'm not happy.
Now the good news is I have the hidden immunity idol,
so I could play it and know that I'm still going to be here tomorrow.
But if I use it and I had the numbers, I look like a chump.
Oh, I don't know what to do.
So the Millennials and Gen X together, this is what you wait for.
David, what are some of the differences you've noticed between the Millennials and the Gen Xers?
I feel like the Millennials eat a lot more food than the Gen Xers.
Our feast food has been wiped out.
Some pineapples and melons, and that's about it.
And Brett, David is clearly saying the Gen Xers didn't eat it.
Yeah, it was Taylor.
But really I wasn't keeping it a secret.
No, he wasn't keeping it a secret, Jeff.
You were open that you're stealing it.
Yeah, yeah. Well, I don't even think I was stealing it. My stomach was super messed up.
Let me just do a quick poll.
Chris, how hungry are you right now?
I'm pretty hungry, Jeff.
Jessica, hungry?
Absolutely.
Hannah?
I could eat you.
So Taylor, clearly the point is everyone's hungry.
Oh, yeah. Oh, definitely.
Chris, is this a difference between the Millennials and Gen X?
Even when it's clear everyone is calling him out, he's still smiling.
Glenn, I know. It's kind of cool.
Where I'm from, when you do something that you're thinking of yourself, it's called selfishness.
That's a selfish move. Let's not get that confused with gameplay.
To clarify, it's not that I was hungry.
If I wake up and my stomach is freaking out, then yes, I'm going to do whatever I have to do.
So you're saying this was a medical emergency.
Exactly, Jeff.
Jeff, we all had medical emergencies that night.
Some of us are still having medical emergencies.
And where are our banana chips to help stop Buster?
I mean, in a game for a million dollars, you have to practice a little delayed gratification.
Because it might cost you a million dollars down the line.
And yet, Hannah, I don't even have to ask Taylor.
I can tell by his demeanor he's not the least bit concerned that he's on the block tonight.
Yeah, he's a chill bro.
Rock on, dude.
All right, so Adam, what is the vibe with a group of millennials and Gen Xers,
the majority of millennials, but you're all playing this individual game?
It's not just a majority millennial.
Yeah, there may be some loyalties from those first 12 days,
but there was also a period where we were in three different tribes getting to know each other really well.
And you can build loyalty during that time as well.
David, Adam brings up an interesting point.
When you switch tribes, it forces new relationships, and then it makes you question your old ones.
How much impact have the switches had?
Yeah, you know, I mean, the phase of the game that we're in right now, it's simply this.
It's the people I trust versus the people you trust.
And so it doesn't really matter whether you're a millennial or a Gen Xer.
That's just secondary to, really, who do you trust?
Jay, does that ring true to you that it really isn't Millennials versus Gen X anymore?
Yeah, I had a tribal with Will a couple of tribals ago, and he said,
when you find someone that's loyal or trustworthy, you latch on to that.
So I'm going to stick by that.
But Michelle, that's what every person who's had their torch snuffed thought or said right before they got it snuffed.
Makayla just did it. Viggy never saw it coming. The list will go on and on.
I'm going to agree with Jay and Will on this.
You know, sometimes I wonder if it's just the person that you mesh with best, someone that you just feel more friendly with.
So, Will, what's your take on tonight's vote? Is it going to be about a very clear objective or is it something else?
There is definitely a clear objective in everybody's mind. The question is, what is the prevailing objective?
Chris, how many objectives do you think are out there?
Well, I'd say there's probably 13, but I think there will be some lines drawn in the sand tonight. That's my perspective on it.
Michelle, you are nodding your head.
I definitely see a line drawn tonight. That means that trust will be broken for some people and strengthened with others.
So, Taylor, still not worried about tonight's vote?
No, no. I don't think worrying does anything. Some people are worried all the time.
There's nothing you can do at this point to change the fate of that.
Why are you smiling, Adam?
Because he looks right at me when he said it. So, you tell me. Does that say something?
How nervous are you right now, really?
Very.
Because you've heard your name?
Yeah. And it's terrifying. Nobody wants to be the first person voted out at the merge.
I mean, this is a big milestone. To make it here is an incredible accomplishment, but this is where the fun begins.
All right. Time to vote. David, you're up.
This one's for Viggs.
I have never been able to trust you.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it, now would be the time to do so.
Okay. Once the votes are read, the decision is final. Person voted out to be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately. I'll read the votes.
First vote. Adam.
Michelle.
Adam.
Michelle. We're tied. Two votes Michelle, two votes Adam.
Adam. That's three votes Adam.
Michelle. We're tied again. Three votes Michelle, three votes Adam.
Adam. That's four votes Adam.
Michelle. Tied again. Four votes Michelle, four votes Adam.
Michelle. That's five votes Michelle, four votes Adam.
Michelle. That's six votes Michelle.
Eighth person voted out, the first member of our jury, Michelle. Seven, that's enough. Need to bring me your torch.
Michelle, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, anytime there are lines drawn in the sand, the question is, will they be there in the morning or will the tides of Fiji wash them away? Grab your torches, head back to camp. Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor.
The battle lines have been drawn. You and Will and Taylor are all on the bottom. They're gone in my way. But Taylor can't keep a secret. I'm not going to leak that to anyone. He can steal someone's reward.
I'm going to put a massive target on his back. Dude that will ruin his game.
Oh man, well I think, I think they didn't trust me or Jay or you know a group of us and I thought that the majority of people were with us. I thought I could lay back and trust what people had said. So I maybe went overboard with my, my laying back.