Previously on Survivor.
There are three idols in play, held by Adam, David and Jay.
It stays between me and you.
After the merge, Chris, Brett and Sunday saw Jessica as the biggest threat.
I'm reading about Jess.
But the majority had already made their decision.
It's the safest bet to split the votes between Taylor and Jay.
This is the last meal.
Cheers.
With little hope left, Taylor revealed Adam's secret.
Adam has an advantage in this game.
But the tribe couldn't forgive him for stealing food.
You ate it?
Yeah, me and Jay ate it today because we thought you guys would vote us out.
Today?
Yep.
Sending him to the jury.
Taylor, the tribe has spoken.
Elevener left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Yeah that was some tribal, huh?
That was insane.
If I can just say, I am very sorry to all of you for not telling you.
It was not possible because Taylor knew about the advantage that I didn't want to reveal
to the group yet.
And I am sorry.
You know, Taylor stole food from us.
That's why he is gone.
Let's look at the bigger picture here.
Oh man, Taylor and Jay dragged my name through the mud.
And now everybody knows about my advantage.
I want Jay out of this game so badly, I can taste his blood in my mouth.
Is there any food left from the feast hidden somewhere?
I do know where it is.
It was a vault.
You said he moved it.
Oh well, I don't know where it is.
He said he moved it because he didn't want you to have any food.
Right, of course.
Dude, so I'm in tribal council just thinking, Taylor, stop talking dude.
You're burying me with you.
Like, not only are you going out, but now you're making sure that I go out next.
How am I going to clean this up?
Here it is.
So I unburied the food just as like a good faith.
Like hey, here's the food, this is what's left and I'm going to be honest about it.
Oh you found it?
A little bit.
Yeah.
I'm literally up against the wall, literally.
But considering the fact that I haven't used my idol this whole time, it's perfect because
now they really think I don't have one.
It's just a good reason we can't leave Taylor.
Who cares?
I don't care.
Yeah, he's still a crazy idiot.
I mean, did anybody not know he was a complete moron?
Taylor leaving was my goal, Taylor left.
Next move, let's go.
Jay is seemingly on the bottom, but he's not right now in my opinion.
That's about to get real.
You understand that, don't you?
Oh yeah.
I don't know what to do.
Well, I know what to do.
We have to get rid of Jess.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's got to be Jess.
90% of it is she's a strategic player, 10% of it is I owe her one.
For the blindsiding Pauly and my alliance, and if I don't hit her first, she's going
to hit me.
And we got to have six solid, me, you, Sunday, keep Zeke close to her.
We need to keep him.
Zeke's good.
We definitely do this, but we get a tip toe, not for big time.
This is a small tactical squad that's got to go in and take out Jess, and if it's the
last thing I do, I will vote her out.
Sunset was nice, but the sunrise.
Beautiful.
It's hard to have a bad day after that, you know?
And Survivor, you got to find a way to connect to someone who's drastically different from
you.
And I do flirt with Ken.
I just, you look at Ken and you're like, Ken, Ken wouldn't have any sort of crush on me.
Cause like, look at him.
Just, you know, the first few seconds of the day you can look at the sun.
Ken, you told me that.
Yeah, and it doesn't hurt your eyes.
But maybe, just maybe.
Yeah, Ken and I, yeah.
No, it's, yeah, I could, I could see that.
How are you feeling this morning?
I didn't even know where the vote was supposed to end up.
I figured it was Taylor, but I didn't know for sure.
Obviously you have more information than me at this point because I wasn't a part of that
big alliance.
Yeah.
So like David, Chris and I brought together the big votes that we've been seeing.
Right?
Cause we each have like our people.
Yep.
But now you know.
Now the game beats up.
Yeah.
I'm done working with Jay.
It's time to jump off the second ship onto a life raft.
And that life raft's name is Zeke.
Now that you are letting me in on all this, there is something I have to tell you.
Jay does have an idol.
We found it together on Ikebukuro.
But if anybody else finds out and that gets back to Jay, then I'm screwed.
So that's me giving up information.
That's good.
Yeah.
I want to give up information to just really solidify this right now that you and Hannah
are my alliance right now.
Good.
Dude, we're a hundred percent.
Okay.
Thank you for telling me.
Yes.
Telling Zeke that Jay is the idol is a way to build trust between Zeke and I.
Just don't tell anybody about the idol.
I won't.
Yeah, I know you won't.
But you know, I don't want to tell too many people, but telling one individual who I need
to build trust with definitely doesn't hurt my game.
If anything, it only helps my game.
Will told me Jay does have an idol.
Does have an idol.
That's good to know.
Jay does have an idol.
But did you hear what Will told Zeke?
No.
What?
Jay has an idol.
We know Jay has an idol.
I can confirm Jay has an idol.
Jay does have an idol.
Okay.
Will told Zeke that Jay has an idol.
So Jay has an idol.
This coming from Will?
Yeah.
He's turning up to be kind of handy.
I need to have the most power in the game and everything in Survivor is about relationships.
There's no better way to build trust with an ally than revealing the location of a hidden
immunity idol.
And on top of that, a person with a hidden immunity idol has a major advantage in this
game.
But if everybody knows that they have it, that advantage decreases significantly.
I think we have like a misinformation campaign.
And make Jay feels like he's the next target.
Yeah.
We can do that.
Blush it.
I'd like to knock Jess out.
That's fine.
I think we do knock Jess out.
But we just got to keep the blind side between six or seven people and leave it be.
Look, I mean, Hannah and Will got them unlocked.
Okay.
You got your people.
Right.
Cool.
Keep our eye on the prize.
What's doing?
All right, buddy.
We wanted to get Jay to think he's the next one to go.
So he plays the hidden immunity idol.
But in actuality, Chris wants to vote out Jess.
You know, we've had these two nice votes with a lot of people voting together.
But now the time has come to turn on each other.
The opening shots have been fired and the war is about to get bloody.
Come on in, guys.
All right, you guys ready for today's reward challenge?
Yeah.
For today's challenge, you're going to be divided into two teams of five.
On my go, you'll swim out to a raft and work together to pull yourself to a platform.
You'll climb up a ladder, retrieve a key, slide down a pole, and erase it to shore.
Once you have all your keys, you will unlock a set of blocks and then stack them so that
there are no repeating colors on any side.
First team to finish wins a reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Yeah.
It is a floating pizza restaurant that will be anchored 50 yards outside your camp where
you can enjoy pizza, chicken wings, cold beer.
While the losers sit at camp so close they can almost smell it.
So far, they'll never taste it.
That's messed up, Jeff, but I love it.
A survivor brother.
Yeah, it is.
We're going to draw randomly for teams, which means one person will not be on a team.
I think everybody would feel that I'm such a crappy swimmer.
Nobody wants me on their team, right?
David, don't do that.
Are you sure?
I mean, I just...
Are you already bailing out of this challenge?
It's just that I don't have a lot of confidence in my swimming ability, and I don't want people
to blame me for them missing out on pizza and beer.
That's all.
You can do it, dude.
You got it.
You never give up.
Yeah, I won't do that.
David, what does it feel like to feel that support?
Because I don't think ever in 33 seasons of Survivor anybody has said, I'll sit out because
I don't want to bring you guys down, and then have the rest of the group say, no, you can
do it, man.
Don't give up.
No, it feels really good.
These guys have really been helping me deal with my anxiety and fear, and I'll never...
You're a good man.
You're a good dude.
It's all right, dude.
You're a good guy.
I'll never forget the support that they've given me, like game or no game, I'll never
forget it.
That said, I do not want to be my ability.
Choose a rock, Dave.
Choose a rock.
Choose a rock, brother.
Yeah, choose a rock.
Everybody's picking rocks.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, my God.
All right, we have our two teams.
It is Ken, Jessica, Chris, David, and Will taking on Brett, Zeke, Sunday, Hannah, and
Adam.
J picked the odd rock.
Will not compete.
Here we go.
Four rewards.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
You got to get to that raft and then pull yourself in.
Everybody's got to be on the raft.
Go, go, go.
Orange is released.
They're starting to pull.
It takes a lot of teamwork to move that raft.
Apples and crabs.
Ken, Jessica, Chris, Will, and David with a slight lead.
Got to get everybody to that platform before you can start working on the keys.
Now you've got to untie five keys.
Go, Orange!
Purple now slowing down.
Got to get everybody on that platform.
Ken up first for Orange.
Ken's got a key.
He dropped it.
He's got to go back and get it.
Come get it.
Purple now at their platform.
Hannah's going to go up first.
Don't drop it.
Ken's got his key.
Take your time.
You got it.
Go ahead, Hannah.
Nice.
Good job, Hannah.
Hannah has her key.
Ken lost a lot of time.
Go.
Good work, Hannah.
It's Jessica now.
Here comes Hannah.
You've got to get all the way up this beach, Hannah.
Put it on the ring.
Go.
Go, Sunday.
It is now Sunday going up for Purple.
Jessica now has a key.
Whiply down that pole.
Come on, Sunday.
Sunday, go.
Go, Sunday.
Sunday has a key.
That's it, Sunday.
Let's go, Sunday.
A big fall by Sunday.
That's the way you're doing it.
Go, Sunday.
Go.
It is now Chris heading up the ladder for Orange.
Come on, Sunday.
Sunday's struggling in the water.
Come on, Chris.
Chris has this third key.
Sunday's taking a long time with that second key.
Go.
Adam is now going up for Purple.
Chris is sprinting through the sand.
A huge effort by Chris.
Go.
Go, Sunday.
It is now Will heading up.
Good job, Will.
That's it.
Adam has a key now.
Orange with a one-person lead right now.
That's it.
Come on, Adam.
Adam's fighting through the water.
Now he's got to track down that key.
He's got it.
Will has the key for Orange.
Adam back with the third key.
Go.
It is now Zeke heading up for Purple.
Will back with the fourth key.
Go.
David, the last one to go for his team.
You got this.
Go on, David.
Zeke working on untying the key.
David untying the key.
Zeke heading down the pole.
David down the pole.
No problem.
Hit those legs up.
Let's go, Zeke.
David fighting through the water.
He has the last key for his team.
Excellent.
I'll do the first key.
Go.
It is now Brett up for Purple looking for that fifth and final key.
They're looking to unlock four locks right now.
Yeah, Brett.
Come on, Brett.
Ken working on that first lock and he's got it.
Chris now working on the second one.
Go.
He's now Zeke going for that first lock for Purple.
Orange already has one.
You got it, Chris.
You got it.
Chris has the second lock for Orange.
That one.
Zeke has the first one for Purple.
And he quickly has the third lock.
Go, David.
Go.
There comes David.
He's still working on that second lock.
What's the last one?
David has the fourth lock released.
That was quick.
Adam finally has it.
Orange can now take those blocks up and start stacking them.
Sunday now working on that third lock for Purple.
It is David and Chris stacking those blocks.
You don't want any repeating colors on any side.
You got two yellows on this side.
Yes.
Nice.
Sunday has the third lock for Purple.
How are you doing?
You got it.
Brett has the fourth lock.
Go.
You're good.
Go, guys.
You guys have good?
Good.
Two reds.
No good over here.
Turn this one around.
It is Zeke and Adam trying to make up a lot of time on the puzzle.
David and Chris have had a lot of time to study it and work on it.
If there are any repeating colors, it's not right.
Come on, guys.
Come on.
Chris, trying to figure out what is missing.
It's easy to get three.
It's getting that fourth one.
Takes the work.
Go to my side.
Is there a pattern?
And this side needs red.
Or is it just process of elimination?
Zeke and Adam think they have something.
Yes, this looks good.
Are they right?
Yes.
You think you got it.
This is good.
That side's good.
Reward.
Adam.
Zeke, Hannah, Sunday, and Brett in a huge come from behind.
Sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, guys.
Zeke, Brett, Adam, Sunday, Hannah, nice afternoon.
Pizzeria brought to you.
You'll enjoy the works while these guys dream about it.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
Thanks, Chef.
You're welcome.
This is cool.
Where is the food?
Oh my God.
Nice fish.
Look at those wings.
Give me the lettuce.
I want the lettuce.
This reward was my first reward.
I couldn't help it.
My body just reacted with elation.
I just collapsed into myself in happiness.
We've got to be quiet.
They're literally right there.
I also felt pretty guilty because I could see people back at camp, people who you know
are hungry, and I've been on that side of it.
Hey, here's a chicken wing.
Guys, it's crazy.
The sound travels, like they literally can hear it.
Okay, Hannah, I'm eating.
I don't care right now.
It's just crazy.
You know, I don't care what everyone else thought back at camp.
Rewards are huge for your game because it makes you feel human again.
It was like I was sitting at a bar having a few beers and some pizza with some friends.
Can you give me a beer?
Absolutely.
I want a beer for Brett.
You like this beer, Zeke?
Yeah, it's a good beer.
I'm not too much of a casey.
It's a little lighter than the other one, but I think I kind of like the other one better.
And it was good because Zeke and I really bond, and I think that's really going to be a big
help down the road because he's been a lot closer with Chris and I needed that bond.
Zeke, cheers.
Cheers, brother.
So, Brett, is this everything you dreamed of?
This is very nice right now.
Yes.
This does not suck.
Fula, everyone.
This is for you guys.
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my gosh.
Got some lettuce from home.
Hey, a pass.
Thanks.
Nice.
No, no way.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
All right, everyone.
Take it easy.
Oh, my God.
Let it take a moment.
To get a letter from home, I don't know that anyone will ever know what that meant.
I'm so glad we won this one.
The other four saw that it meant a lot to me, but they don't know that my mom was diagnosed
with cancer.
And one of the hardest parts out here is the fear that at any point it's not going to be
good news for me.
So every day that I know my mom's doing okay and every day that I stay here, that I make
it further in the game, that I get closer to that loved one's visit and closer to the
end is another big win.
My dad sent a message from his dog, Memphis.
Wait, let me see.
It's nice to hear from family, isn't it?
Yeah.
Just that little piece.
It's enough to keep me going, to get me through these last two weeks of the game.
Is everyone ready?
Three, two, one.
Yeah!
It is cold blooded of Jeff to put that right out there in front of us.
But so goes the game.
So how are you holding up, man?
Pizza and beer is exactly what I was craving, have been craving for days.
But you know what?
We'll have our own dinner here.
Mentally and emotionally, how are you holding up?
I don't want to cry again, so I don't want to talk about it really.
I really appreciate your support and everyone's support.
You guys have really been awesome.
Dude, what you've done and what you've accomplished, the ways that you've evolved, changed, grown
since you've been out here, everybody respects.
I'm on a journey and it's about coming out of this game as a better person than the person
I walked in as.
My whole life I've had this gigantic fear of death, but over the years it became something
far worse.
It morphed into a fear of life and that's why I'm here.
I'm here to start taking control of my life and I really believe that if any experience
can give me that power, it's this game of Survivor.
Even though I really wanted to win that challenge more than anything, it's nice to reconnect
with you.
We're always going to be good in this game, you and I, okay?
I'm still all about final three with you, okay?
I want to sit next to you there.
I trust you, that's why.
You know you can, man.
Ken and I had some alone time and he really gives me a sense of confidence within myself
and I'm realizing just in life and in this game, you have to take control of your own
destiny and you know what?
Timing is everything in Survivor, but the threesome of Chris, Brett and Sunday is too
strong.
I'm uncomfortable with how deep in this game they've made it.
It's time for me, Jessica and Ken to make a big move right now.
The thing is, Chris, Brett and Sunday, they're a threesome.
Yeah.
We just gotta break that up.
Yeah, we gotta cut off on the heads.
So three of us vote out Chris.
Chris?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I gotcha.
And I think Hannah and Zeke will vote against Chris.
And Adam.
Yeah, and Adam, that's six.
You're 100% sure on Zeke.
He's pointing Chris aside to go on walks.
Look, here's the deal.
Okay, I'm just asking.
No, no, no, I'm just telling you what's happening, or what I see happening.
Honestly, if I had to pick anybody in this game that is playing it the best, it's Zeke.
But with this particular vote, I believe that maybe I'm wrong, but I really do believe it's
in his best interest to get rid of Chris as well.
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
David wants to vote out Chris, which would be incredible because I feel like he's my
arch nemesis out here.
We had some issues on our initial tribe together.
So as far as I'm concerned, Chris needs to go home.
Come on in, guys.
All right, you guys ready to get to today's immunity challenge?
Yeah.
First things first, Ken.
Come back.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're gonna stand on a narrow beam while balancing a statue
with a long pole.
At regular intervals, you're gonna move farther away from the statue, making it more difficult
to balance.
At any point, you fall off the beam where your statue drops, you're out.
The first person left, Sam, wins immunity.
Safe from the vote, losers go to tribal council where somebody will be the 10th person voted
out and the third member of our jury.
We'll drop your spots.
We'll get started.
Let's do this.
All right.
Everybody has their statue balanced at the end of the pole, and this challenge is on.
You can push it off or it can fall backward.
Either one, you're out.
What about ants crawling on your stomach?
You have ants right now or just daily?
I meant literal ants crawling on me right now.
We'll go five minutes in this section and we will move a little farther away from that
statue.
All right.
Everybody has transitioned to the second stage of this challenge.
Now the balance beam is a little more narrow.
You're a little farther away from the statue.
It's a little more difficult.
We'll go five minutes again in this section.
Sunday's pole and she's closer and closer to the top of her statue, but she's still
in it.
Hannah Drops is the first person out of this challenge.
No shot at immunity.
Have a spot on the bench.
And Ken is the second person out of this challenge.
We're down to nine.
All right.
Everybody has now moved back to the third section of this challenge.
The beam just got even narrower and now you're even farther away from the statue and holding
onto more pole.
Ken's ants have moved on to me.
Adam with ants and movement.
Not a good combo.
Nine people still left in this challenge and no sooner do I say that, we are down to eight.
Chris, right behind her.
Will drops.
Will is out of the challenge.
Jay, the slightest bit of a slip and Jay is out followed right behind him by Brett back
to back.
Do you have something in your eye?
Yeah, an ant crawled in there.
Ants proving to be a big nuisance at this challenge.
We are down to four.
Jessica, the only woman left in this challenge along with Adam, Zeke and David.
We are now in the last phase of this challenge.
Most of your feet are at the farthest end of the beam and the most narrow.
You're fully extended on a 10 foot bamboo pole.
We go now until we have a winner.
No more time limits.
Zeke quickly in trouble.
Statue moving.
This pole has dropped now to the very bottom.
Here comes the wind and the wind knocks Adam out.
Adam is out and we are down to three.
It is Jessica, Zeke and David.
Zeke trying desperately to keep that statue balanced.
A lot of movement.
Out of nowhere, Jessica drops and we are down to two.
She looked so solid.
Just how difficult this challenge is and how much toll 28 days can take on you.
It is now Zeke and David.
David has proclaimed himself the underdog.
Who would have predicted this final two?
Zeke, very close to dropping again and saves it again.
David, looking very solid.
Don't lose your concentration.
Keep doing what you're doing.
Let's stay here all day.
Zeke, back and forth, teetering dangerously close to dropping.
Here comes the wind again.
No.
Big gust blowing David's buff nearly off his head but he's still in it.
Zeke drops.
David wins individual immunity.
Nice job.
Nice work.
Nice job, David.
Huge battle between Zeke and David.
All right, David.
Great job.
David, come on over.
Individual immunity.
I got to ask, you came into this game and you have been so vulnerable about the things
you see as flaws, your inability to swim, you're not as athletic and yet here you stand
with the most valuable thing around your neck that you earned.
You're going to make me cry again, Jeff.
Well, what is it?
There are so many people that watch this game and think I could never do that.
You were one of them.
Yeah, and I'm just trying to like tamper down that voice in my head that says I can't and
start listening to a voice that says I can't.
David, safe tonight.
We'll live to see day 29, make it to the final 10.
As for the rest of you, somebody will be voted out and become the third member of our jury.
It will not be you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp, see you tonight at tribal.
Congrats.
Thanks, Jeff.
This immunity necklace can only be the beginning.
It can't be the end.
And it's a risk to put your foot down.
If I have anything to say about it, Chris is going to go home.
Hello, David.
Congrats.
Thanks a lot.
I appreciate it.
Thank you for all the support.
Nice job, buddy.
Thanks, man.
I appreciate it.
So the immunity challenge was today and I freaking blew it.
Damn it.
Good job, brother.
Thanks.
Amazing job.
Now I got to go to tribal without immunity and it freaks me out because I have no idea
what's going on.
What's the word?
I don't know.
Yeah, you do.
Kids hold multiple words.
Well, I know I'm one of them.
No one wants to talk to me.
All I know is if I feel it in my gut to use this idol, I'm going to pull it out and just
throw it out there.
Something in my gut says if we don't get Jess out, we're going to get played.
What we're talking about is we still move on Jess, but we got to play it up to Jay.
You better play your idol.
Chris and Brad are ready to vote out Jessica.
And that's exactly what I wanted to do the last vote because I'm worried literally every
day that she's putting something together to get me out of the game.
Nobody should tell him to play an idol because I know we're trying to flush it.
No, we are.
I know.
Yeah.
Tonight's the night that we finally make a move on Jess.
My man Zeke and his group are on board and in a perfect world, Jay would play his hidden
immunity out tonight.
It would be flushed and Jess would go home.
It's written stone going after Jess.
That's it.
How you feeling about tonight?
Well, I'll just make my pitch to you and maybe it lines up with yours.
And if it doesn't, let me know what yours is and I'll it'll probably be better than
mine.
Sure.
I feel like we just got to go after Chris.
Chris wants to go after Jess and David wants to go after Chris.
So this is what I am deeming the Gen X Civil War.
And I think I feel secure because Will will vote.
This is going to be real easy, I think.
Yeah.
I'm tight with Chris, but if this war is starting, I want to have the power and the control.
So now it's time to pit the Gen Xers against each other.
And you know Chris is coming after Jess.
Chris is targeting Jess.
He's been targeting Jess since the beginning of the game.
So Jessica is not safe as long as Chris is in this game.
You are next according to Chris, okay?
The plan, his plan is to vote you out next and get Jay to play as item.
So I'm wondering what's going on between Zeke and Chris.
Nothing.
I have been told point blank that my name is getting written down by Chris and that's
a scary feeling because I feel like he's got it out for me.
Like he has been gunning for me since the decision to vote Paul out.
If I get voted out, I have to give the legacy advantage to someone else.
But that's not happening because I'm a fighter and I'll do whatever I have to do to survive.
Chris is going to be voting for me.
Okay.
Not Jay.
Obviously you, me, Ken, Dave are 100%.
I do think that Zeke is with us.
I think so too.
But it's not 100%.
And we don't.
I wish it wasn't coming to this already.
I know.
Why can't we just vote out Jay?
We will but we got to take care of the Chris problem first.
Right.
The best thing for me is to have Chris go home.
But we need to have Zeke.
Tonight I have to trust an enormous amount of people.
Like what do you think?
You know, both sides think they're pulling off a blind side.
Yeah.
And they don't want to feel like they can trust the one who's, you know.
I know.
It's a game of trust, you know?
Yeah.
Right now I have what I've always wanted to have, which are options, right?
Two sides think they're pulling off a blind side.
Right.
That's crazy.
And then we're trying to flush and idle.
My little clique of nerdy millennials can't work with Chris, my like oaky buddy, or I
can work with David and make this huge move.
But it's hard for me because like I trust both of these guys.
To win this game, you have to know where you're going and you have to know who you need to
get there.
And so this next vote is all about amassing the soldiers I need to march my army down
the field.
Now bring in the members of our jury.
Michelle and Taylor voted out at the Last Tribal Council.
So Jay, pick up from Last Tribal.
The food scandal erupted.
Taylor's voted out.
That leaves you.
Yeah.
Today I kind of felt like this lone wolf just traveling around waiting for like a crack
to happen or someone to approach, but I'm still in the outs right now, Jeff.
David, did you see that going on in relation to Jay because he had to be a central figure
in the conversation one way or the other?
Well that's an interesting question.
There are different voting blocks.
So tonight is about whether the voting blocks decide to unite to eliminate a single threat
or there's a division and multiple targets emerge.
So it's predictability versus blindside tonight.
Zeke, is voting block the right term for what's happening?
I think what we're maybe seeing is some sort of permutation between a voting block and
an alliance, but it's premised upon trust just as an alliance is, it's just smaller.
Hannah, what's your take?
It is something between an alliance and a voting block.
I call it a trust cluster.
Trust cluster is a great term.
Because voting blocks can be broken up in the blink of an eye and an alliance never
changes but a trust cluster is somewhere in between.
Brett, where do you weigh in on the trust cluster?
Why is that funny?
It's just amazing to hear you say a term I just created.
I'm sorry.
It's just like the fan in me is like I said trust cluster and now you're asking about
it but I'm very focused.
Hannah, you're fantastic.
I love it.
So Brett, do you think there are multiple trust clusters tonight?
Yeah, Jeff, I do.
And you know, my thing is the trust part of it.
You know, who can I trust going forward in this game and getting rid of people I can't
trust going forward in this game.
Chris, where is the game right now from your point of view?
I think there's a couple of groups but where are you going to fall trust wise within those
groups?
Every vote, the line gets drawn again but trust should not be an issue tonight.
And yet, Adam, tribal after tribal, when I read the last vote, there's somebody going,
oh my God, another blind side.
I think it's because Jeff, there's sort of a Cold War brewing and the question is can
we focus on a single threat?
And Jay would be one of those people that we're talking about.
Jay, backhanded compliment.
Thank you.
But I know what's happening.
Hi, I'm like the biggest target on the board right now so it's kind of nerve wracking at
the moment.
Sunday, where do you think this vote is going to go tonight?
I think it's more about who we can't trust than who we can trust in the end of the vote
but the truth is when you have to trust somebody, the only way you can trust them is by looking
at their past actions.
So who here believes they've done something that might be viewed as a past action that
would get them a vote?
Okay, so we've got Adam and Jay and that's the whole food thing.
Jessica, what's yours?
I unfortunately had some run-ins with the Gen Xers way back when.
Chris, she's talking in code.
Do you know what Jessica's referring to?
Yeah, she blindsided Brett and Polly, you know, and me but you have to have a short
memory in this game so Jess has nothing to worry about.
David, how certain are you that tonight's vote will go as you think it's going to go?
I actually feel 100% certain, maybe it's because I'm wearing this necklace but I'm not worried
about tonight's vote.
Zeke, David's 100%, where are you?
100%.
This is fantastic.
Sunday, how confident are you?
100%.
Chris, 100%?
You bet.
Jay?
I'm 100% sure I'm ready to go.
I have no idea what the hell is going to go on tonight.
Zeke, if somebody had approached Jay, the last thing Jay's going to do is say, yep,
I'm solid tonight.
Yes, that's very true.
From a group of people who have all participated in blindsides, we're very good at playing
that we can stick to the plan.
So appearances are very deceiving in this game.
All right, it is time to vote.
Phil, you're up.
You still are holding a grudge, regardless of what you said tonight at tribal.
I'm going to go tally the votes.
Somebody has a hidden immunity idol and you want to play it?
Now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked to leave the tribal council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Chris?
Jessica?
Jessica we're tied.
Two votes Jessica, two votes Chris.
Chris?
Jessica, we're tied again.
Three votes Jessica, three votes Chris.
Chris, that's four votes Chris.
Jessica, tied again.
Four votes Jessica, four votes Chris.
Chris, that's five votes Chris, four votes Jessica.
Tenth person voted out, the third member of our jury.
Chris, that's six, that's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Chris, tribe is spoken.
Boomer.
Sooner.
Well, alliances, voting blocks, trust clusters, whatever you call it, this game is being played
at a very high level and that means one thing, more blindsides to come.
Grab your torch and head back to camp, good night.
I was completely blindsided today.
It's disappointing, I wanted to go further in the game, but Jess outplayed me man.
I've been going after her for a long time, so I'm just having a hard time processing
it.
But no regrets, I'm coming home to my boys soon, Jackson Costner and my wife, I love
you for letting me have the adventure of a lifetime.
Great move.
Holy crap, I didn't know what the heck was going on.
That was so awesome.
I was sitting there, I'm like, no one's really talking about me, don't use it.
It was a million dollar gamble and I was right and my name didn't even show up once.
Sorry I wrote your name.
You don't need to apologize, you have no reason to apologize at all.
Sending Chris home solidifies things for the group that I trust because we had a plan and
everybody stuck to it and the next vote should be Jay.
He was totally in control, so that move needed to be done whether it was now or in a couple
days and I'm a huge fan of Chris, but he would have won the whole game.
Yeah, I think that was just short of the feeling, but I want to say I'm sorry that we couldn't
have done this together and in my mind, you and Sunday are not on the bottom.
I appreciate you hearing that, I knew you and I had a really good before in the last
couple days.
Yeah.
Tonight's vote went as I anticipated, it was necessary to see Chris go because Chris was
in a major power position.
He controlled Brett and Sunday.
I would love to move forward if you'll do it.
Alright, I'd love that too, Brett.
Alright, awesome.
Let's talk more in the morning.
Definitely.
Great.
I saw going forward, I was going to need to make a move against David and his coalition.
If I'm going to come for David soon, I need at least six.
Brett and Sunday are integral to that six and I like most of all that I got to them
before David did.
Look at the calm the water is today.
It's beautiful.
I just want to tell you guys just because like, you know, I flipped on Chris yesterday
doesn't mean that I'm like, okay, now you, now you.
No, no, no, no, listen, we had to all think about it at some point.
Yeah.
And Chris is my buddy too.
I know, I know.
And he could have won this whole thing.
He's a strong player.
It's out with, out mass and out play.
Yeah.
So like you said, just do what you can until I tell you that.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
I still think Jay should go.
Don't you think?
Is it next time?
Yeah.
I want to make Jay the next vote, but the fact is the person winning this game right
now is Zeke.
And so I think I need to eliminate Zeke in three votes because I do want to get rid of
Jay, then Will, then Zeke.
You guys know who's playing the best game right now.
Okay.
The guy has an individual conversation with everyone in this game.
He gives up enough information so that people trust him.
He's going to win.
Unbeknownst to David, I've signed on with Zeke because David, I know he can't be trusted.
So I'm nodding and I'm thinking David needs to go and he needs to go fast.
How are you feeling this morning, dude?
I feel, no, I feel good, man.
What concerns me is that I think David needs to go.
He mentioned to me this morning, Zeke's playing the best game, Zeke's friends with everyone,
Zeke needs to go.
Wouldn't you know, I wake up this morning and David has already started to come for
me.
I mean, like it's understandable, right?
Because I've already started to come for David.
You want to know something about David?
What?
He has an idol.
I know he's got an idol.
Okay.
Do you know why I know he has an idol?
Because he always has an idol.
Yeah.
If you're going to snuff him, you got to do it without him knowing and that's going to
be hard.
I'm like the doughy little gay guy and like a lot of people just didn't believe I could
hack it out here.
And I think it's developed the toughness in me.
But I'm telling you, watch David.
Yeah, no, I know.
Today I am a warrior because my goal ultimately is to make a move against David.
That's what I call foilant.
I will make coconut popcorn for my friend.
Yes.
The thing about Zeke and I, I think we're chess players in this game of Survivor.
And I feel like I can read Zeke's mind.
I feel like we're having much the same thoughts.
And I hope people see Zeke as playing harder than I am.
So I don't think it'll be such a hard sell when it comes time to vote him out.
David and I are very similar people.
But like I understand that I'm threatening.
David understands that I'm threatening.
I think people see it.
But I think David is more of a threat to win than I am.
This is the war that everyone has been alluding to.
And now it's a scramble for who has the troops.
I had a good talk with Brett this morning.
He told me that David approached him this morning and said that I am David's next target.
So interesting.
So David has an idol.
He found it the morning after he played it.
Get out of town.
I think the more dangerous couple right now is Will and Jay.
I just want to object to this by saying that like neither Will nor Jay is coming after
me right now.
It's true.
Yeah.
I want both David and Zeke to feel like I'm in their corner.
And they're both two extremely threatening players.
Look, like this is the first time someone's brought your name up.
Right.
I mean, I would love to work with David.
Ben and I are very similar, both very neurotic people.
But it's been a month of Zeke and me working side by side.
So I don't know who I choose, either Zeke or David.
Come on in, guys.
All right.
You guys ready to get to today's reward challenge?
Yes.
For today's challenge, you'll be divided into three teams of three.
Your feet will be tied together.
Your arms will be bound to your sides.
One at a time, you will slither through the sand through a series of obstacles.
Then you'll work together to solve a snake puzzle.
First team to finish wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Yes.
The winning three will be picked up here in this beautiful sand spit in the middle of
Fiji by Chopper.
Oh, my God, Chopper.
You'll go up in the air and get a nice tour of this beautiful place you've been living
for the last 29 days.
You'll then touch down and enjoy a survivor picnic.
Oh, my word.
Fried chicken.
Oh.
Mac and cheese.
Mac and cheese?
Wine, beer, soft drinks, pie.
Oh, Lord.
Great afternoon and a nice chance to strategize away from all the losers.
There's one twist to this challenge because only nine of you are going to run.
That means one person will not have a chance to earn their shot at reward, and they won't
have to.
If you draw the white rock, you don't participate.
You automatically earn a spot.
Whoa.
Think of it as a survivor lottery.
Give me the white one.
We're going to draw for teams.
We'll get started.
Let's do it.
All right.
We have our teams.
It is Hannah, Jessica, and Adam.
It is Will, Ken, and Jay, and it is Sunday, Zeke, and Brett.
David chose the white rock.
This is going to be one of the most physical challenges, and all David has to do is just
wait for it to end.
He's going on reward either way.
Here we go.
I'm going to draw for reward.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Go, Hannah.
Come on, Sunday, you got it.
Hannah, Will, and Sunday, like inchworms.
Will off to the fast start.
Face down, not afraid to get dirty.
Will is working it.
Go, Willie.
Starting to lose those shorts.
That American flag about to get left behind.
Come on, Hannah.
You're almost there, Hannah.
Hannah, like an elephant seal, trying to beat yourself.
All right.
You got it.
Hannah like an elephant seal trying to beat herself.
Kick it!
And Sunday at last will very close to the relay point.
Go Ken!
Come on Ken!
Now Ken's got to start up and over these sand mounds.
Here comes Hannah!
Push, push, push, push, push!
Go Jessica!
It is now Ken in the lead.
Come on Ken!
Warrior!
Jessica digging!
This is difficult!
Come on Sunday you're almost there!
Go Z!
Come on Zeke you got this man!
Zeke now going up and over.
Jessica working.
You can do it Jessica!
Ken is moving very fast extending the lead for green.
Go Jen!
Go!
Now green with a huge lead over purple and orange.
Zeke now starting to get a rhythm going.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice!
You're almost there Jess!
Jessica struggling.
I can't get it!
Almost there.
Jay is flying through the course.
Once Jay gets to the end, all of green can release.
Go green!
Starting in time you can work on the puzzle!
Zeke is almost here!
Face down covered in sand!
You got it buddy!
Zeke looks like a survivor mind.
Go Brett!
Orange trying to get in it now.
Jessica still trying to get up that last mound.
I can't do it!
Will, Ken and Jay working on that snake puzzle.
Good job Brett!
Brett is really moving.
He's going to make up a lot of time.
Let's go Brett you're almost there!
You got it!
That white butt glowing in the sun!
Jessica really struggling!
A massive setback for purple.
One last effort away!
Go Adam!
Push!
Adam has not slowed down at all.
Touch that mat and you are good.
Go purple!
Start in time!
We've now got two groups working on the puzzle.
Look for small pieces that go towards the tail.
And purple is now back in it thanks to Adam.
I'm here, come on Jess, come on.
Everybody working on the puzzle now.
Ken, Will and Jay have had a big head start working on this puzzle for a while.
There we go.
Jessica, Hannah, Adam, and Jessica are all working on the puzzle.
Brett, Zeke and Sunday are making a lot of progress very quickly.
It is now Will, Ken and Jay that are trying to catch up.
Look at the piece that we need next and look forward on the table.
Suddenly all three teams are in this.
That is why you never, ever give up.
Oh my God.
Three people will join David on a massive reward.
There we go.
Brett with another piece.
That's it.
Try that again.
Out of nowhere it is Brett, Zeke and Sunday about to close the door on this.
Let's go, keep going, keep going.
There we go, there we go.
Yes, yes, yes!
They think they have it.
And they do!
Yes!
A massive comeback for Brett, Zeke and Sunday's reward chopper ride of Survivor Picnic.
We get our helicopter ride.
I got naked on Survivor.
Sunday, Brett, Zeke and David, come on over.
Your ride is coming in right now.
Oh my God.
I have an advantage in this game that allows me to steal a reward from another player.
I was very tempted to use it, especially because David didn't earn this one.
But I felt like it was the best decision for me to hang on to my advantage and save it for another day.
All right, Adam, Jessica, Hannah, Ken, Jay, Will, got nothing for you, grab your stuff, head back to camp.
My dream was not only to get on Survivor, but to win a helicopter reward.
So this ranks up there as one of my favorite days, literally ever in my life.
I feel like I'm 10 years old.
Cheers.
Oh, cheers, guys.
Wow.
Zeke, here we go again, brother.
Here we go again.
I got a nice buzz on, I'll tell you that right now.
My new drinking buddy is Brett.
I don't really like to drink beer, but I really want to cultivate a relationship with Brett.
So if he wants me to be his new drinking buddy, I'm his new drinking buddy.
I need to take a walk.
I'm going to take some beer and wine with me.
Yeah, do something, will you?
Really cool.
And then there were two.
Two drunks.
Don't talk about anything important while I'm gone.
No, I won't.
Two drunks sitting on a beach in Fiji.
My drinking buddy.
Well, it's nice breaking bread with you.
We're going to be part of each other's lives, whether we like it or not.
You know, I've been a big fan of Survivor, and it's just a part of my life.
And as I get older, you start to learn who you really are, and you start to not care what people think.
What's up?
I'm trying to get closer to Zeke, because I want to work with Zeke.
And I just like him as a person.
My family's going to play it down in the cave, so.
Yeah, we'll do it if we can, like, you know, in like July or August or whatever.
Absolutely.
Right on.
Yeah.
Well, I will tell you, you're not the only gay guy out here.
You?
I'm playing a game here.
Fine, dude.
I was going to tell everyone, and then I had, you know, macho group.
I had Ken, Chris.
Sure.
I was like, I got to shut my mouth here.
Yeah, yeah.
So it just didn't happen.
Oh, yeah.
It will, brother.
Right on.
I'm a different generation.
No, I understand.
You know, we don't talk about it.
It's different for everybody.
Yeah.
I didn't grow up in a time when it was normal to talk about being gay.
And the millennials do not care.
Zeke finds comfort in being himself, and I think that's great.
And I'm hoping that, you know, as my life goes on from here on out, I can be that way.
I've never had a problem.
Like, you tell your friends, nobody cares.
You know what I mean?
It's just in my head.
It's been in my head my whole life, you know?
Yeah.
So it's, but, you know, you become forward and you're like, I don't care what anyone
thinks anymore.
You know what I mean?
I am who I am.
I have great friends.
I do whatever I do.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, no.
It's interesting because, like, I never thought about not saying anything.
All right.
I've lived with not saying anything.
So for me to come out here and not say anything...
It's life.
I've lived like that.
Well, you have to, like, play Survivor the way you live your life.
You know?
That's like, I think you can't try to do something new on Survivor.
I owe a lot to Brett's generation.
I would not be able to come out at 15 were they're not the pioneers who paved the way.
And I think it really reflects this millennial Gen X divide, right?
He spent time in the military during the Don't Ask, Don't Tell era where he couldn't have
been in the military if he told people he was gay.
And I'm excited that now Brett is getting a chance to, like, reap the rewards of what
he has sowed.
Cheers.
Cheers, brother.
So Zeke and I were starting to talk.
Yeah.
But we wanted to wait till you get back.
Oh, thank you.
So what's your thoughts on...
David?
Yeah.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous, too.
You?
I'm nervous.
I'm glad he's here.
Me, too.
So I can...
I know what he's up to, you know?
I think, like, if we can get Jay and Will on board, then I can bring in Hannah.
We can pull off the blind side.
We just have to make sure David doesn't sense that we're coming for him.
Right.
Brett and I, we've got, like, the rainbow connection.
And Brett, Sunday, and I, we're all like, David's the biggest threat in this game.
And I am delighted to hear this because now, I think, I have united them against an enemy,
and they are my loyal soldiers.
Hey, kids.
Hello.
Hey, Hannah.
Was it cool?
It was great.
It was all right.
Shut up, Brett.
You loza.
So the winners get back, Zeke, Brett, Sunday, and David, and I immediately grab David.
Yeah.
I've never...
I'm playing between you and David.
Yeah.
I'm playing between David and Zeke, but I'm going with my gut, and my decision is to go
after Zeke because Zeke, he's condescending, and he can be a flip-flopper.
Go ahead.
So Brett tells Zeke, you're gunning for him.
Zeke turns to Adam and tells him you have an idol.
Oh.
But don't freak out.
Don't freak out because here's the good part.
Wait, wait, wait.
What is the good part?
No, no, this is the good part.
Ready?
What?
The good part is, Zeke trusts me.
No, but, I mean, I appreciate that, but...
No, no, no, no, no.
So if he's going to make a move against you, I'm going to know.
Okay, here's the deal, Hannah.
My idol, it's for me and it's for you.
Okay.
Okay?
Okay, Brett's walking up.
He's walking up?
He's walking towards the water.
He's just there.
So here's the thing.
You're making me so nervous and Brett just...
We should stop looking.
Zeke is now telling people that I have an idol at the very...
Oh, here comes Jay.
Oh, my God.
You look beautiful, like a Peruvian Ozzy.
Here's the other thing.
Hannah, Hannah, I blew up my game, clearly.
No, you didn't.
I blew up my game.
Hannah tells me that Brett told Zeke that I'm gunning for him, which is, like, complete
miscalculation on my part.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
I knew you'd be upset.
I know you're not.
You're not.
Hey, hey.
Don't get neurotic on me.
I'm not.
Because then you're gonna waste your idol.
Here's...
Okay, can I pitch something?
We go after Zeke now.
Let the vote be me.
I play my idol.
Zeke goes home.
I want to see where Zeke's head is at.
If Zeke finds out I'm working with you, then I'm...
Hey!
Come on in, guys!
All right, shall we get to today's immunity challenge?
Yes!
First things first, David.
I need to give it up.
I know you do.
Once again, immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're gonna stand behind a cage door,
and you'll maneuver a handle through a maze.
Once your handle's free, you'll unlock the door
and race to complete a slide puzzle.
First person to finish wins immunity, guaranteed a one-in-nine shot
at winning this game.
Losers, tribal council, somebody will become
the fourth member of our jury.
Draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
First, you've got to untie your handle.
Then you start working it through the maze.
You are blind, you cannot see where the maze is leading,
so you have to do all of this by touch.
This is gonna be about trying pathways that work,
and then running into a dead end, and trying to remember,
I don't want to go back there.
Where was that?
How'd I get out of here?
So easy for me, I can just follow the color.
I know if you're doing well or not.
I will not be saying who is in the lead and who is falling behind.
You will not know where you are in the maze until you're out of it.
Everybody trying to figure this out, is there a pattern?
Am I at the same dead end?
You can use your hands to try to feel ahead, or you can just go for it.
But if somebody gets through this quickly,
you will have a giant start on that slide puzzle.
Jay has his free.
Jay is through his door.
Jay can start working on the slide puzzle.
Now we got it going on.
Now you are trying to catch Jay.
Jay quickly gets to work on that puzzle, sliding pieces around.
It looks so close, and you can be one piece off, and it's a setback.
This could be over quickly if Jay is good at slide puzzles.
Mechanic now really setting in.
Am I even close, do I have a shot?
Jay thinks he has it.
That looks like the survivor logo to me.
Jay wins individual immunity.
Not even close.
Nobody even out of their maze.
That is an official survivor blowout.
Wow.
Jay, come on over.
It was pretty to watch.
It's because I was in pink, Jeff.
Individual immunity.
Jay, safe tonight at Tribal Council.
You will not be going home.
As for the rest of you, 30 days is a long time to play this game.
But for one of you, that's as far as it goes.
Somebody voted out will become the fourth member of our jury.
It won't be you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
We had an immunity challenge today, and guess who came out?
Champion.
Oh, boy.
I did.
I won.
I crushed these fools.
So who are you going to give it to?
For this one?
I think it's going to stay there.
And surprise, I still have an idol.
But I'm not playing it tonight.
I saved it so long for myself, I'm going to keep it for myself.
Boy, I deserted up here quick.
Is it just you and I?
It appears that way.
I have a favor to ask you.
Basically, all I did, I was trying to lure Brent and Sunday over to our side.
And I told Brent that I'm like, you know who the biggest threat in this game is?
And you know who it is, right?
Oh, Zeke.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's not a good thing that you did.
I need us to write down Zeke's name tonight.
You, me, and Ken.
Why are we doing that?
Because he's gunning for me tonight.
Oh, Lord.
I have to protect David and vote for Zeke.
Because David actually played a hidden immunity idol for me.
But if David had just let well enough alone and not said anything, this wouldn't be happening.
Zeke.
Zeke is going to vote David.
I'm going to stay with David.
I made a promise to the man that I would never put his name down.
And so I want to go out swinging and fighting with David in this game.
Like, I want to work with you.
David is a guaranteed winner who has an idol.
So would you say that overall, like ranking threats, that David is the most threatening
person in the game?
Uh.
Would you agree with that assessment?
It said a little harshly, but I just.
No, here, just, just, Ken, is that fair?
Because I'm trying to make a larger point.
I know, I'm thinking.
I have attempted to cultivate Hannah as a very, very close ally.
And as we're talking, it becomes very clear to me that Hannah does not have my best interest
at heart.
You don't talk to David and tell him I'm like coming for him hardcore, are you?
You both know you're coming for each other.
Right, but you don't like talk to him about that, do you?
David, through the grave, like, you both know it.
Right.
I think this is a question of whether or not you're going to play the rest of this game
with David or you're going to play the rest of this game with me.
Okay.
I realize that I'm no longer going to be working with Hannah.
The vote.
I'm going to be David, but David has an idol and if David plays an idol, we're screwed.
So if Hannah wants to become one of David's numbers, she becomes my enemy and I have no
problem voting her out of the game.
Hannah is in David's pocket.
We can vote for Hannah.
I don't trust Hannah.
Yeah, I need to do it.
Hannah is in David's pocket.
I think so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm going to vote Hannah.
Okay.
Okay, we got it.
J. I'm ready, Hannah.
H-A-N-N-H.
That's how you spell her?
Yeah.
Deal, I'm going to write Hannah.
We've come to the day where it's going to be either David's army or my army.
So I'm trusting Brett and Sunday and Jay and Will.
So we have five votes together, which is half, which means at worst we talk.
Zika Roni wants David out.
Right.
David wants Zika Roni out.
What you and I need to do is stick together and choose a side.
I trust you because you and I genuinely want to sit at the end and switch houses.
Yeah.
Yeah, so what do you want me to do?
Who do we vote for?
Zika.
Hannah wants to vote for Zika tonight, but I'm not confident about the plan tonight because
I have been sitting back a little bit and allowing Hannah to run the show a little bit.
And Hannah is a nervous girl and it makes me nervous.
Adam wants to work with me.
I'm with you 120%.
So who do we have then?
Just...
Me, you, Adam, Jess, Kenneth, all vote for Zeke, which gives us five.
But if they put five in five, I'm the one they're going to target.
Well, you don't know that's just a gut feeling.
You're nervous.
You're getting neurotic.
No, Zeke, he doesn't trust me.
I just, I have a feeling, I know it's me.
I'm probably going to need your idol tonight.
Right.
My OCD is going crazy right now.
It's like the anxiety is like too much.
My body can't handle it.
I feel like David should play his idol for me because if the vote changes at all, it's
going to be against me.
If it is a five-five tie, let's say I did play the idol for you and it's not you, then
there's a revote.
It'll probably come back as a tie again and then rocks get drawn.
Tonight is huge.
If we really do have five votes and there's no really anymore, who the hell knows what's
happening?
But if we really do have five votes against Zeke, then it would be a tie and then we'll
have to revote and it will require somebody flipping.
Question is, who would flip my people, their people?
But I'm not even sure that it will be five-five.
So I'm really schizophrenic about what I'm going to do with my idol.
I hope I play the idol for the right person.
This is really the scariest part of the game for me thus far.
Now bring in the members of our jury.
Michelle, Taylor, and Chris voted out at the Last Tribal Council.
Alright, so let's get into this.
At the Last Tribal Council, I asked how many people are pretty certain you know where the
vote is going and quite a few of you said 100%.
How many people tonight feel the same way?
Nobody?
Wow.
Okay, how many of you feel some sense of security that it won't be you tonight?
You're the only one.
David, is it going to be just another crazy vote or is this a turning point in the game?
You know, I don't know.
Here's the deal.
I feel like one of those fruit bats back at camp.
Like the world looks upside down right now.
This is like the most chaotic tribal I think we've seen yet, or at least it's about to
be.
Really?
Yeah.
Alright, that to me says the gameplay is so good.
You guys are playing as if this is your second time, but it's not.
Yeah, I mean honestly everyone here is playing full on pedal to the metal.
Let's do this because everyone's such a super fan of this game.
See all this whispering.
I don't know what is even being said.
David, you're sitting almost smack dab in the middle.
Yeah, this is what's known as a trust cluster muck.
Oh, there's no clusters.
There's a must, there's knock that crap off, alright?
Brett, why did that get you so upset?
Because this trust cluster, enough with this.
Give me a break, okay?
This is every man for himself right now.
I mean this is insane.
Listen, you talk, you hope what's being told you is correct and you move forward, you know?
Well would members of Zeke's Alliance like to raise their hands?
Oh David.
The members of David's Alliance like to raise their hands.
Oh no, I'm going to cry because I've got anxiety.
Oh don't cry David.
Oh stop.
Is this affecting you?
Okay, let's not bully.
That's a personal attack.
I haven't personally attacked anybody.
Personal attack.
Alright, alright.
But that's where we're at right now.
I don't even know what to say.
Adam, what are you thinking right now?
Are you nervous?
Hell yes, I'm nervous, Jeff.
I am now less sure of what was going on than I was when I walked into tribal council tonight.
The vote is still very much live.
Jessica, you look like, huh?
How could it be live?
What's going on?
I am so utterly confused right now.
I really have no idea what's happening.
Wow.
Ken, how do we know when it's time to say pencil's down, let's vote?
Yeah, we got the guillotine ready, the knife's about to drop and we're still trying to figure
out whose head are we throwing under.
I've never seen anything like this.
There's so many conversations happening right here.
I'm curious why we're so easily mixed up by someone simply whispering from us.
That's insane.
Ken, this is the game.
I'm going to do it.
Whoa.
Oh, I'm know, I'm very well aware of that, Brett.
What are we doing right now?
That's what I'm asking.
This is all smoke and mirrors, huh?
You know, that's all nonsense.
Smoke and mirrors.
So Zeke, is tonight's vote about what is really true and what is just one big facade?
Yeah, everyone wonders who they can trust, who they think they're voting with.
I don't think anyone feels sure that those they have had conversations with are going
to do what they said they were going to do.
Wow.
You know, Tribal Council's theater, Jeff, and I think we've proven that tonight.
I say we vote.
Should we vote?
Yeah.
Yeah, no, let's vote.
All right, it is time to vote.
Will, you're up.
Oh.
Oh my God.
What the hell off me?
What the...
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity item and you want to play it, now would be the time
to do so.
Sorry Jeff.
What?
Wait.
Uh, here you go Jeff.
Hold on.
They were whispering over here that they want to vote for Ken.
Wow.
Jeff the idol is for...
Ken.
Whoa.
All right, any votes cast for Ken will not count.
Damn.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Zeke.
Hannah.
Damn it.
Knew it.
Told you.
Zeke.
Hannah.
Two votes Zeke.
Two votes Hannah.
Zeke.
We're tied again.
Three votes Zeke.
Three votes Hannah.
Zeke.
We're tied again.
Four votes Zeke.
Four votes Hannah.
Zeke.
That's five votes Zeke.
Four votes Hannah.
One vote left.
Hannah.
We're tied.
So here's what's going to happen.
We're going to have a revote.
Hannah and Zeke, you will not vote.
Everybody else, you can only vote for Hannah or Zeke.
Will you come grab the urn?
Oh, I'd love to, Jeff.
I have real line with people all the time.
Jessica.
Oh my God.
I'm just gonna flip up here.
I'll go tally the votes.
I'll read the votes.
Hannah.
Zeke.
Two votes Hannah.
Two votes Zeke.
Hannah.
Zeke.
Tied again.
Three votes Hannah.
Three votes Zeke.
Hannah.
That's four votes Hannah.
Three votes Zeke.
One vote left.
Zeke.
Oh my God.
We are deadlocked.
Here's what will happen.
Per the rules of Survivor, if the eight of you can unanimously agree on either Hannah
or Zeke, they go home.
If you cannot unanimously agree, then Hannah and Zeke become immune and they join Jay and
Ken, and all four become safe.
And Will, Brett, Sunday, Adam, David and Jessica will all draw rocks.
The odd rock goes home.
This is a do or die moment right now.
Guys, can the eight of us agree that none of us are willing to give up our games for
either one of these two?
I don't want to go home tonight.
I don't think anybody wants to go home tonight.
So let the eight of us come to a decision on one or the other because I'm not going
home.
And if I can pitch something, I really do believe that Zeke is playing the best game
of the people up here, but if you really believe that I am, then fine, just vote me out next.
But tonight it has to be Zeke.
David is never going to let me stay in this game and neither is Adam.
Who wants to vote Hannah?
Right here.
You wanted Jessica.
I was trying to get you to actually go home with that plan.
Who did you vote for?
You voted for Chris.
You said you wanted to vote for Chris.
I never said that and I didn't vote for Chris.
I don't want to draw rocks.
I do not want to draw rocks.
Well, it's going to go there.
So what I'm hearing right now is complete disarray.
We don't have a unanimous decision.
Wow.
So here's what has now happened.
Oh, boy.
Because you guys can't control your own fate by coming to an agreement, Hannah, who was in trouble, is safe.
Zeke, who is in trouble, is safe.
Jay has immunity.
He's safe.
Ken has the immunity idol thanks to David.
So six people will draw rocks.
Will, Brett, Sunday, Adam, David and Jessica.
One of you is about to go home after 30 days in Survivor by making the biggest move you can in this game, going to rocks.
Wow.
There are five white rocks.
There was one black rock.
White means you're safe.
Black means you're going home.
All right.
Oh, my God.
Grab it and don't look.
Jeff, I think I'm going to cry.
All right.
Million-dollar rock draw.
Black means you are out of this game.
Reveal.
Oh, my God.
Jessica.
Sorry, Jessica.
I didn't want to go to rock.
David did.
Oh, my God.
You played a great game.
Great job, Jessica.
Jessica, I think it's more appropriate tonight to say the game has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
We drew rocks.
Now I'm out of the game.
I found the legacy advantage, but since I'm not in the game anymore, I have to will this to somebody.
So I am leaving this legacy advantage to Ken, and I hope that he will be able to do it.
I'm going to go to rock.
I found the legacy advantage to Ken.
And I hope that he is here on day 36 so he can take advantage of whatever is contained within this envelope.
Well, drawing rocks is the ultimate survivor, all-in move.
And with this many people making an all-in move, it says the rest of this game is going to be insane.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
I'm gonna set back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor, David gets a glimmer of hope.
David, I'm ready to start playing this game hard.
I'm an endangered species, but there was music to my ears.
And the loved ones visit.
I think it is a perfect time for love.
Oh, my God.
Eclipse the game.
I actually have an advantage in this game.
This truly has been the most incredible experience that I could have ever hoped for.
I'm incredibly proud of myself that I've made it as far as I have, but if I had just switched
my vote to Hannah, I wouldn't be sitting here right now.
Hannah would be.
Oh, my God.
I'm so proud of you.