Hello, Survivor fans.
We are live backstage
at CBS in Los Angeles
for the two-hour season finale
of Survivor: Game Changers.
Here they are, the Game Changers.
The season players.
You knew it was going
to be bloody when
when Nalcolm went out
early, Sandra was dethroned.
Even this nut, Tony, couldn't
get any traction.
This season had some of the most
Intertaining and risky game play
ever, and the good news,
it's not over.
More history will happen tonight.
All right, here's what's going on.
We have a two-hour season finale.
We're going to read the votes.
We'll announce the winner.
Then we bring everybody on stage
for the live reunion show,
and there is a lot to cover.
Including one of the
most talked about
moments in the history of Survivor:
when Zeke was outed
as being transgender.
If you have questions or
comments for the group
it's not o late, you can
hit me up at @JEFFPROBST
at Twitter, hashtag #SURVIVORFINALE.
Also tonight, we are going
to show you what
we are doing next season.
We have a packed
house here on CBS.
They are ready.
I know you are.
Here's the deal.
Six people left.
Tai has patiently held
on to two idols.
Troyzan has an idol.
Sarah has the Legacy Advantage.
It's a lot of game-changing
power still left in the game.
And once again, we go into a
finale still very uncertain who
will take home
the title of Survivor
and the million dollars.
Here it is, the season
finale of Survivor.
For the first time
ever, we brought 20 of
Survivor's biggest game
changers to Fiji
to battle against each other.
You gotta go big or go home.
The game play started early.
They're going to be looking
for spy shacks.
They ain't going to be looking
for an underground bunker.
And the players lift up
to their high.
Crazy!
As they revolutionizinged Survivor again.
With bold moves...
wild game play...
I was loyal to you completely
and you crushed my heart!
It's frustrating, and i'm pissed!
and unforgettable Tribal Councils.
What the hell is
going on here, Jeff?
Oh, my gosh!
Where risky idol plays...
I'm going to give the idol to...
pretty lady.
I'm going to vomit.
epic face-offs...
J.T.
Damn!
and raw emotion.
I didn't want to be, like,
the tran Survivor player,
i want to be Zeke
the Survivor player.
- And you are.
- And i feel like i am.
All led to a slew
of devastating blindsides.
The tribe has spoken.
And at the last Tribal Council...
There is a rat in this group,
so i am going
to steal Sarah's vote.
Well, actually,
that's my advantage.
It's nontransferable.
It says it on the bottom.
Cirie, sarah is the only person
who can use that advantage.
a foiled attempt by
Cirie to flip the game
upside down resulted in more chaos.
You know what, Jeff?
I'm going to use my advantage.
Whose vote are you
going to steal?
I'm going to take Tai's.
And Michaela was
sent to the jury.
Michaela, the tribe has spoken.
Leaving everyone scrambling for
a seat in the final three.
Now, only six remain.
Sarah, since the merge, she has
played an aggressive game,
bouncing from one alliance to
another taking out anyone
standing in her way.
Sierra.
I will be giving it to Sarah.
It worked.
With the Legacy Advantage
guaranteeing her a
spot in the final five, she is
in a power position
to shift the game again.
I deserve to be a Game Changer.
I didn't leave my son for 39
days to not win $1 million.
Troyzan, for weeks,
he has quietly played
from the bottom.
Oh, my god!
Good job, guys!
But with a hidden
immunity idol still in his pocket,
and alliances in turmoil,
the timing may be right
for Troyzan to make a move.
When everything is not
looking your way, there is
something always in you,
Troyzan, that is going to click
and say: "Never give up,
you can make it through anything."
Tai, his uncanny ability to
find hidden immunity idols...
Holy cow!
Survivor gods really looked at me.
and his patience to not
play them leaves Tai in a
powerful position, with two idols
and only three Tribal
Councils remaining.
I'm not afraid to make big moves.
Because you want
to make big moves.
You have to take
the bull and own it.
Culpepper, his social
game was dominant early.
You've got to think about
what's best for your game.
Are you in it for him or you?
But since merge, he
has been on the wrong side
of the numbers.
I have to win immunity for me
to be able to make it another day.
With no immunity
idols or advantages,
winning challenges may
be of the only way Culpepper
can make it to the
Final Tribal Council.
Playing Survivor your
guard is always up.
And if you relax,
if you nap on the job,
you're going home.
Aubry, it's been another
season of highs and lows
for this strategic force.
Aubry has it!
It really felt great at the
immunity challenge winning.
but had a good
relationship with Andrea,
so, naturally, she's
killed off too.
But she is once again
within striking distance
of the end.
Can Aubry find her way back to
the final three or will she be
voted out for the first time in
her Survivor career.
I'm in deep doo-doo, but
that's the Aubry way, always
hanging on by the skin of my teeth.
Cirie, this Survivor
legend and perennial
fan favorite has once again
relied on social relationships
and savvy game play.
Tai sees Sarah as a threat.
I need to get Tai comfortable
enough to trust me.
Can i believe you?
When you see me stand up and
play that advantage, are you still
can't believe me?
Okay.
In her four seasons,
Cirie has never found an idol or
won an individual
immunity challenge.
You got it, Cirie.
But with the million
dollars once again in sight,
is this when it finally
all comes together?
To stay in this
game at this point,
you have to see everything.
And if you skip over the picture
that's right in front of you
because you're
looking down the road,
it will get your torch extinguished.
Trust me.
I know.
With six game-changing
players, three idols,
and the Legacy Advantage
still in play,
the stage is set for a wild
and historic finish.
Who will have what it takes to
outwit, outplay, and outlast all
the rest to win the million dollars
and the title of Sole Survivor.
Subtitulado por: TwiNe
All right, i want to
know who the rat was.
I want to know
what did Michaela do.
Nothing.
So it was just random...
I felt betrayed by
Cirie at Tribal Council
playing my "steal a vote."
So i targeted Michaela because
Michaela is Cirie's
right-hand man.
But now, i don't
know who i can trust.
Fortunately, i still have the
Legacy Advantage,
which can be played at six.
So i know i'm safe.
Tthat was my advantage
to use, not yours.
Why would you take my vote?
Because Tai said: "Sarah,
she's the biggest threat."
If somebody says your name--
You need to talk to me about this
if we're going to be in an
alliance together.
Because i wanted to use
that at another time
and now i can't because of you.
This is true, this is true.
I'm in a lot of trouble right now.
Sarah is really pissed and
thinks i'm trying to pull an
okey-doke on her.
And kind felt like:
"Whoa, i'm trying to do you a favor."
But as the saying goes: "No good
deed goes unpunished."
Hopefully there's something to
be saved, salvaged.
I don't know.
I want to know who the rat
was supposed to be exposed?
- Honestly?
- Yeah.
I felt that Tai was playing
you, me, and them.
Nope.
Aubry, you know?
You've been a part of those
conversations.
Tai said that we
should get Sarah out.
So i told him about the advantage.
Nope.
I didn't tell you
about my advantage?
Just found it out when?
- Before we go Tribal?
- Tonight.
You did tonight.
- Before we left.
- No.
Oh, my god.
Tai, are the one that threw
my name out there?
Just answer that honestly to me.
Was it you?
I did say that.
I just said: "Theoretically who is
the biggest threat?"
You were going to
vote me out tonight.
- Yes, because she told me--
- I apologize.
- I've been trying to tell you this.
Sarah.
- You and i--
- You know Tai...
I don't need to hear
anymore right now.
Please, hear me.
You're going to fucking
vote me out tonight!
I put my ass on
the line for you,
and i would have
gone home tonight
because you stabbed
me in the back.
So i don't need to hear anymore.
- She set me up, i thought--
- No, Tai!
With you.
Then why would
you vote me out?
I don't know.
I panicked.
Last time i played i didn't do
any lying, didn't do anything.
And this time i said
this is Game Changers.
I want to play a little bit.
I felt like i was doing what
everybody else was doing anyway
but i got caught.
Now i am Tai, the liar.
I think i screwed up my game,
now my options are limited.
Luckily, i still have two idols
that nobody knows about.
Maybe i can use
them to gain trust.
I need to have
someone to lean on.
I found one here, and found
one there with the same clue.
I was going to tell you
and Sarah at the same time.
I'm not, i'm not.
She's so pissed off.
- No, i´m not. I'm with you now.
- Okay.
I'll play it today, play it
tomorrow without telling you,
but i feel i owe you that.
Tell me what you
want me to do with it.
Just hold on to
it for right now.
Tai's whole game has imploded.
He's been caught in a web of lies.
He felt so bad this morning he
wanted to make amend with me
and told me he had two idols.
Now, do i really believe him?
I don't know.
I haven't really trusted Tai
since he voted out Sierra.
But if he's looking for a home,
i can definitely use him as a number.
I can help him get
further in the game,
but i have to have collateral.
You want to keep playing,
i'm your key.
- Yes.
- Don't fall into any trap.
- I'm not.
- We'll keep it locked.
I manipulated him
on the first one,
and i'm going to manipulate
him on these two as well.
He lied to me numerous times.
I have no problem throwing him
under the bus voting him out
with his own idol.
Come on in, guys!
Day 36, six people left.
Shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
Yes.
First things first,
Culpepper, take it back.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to race through a giant
maze, collecting three bags of
puzzle pieces along the way.
Once you have all your bags,
you'll use the pieces inside to
solve a compass rose puzzle.
First to finish wins immunity,
safe from the vote.
Losers, tribal council, where
somebody will be the 15th
person voted out of this game
and become the eighth member of
our jury.
In addition, you're
playing for reward.
The winner will have delivered
to them at camp chicken parm.
Oh, man!
Spaguetti with meat sauce.
Garlic bread, and key lime pie...
- Damn!
- for dessert.
Worth playing for?
Yeah.
We'll draw spots and get it on.
Here we go, for immunity.
Guaranteed spot in the final
five, and a nice reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
There are two sides to this maze.
Troyzan, Aubry, and Cirie are
working one side.
Culpepper, Tai, and Sarah
working the other.
You have three bags
total that you have to
collect from your side.
That's it.
Once you have all three bags,
you start working on that puzzle.
Troyzan at his first station.
Culpepper heading to his first station.
Tai right on his tail.
Troyzan has his first bag.
He's heading back.
Culpepper coming
back with his first bag.
Culpepper takes a big fall!
Tai right behind him.
Tai falling down now!
Troyzan is back with his first bag.
Culpepper coming
back with his first bag.
Tai right behind him.
Literally just following the
path that Culpepper is leading.
Culpepper drops his first,
heads back out.
Tai heading back out
for his second bag.
Aubry has her first bag.
Cirie now has her first bag.
Sarah has her first bag.
She's heading back.
After 36 days,
who wants it more?
Cirie right on Aubry's tail now.
Sarah has her first.
She's looking for her second.
Troyzan is in the lead.
He has that second bag.
Culpepper at the second station.
And once again, Tai is just
trying to follow Culpepper.
Aubry untying that second bag.
She's heading back now.
Troyzan drops his second bag.
But he dropped it
at the wrong puzzle.
I'm color blind.
I'll take it!
Culpepper back with
his second bag.
He has distanced himself from Tai.
It is Aubry, Troyzan, Culpepper,
and Tai all looking for their
third and final bag
as Sarah and Cirie
head back with their second.
Sarah looking lost in that maze.
Aubry trying to get
to that third station.
And she's done it!
Aubry has her third bag.
She starts untying.
She's heading back.
Culpepper's now racing
back with his third bag.
Sarah back out now.
Culpepper will be back first.
He can start working on that puzzle.
Aubry right behind Culpepper.
Here comes Cirie.
It is Culpepper, Cirie,
Aubry and Troyzan with the
early lead working
on their puzzles.
Huge stakes, guaranteed
certainty tonight at Tribal.
There are 41 pieces in this puzzle.
All you have to do is
figure out where they go.
Tai back with his third bag.
Sarah coming back
with her third bag.
36 days in, you
want to get to 37.
you will most
definitely earn it.
A lot of these pieces require
another piece or two.
You have to figure out where
they go, remember,
and then find the supporting
piece that goes with it.
Right now it is Culpepper and
Aubry with the most pieces placed.
Sarah's got a couple
of pieces in there.
Slow going for Tai right now.
Both Cirie and Troyzan taking
a different approach,
studying their pieces first.
Sarah working methodically.
Now Culpepper pulling pieces
out, trying to rearrange them.
It is difficult.
But once you start to figure out
how this puzzle working,
you can get on a roll.
Culpepper with another piece.
Sarah with another piece.
Aubry starting to fall behind.
Tai struggling.
Troyzan trying to get in on this.
Cirie has yet to place
a single piece.
Culpepper down to 12 pieces left.
Sarah slowly, piece by piece,
gaining on Brad's lead.
But it's Sarah and
Culpepper right now
battling it out for immunity.
Culpepper now down
to six pieces left.
Sarah trying to catch up.
Can she do it?
Culpepper reworking it now.
Sarah looking for
the right pieces.
Culpepper down to his last piece
but something isn't right.
Culpepper now searching
bags for a missing piece.
And it's been in his
bag the entire time.
Will that make a difference?
Can Sarah catch Culpepper?
Culpepper adds another.
Culpepper down to
his last two pieces.
It would be his third
individual immunity win.
And he does.
Culpepper wins individual
immunity and reward!
Guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Holy shit!
Pretty good for a dumb jock.
Culpepper, come on over.
For the third time, individual
immunity is yours.
You are safe
tonight at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out of this game.
In addition, you have won reward.
Choose one person that will join
you at camp to enjoy this meal.
Troy.
Didn't even hesitate
with Troyzan.
He hasn't been on
anything in a long time.
Troyzan going to
enjoy the meal tonight.
Thank you so much.
Choose one more person.
Everybody hungry.
Big decision because you are
choosing one person
to eat with you and
three that will not.
- Sarah.
- Sarah, come on over.
All right, so here's
what's going to happen.
You guys are all
going back to camp.
Food will be delivered
for you three.
After you eat, i will see you
tonight at Tribal, where
somebody will be the 15th
person voted out of this game
and become the
eighth member of the jury.
It will not be you.
Congrats.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp, guys.
See you guys at tribal.
Given the drama that happened
at the last Tribal Council,
i'm not really sure
where i stand with people.
And this reward is
what i needed.
I've got to find out who is
willing to go to the end with me
And i'm going to do whatever i
have to do to solidify my spot.
This is insane.
I cannot even tell you
how good this tastes.
The fact that Brad won
is just outstanding.
Brad and i, we're
as solid as it gets.
So if he wins, i win.
And i have an idol which i can
play either tonight or the next
Tribal Council, which
makes me feel safe.
So i feel like i'm
in a good place.
But we've got stuff to do.
We have to win immunities.
We have to play immunity idols.
We have to be smart.
Nice done Brad Culpepper.
Amazing victory.
Thank you, Brad.
I've got the Legacy Advantage,
and nobody knows about it.
So i'm lucky that i'm safe tonight.
But at this point, i
have to go with people
that are gonna take
me to the end.
I felt betrayed by Cirie at
Tribal Council, and Tai,
i clearly can't trust him.
So the only choice i have right
now is to go with Brad and Troy.
Who do you guys
want to vote out, though?
I think we put votes on Tai
and votes on Aubry.
I really think Aubry is a
bigger immunity threat than him.
- Let's all three vote Aubry.
- Okay.
Tai informed me this
morning he has two idols.
That puts Tai in a power
position that makes me super
leery because i've seen
him flip a couple of times.
So i need to get back to camp
and make sure everybody is on
the right page because i don't
want any funky business
with two idols tonight.
What's up?
Do you want to go to the end?
Okay.
Good.
Here's the plan.
Aubry's going home.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You're going to give me
your other one to hold.
because i don't want
any funny business.
It's just i need a leap of faith
from you because
of the way things have been.
I know.
Brad come back, and he said:
"This is what needs to happen.
Aubry's going home, but...
in order to gain
complete trust from me,
you can't have both idols.
You need to give me one."
You want to go to the end,
that's what you've got to do.
Listen, every single Tribal
Council i have gone to
has not gone as i expected.
And i'm not going in there
tonight with you playing an idol
and somebody else playing an
idol, and it all goes haywire.
Well, maybe you did.
It's in my hands.
Your destiny now is
tonight, and that's it.
You've done that.
But if i do that, he'll
bring me to the final three.
I said: "great, now i
belong somewhere."
But the back of my mind, i worry
if i give the idol to Brad,
he'll make a fool out of me.
Not right now, i have to
think this through.
Tai showed me his two idols
and i'm like: "holy crap."
I guess in some way he's
reaching out like:
"I want to be a trustworthy guy,"
but at the same time,
he's still acting sketchy.
The thing is he could play it
tonight, he could play it tomorrow.
And then confirm his 4th position.
Yeah.
So tonight i will play with you.
Em, i need...
Are you being
straight with me, Tai?
- I'm being so straight with you.
- I know, i know.
I know, Tai, after everything,
it's hard for you to trust me.
I understand that.
However, if we don't do anything,
they're going to just
pick us off one by one.
At this point, Sarah,
Troyzan, and Brad
just came from the reward.
And i'm not sure
what they discussed.
After last night's Tribal, i'd
be surprised if they weren't
going to come after me.
So i tried to tell Tai that we need
to put all our differences aside
and come together and get
on rid one of those three.
We can't do Brad.
It's either Sarah or Troyzan.
We have to do something.
I promise i won't betray you.
I swear, right hand to god,
i promise i won't screw you, Tai.
The only thing is, Tai knows
everything that happened to him
last night was because of me, so
i'm sure he doesn't trust me.
Please, Tai, i'm sorry.
- Go, go.
- Okay, okay.
I don't know.
Once again, i feel like my
life in the game is in Tai's
hands, which kind of sucks
because 10 minutes before
Tribal, he's having
an emotional breakdown.
Like what?
- Tai has two idols.
- He's got two?
Yeah.
So did he give
Brad one of them?
Not yet.
I can't decide what to do.
Brad, he ordered me around.
It's like a threat.
At the same time,
i don't trust Cirie at all.
Are we sure he's
going to vote with us?
I don't know.
- What else do we have right now?
- Nothing.
I don't know.
I need to toughen up.
I'm still here.
I still have two idols.
And i just have to figure
out what's best for me.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie,
Zeke, Sierra, Andrea
and Michaela voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, let's
get straight into it.
Aubry, what was your take on the
fallout from the last Tribal?
There was a lot of talking
when we went back to camp.
It was kind of a therapy
session, and we kind of got to
the bottom of what things were.
What conclusion did you come to?
That we had a rat in our midst.
- Tai.
Is that what happened?
You went back to camp,
and all the fingers ended
up pointing at you?
Yes, it did.
It's a game of lie and deceive.
Everybody lies.
Everybody deceives.
But somehow,
i was the only bad guy
here and i take all the blame.
But you were going
to vote me out!
- No.
- That's a lie right there.
Because Cirie told me you
were targeting me first.
This is a game of deceive
and a game of lying.
Everybody does that.
It sounds like Tai is
making the point that we were
all caught lying.
Why am i the one that's
getting the most heat?
The reason all the heat is
coming on Tai is because he's
not taking any
responsibility for his lies.
- I think this is so hypocritical.
- It's not.
I have not lied to you.
Your whole alliance wanted
you out yesterday.
Sarah, it's an interesting situation.
There's a group of six.
Three shared a reward today.
Are you concerned that with Brad
choising Troyzan and you, that
the appearance would be that
the three of are you tight,
and that might push these
three to try to do something?
I think at this point, you
have five people that are tight.
Meaning everybody but Tai?
Yeah.
Clearly, you can tell by the way
everybody's frustrated with Tai
that nobody's on the
same page as Tai right now.
Troyzan.
Is it likely that Tai could
recover this late in the game?
Honestly, i say no, like, 90% no.
Cirie.
Have you ever seen somebody
in this kind of a hole before?
This game is like no other.
I've seen people in
worse holes than this
and somehow make it to the end.
So i never say never.
So, Tai, where are you
right now, emotionally, day 36?
You've made it to six.
You have a lot of enemies right now.
They all say i'm doing all the lying.
On top of that, there was a
conversation with me already.
A lot of offers, a lot of bribes.
Like threaten as well.
So you're saying people
came to you and offered
- to make a deal with you.
- Yes.
Culpepper, are you
surprised to hear Tai say he was
approached today with offers?
No, i mean, we're late in the game.
You need numbers.
So it makes sense that someone
would try to repair something
for a vote.
Does it concern you?
Buyer beware if you
try to do a deal with Tai.
It could maybe benefit you
or bite you in the ass.
Tai, what do you think
is going to happen tonight?
The only thing i know is my
vote, who i'm writing down.
That's the only
thing i can tell you.
How about you, Cirie?
How confident are you
about tonight's vote?
I feel as confident as the
people around me that i can trust.
Which is not saying a lot.
Wow, Aubry.
This game truly is alive
and moving moment by moment.
You think there's something
stable, and then it shifts.
I don't know.
I feel like i've been kind of
hanging on by the bottom rung,
and i'm going to
keep the faith tonight.
All right, is is time to vote.
Sarah, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Jeff.
The blue idol i'd like
to play for myself.
Okay.
And i have another one.
A red one.
I would like it play for Aubry.
Thanks, Tai.
These are both hidden
immunity idols.
Any votes cast for Tai and
Aubry, will not count.
Hey, Jeff.
This is a secret advantage which
is a Legacy Advantage.
This is only good for right now
and i don't need a souvenir.
- So there you go.
- All right.
This is the Legacy Advantage.
Any votes cast for
Sarah will not count.
Jeff.
I'm going to get on the
immunity train and give you that,
because i just feel like
being in the final five.
All right.
This is also a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for
Troyzan will not count.
So, any votes cast for Tai,
Aubry, Sarah, Troyzan, will not count.
You could not vote for Culpepper.
He had immunity, which means
Cirie, it doesn't matter what
votes are in the urn,
because the only person
who can receive votes...
What?
Is me.
Is you.
And for what it's worth,
not a single vote in here
has your name on it.
This is a historic Tribal Council.
Most idols ever played
at a Tribal, three.
Most people ever
safe at a Tribal, five.
And the most significant and
devastating part of tonight's
history-making Tribal for you,
Cirie, is you become the first
person in 34 seasons to be
voted out simply because their
literally is no other choice.
There's no need to revote.
Wow.
Cirie, you came out here
11 years ago to play this game.
You've played it four times now.
You famously got up off the couch
to see what you were made of.
You had another moment this
season where you conquered
a personal obstacle.
If this is the end
of your Survivor run,
what is the story?
This has been one of the most
grand experiences of my life.
It changed me.
I would have never done
any of this stuff if i...
didn't get off that
couch 11 years ago.
I would never have met
so many different people.
I would have never had so
many amazing experiences.
So it's bittersweet.
However, i'm going out in grand
style, it never happened before.
And it just makes this
experience that much more
special for me.
Cirie, how many days
of Survivor have you played now?
Not enough.
Cirie, i have to say,
you have played every day of
Survivor with grace.
And it has been
an honor to have you,
be a part of the Survivor family.
You are the 15th voted out
of this season.
You become the
eighth member of the jury.
- You need to grab your torch.
- Sure.
Cirie, you want to say it?
The tribe has spoken.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Time for you to go.
Thank you, Cirie.
Well, a Survivor legend
goes out in legendary style.
You have made
it to the final five.
But this game is
clearly far from over.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
It's a very bittersweet
moment for me.
But i'm so thankful to
have had every single day.
I'm going to encourage my boys
and my family to get off the
couch and live because look at
what you miss out on
if you don't try.
Look out, world. You never know
where you might see Cirie.
Well, they don't come
much classier than Cirie.
Cirie, come out here.
So close, and once again, a
unique set of circumstances.
Come here, girl!
Look at that!
Oh, my god!
What does that feel
like, a standing ovation?
Take it in.
You've given a lot.
Take some back.
Thank you. All right, let's
hear what she has to say.
So, Cirie, first, that.
and, you know, it's interesting
to me that i rarely comment on
somebody personally in Survivor.
I try to remain neutral,
even though people
would say that's not true.
But with you, in that moment, it
was undeniable to say what a
part of this and
what you represent.
So what is it like to come out
here after a decade of exposing
yourself to all of your
vulnerabilities
and feel that love?
It's amazing.
I don't feel worthy.
It's... life changing.
It just... it tells the world
what a great thing a great game
this is, and what...
you can accomplish
if you just try.
these people would have never
known Cirie Fieldes.
I'm going to hug you now.
Oh, you're one of a kind.
Survivor: Game Changers,
season finale.
So far from over.
Next time i see you,
i'll have the votes.
Enjoy it, woman!
Take a bow!
Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
First things first, for the
third time, Culpepper other i
will take it back.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to use
paddles to maneuver
a ball through a
series of obstacles.
If the ball drops, you go back
to the start and begin again.
The first person to
transfer three balls
to the finish wins immunity.
Safe from the vote, guaranteed
a spot in the final four.
Losers, Tribal Council, where
somebody will be the 16th
person voted out of Survivor,
become the ninth
member of our jury.
We'll draw for spots
and we'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Guaranteed spot
in the final four.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Definitely a learning curve
to this challenge.
You're going to be dropping
balls and starting over.
That's part of it.
Sarah working on that first transition.
She's got it.
Culpepper makes that first transition.
Tai is through his first obstacle.
Sarah's through that second obstacle.
Culpepper working around that
second obstacle.
Tai now heading for
the second obstacle.
Tai drops.
He's got to go back.
Sarah navigates
that third obstacle.
Culpepper right at the third obstacle.
Aubry and Troyzan struggling to
get out of the gate.
Culpepper neither
that final obstacle.
Sarah right behind him.
It's Culpepper and Sarah at the
same spot in the challenge.
Culpepper makes the final transition.
Sarah does not.
Sarah has to go back.
Culpepper now very close to the
finish with his first ball.
Culpepper drops and has his
first of three balls.
Culpepper now
knows it is possible.
He can do it.
Tai, Aubry, Troyzan trying to
get something going.
Aubry having no luck at all.
Sarah now at the third obstacle.
Culpepper now at the third obstacle.
But he's on his second ball.
Culpepper navigates it now,
heading into that final obstacle.
Sarah still sitting
on that third obstacle,
ball really moving and it drops.
Sarah once again losing
all of her progress,
has to begin again.
Culpepper very close to
finishing his second ball.
Culpepper has his second ball.
One ball left for immunity.
It would be culpepper's fourth
individual immunity win and
would put him within striking
distance of the Survivor
record, which is five, held by a
very small and elite group.
Troyzan at the fourth
and final obstacle.
He's got to move.
Troyzan drops.
All progress lost.
Has to start again.
Nobody else even close.
Culpepper working his way up
that final obstacle.
Aubry just going to watch now.
It would be a dominating fourth
individual immunity win
within one of the record.
Culpepper wins his fourth
individual immunity!
Guaranteed a spot in the final four!
Culpepper, come on over.
Where is the emotion?
What's happening?
- That one was for her?
- Yeah, yeah.
Fourth individual immunity win.
Culpepper is guaranteed a
spot in the final four.
You will see day 38.
As for everybody else, for
somebody, this is the end.
Tribal Councin tonight.
Somebody will be the 16th
person voted out of this game
and the ninth
member of our jury.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Brad smoked us all, and the
tough part is Brad doesn't seem
to really want to work with me.
So i feel like i could
be going home.
So i'm going to make
a pitch to save myself,
but i need the numbers right now.
Nicely done!
I've got one of
those in my house.
Oh, gosh!
I won my fourth individual
immunity today.
Walking into those challenges,
i'm so focused on what i've got
to do that all i think about is
the challenge itself.
Being a part of the
record is a side note.
My eyes are on the prize
and i think i'm really close to
be able to take the bell.
You're looking kind of
golden right now, buddy.
We want Aubry out, correct?
- Correct
- Okay.
My alliance is solid with
Brad and Sarah is with us as well.
That's a majority.
So we're going to vote out Aubry
next because when it comes to
the final Tribal Council
speeches, Tai is easier to beat.
But you tell me what's
been easy in this game,
and i'll be like this.
This is... zero.
Nothing's been easy.
I think that there are some
very clear things in this game.
Like, if i'm not here tomorrow
and Brad wins immunity again,
you guys have a 50% shot of
making the final three because
he's keeping Troyzan, no matter.
- If we get rid of Troy--
- It maximizes.
We have to pick
between the two of us.
If Brad wins the immunity
challenge tomorrow
he will be taking Troyzan
to the finale with him.
Then Sarah and Tai
each have a 50% shot
at vying for that final spot.
If, however, we make a move
tonight together to take out
Troyzan, that leaves
two spots open.
I don't want to be
wiped out by the boys.
I agree.
After we have worked together
off and on or whatever.
This is a chance to say, look,
we actually pulled it together
- when it mattered.
- Right.
I agree.
The story of my game
this whole season is
i'm always in the middle.
So i've got a decision
to make tonight.
But first, i need to make sure
that i can trust Tai.
- We're good, right, you and i?
- Well, are we?
Yes, yeah.
Because you were--
If you knew out of
anyone in this entire game
you are the one person they
cared about the whole time.
And that's why i got so hurt.
Tai, i'm telling you, i've
had your back the whole game.
- I know.
- So...
give me what you would
like to do, and i'll tell you if
i think it's a good idea or not.
I think get Aubry out.
Is that what you
want to do, Aubry?
If you want to,
i'm okay with that.
- Are you okay with that?
- Yeah.
I love Aubry as a person.
But she's also
a really good player.
So she's the one who needs to go
home because i can't beat her.
- I'll shake with you right now.
- I'll shake with you.
- We're not going home tonight.
- We're voting out Aubry.
- Okay.
- Perfect.
I control who goes to the final four.
- I do.
- Yes, you do.
I can control who goes to final four.
I give you to tomorrow, you
have to assure me from here on out,
you're voting whatever i vote.
Okay?
It's not complicated.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Do you understand that?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Do you believe that?
- I believe it.
You're very sincere. Every time
you say it, i believe it.
It's not about me.
It's what you believe.
Are you really got have my back
tonight and tomorrow night?
I will have your back tonight
and tomorrow night.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll see what you vote because
i'm going to be here tomorrow.
Brad and i happen to want the
same thing, but the way he
talked to me is, like, i am the
minority or subserveiant or
something.
It's not an equal partnership.
He has no respect for me.
He's intimidating big time to me
because i'm a little guy.
He said if i don't want to go
home tonight, i have to make him
- a promise.
- Okay.
That i vote whatever
he tell me tonight.
And he said i have no choice but
to go with him plans.
I don't take orders from nobody.
- We can flip on him.
- Okay, okay.
And vote Troyzan, we
flip on him tonight.
Tonight is huge.
This could be a million-dollar move.
And sure enough, Tai is
changing his mind
again at the last minute.
Tonight is actually the
biggest vote of the game.
It's going to determine who will
be in the final four.
So Tai and i have to
figure out which way to go.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie, Zeke,
Sierra, Andrea, Michaela
and Cirie, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, so let's
get straight into it.
Culpepper's fourth
individual immunity win.
Troyzan, what's the feeling for
you when you see it happening
again and again?
Because we're at the point in
the game now where Culpepper
could win his way to the end.
Yeah, it's tough, you know.
The last time i played,
you know, i felt like
challenges were my deal.
And looking at this guy just
romp through it like it's nothing.
It's tough to see and it's, you
know, i'm hoping that the next
challenge, if i'm there, will be
something right down my alley.
Aubry, why are you
smiling during this?
We're talking about Culpepper
dominating, and you're smiling.
I mean, that's Survivor.
Sometimes it's with you,
and sometimes it's not.
Where is it for you tonight?
I'm definitely on the
chopping block.
So, Sarah, what does
the conversation center around
with five people left?
People are just trying to
survive one day at a time right now.
It's kind of where the
conversation circulates is how
do i make it through
tonight's Tribal Council?
So, Troyzan, is everybody
pitching everybody?
Yeah, pretty much, that's how
it goes because this is where
it's critical that you basically
negotiate yourself
into a final three thing.
Aubry, this really is
about final three at this point.
It is.
And you know the social dynamics
and you can make some logical
conclusions about where things
are going, and i believe that
Brad and Troyzan will be two of
the spots in the final three if
one of them wins
immunity tomorrow.
So if someone wants to have a
higher chance of going to the
end, there's another way to go.
Which would be voting out Troyzan.
That's only option.
You can't vote out Culpepper.
Yes.
- Tai, did Aubry pitch you this?
- Yeah.
Aubry has talked to me
about it with percentage.
It's interesting argument and
i'm taking that into consideration.
Sarah, what would be
the advantage of going with
Aubry's strategy?
At that point, that's where
you have to start considering
who you're willing to put on the
jury and who you would like to
sit next to.
And what's right for me, what's
right for Aubry, what's right
for Tai could all be the same
thing or they could all be
different things.
I'm not sure.
Troyzan are, you aware
that there's this feeling
that you and
Culpepper are connected?
Not as much as Aubry says
because that's her opinion.
How do you know... i don't win
immunity and there's two spots
left with me.
So, hello.
Culpepper, just because
you have immunity today
doesn't mean you can sit on your
hands because you have to make
sure that if you don't win the
next challenge, you've got a shot.
Absolutely.
I mean, i've talked to everybody
just like everybody else talked
to everybody else.
But from what i'm hearing
tonight sounds like i have to
win to get in.
Culpepper, are there
people in the game for you think
if i go to the end with them,
i'm not sure i could win?
Yes.
How about you, Sarah, people
you are concerned you can't beat?
- Absolutely.
- Tai.
- Yup, definitely.
- How about you, Aubry?
Yeah, there are people i
think i can't beat.
- Troyzan.
- No.
- So you feel confident.
- Yes.
Wow.
Sarah, it is interesting
that Aubry's case is
against Troyzan, and Troyzan is
the one guy that says:
"I can beat anybody
here in this game."
You know, if Troyzan feels he
can beat everybody here,
then maybe he's not
someone i want to go with.
So if it's about a final three
right now tonight,
then you better pick
the right final three.
All right, it is time to vote.
Aubry, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the tribal council area inmediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Aubry.
Troyzan.
One vote Aubry, one vote Troyzan.
Aubry.
Two votes Aubry,
one vote Troyzan.
16th person voted out and
the ninth member of our jury: Aubry.
That's three, that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Aubry, the tribe has spoken.
You can leave it here.
Well, you've made it
to the final four.
Tomorrow, you will compete in
your final immunity challenge.
You are this close.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
I decide to not be cagey and
go for broke in Tribal, but
Survivor has taught me you
can't control everything, and i
gave it my best shot.
And i took everything that i
could from the experience.
I'm so excited to be on the jury.
I''m so freaking excited to
watch these psychopaths.
Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys
ready to get to your final
- inmmunity challenge?
- Yes.
First things first,
Culpepper, for the fourth time,
i will take it back.
For the last time, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to race through an
obstacle and down a giant water
slide collecting bags of puzzle
pieces as you go.
Once you have all three bags,
you'll use the pieces inside to
solve a lighthouse puzzle.
First to finish guarantees
themselves a spot at that final
Tribal Council.
Losers, one of you will be the
17th person voted out and
the tenth and final
member of our jury.
This is the biggest
challenge of the game.
Win, you go to the end.
Lose, you may not.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
Good luck.
All right, here we go.
Final immunity, guaranteed a
spot at that Final Tribal Council.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First job, untie those knots,
get that for us ring of keys and
head through the obstacle.
Who will be out
of the gate first?
It is Culpepper.
Then Sarah.
Then Tai and Troyzan.
Got to make your way through
that first obstacle.
Halfway through, you're going to
get your first bag of pieces and
you've got multiple keys.
You need a little luck right
here to find the right one as
fast as possible.
Sarah has her first bag.
Troyzan has his first bag.
Sarah flying through this obstacle.
Culpepper now has his first bag.
Tai has his first bag.
Troyzan heading down.
Sarah heading up for
her second set of keys.
Troyzan heading back out.
Culpepper and Tai side by side
with their first bags,
down the pole they go.
Get them on the
table and head out!
It is Sarah up the slide first.
You have to untie
that second set of keys.
Sarah has it, down the slide.
That's how you do it!
Culpepper has his
second set of keys.
Troyzan working on his second set.
Troyzan has his keys.
He's headed down.
Culpepper heading down now with
his second set of keys.
Here comes Tai!
Sarah releases her second
bag, still in the lead.
Troyzan at his second bag.
Culpepper is at his second bag.
Tai at his second bag.
Everybody trying keys now as
Sarah extends her lead.
Culpepper's got his
second set heading down.
Troyzan still working
on his second set.
Tai has his second
set of puzzle pieces.
He's heading down.
Sarah has her third
and final set of keys.
Tai heading up now.
Troyzan still trying to
release that second set.
He is losing a lot of time.
Sarah in the lead.
Culpepper in second.
Then Tai.
Here comes Culpepper.
He's good to go heading through
the obstacle for the final time.
Tai has his third set of keys.
Troyzan finally has
his second bag.
Sarah now working on her third
and final bag of puzzle pieces.
Culpepper right behind her.
Here comes Troyzan.
Trying to get back in this.
Tai now heading
for his third bag.
Culpepper gets his quickly!
It is now Culpepper in the lead.
Sarah taking a long time,
has lost her lead.
Sarah now has her third bag.
It is Culpepper and Sarah now
working on their puzzle.
Tai has his third bag.
Troyzan has his third and final
set of keys!, let's go!
It is Tai, Culpepper and Sarah.
Troyzan needs to get lucky
quickly and find the right key
fast if he's going to be in this.
Final immunity challenge, all
the marbles, right here.
Troyzan has his third bag.
He's back in this!
Everybody is in this.
This is what you want in the
final challenge of Survivor,
everybody competing for the win.
Tai has his first piece.
Culpepper has his first piece.
Culpepper has his second piece.
Troyzan looking for the first
piece, and he's got it.
Culpepper with the third piece.
Sarah just looking
to get on the board.
Culpepper with his fourth piece.
Tai with his second piece.
Culpepper with his fifth piece.
He took the lead at the very end
and does not want
to give it up now.
Tai with the third piece.
Sarah still struggling.
Now he's got one as
Culpepper adds another.
Tai with his fourth piece.
Sarah adds a piece.
Culpepper down to his last piece.
He just needs the top.
Now you've got to untie your
three number tiles and use them
to solve a combination lock.
That holds the top of the
lighthouse, so you are close,
but not there yet.
Tai with a fifth piece.
Tai is the only one who has a
shot right now at catching Culpepper.
Culpepper has it.
He's got the top!
For the win.
Culpepper wins his fifth
individual immunity,
guaranteed a spot
at the Final Tribal Council!
Where he will get a chance to
plead his case for the million
dollars and the title
of Sole Survivor.
Culpepper, come on over.
Hello, my old friend.
Once again, immunity is yours.
A couple of significant things.
With this win, you join a very
small group of people who have
won five individual immunity
challenges in a single season.
The bigger news, with this win,
you are guaranteed a spot at
the Final Tribal.
One big decision left in this
game, who will go to the final
three with you, and who will
become the tenth and final
member of our jury, their
dream falling this short.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you guys at Tribal.
Congrats.
After winning five immunity
challenges i'm clearly in
control of this game.
I'm in the final three, and
quite frankly, i think i can
beat every single one of them
but as for tonight, Tai has
betrayed me this entire game
and so he's going home
and it's good to be the king.
Dude!
- Oh, my god.
- You did it.
He did a lot better than i
thought he would.
I know.
I knew i was going to win
that challenge.
I was so prepared mentally, that
in my head i had already won it
before i started.
and this necklace makes me
Superman, makes me bulletproof.
I'm going to the final three and
it's my decision who is going
home and it comes down to who
has done me wrong the most.
And that would be Tai.
- Just let him down easy.
- No, no.
- No?
- No.
- It's my island right now.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm just throwing it out there.
- I know, i know.
But i'd rather him think he's
got some glimmer of hope,
and i'm going to let
him down at Tribal.
He's done nothing but backstab
me this whole game.
I said: "buddy, give me an idol
and we'll go to the end."
Right.
He did not give me the idol.
He played the idol.
Were you going to fulfill that?, no.
- No.
- Okay.
You're going in
and Sarah is going in.
As far as jury is concerned,
after winning five immunity
challenges, i know i can beat
both Troyzan and Sarah, because
after football, i became a trial
attorney, so i think i can sell
my case better to the jury.
So i'm in control, and Tai is going
to get what he deserves.
I know.
One of us is going home.
Yeah.
Right now, i think the most
obvious, logical conclusion is
Brad will vote me out for
betraying himself so many times
and now my life's on the line.
- It's whoever those who vote for.
- Yeah.
How?
And we both go to final together.
Brad and Troyzan have been
tight the entire game, so,
clearly, they're going to make a
move against me or Tai.
So he said let's vote for
Troyzan, and force a tie, which
would come down to
a fire-making challenge.
I have to consider it.
Even though it scares
the crap out of me.
I'm not super good at fire.
I don't think Troyzan is very
good at making fire.
- Yeah, probably not.
- No.
I think we can do it.
Brad's pretty cocky right now
and thinks he's calling the shots.
But i'm thinking, screw that.
If i can win a fire-making
challenge, i can decide who's
going to the final three.
The jury hates me, they do.
Because i appear like a liar.
Yeah.
Tai's telling me that he can't win.
But he's made moves and found
three idols, so he has a resume.
However, Tai is so all
over the place,
he might have alienated the jury.
And then there's Troyzan, who
hasn't done anything without
Brad's permission
this whole game.
But at the same time,
he hasn't made anyone mad.
And Sandra won twice by not
making anyone mad.
How do you start... like,
what do you need to do?
- Okay.
- Watch the wind.
I think i can do it.
If i do this and win, i could
rack up a ton of points with the jury.
But i have to decide if this is
a risk that i'm willing to take.
It's a coin flip, and i've got
to pick heads or tails.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie, Zeke,
Sierra, Andrea, Michaela, Cirie
and Aubry, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, so, last big decision
to be made by you guys tonight,
who you're going to send over to
that jury and which three will
get to face the jury.
Culpepper, first, congratulations.
Your fifth individual immunity win.
Tell me about the moment
right after you won it.
It's an amazing feeling
when it happened.
I know i'm guaranteed a 39 day.
But now i've got to figure out
who we want to put on the jury,
so it's that could affect tomorrow's
vote and everything else.
Sarah when Culpepper says:
"now we have to decide who
to put on the jury,"
who is the "we"?
I think he's implying himself
and Troyzan, which would leave
Tai and myself on
the chopping block.
Tai, does that ring true?
That's absolutely true that
Sarah and i are at the bottom.
One of us is going
to go home tonight.
But if we work together,
our chance might go up.
Because we, obviously, can't
vote for Culpepper.
And if we join forces we
can vote for Troyzan.
- And force a tie.
- Force a tie.
So, Sarah, did you
guys talk about it?
Yeah.
That's exactly what could
happen tonight.
Where do you sit with that?
Because you're weighing a lot?
For me, personally, my decision
is going to come from who
do i want to sit
with in a final three?
But both of us get to the
final three, you know.
If i was Sarah, i would say,
well, you cannot be absolute sure.
I mean, Culpepper told me if i
gave him one of my idols for him
to hold on to, they
could buy back his trust.
I mean, he just
thinks like i'm so naive.
I'm like i have a brain.
It's common sense.
But you have no leverage.
I've got the necklace.
You're in the minority.
I'm giving you an opportunity.
I'm throwing you a lifeline,
but nothing's for free.
That's fine.
But you treating me like a
little child, like a little
simpleton, "give me the idol."
I don't need that.
I decide on my own
term how my destination is.
Troyzan, the tough
part about tonight for you is
you have no idea if that is the
truth or part of a scheme to
make somebody else feel safe
when they're not.
Well, yeah, this is the first
news i have of a tie happening.
And it seems like every day,
every hour, there's been
something crazy happen.
So it wouldn't be out of the
normal for me to go, "wow"
again, and say,
"okay, here we go.
break out the sticks,
and let's build a fire."
Brad, this is not a
revolutionary idea to think about
forcing a tie if
you think two are tight.
This is basic Survivor strategy.
We can up our odds by forcing
a tie and going to fire.
Absolutely, if they both feel
uncomfortable, they can
absolutely do that.
Tai, how do you feel about this?
There's some doubt.
There's got to be, that they're
voting for you, not for me.
Whatever they're telling you,
who knows if it's true or not.
Troyzan, it's one
simple vote to get to the end,
but there are all these
possibilities.
It's never a simple vote, Jeff.
So i'm going to put my trust in
myself because i'm trusting my
intuition, and if it's right,
i'll walk out of here a final
three guy. If i'm not, i'm
building a fire tonight.
All right, Sarah,
Tai, Troyzan, one of you is
about to be the tenth and
final member of our jury.
It is time to vote.
Troyzan, you're up.
This is the hardest name that
i've had to write down this season.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Tai.
Troyzan.
That's two votes Tai, one vote Troyzan,
one vote left.
17th person voted out and
the final member of our jury: Tai.
You need to bring me your torch.
Tai, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you, Jeff for a great season.
- Thank you for coming back.
- Appreciate it.
Time for you to go.
Congratulations, you made it
to the final three.
You have one more night
in beautiful Fiji.
We'll see you here tomorrow
night for your final Tribal Council.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
I would like to be on the final
three and possibly could have won.
I mean, i did a lot, idol, made
a couple of big moves, socially,
people liked me.
I mean, this is a
really tough game.
But i bounced back, and i'll
just grow stronger.
39, baby.
39 days.
Who would have thunk it?
This was a dream they truly put
out there 16 years ago when i
watched the first episode.
I'm like: "i want to
be the Sole Survivor."
And to get to the three
almost feels like i'm there.
- Are you crying?
- Yeah.
No... it's the smoke.
My social game was real.
I have the ability to speak to
people openly, and i worked that
angle from the
bottom to the middle
to the top the whole game.
I think that's what helped me
because people did trust me,
never wrote my name
down, and i got to day 39.
Maybe this season your
personality, your loyalty, your
game play from the inside
maybe will count more.
And i got a good
feeling about this.
Holy mackerel.
Three baskets.
Oh, look at the muffins.
Look at that, guys.
Well-deserved meal.
- Final three.
Way to go.
Knowing that i'm the final three
is the best feeling in the world.
It's what you
dream of when Jeff
says the word "go" on day one.
I worked my butt
off to get here.
I made moves that other people
were scared to make.
I made moves that
i was scared to make.
And i'm very proud
of how i played.
Brad, are you even
nervous about tonight?
Not really.
As a police officer, i don't
respect being lied to.
It makes me feel like
you think that i'm stupid.
But i'm the criminal tonight.
And those people on the jury
are the police officers.
So if they're asking for the
truth, i'm going to give them
the truth because i reward honesty.
I hope they reward
my honesty tonight.
The whole day i've been thinking
about, okay, what have i done?
And i feel that i'm in a good
position because i've been a
game changer and maneuvered my
way to where i controlled my
destiny this entire game.
I've won five immunity challenges.
I put myself here.
I wasn't drug here.
I did it on my own.
And i brought the people
i want with me here.
I don't need the money, but i
desperately want to win.
Winning the game of Survivor
means everything to me.
And i can argue my case at the
end of the day and walk out of
trial thinking
i've got it, slam dunk.
But quite frankly, i have
not been in a trial
for a million-dollar case.
I'm kind of in a trial for a
million-dollar case tonight.
We'll now bring in your jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie, Zeke,
Sierra, Andrea, Michaela, Cirie, Aubry
and Tai, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
So welcome to the final Tribal
Council of Survivor: Game Changers.
It has been a
season full of firsts.
Most idols ever played
at one Tribal: three.
Most people ever
safe at one Tribal: five.
First person in Cirie ever voted
out simply because there was no
one else to vote for.
First time the steal a vote was
played effectively when Sarah
used it to knock out Michaela.
Culpepper with five individual
immunity wins joins a very elite
group that includes Ozzy.
We also have a new leader in
most days played on Survivor,
Ozzy at 128 days.
Followed right
behind with Cirie, at 121.
Nice!
Congratulations.
So given that this is
Survivor: Game Changers, and
that there have been so many
firsts, it seems only
appropriate that we
end with another first.
We're change Tribal
Council up this year.
In a way that will allow for a
more open discussion between the
jury and the final three.
We're going to center it around
the three aspects of the game:
Outwit, outplay, outlast.
Outwit would be the social part
of the game, the emotional
intelligence, your alliances,
relationships you had outside of
those alliances.
The outplay portion would be how
you respond to the conditions
put on you by the game.
You have to build shelter.
You have to compete in challenges.
There are switches.
There will be twists.
How do you respond to
the hand you're dealt?
And the final phase, outlast.
Most critical.
Did you put people on the jury
who respect the we you outwitted
and outplayed more
than the other two?
And if not, tonight is your
last chance to sway them.
I'm going to give you
a moment to take it in.
We'll get started.
All right, let's start with the
outwit portion of the game,
the social part of Survivor.
Who wants to address Sarah,
Brad, or Troyzan first?
- I'll do it.
- Okay.
Sarah, on day three of this
game, i gave you my jacket.
And then i was blindsided, and
every night, you wore my jacket
to Tribal Council.
And all i could think was:
"hot damn!, that is bad ass."
You made such amazing
relationships.
Sierra, whom you were
responsible for voting out, gave
you the legacy advantage because
she didn't process that you were
responsible for
controlling this game.
So, Sarah, i am your
champion tonight.
- And i wish you the best.
- Thank you.
I am going to say, i'm in
such a dilemma here.
So, you know, Sarah, you had
some brilliant game moves, really.
Like, you convinced everyone
here that they were your best friend.
And you brought people's
personal feel into emotions.
And i feel... i feel kind of gross.
Did you know that you were going
to have this effect on people?
Yes, on one side, i can respect,
hey, she fooled us all.
But am i going to feel good
about that vote?
I want everyone over there to
know, my personal relationships
were 100% real from
the bottom of my heart.
Well, i'm just trying to be honest.
I think the problem is why
should we trust what you're
saying to us right now?
Look, i played this game, as we
found out, more than anybody else.
There is a way to
play this game without
going as low as you had to go.
Yeah, i lied.
But it's what i
had to do sit here,
and i was willing to
do whatever it took.
Then again, somebody like
Brad, who as a competitor,
i give you props.
You get put into a position
where you've got to win, win,
win, win, win.
And nobody,
very few people, you and i
and a few other people
understand how hard that is.
And he didn't have to
get his hands dirty.
He could do it in a way that was
more clean and more loyal.
So i will be Brad's
champion at this point.
Cirie, social part of
the game, outwit.
What's on your mind?
Brad, most of us sitting here
voted Sierra out because we knew
she was the brains of your
operation and that without her,
you and Troyzan probably would
have just bumped into each other.
Explain how she didn't run the
first portion of your game.
When i landed on the beach, i
started working with people,
with Tai, with Sierra.
Most importantly, with J.T.
I was able to make the
game-changing, i think, move of
the season, when we ended up
going to Tribal Council
with two groups.
But i had built such a good
relationship with J.T., that he
came to me in the middle of the
whole Tribal Council and told me
exactly who they were voting out,
and i saved Sierra that night.
And i'm calling it the turning
point of the game because i got
rid of malcolm, and we all might
not be here if Malcolm were here.
I'll put in an opinion.
From the outside looking in, it
did look like Sierra was the
brains of the operation.
But considering that this is a
social game built on
relationships, i'm
interested to know
how much you actually
know about me.
Well, you're from Texas.
You went to Texas christian.
You have... you work with a sales
company for vacations.
I mean...
What...what do you
want to know, you know?
No further questions.
Ah... then...
I mean, Brad, that's maybe
where you were lacking.
I mean, Sarah, even though a lot
of us feel gross about it
she developed
personal relationships.
However, Sarah, i'm actually just
curious how did you it.
How did you manage people's
personal feelings and emotions?
Sarah, before you answer
that, i'm shocked to learn that...
Because what i had with you
was... i thought was real.
Now coming from your mouth.
We all had the same
experience with you.
- So tell me...
- Well...
my first season, i played
who i was in real life.
And that got Sarah nowhere.
And my support systems at home
basically gave me the permission
to open the floodgates and
do whatever i needed.
But i think what Andrea is
asking is not for a generality.
What specifically allows you to
say, "this is real Sarah.
this is game Sarah?"
Honestly, it comes from being
a police officer for the last 10 years,
working under cover.
When you're under cover,
you have to shut off
who are you and be someone else.
You're buying drugs,
you're a drug user now.
If you're a prostitute,
you're a prostitute.
I have to play a role
of someone i am not.
And i get what you're saying
that it's scary how it shuts on
and off, but i have to
do that for a living.
But, you know, if the ends
don't justify the means,
then what does?
Think Machiavelli the prince,
think Lady Mcbeth.
You know you want to win this
game and you do it at all costs.
I have zero respect for you and
your game play, and that's why i
am his lieutenant in arms for
you, Brad, because she never
would have been sitting
there without you.
Michaela, you have a
look on your face to Debbie's comment.
I guess i don't understand
the emotional feeling that
people have towards Sarah.
Like, even when Sarah used the
advantage to vote me out, it
wasn't something
they took personally.
I was just, like, good thing you
got rid of me, because i'm the
only one that could beat Brad.
However, i did want to ask a
question of Troyzan.
Wow!
What can you tell the jury
what you actually did from a
social perspective in this game?
Well, you know, i've talked
to every single one of you, and
i had personal relationships.
And i was ready to have an
alliance with all of you, if
that was to my benefit.
But it was difficult for me to
play full out because i felt like
i was playing with, like,
two loved ones.
Hold on, hold on.
From my standpoint, there's a
difference between being a
passenger and being a driver.
I'm sitting here, though.
I'm sitting here.
- And you're sitting there.
- For sure.
- What's the difference.
I made moves, so basically
help my game.
When i got to the merge, i got
together with six people that they
knew i could trust at that point.
And if they wanted
to vote you out,
of course, i'm
going to do that.
But you said "they" wanted to.
You didn't say "i" wanted to.
So then you were a
passenger like he's saying.
Yeah, Troyzan, in terms of
the decision making what, role
did you play in that?
Well, it wasn't as direct to
say: "this is the person.
That's the person."
I did things in a sense more
sneaky and made suggestions--
I'm hearing it's a little bit
of can "anyone but me."
A little bit Sandra
without the fat.
It's a little bit "anyone but
me"but i can make moves from the
the middle or the
bottom just as easy.
It sounds like you're sitting
in the right place.
But i just want to say people who
didn't get in an alliance didn't
get to see the way he played.
You were a part of votes.
You just did it in
a more subtle way.
- Thank you.
- Own it, it's not done yet.
Thank you.
Andrea, weigh in on
Culpepper's social part of the
game, the outwit portion.
Okay, Brad, you played a
pretty solid game.
You were loyal.
You won a bunch of immunities.
But you never reached out and
tried to form relationships with
people on the bottom, people
like Michaela, and you were very
nasty towards people like Tai.
So i would love to hear your
thoughts on that.
As far as Michaela, for
whatever reason, Michaela and i
were oil and water.
I don't know why.
You and i just didn't connect.
And you talk about Tai,
basically, i must have been
doing something right socially
because you told
you have two idols.
So i was trying to do everything
i could to make you
uncomfortable to make you either
give me an idol so i could
protect you or you
played both your idols.
I think...
Do you realize how
you talk to people?
Do you realize the way you
approached talking to me
time after time after time saying:
"i control you or
you go home next."
- I said, "no, why--"
- I understand.
You realize that's how you
came across to me?
You made a choice to go with
the girls and not stay with the
alliance i tried to make
and that's fine.
After that i gained power
winning immunities
and i was trying to use this power to
manipulate you and your idols.
So, Brad, did you just say
you used condescension as a
strategy to control Tai?
I didn't say i condescend.
I said: "this is an option i'm giving you"
That was a choice.
I was simply trying to make a
deal, but it came with a price.
And the price was the idol.
Debbie, your opinion about
Culpepper's social part of the game.
Well, i've got three brothers.
I'm surrounded by
people in the military.
I understand your testosterone
level is 100 times the average male.
I do get that you are not the
warmest, fuzziest, cuddliest
teddy bear.
Love you, anyway.
But to be honest, like, this
game, this ship, had one driver.
And that was Sarah.
Sarah always voted the right way.
Because Sarah always knew the
right way to vote.
Because Sarah was always
directing the right way to vote.
I just want to throw it out there.
i mean, this is so rich and so
informative and helpful.
And my mind is even less made up
now in a great way than when i
stormed into this Tribal Council.
All right, so, clearly, there are
varying opinions about each of you
in terms of the social
part of Survivor.
Let's move into the outplay
portion of the same game.
You have to make shelter,
compete in challenges,
switches and advantages.
Anyone have anything they
want to say at the top?
Brad the outplay
portion goes to you.
You never stopped working.
If you haven't won immunity the
last five times, the chances of
him sitting there probably zero.
He took a risk playing in a way
i respect, and a lot of you
guys will never know what this
means because you brutalize your
body to get to this point.
I failed every single
time i've played.
I've not been able to do it.
And i think that
this man, he did it.
And i think he deserves to win
because he relied on himself
when he needed to.
We are the authors of our destiny.
We are the authors
of our story in this game.
And Brad played from the very
beginning to win this game,
that's what he did.
Debbie, how much value
do you give to camp life
and providing?
Does it weigh in on your vote?
To me, Survivor has always
been "the lord of the flies."
And i agree with Ozzy
completely.
I know it's your make up.
It's your character.
It's your very nature to say:
"this is what has to be done."
They would not be sitting
there without you, sir.
Thank you, thank you, Ozzy, too.
Thank you both.
I mean, as far as the outplay,
Brad's a professional athlete, people.
I'm 47, i was.
I'm just making a point.
He's a professional athlete.
But, the puzzles
are not athletic...
- Let her finish the statement, please.
- Here's the thing.
I'm not trying to take anything
away from Brad at all.
Winning five immunitys is tough.
But what i had to
rely on was my tools
that i had in the outplay department.
Sierra tells me in the event she
gets voted out she will will her
Legacy Advantage to me.
So now i need to get Sierra out.
But how am i going
to vote her out
and still get her
to will it to me?
And i had to adapt to the
situation and act like that.
And the day that Cirie got
across that beam was an
emotional day for everyone.
The game didn't stop, though.
And guess what?
Michaela's sitting on the
sit-out bench not getting to play.
And at the bottom of her feet i
seeing in something.
It says, "secret advantage" on it.
Anyone that was there that day
had the opportunity to see that.
It wasn't hidden.
Paying attention to detail is
how my playing the game got me
right here.
Michaela, you were
involved in a twist when the
advantage was at your feet that
you didn't even really know about.
Yeah, like, it was a great move.
And the thing that makes Sarah
so bad-ass, is that she got the
advantage from the
sit-out bench that i was on.
If you are working people so
well that you can be so bold as
to say, "that was an advantage
that was meant for you, and i
took it," that's
some bad-ass stuff.
And then to top it off, you used
it against me and sent me home.
That was brilliant!
Cirie, it's very interesting
that we have so many
different opinions.
What does that say about all the
elements that come in to
deciding who wins?
It matters, Jeff, because we
have to look at every single
aspect, and if you fell short
anywhere, we have to bring it up
because we're going to award
somebody a million dollars
that's not one of us.
We want to make sure that we're
giving it to the right person.
So, the game is
clearly still alive.
Now we're at the outlast
portion of the game.
Did you put the people on the
jury that respect your outwit,
and your outplay more
than the other two?
Culpepper, we'll start with you.
This is your last chance
to move anybody
that you think might not
be on your side.
I don't think you have to
deceive and lie to every single
person to win this game.
I came into the game,
let people come to me.
I built relationships that
changed the game at certain points.
Got flipped upside down.
So at that point, i had to rely
on my athleticism or brain
And i did just that.
So i was able to get to the end,
and i won the five immunitys.
And then as far as the living
and the camp life, i don't know
that i did all that
to get your votes.
I did all that because
that's who i am.
But anyway, it's been an honor
and a privilege to play with all you guys.
Sarah, last chance to
sway the jury.
Okay, here's the thing.
You have to strike
first in this game.
The reason you guys are there
and these two aren't is because
i truly believe you guys could
have beat me.
I just hope that you guys can
respect the game play and how
hard it was to play with 20
people at such a high-caliber a
player, and be one
step ahead every time.
Because i was the one person
here that was in on every vote.
I think the history shows that
the training and the ability to
adapt to the situations that
you're placed in is what saves
my life when i'm at work.
And that same
training i applied out
here to save my
life in this game.
All right, Troyzan.
I'm just going to keep it
light, you guys, and i have a
pretty good idea where
you stand with me.
So i might not have been
the best strategist.
I might not have been
the best game player.
But i want to tell you
how much i appreciate
all of you for this adventure.
You're a part of my dream.
I've watched from season one,
you know, when Richard Hatch was
running around naked
and people eat rats.
And i'm like whatever that is.
I have to be a part of it.
I appreciate it from the
bottom of my heart.
Really, it means a lot, you
guys, and i'm out.
Good job, everybdoy.
All right, a great Final Tribal.
Very healthy discussion.
I'm going to give the jury a
moment to take in everything
you've heard tonight,
and then you will make
a million-dollar decision.
All right, jury,
tonight, you are voting for a winner.
The person you think most
deserving of the title of Sole
Survivor and the million
dollars that goes along with it.
For the last time,
it is time to vote.
Sierra, you're up.
You played a flawless game, girl.
Anybody who doesn't
vote for you is a bitter betty.
I hope that you can do what
i've tried to do four times.
I think you deserve it.
I am so honored to be voting
for you, one of the great
masters and great
players of this game.
Congratulations, officer Sarah.
Because in this jaded, crazy
world, good guys finish first.
I'll go get the votes.
Culpepper, Sarah,
Troyzan, jury, thank you for a
great Final Tribal.
I will see everybody back in the
states for the reading of the votes.
Cochran!
All right.
Thank you.
Awesome, have a seat!
Let's not waste any time.
Thank you for that nice welcome.
So here's its deal.
When we had this idea to do
Game Changers we talked about,
we thought about who
we wanted to come back.
We said we have,
truly, one hope.
Please let there
be some big moves.
That was a genuine hope.
You guys delivered so many big
moves, you made history.
Thank you for another amazing
season of Survivor.
But now, it comes down to this.
After 39 days of decisions,
Brad, Troyzan, Sarah,
did you make the right one?
The jury, did you put people on
the jury who think you deserve
it more than the other two?
I'm going to read the votes.
Here we go.
First vote...
Sarah.
Culpepper.
One vote Sarah, one vote Culpepper.
Sarah.
Two votes Sarah, one vote Culpepper.
Culpepper.
We're tied.
Two votes Sarah, two votes Culpepper.
Culpepper.
Three votes Culpepper,
two votes Sarah.
Sarah.
We're tied again.
Three votes Culpepper, three votes Sarah.
Sarah.
That's four votes Sarah,
three votes Culpepper.
Sarah.
Five votes Sarah, four--three votes Culpepper.
The winner of Survivor: Game
Changers: Sarah.
It was an epic win.
You could hear the energy here.
Sarah, here's your check.
She's celebrating.
You'll take it.
All right.
We called them Game Changers
and they lived up to it.
Historic game play, plus a
moment that had the entire world
talking when zeke was
outed as transgender.
We have a Zeke, Varner
and everybody else.
Live reunion show coming up next.