Previously on Survivor...
In the Mana tribe,
Hali and Michaela were left out of Culpepper's alliance.
I have people with whom I want to move forward.
In the Nuku tribe,
Varner knew his game was breaking down.
If I leave tonight, I'll bring them all to their knees.
At the council,
Varner made a desperate blow.
There is deception here.
Deception on one level, Jeff,
that they don't even understand.
Why didn't you tell anyone you were transgender?
But it's personal.
He does not deceive us at all.
It's personal. You should not have done that.
It's disgusting to mention that.
We don't have the right to do that.
And he was eliminated.
Varner, the tribe has spoken.
There are 13 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Last night each of you
forgave Varner. I don't forgive him.
And it is your right. No problem.
I wanted to comfort him a little.
Out of sympathy. I am like this.
No problem.
No problem for me.
I hope you don't blame me... Not at all.
He took so much from Zeke.
Thinking about it, it bothers me.
I come from a very conservative background.
I didn't know a transgender person before.
And to have been with Zeke,
to have known him, as a person,
since the first day,
i love this guy.
And it doesn't change
who he is to me.
Ultimately, it strengthens our bonds.
So this morning I woke up, and Zeke is Zeke.
It's almost unreal.
To me, you're just Zeke.
You see ?
Yeah. I don't want people crying, screaming,
so I was just, well... No worries.
I know, but that wasn't cool.
No, indeed.
And I was very touched by your reactions.
I didn't say it especially so that people would see me as I am.
Often in my life
when I say I'm trans, that's what we're talking about.
And everything else is set aside.
But Survivor makes you strong, enduring, more flexible.
I think I had these qualities before,
but they have been strengthened and developed.
I think I was able to show myself a little more courageous,
a little bolder, to help others,
and also to overcome my own fears,
exceed...
...My problems, complexes and anxieties
related to being transgender.
I'm glad we got past that.
It brought us closer.
I really like my playmates.
And it's comforting, in this game, that often,
when you're down, something ugly happens to you,
people who, in a sense, are your enemies,
come to your defense.
I was really touched.
But at the same time,
there is still a job to do, which I am determined to accomplish.
I'm here to make a million, to play Survivor.
It's time to get back to it.
Over here, everyone!
We come to the test
and there is a buffet on a table.
So I say to myself:
"Wow, a fusion feast!"
So we are happy.
Oh my God ! Look !
But at the same time,
there's Jeff, next to a covered table.
So I'm like, "Oh, oh!
Something is off."
My heart is pounding.
Sierra, arriving
and noticing the fusion feast,
you said, "My heart is racing."
It's always like that.
I'm starving.
Ozzy.
How important is food at this stage?
We are all incredibly hungry
and are hyper aware of the importance of this,
just like what's underneath.
Interesting. Because it's about to come into play.
Before officially merging,
you have one last decision to make in tribes.
To be able to enjoy this splendid meal,
a person
of each tribe
must accept
not to take part.
Oh my God !
If we don't have two volunteers,
one in each tribe,
who renounce the feast,
the feast disappears,
and instead you will celebrate merging
with a biscuit per person and a sip of cold tea.
Oh my God !
Big dilemma.
Zeke.
This decision has several levels, it's complicated.
On the one hand, I could allow my allies to eat,
if I was ready to accept the burden.
On the other hand, I might need that energy,
because I could be targeted.
I'll do it, it's good.
It's good, it's good.
I'm not trying to... I can fish, I promise.
Culpepper.
You immediately said, "I'll do it."
Its good.
That's what Monica would do.
The Thing, with Brad Culpepper,
is that I doubt he liked his image in Blood vs. Water.
So he sacrifices himself
to be the hero, the great supplier.
It's part of the "Culpepper brand",
to sacrifice for others.
Well, we have a volunteer for Mana.
Nuku. Difficult decision.
Is anyone ready to say, "I'll do it." ?
I don't think I can do it.
It's decided.
Tai, is it decided? Yes.
I believe they will benefit more than me.
Andrea. Surprised by the speed at which two people
said, "It's not that important." ?
It doesn't surprise me that Tai does that.
He's so selfless, so caring...
Thank you so much. Oh no, I...
Seriously, you'll eat all the rice you want on camp.
No problem. It's okay with me.
Well, we have our two volunteers.
Brad for Mana
and Tai for Nuku
made the last tribal decision,
because it's officially the merger!
Y'all can throw away your bandanas.
Oh my God !
Brad and Tai scored symbolic points
by allowing, in a sense, the supply of everyone.
But it makes me suspicious
because in this game, everything is calculated.
Brad and Tai,
go to the beach, there is a trunk with two yellow bandanas.
En route!
Thanks guys ! Thanks !
Everyone else: happy feasting!
Oh, my God, cheese!
This is the best fusion feast!
Of pineapple !
Who wants ham?
I want some ! Am I going to be sick?
I have reached fusion,
I have to eat, I am a new woman.
And now I'll take out the heavy artillery.
I am ready to act.
I also have the Heir Advantage.
But it can only be used when there are 13 or 6 people left in the game.
There we are 13.
But I will do anything
to keep it until the last step.
Too bad for my figure. It was off to a good start.
It was starting to get better!
At fusion, everything takes off like a jet plane.
Yes, we are all happy, we eat, we drink,
we have our last meal together,
people are talking,
meet up,
we evaluate each other.
Things will take off, heads will roll,
so that's where I get stronger.
Congratulations to all !
Poor Brad and Tai!
Brad is great because he's really starving.
I feel guilty. I love you, Brad and Tai!
Do not worry !
I love you ! We are fine !
My friend !
In football, only the next match counts.
I reached the fusion? Great.
It's in the rear view mirror.
I look in front of me.
Who will be the next one ? Not me.
Congratulations on the merger. I am delighted.
Me too. It's a...
Tai and I have gotten closer more than once before.
I'm taking a bit of the role Caleb had in his season.
I think I can trust him.
And in my old tribe,
Michaela and Hali were at the bottom of the scale.
So I want to target them first.
How was it going over there?
What's going on ? You know...
First I have Sierra,
we have Troyzan, so we have lots of people.
But Michaela is a target.
And Hali too, they are immediate targets.
At the bottom of the ladder ? Yeah.
Why ?
Because we don't need them. It's a staffing issue.
If you are sure of yourself,
I'm happy, because there are a lot of us there.
We fire them first and then we advise.
And then... That's perfect.
I love Brad.
We have a lot in common.
I believe he protects me.
I have a majority, I am calm, I am happy.
Twerk ! Twerk ! Twerk !
What are they happy about?
I don't know, food.
We do a little dance.
What did you take? You drank ?
Oh yeah. Here, come with me.
Shake with me! Turn around!
Come on, everyone!
Oh my God !
Little Debbie went wild, we couldn't stop her.
I think alcohol was an excuse
for Debbie to let loose.
We'll vomit together.
You have drunken eyes!
Oh my God !
It's okay with me
if you think I'm drinking.
But I never drank a drop of alcohol.
Debbie, are you drunk?
This!
Oh my God !
I don't... She showed me her ass!
I love you, sweetheart !
If I have to fake drunkenness
and twerk and shake my body to make them laugh
and make them feel comfortable around me,
I will do it.
I love you all !
No one is going to leave, I love you all!
At this point, 13 is still a lot.
And we don't know where the alliances are.
So relationships are important.
Because if you believe that this camp
not going to turn into total chaos, you are stupid.
Welcome !
Well, well! Not naughty!
Just as we left it.
Congratulations to all for reaching the fusion!
Congratulations to all !
We're a big family now!
Happy to see you. Me too.
I was wrong, sorry. I yelled at you, I freaked out.
We're hungry, we're stressed, we're tired... I know, I know.
I am on your side.
I say. I know it.
I swallowed my pride and apologized to Brad.
For in Exile, Cochran said:
"Reach out to everyone."
We reconciled.
I want to be sure
that Brad and I are as close as can be
in a game of deception and conspiracy.
Tell Jeff's story. And Sandra!
I'll tell you about Varner. So.
We come to the council
and in less than five minutes,
Varner decides to say:
"Zeke is cheating on you.
Because what Zeke doesn't tell you,
it's that he's transgender."
He said that?!
And that's true. Wait, let him talk.
I'm.
Even if it happened in an unhappy way,
I think I'm like all of you
changed forever,
changed forever by my experience in Survivor.
I am now much stronger, much more capable.
Nice bro. Much better for you.
I was super proud of Zeke. Unbelievable.
I have much more respect for him, for telling his story,
that for many of these jokers
I've known for 20 days.
And I think Zeke is right.
Survivor's experience makes you stronger.
And nothing will be easy in this fusion.
There are 13 people on this camp.
Now the game is to figure out who is where,
who is in and who is not.
Whatever you want to do, at this point,
with you two, Sierra...
I have Debbie in my pocket. As we all.
For my part,
everyone is cool.
My main goal is to reconnect
and consolidate ties with the people I was with,
those with whom I have had clashes.
I bonded with Tai.
Debbie came back and apologized to me.
And with Sierra, Troyzan and me... So far so good.
We can do whatever we want at this point.
It's Michaela or Hali. It's okay with me.
I was thinking: Michaela first.
She could do the tests. Sure.
She has always been at the top of my list.
If I think of me and who I can play best with,
I don't feel Michaela too much.
Its reputation precedes it a little.
In the long run, I don't trust her.
So here, I'm bringing everyone together so that we all agree.
And Michaela will be the first
to sink after melting.
As long as we start with Michaela...
Then we will have control.
It's okay with me.
OK. Cool. Let's do that.
Michaela. It's the first ?
I think so.
We're going to Michaela.
Oh. OK.
I believe it's Michaela.
Everyone is leaving.
Well, if that's the direction it's going.
There is a consensus, I believe,
to take out Michaela, then Hali.
It will be Michaela first.
100 %.
It's okay with me. Easy.
It's pretty.
Maku Maku?
I like it. Maku-Maku?
Who are you concerned about?
Michaela ?
I think Ozzy wants to take her out. As we all.
But she must ignore it.
Provided she does not gain immunity!
So her first. Wait, she's coming.
Brad and I don't want to work with Michaela.
I find it a bit dodgy.
She's not easy to live with, she's unpredictable,
She is a hit in the tests...
She will meddle in every conversation.
She is dangerous on so many levels.
Keeping it in play would harm many of us.
It's super easy, if you just...
...sticks to the plan! Yeah, we're sticking to the plan!
It's just.
This is Michaela.
Damn, we can't do anything without her showing up.
She drives me crazy.
As soon as I talk to someone,
Michaela rapplique,
always lurking around.
She doesn't let anyone argue.
Do you have a private conversation?
No. We do our laundry.
She's also very abrupt.
she lacks tact.
What did you tell people about me?
That you were very good at the tests.
And we can always read what you think on your face.
I'm always on edge
when she is there.
You have to take it out by surprise. She must know nothing.
If something sets it in motion,
we're all screwed.
There's something on the roof that makes things fall!
What is a hen? But yes !
What morons!
Go ahead, talk, it's okay.
You, me, Andrea
and Sara...
It's us four.
Until the end. [???]. I believe you 100%.
Genre...
If Michaela is number one, frankly...
So that would be...
And after ?
We gotta strike before Brad
and Sierra did come out one of us.
Just.
Michaela is a potential ally.
So this vote
is much more important than it seems.
There are more or less two natural groups
who are vying for the position of power.
It's Cirie, Sarah, Andrea and me
against Brad and Sierra's group.
And everyone wonders: "Are the others going to strike first?
Am I going to get screwed like a rookie?"
Well, let's be clear: the hen must come down from the roof.
She keeps dropping things on me.
And we have to strike first.
These are the last moments of this simulacrum of cordial agreement.
What is she doing up there? I do not know.
It's the smiles before the bloodbath.
Eh !
That's why she came up!
Who is it ?
Andrea.
Attractive !
We're fixing the bench, because a part is broken.
We need a screwdriver. I say.
During a merger,
it is...
There are people everywhere,
conversations in every corner.
It's impossible to track who's talking to whom.
Few people work with me at this point.
Michaela seems to be on the hot seat.
But I want to work with her. I find her great.
And she would strengthen my ranks.
So I gotta shake it up a bit
to launch a strategy that could benefit me.
Bravo !
I think
that at this stage of the game,
we just have to make sure we have the majority on this vote,
to know who will vote with you and not against...
...toi.
Are people trying to vote against me?
I heard your name once.
We can become a target
very quickly here.
My name is already out, and I didn't do anything.
And that tends to annoy me.
I was about to explode.
To be out of the game at this stage of the game is very dangerous.
I'll have to find people I can trust
to avoid leaving.
And it could be Cirie.
I heard that my name was being mentioned.
It's a good way to piss me off.
You are very smart.
You have to control your emotions.
You can't ignore other people's discussions,
but you don't have to...
...show nothing.
I wanted to take you aside
between women,
to tell you to calm down about it.
Whatever's going on in your head, if you're hungry,
starve yourself.
If you're pissed off, get pissed off.
I have to work on this. Yes. I experienced that.
Michaela is on edge.
I was like that.
When I was his age,
I was a hothead like her.
I thought I knew...
I thought I knew everything. But I learned
that being on the defensive pushes people away.
And in such a game, you have to attract as many people as possible,
not push them away or make them feel uncomfortable.
You know, I don't know how to handle this merger.
It's new for me.
Go cool. Let me tell you something.
You have to let go
and be as normal as possible.
Because if you generate any tension...
It doesn't take much here to attract attention.
You learn that in this game: your reputation follows you.
And people's perception is their reality.
No matter what it really is, reality...
That's what they think. So. This is reality for them.
Cirie and I had
a real heart-to-heart discussion.
Because we have a lot in common.
My confidence in Cirie skyrocketed.
I'm very excited to play with her.
I don't believe that two black women have already reached the final.
No never.
You may have guessed it from my aura, I [???],
I want to show people that we can work together.
For now, Michaela is public enemy number one.
But I really appreciate it.
And as a human being,
as an eldest
vis-à-vis a younger one, we want to save her,
and if I succeed,
I can count on her to support me.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for your first individual immunity test?
First of all, Ozzy...
I'm taking back tribal immunity.
Merci.
Tribal immunity is over.
Let's see.
Individual immunity is what you covet.
Attractive. Funny face.
With that around your neck, you're safe.
Without, you are not.
Shall we pass the test?
Today,
you'll be on tiptoe
with a block wedged between your head and the frame.
The longer the ordeal lasts,
the more your legs will tire.
When they finally let go, the block will fall
and it will be over.
The last person standing wins immunity,
is shielded from the board.
The losers: someone will be the eighth person
eliminated from the game.
We draw the places at random and we start.
Good.
Place the block above you.
I will count.
Three,
of them,
and...
Well, take all your hands off!
Everyone looks good.
This test is on.
It's very simple: no touching the frame...
Hali is eliminated in seconds. And Troyzan.
Et Zeke.
You are only ten.
Three people eliminated in three seconds.
Shame.
I was saying...
No touching the frame or the block.
Relax.
It will be painful, instantly.
I'm already shaking. That's crazy.
Fight the pain.
Ouch. Style is secondary.
Cirie is eliminated.
She felt him slip.
In this ordeal, you cannot pitch.
Hold on. Hold on.
Michaela chants, talking to herself.
Do what it takes.
Relax.
Michaela falters.
Incredible recovery.
His block really took off,
but did not fall, she picked herself up.
Debbie can't take it anymore.
Debbie is eliminated.
You are only eight.
Hold on. Hold on.
Michaela struggles.
Its block evolves slowly towards the back of the frame.
Michaela is right on the edge.
Michaela is eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
You are already only seven.
Six fell quickly.
The remaining seven look good.
Only five minutes have passed.
It could easily take an hour.
We're going to tan a little.
That is to say if you will have to suffer to win.
Ozzy does a little dance,
attempts to stimulate blood circulation,
to stretch the muscles.
Ozzy,
without warning,
falls.
Ozzy is eliminated.
Aubry falters.
Aubry
falls without warning.
And you are only five.
You are going to deserve it, this immunity.
This first board after the merger
is such a dangerous step.
It's certain.
Everyone is together, nobody really knows
Where is the truth.
It's certain.
Culpepper lutte.
Culpepper is eliminated.
And you are only four.
First individual immunity test
with a big tip in perspective.
25 minutes have passed.
Several people did not last 25 seconds.
Three women, one man.
Never has a woman won this test.
Sierra goes through many small spasms.
Unbalanced, she pulls herself together.
Sarah suddenly loses her block, and there are only three of you.
And suddenly,
Sierra is eliminated.
Very hard legs.
And you are only two.
Or you don't Andrea.
Andrea ate at the Fusion Feast.
Tai, don't.
Will it make the difference?
They clash
in the 34th season of Survivor.
Tai didn't move.
Andrea falters.
It is very painful.
Really.
That's Survivor.
Who wants her the most?
It's...
...falls suddenly!
Tai is eliminated!
Andrea gagne
the first individual immunity!
You rock. 1st woman to win this event!
You're great.
Andrea, come here!
The first person to wear this necklace.
Individual immunity is up to you.
You're safe at tonight's council.
You cannot be eliminated from the game.
As for you guys, you know the song.
21 days is not enough.
Someone will see their dream fade away
and will become the eighth person eliminated from Game Changers.
Take your things. See you tonight at the council.
Congratulation.
Tonight's vote seems very simple.
But that's Survivor Game Changers.
No vote is easy. Everyone has hidden motivations.
The challenge of this advice is to take control of the game.
Congratulations, Andrea! Cheer !
Merci !
How long could you have lasted?
The key is to maintain strong pressure.
At this point, I think I hold the reins.
I love having control.
From my point of view, there is this large group,
and two underdogs, Hali and Michaela.
I think eliminating Michaela tonight is best.
But I dread seeing an idol come out.
I have already played with Hali.
This time around, she's absurdly confident.
She plays quite differently.
I think she has an idol.
Someone has the one from the old Nuku beach.
I do not know.
But that's my feeling. If that's okay with you, we'll split the votes.
The majority on Michaela.
Seeing how Hali plays
compared to his first time,
she plays completely differently.
And that makes me think she might have an idol.
I think she has an idol.
I think so.
But it is okay.
It does not matter.
There, we have such a majority
which can be divided between the two, whenever there is an idol.
What's up, ladies?
We can talk quickly.
Yeah, because I don't know what's going on.
Four people will vote Hali.
Everyone else votes Michaela.
So... Michaela is leaving tonight.
Do you think Hali has an idol?
Who are we telling them we're voting for?
We stay on Zeke?
Oui.
So we tell them we're voting for Zeke?
I have no idea what is going on.
I am dropped.
We think of Zeke.
Because if he goes to the end, he will win.
He clearly has the best story.
Everyone says "Zeke".
So I'm going to vote Zeke.
'Cause what else can I do?
But I'm not comfortable.
What do you say ? You're hesitating ?
I do not care.
I just feel like my name is going to come out, I don't know why.
This vote for Michaela, I don't particularly like it.
Is it good for my game?
Why would I follow their plan? Because Sierra said so?
Since there are two options, Michaela or Hali...
Why not Hali?
What's new ?
The vote is supposed to be Michaela, then Hali, right?
For all I know.
My only concern,
is that if they want Michaela,
it is to be able to join Hali.
So if we do that,
we play their game.
I thought we were worried that Hali had an idol.
That's what they say, but I don't know.
I just know that they will strengthen their ranks.
And if they do that, what happens to us?
It's certain.
Tonight is the outbreak of hostilities between two alliances.
And I think everyone sees Michaela and Hali
as potential recruits.
So this vote is to reduce the opposing ranks.
See if they try to convince you to vote Michaela and not Hali.
I bet they will.
But I don't see the point, except for their side.
I have a question.
I've just been told how the vote is going.
I'm puzzled: why not target Hali?
Why don't we do it?
For me, if she has an idol,
but don't play it
then she remains in play with an idol.
It's decided like that.
If we keep Michaela,
it will sow chaos.
It will be horror.
But we will release it two days later!
But hey, if it bothers you that much...
No, that just seems a little absurd to me.
We can do one or the other.
We are many. We must remain calm.
Both positions defend themselves.
That's the thing.
We can't win the war
without a sufficient army.
And if Michaela leaves,
it's one less person I can count on.
What is his problem ?
Is that he... ...wants to be in charge?
Well, guess what?
There's a new sheriff in town.
Listen, my daughter. I'm trying to save your life here.
They lie about Zeke.
I am in the hot seat.
But I don't want to explode.
Because that won't help me.
I'm super happy to have Cirie.
My life is completely in his hands.
And I trust.
That's why I like to play with people I trust.
We're trying to save you.
You can't tell anyone about it.
You hear me ? Nothing.
Everyone is on edge.
Everyone watches everyone.
So I need Michaela to vote Zeke,
she follows the plan.
So no one knows it was Cirie who changed the plan.
I will not tell anything. To no one.
Just tell me how to vote.
Stay on Zeke, okay?
OK. Thanks.
For me, the purpose of this advice
is to save someone I can rely on
and who can strengthen our ranks.
And if I succeed in this,
my future in this game looks bright.
Cirie, the last person to come to the council.
There is a torch for you.
Take it, turn it on.
It is part of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears
you too.
13 people.
Zeke.
The game goes from two tribes
to this mass of individuals.
How significant is this change
in how you should view the game?
This is madness, Jeff.
There are so many people to watch, and so many people you can't watch.
You have to accept that a lot of things are going to happen around you
and that you are powerless to control them.
Andrea. If you had to explain the merger
to someone who has never seen Survivor,
what would you say ?
It's the moment of the game where...?
This is when the battle lines are set.
The two votes following the merger are crucial.
They will show where the alliances are.
It sets the tone for the rest of the game.
Debbie. Is it a bit like musical chairs?
Turn and wait for the music to stop to take a seat?
Not tonight, no.
I don't expect to be shocked tonight.
Hali, when you hear Debbie say that,
does that reassure you?
"That's what I think too." ?
Or are you worried because it's new to you?
I am in the dark on this vote.
It's like being in a room
with armed people
and 3 or 4 of us are blindfolded.
One of us is going to be shot.
I don't know who.
Michaela.
You nod. Do you agree with Hali?
Yeah. Basically, no one tried to talk to me today.
So you are worried.
Sure.
But if people really played an individual game,
they would consider the various existing links,
would look at who threatens them,
who plays the most strategically,
and who finds himself by chance in the hot seat
without valid reason.
I'm trying to understand what motivates people to vote,
but I feel like Hali, a bit in the dark.
This.
How to determine who to vote for tonight
when there are so many people,
and yet, as Andrea said,
Could it be a deciding vote?
It should not be considered that tonight's vote,
but also the following two or three.
Ozzy. At some stage,
a name must be advanced. "Why not so and so?"
From your point of view,
what is the criteria?
The risk.
Also, the possibility of an idol being played.
And if possible, guide the vote
towards the person who might have an idol.
These are big questions in this game.
Debbie. Has it been discussed a lot, idols?
If anyone has one or not,
and if so, should it be targeted?
I love the board, it's the quintessence of the game.
It's the Colosseum.
Here you live or you die.
Tonight, I always find it exciting,
but I think
that now, this moment,
it's always a good time to clear an idol.
Cirie.
Are there ever people who say, "Listen,
I'll undress, search my bag,
I'll go naked to the council,
I don't have an idol."
The person suspected of having an idol
may not know she is
and therefore not being able to say: "Here are my pockets, I don't have it!"
If you think a person has an idol, you don't:
"Hey, I think you have an idol!"
Eh !
If this is the time to do this,
I want to empty my bag.
Hali, you're afraid you're the one
suspected of having an idol, hence your blindfolded eyes.
If so, let me know if it's necessary!
I just want to die another day, not today.
Zeke. Why not accept such an offer?
This is additional information.
I don't think anyone wants to be the one who says:
"Yes, go ahead, Hali!
Vide ton sac !"
If you want more security, show a little courage.
Tell me, can we do a bag search
to sort things out, if that's what it takes.
But I will only do it if asked.
Aubrey. Light my lantern.
Why would Hali say:
"I'm ready to empty my bag, to show that I have no idol,
but not if no one is willing to ask me."?
It's the sign of a good player.
We can claim to want to be as frank and clear as possible,
but there is always a part of mystery in this game
and everything can change in an instant.
I would invite people to consider those who are blindfolded.
Aren't they the weakest in the game?
Are they really the game changers?
Is this the minority?
Sierra. Hali says, "If you target me,
you are making a huge mistake.
Pick a real target, not me."
Yes, that clearly makes sense.
Free electrons are crucial, they define majorities.
But there is a moment to muster a majority.
Is it now?
Is this the start of the game? You don't know.
Good. It's time to vote.
Troyzan, over to you.
It's to save your life and mine.
Hopefully it brings us longevity in this game.
It's meaningless.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read, the decision is final.
The eliminated person will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Premier vote :
Zeke.
Two votes Zeke.
Michaela.
Status.
Even. Two votes Zeke,
two votes Michaela, two votes Hali.
That's three votes Michaela.
Halli. Three Hali votes.
Michaela. Four votes Michaela.
Halli. Four Hali votes,
four votes Michaela,
two votes Zeke.
Halli. That's five Hali votes.
Eighth person eliminated and first member of the jury...
Halli. That's six, that's enough. Bring me your torch.
Hali, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
I enjoyed getting to know each of you.
May the best win !
With this vote,
we have the first member of the jury.
Which means that now every vote
becomes part of your CV
in case you reach the final.
Take your torches, return to camp.
Good night.
I just feel like they're stupid.
Why did you eliminate me?
Do you want to face the strong and the strategists?
Or a bunch of puppets?
I'm happy to be a juror, to still be part of the game.
I don't know what mistake I made,
but whatever the reason for my departure,
they are still in play, so kudos to them.
Michaela, how did you sleep?
Perfectly well.
The most peaceful of sleeps.
Cirie put herself in danger for me on the council,
and I will do the same for her
if I have the chance.
I can't guarantee we stay in the game
that if you don't tell anyone about my role in this
or our discussions.
You should be able to trust me here.
I told you what would happen. I believe in you.
And I did everything in this direction. Here's Brad.
For someone of my origin,
a black american,
be able to play with another black American,
there is a level of spontaneous confidence.
So for now, I leave it to her.
She understands the different dynamics better than I do.
Above all, I don't want to harm her when she helped me.
What is being said?
You must know more than me.
Right now, you're the one informing me.
On the board, I voted for Michaela,
and Michaela for Zeke,
according to plan.
But I have my own ideas and I want to play my game.
So on the next tip, the dragon will be unleashed.
Everything will be revealed and the war will begin.
But hey... Brad and Sierra are united.
I don't even think we need them.
I know where I stand vis-à-vis them.
If we're going for Brad or Sierra, then...
We can go directly to the vote.
Sierra and Brad, as I see them,
Sierra is like the godfather.
She controls Brad
who controls Troyzan.
It's like a chain.
If we remove the first link,
the chain will be destroyed.
She could therefore be in the hot seat.
If we want to release Brad or Sierra,
I doubt anyone will object.
Zeke agrees.
Andrea is in.
I trust Agent Sarah,
and I know Michaela will follow. We are ready for war.
Armed to the teeth!
There are four people I'm sure of.
Zeke, moi, Andrea, Sarah.
Five with you.
Six with Michaela.
And seven with Ozzy.
I feel like I'm in the middle
of a fight in a large Italian family.
There are two camps and Cirie
is the black Italian grandmother.
Or the aunt. More like an aunt.
And if I gotta be in Cirie's band,
it's okay with me.
Just... Sorry.
Its good.
I wanted to talk to you long term.
It suits me that we are not fixed on the last five,
because we already have to get there,
but Sierra is eyeing around here, we're making her super nervous.
I'm dying to get Brad or Sierra out.
I'm starting to gather a majority
to gently take over,
which would be ideal.
Sierra and Brad,
we make them nervous.
And reciprocally.
Exactly.
But I don't think we can tell Debbie
or in Tai.
Debbie is going all out right now.
And she really likes Sierra.
Let's keep her out of it.
If you argue, I don't want... No, no!
We are resting.
In general, I have control.
But I don't see it quite clearly, so far.
'Cause most of my info comes from Cirie
and Andrea. They are the ones in control.
Something is wrong.
I do not occupy the position that I would like.
Debbie is not with us. I do not know.
Finally, yes, but it is unpredictable,
she will do whatever comes into her head.
The last time I played
I may have taken action too soon.
But if you have to have regrets,
is it better to regret having acted too quickly
or of not seizing an opportunity to act?
Better to regret having acted.
This is...
You have to play.
On sort Sierra.
Then Debbie.
It'll work, because she's shady.
That's why we shouldn't tell him about the vote against Sierra.
There will be enough of us to take it out then.
To be honest,
Brad and Sierra
are more or less dangerous,
but not that much.
But I see Cirie
and Andrea
as far more strategically dangerous than Sierra.
They try to control the game.
Then I could take out Cirie or Andrea.
To this vote, right now.
Why wait ?
Over here, everyone!
Ready for today's reward event?
Today you will be divided
into two teams of six.
At my signal,
two members of each team will swim
to retrieve a net filled with wooden fish.
You will bring it back to earth.
There, two other crew members will untie the fish,
hook them to a pole and bring them to the finish.
There, the last two team members
solve a puzzle with the fish.
The first team to do so wins the reward.
Want to know what's at stake? Yeah !
A day...
luxury.
Oh my God !
The winning team will leave for the lounge "Marshalls"
where you will enjoy a shower...
A shower ! ...with soaps and shampoos.
You will dry yourself
with Egyptian cotton towels.
Enough, Jeff!
You will relax in soft branded bathrobes
and pamper yourself with lotions.
And when you're clean,
a little more comfort
in the form of burgers.
Apple pie.
Apple pie !
It's worth it ?
We form the teams like a schoolyard and we go.
Let's go.
Oh my God !
Well, we have our two teams.
Sarah was captain.
She chose Culpepper,
Aubry, Michaela,
Cirie and Sierra.
Andrea was captain.
She chose Tai,
Ozzy, Troyzan,
Debbie and Zeke.
Here we go, for the reward.
A day of luxury.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
It's Sarah and Culpepper for the Oranges,
Troyzan and Ozzy for the Blues.
Troyzan takes care of the knots out of the water
while Ozzy dives.
Both Culpepper and Sarah are underwater.
Once detached,
start bringing in those fish!
Culpepper undid his knots out of the water.
Ozzy stayed underwater for a long time for the Blues.
Sarah et Culpepper
released their fish.
Good !
Troyzan and Ozzy are still struggling with the last knots.
There is a fish in the water.
Sarah, the fish! Go and get it !
Go get the fish!
Sarah and Culpepper, we have to get it back!
Go-y, Sarah!
Sarah swims towards the fish.
This allows Ozzy and Troyzan to return.
Come on, guys, keep going!
Culpepper now has to pull this very heavy net all by himself.
Troyzan and Ozzy close the gap.
Well done, Troy and Ozzy!
Great ! It's good !
The Blues now lead.
Biggest reward of the season.
Both teams
are clearly motivated.
Ozzy and Troy carry it and walk now.
You have to put it on the mat.
Go for it !
Now Andrea and Tai untie the fish from the Blues.
This is Culpepper and Sarah,
just behind.
We see the weight of these parts.
Drop it, it's good!
Sarah and Culpepper, it's over.
Aubry and Michaela's turn.
It's very tight.
Tai continues to untie,
Andrea hooks the fish.
Good Andrea!
There are 14 fish. They must be placed on all the hooks
then transport them to the "puzzle" station.
Michaela hooks the fish for the Oranges
while Aubry unties the knots.
There should be 14, two per hook.
To the right !
Ready? Go!
On court, on court !
Andrea and Tai take off.
You are missing one!
Hey, come back!
Come on, you're missing one!
Tai, don't!
Come on Tai!
Go back!
New setback for the Blues!
Andrea and Tai
lost time without having all the parts.
An opportunity for Michaela and Aubry,
who have all the parts.
They regain their heads.
Huge mistake by Tai and Andrea.
And we can see it,
at this very moment, exhaustion is setting in.
Its good !
Now, Sierra and Cirie
attack the puzzle for the Oranges.
Tai and Andrea thought they were well organized.
They went too fast.
It wasted a lot of their time.
Now they have to carry this pole,
again, until the finish.
Cirie and Sierra have already attacked the puzzle.
Zeke and Debbie must land all the coins
before you can start.
It's kind of a head start
which can make you win.
The Blues had a huge lead
and lost it.
Zeke and Debbie will have to make up time on the puzzle.
The "Marshalls" lounge for the winners.
A hot afternoon in camp for the losers.
You solve two puzzles side by side.
Both must be fair.
As with any good Survivor puzzle,
you won't know until the very end if it's right.
Cirie and Sierra finished a puzzle.
If that's right!
Debbie and Zeke attempt to climb back up.
Cirie and Sierra are starting to struggle
with their second puzzle.
It doesn't work nearly as well as the first one.
Wait, here, Debbie.
Zeke thinks he's got something.
Zeke and Debbie move very quickly.
It would be quite a comeback if they were successful.
Cirie and Sierra think they're on the right track.
Not, there, there! Celui-ci!
Zeke thinks he found it.
It will be played on the wire.
Who will finish first?
Hurry up ! We hurry!
Yes ! Jeff! Jeff!
Debbie and Zeke think they've found it.
And that's the case !
Le lounge "Marshalls"
for Zeke, Debbie, Troyzan, Tai, Ozzy and Andrea!
Andrea, Debbie, Zeke,
Troyzan, Ozzy, Tai.
You will pamper yourself, eat,
while the other six return to the camp.
You know what it is.
Take your things, let's go!
Oh my God !
We wasted the day at the "Marshalls" spa.
It's a big disappointment.
But I am in a central position.
I have options.
And it will be: which group wants to date the person I want to date?
This is the one I will go with.
We come back to the camp
after losing the "Marshalls" reward event.
No one is at fault.
It was up to Sierra and me to win it
and we didn't succeed today.
We feel miserable.
"Will I accomplish anything,
accomplish anything?"
Sometimes we crack and then it gets better.
I'm close to cracking.
I was a young mother, so I worked very hard
to meet their needs.
I wanted never
my children have a need that I cannot meet.
But this game
makes you feel the deepest
and painful feelings that you may have known.
Especially in defeat, like today.
Not being able to win for them,
it's like not being able to feed your family.
This game is so hard.
I always forget how hard it is.
Stopped. You're going to make me cry.
You don't have children yet, but imagine if you had
four children
and they haven't eaten for three days.
You are responsible for finding food for them.
and you fail.
You feel like a nobody.
Nobody wants to feel that.
I worked hard, in my life,
never to feel that way.
And that brings you right back to this:
"Are you good for nothing?" That's crazy.
It's heavy.
My family is my motivation.
I intend to win for her.
That's probably why I'm moved.
It's not your fault, Cirie.
I'm super excited!
Oh my God ! Yes !
Merci, Marshalls !
So cool !
Marshalls has concocted an incredible spa for us.
This is the biggest reward to date.
We have a shower!
There are very nice towels,
amazing relax chairs,
coconut shampoo and conditioner...
Lord !
Smell that, we would eat it!
Do you have the snacks? Oh my God !
Who wants Coke?
Arriving at the "Marshalls" spa,
I first noticed the smell.
Here, we are deprived of a lot of smells.
We all smell the campfire and the sweat.
So, to smell these pleasant perfumes,
just that,
it is a reward in itself.
I heard about streaking in the 80s.
Oh my God !
Tai, what the hell are you doing?!
Yeah, buddy!
Troy, you're next!
You weren't all doing that in the 60s or 70s?
I was not born! I was not born!
Oh, I know, you're all kids.
My ex-boyfriend was always talking about streaking in Arkansas.
I don't know, it seemed appropriate to me.
I promised myself to have fun.
And it was a fun time.
Are these cheeseburgers?
They are huge!
Rewards are great.
I'm having fun.
Like suddenly I wasn't in Survivor anymore.
It's the high life!
But by withdrawing from the game like this, sometimes you can get lost.
C'est Game changers.
Your mind must be working. If it doesn't work all the time,
you're probably not in the game anymore.
Marshalls was great!
I'm just saying, we could talk
what we would like to put in place over the next few hours.
We could target Brad and Sierra.
But Cirie and Andrea
are very close-knit.
We agree ? Is not it ?
I'm assembling a team of snipers.
'Cause I know war is coming.
Many think here
that it's going to start somehow.
But I'll make sure she starts my way.
Cirie has her own plans.
Cirie and Andrea are more or less with us now, but...
I talked to Andrea, and she said:
"Don't tell Debbie about it."
It may not be important.
Donc on sort Andrea.
Zeke throws a story
to get Tai and me to vote for Andrea.
I was immediately skeptical.
The first question we should always ask in Survivor,
it's: "Is this information true?"
I can't beat some of them.
Sometimes it's better to ask for forgiveness than to ask permission.
As in the Air Force: "Act, ask for forgiveness afterwards."
I find it hard to take what Zeke says
for cash.
Because he is trying to build a coalition.
But I don't have in mind to join Zeke's camp.
Make a big hit, okay.
But I don't know what that means for me.
I want to make a big hit, but I don't need Zeke.
Over here, everyone!
Wow.
Ready for today's immunity test?
First of all,
Andrea, I'm taking the necklace back.
Merci.
Once again, immunity is at stake.
Today,
you will cling to a pole
as long as you can.
When you let go, it's over.
The last person to hold
gain immunity.
The losers: on the board,
someone will be the ninth person eliminated
Game.
We draw the places at random and we start.
Good.
Everyone chose their starting location.
There are many different starting strategies.
And this ordeal
is thrown.
It's a Survivor classic.
It is not easy.
From the first moment, you struggle.
Sierra has competed in this event once.
She didn't win.
Ozzy wrestled her twice.
He didn't lose.
He is undefeated in this event.
in his career in Survivor.
No one else here has competed in this event.
Culpepper begins to slip.
15 seconds have passed
and it could last two hours.
Cirie slips quickly.
Cirie tries to have bon.
Non.
Cirie is the first eliminated.
Take a seat on the bench.
Sarah begins to move.
Culpepper slides down.
And... Finished!
Culpepper exits the ordeal.
You are only ten.
Debbie is sliding ever lower.
Sarah slides ever lower.
There is no comfortable location.
Aubry will come out of the ordeal.
No immunity for Aubry.
You are only nine, already.
Suddenly, Debbie descends and leaves the event,
by giving up some skin in Fiji.
It's clear !
You are only eight.
Zeke is eliminated.
You are only seven, it goes quickly.
Damn, that hurts!
This is serious.
It's way harder than it looks.
Sierra is eliminated.
You are only six.
Half the tribe is eliminated.
Troyzan is at its last fulcrum.
Sarah is at her last foothold.
Troyzan...
The body finally gives in.
Well done, my friend!
Bel effort.
Sarah suit Troyzan.
His body gives in.
Ozzy, you're one hell of a champion! More than four.
Michaela,
Andrea,
Or you don't Ozzy,
who compete for an immunity collar.
ELAPSED TIME, 20 MINUTES
There is no good grip on this post.
Michaela gives the impression of standing on her fulcrum,
which is amazing.
Andrea lutte
to hold on.
I intend to break my record!
Andrea. Basically, he said,
in other words, you don't stand a chance.
It is justified.
I think it can happen again.
Michaela adjusts her grip and goes down.
Bravo !
She comes down from the pole.
Wow, Michaela, what happened?
Ozzy won't come down.
So... I have to think and choose my battles.
You assured.
ELAPSED TIME, 40 MINUTES
Your feet are starting to hurt.
You've been in balance for quite a while.
Andrea replaces.
Always in the race.
Tai didn't move.
Ozzy didn't move.
Lord !
Big fall for Andrea. How are you ?
Yes. I didn't want to slip.
Andrea quits the ordeal.
Which leaves us face to face,
Tai versus Ozzy.
two guys
who seem very comfortable in the trees
or hung on a pole.
ELAPSED TIME, 1 HOUR
It's been an hour.
Lord ! Good job guys !
To do one of the hardest things in your life.
It brings them back
in the "legends" category,
to stay on this damn thing like that.
Tai is replaced.
We must keep this body alive.
He goes numb quickly.
Ozzy se replace.
Ozzy, how confident are you,
knowing that you did it twice and won twice?
I know what comes next.
And it's rough.
We start to suffer, to sweat, to slip...
But I already did
and if I win, I can go fishing today.
But otherwise...
We will be hungry one more day.
That's using your influence!
Sorry, buddy!
No problem.
I try my luck.
ELAPSED TIME, 1 HOUR 35 MINUTES
Tai and Ozzy, in similar positions.
Like two monkeys clinging to a tree.
No problem.
Ozzy repositions himself slightly.
Hands can go up to the rope, not over it.
Ozzy try
to keep his record.
Tai begins to move.
Ozzy repositions himself again.
Nice recovery.
Tai moved a lot
after standing still.
Tai struggles to find a foothold.
Ozzy slides down
and Ozzy is eliminated from the event!
Tai wins individual immunity!
He dethrones Ozzy,
who had never lost.
He sends Ozzy,
and all the others,
to the board without immunity. You are a beast!
Tai will be safe.
Good job guys !
Amazing, guys!
Unbelievable !
You are bleeding. Well done, my friend!
Tai, come here!
I can't believe I beat Ozzy!
The queen, the double champion!
The king, the king! Not the queen!
From king to queen!
I wanted to go as far as him.
I have to say, it was an epic ordeal.
Tai, you won.
You're safe at the council tonight.
As for you others,
tonight someone will be eliminated from Survivor Game Changers.
Take your things, return to camp. See you tonight at the council.
I believe the camps are beginning to form.
You have to choose one
fast enough, on pain of being on the losing side.
It will be crazy advice,
as he could define the rest of the season.
Look at this!
It tore the skin off my feet.
After the ordeal, back at the camp,
I was glad Andrea didn't win immunity,
because I am preparing for THE battle of the season:
Eliminate Andrea.
It is your name that is mentioned for the vote.
By Cirie, Andrea and Aubry.
But I'm not really interested in doing that.
What interests me is that Andrea leaves.
I thought you were pretty close to them.
You might think so, but no.
Zeke suddenly seems to want to switch sides.
But every time I talk to him,
I feel like he thinks I'm stupid.
And I don't trust him.
But if they mention my name,
I have to find a way to have a majority
to avoid leaving.
I was told that my name was mentioned.
It was Zeke.
Sierra approached me and said Zeke told her
that she was going to be eliminated.
Why the hell do that?
No idea. It does not make sense.
I'm furious with Zeke.
I've been working with him since day one.
I thought we were not only allies, but also friends.
Best would be to take Zeke out.
How to achieve it?
Impossible.
I learned that in this game, timing is everything.
And between Cirie and me, everything is fine.
I want her on my side, voting with me
against other people, like Zeke.
Elle a dit : "Zeke me l'a dit."
Really ? Yes.
I was disgusted to hear that.
I am disgusted. We have to get Zeke out.
I can't... Is this the new plan?
How can he believe that it will turn out well for him?
So that !
What does your instinct tell you?
The voter Zeke.
What are you going to tell Zeke?
Aubry ?
You know, do you really want to take the hand?
On vote Ozzy.
I'm in.
And I would.
But deal with these idiots,
it's almost mission impossible.
We could make the decision
and impose it on them, this time.
It would be a huge and awesome blow.
We did it.
If you follow us and shut up...
No doubt about it. We take out Ozzy.
This evening ? Yes.
Oh my God !
You love Me ?
I don't mind being thought of as eccentric.
Underestimate me at your peril.
But if everyone listens to me,
Brad, Sierra, Sarah, Troyzan, Tai...
We take Ozzy out by surprise, we don't tell anyone.
...it'll work, and we'll be great game changers tonight.
Largely thanks to me.
And I have an extra vote.
I don't want to use it so soon,
but I don't know if I have a majority.
We vote Ozzy, we'll take him out by surprise.
At this stage,
I am in the middle of two groups
which are beginning to emerge.
Brad's group, Sierra,
Troyzan,
This, Debbie,
wants to eliminate Ozzy.
And there is another group:
Cirie,
Andrea,
Michaela,
Aubry
et Ozzy.
They want to take Zeke out.
And I'm weighing my options.
sort Ozzy,
it's out a social and physical threat.
This is the move to do soon after the merger.
But many want Zeke out,
because he is smart
and ready to hit.
And if we trust someone like that,
we end up being had.
My position is therefore difficult.
But with this vote, a demarcation will be established.
Here is now the first member of the jury.
Hali, eliminated at the last council.
Ozzy.
You are among those who have participated the most in this game.
What is unique about this season?
Somehow, the stakes seem higher.
Everybody's trying to act like a secret agent,
it spies behind every coconut tree,
idols appear
then become untraceable,
where were found...
The mentality is more ruthless.
Sarah.
It is the 24th day.
There have been so many changes, different tribes.
Is it hard to know where the real relationships are?
Oui.
I don't know who is with whom.
We're like a bunch of bachelors looking for partners.
So if anyone wants to ask me out on a date,
I'm available.
Tai. In a game where mistrust is so important,
gain immunity
becomes very important.
Yes. I surprised myself.
When I run a marathon
it's one step at a time.
But I feel the need to do it, for myself.
Me against Ozzy, and no longer alone on the post.
And so, Ozzy.
You had never lost this event.
You lose and return to camp.
You definitely feel pressure.
Still.
We talk to as many people as possible
and we have to trust
to those who say you can trust them.
I have value in this game,
because there is nothing to eat in the camp.
So I'll give my all
to make sure people are fed.
It's no small thing to be able to offer that.
Especially when there are 15 days left.
Aubry.
You've played before, so you know how it feels.
After 24 days,
could you hold out if no one caught fish?
I have to say, Jeff, it's a lot harder than my first time.
Apart from the fact that everyone is suspicious,
it's hard. Coconuts, proteins,
we only get it when Ozzy brings it back.
And it's not just physical,
it's mental, it's moral.
I think we've all had our emotional moments.
And it affects everything.
Alors, Zeke.
In Survivor you want to reach the end
and make sure you put people on the jury
who will vote for you.
Is this still the approach to follow?
I think we follow more or less the same rules,
we say to ourselves: "Can I beat this or that?"
One must also ask oneself: "Do they think they can beat me?"
And if I think they think
that they can't beat me,
how do i introduce myself
so they think they can beat me?
It's the most complicated in this season,
find a way to say:
"I know that you fear me for such and such a reason,
but it's actually not an asset,
on the contrary, it is what will enable you to beat me."
Tai. Did you notice a difference between your first participation
and this one, in terms of subtlety,
nuances of communication,
when English is not your mother tongue?
Yes, it's incredibly different.
Everyone is very suspicious.
And even now, hearing that,
I'm like, "Wow, now I get it!"
What Zeke just said? Exactly.
It's incredible,
his way of seeing things from different angles.
It had never occurred to me to think about it like this.
Zeke, when you hear another player, on the board,
say, "He's amazing!"
do you want to say:
"Oh no, please don't say that right before the vote!" ?
There is always a minimum of worry, that's for sure.
But sometimes I think it's gonna be okay for me.
And these moments of peace are necessary to last 24 days.
Otherwise, I'd be on my toes all the time.
Debbie. At the end of the day, Survivor is all about strategy.
Who to eliminate, who you think will vote for you
if you go to the end?
Absolutely.
As an Air Force Auxiliary,
one must gather facts, evaluate information,
make a plan, execute it.
The difference,
it's that the people around me would have my back.
These people are pointing their daggers at my back!
This is madness.
So,
I don't know who I am with.
It's crazy.
Ciri. what did you think about,
today, thinking about who to eliminate?
Well, in this moment,
to whom, in my opinion,
showed a certain level
of confidence so that I can believe his words,
or vice versa.
This is how I determine my vote tonight.
Good. It's time to vote.
Sierra, over to you.
Terrible initiative, you suck at this game.
I hope never to see you again.
It's just to spice it up.
I will count the votes.
Jeff.
Before that...
And so, in Exile,
I gave up the vital essential
to be able to have an advantage in the game.
And that benefit is...? An additional vote.
And you're going to use it tonight. Yes.
Good. Go use your extra vote.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read, the decision is final.
The eliminated person will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Premier vote :
Ozzy.
Zeke.
Sierra.
Aubrey. One Aubry vote,
a Zeke vote,
vote Sierra,
un vote Ozzy.
Zeke. Deux votes Zeke.
Ozzy. Two Ozzy votes.
Zeke. That's three Zeke votes.
Ozzy. Three Ozzy votes,
three votes Zeke.
Zeke. Quarter votes Zeke.
Ozzy. Quatre votes Ozzy,
four votes Zeke.
That's crazy.
Ozzy. That's five Ozzy votes,
four votes Zeke.
Ninth person eliminated and second member of the jury...
Ozzy. That's six, that's enough. Bring me your torch.
I don't know, man.
Ozzy, the tribe has spoken.
Bravo.
Good luck with the food.
It's time to go.
Well, it's very clear,
in view of the reactions,
that after all these debates on mistrust,
a punch has just been given.
Take your torches, return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
We don't take gloves anymore.
You are all weird.
Will I trust Zeke again?
Of course not.
An alliance seems invincible.
Now that we have Sarah,
the boundary is concrete.
But nothing is set in stone.
We can take a hit.
And how do I want to make a hit!
I didn't see it coming.
But I knew it was inevitable.
I played hard. I must have overestimated my worth.
But if we don't win immunity, we don't have an idol,
we meet in my place.
Survivor is a way of life.
It changed me in an unforgettable way.
I am infinitely grateful.