>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT EXILE ISLAND,
DEBBIE WAS LIVING IN THE LAP OF
LUXURY WITH COCHRAN.
>> I'M PRESENTING YOU WITH AN
ADVANTAGE OPTION.
>> I'M TAKING THE EXTRA VOTE.
>> Jeff: AT THE MANA TRIBE,
BRAD WAS WORKING HIS WAY TO THE
TOP.
>> I'M IN WITH SIERRA.
YOU JUST ARE TO STICK WITH US.
>> Jeff: AT THE NUKU TRIBE,
VARNER AND SANDRA WERE AT THE
BOTTOM BUT TAI BECAME PARANOID.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS A CHANCE THEY
MIGHT BLIND SIDE ME.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL...
>> IF TAI WANTS TO SPIT OUT A
NAME, I'M VOTE WITH YOU, TAI.
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> I NAMED AS YOU.
>> Jeff: BY THROWING OZZY
UNDER THE BUS.
IN THE END, SANDRA WAS TOO BIG
OF A THREAT.
SANDRA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> DON'T DO IT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE JOINED THE
NUKU TRIBE.
>> THAT TRIBAL WAS SCARIER THAN
EXILE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> HOW WAS IT?
>> WOOO!
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> OH, I'M GOOD.
I MAY BE THE ONLY PERSON WHO HAS
EVER GOT TO SIT IN AND BE PRIVY
TO A TRIBAL COUNCIL LIKE THAT
WITHOUT HAVING JURY DUTY.
AND NOW SANDRA IS GONE, AND I AM
BACK WITH NUKU, WHERE I BELONG.
IT'S GOOD TO BE HOME.
>> IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> OH, GOD.
>> I HOPE EXILE WASN'T TOO
TERRIBLE?
>> IT WAS, BUT--
>> HEY.
>> THAT'S WHY I'M PLAYING THIS
GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> THERE WAS NO FLIPT, YOU GUYS?
>> THERE WAS NO FLINT?
>> NO.
>> SO PEOPLE ASKED ME ABOUT
EXILE.
LOOK, WHAT HAPPENED ON EXILE
STAYS ON EXILE.
AND I HAVE NO INTENTION OF
LETTING MYSELF OR MR. COCHRAN
DOWN.
LIPS ARE SEALED.
>.GREAT TO BE BACK.
>> ME, TOO.
I WAS ABOUT TO VOTE TAI OUT.
>> YOU WERE WORRIED, REALLY?
NO, YOU WERE NOT.
>> I WAS SUPER WORRIED AND IT'S
ONLY BECAUSE IT WAS ONE OF THOSE
THINGS--
>> YOUR NAME.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE JUST LIKE OH, MY
GOD.
>> THE CONVERSATION CONFUSED ME.
I SAID MY GOD.
I MIGHT BE AT THE BOTTOM RIGHT
NOW.
AND OZZY IS THE ONLY NAME THAT
MAKES SENSE.
OZZY IS A THREAT.
HE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
I SAY IT OUT LOUD BECAUSE I
THINK I NEED TO GO THERE.
I'M TERRIBLE AT TRIBAL AND THAT
WORRIED ME A LITTLE BIT.
>> WHEN YOU GUYS STARTED TALKING
ABOUT OZZY, I COVERED MY HANDS
OVER AND WAS PEEK OUT LIKE IT
WAS A HORROR MOVIE.
I WAS LIKE, "DON'T YOU GUYS TURN
ON HIM."
I WAS PEEKING OUT MY FINGERS.
I THOUGHT OH, MY GOD, THIS IS
WORSE THAN EXILE.
LEAST I HAD PEACE THERE.
>> SO IN CASE MY NAME IS OUT
THERE, I HAVE TWO IDOLS, BUT I'M
NERVOUS.
SOMEHOW THIS THING HAPPENS...
>> YOU GUYS REALLY BURNED A LOT
OF WOOD.
>> WE DID I GOT BLINDSIDES BIG
TIME.
THOSE BITCHES EVERY ONE OF THEM.
I WANT TO PUNCH THEM ALL IN THE
THROAT BOARNG EVERY ONE OF THEM.
I'M MAD BUT I CAN'T SHOW IT.
I CAN'T LET THEM KNOW THAT I'M
MAD BECAUSE I NEED THEM.
>> I'M SO SORRY ABOUT NOT
INCLUDING YOU IN THE VOTE
TONIGHT.
IT SHOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> BUT--
>> IT'S A NAME GAME, YOU KNOW,
AND I'VE NOT INCLUDED PEOPLE IN
MY PLANS, TOO, SO IT'S MY TURN
TO GET BLINDSIDED AND IT'S OKAY.
I'M STILL HERE.
I WOULD HAVE VOTED FOR HER
WITHOUT TELLING HER ANYTHING.
WE DIDN'T HAVE TO DO ALL THAT.
I WENT TO WORK IMMEDIATELY.
WHY NOT?
I MEAN, WHY WAIT?
AND I HAD A GREAT CONVERSATION
ZEKE, AND ZEKE JUST POURED
EVERYTHING OUT TO ME.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL-- SO I'M
GOING TO BE, LIKE, PERFECTLY
HONEST WITH YOU, RIGHT?
YOU CAN TAKE THIS INFORMATION
AND DO WHAT YOU WANT WITH IT.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I
AM VERY SINCERE IN WORKING WITH
YOU TO THE END OF THIS GAME.
I DON'T WANT TO GET YOU A SEAT
ON THE JURY.
I WANT TO GET YOU A SEAT IN THE
FINAL THREE.
YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> I'VE BEEN THERE.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
I'M ALL RIGHT WITH IT.
I APPRECIATE IT.
I REALLY LIKE YOU AND I HOPE WE
CAN BE FRIENDS.
>> ME, TOO.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
JUST, YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO LIE TO ME.
>> NO MORE LIES FROM HEREON OUT.
>> I PROMISE.
>> WHATEVER YOU WANT TO KNOW.
>> ZEKE AND I HAVE BONDED, AND I
THINK HE GENUINELY FEELS BAD
ABOUT WHAT HE DID TO ME TONIGHT.
SO I'M NOT DONE JUST YET.
Captioning funded by CBS
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
MANA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW NUKU TRIBE.
>> OH!
SANDRA.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, THE ONLY
TWO-TIME WINNER FINALLY VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR" AFTER 94 DAYS
OF PLAYING THE GAME.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: AND DEBBIE JOINS THE
NEW NUKU TRIBE.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO WORK
TOGETHER TO UNSPOOL ROPES
RELEASING A KEY.
YOU'LL THEN BUILD A LADDER,
CLIMB TO THE TOP, USE THE KEY TO
UNLOCK A BAG OF BALLS.
YOU'LL THEN SQUEEZE THROUGH A
NET SLING TO THE FINISH, WILL
ATTEMPT TO LAND THE BALLS IN A
SERIES OF TARGETS.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ONE BALL IN
EACH OF THE FIVE TARGETS WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> YES!
>> AAH!
>> PIZZA!
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> PIZZA!
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" PIZZA.
>> OH, MY GOD!
CAN WE HAVE A BITE JUST TO TASTE
IT?
>> CAN WE GET A SAMPLE?
>> Jeff: NO SAMPLES.
YOU WANT IT YOU GOTTA EARN IT.
10 PIZZAS.
PEPPERONI, CHEESE, MEAT LOVERS,
VEGETARIAN.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> HAWAIIAN.
>> HAWAIIAN!
>> Jeff: AND ICE COLD SOFT
DRINKS TO GO ALONG WITH IT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE
AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO, FOR REWARD IN THE FORM OF
PIZZA AND SOFT DRINKS, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
>> BE STILL, BE STILL!
>> Jeff: IT IS SIERRA LEADING
HALI AND KAYLA FOR NUKU.
FIRST PART OF THIS IS WORKING
TOGETHER TO UNSPOOL THAT ROPE TO
DROP THE KEY.
OZZY, ANDREA, AND SIERRA IN THE
LEAD RIGHT NOW, AND SIERRA,
HALI, AND MICHAELA HAVING A LOT
OF TROUBLE.
>> THAT'S IT!
>> Jeff: GREAT COMMUNICATION
BY OZZY, SARAH, AND ANDREA RIGHT
NOW.
>> YOU GOT IT!
THAT'S IT!
THAT'S IT.
>> Jeff: THEY'VE GOT IT.
UNHOOK!
YOU'RE GOOD!
GET THAT KEY AND GET TO THE MAT!
>> NOW WE ALL GO.
>> Jeff: NUKU WITH A NICE LEAD
NOW.
ONE PERSON--
>> TAI, GO!
>> Jeff: UNTIES THE LADDER
RUNGS.
IT'S GOING TO BE TAI.
>> HALI, MICHAELA, UNDER YOUR
HOOK.
>> Jeff: MANA HAS THEIR KEY
RELEASED.
>> LET'S GO!
>>
>> Jeff: LET'S GMANA!
TAI IS RIPPING THROUGH THOSE
KNOTS.
IT'S GOING TO BE AUBRY ON THE
KNOTS FOR MANA.
GO!
IT IS NOW VARNER AND ZEKE
WORKING TOGETHER TO BUILD THE
LADDER.
AUBRY HAS MADE UP A LOT OF TIME.
AUBRY'S GOT IT, GO!
IT'S NOW CULL PEPP CULLPEPPER
AND TROYZAN WORKING TOGETHER.
THERE'S A HUGE REWARD ON THE
LINE-- PIZZA AND SOFT DRINKS.
DEBBIE HEADS UP NOW TO RELEASE
THAT BAG OF BALLS.
CULLPEPPER AND TROYZAN WORKING
TOGETHER.
>> FASTER, DEBBIE, FASTER, GO,
GO.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE HAS THE BALLS.
HEAD OVER NUKU.
MANA HAS GOT TO PICK IT UP!
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: GU, NUKU.
NUKU CONTINUES TO LEAD IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
CIRIE GOES TO THE TOP.
NUKU MAKING THEIR WAY THROUGH
THE NET SWING.
MANA LOSING A LOT OF TIME.
>> GO, OZZY, GO!
>> Jeff: ALWAYSY IS THROUGH.
YOU CAN UNTIE THE BALLS.
>> I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: CIRIE HAS THE BALLS.
EVERYBODY UP AND OVER.
MANA TRYING TO MAKE UP MORE TIME
AGAIN.
NUKU HAS BEEN IN THE LEAD FROM
THE GET-GO.
>> HERE THEY COME, OZZY, HURRY.
>> Jeff: OZZY HAS THE BALLS.
HE'S GOING TO START LAUNCHING.
>> YOU GOT IT, OZZY.
>> Jeff: HERE'S COMES MANA.
IT IS NOT EASY TO GET THROUGH
THAT NET OZZY LAUNCHES AGAIN.
OZZY CONNECTS, SCORES ONE FOR
NUKU!
GO, SIERRA!
>> THIS IS YOURS, SIERRA!
THIS IS YOURS TO WIN.
>> Jeff: OZZY LAUNCHES AGAIN
FOR NUKU, AND HE CONNECTS.
OZZY HAS THE SECOND TARGET.
SIERRA HAS THE BALLS FREE.
>> THERE IT IS, BABY.
>> Jeff: AND HE CONNECTS FOR
NUKU.
NUKU WITH THREE!
MANA WITH ZERO!
CULLPEPPER GOING TO TAKE OVER
FOR MANA.
OZZY LAUNCH AGAIN.
>> OH, MY GOD, THERE IT IS!
>> Jeff: JUST MISSES.
CULLPEPPER QUICKLY SCORES WITH
HIS FIRST HIT.
MANA HAS ONE NOW, IT IS 3-1.
OZZY LOOKING FOR NUMBER FOUR.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
ONE LEFT FOR NUKU.
CULLPEPPER TRYING TO PICK UP THE
PACE NOW.
NUKU HAS FOUR, OZZY FOR THE WIN.
AND NAND OUT.
OPENS THE DOOR FOR CULLPEPPER
BUT HE CAN'T GET IT TO DROP.
OZZY COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE AND
HE DOES!
NUKU WINS PEETS DIS PIZZA AND
SOFT DRINKS BACK AT CAMP!
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD, PIZZA!
>> Jeff: NUKU, NICE JOB, BIG
WIN, PIZZA, SOFT DRINKS.
COME GET IT.
HAVE A GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NICE GUY.
>> SMELL NATHA!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MANA, GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> THE PIZZA WOULD HAVE MADE A
WORLD OF DIFFERENCE.
I MEAN, I'M FROM JERSEY, I'M AS
TOUGH AS THEY COME, BUT CERTAIN
THINGS YOU BREAK DOWN.
IT'S BEEN 17 DAYS.
IT'S ROUGH.
IT'S TAXING ON YOU PHYSICALLY,
EMOTIONALLY.
SO WE DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> 10 PIZZAS.
>> IT'S GOING TO MAKE THEM
SLUGUSH.
>> THAT'S MORE THAN A PIZZA
APIECE.
WHEN WE LOST 10 WHOLE PIZZAS, I
TRIED TO HOLD MY HEAD HIGH, BUT
I AM EXHAUSTED.
I HAVEN'T ATE FOR THREE DAYS.
I CAN'T SLEEP AT NIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE LOST A CRAP-TON
OF WEIGHT.
I MEAN, IT IS 100% REAL RIGHT
NOW.
THIS GAME IS HARD.
I CRIED BEFORE I CAME.
I WAS LIKE--
>> ME, TOO.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO
YOURSELF?
YEAH.
>> IT'S SO MUCH MORE THAN THE
HUNGER.
>> BUT YOU LOVE IT?
>> I KNOW.
WHEN YOU GET TO A CERTAIN POINT
ON "SURVIVOR," YOUR MIND GOES TO
PLACES YOU DON'T THINK IT'S
GOING TO GO, AND WHEN YOU GET
HOME, IT'S REALLY, REALLY HARD
TO EXPLAIN WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH.
AFTER I PLAYED, WHEN I WENT
HOME, PEOPLE SAID, "WHY ARE YOU
DIFFERENT?"
AND I COULDN'T SAY WHY.
>> ARE YOU CRYING NOW?
STOP!
>> I DON'T EVER CRY.
>> I'M KIND OF CRYING, TOO.
IT'S SO HARD.
IF YOU'VE NEVER DONE TYOU DON'T
REALIZE WHAT YOU GO THROUGH.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> IT IS.
IT'S A LONG-- A LONG JOURNEY.
>> YOU KNOW, I PLAYED THE GAME.
I PLAYED FOR 12 DAYS.
I DIDN'T HOW HARD IT WAS ON
MONICA TO GET THIS FAR.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE GOT HOME AND SHE WAS---
SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, SHE HURT.
I NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHY SHE WAS
HURTING.
I MEAN, IT'S ONLY BEEN 17 DAYS,
BUT I GET IT.
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME.
GOD.
I GOTTA GO WASH MY CLOTHES.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOOD.
WHEN MONICA AND I PLAYED "BLOOD
AND WATER" SHE GOT ALL THE WAY
TO DAY 39, AND I DON'T KNOW I
TRULY APPRECIATED UNTIL I, YOU
KNOW, HAVE BEEN HERE FOR 17
DAYS.
FOR HER TO DO WHAT SHE DSHE'S A
TOUGH COOKIE.
IT'S KIND OF BEEN A GUIDE FOR
ME.
I GUESS SHE'S BEEN MY STRENGTH
AND MY COMPASS RIGHT ON MY ARM.
>> I CAN JUST SAY THANK YOU FOR
OPENING UP LIKE THAT BECAUSE
NOBODY EVER GETS AT HOME
EVERYONE IS LIKE, "YOU CHANGED.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
AND I'M LIKE, "YOU REALLY DON'T
GET IT."
>> NO.
>> SO THAT MEANT A LOT TO ME.
>> OKAY.
>> I AM CONSISTENTLY AMAZED AT
BRAD CULPEPPER AND HIS ABILITY
TO OPEN UP.
LIKE, BRAD IS TO ME THE MOST
GENUINE PERSON THAT I'VE MET OUT
HERE.
AND IT'S THE FIRST TIME I FEEL
LIKE I THINK I HAVE A PERSON
WORKING WITH ME.
>> PURE EMOTION.
I COULD FEEL IF.
IT WAS, LIKE, PALPABLE.
SO REAL.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
I'M IMPRESSED WITH YOU, GIRL.
>> LIKEWISE.
>> CIRIE AND AUBRY CAME UP AND
SAID IT'S SO SPECIAL YOU SAID
THAT BECAUSE THEY SAW THE REAL
ME, AND SURPRISINGLY, MADE US
FEEL CLOSER AND REALLY
GALVANIZED MY RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN THOSE TWO.
TROYZAN, SIERRA, AND MYSELF HAVE
ALREADY GOT A GOOD CONNECTION.
SO I THINK IT SLIDDIFIES THE
FIVE PEOPLE I HAVE ON THIS SIDE
AS FAR AS WHO I WANT TO GO WITH.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> OH, MY GOD.
LET'S EAT!
>> WE DOMINATED THE REWARD
CHALLENGE.
IT WAS EPIC.
>> CHEERS!
>> AT THIS STAGE OF THE GAME,
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR THE
TRIBE MORAL TO WIN SOMETHING
LIKE THAT BECAUSE THE GAME IS
JUST STARTING TO WEAR ON PEOPLE,
AND THE EXTRA BOOST IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, MY GOOD GOD!
>> I'M GOING TO DESTROY THIS
PIZZA.
>> I'LL EAT THIS WHOLE THING.
>> IT FELT SO GOOD TO FINALLY
JUMP UP AND DOWN AND SAY, "WE
WON."
BUT I'M ON THE BOTTOM WHEN YOU
LOOK AT IT.
SO TO WIN SOMETHING LIKE THAT
DOESN'T MEAN A DAMN THING.
>> OH, MY GOD, OZZY, MAY I JUST
SAY, YOU'RE A BEAST, BABE.
>> IT WAS ALL YOU GUYS JUST
DIRECTING ME HOW TO DO IT
BECAUSE I COOPERATE HAVE DONE
IT.
>> I AM THINKING TO MYSELF, IF I
WANT TO SAVE MY OWN BUTT OUT
HERE.
>> HAVE TO FIND THE WAY TO THROW
THE SHADE ON SMEBLES.
OZZY IS WELL ROUNDED, HE'LL WIN
THIS GAME.
OZZY IS VERY STRONG.
YOU LET HIM LOOSE IN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES, HE'LL WIN
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM SO NOW
IS THE TIME TO GET RID OF OZZY.
NOW IS THE TIME.
GUYS NEED ME AS MUCH AS I NEED
YOU WHEN IT COMES TO A MERGE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND I THINK IT WILL BE GOOD.
>> YEAH.
OKAY, SO, SAY WE MERGE.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'VE GOT
PEOPLE OVER THERE THAT WE CAN
BRING IN?
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
TODAY, AFTER THE REWARD, VARNER
STARTS SAYING, "I REALLY WANT TO
WORK WITH YOU GUYS."
AND I THINK WE CAN PULL VARNER
AND ACTUALLY USE HIM AS A
NUMBER.
AND I REALLY, TRULY FEEL WE HAVE
MADE THAT CONNECTION.
SO DO YOU HAVE YOUR EYES ON
ANYONE THAT YOU WANT TO GET RID
OF FIRST, EAR DO YOU NOT CARE
AND WE CAN LET EVERYONE ELSE
DECIDE?
>> I WANT TO GET RID OF OZZY.
>> YOU DO.
>> I DO?
>> JUST SO WE ALL HAVE A
FIGHTING CHANCE.
I'M SICK OF WATCHING "SURVIVOR"
WHERE ALL THE A.PEOPLE GET TO
THE END AND PEOPLE LIKE US JUST
SORT OF SIT THERE AND HOPE HE
LOSES.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
I'D LIKE TO WIN THAT NECKLACE
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
>> I KNOW, I WANT TOW WIN ONE.
THEN HE SAYS COULD OZZY
POTENTIALLY BE THE VOTE?
THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKING OF
RIGHT NOW.
I NEED TO BE CAREFUL BECAUSE
THAT'S A HUGE MOVE BUT I'M READY
TO PROVE WHY I AM A GAME
CHANGER.
>> THIS IS ELIMINATION NUMBER
SEVEN, AND THAT'S WHEN YOU START
TAKING OFF THE BIG, PHYSICAL
THREATS.
I'M GOOD.
I'M GREAT.
>> WE'RE CLOSE TO A MERGE, AND
WE NEED TO TAKE OUT WHO IS THE
BIGGEST THREAT.
IT MIGHT BE TIME TO CUT OZZY'S
THROAT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS.
>> IF AUBRY, WE'VE GOT TO TAKE
IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, FOUR
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE SWIM OUT
TO A RAFT.
YOU'LL THEN PULL YOURSELF TO A
SERIES OF STATIONS.
AT EACH STATION, YOU'LL DIVE
DOWN, RELEASE A SET OF BOWIES,
PLACE THEM IN A BAG.
ONCE YOU HAVE COLLECTED ALL THE
BUOYS, THE THREE REMAINS TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL USE THEM TO SOLVE A
13-LETTER WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMIEWNTS, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SEVENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THE
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS."
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
IN THE WATER FOR NUKU IT IS TAI,
ZEKE, SARAH, OZZY.
IN THE WATER FOR MANA AUBRY,
HALI, CULPEPPER, TROYZAN.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU'RE ONLY AS FAST AS YOUR
SLOWEST SWIMMER.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET TO THAT
FIRST PLATTFORM, THEN YOU CAN
START PULLING YOUR RAFT.
GO, NUKU!
>> PULL!
>> Jeff: GO, MANA!
BOTH TRIBES PULLING QUICKLY.
>> PULL!
>> Jeff: NUKU OFF TO A BIT OF
A LEAD.
MANA SLOWER OUT OF THE GATE.
ONCE YOU'RE ACROSS FROM THE
BUOY, YOU CAN GET IN THE WATER.
OZZY IS IN THE WATER.
CULPEPPER IN THE WATER FOR MANA.
IT TAKES OZZY NO TIME AT ALL.
OZZY RELEASES THAT FIRST BAG OF
BUOYS.
GOTTA GET THEM ALL BACK TO THE
RAFT!
CULPEPPER POPS UP WITHOUT THE
FIRST BAG, GOTTA GO BACK DOWN.
THIS IS GOING TO OPEN THE LEAD
FOR NUKU.
CULPEPPER HAS HIS RELEASED.
NUKU LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND SET
OF BUOYS.
CULPEPPER STILL TRYING TO GET
THE BUOYS BACK TO HIS RAFT.
OZZY DOES IT IN ONE BREATH,
RELEASES THE NEXT ACCEPT THE OF
BUOYS, AND QUICKLY GATHERS THEM.
NUKU CONTINUES THEIR LEAD IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
GO, MANA!
CULPEPPER FINALLY HAS ALL THE
BUOYS FROM THAT FIRST BAG.
NUKU HAS THEIR SECOND SET OF
BUOYS.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR THAT THIRD
AND FINAL SET OF BUOYS.
AUBRY GOING TO GIVE IT A GO THIS
TIME FOR MANA.
OZZY BACK IN THE WATER FOR NUKU.
AND ONCE AGAIN, OZZY IS DOWN AND
BACK UP, EXTENDING THE LEAD FOR
NUKU.
AUBRY SUPFOR MANA.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: NUKU HAS ALL THEIR
BUPEEPS THEY'RE HEADING TO THE
FINISH.
NUKU NOW WITH A HUGE LEAD.
GOTTA GET IT IN THE BAG.
AUBRY'S GOT TO GET ON!
GO, MANA.
NUKU WITH THE BOWIES.
VARNER, DEBBIE, AND ANDREA
WORKING ON FIGURING OUT THAT
13-LETTER PUZZLE.
>> YOU GOT IT, BRAD!
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER DIVES BACK
IN FOR MANA.
CULPEPPER BACK UP FOR MANA WITH
THAT LAST SET OF BUOYS, BUT NUKU
IS ALREADY STARTING ON THIS WORD
PUZZLE.
GO, MANA!
MANA HAS THEIR THIRD SET OF
BUPEEPS THEY'VE GOT A LOT OF
TIME TO MAKE UP.
MANA IS BACK.
GET THOSE BUOYS.
NOW SYSTEM CIRIE, SIERRA, AND
MICHAELA GOING TO START WORKING
ON THAT WORD PUZZLE.
IT IS ANDREA, DEBBIE, AND VARNER
SOLVING FOR NUKU.
AND THEY'VE HAD TIME TO START
LOOKING AT THESE LETTERS.
BIG TIME ADVANTAGE FOR NUKU.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKING.
>> TRY "SHIPMASTER."
>> Jeff: MANA IS GOING TO
REARRANGE LETTERS AND SEE IF
THEY CAN FIGURE THAT OUT.
EVERYONE RUNNING WORDS IN THEIR
HEADS, TRYING DIFFERENT LETTER
COMBINATIONS.
WHAT COULD IT BE.
ANDREA AND VARNER HAVE A NEW
IDEA.
WILL THIS BE IT?
>> MY GOD, THIS IS TOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
>> LET'S TRY SOMETHING WITH
THE-- WITH THESE GUYS.
>> Jeff: ANDREA NOW HAS A
DIFFERENT IDEA.
SHE'S MOVING SOME LETTERS
AROUND.
>> LET'S TRY IT.
LET'S TRY IT.
>> Jeff: MANA THINKS THEY HAVE
SOMETHING.
A LITTLE BIT OF EXCITEMENT OVER
AT MANA.
THEY'RE STARTING TO QUICKLY MOVE
LETTERS AROUND.
NUKU HAD A HUGE LEAD AND BLEW
IT.
>> I GOT IT, TAI!
I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: COULD MANA BE RIGHT?
>> CULPEPPER THINKS SO.
>> Jeff: WHAT IS IT?
>> METAMORPHOSIS.
>> Jeff: MANA WINS IMMUNITY
WITH MET MORPH FIST.
THE ONE WORD THAT CAPTURES WHAT
"SURVIVOR" IS ABOUT.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
>> Jeff: MANA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
( APPLAUSE )
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD ON OUT.
ALL RIGHT, NUKU, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> I KNOW I'M PROBABLY IN
TROUBLE.
I'M ON MY OWN.
I HAVE TO MAKE EVERYBODY VOTE
FOR OZZY.
AND I'LL BE DOING EVERYTHING I
CAN TO GUARANTEE I'M NOT THE ONE
GOING HOME.
>> AAH!
I WASN'T EVEN CLOSE.
WAS ANYONE CLOSE?
>> NO.
>> THAT ONE IS ON ALL OF US.
WE ALL WERE STANDING THERE
STARING AT THOSE LETTERS.
NOBODY DID ANYTHING WRONG.
>> NO.
>> SO IT'S SCRAMBLE AFTERNOON,
HUNAHPU?
YEAH.
>> I GUESS MY NAME IS ON THE
BLOCK.
CAN I HAVE ONE-ON-ONE TIME WITH
EVERYBODY?
I'LL MAKE MY PITCH AND BE AT
PEACE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LIE TO ME.
I DON'T HAVE AN IDOL.
>> ANYBODY NEED WATER?
>> I'LL GO WITH YOU.
>> GOOD.
>> PERFECT.
FIVE OF US ARE HERE.
>> OKAY, MY GUT-- AND IT'S JUST
MY GUT.
I WANT EVERYBODY TO TALK.
IF WE HAD TO TAKE A VOTE NOW,
CAN WE JUST DO IT QUICK.
VARNER.
WHAT DOES YOUR GUT SAY SARAH?
>> MY GUT SAYS GET RID OF OZZY.
>> TONIGHT?
>> I TRUST VARNER MORE THAN OZZY
AT THIS POINT.
HE MAY NOT STICK WITH US FOREVER
BUT FOR A COUPLE VOTES.
I DON'T THINK OZZY WILL STICK
WITH US FOR A COUPLE OF VOTES SO
THAT'S JUST MY PERSPECTIVE BUT
I'LL VOTE WHEREVER YOU GUYS
VOTE.
>> I WOULD LIKE NOTHING MORE
THAN KEEP VARNER IN THE GAME.
I LIKE HIM AS A PERSON, I DO.
BUT TO BE HONEST, I THINK OUR
BEST BEST IS TO STICK-- I REALLY
THINK OZZY WANTS TO VOTE WITH US
FOR ONE OR TWO VOTES.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU GUYS, I'M REALLY CONVICTED.
>> I WANT TO SAFE JEFF VARNER,
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT, BUT I DON'T
WANT TO LOSE RAWZ OZY BECAUSE
THE WAY I'VE SET IT UP IS TO
HAVE BIGGER THREATS OUT THERE
THAN MYSELF.
SO WE'RE IN A PRECARIOUS
POSITION.
>> WHAT'S THE PROBABILITY IN
YOUR MIND THAT I'M GOING HOME
TONIGHT?
>> HONESTLY, IT'S ABOUT 50%.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I'M JUST LETTING YOU KNOW
BECAUSE I LIKE YOU.
>> NO, I APPRECIATE IT.
I TOLD YOU ALL TO LET ME GO.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU DON'T WANT TO GET RID
OF OZZY.
>> LOOK, VARNER, I'M GOING TO DO
WHAT I CAN TO SAVE YOU.
I'M GOING TO BE PERFECTLY
HONEST, I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
>> ZEKE HAS BEEN MY PARTNER AND
I THOUGHT I COULD PITCH, "LET'S
GET RID OF OZZY," BUT WHEN I
THREW THAT OUT THERE ZEKE SHUT
ME DOWN WHICH WAS VERY TELLING
TO ME BECAUSE ZEKE DOES NOT WANT
TO GET RID OF OZZY.
WHAT I DO NEED TO DO TO STAY
HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT ANDREA AND
CIERA ARE GOING TO MAKE YOU FEEL
SAFE.
>> A LITE BULB WENT OFF.
AS YOUY AND ZEKE MAY BE WORKING
TOGETHER.
I FEEL LIKE ZEKE IS WORKING WITH
OZZY MORE THAN HE'S WORKING WITH
YOU AND ANDREA.
>> REALLY?
>> ZEKE SAT ME DOWN AND HE SAID,
"YOU'RE PROBABLY GOING HOME."
>> YEAH.
>> AND THE GIRLS ARE GOING TO
LIE TO YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> BECAUSE THEY JUST DON'T WANT
YOU TO KNOW.
ZEKE IS WORKING BOTH SIDES, AND
I LET SARAH KNOW THAT, AND IT
PISSED HER OFF.
>> ZEKE IS WORK OZZY.
HE'S NOT ON YOUR TEAM.
IF I'M GOING THOAM TONIGHT, I'M
GOING TO CUT THEM ALL OFF AT THE
KNEES.
ZEKE IS NOT BEING TRUTHFUL.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT ZEKE
NOBODY KNOWS.
I FEEL LIKE I KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT ZEKE THAT NOBODY ELSE HAS
PICKED UP ON, IS INSIGNIFICANT
TO THIS GAME.
IT MEANS NOTHING, BUT THIS IS
NOT THE GUY YOU THINK HE IS.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE HERE.
IF I HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL
TONIGHT AND RAISE MORTAL HELL,
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M NOT GOING QUIETLY OFF THIS
ISLAND.
>> WHY WOULD ZEKE DO THAT?
>> BECAUSE HE'S A COWARD.
>> THAT PISSES ME OFF, ANDREA.
>> IT MADE ME MAD, TOO, I WAS
PISSED.
>> I'M IRATE RIGHT NOW.
ZEKE THREW US UNDER THE BUS.
I REALIZE THAT, BUT RIGHT NOW,
ZEKE IS WITH US, SO WE'LL GET
THROUGH THIS VOTE BUT IT'S NOT
COOL.
>> IS HE?
ZEKE SAT HIM DOWN AND SAID THE
GIRLS ARE GOING TO LIE TO YOU
JUST TO MAKE YOU FEEL GOOD.
AND I'M LIKE WHAT?
WHY WOULD YOU THROW US UNDER THE
BUS SO YOU COULD SAVE FACE.
THINGS ARE STARTING TO LOOK
WEIRD NOW.
ZEKE DIDN'T DOESN'T WANT TO GET
RID OF OZZY AND ZEKE THREW
ANDREA AND I UNDER THE BUS AND
I'M LIKE THIS IS KIND OF
STARTING TO STINK.
DO ZEKE AND OZZY HAVE SOMETHING
MORE GOING ON THAT I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT?
AND THAT REALLY SCARES ME.
THIS COULD BE A HUGE MISTAKE,
BUT MAYBE WE NEED TO GET RID OF
OZZY, AND KEEP VENTURA.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, SANDRA'S
VOTED OUT.
VARNER, YOU SEEMED TO THINK THAT
IT MEANT YOU WOULD BE NEXT.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THAT'S LOGICAL.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
I'M ON THE BOTTOM.
I'M NEXT.
I TRIED MY BEST TO NOT BE NEXT,
BUT IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THAT
WORKED.
>> Jeff: YOU KNOW BECAUSE YOU
KNOW YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM OR--
>> I KNOW.
I'VE HAD CONVERSATIONS WITH
EVERYBODY IN THIS GROUP TODAY.
I KNOW I'M GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE, THAT GOT A
REACTION FROM YOU.
>> YEAH, WHEN SOMEBODY IS THAT
CERTAIN, A LITTLE FEELING OF
UNEASE JUST CREEPS OVER ME LIKE
I'M JUST TRYING TO PREPARE
MYSELF TO BE ABSOLUTELY SHOCKED
TONIGHT.
>>
>> Jeff: JEFF, TELL ME WHAT
HAPPENED AT CAMP?
DID EVERYBODY JUST SAY, "VARNER,
YOU'RE GOING HOME?"
>> I WENT AND TALKED TO EACH
PERSON INDIVIDUALLY AFTER THE
CHALLENGE TODAY.
I'VE BEEN TALKING TO PEOPLE FOR
THE LAST TWO AND A HALF DAYS.
I FEEL LIKE I KNOW-- KNEW--
WHERE PEOPLE STOOD.
I FELT LIKE I WAS GETTING IN THE
CRACKS.
I FELT LIKE I WAS MOVING OFF THE
BOTTOM.
BUT IT WAS REVEALED TO ME TODAY
HOW LITTLE I KNEW ABOUT WHAT
ACTUALLY IS GOING ON HERE AT OLD
CAMP NUKU.
THEY ARE NOT SIX STRONG.
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN ARGUING ALL
DAY LONG WHO DO YOU WANT TO VOTE
OUT?
HALF THE GROUP SAYS, "IF YOU GET
ENOUGH NUMBERS TO VOTE OZZY,
I'LL VOTE OZZY, BECAUSE OZZY IS
A STRATEGIC THREAT.
HE IS THE TOTAL PACKAGE."
SO IT BEGAN TO REVEAL ITSELF TO
ME THAT THERE WAS A SECRET
ALLIANCE BETWEEN ZEKE AND OZZY.
OKAY?
THERE IS DECEPTION GOING ON
RIGHT HERE, AND YOU GUYS ARE THE
VICTIMS OF IT.
BOTTOM OF THE ALLIANCE.
BOOM, BOOM, AND BOOM.
BOTTOM.
SO I AM PROPOSING TONIGHT VOTE
FOR OZZY.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF THE WHOLE
SITUATION IF YOU WILL VOTE AND
YOU WILL VOTE AND YOU WILL VOTE.
I'LL HOOK US UP.
THAT'S THE PITCH I'M MAKING TO
YOU TODAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> THERE IS DECEPTION HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> DECEPTIONS ON LEVELS, JEFF,
THAT THESE GUYS DON'T EVEN
UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S MORE.
>> Jeff: CONTINUE.
>> WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD ANYONE
YOU'RE TRANSGENDER?
WHAT I'M SHOWING IS A DECEPTION.
>> BUT THAT'S PERSONAL.
>> THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
THE GAME.
>> THAT'S NOT A DECEPTION.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> THAT IS SO WRONG.
FOR TO YOU BRING THAT UP.
>> I'M NOT USING THAT AS
ANYTHING NEGATIVE.
>> THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
THE GAME.
THAT'S PERSONAL.
>> I'M NOT KNOCKING HIM.
>> THAT'S NOT DECEPTION--
>> THAT WAS SOMETHING TO REVEAL
WHO WHOM HE WANTED.
>> I ARGUE FOR THE RIGHTS OF
TRANSGENDER PEOPLE EVERY DAY IN
THE STATE OF NORTH CAROLINA.
I WOULD NEVER SAY OR DO ANYTHING
TO HURT ANYONE HERE.
JEFF, I'M ARGUING FOR MY LIFE.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE GOT TO THROW
EVERYTHING AT THE WALL.
>> OUTING SOMEBODY--
>> I'M NOT OUTING HIM.
>> YES, YOU ARE!
YOU OUTED HIM!
NOBODY HAS THE RIGHT TO OUT
ANYBODY.
>> I AGREE WITH TAI.
IT WAS FOR ZEKE TO DISCUSS WHEN
HE WAS COMFORTABLE DISCUSSING
IT.
>> IN TWO REASONS I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR," I TOLD NOBODY.
>> I DON'T WANT THE PERCEPTION
TO BE THAT I'M THIS EVIL,
HATEFUL PERSON.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR GOAL IN DOING
THAT?
>> TO SHOW THIS DECEPTION.
>> THAT ISN'T DECEIVING US
STRATEGICALLY IN A GAME.
I DON'T THII DON'T THINK SO.
>> IT REVEALS THE ABILITY TO
DECEIVE.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WHEN YOU SAY BY
REJEELG THAT ZEKE IS
TRANSGENDER, YOU'RE PROVING THAT
HE'S DECEPTIVE--
>> I'M NOT SAYING, JEFF, THAT
TRANSGENDER PEOPLE ARE
DECEPTIVE.
>> Jeff: NO, YOU'RE SAYING BY
HIM NOT REVEALING IT THAT HE'S
CAPABLE OF DECEPTION.
THAT IS A GIANT LEAP OF LOGIC.
DO YOU HONESTLY NOT SEE THAT?
>> I DO SEE THAT.
AND I FEEL HORRIBLE ABOUT IT.
I'M JUST TRYING EVERYTHING THAT
I CAN.
AND I AM SO SORRY, ZEKE.
I'M NOT-- I SUPPORT YOU.
>> Jeff: JERVEG YOU CAN'T
UNRING THE BELL.
>> I'M NOT UNRINGING THE BELL.
I'M JUST APOLOGIZING, JEFF.
>> JEFF, YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
>> I AM A LITTLE BIT.
>> I SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF FOR WHAT YOU'RE WILLING
TO DO TO GET YOURSELF FURTHER IN
A GAME FOR $1 MILLION.
YOU'RE PLAYING WITH PEOPLE'S
LIVES AT THIS POINT.
>> AND I AM SO SORRY, ZEKE.
>> Jeff: JEFF, WHEN YOU LOOK
AT ZEKE'S EXPRESSION, WHO
TYPICALLY IS VERY CONNECTED, AND
NOW JUST VISUALLY TO ME LOOKS A
LITTLE BIT LIKE HE'S ON AN
ISLAND OF HIS OWN, DO YOU--
>> ZEKE, I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE SORRY?
>> I'M SORRY.
THAT'S NOT THE INTENTION I HAD.
>> THERE'S A GREAT KICK TORE
THIS.
I REALLY LIKED VARNER.
I THOUGHT WE, LIKE, CONNECTED
OVER THE PAST COUPLE OF DAYS.
WE SHARED A LOT OF STORIES.
HE SHARED A LOT ABOUT HIS LIFE.
AND IT'S BEEN TEARING ME UP THAT
I HAD TO VOTE THIS GUY OUT.
AND I'M THE ONE WHO GAVE HIM THE
HEADS UP TODAY BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT TO BLINDSIDE HIM.
>> Jeff: JEFF WHAT, DO YOU
THINK THE L.G.B.T.EE COMMUNITY
REACTION WILL BE TO THIS?
>> THE COMMUNITY AROUND ME KNOWS
WHO I AM.
THEY KNOW WHAT I SUPPORT.
MY TRANSGENDER FRIENDS KNOW WHO
I AM AND WHAT I SUPPORT.
AND THEY KNOW I'M NOT THIS
HORRIBLE MONSTER.
>> Jeff: BUT IN A WAY, YOU'RE
SAYING THERE IS NO LINE, IF I'M
DESPERATE ENOUGH, I WILL DO OR
SAY ANYTHING.
>> IT'S A GAME FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS, AND I CLEARLY HAVE MADE
THE WRONG CHOICE TONIGHT.
AND MY CONSCIENCE IS IN PAIN.
I FEEL HORRIBLE.
I DIDN'T THINK THAT WOULDN'T
REACTION.
I THOUGHT HE WAS PROUD AND OUT
AND LOUD ABOUT IT.
AND I DIDN'T DNOT UNDERSTAND
WHAT EXACTLY--
>> IF YOU THOUGHT HE WAS OUT AND
PROUD AND LOUD ABOUT IT, WHY DID
YOU MAKE IT A POINT THAT
EVERYBODY WOULD HAVE TO KNOW
THAT?
>> BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T DISCUSSED
IT.
AND HE--
>> BECAUSE HE'S NOT OUT AND
PROUD AND LOUD ABOUT IT.
>> I GET THAT NOW.
YOU GUYS, I'M GOING TO BEAT
MYSELF UP ENOUGH ALREADY.
>> Jeff: JEFF, YOU CAN'T HAVE
IT BOTH WAYS.
YOU CAN'T SAY ON ONE HAND THE
REASON I'M TELLING PEOPLE IS TO
PROVE THAT HE'S CAPABLE OF
DECEPTION, AND THEN IMMEDIATELY
SAY, "HE WAS OUT AND PROUD OF
IT."
BOTH CAN'T EXIST.
>> AND I'M SO SORRY, ZEKE.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> Jeff: TAI,S AS A PLAYER IN
THIS GAME, AND AS A GAY MAN
YOURSELF, YOU ARE CLEARLY VERY
UPSET AND LET JEFF KNOW IT.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING NOW?
>> I THINK I CAN UNDERSTAND
VARNER.
HE WAS JUST DEPS EXPRAT TRYING
TO SAVE HIMSELF.
I THINK HE CROSSED A LINE AND
DIDN'T REALIZE HE DID.
I THINK HE SINCERELY FEELS BAD
ABOUT IT.
AND HE JUST HAS TO LIVE WITH IT.
BUT STILL, I HAVE THIS REALLY
STRONG STAND, WHENEVER YOU WANT
TO COME OUT AS A GAY PERSON, AS
TRANSGENDER, IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
NOBODY SHOULD OUT ANYBODY.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, YOU HAD A
VERY BIG AND INSTANT REACTION.
YOU'RE STILL EMOTIONAL ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING WITH ZEKE FOR
18 DAYS.
AND I DIDN'T KNOW.
AND JUST TO SEE SOMEONE OUT
SOMEONE ELSE IS PRETTY PAINFUL.
BUT I UNDERSTAND THAT JEFF IS
FEELING VERY ON THE OUTS AND
HE'S VERY DESPERATE, SO I DO
BELIEVE HE REGRETS IT.
IT'S JUST-- THAT WAS REALLY
TOUGH.
I FEEL-- I REALLY FEEL FOR ZEKE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S HIS RIGHT TO TELL
PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: VARNER, IS IT
STARTING TO HIT YOU THE GRAVITY
THAT YOU DIDN'T JUST TELL SIX
PEOPLE.
YOU TOLD MILLIONS OF PEOPLE.
IS THAT WHAT'S HAPPENING?
YOU'RE REALIZING NOW THIS WAS--
>> JEFF, I ASSUMED THAT EVERYONE
IN HIS WORLD KNEW.
SO THAT'S MY IGNORANCE.
AND I THOUGHT HE WAS JUST
DECEIVING THESE PEOPLE.
IT NEVER DAWNED ON ME THAT NO
ONE KNEW.
AND SO, I'M JUST DEVASTATED.
>> Jeff: ZEKE, YOU'VE BEEN
AMAZINGLY STRONG THROUGH THIS.
WAS THIS SOMETHING THAT WAS A
PART OF YOUR LIFE?
WERE YOU OUT TO YOUR FRIENDS?
OR WAS IT EVEN ANYTHING THAT WAS
IN YOUR NORMAL DAILY LIFE?
>> WELL, CERTAINLY.
YOU KNOW, BEING TRANS,
TRANSITIONING, IT'S A LONG
PROCESS.
IT'S A VERY DIFFICULT PROCESS.
AND, YOU KNOW, THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO KNOW.
BUT THEN I SORT OF GOT TO A
POINT WHERE I STOPPED TELLING
PEOPLE BECAUSE WHEN PEOPLE KNOW
THAT ABOUT YOU, THAT'S SORT OF
WHO YOU ARE.
THERE ARE QUESTIONS PEOPLE ASK.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW ABOUT YOUR
LIFE, AND THEY WANT TO KNOW THE
THIS AND THAT.
SORT OF OVERWHELMS EVERYTHING
ELSE THEY KNOW ABOUT YOU.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE NO LONGER
ZEKE.
>> RIGHT, YOU'RE THE TRANS
PERSON.
AND I THINK I'VE BEEN FORTUNATE
TO PLAY "SURVIVOR" AS LONG AS
I'VE BEEN PLAYING IT AND NOT
HAVE THAT LABEL.
AND ONE OF THE REASONS WHY I
DIDN'T WANT TO LEAD WITH THAT
AND I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THE
"TRANS" SURVIVOR PLAYER AND I
WANTED TO BE ZEKE THE SURVIVOR
PLAYER.
>> YOU ARE.
>> AND I FEEL LIKE I AM.
I KNEW SOMEONE MIGHT PICK UP ON
IT OR IT MIGHT BE REVEALED.
SO I AM PREPARED TO TALK ABOUT
IT, TO HAVE IT BE PART OF MY
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE.
IT'S KIND OF CRAPPY THE WAY IT'S
HAPPENED.
>> I'M SORRY, ZEKE.
I'M SORRY.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, METAMORPHOSIS
IS THE WORD OF THE SHOW.
I THINK I'VE SEEN SUCH A MET
MORPH FIST OF MYSELF, TODAY IS
52 OF THE DAY OF PLAYED
"SURVIVOR."
AND I DON'T KNOW THE SCARED KID
WHO HIT THE MAP AT 33 WOULD BE
AS CALM AS I AM RIGHT NOW.
BUT I'VE STARTED TWO FIRES WITH
JUST BAMBOO.
I'VE WON CHALLENGES.
I'VE BEEN PART OF BLINDSIDES.
I'VE DONE ALL KINDS OF CRAZY
STUFF AND I AM A CHANGED,
STRONGER, BETTER MAN TODAY THAN
I WAS THEN.
SO, YOU KNOW, WHAT?
VARNER, IT'S REALLY NOT COOL.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M FINE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A BIGGER
CHEERLEADER IN ANYONE BUT ME.
>> I DON'T EVEN NEED A
CHEERLEADER.
>> I KNOW.
>> BECAUSE I KNOW I CAN DO
WHATEVER I WANT TO.
>> I KNOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
NOW THAT I CAN SIT HERE AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENED, I'M SHOCKED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT I DID THAT.
AND I FEEL HORRIBLE.
>> Jeff: SARAH, YOU'RE STILL
SHAKE YOUR HEAD AT VARNER.
>> I'M-- THAT'S NOT ME.
AND... LIKE-- I'M SORRY THAT I'M
CRYING THIS BUT --
>> WHEN YOU SAY, "THAT'S NOT
ME," WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THAT WAS A MALICIOUS ATTACK,
WHAT HE DID.
IT WAS I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU
SAID.
>> THERE WAS NOT MALICE IN THAT.
>> IT WAS.
THAT'S YOUR OPINION.
MINE IS THAT IT WAS.
>> I KNOW BUT MALICE SAY PRETTY
HEFTY CLAIM.
AND THERE'S NO MALICE THERE.
>> OKAY.
I DON'T TREAT PEOPLE THAT WAY.
AND--
>> I DON'T TREAT PEOPLE THAT
WAY.
>> I CAN TALK?
>> YES, I'M JUST-- I DON'T WANT
YOU TO PAINT ME AS SOMETHING I'M
NOT.
>> JUDGE DON'T YOU GO AHEAD.
>> Jeff: THAT IS AN IRONIC
STATEMENT.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
>> UM... YOU KNOW, I'M JUST
THANKFUL THAT I GOT TO KNOW ZEKE
FOR WHO ZEKE IS.
I'VE BEEN WITH HIM FOR LAST 18
DAYS.
AND HE'S, LIKE, SUPER KICK-ASS.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M FROM THE
MIDWEST.
I COME FROM A VERY CONSERVATIVE
BACKGROUND.
SO IT'S NOT VERY DIVERSE WHEN IT
COMES TO A LOT OF GAY AND
LESBIAN AND TRANSGENDER AND
THINGS LIKE THAT.
SO I'M NOT EXPOSED TO IT AS MUCH
AS MOST OF THESE PEOPLE ARE.
AND THE FACT THAT I CAN LOVE
THIS GUY SO MUCH AND IT DOESN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING FOR ME MAKES ME
REALIZE THAT I'VE GROWN HUGE AS
A PERSON.
, OF COURSE, WE WANT TO COME
AWAY WITH WITH THE MILLION
DOLLARS, BUT THE METAMORPHOSIS
THAT I'VE EVEN MADE AS A PERSON
THEY DIDN'T REALIZE UNTIL THIS
MINUTE IS INVALUABLE.
AND I'M SORRY IT CAME OUT THAT
WAY, BUT I'M GLAD IT DID.
AND, LIKE, I'M SO GLAD THAT I
GOT TO KNOW YOU FOR ZEKE AND
NOT, YOU KNOW, WHAT YOU WERE
AFRAID OF US KNOWING YOU AS.
AND I'LL NEVER LOOK AT YOU THAT
WAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, I'M CERTAINLY
NOT ANYONE WHO SHOULD BE A ROLE
MODEL FOR ANYBODY ELSE, BUT
MAYBE THERE'S SOMEONE WHO IS A
"SURVIVOR" FAN AND ME BEING OUT
ON THE SHOW HELPS HIM OR HELPS
HER OR HELPS SOMEONE ELSE.
AND SO MAYBE THIS WILL LEAD TO A
GREATER GOOD.
>> Jeff: WELL, I THINK I KNOW
THE ANSWER TO THIS QUESTION, BUT
THERE'S NO QUESTION WHO'S GOING
HOME TONIGHT, RIGHT?
>> NO, SURE.
>> Jeff: ZEKE?
>> NO.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE?
>> TAI, OZZY, ANDREA?
>> NO.
>> IT'S VARNER.
>> IT IS.
>> I'M READY TO GO.
>> Jeff: WE DON'T NEED TO
VOTE.
JUST GRAB YOUR TORCH.
>> Jeff: VARNER, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT WAS A
COMPLICATED BUT ULTIMATELY
BEAUTIFUL NIGHT THAT WILL NEVER
BE FORGOTTEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
WHEN 13 GAME CHANGERS COME
TOGETHER.
... WE ARE OFFICIALLY MERGE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> GAME IS ON.
>> Jeff: IT'S A SCRAMBLE FOR
POWER.
>> IT'S JUST LIKE PEOPLE ARE
EVERYWHERE.
>> I'M READY TO GO IN GUNS
BLATION.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
IT WAS A HORRIBLE MOVE.
IT WAS ME WRAPPED UP IN THIS
GAME TRYING TO DO EVERYTHING I
POSSIBLY COULD.
BUT NOBODY ON THIS PLANET SHOULD
DO WHAT I DID TONIGHT, EVER.
AND I'M SO SORRY TO ANYONE I
OFFENDED, ESPECIALLY ZEKE AND
HIS FAMILY AND HIS FRIENDS.
I CAN'T EVEN TALK.
I'M SORRY.