THIS TIME I'M PLAYING LIKE A
CRIMINAL.
IF YOU SAY ANYTHING ABOUT US
TALKING, YOU'RE A DEAD MAN.
THERE ARE SMALL WINDOWS OF
OPPORTUNITY IN THIS GAME, AND IF
YOU MISS THEM, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO WIN.
I SWORE TO MYSELF I'M GONNA MAKE
BIG MOVES.
DON'T YOU THINK TO BE IN WITH
THE ENEMY COULD BE A GOOD THING?
I MADE MOVES THAT OTHER PEOPLE
WERE SCARED TO MAKE.
I WILL GIVE YOU MY ADVANTAGE.
I MADE MOVES THAT I WAS SCARED
TO MAKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF?
I'M GOING TO USE MY ADVANTAGE.
AND IT WORKED.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO THE
"SURVIVOR" LIVE REUNION "GAME
CHANGER" SEASON WHERE SARAH HAS
JUST WON $1 MILLION.
CONGRATULATIONS ON A REALLY
NICELY PLAYED GAME.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, BEFORE WE GET INTO YOU,
GLENN, GIVE ME A BIG SHOT OF
EVERYBODY.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THANK YOU TO
ALL YOU GUYS BECAUSE THIS REALLY
WAS A GREAT SEASON, AND TO GIVE
UP WHAT YOU GIVE UP AND TO DO
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO WITH YOUR
FAMILIES AND YOUR JOBS AND YOUR
LIVELIHOODS AND TO COME OUT HERE
AND PLAY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT WAS REALLY FUN.
( APPLAUSE )
ALL RIGHT, SO, SARAH, I THINK
ONE OF THE BIGGEST, REALLY
BIGGEST GAME-CHANGING MOVES OF
THE ACCEPT FOR YOU WAS YOUR VERY
SIMPLE-- YOUR SWITCH OF
PHILOSOPHY FROM COP TO CRIMINAL.
AND WHAT I THOUGHT WAS REALLY
INTERESTING IS YOU ENDED UP
PLAYING A LOT LIKE YOUR FORMER
ADVERSARY, TONY.
DID YOU FIND SOME TRUTH IN THAT?
>> RIGHT, SO, IN CAGYAN, WE SAW
HOW THAT WORKED OUT FOR ME AND
HOW IT WORKED OUT FOR TONY.
I HAD A FRONT-ROW SEAT TO WATCH
TONY PLAY SO MASTERFULLY.
AND HE WAS SO SUCCESSFUL AT IT
--
>> WAS HE REALLY A MENTOR IN
THAT SENSE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND WHAT PEOPLE DON'T GET ABOUT
TONY IS THE GUY CALLED ME AT
5:30 IN THE MORNING EVERY
MORNING PREPPING ME FOR THE
SHOW, BUT HE WAS, LIKE, TRYING
TO PREP HIMSELF.
AND HE'S LIKE, "GET UP, YOU
BUM."
I'M LIKE,"IT'S 5:30, DUDE."
HE'S LIKE, "YO, SARA, WE'VE GOT
TO TALK."
>> Jeff: SO HE WAS TRYING TO
HELP YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: I HAVE ANOTHER
QUESTION.
>> SURE.
>> Jeff: YOU SAID SOMETHING
THAT CONTINUES TO BAFFLE ME THAT
SURVIVOR IS A GAME BY DEFINITION
OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
AS TAI SAID, IT'S ABOUT
DECEIVING.
HOW DO YOU DO THE SLEIGHT OF
HAND WITH EMOTIONAL AND SOCIAL
POLITICS.
AND YOU SAID I HAD TO GET
PERMISSION FROM MY FRIENDS.
WHY IS THAT SO IMPORTANT FOR
PEOPLE TO KNOW THEIR FRIENDS
WILL KNOW UNEMPLOYMENT I'M NOT
THIS PERSON.
>> SO NOBODY WANTS TO GO OUT AND
MAKE THEIR FAMILY, THEIR
FRIENDS, THER PROFESSION LOOK
BAD, SO THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED,
THAT WEIGHED HEAVILY ON ME.
IN ORDER TO COME OUT AND BE
SUCCESSFUL, I HAD TO LET THAT
GO.
I WAS GIVEN THE RIGHT OF WAY BY
EVERYBODY, AND I JUST CAME OUT
GUNS A-BLATION BECAUSE THE GATES
WERE OPEN FOR ME TO DO WHATEVER
I HAD TO DO.
>> Jeff: KNOWING THEY WOULD
LOVE YOU.
>> KNOWING THEY KNOW WHO I AM.
AND IN FACT, THEY KIND OF BEAT
ME DOWN FOR NOT BEING MORE LIKE
THAT THE FIRST TIME.
SO YEAH.
IT WAS REALLY NICE TO HAVE THEIR
BLESSING TO COME OUT AND PLAY
THIS WAY.
EVEN THOUGH I HURT A LOT OF
PEOPLE OOP.
IT'S NOT EASY TO WATCH BACK.
I'M VERY PROUD OF THE GAME I
PLAYED.
I'M NOT PROUD OF HOW I TREATED
PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU CAN'T HAVE
IT BOTH WAYS.
THAT'S A WHOLE OTHER DISCUSSION.
>> RIGHT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS "SURVIVOR" SHOWS IS YOU
HAVE TO OWN IT BECAUSE THE JURY
WILL HOLD YOU ACCOUNTABLE.
CULPEPPER, IT COMES DOWN TO ONE
BIG DECISION.
I WAS WATCHING WITH FRIENDS
BACKSTAGE AND THEY WERE RIVETTED
WITH THE DECISION BEING MADE
AMONG THE FOUR OF YOU, WHO IS
GOING TO GO TO THE JURY-- IN
THIS CASE TAI-- AND WHO IS GOING
TO GO TO THE FINAL THREE.
YOU SAID AS YOU'RE VOTING TAI
OUT, AND YOU SAID IN THE SHOW,
"I FEEL LIKE I CAN BEAT
ANYBODY."
SO I JUST WANT TO WALK THROUGH
THAT.
HERE ARE THE VOTES.
GLENN, SHOW THE VOTES OF THE
TRIBAL.
WE DON'T NORMALLY DO THIS.
LET'S SEE WHO EVERYBODY VOTED
FOR.
BECAUSE WHAT I'M WONDERING IS,
DID YOU MISCALCULATE?
>> CLEARLY
( LAUGHTER ).
>> Jeff: BUT, NO, SPECIFICALLY
DYOU MISCALCULATE THE BITTERNESS
THAT YOU THOUGHT THE JURY MIGHT
HAVE TOWARD WHAT SARAH JUST
SAID, WHICH IS HURTING THEIR
FEELINGS.
>> I DID.
BUT FIRST, CLEARLY LET ME SAY
THIS.
I CLEARLY NEEDED A SNICKERS OUT
HERE, I LOVE THIS GUY RIGHT
HERE, AND I HATED WATCHING THAT,
BEING THE BULLY.
TAI, I LOVE YOU.
AND WE HAD A COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
( APPLAUSE )
TAI, WE WERE TOGETHER.
I WAS FRUSTRATED.
AND IT CAME ACROSS TERRIBLE.
AND I APOLOGIZE.
THAT IS AWFUL.
>> OH, NO YOU DON'T NEED TO
APOLOGIZE.
IT'S A GAME.
YOU'VE BEEN A GREAT GUY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS PERFECT.
LET'S FORGET WHAT I JUST ASKED.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE, STAY WITH
WITH ME.
STAY WITH ME.
THAT EMOTION THAT YOU JUST
TALKED ABOUT "I WAS SO
FRUSTRATED WITH TAI.
OF.
>> YEAH, I WAS.
>> Jeff: HAD AN IMPACT IN YOU
VOTING TAI OUT, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: SO NOW YOU
MISCALCULATED WITH SARA,
CLEARLY.
SHE WON, RIGHT?
>> YES, YES.
>> Jeff: LET'S SEE WHAT WOULD
HAVE HAPPENED.
LET'S PLAY A PRETEND GAME.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT GAME.
>> Jeff: BUT I LOVE IT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WHEN YOU'RE
OUT THERE --
>> I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME.
CULPEPPER, COME OIT'S FUN.
YOU LIKE GAMES.
BUT WHAT?
>> THE FEELING YOU HAVE OUT
THERE, EVEN THE PERCEPTION OF
THE JURY OUT THERE, IS MUCH
DIFFERENT THAN IT WOULD BE NOW.
>> Jeff: I UNDERSTAND THAT.
I TRUST THE JURY TO BE HONEST
WITH ME.
JUST GO WITH ME.
THIS IS WHAT IT'S LIKE AT TRIBAL
WITH ANY CULPEPPER.
MONICA OR BRAD.
( LAUGHTER )
OKAY, SO, SARAH, YOU'RE ON THE
JURY.
TAI, YOU'RE IN THE FINAL THREE.
OF THE PEOPLE--
>> NO, I'M FOUR.
>> YOU'RE FINAL.
>> Jeff: COME ON, GUYS.
>> IF I HAD CUT YOU LIKE, THAT
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE VOTE FORWARD
ME.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, WILL YOU
JUST STOP FOR A SECOND!
( LAUGHTER )
SO EVERYBODY THAT'S IN THE JURY,
INCLUDING SARA, BUT NOT YOU,
TAI, BECAUSE YOU'RE NOW IN THE
FINAL THREE.
WHO WOULD HAVE VOTE FORWARD
BRAD?
HOW MANY PEOPLE.
OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT IN THE JURY, TROYZAN!
HOLD YOUR HANDS UP!
HALI, DEBBIE, ZEKE, SIERRA,
ANDREA.
SO THAT'S FIVE VOTES.
THE OTHER FIVE WOULD YOU HAVE
VOTED FOR SARAH-- I MEAN TAI?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO.
>> Jeff: OKAY, SO FIVE-- OKAY,
SO THIS IS SOMETHING WE'VE NEVER
TALKED ABOUT, AND IT'S A PERFECT
TIME.
EVERYBODY ASKS, WHAT, WOULD DO
YOU IN THE CASE OF A TIE AT
FINAL TRIBAL?
WE WOULD HAVE HAD ONE HAD YOU
SAID "YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M GOING
TO KEEP TAI AND GET RID OF
SARAH."
WE WOULD HAVE HAD HAD A TIE,
5-5.
THIS IS THE RULE.
HS WHAT WOULD HAVE HAPPENED IN A
FUTURE SEASON.
THE PERSON WHO WAS NOT IN THE
TIE.
WE HAVE BRAD WITH FIVE, TAI WITH
FIVE.
TROYZAN, YOU GO TO THE JURY AND
DECIDE THE FINAL VOTE.
>> WOW!
>> Jeff: SO, TROYZAN, IN THIS
CASE--
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TROYZAN, IN THIS CASE, HONESTLY,
BACK THEN, NOT WATCHING THE
SHOW, WHEN YOU WERE IN THAT
MOMENT, WHO WOULD YOU HAVE VOTED
FOR?
>> TAI, SAY IT.
>> IF IT WAS TAI OR BRAD?
BRAD.
>> Jeff: SO, CULPEPPER, I
BRING THIS UP BECAUSE-- AND YOU
GUYS ARE-- ARE MAKING IT
DIFFICULT TO MAKE THIS POINT.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT I BELIEVE THE JURY'S TELLING
THE TRUTH.
AND THE REASON I'M BRINGING IT
UP IS IT SHOWS HOW HARD THIS
GAME IS.
YOU ACTUALLY DID PLAY A GAME
GOOD ENOUGH TO WIN.
AND ONE DECISION WILL HAUNT YOU.
YOU MADE ONE WRONG DECISION.
>> OH, NO.
>> Jeff: IT WILL HAUNT YOU
BECAUSE I WILL BE STAYING TO YOU
ALL THE TIME.
ANYWAY, THAT'S HOW TOUGH THIS
GAME IS.
( APPLAUSE )
LET IT GO.
I'M MOVING ON.
AND IT'S NOT LOST ON ME, SARAH,
THAT THE-- THE-- NO, THAT THE
NUANCED WAY IN WHICH YOU
MANEUVERED THAT KNOWING WHAT
NEEDED TO HAPPEN SHOWS YOUR
SOCIAL PLAY AT WORK.
BRILLIANT.
TAI, WHY IS THIS GAME SO HARD
FOR YOU EMOTIONALLY?
WHAT IS IT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
I THINK IT'S JUST IN MY NATURE.
IT'S SO HARD STORY ME TO-- IT'S
EASY TO BE NICE AND KIND AND
TAKE CARE OF PEOPLE.
BRAD DOES A LOT AT CAMP.
HE CARES FOR THE CAMP AND
EVERYTHING ELSE.
IT'S JUST, I DON'T KNOW, I GO
INTO THIS GAME.
I SAY IT'S EYE GAME.
SOMEHOW OUT-- I ALWAYS GET WHAT
I WANT OUTSIDE OF THE GAME, I
SLOWLY CAN MANIPULATE PEOPLE TO
GET WHAT I WANT.
SOMEHOW, IN SOME GAME, IT JUST
SEEMS BIGGER-- I JUST --
>> BUT WHY IS IT EMOTIONAL?
TO SARAH'S QUESTION, WHY DO YOU
NEED TO ALWAYS BE KIND AND NICE?
IF YOUR FRIENDS GAVE YOU
PERMISSION TO LIE, WOULD YOU BE
ABLE TO?
>> I GIVE MYSELF PERMISSION TO
LIE.
ON THE SHOW ITSELF, IT'S NOTABLY
TO DO IT.
I GO TO MY HEART INSTANTLY.
THERE ARE SO MANY CHANCES I FEEL
I SHOULD BE PLAYING THE IDOL AND
I DON'T.
I KNOW I FEEL COMFORTABLE IN THE
GAME.
I KNOW HOW THE GAME IS GOING.
AND SMOWRK I DON'T KNOW.
IT IS JUST REALLY HARD-- IT'S
JUST NOT IN MY NATURE.
AND I HOPE I GROW FROM IT.
IF YOU EVER WANT ME BACK --
>> I LOVE HEARING THAT.
CIRIE, I HAVE TO GO DOWN TO YOU.
WE SAW THE RECEPTION YOU
RECEIVED EARLIER.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
CIRIE, SO, I THINK THIS IS A
QUESTION I SINCERELY AM
INTERESTED IN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
LIKE, I WOULD ALWAYS SAY ABOUT
YOU,"WELL, SHE'S THE WOMAN WHO
GOT UP OFF THE COACH," WHICH
MEANT TO ME, YOU'RE THE WOMAN
WHO THOUGHT, "COULD I DO THAT?"
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS ABOUT
YOU?
WHAT DO YOU REPRESENT?
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, I THINK THAT
BECAUSE I HAVE, LIKE-- OR I HAVE
HAD SO MANY INSECURITIES ABOUT
MYSELF-- I'M MY HARDEST CRITIC.
AND I DON'T COME IN TO ANY
SITUATION JUDGING ANYONE BECAUSE
WHO AM I TO JUDGE ANYONE?
AND I THINK BECAUSE I AM NOT UP
HERE LIKE A BIG ATHLETE AND I'M
NOT, LIKE, A CRAZY CHALLENGE
BEAST, I'M MORE LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE AT HOME.
SO I'M EASY TO RELATE TO.
I'M NOT THREATENING TO ANYONE.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO, JEFF?
>> Jeff: SO YOU'RE ARGUINGURE
YOU'RE THE EVERY PERSON IN THAT
SENSE?
LET'S BOIL IT DOWN TO ITS
ESSENCE.
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN
WATCHING LIKE YOU FOR YEARS AND
YEARS DEBATING, I SHOULD DO IT.
>> THEY SHOULD ABSOLUTELY DO IT,
JEFF.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
YOU ASKED ME THAT 12IERS YEARS
AGO.
I SAID STAY ON THE COUCH.
GET OFF THE COUCH AND GO OUT AND
DO IT.
>> Jeff: WHAT DOES IT MAKE
TAKE?
WHAT IS THE IBGREEDIENT FOR A
GOOD PLAYER?
JUST PHILOSOPHICALLY.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE TO
CONNECT WITH PEOPLE ON A GENERAL
PERSON-TO-PERSON LEVEL.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN AND HEAR WHAT
THESE PEOPLE HAVE TO SAY.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN ABOUT THEIR
FAMILIES.
FEARS.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN SOMETHING
ABOUT THESE PEOPLE TO RELATE TO
THEM.
IF YOU CAN'T ISRAEL TO THEM,
IT'S LIKE TALKING TO A BRICK
WALL.
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO GET THEIR
VOTE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE
HAVE A LOT TO TALK ABOUT
TONIGHT, INCLUDING ONE OF THE
BIGGEST MOMENTS IN ANY SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
IT MADE NEWS AROUND THE WORLD.
PEOPLE ARE STILL TALKING ABOUT
IT.
I THINK IT'S FAIR TO SAY IT WAS
A CULTURAL MILESTONE WHEN ZEKE
WAS OUTED AS BEING TRANSGENDER.
>> WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD ANYONE
YOU'RE TRANSGENDER?
>> Jeff: ZEKE, AND JEFF VARNER
ARE NEXT.
( APPLAUSE )
I DIDN'T WANNA BE LIKE
THE TRANS "SURVIVOR" PLAYER.
I WANTED TO BE ZEKE THE
"SURVIVOR" PLAYER.
>> AND YOU ARE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I AM.
>> YOU ARE.
.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: WELL, IT WAS ONE OF
THE BIGGEST GAME-CHANGING MOVES
OF ALL TIME ON ANY SHOW ANYWHERE
AND IT BECAME A WORLDWIDE
CULTURAL MOMENT.
IT STARTED SO MANY
CONVERSATIONS.
IT BROUGHT AWARENESS TO WHAT IT
IS TO BE TRANSGENDER.
I'M STILL HEARING FROM FAMILIES
WHO SAID IT GAVE THEM AN
OPPORTUNITY TO TALK TO THEIR
KIDS ABOUT IT.
AND EVERY SINGLE PERSON AGREES
ON ONE THING AND THAT IS HOW
AMAZING ZEKE WAS IN THE MOMENT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
ZEKE, I KNOW-- I KNOW THIS
ISN'T-- EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE BEING
CELEBRATED, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU CELEBRATE.
BUT TAKE US BACK TO THAT MOMENT
JUST IN TERMS OF WHAT WAS
HAPPENING FOR YOU EMOTIONALLY AS
IT WAS UNFOLDING.
>> RIGHT, WELL I WAS REALLY
SCARED.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN TO MY WORLD.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THE REACTION
WAS GOING TO BE.
AND YOU'RE GROWING UP IN
OKLAHOMA, I DIDN'T ALWAYS HAVE A
LOT OF FRIENDS.
AND EVEN THROUGHOUT MY LIVES,
PEOPLE HAVEN'T ALWAYS STUCK BY
MY SIDE THROUGH THE HARD TIMES.
BUT WHAT THIS EXPERIENCE HAS
SHOWN ME IS I HAVE SO MUCH LOVE
IN MY LIFE.
( APPLAUSE )
MY FRIENDS ARE HERE TONIGHT, AND
THEY WERE WITH ME THAT NIGHT.
AND MY FRIENDS ARE A BIG PART OF
MY FAMILY, AND I DID NOT GET
THROUGH THIS WITHOUT THEM.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WATCHED WITH
THEM AT HOME.
>> YEAH, I DID.
AND I NEVER FELT AS LOVED AS I
DO RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE
MOST CHALLENGING MOMENTS FOR ME
WAS TELLING PEOPLE THAT THE
METAMORPHOSIS MOMENT WASN'T
SCRIPTED.
THIS IS AN UNSCRIPTED SHOW.
BECAUSE IT WAS SUCH AN AMAZING
MOMENT FOR YOU TO GRAB THAT WORD
AND PULL IT INTO THE
CONVERSATION.
SO WHAT, IN TERMS OF
METAMORPHOSIS, WHAT HAS THIS
EXPERIENCE-- WHERE ARE YOU NOW
WITH IT?
>> YEAH, WELL, I.
>> -- SO.
WHEN I TRANSITIONED, I WAS HIT
WITH A PRETTY BIG BOWPT OF
DEPRESSION, LIKE A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE.
AND I-- I ALMOST FAILED OUT OF
HARVARD.
I WAS LIVING AT HOME.
I WAS ALONE.
I WAS PRETTY HOPELESS.
ASK & I STARTED WATCHING
"SURVIVOR."
AND I BINGED 20 SEASONS.
IT & IT TOOK ME AWAY.
I GOT TO GO ON ADVENTURES WITH
OZZY AND CIRIE AND SANDRA.
AND IT GOT ME THROUGH.
AND SLOWLY I PUT MY LIFE BACK
TOGETHER.
BUT THERE WAS SOMETHING MISSING,
A COURAGE AND BOLDNESS.
AND SOMETHING INSIDE OF ME KNEW
I HAD TO GO PLAY "SURVIVOR."
AND I FOUND THAT BOLDNESS IN
FIJI, I FOUND IT ON THE BEACHES.
AND IN SO MANY WAYS "SURVIVOR"
HAS GIVEN ME MY LIFE BACK.
>> Jeff: SARA, AT LEAST FOR
ME, WHEN I WAS WATCHING IT, THE
OTHER NECESSARY HALF OF THE
EQUATION FOR CHANGE TO HAPPEN IS
WHAT YOU SAID WHICH IS, "HERE I
AM, SOMEBODY TRISTATE MIDWEST,
NOT EXPOSED TO THIS, ANDS I SEE
YOU AS ZEKE, AND I LOVE YOU AS
ZEKE."
WHAT WAS THE REACTION TO YOUR
FRIENDS WHEN THEY SAW HOW YOU
HAD HANDLED IT?
>> SO I WAS A LITTLE NERVOUS HOW
MY STATE WOULD REACT TO IT.
AND EVERYBODY'S BEEN SO
POSITIVE.
AND, YOU KNOW, I TALKED TO MY
DAD ABOUT IT, BEFORE THE SHOW
HAPPENED.
AND HE WAS LIKE, YOU KNOW, I'M
SO PROUD OF THE WAY THAT YOU
HANDLED IT."
AND THEN MY GRSMS THE ONE THAT I
WAS REALLY CONCERNED ABOUT.
AND WHEN WE GOT OUT HERE, WELL,
FIRST OF ALL,.
>> WHEN VOTED ZEKE OUT, SHE
SCOLDED ME FOR IT.
SHE SAYS, "HE GAVE YOU HIS
JACKET!"
AND I'M LIKE, "I KNOW, BUT" --
>> SO THEY WERE ACCEPTING.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
AND WHEN SHE GOT OUT HERE, HE
WAS THE ONE PERSON SHE WANTED TO
MEET AND SHE GOT TO MEET HIM
YESTERDAY.
>> Jeff: OH, GOOD.
OH, NICE.
WELL, ZEKE, SINCE THEN.
MAN YOUR WORLD-- YOU HAVE BEEN
WRITING-- ONE THING YOU HAVE
BEEN WRITING A LOT FOR THE
"HOLLYWOOD REPORTER."
>> YES, I LOVE TO WRITE.
THERE'S A GREAT TEAM AT THE
"HOLLYWOOD REPORTER."
IT'S BEEN INCREDIBLE AND I'M SO
GRATEFUL FOR THE PLATFORM
THEY'VE GIVEN ME.
>> Jeff: AND YOU'RE WORKING
WITH ANOTHER PLATFORM, GLAD.
>> YES, I PARTNERED WITH GLAD,
PARTICULARLY NICK ADAMS OF THE
DIRECTOR OF THE TRANSGENDER
MEDIA PROGRAM.
AT THE CORE OF GLAD'S PHILOSOPHY
IS AUTHENTIC L.G.B.T.Q.
REPRESENTATION ACCELERATES
ACCEPTANCE AND SAVES LIVES AND
THAT'S WHY I'M SO PROUD TO BE
PART OF "SURVIVOR" AND CBS
BECAUSE YOU HAVE ALWAYS
EMPOWERED ME TO SPEAK
AUTHENTICALLY AND TO TELL MY
STORY ON MY OWN TERMS.
AND I FEEL LIKURE PARTNERSHIP IS
THE MODEL FOR HOW TRANS STORIES
SHOULD BE APPROACHED IN WANT
MEDIA GOING FORWARD.
>> Jeff: VERY COOL.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, I LOVED THAT-- BECAUSE
I FEEL A LITTLE BIT FOR YOU THAT
THERE'S THIS PRESSURE OF
EXPECTATION WHICH I KNOW YOU'RE
TAKING CARE OF AND YOU'RE DOING
YOUR PART.
BUT I AM GLAD TO HEAR THAT
YOU'RE ALSO USING THIS-- BECAUSE
YOU'RE A GREAT STORYTELLER.
YOU'RE COMPELLING-- THAT'S WHY
WE PUT YOU ON THE SHOW.
SO I'M GLAD YOU ARE GIVING
YOURSELF PERMISSION TO PURSUE
YOUR OWN PERSONAL DREAMS AND NOT
FEEL LIMITED TO HAVING TO TALK
ABOUT THIS ALL THE TIME.
SO IF THIS IS A PERFECT WORLD,
BEFORE WE GET TO JEFF, IN A
PERFECT WORLD, WHAT COMES FROM
THIS?
>> WELL, I THINK FOR ME, I FELT
THAT I WAS SOMEHOW LIMITED
BECAUSE I WAS TRANS.
THAT THERE WERE THINGS THEY
COULDN'T DO.
AND I DON'T BE THAT ANYMORE.
SO THAT SHATTERED THAT FOR ME.
THERE WERE DREAMS THEY BURIED
THAT I THINK ARE ALIVE AGAIN.
AND I ALSO DON'T WANT ANY YOUNG
TRANS PERSON TO BELIEVE THEY ARE
IN ANY WAY LIMITED.
AND IN THE MEANTIME, THE JOURNEY
MIGHT BE HARDER, BUT THE
ADVENTURE IS SO WORTH TAKING.
>> Jeff: AWESOME, GREAT, I
LOVE THAT.
SO THE OTHER PERSON IN THIS
CULTURAL MOMENT WAS JEFF VARNER,
WHO TOOK A LOT OF HEAT,
DESERVEDLY SO.
BUT SINCE THE EPISODE, JEFF, YOU
HAVE BEEN REALLY PUBLIC IN
OWNING YOUR MISTAKE.
YOU MADE A POST ON YOUR FACEBOOK
PAGE, I THINK WHERE YOU TALKED
ABOUT IT.
WE ALL KNOW WHAT THE REACTION
WAS THAT NIGHT.
I'M CURIOUS, WHAT HAS THE
REACTION MEANT TO YOU SINCE
PEOPLE HAVE SEEN YOU SAYING, "I
AM SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE IT."
HOW ARE THEY RECEIVING YOU?
>> WELL, THIS HAS BEEN A VERY
DIFFICULT SITUATION FOR BOTH OF
US, AND I DON'T EVER WANT TO
TALK ABOUT MY JOURNEY WITHOUT
ACKNOWLEDGING THE IN FACT THAT
THE REAL JOURNEY IN THIS
SITUATION HAS BEEN FOR ZEKE.
THIS HAS BEEN VERY DIFFICULT.
I GOT HIT HARD.
WE KNEE WE WOULD.
YOU TOLD ME I WOULD, "PREPARE
YOURSELF" AND IT WAS REALLY UGLY
FOR A PERIOD OF TIME.
AND THEN IT CHANGED.
AND I WAS TOLD THE WAY THEY
REACTED AND THE WAY I HANDLED
IT-- I'VE ALWAYS BEEN TAUGHT TO
STAND UP AND ADMIT YOUR MISTAKES
AND OWN THEM AND TURN THEM INTO
SOMETHING POSITIVE, AND I DID
THAT EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY DAY.
AND--
( APPLAUSE )
I'VE HEARD THAT FROM EVERYBODY.
AND I'M --
>> SO WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THAT?
>> AS MUCH AS HE IS HAPPY ABOUT
THE LOVE IN HIS LIFE, I AM
THRILLED WITH THE SUPPORT IN
MINE, AND IT WILL ULTIMATELY BE
A GOOD THING.
I GOT FIRED, COWARDLY.
BUT KELLER WILLIAMS, THE NUMBER
ONE REAL ESTATE AGENCY IN THE
COUNTRY HIRED ME AND I'M SO
PROUD OF THEM.
BUSINESS HAS BEEN GREAT.
>> I LOVE THAT, JEFF, WELL
HANDLED.
>> Jeff: WELL, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
IT WAS-- IT WAS VERY HARD
TRANSITION TO MAKE THIS ONE
BECAUSE THAT WAS POWERFUL AND
AMAZING.
THIS WAS TINY BUT INTERESTING.
IT WAS A LITTLE MOMENT.
YOU MIGHT HAVE SEEN IT IN LAST
WEEK'S EPISODE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THIS IS A "SURVIVOR" CLASSIC,
LAST WON BY COCHRAN.
SET A RECORD.
17 MINUTES.
>> MY BOYFRIEND.
>> Jeff: GOT A LITTLE CRUSH.
THIS COULD BE THE BEGINNING OF A
LITTLE "SURVIVOR" LOVE AFFAIR.
BREAK THIS RECORD, YOU MIGHT WIN
HIS HEART.
COULD WE HAVE A NEW "SURVIVOR"
COUPLE?
PLUS, SHE RUBBED A LOT OF PEOPLE
THE WRONG WAY, MICHAELA DID.
SHOULD SHE IMMATURE OR JUST
MISUNDERSTOOD.
SHE'S ONE OF MY FAVORITES,
MICHAELA.
NEXT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'LL CIRCLE BACK.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: WELCOME BACK TO THE
"SURVIVOR" LIVE REUNION SHOW FOR
"GAME CHANGERS."
AUBRY, THIS ISN'T A BIG THING
BUT YOU BROUGHT IT UP.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
YOU WERE TWEETING ABOUT COCHRAN.
AND I KNOW YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
BUT IS THIS-- WHAT IS THIS, A TV
CRUSH?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> I WAS CRESTFALLEN WHEN DEBBIE
GOES AND STEALS MY MINE, BUT
EVERYONE HAS A CRUSH ON COCHRAN.
LIKE, WHO DOESN'T?
YOU DO.
>> Jeff: I HAVE A COCHRAN
CRUSH.
THAT'S TRUE.
FAIR ENOUGH.
WHERE'S SANDRA.
SANDRA.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THIS GAME, IT SEEMS SO EASY FOR
YOU.
IT'S REALLY JUST A SIMPLE
QUESTION-- IS IT AS EASY AS IT
APPEARS?
>> IT'S A JOB TO ME.
I HAVE 39 DAYS TO GO GET MY
MILLION DOLLARS, AND I'LL DO
WHATEVER TO WHOEVER TO GET TO
THE END.
THAT'S MY JOB.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: MICHAELA, WHAT
ADVICE-- I WATCHED YOU PLAY
TWICE.
I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW HOW CARING AND EMPOWERING
ARE YOU ABOUT-- ALL THESE THINGS
THAT OTHER PEOPLE ARE GOING,
"MICHAELA?
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT MICHAELA?"
WATCHING YOURSELF NOW BACK TO
BACK, WHAT ADVICE DO YOU GIVE TO
MICHAELA?
>> MY ADVICE TO ME IS RECOGNIZE
THAT THE OUTPLAY PART OF THE
GAME IS NOT JUST A PHYSICAL
THING.
IT'S ABOUT RESPONDING TO THE
SITUATION YOU'RE PUT IN, IN THIS
GAME, AND LEARNING HOW TO DO IT
WITH GRACE, WITH STYLE, WITH
FINESSE, WHEN YOU NEED TO, AND
IN YOUR FACE WHEN YOU NEED TO,
BUT WITHOUT ISOLATING YOURSELF.
>> Jeff: DID YOU FIND THAT
MILLION DOLLAR-- YOU WERE SO
BLINDED BY RAGE, LITERALLY, AS A
METAPHOR, YOU DIDN'T SEE A
MILLION-DOLLAR OPPORTUNITY.
>> I'M CHECKING THE STUMP RIGHT
NOW.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: SIERRA, QUESTION-- I
GOT THIS QUESTION A LOT.
I HAVE TWO QUICK QUESTIONS FOR
YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WE'RE LIEFG, WE'RE
RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
BUT WHY-- LIKE, YOU TELL SARAH,
"I HAVE A LEGACY ADVANTAGE."
AND EVERYBODY GOES, "WHY DID YOU
TELL HER!"
WHY DO YOU GUYS FEEL THE NEED AT
TIMES TO SHARE THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING IN THE GAME,
INFORMATION?
>> RIGHT.
I AT THAT POINT MADE THE BIGGEST
MISTAKE YOU COULD MAKE IN
"SURVIVOR" WITH MY HEART.
I WAS SITTING WITH HER.
I WAS BEING HONEST WITH HER.
I WAS BEING VULNERABLE WITH HER.
I HAD JUST SEEN MY FATHER, AND I
WAS IN A WEIRD PLACE AND THOUGHT
I COULD BE HONEST WITH SOMEBODY
WAS ALIGNED WITH.
>> Jeff: IT'S ULTIMATELY
TRUST.
>> I TRUST HER 100%.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, WHEN YOU
COME OUT AND DO EVERYTHING YOU
HAVE TO DO TO GET INTO THIS GAME
AND YOU'RE BLINDSIDED IN A CRAZY
TRIBAL, HONESTLY, HOW HARD IS IT
TO RECOVER FROM THAT?
>> YOU CRY FOR A FEW DAYS.
NO, WE'VE ALL DONE THIS BEFORE.
WE KNOW HOW UNPREDICTABLE IT CAN
BE.
ALL THE WINNERS ARE SITTING IN
THE BACK ROW THIS SEASON.
BUT THAT'S PART REASON WHY WE
LOVE PLAYING IT.
IT'S THAT MUCH FUN.
IT'S WHY MILLIONS OF PEOPLE LOVE
WATCHING IT.
AND THAT'S WHY 17 YEARS LATER
IT'S STILL THE GREATEST THING ON
TELEVISION.
>> Jeff: OZZY, AS WE GO TO
BREAK, YOU SEEMED TO REALLY BE A
GREAT SPOKESPERSON IN TERMS OF
WHETHER OR NOT YOU GUYS LIKE THE
NEW TRIBAL FORMAT, THE Q & A.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK SURVIVOR IS SUCH A
BEAUTIFUL MICROCOSIM FOR THE
WORLD.
AND WE ALL COME TOGETHER.
AND THE GAME-CHANGING THEME FOR
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL, TO HAVE THIS
OPEN FORUM, TO BRING US
TOGETHER, TO REALLY EXPRESS
THESE IDEAS THAT'S CORRECT
DIFFERENT IDEAS AND BRING OUR
DIFFERENT WALKS OF LIFE.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL MICROCOSM, AND
I THINK IT'S REALLY AMAZING THAT
IT ALLOWED US TO ACTUALLY CHOOSE
THE RIGHT PERSON THAT WON,
SARAH.
AND IT'S A MICROCOSM FOR THE
REST OF WORLD THAT WE ALL NEED
TO UNITE AS A PEOPLE TO CHANGE
THE WAY THE UNITED STATES IS
GOING.
AND WE NEED TO MAKE BETTER
DECISIONS ON HOW THE UNITED
STATES IS RUN.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT!
WELL OTHAT NOTE!
AS ONE SEASON ENDS, THERE'S ONLY
ONE QUESTION TO ASK, "WHAT'S
NEXT?"
WE'LL SHOW YOU, BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪ ♪
FOR OUR 35th SEASON,
"SURVIVOR" RETURNS TO ONE OF THE
MOST BEAUTIFUL PLACES ON EARTH,
FIJI.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER,
WE'LL DIVIDE THE TRIBES BASED ON
THE POSITIVE TRAITS MOST OFTEN
ASSOCIATED WITH THEM BY OTHERS.
HEROES.
THEY ARE HERALDED FOR THEIR
COURAGE, THEIR ACHIEVEMENTS AND
IDEALS FOR WHICH THEY STAND.
>> TO BE A MARINE IS HONOR,
COURAGE, AND COMMITMENT.
YOUR JOB IS TO SERVE THE COUNTRY
AND PROTECT THE COUNTRY.
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING FOR PRAISE
FOR WHAT YOU DONE AND WHO ARE
YOU.
YOU'RE JUST DOING YOUR JOB.
>> BEING A LIFE GUARD, WHEN YOU
RUN IN THE WATER TO SAVE
SOMEONE'S LIFE, YOUR ADRENALINE
IS GOING, YOUR HEART IS PUMPING.
BUT OUT HERE HERE IT'S EITHER
SINK, SWIM, OR GET OUT OF THE
OCEAN.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M GOING TO LET PEOPLE SINK.
>> Jeff: HEALERS, THEY RECEIVE
GRAT FEUD TOOUD FOR THEIR ACTS
OF SERVICE AND HELPING PEOPLE
HEAL THEIR EMOTIONAL AND
PHYSICAL PAIN.
>> I'M A SURGEON THAT DEALS WITH
A STRESSFUL SITUATION ON A DAILY
BASIS.
SO WHEN YOU PUT ME IN A
SITUATION LIKE, THIS I'M NOT
GOING TO FREAK OUT.
I'M GOING TO COME IN HERE WITH
SURGICAL EXPERTISE AND CARVE MY
WAY UP TO THE TOP.
>> PHYSICAL THERAPY IS VERY
GIVING, AND IT'S ABOUT OTHER
PEOPLE.
THIS IS A VERY SELFISH GAME, SO
IT'S TIME TO BE SELFISH AND ANY
OPPORTUNITY TO SHOW I'M TOUGHER
THAN YOU, STRONGER THAN YOU,
SMARTER THAN YOU, I'M ALL FOR
IT.
>> Jeff: HUSTLERS, THEY ARE
RESPECTED FOR THEIR WORK ETHIC,
GET IT DONE NO MATTER WHAT.
THEY STOP AT NOTHING TO ACHIEVE
THEIR GOALS.
>> I'M A PERSONAL ASSISTANT.
I DO ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING,
AND THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF IN
"SURVIVOR" THAT YOU HAVE TO DO
THAT YOU NORMALLY DON'T WANT TO
BE DOING BUT YOU GOTTA GET IT
DONE.
AND I'M USED TO DOING THE JOB
THAT NOBODY ELSE WANTS TO DO.
>> WORKING AS A BELLHOP, I'M 125
POUNDS SOAKING WET.
IT'S SO TOUGH, BUT I'M MORE
ATHLETIC THAN I LOOK, AND I GO
TO SLEEP THINKING ABOUT
"SURVIVOR."
AND NOW I'M READY.
I LOVE TURTLENECKS.
I DON'T DRINK AND I DON'T HAVE A
GIRLFRIEND.
COME ON, WHO WANTS TO ALIGN WITH
ME?
>> Jeff: THREE VERY DIFFERENT
APPROACHES TO LIFE.
ONCE AGAIN WILL BE TESTED IN THE
GREATEST SOCIAL EXPHERMT ON
TELEVISION.
IT'S "SURVIVOR: HEROES VERSUS
HEALERS VERSUS HUSTLERS."
CBS THIS FALL.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH "SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS"
LIVE REUNION SHOW.
>> Jeff: IT IS TH THE "SURVIVOR"
JEFF VARNER YOU SAID SOMETHING
TO ME DURING THE BREAK YOU
WANTED TO ADD.
>> I HAVE BEEN LIVING IN SHAME
FOR A YEAR AND I JUST CAME
THROUGH IT AND.
THERE'S A BOOK I'M WORKING ON
TITLED "SURVIVING SHAME" AND YOU
GETS THE FIRST COPY.
>> Jeff: IF THIS ADVENTURE,
ALL OF IT, EVERYTHING WE TALKED
ABOUT IN THE LAST 34 SEASONS
SEEMED FUN AND YOU WANT TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR," FIRST STEP, YOU HAVE
TO SHOW US WHO YOU ARE.
IF YOU WANT TO BID ON PROPS FROM
THIS SEASON GO TO
SURVIVORAUCTIONS.COM.
PROCEEDS GO TO STAND UP TO
CANCER.
YEAH, KICK IN THAT MUSIC,
BECAUSE I WANT TO SAY THIS FROM
MY HEART.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR LOYALTY!
THANK YOU FOR STAYING WITH US!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WE LOVE OUR JOBS, AND WE'LL
CONTINUE TO TRY TO GIVE YOU
GREAT "SURVIVOR" SEASONS.
GOOD NIGHT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
Captioning funded by CBS