>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," ZEKE AND ANDREA
FACED OFF.
>> IT'S JUST ALL SHADY.
WILL I TRUST ZEKE AGAIN?
OF COURSE NOT.
>> Jeff: AN ALLIANCE OF SIX
SEEMED UNSTOPPABLE.
>> NOW THAT WE HAVE SARAH, THERE
IS A LINE DRAWN IN CONCRETE.
NO BUT A CRACK HAD ALREADY
FORMED.
>> WE CAN MAKE A MOVE.
>> HELL, YEAH, I WANT TO MAKE A
MOVE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO NEED ANDREA.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SARAH BROUGHT THE MINORITY
TOGETHER AND SENT DEBBIE TO THE
JURY.
DEBBIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SHOCKING CULPEPPER, SIERRA,
TROYZAN, AND TAI.
TEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WELL PLAYED, GUYS.
BRAVO.
QUITE THE BLIND SIDE.
COMING BACK FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I'M IN SHOCK.
I WAS TOTALLY BLIND SIDED, AND
SIX VOTES DEBBIE, FIVE VOTES
ANDREA.
>> IT'S THE QUIETEST IT'S EVER
BEEN AFTER TRIBAL.
>> I WAS IN A GREAT POSITION
BEFORE TONIGHT.
I WENT FROM BEING IN PRETTY GOOD
SHAPE WITH THE SIX TO IN
TERRIBLE SHAPE WITH THE FLOOR.
>> ARE YOU CONFUSED ON WHO
FLIPPED?
I DID.
IF ANYBODY WANTS TO TALK TO ME.
>> TONIGHT ON TRIBAL COUNCIL, I
WAS THE DECIDING VOTE IN WHICH
ALLIANCE WAS GOING TO GET THE
MAJORITY OF THE NUMBERS.
>> DEBBIE SEEMED LIKE SHE WAS
THE ONE IN CHARGE.
>> THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
IT'S GAME CHANGERS.
HOPEFULLY IF I MAKE IT TO THE
END, THE JURY WILL REWARD THE
FACT THAT I WAS A GAME CHANGER
TO MAKE THIS TYPE OF MOVE.
>> HOW IS THE GAME CHANGING?
WE HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER.
I'M HAPPY.
>> I'M COMPLETELY CONTENT WITH
GOING WITH OUR GROUP.
>> GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY.
WE TOOK THE CONTROL FROM SIERRA
AND BRAD TONIGHT.
BUT IN "SURVIVOR," THERE'S NEVER
ANY REST AT ALL.
YOU HAVE TO BE LIKE AN EVIL EYE.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH EVERYTHING,
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE NOT WATCHING,
IT JUST TAKES A SECOND AND THE
WRONG MOVE AND THE NEXT THING
YOU KNOW YOU'RE SITTING ON THE
JURY.
Captioning funded by CBS
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEP.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL BE DIVIDED INTO TWO TEAMS
OF FIVE.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON FROM EACH
TEAM WILL RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES TO A CHAIR WHERE
YOUR TEAM WILL LIFT THE CHAIR,
ALLOWING YOU TO RETRIEVE TEN
NUMBERED BAGS.
ONCE YOU HAVE YOUR TEN, THE NEXT
PERSON GOES.
ONCE YOU'VE COLLECTED ALL 30
BAGS, YOU'LL USE THE LETTERS
INSIDE TO SOLVE A WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST TEAM TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR IN.
>> IMRE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING FIVE WILL
BE TAKEN BY CHOPPER TO A LUXURY
RESORT, WHERE YOU WILL ENJOY A
NICE MEAL OF BEEF, CHICKEN
WRAPS, AND CHEESECAKE FOR
DESSERT.
>> CHEESECAKE, OH, MY GOD.
CHEESECAKE.
>> Jeff: THERE'S MORE.
YOU WILL SPEND THE NIGHT.
>> OH, WOW.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: AND YOU WILL SLEEP IN
A REAL BED.
>> YOU'RE KIDDING ME?
>> Jeff: THIS WILL BE YOUR
FIRST GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP IN 27
DAYS, AND CLEARLY YOU NEED IT.
>> THIS IS NOT REAL LIFE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
I KNOW IT'S WORTH PLAYING FOR.
WE'RE GOING TO DO A SCHOOLYARD
PICK AND WE'LL GET IT ON.
LET'S DO THIS!
THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
RUNNING FOR BLUE, IT IS ANDREA,
SARAH, AUBRY, ZEKE, AND
CULPEPPER.
RUNNING FOR ORANGE IT IS SIERRA,
TROYZAN, CIRIE, TAI, AND
MICHAELA.
FOR A HUGE REWARD, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
>> YOU GOT IT, CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA FINALLY
GETTING A CHANCE TO SHOW WHAT
SHE'S MADE OF.
SHE SAT OUT OF A LOT OF
CHALLENGES.
SHE IS HITTING IT HARD.
IT IS CULPEPPER VERSUS MICHAELA.
MICHAELA NOW IN THE LEAD.
>> YOU GOT IT, CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: HIGH STEPPING IT
THROUGH.
THERE MICHAELA GETS TO THE CHAIR
QUICKLY.
CULPEPPER RIGHT BEHIND.
START PULLING HER.
START PULLING HIM.
>> PULL, PULL!
>> PULL.
PULL, PULL.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO GET THEM
IN ORDER ONE THROUGH TEN.
>> KEEP PULLING.
DO NOT STOP PULLING.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER HAS HIS
FIRST.
MICHAELA HAS ONE.
>> Jeff:>> KEEP PULLING, TAI.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER NOW HAS
TWO.
MICHAELA LOOKING FOR TWO NOW.
THE BETTER TEAMWORK, THE FASTER
YOU MOVE THEM UP AND DOWN, THE
FASTER YOU WILL FINNISH.
BLUE WORKING VERY WELL TOGETHER.
CULPEPPER WITH EIGHT.
>> DOWN, BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: ORANGE IS CATCHING
UP.
THEY ARE CLOSING THAT GAP.
>> PULL, PULL!
>> Jeff: MICHAELA TRYING TO
GET A RHYTHM GOING.
MICHAELA WITH EIGHT.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER HAS TEN.
HE NEEDS TO COME DOWN.
MICHAELA HAS TEN.
SHE CAN COME DOWN.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET ALL TEN BAGS
ON THE PUZZLE TABLE.
CULPEPPER DOING ONE.
WE'RE NECK AND NECK FOR A HUGE
REWARD.
IT IS ANDREA HEADING OUT NOW AND
TROYZAN.
>> COME ON, ANDREA.
>> Jeff: WE'RE VERY CLOSE
RIGHT NOW.
>> COME ON, TROYZAN.
>> Jeff: IT IS ANDREA WITH A
BIT OF A LEAD OVER TROYZAN.
>> THAT'S IT, ANDREA.
>> GO, TROYZAN.
>> Jeff: BLUE IS BACK UP
QUICKLY.
HERE GOES ORANGE.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR 11 THROUGH
20 NOW.
>> ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP.
>> Jeff: THE NEXT TEN NUMBERS.
>> GOT IT, GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ANDREA WITH 11.
ORANGE MAKING VERY LITTLE
PROGRESS.
GOING VERY SLOW.
BLUE IS MAKING QUICK WORK OF
THIS ROUND.
ANDREA ALREADY TO 14.
ANDREA LOOKING FOR 15 NOW.
>> LEFT, LEFT!
>> Jeff: TROYZAN NOW HAS 14.
ANDREA'S ALREADY GOT 17.
MAKE IT 18.
TROYZAN NOW STARTING TO GET A UM
GOING WITH HIS TEAM.
HE'S AT 17.
ANDREA LOOKING FOR THAT LAST
NUMBER OF THIS ROUND, NUMBER 20,
AND SHE'S GOT IT.
YOU CAN HEAD DOWN.
TROYZAN HAS 19.
HE'S HEADING UP FOR 20.
>> GRAB IT, TROY.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN HAS 20.
HE'S HEADING DOWN.
>> GO, TROYZAN.
>> Jeff: YOU GOT TO GET THEM
ALL ON THAT TABLE.
ONCE AGAIN WE'RE TIGHT.
IT IS SIERRA AND SARAH SIDE BY
SIDE.
>> YOU GOT IT, SIERRA.
>> Jeff: A GIANT REWARD ON THE
LINE.
SARAH TAKES A BIG FALL.
>> YOU GOT IT, SARAH.
>> Jeff: BOTH WOMEN IN THEIR
CHAIRS NOW.
WHICH FOURSOME WILL PULL
FASTEST.
ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP FOR
NUMBER 21.
>>
SARAH HAS HER FIRST LETTER TILE.
>> KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
NOT YET.
>> TAI, YOU TELL US.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN ORANGE
STRUGGLING TO GET THEIR PERSON
ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP.
AND IT IS COSTING THEM VALUABLE
TIME.
SARAH FLYING THROUGH THIS.
SHE'S AT 28.
MAKE IT 29.
SIERRA FALLING BEHIND NOW AT 26.
SARAH HAS ALL 30.
ORANGE STRUGGLING.
SARAH'S GOT TO GET THOSE TILES
TO THE TABLE.
SIERRA NOW WORKING ON 30.
DROP HER.
SARAH GOING TO HAVE THE MAKE TWO
RUNS.
YOU'RE GOOD, BLUE.
UNCLIP.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
SIERRA DOES IT IN ONE.
YOU'RE GOOD, ORANGE.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
ANDREA, CULPEPPER AND ZEKE FOR
BLUE.
IT IS MICHAELA, CIRIE, AND
SIERRA FOR ORANGE.
YOU ARE SOLVING A WORD PUZZLE
USING 30 LETTERS.
>> THERE'S NO C, THERE'S NO
HELICOPTER.
>> Jeff: BOTH MICHAELA AND
ZEKE RAN THIS CHALLENGE IN THEIR
SEASON.
BOTH WERE ON THE WINNING TEAM.
NOW COMES THE HARD WORK.
WHAT IS THE PHRASE?
>> HOW DO YOU SPELL LONGEVITY?
>> Jeff: IT'S VERY CLEAR THAT
EVERYBODY'S COGNITIVE FUNCTIONS
ARE STRUGGLING, AND YET YOU HAVE
TO SOLVE ONE OF THE MOST
DIFFICULT THINGS IN THIS GAME.
>> IT HAS TO BE 11.
>> Jeff: COULD BE LITERALLY
ANY PHRASE THAT YOU CAN THINK
OF.
>> N-E -- THERE'S AN L.
>> HEY, IS NUTRITIONAL 11
LETTERS?
>> REVITALIZE?
REPLENISH?
HOW DO YOU SPELL WITHERING?
LIKE WITHERING AWAY?
SUSTENANCE?
>> NOURISHMENT IN
>> DEPRIVATION?
>> REJUVENATION?
>> PERSPIRATION?
>> Jeff: RARELY DO PUZZLES GO
THIS LONG, BUT RARELY ARE THEY
THIS DIFFICULT.
>> 11-LETTER WORD.
>> Jeff: AS "SURVIVOR"
CONTINUES TO EVOLVE, SO DO THE
PUZZLES, SO YOU CAN NEVER RELY
ON WHAT YOU USED BEFORE AS THE
CRITERIA BECAUSE THE GAME IS
CONSTANTLY CHANGING.
YOU GUYS ARE CHANGING IT.
>> WE HAVE LETTERS FOR GAME.
>> Jeff: THIS PUZZLE IS A
GREAT METAPHOR FOR THIS SEASON,
BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS ALWAYS
CHANGING IN THIS GAME.
BLUE MOVING LETTERS AROUND
AGAIN.
IS THIS THE IDEA THAT WILL WORK?
>> LOOK AT THEM IN
>> ZEKE CONTINUES TO MOVE PIECES
AROUND.
ORANGE TRYING TO GET SOMETHING
GOING.
IS BLUE RIGHT?
COULD THEY HAVE PULLED IT OUT OF
THIN AIR?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: ZEKE SEEMS CERTAIN.
ANDREA SEEMS CERTAIN.
JEFF?
>> SAY IT.
>> REINVENTING HOW THIS GAME IS
PLAYED.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, CULPEPPER,
SARAH, ZEKE AND AUBRY WIN REWARD
AT A LUXURY SPA.
>> OH, ZEKE, THAT WAS
UNBELIEVABLE.
ALL RIGHT.
ZEKE, AUBRY, SARAH, CULPEPPER,
ANDREA, GREAT REWARD.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT,
ENJOY.
ALL RIGHT, CIRIE, TAI, SIERRA,
MICHAELA, TROYZAN, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> WALKING OFF I CAN HARDLY
CONTAIN MYSELF.
I'M GOING ON MY REWARD.
I'M GOING TO HAVE AN
UNBELIEVABLE MEAL, BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY I'M WITH THE PEOPLE
I NEED TO BE WITH FROM A
STRATEGIC STANDPOINT TO CHANGE
THE GAME.
IT'S A WIN-WIN.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN IN A
HELICOPTER.
SUPER STOKED.
I GET A WINDOW SEAT.
FIJI.
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
IT'S INSANE HOW MANY ISLANDS AND
HOW BEAUTIFUL THEY ARE.
THE HELICOPTER LANDS BASICALLY
RED CARPET ROLLED OUT.
THERE'S A GUY WAITING WITH
DRINKS FOR US.
>> WELCOME.
>> OH, YES.
>> CHEERS.
>> HERE'S TO REINVENTING HOW THE
GAME IS PLAYED.
>> CHEERS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NO WAY.
>> NICE INFINITY POOL.
>> HOLY SMOKES.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS, YOU GUYS.
>> NICE.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO START WITH.
>> I'M STARTING WITH THE
CHOCOLATE.
>> CALAMARI.
>> AN EGG.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A RESORT
AS INCREDIBLE AS THIS PLACE.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A GORGEOUS
FIJIAN MANSION.
LIFE IS FANTASTIC RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS A LAZY SUZANNE.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> HELL YEAH.
>> WE GET A BEAUTIFUL MEAL AND
WE GORGE OURSELVES BECAUSE
PLAYING SURVIVOR IS LIKE
CLIMBING EVEREST.
IT GETS HARDER AND HARDER THE
FURTHER YOU GO UP, AND YOU
REALLY HAVE TO REFUEL YOUR BODY
AND YOU MIND, SLOG IT THROUGH
THESE LAST DAYS.
IT ONLY GETS HARDER EVERY SINGLE
DAY.
>> THIS IS EXCELLENT.
>> 2007 FLORIDA-OKLAHOMA GAME.
>> I WAS THERE.
>> WERE YOU?
>> YEP.
>> WHERE WAS IT, TEMPE?
>> NO, IN MIAMI.
I WAS THERE FOR THE S.C.
OKLAHOMA GAME AND THE FLORIDA
GAME.
>> REALLY?
>> LOOKING AT THE PEOPLE IN THE
REWARD, IT WOULD SEEM LIKE BRAD
IS THE ODD MAN OUT, BUT THERE IS
WEIRD BONDING BETWEEN BRAD AND
ZEKE.
>> THAT FLORIDA GAME WAS THE ONE
MY DAD AND I STOPPED GOING TO
BALLGAMES.
>> AS A "SURVIVOR" SUPER FAN, I
WOULD THINK ZEKE WOULD KNOW
BETTER THAN THIS.
ZEKE VOTED WITH US LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BUT I DON'T THINK WE'LL
EVER GET BACK TO THE PLACE WE
WERE BEFORE HE BETRAYED ME, AND
I'M NEVER GOING TO FORGET THAT
HE DID THAT, SO I AM A LITTLE
NERVOUS THAT NOW HE'S GOING TO
TRY TO DO SOMETHING WITH BRAD,
IT'S SUPER LAME.
>> DREAMS DO COME TRUE.
>> THEY DO.
>> SERIOUSLY, AN OVERNIGHT STAY.
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> I'M SO HUNGRY AND TIRED.
>> IT WAS REALLY CRAPPY NIGHT.
I MEAN, I GOT NO SLEEP.
I'M EXHAUSTED.
AND I'M STILL TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT THE HECK HAPPENED THE
OTHER NIGHT AT TRIBAL.
IT'S SUPER HUMBLING TO BE LIKE,
OKAY, I'M AT THE BOTTOM WITH
BRAD, TAI AND TROYZAN, BUT
HOPEFULLY SOMETHING HAPPENS
WHERE I CAN GET INTO THE
NUMBERS.
>> YESTERDAY WAS DOOM.
>> WE'RE STILL HERE.
THE GAME'S STILL GOING ON, YOU
KNOW?
IT CHANGES A LOT.
>> SO IF YOUR NAME COME UP, IF
MY NAME COME UP...
>> THIS IS MY FIRST TIME IN
PLAYING TWO SEASONS I FEEL LIKE
I'M REALLY AT THE BOTTOM.
>> MAYBE THEY PLACED ANOTHER
IDOL OUT HERE THAT.
COULD CHANGE SOME THINGS.
>> MAYBE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M NOT TELLING ANYBODY THAT
I DO HAVE TWO IDOLS, BUT I'D
RATHER NOT PLAY IT.
THE LONGER I AM HAVING THE
IDOLS, THE LONGER I'LL BE IN THE
GAME.
IF MY NAME COMES UP, I'M GOING
TO PLAY IT.
>> THEY'RE BACK.
>> MY GOD.
WHY DID YOU GET BACK SO EARLY.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU GAINED
WEIGHT.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
YOU GAINED WEIGHT.
>> COMING BACK FROM THE REWARD,
I FEEL SO LUCKY.
IT FELT LIKE LIFE STYLES OF THE
RICH AND FAMOUS.
IT WAS AWESOME.
HOWEVER, I'M A LITTLE BIT
CONCERNED ABOUT THE FACT THAT I
FEEL LIKE BRAD AND ZEKE HAD TIME
TO BOND WITH EACH OTHER.
SO I THINK WE NEED TO KIND OF
THINK VERY CAREFULLY ABOUT WHO
WE WANT TO TAKE OUT IN THE NEXT
VOTE.
>> I KNOW ZEKE'S GOING TO COME
AFTER ME AT SOME POINT.
>> I GOT YOUR BACK.
>> WE COULD TAKE HIM OUT AND
WE'D STILL HAVE NUMBERS OVER THE
OTHER PEOPLE.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> AN OPTION.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THE
PERSON THROWING OUT NAMES.
YOU ALSO DON'T WANT TO BE THE
PERSON THAT WAITS TOO LONG TO
MAKE A MOVE.
SO NOW I'M TRYING TO PUT THE
TARGET ON ZEKE.
IF ZEKE THINK IT'S THE SIX
THAT'S GOING THE STAY TOGETHER
FOR A FEW VOTES, MAYBE TAKE ONE
OF THOSE VOTES AND BLIND SIDE
HIM.
>> HE THINKS HE'S THE SMARTEST
PERSON OUT HERE.
IT WOULD BE EASY FOR US SIX TO
VOTE SIERRA AND GO ALONG, BUT
ZEKE IS WAY MORE THREATENING TO
ME THAN SIERRA.
HE KNOWS THIS GAME BETTER THAN
ANY OF US OUT HERE.
I PLAYED FOUR TIMES, AND ZEKE
KNOWS THIS GAME BETTER THAN I
DO.
>> WE CAN FEEL OUT AUBRY AND
SARAH.
ASK HER WHAT SHE WANTS TO DO.
NOW I HAVE TO GET SARAH ON
BOARD, BUT OFFICER SARAH'S REAL
TOUCHY ABOUT ZEKE, SO YOU GOT TO
HANDLE OFFICER SARAH VERY
CAREFULLY.
WOULDN'T IT BE SMART WE VOTED
ZEKE TOMORROW AND WE STILL HAVE
THE NUMBERS TO GET ONE OF THEM
NEXT TIME.
>> HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT
THAT?
>> WELL, I'M NOT CONCERNED ABOUT
ZEKE.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE I ALREADY KNOW HOW I
WANT TO HANDLE ZEKE.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
>> AND THAT'S WITH BACK-UP.
WHEN CIRIE PRESENTS THE IDEA OF
GETTING RID OF ZEKE, I'M
DEFINITELY NOT DOWN FOR IT
BECAUSE I CAN TRUST ZEKE, SO I
NEED TO REASSURE HER TO KEEP HIM
IN THIS GAME AS LONG AS I CAN.
I NEED TO FILL HER IN ON WHAT MY
SECRET ADVANTAGE IS.
TYPICALLY IN "SURVIVOR" YOU
DON'T WANT TO SHOW YOU CARD, BUT
SOMETIMES IT'S NECESSARY TO LOCK
PEOPLE IN.
>>THE REASON I'M CONCERNED
BECAUSE
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT
BACK-UP IS.
>> WHAT?
>> I STEEL -- STEAL A VOTE.
I GET A VOTE AGAIN.
THE SMALLER IN NUMBERS WE GET,
THE EASIER IT IS TO GET ZEKE
OUT.
YOU'RE ONLY GETTING TO SIX,
BUDDY.
>> OKAY.
>> I FEEL PRETTY GOOD WITH
CIRIE.
I THINK IT COMPLETELY CALMED HER
AND SMOOTHED OVER THE SITUATION,
BUT IN THE EVENT THAT THEY WANT
TO FLIP THE SCRIPT, I COULD JUMP
SHIP NEXT VOTE AND GO BACK AND
WORK WITH TROYZAN AND BRAD AND
SIERRA AND TAI BECAUSE I WANT TO
GO WITH WHATEVER SIDE CAN GET ME
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> WE CAN MAKE IT TO THE END.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE GOING TO STICK WITH THE PLAN,
SO IT'S GOING TO BE SIERRA?
>> I FIND MYSELF SITTING IN THE
MIDDLE, WHICH AGAIN WORKS
PERFECT FOR ME.
SO I'M GOING TO LET THE PLANS
DEVELOP.
AND THEN I'M GOING TO PICK A
SIDE.
>> HERE'S WHY I'M NERVOUS TODAY.
THERE'S AN EERIE CALM ABOUT
CAMP.
THESE PEOPLE I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO MAKE HEADS OR TAILS.
IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD FOR ME TO
GET A READ ON WHERE THE LINES
ARE DRAWN, AND I FEEL LIKE I
SORT OF HAVE BEEN HANDCUFFED AND
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO PLAY LIKE I
WANT TO PLAY, BUT NOW THE GAME
HAS BEEN BROKEN OPEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I'M FINALLY GETTING TO USE MY
"SURVIVOR" SKILL SET, WHICH IS
THE RUNNING AROUND AND THE
SCHEMING AND THE PLOTTING AND
THE VOTING PEOPLE OUT.
>> IF WE GET RID OF SIERRA AND
THEN WE GET RID OF ANDREA AND
THEN WE GET RID OF TAI...
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> SO IN A ROUND ABOUT WAY,
LET'S HAVE THAT BE OUR OUTLINE,
OUR BLUEPRINT OF HOW WE WANT
THIS TO GO.
>> GOOD.
>> I FEEL GOOD WITH ZEKE.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SINCE DAY
ONE.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE STAYING WITH THE
GIRLS, BUT AT THE END OF THE
DAY, I DON'T TRUST THEM, I TRUST
ZEKE.
>> I THINK THAT OUR MAIN MISSION
IS BRINGING IN BRAD AND TROYZAN.
>> AND SO... LOOK, I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS WITHOUT YOUR
PERMISSION, BUT I SORT OF WANT
TO MAKE LIKE A FINAL FIVE DEAL
WITH BRAD AND TROY.
>> AND ME AND YOU AND WHO?
>> MICHAELA.
OR AT LEAST TELL THEM, THAT
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M LOCKED IN WITH SARAH
BECAUSE I BELIEVE I CAN TRUST
SARAH TO THE END, BUT I DON'T
TRUST ANDREA AND AUBRY, WHO ARE
A VERY TIGHT PAIR.
I NEED A COUPLE OPTIONS.
BRAD AND I BONDED ON THE REWARD.
NOW WE'RE GETTING TO THE POINT
WHERE I NEED TO BRING IN ENTERED
AND TROYZAN.
>> WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
>> I JUST WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
GUYS BECAUSE I WOULD LIKE TO
WORK WITH YOU, I DON'T KNOW, WE
COULD SAY FINAL FIVE BUT I'M NOT
CLOSING THE DOOR ON FINAL FIVE,
RIGHT?
>> CORRECT.
>> I HIT THINK IT WOULD MAKE
SENSE.
>> I CAN'T LOOP YOU IN ON THIS
NEXT VOTE I CAN SAY WITH
CERTAINTY IT'S NEITHER OF YOU
GUYS.
THEN ON THE NEXT VOTE I THINK WE
DO SOMETHING INTERESTING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT'S MUSIC TO MY EARS.
I MADE TREMENDOUS HEADWAY
GETTING IN WITH ZEKE AT THE
REWARD.
>> THE T TWO OF YOU, THREE OF
US.
>> SO IN 24 HOURS I WORKED MY
WAY UP VERY QUICKLY, NOT WITHOUT
EFFORT, INTO A GOOD POSITION.
IT WILL BOTHER ME IF I HAVE TO
VOTE FOR TAI OR SIERRA, BUT MAKE
NO MISTAKE, I AM HERE TO WIN THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET INTO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TROYZAN.
GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
SPINNING GREEN.
>> IS THAT A NEW HASHTAG?
>> Jeff: JUST FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
I LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO STACK A SERIES OF
BLOCKS ON A BEAM WHILE
ATTEMPTING TO AVOID A TRIP
OBSTACLE.
IF YOU HIT THE OBSTACLE, YOUR
BLOCKS WILL FALL.
YOU'LL HAVE TO RESTACK.
YOUR GOAL IS TO STACK THE BLOCKS
SO THEY FALL LIKE DOMINOES,
ULTIMATELY HITTING A GONG.
THE FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY SAFE FROM THE VOTE,
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE 11th
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
AND BECOME THE FOURTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY.
DRAW FOR SPOTS, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HOAR WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THIS IS ALL ABOUT FACING THE
BLOCKS AND ANTICIPATING HOW
QUICKLY YOU CAN MOVE THROUGH
THIS OBSTACLE WITHOUT HITTING
IT.
LOTS OF DIFFERENT STRATEGIES.
TRYING TO GUESS HOW MUCH SPACE
DO I NEED, WHAT'S THE FEWEST
AMOUNTS OF BLOCKS I CAN USE THE
MAKE THIS THING WORK.
AND YOU HAVE TO AVOID THAT TRIP
OBSTACLE BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
WILL MAKE YOUR TABLE WOBBLE.
SO FAR EVERYBODY DOING A VERY
GOOD JOB OF BEING VERY NIMBLE,
GIVEN IT IS DAY 29.
VERY IMPRESSED.
IT TAKES A LOT OF ENERGY TO HIGH
STEP EACH TIME.
THIS IS A VERY CLOSE CHALLENGE
OUT OF THE GATE FOR QUITE A FEW.
CIRIE, ANDREA, SARAH, MICHAELA,
SIERRA ALL VERY CLOSE.
THOSE ARE THE LEADERS RIGHT NOW.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKING A SLOWER
APPROACH, HOPING FOR FAILURE
FROM SOMEBODY ELSE.
FIRST PERSON TO DROP IS
CULPEPPER.
HE LOSES EVERYTHING.
GOT TO START OVER.
THAT'S HOW QUICKLY YOUR LEAD CAN
VANISH.
IT IS NOW ANDREA, SARAH, DEAD
EVEN.
HERE COMES MICHAELA WITH CIRIE
RIGHT BEHIND.
MICHAELA TIES UP WITH SARAH AND
ANDREA.
IT IS THREE WOMEN, MICHAELA,
SARAH, AND ANDREA, ALL AT THE
SAME SPOT IN THIS CHALLENGE.
SARAH WITH A BIT OF A LEAD.
BUT MICHAELA ON HER TAIL, AND
ANDREA RIGHT THERE.
SIERRA NOT GIVING UP.
SHE'S STILL IN THIS.
TROYZAN PICKING UP HIS PACE.
AUBRY IS STILL IN IT.
ZEKE TRYING TO STAY IN THIS.
NOW IT IS ANDREA IN THE LEAD.
MICHAELA IS IN SECOND.
THEN SARAH SLOWING DOWN.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS HOPING FOR A
MISTAKE RIGHT NOW.
>> I DON'T HAVE TOO MUCH SPACE.
>> Jeff: ANDREA NEARING THE
END.
NOW COMES THE BIG QUESTION: DID
I SPACE THESE CORRECTLY?
DO I HAVE ENOUGH BLOCKS TO
FINISH.
ANDREA DOWN TO ONE BLOCK LEFT.
WILL IT BE ENOUGH OR IS SHE
GOING TO COME UP SHORT AND HAVE
TO RESTACK EVERYTHING.
MICHAELA STILL HAS THREE BLOCKS
LEFT AND SARAH STILL HAS FOUR
BLOCKS LEFT.
THIS COULD BE THE DIFFERENCE.
ANDREA REALIZING SHE'S GOING TO
HAVE TO RESTACK HER ENTIRE LINE,
WHICH PULLS HER OUT OF THE LEAD
AND OPENS THE DOOR FOR MICHAELA,
SARAH AND SIERRA NOW.
IT IS A RACE.
CAN SIERRA, SARAH AND MICHAELA
GET THEIR BLOCKS TO THE END
FASTER THAN ANDREA CAN
REPOSITION HERS?
HERE COMES SARAH WITH ANOTHER
BLOCK.
SHE HAS TWO LEFT.
ANDREA IS RACING TO RESPACE.
MCDONALD'S RACING FOR THAT LAST
BLOCK.
THIS IS IT.
ANDREA THINKS SHE HAS IT.
SHE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
AND SHE DOES.
ANDREA PULLS OUT INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
>> DAMMIT, MINE WOULD HAVE BEEN
GOOD.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, COME ON OVER.
SECOND INDIVIDUAL WIN, AND I'M
QUESTIONING GIVEN THE CRAZINESS
OF THE LAST TRIBAL, THIS IS
GOING TO COME IN VERY HANDY.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ANDREA SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 29
DAYS,.
IT WILL FALL SHORT.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> I REALLY NEEDED IT TODAY.
I'M AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
NUMBERS.
I'M NOT SAFE.
I DON'T FEEL SAFE.
SO I'M TERRIFIED.
I'M HOPING I CAN GET BACK THE
CAMP, MAKE A BIG MOVE AND THEY
KEEP ME HERE JUST ANOTHER DAY
LONGER.
>> NOW THAT I WON THE CHALLENGE,
LET'S MAKE A BIGGER MOVE HERE.
I'M FOR SURE SAFE TONIGHT, SO
WHY NOT GO FOR SOMEONE THAT'S
BEEN COMING FOR ME, AND THAT
WOULD BE ZEKE.
>> NICE JOB, ANDREA.
>> GOOD JOB.
YOU ARE FAST, GIRL.
>> INITIALLY WE WERE TARGETING
SIERRA.
WE HAVE SIX, THEY HAVE FOUR, WHY
NOT JUST PLUCK ONE OF THEM OFF,
BUT MY RELATIONSHIP WITH ZEKE
HAS BEEN SO OUT OF CONTROL, WE
WENT FROM WHAT I THOUGHT WAS
BFFs TO HIM TOTALLY BETRAYING
ME.
AND NOW I CANNOT WAIT TO GET HIM
OUT OF THIS GAME.
I KNOW HE'S GOING TO COME AFTER
ME AT SOME POINT, SO THAT'S WHY
THIS PLAN IS SO BRILLIANT,
BECAUSE HE WON'T SEE IT COMING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?
>> I THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
I THINK THAT ZEKE IS BOUND TO
TURN ON ME AND YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO IF WE TAKE HIM OUT, IT
WILL PROBABLY BE A BLIND SIDE.
>> HOW ARE WE GOING TO DO IT
UNLESS I CAN... UNLESS WE CAN
ALL TALK HER INTO IT WITHOUT HER
RUNNING AND TELLING.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING.
BUT I WAS THINKING OF SOME OTHER
THING, THOUGH.
>> YEAH?
>> I THINK FOR SURE SIERRA WILL
GO WITH US.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT BRAD.
>> HEY.
>> I'M NOT FOLLOWING YOU.
>> COMING TO SEE WHAT'S UP AND
POSSIBLY PLEAD A CASE.
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
YOU.
>> WE WERE, AND YOUR CASE.
YOU GOT TO GIVE US A MINUTE.
>> IF YOU WANT TIME...
>> NO, NO, NO, YOU CAN STAY.
WE WERE JUST...
>> OBVIOUSLY YOU WOULD BE ON
BOARD TO VOTE FOR WHOEVER,
RIGHT?
>> WHOEVER.
I PROMISE YOU, I WILL STAR IT, I
WILL MAKE A LITTLE THING SO YOU
KNOW IT'S ME.
THERE'S NO QUESTION.
I PROMISE YOU.
>> AT THIS MOMENT I'M REACHING
FOR STRAWS, AND I'M GOING TO DO
WHAT THE GIRLS TELL ME TO DO.
TONIGHT I'M GOING TO TURN MY
BACK ON MY INITIAL ALLIANCE, AND
I'M WILLING AT ANY MOMENT TO
THROW ANY ONE OF THEM UNDER THE
BUS.
I PROMISE I WILL VOTE WHERE YOU
WANT ME TO.
THANK YOU, SERIOUSLY, FROM THE
BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
I'M TRYING TO BE PATIENT AND SIT
BECOME AND WAIT FOR THE WORD,
AND I HOPE THAT IT'S NOT ME.
>> WE NEED TO HAVE THIS
CONVERSATION WITH SARAH SOONER
THAN LATER.
PERFECT, HERE SHE COMES.
>> BE EASY.
WE GOT TO BE REAL, REAL EASY.
>> WHAT'S UP, LADY?
>> HEY.
>> NICE WIN, GIRL.
>> THE ONLY REASON I'M A LITTLE
PISSED IS BECAUSE I WAS SO
CLOSE, BUT I...
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> SO WHAT'S THE DEALO?
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WANT TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT?
>> OKAY.
THIS IS MY PLEA BECAUSE I KNOW
HE WILL COME AFTER ME.
IF WE GOT RID OF ZEKE AND BLIND
SIDE HIM, IT COULD BE VERY
DANGEROUS.
HE WOULD HAVE FIVE, THEY WOULD
HAVE FOUR.
>> JUST BECAUSE ANDREA'S GOT A
LITTLE POWER NOW, SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT POTENTIALLY TAKING OUT
ZEKE THIS VOTE.
I'M DEFINITELY NOT DOWN FOR IT.
I NEED ZEKE FOR A FEW MORE
VOTES.
BUT I REALLY NEED TO KEEP MY
MOUTH SHUT, BECAUSE IF I START
SCRAMBLING AROUND TO TRY TO SAVE
ZEKE, I'M GOING TO GET IN HOT
WATER.
>> I'M GOOD WITH THIS, BUT THEN
AT FIVE WE'RE STAYING STRONG?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I THINK THIS PLAN...
>> I THINK IT'S FOOL-PROOF.
>> WHAT IS IT NOW?
WHAT'S THE NUMBER?
>> 6-4.
>> WE CAN KNOCK OFF AS MANY OF
THEM AS WE WANT, BUT IF WE GOT
RID OF ZEKE AND BLIND SIDED HIM,
WE WOULD HAVE FIVE, THEY WOULD
HAVE FOUR.
>> ZEKE'S A REALLY SMART PLAYER.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY CALCULATING
THINGS MANY MOVES DOWN THE LINE.
AND SOMETHING YOU HAVE TO DO IN
"SURVIVOR" IS YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO
STRIKE BEFORE THE OTHER PERSON.
>> IF I CAN FEEL CONFIDENT WITH
EACH PERSON, THEN I'M GOOD.
>> I DON'T SEE HOW GETTING RID
OF ZEKE RIGHT NOW IS A SMART
MOVE.
THEY DON'T SEEM TO SEE THAT IF
YOU LEAVE FOUR PEOPLE ON THE
BOTTOM, THEY ONLY NEED ONE MORE
PERSON TO BE IN THE MAJORITY FOR
THE REST OF THE GAME.
>> EVERYONE GOOD?
>> YEAH, THERE'S NO FUNNY STUFF
GOING ON, RIGHT?
>> NOT TO MY KNOWLEDGE.
>> ZEKE IS SOMEBODY THAT I CAN
TRUST TO SOME LEVEL, BECAUSE WE
HAVE PLAYED TOGETHER BEFORE.
SO AT THIS POINT, I DON'T WANT
TO VOTE OUT ZEKE.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE ONE OF THOSE
FOUR NEEDS TO GO HOME.
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT TO ME WOULD BE THE
SAFEST THING, AND THEN THAT WAY
WE GOT MORE WIGGLE ROOM.
>> I KNOW.
>> ALL IT TAKES IS ONE PERSON,
AND I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> TONIGHT IS NOW ABOUT SIERRA
VERSUS ZEKE.
THIS VOTE FOR OUR ALLIANCE IS A
HUGE DECISION, BECAUSE RIGHT NOW
IT'S 6-4.
WE VOTE OUT ONE OF OUR OWN, IT'S
5-4.
ONE PERSON FLIPS OVER, AND
THEY'VE GOT THE NUMBERS.
>> TONIGHT WE FIND OUT IF THE
SIX STAY TOGETHER.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IF I
PRESS THE ISSUE OF KEEPING ZEKE,
THEY'RE GOING TO THINK I HAVE AN
ULTERIOR MOTIVE, THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO TRUST ME AND TRUST IS
EVERYTHING IN THIS GAME, SO I
DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO,
BUT I HAVE A FEELING THE
DECIDING VOTE IS GOING TO COME
DOWN TO MICHAELA AND ME.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
HALI, OZZY, AND DEBBIE VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL, IT WAS
CLEAR FROM THE LOOKS ON
EVERYBODY'S FACES THAT SOMETHING
BIG WENT DOWN.
SARAH, WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU
GOT BACK THE CAMP?
>> YEAH, WE GET BACK, AND IT'S
COMPLETE SILENCE.
I SAID, IS ANYONE WONDERING WHO
FLIPPED, AND, YEAH, I AM, I AM,
I AM, AND I OWNED UP TO IT.
>> Jeff: BRAD, IN THAT MOMENT
WHEN IT'S ALL BECOMING CLEAR,
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING AS A
PLAYER?
>> WELL, SIERRA, MYSELF, TROY
AND TAI WENT FROM FEELING PRETTY
GOOD ABOUT THE NUMBERS TO BEING
ON THE OUTS.
LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: TAI, SO YOU FEEL IT'S
YOU, TROYZAN, SIERRA AND
CULPEPPER WHO ARE NOW ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> OH, DEFINITELY, I FEEL I'M ON
THE BOTTOM.
THE OTHER SIX HAVE THE POWER.
NOBODY TELL ME ANYTHING, SO THIS
IS THE FIRST TIME AFTER TWO
SEASONS I'M PLAYING I FEEL LIKE
I MIGHT BE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, WHY DID YOU
REACT TO THAT?
>> I'M WITH TAI.
I'M ON THE BOTTOM FOUR.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE CONNECTIONS
WITH THESE PEOPLE, BUT REALLY
IT'S LIKE PLAYING RUSSIAN
ROULETTE, AND WHEN THE GUN IS
POINTED AT ME, I HOPE THERE'S NO
BULLET IN THAT CHAMBER.
>> Jeff: ZEKE, DOES THAT RING
TRUE, THERE ARE SIX PEOPLE AND
THEY'RE PLAYING A GAME OF CAT
AND MOUSE WITH THE OTHER FOUR?
>> DEFINITELY.
IT'S A MIRROR IMAGE OF WHAT
HAPPENED AT THE LAST VOTE.
IF YOU HAVE A GROUP AND YOU
TRUST THEM AND YOU WANT TO
PROTECT THE VOTE, THE BEST
OPTION IS TO KEEP IT TO
YOURSELF.
>> Jeff: ANDREA, CAN YOU
COMPARE WHAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW TO ANY OTHER SEASON YOU'VE
SEEN OR BEEN PART OF?
>> OH, GOSH, NO.
I'M JUST USED TO, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A MAJORITY ALIGNS AND
YOU PICK OFF PEOPLE AND MAYBE
THERE'S FLIPPERS, BUT HERE IT
JUST FEELS LIKE TRYING OUT
DIFFERENT MAJORITY ALLIANCES AND
SEEING WHICH ONE WILL FIT.
SO TONIGHT I'M ASSUMING THE NEW
SIX WILL STICK TOGETHER, BUT YOU
JUST NEVER KNOW.
>> Jeff: SO MICHAELA, IF YOU
COULD FORECAST THE FUTURE, WHAT
DO YOU THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT?
>> I SEE OUR SIX STICKING
TOGETHER TO A POINT WHERE WE
HAVE SOLID NUMBERS.
SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO MAKE THE
SIMPLE MOVE JUST TO PROGRESS
EVERYONE FURTHER IN THE GAME.
>> DREW: ZEKE, MICHAELA LAID IT
OUT PRETTY CLEAR.
SIX VERSUS FOUR IS NOT A BIG
ENOUGH ADVANTAGE.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
>> I DO HAPPEN TO AGREE WITH
THAT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THIS GAME IS
ABOUT TIMING.
SO IF YOU ARE GOING TO MAKE A
MOVE, IT HAS TO BE AT THE RIGHT
TIME.
NOW IS CERTAINLY NOT THE RIGHT
>> DREW: CIRIE, WHEN YOU HEAR
MICHAELA AND ZEKE BOTH TALKING
ABOUT NUMBERS AND TIMING, IS
THERE A GRID AT THE FRONT OF
YOUR BRAIN THAT'S GOING, OKAY,
HERE'S OPTION A, HERE'S B,
HERE'S C, I THINK IT'S TIME FOR
D TONIGHT.
>> I THINK THERE IS A BUILT-IN
GRID.
YOU'RE RUNNING NUMBERS, RUBBING
SITUATION, TRYING TO FIGURE OUT,
IS IT TIME, IS IT NOT TIME?
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE TALKING TO US
AND ASKING QUESTIONS, THE GRID
IS STILL MOVING RIGHT NOW.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, YOU'VE BEEN
ON BOTH SIDES.
YOU WERE THE SIX.
NOW YOU APPEAR TO BE THE FOUR.
WHAT DO YOU TRY TO DO TO MAKE
SURE IT'S NOT YOU?
>> JEFF, I TRIED TO PLEAD MY
CASE.
I MEAN, I AM A VOTE, AND YOU MAY
NEED ME IN THE FUTURE.
MY HANDS ARE TIE.
I'LL GO WHERE YOU WANT TO GO.
>> Jeff: SARAH, IS THERE
SOMETHING SOMEONE COULD SAY THAT
WOULD MAKE YOU GO, GOOD POINT,
I'M GOING TO KEEP YOU AROUND?
>> I MEAN, THEY BRING UP GOOD
POINTS, BUT THEY'RE TRYING TO
SELL THEMSELVES.
NOBODY'S GOING TO MAKE A BAD
PITCH FOR THEMSELVES AND SAY,
YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M PROBABLY THE
WORST ONE SO PICK ME.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA, DO YOU GET
SWAYED BY WHAT PEOPLE SAY AT
ALL?
>> I LISTEN TO WHAT PEOPLE SAY,
AND I'VE LEARNED THAT LIKE THESE
CAN BE FRIENDS OUTSIDE OF THE
GAME, LIKE AFTER DAY 39, BUT IF
YOU'RE HERE PLAYING AND STARVING
JUST LINE EVERYBODY ELSE,
SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO TURN THE
HEART DOWN SO THAT I CAN MAKE
SURE I GET TO THE NEXT DAY AND
MAKE THE MOST OF THIS EXPERIENCE
FOR ME.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, TO GET TO THE
END, OTHER PEOPLE HAVE TO GO,
NOT ME.
>> Jeff: AND ANDREA, THE FLIP
SIDE OF TURNING THE HEART OFF IS
LEAVING THE HEART ON, BECAUSE
SOMETIMES THAT RELATIONSHIP THAT
YOU STAY TRUE TO EMOTIONALLY IS
THE ONE THAT GETS YOU TO THE
END.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU DO HAVE TO HAVE GENUINE
FRIENDSHIPS AND RELATIONSHIPS
OUT HERE, BECAUSE IF YOU JUST
TURN YOUR HEART OFF AND YOU'RE
JUST TREATING EVERYONE LIKE
HUMAN CHESS PIECES, THEN I FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET TO
THE END.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
AUBRY, YOU'RE UP.
>> I LOVE YOU, BUT I HOPE IT'S
YOU AND NOT ME TONIGHT.
>> SO LONG, COWGIRL.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE TAI.
SIERRA.
TAI.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES TAI, TWO
VOTES SIERRA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES TAI.
ZEKE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ZEKE.
WE'RE TIED, THREE VOTES ZEKE,
THREE VOTES TAI, TWO VOTES
SIERRA.
ZEKE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES ZEKE.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ZEKE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ZEKE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> KEEP PLAYING HARD, GANG.
>> BYE, ZEKE.
>> Jeff: WELL, ONCE AGAIN
TRIBAL COUNCIL WITH A LOT OF
SHOCKED FACES AND A LOT OF
EMOTION, AND IT MOVES AN
UNDENIABLE TRUTH OF THIS GAME:
JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVE THE
NUMBERS DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE
TRUST.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," A WILLINGNESS TO
TRUST --
>> I FOUND THE ADVANTAGE.
>> THE DOOR IS OPENING FOR HER
TO STAY.
>> Jeff: CAN FORM AN
UNBREAKABLE ALLIANCE.
>> I SEE A HUGE OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: BUT NO BOND IS
STRONGER THAN BLOOD.
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR YOUR LOVED
ONES.
>> IT WAS SMART FROM ANDREA TO
COME AFTER ME, BECAUSE I WAS
JUST ABOUT TO COME AFTER ANDREA.
IT WAS A GREAT MOVE WORTHY OF
THE TITLE "GAME CHANGERS."
I HAVE SUPPRESSED SO MANY FEARS
AND PROVED BEYOND BOUNDARY, IT
WAS A TREMENDOUSLY SIGNIFICANT
PERSON.
I WILL FOREVER BE A BETTER
PERSON BECAUSE I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR."