>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR"... GO!
20 OF THE BIGGEST GAME CHANGE
CENTERS "SURVIVOR" HISTORY WERE
BATTLING IT OUT.
THE MANA TRIBE WAS ON A LOSING
STREAK.
NUKU WINS THEIR SECOND CHALLENGE
IN A ROW.
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL, IT WAS A
BATTLE BETWEEN "SURVIVOR"
ROYALTY.
AND ONLY ONE COULD KEEP THEIR
CROWN.
>> YOU KNOW THAT SAYING, "YOU'RE
ONLY THE KING UNTIL THE QUEEN
ARRIVES?
I'M HERE.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NOBILITY TOOK A BACK SEAT.
>> TO TONY EVERYTHING IS
PARANOIA.
>> Jeff: AS SANDRA SLAYED HER
NEMESIS AND KEPT HER TITLE.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR
PLOTTING AGAINST ME.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET, AND THE
QUEEN STAYS QUEEN.
>> Jeff: TONY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: CAN SANDRA KEEP HER
EMPIRE INTACT?
18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
COME ON IN, GUYS.
NUKU GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW MANA TRIBE.
TONY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> WOW.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE HOW SAVVY YOU GUYS ARE
AS A GROUP.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> WE'RE ABOUT TO SWAP.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE RIGHT.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> WOW.
>> BYE, BABY.
>> I WAS LEADING THE SHEEP TO
SLAUGHTER, SO I AM IN A GOOD
SPOT WITH MANBACK BUT NOW
THERE'S A SWAP, AND I HOPE I'M
ON THE RIGHT SIDE WITH THE
STRONGEST PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: SHALL WE GET TO IT?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
>> OH, MY GOSH, MY HEART IS
POUNDING.
>> MINE IS, TOO.
I'M GOING TO HAVE A HEART
ATTACK.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA DOESN'T EVEN
WANT TO LOOK.
HALI.
SIERRA, CIRIE, J.T. CLOSES HIS
EYES.
NOBODY IS LOOKING.
ZEKE.
>> THE GODS CHOSE FOR ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
YOUR NEW TRIBES.
HOLD 'EM UP ONCE YOU GET IT, PUT
'EM ON.
>> OH, BOY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I'M GREEN?
>> Jeff: FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DREW A GREEN BUFF, YOU ARE NOW
REALIZING WE ARE CHANGING FROM
TWO TRIBES TO THREE TRIBES.
>> YOU'RE STARTING OVER.
>> Jeff: IF YOU ARE GREEN,
TAKE A SPOT IN THE MIDDLE.
YOU ARE ON A BRAND-NEW TRIBE.
>> WELCOME.
>> Jeff: JUST LIKE THAT,
EVERYTHING IS A MIX.
>> I'M MICHAELA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S LOOK AT OUR NEW TRIBES.
MANA, CALEB, IMMEDIATELY YOU AND
HALI ARE A LITTLE BIT ON THE
WRONG SIDE OF THE NUMBERS AS THE
ONLY TWO FROM MANA.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TAI, WHAT'S IT LIKE
TO BE REUNITED WITH CALEB?
THE LAST TIME YOU WERE WITH
CALEB WAS AS HE GOT ON A
HELICOPTER AND WAS BEING
EVACUATED FIGHTING FOR HIS LIFE.
>> IT'S WONDERFUL TO SEE HIM ALL
GOOD.
I'M STILL LOOKING FOR THAT KISS.
>> DO IT, DO IT!
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> THERE.
NOW I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S LOOK AT THE NEW NUKU
TRIBE.
J.T., YOU'RE THE ONLY GUY FROM
YOUR OLD TRIBE.
YOU'RE WITH FIVE PEOPLE FROM
MANA.
HISTORICALLY IN "SURVIVOR," THAT
WOULD PUT YOU ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE NUMBERS.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS A BAD SIDE OF
THINGS, BUT IT ALWAYS ENDS UP
GOOD.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: AND NOW LET'S GO TO
THE BRAND-NEW TRIBE.
GREEN, YOUR NAME IS TAVUA.
TROYZAN, MUCH LIKE J.T., YOU'RE
THE ONLY GUY FROM YOUR FORMER
TRIBE MIXED WITH FIVE FROM NUKU.
IS THIS A BAD THING, OR IS IT
UNKNOWN?
>> AT FIRST IT'S BAD BECAUSE
IT'S FIVE AND ONE, BUT I HAVE
THE LOOK FOR THE SILVER LINING
SOMEWHERE.
>> Jeff: HERE'S A MAP, TAVUA,
TO YOUR HOME, AND A FLINT TO GET
YOU STARTED.
TO BE CLEAR, YOU'RE GOING BACK
TO A NEW CAMP.
YOU'LL HAVE THE SAME ORIGINAL
SUPPLIES THAT YOU STARTED THE
GAME WITH.
BASIC FISHING GEAR, A POT,
MACHETE, AND A TINY PORTION OF
RICE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO BUILD A NEW
SHELTER.
YOU ARE STARTING OVER.
BUT THE ADVANTAGE THAT ALL OF
YOU HAVE IS HAVING PLAYED
BEFORE, YOU KNOW THAT AT THIS
MOMENT ANYTHING IS STILL
POSSIBLE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD LUCK.
>> WITH GAME CHANGERS, THE GAME
CHANGES FAST, BUT WHATEVER I'M
DEALT WITH, I'M GOING TO MAKE
THE BEST OF IT.
IT'S AN EXCITING TIME I THINK.
I LOVE IT.
I'M READY TO GO.
>> THE CHICKENS ARE LOOSE.
THEY DON'T FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
RUNNING AWAY.
THEY CAN CLEAN UP AROUND CAMP.
THEY'RE PRETTY TRAINED.
>> THEY'RE TRAINED CHICKENS?
>> YOU WALK INTO THE NUKU CAMP
AFTER SPENDING SIX, SEVEN DAYS
AT MANA WHERE WE DIDN'T GET THE
CHICKENS AND TOOLKIT, IT'S
SHOCKING.
I COULDN'T PICK MY JAW UP OFF
THE FLOOR.
LOOK AT ALL OF THIS.
HOW DOES THIS HAPPEN?
>> THE BALL.
>> THE TREES HAVE BALLS.
>> THEY DECORATED THE DAMN
TREES.
IT'S THE "SURVIVOR" JACKPOT.
IT'S LIKE GOING TO A RESORT.
EVERYTHING IS ALREADY BUILT.
THEY HAVE A BUNCH OF FOOD THEY
DIDN'T TAKE WITH THEM.
THE CHICKENS ARE WALKING AROUND
FREE LIKE THEY OWN THE PLACE.
THEY HAVE AN AWESOME SHELTER AND
THEY DECORATED.
THAT'S HOW WELL IT'S GOING ON IN
THIS TRIBE.
THEY'VE TAKEN THE TIME TO HANG
DAMN ORNAMENTS IN THE TREES LIKE
WE'RE AT SOME DINNER PARLOR IN
MEXICO.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE'VE RUN A
REWARD.
I'M SPEECHLESS.
I THINK I'VE SAID THREE WORDS
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
I'M KIND OF HAPPY ABOUT THIS
SWAP.
I DIDN'T EXPECT I'D BE SWAPPED
OUT 5 TO 1, BUT I'LL TAKE IT.
I FEEL LIKE THE "SURVIVOR" GODS
REALLY LET ME DOWN.
5 TO 1 IS ABOUT AS BAD AS I CAN
HOPE FOR.
IN ALL LIKELIHOOD I'M A SITTING
DUCK.
THE ONLY THING AT THIS POINT
THAT CAN SAVE ME WOULD BE A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO
STIR THINGS UP HERE.
I GOT TO TAKE YOU ALL OUT
SNORKELING?
>> YEAH.
>> IN THE BACK OF MY MIND, IF I
CAN GET THEM OUT THERE IN THE
OCEAN, I CAN GET BACK THE CAMP
AND START LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
>> GEEZ, LOUISE, THIS IS
GORGEOUS.
>> THERE MUST BE SOME FISHING
GOING ON OVER HERE.
>> WOW.
BEAUTIFUL.
I GET EVERYONE ON THE RAFT, I
DRAG THEM OUT TO SEA A GOOD HALF
MILE.
WE SNORKEL A LITTLE BIT.
GET 'EM STARTED FISHING.
AND FINALLY THAT OPPORTUNITY
PRESENTS ITSELF WHEN MALCOLM
BENDS THE SPEAR.
>> THAT'S LIKE ONE HIT ON THE
CORAL.
>> YEAH.
>> DID YOU LOSE ANOTHER ONE OR
JUST ONE?
>> NO, JUST THE ONE FELL OFF,
LIKE CLEAN OFF.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WE REALLY NEED,
WE REALLY NEED THE PLIERS.
>> I FEEL BAD.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> I'LL GO BACK AND GET THE
PLIERS.
YOU ALL JUST ENJOY THIS GOOD
TIME OUT HERE ON THE OCEAN.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ISN'T THIS WEIRD J.T. IS IN
THE HERE?
WE KIND OF RAIDED THEIR CAMP AND
HIJACKED IT FOR THE DAY.
>> I CAME TO GET THE PLIERS.
I NOVI TO BE BACK SOON.
I HAVE TO TAKE EVERY SECOND I
CAN TO LOOK.
I'M LOOKING IN EVERY NOOK, EVERY
TREE, EVERY CORNER, EVERY SPOT,
EVERY HOLE IN A TREE, UP IN THE
TREES.
>> WHAT DOES HE THINK HE'S
DOING?
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BUDDY?
>> HE MIGHT KNOW WHERE THE IDOL
IS.
>> HE MIGHT KNOW.
HE HIGH KNOW SOMETHING.
>> HE MIGHT BE UP THERE SAVING
HIS ASS.
>> WE SAT OUT THERE ON THAT
RAFT.
HE DOESN'T TAKE THAT LONG.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
I'M THINKING, HE'S LOOKING FOR
AN IDOL.
WHAT A GREAT WAY TO GET RID OF
THE FIVE PEOPLE THAT MIGHT TAKE
YOU DOWN.
BRILLIANT.
>> PRETTY MUCH.
>> NOPE.
IDOLLESS.
I'M JUST FRANTICALLY LOOKING
EVERYWHERE.
NOPE.
IT'S NEVER OVER UNTIL IT'S OVER.
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
AND THEY PROBABLY KNOW I'M
LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
I TOOK THEM AS FAR OUT IN THE
OCEAN AS I COULD, AND I LEFT THE
PLIERS ON PURPOSE.
MY JOB IS TO KEEP LOOKING.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
>> HE TOTALLY LEFT US OUT HERE.
HE LEFT US.
THAT'S LITERALLY WHAT HAPPENED.
>> HE'S DANGEROUS.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT HE'S DOING.
IF J.T.'S OUT LOOKING FOR AN
IDOL.
GOOD FOR J.T.
IT JUST DOESN'T MATTER.
WE HAVE THE MAJORITY, 5-1, SO
J.T. IS SCREWED.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE'RE GOING THE MAKE THIS HOUSE
A HOME.
>> OH, HE'S AN INTERIOR
DESIGNER.
>> THIS IS MY NEW HOME, SO I
START THINKING, LET ME MAKE THIS
HOUSE A HOME.
I LOVE ANTIQUING AND I LIKE TO
DECORATE.
MONICA AND I SPEND A LOT OF...
WE DECORATE OUR OWN HOUSE.
WE'LL MAKE THIS A HOME NOW.
>> YEAH, BRAD.
>> I RELAX AS I'M DOING THAT.
IT GIVES ME SOMETHING TO THINK
ABOUT.
>> AWESOME.
AWESOME, BRAD.
>> WE'RE HERE, MEAGER SUPPLIES,
MEAGER FOOD, IN AN UNBELIEVABLE
GAME, DIFFICULT, BUT I'M HAVING
A LOT OF FUN BECAUSE IT'S 4-2,
AND I'M THINKING, I'M IN GOOD
SHAPE.
THE FOUR OF US IN NUKU ARE GOING
THE STAY TOGETHER.
IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN TO HALI
OR CALEB.
>> HALI, I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER
BEING AROUND THESE PEOPLE.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> I REALLY DO.
>> REALLY?
GOOD.
>> I LIKE YOU ALL A LOT.
>> WE HAVE TO PLAY IT LIKE WE'RE
ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
CALEB AND I ARE AT THE BOTTOM
NUMBERS-WISE.
>> IT'S SO DIFFERENT THE SECOND
TIME.
WE'RE NOT NAIVE.
>> CALEB AND TAI COULD GET BACK
TOGETHER AND PUT A BIG TARGET ON
THEIR BACK.
SO ALL OF A SUDDEN I'M MAYBE NOT
THE MOST OBVIOUS TARGET.
>> I FEEL GOOD WITH YOU HERE.
THE TRIBE IS REALLY STRONG.
>> WE SHOULD KEEP CALEB BECAUSE
HE'S GOING TO HELP WITH
CHALLENGES.
SERIOUSLY, I WOULD CHANGE DEBBIE
FOR CALEB.
>> SHE SEEMS TO BE LOYAL.
>> YOU THINK SO IN.
>> I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT OVER
CALEB.
I'M TALKING ABOUT CALEB.
I MEAN, CALEB AFTER DEBBIE.
>> IT'S UP TO US.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOOD.
WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
>> TRUTHFULLY, I WOULDN'T MIND
GETTING RID OF CALEB FIRST.
>> WHAT?
STOP IT.
>> CALEB, DEBBIE AND TAI PLAYED
TOGETHER ON "SURVIVOR."
I'M TRYING TO BRING TAI AND
DEBBIE CLOSER TO ME THAN ANYBODY
ELSE.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
WE GOOD?
>> HUH?
GOOD?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> WAIT, WAIT.
I JUST TALKED TO BRAD.
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO SIERRA YET.
I SAY I'D RATHER YOU WITH US
BECAUSE YOU WOULD BE A LOT
STRONGER TO HELP WITH
CHALLENGES.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> TAI ANDRY BACK TOGETHER
AGAIN.
IT'S A GREAT FEELING BECAUSE WE
JUST HAVE REALLY GOOD, CLOSE
FRIENDSHIP.
I HOPE WE CAN CONTINUE WHAT WE
HAD BEFORE.
>> DO YOU WORK WITH ANY OTHER
PEOPLE ON OUR OTHER TRIBE?
>> JEFF AND MALCOLM.
NO ONE ELSE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S HAVE THAT AS AN OPTION.
THE PLAN IS TO VOTE OFF HALI AND
CALEB.
I KNOW I CROSSED THE LINE, BUT I
THIS WANT THE PLAY WITH CALEB.
WE HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH
BEFORE.
WE HAVE A PRETTY BIG
RELATIONSHIP.
BUT THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT
HAPPENED LAST TIME.
I'M PUT IN A POSITION TO BETRAY
MY FRIENDS, BUT I PROTECT MY
BUDDY, I HAVE TO BETRAY BRAD.
SO I'M WEIGHING THE RISKS.
EITHER WAY IT'S GOING TO HURT.
>> ALLIGHT.
OUR NEW HOME.
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> WELCOME.
>> OH, THANK YOU, GUYS.
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF NICE
BECAUSE I'VE GOT A BUNCH OF... I
HAVE A CHAOTIC TRIBE.
WE GET UP TO CAMP AND THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FISHING GEAR AND A
MEAGER AMOUNT OF RICE, A POT AND
A MACHETE.
YOU KNOW IT'S CONGENIAL.
WE'RE TRYING TO BE NICE TO
TROYZAN.
I'M SURE HE FEELS LIKE HE'S ON
THE OUTS BECAUSE FOR ALL INTENTS
AND PURPOSES HE IS.
>> WE MIGHT HAVE A SLIGHTLY
WORSE CAMP THAN OUR OLD CAMP.
WE HAVE MORE COCONUTS.
WE HAVE MORE PALM FRONDS FOR
SHELTER.
SO THAT'S NICE.
>> WE GOT TO START FROM THE
BEGINNING, AND I'VE GOT TO TAKE
THE LEAD BECAUSE I GOT LIKE 115
DAYS ON "SURVIVOR" MORE OR LESS.
THIS IS A POST.
I AM ONE OF THE VETERANS IN THIS
GAME.
I HAVE PLAYED THIS FOUR TIMES
NOW.
AND THIS IS A CHANCE TO LET MY
TRIBE KNOW THAT I STILL GOT THE
SKILLS AND THAT THEY CAN'T GET
RID OF ME YET.
>> WE'RE SAFE, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE'RE GOOD?
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> I WASN'T ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF
THE NUMBERS IN THE OLD NUKU
TRIBE, AND I THINK OZZY IS STILL
A LITTLE SKITTISH OF ME, BUT I'M
TRYING TO CULTIVATE A
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM, SO I NEED
THE TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS NEW
START.
I'M HOPING THAT WILL HELP ME
LATER ON DOWN THE LINE.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> I FEEL GOOD.
WE GOT NUMBERS.
>> HELL, YEAH.
>> I FEEL GREAT.
>> ON THE ORIGINAL NUKU TRIBE, I
DIDN'T HAVE A STRONG ALLIANCE
WITH CIRIE, BUT HERE WE NEED
EACH OTHER, SO THIS IS A CRUCIAL
TIME FOR ME TO BUILD TRUST.
IF WE DO, TROYZAN CAN BE AN EASY
FIRST ONE TO GO.
>> TO ANDREA, I HAVE THE FLAG?
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> I DON'T?
>> TROYZAN IS A SUPER COOL GUY,
BUT IT'S "SURVIVOR" AND IT'S A
NUMBERS GAME.
SO WE HAVE TO MAKE HIM FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ALL THE
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> RIGHT.
>> SOMEONE MIGHT HAVE OTHER
IDEAS.
>> I JUST WANT THE SAY AT LEAST
HELLO.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW, OF COURSE.
>> ANDREA, COME ON, SHE ACTS
LIKE SHE'S MY BUDDY, BUT SHE'S A
LITTLE DEVIL THAT ONE.
SHE JUST... I KNOW SHE'S PLAYING
A GAME.
SHE'S NOT AS CLEVER I THINK AS
SHE THINKS SHE IS.
>> I'M GOING TO PROBABLY TAKE
THIS UP BECAUSE I'M BURNING.
>> OKAY.
I'M GOING TO GO GET WATER.
>> COME ON.
I'M 54 YEARS OLD.
I'M THE OLDEST GUY OUT HERE.
BUT MY INTUITION IS GOOD.
AND I FEEL LIKE I LEARNED SO
MUCH FROM ONE WORLD.
I FOUND AN IDOL THEN WHEN I HAD
TO FIND ONE.
I WON IMMUNITY WHEN I HAD TO AND
CHANGED THE GAME.
SO THIS TIME I WILL NOT LET ANY
STONE BE UNTURNED.
I'M GOING TO START TO AT LEAST
LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
>> WE REALLY DO HAVE TO WATCH
HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE WE DON'T WANT HIM
GETTING AN IDOL.
>> NO.
>> HE'S SMART ENOUGH TO KNOW
THAT WE'RE ALL WATCHING HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO GO FOR A
LONG TIME.
>> WOW.
I THOUGHT I LOST MY LIFE FOR A
SECOND THERE.
THANK GOD.
OKAY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND A CLUE TO A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, BUT IT
WILL REQUIRE YOU TO BE DARING.
I'M THAT.
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO BE A PUZZLE
SOLVER IN ORDER TO NAB IT.
THANK YOU.
YOUR NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, IF
YOU ARE BOLD ENOUGH TO RISK
MAKING A GAME-CHANGING MOVE IN
FRONT OF YOUR UNSUSPECTING TRIBE
MATES AND IMMONTI IS YOURS AND
IT WILL BE -- AT THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, IT'S GOING
TO BE CRAZY.
IT'S GOING TO BE HUGELY
DIFFICULT BECAUSE I HAVE TWO
THINGS TO THINK ABOUT, WINNING A
SUPER TOUGH GAME-CHANGING
CHALLENGE, PLUS I ALSO HAVE TO
FIND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IN
FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
I HAVE TO FIGURE IT OUT.
BUT IF I CAN DO IT, IT'S A
COMPLETE 180.
TROYZAN'S BACK.
I THINK.
>> THERE ARE GOATS EVERYWHERE
HERE.
I CAN GET PROBABLY 20 YARDS FROM
THEM.
>> WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO GET
ONE?
>> IF YOU'RE HUNGRY ENOUGH WE
CAN.
I TOLD THEM WE COULDN'T CATCH
IT, BUT WE CAN.
SANDRA SAID SHE'D LOVE A GOAT.
I COULD PROBABLY CATCH ONE FOR
YOU.
>> AND THERE GOES ONE OF THE
GOATS RIGHT THERE, A GRAY AND
WHITE ONE.
THAT'S OUR MEAL RIGHT THERE.
OH, THEY'RE LIKE RIGHT THERE.
>> THERE'S AT LEAST SIX.
I'VE SEEN SIX.
>> I DON'T REALLY WANT THE CATCH
AND EAT A GOAT, BUT FIRST THING
I NEED TO DO IS KEEP MYSELF
SAFE.
IF I CAN FEED SANDRA AND MAKE
HER HAPPY, I THINK SANDRA WILL
PROBABLY LOVE ME TO DEATH, AND
THAT WILL PROBABLY KEEP ME SAFER
IN THIS GAME.
>> THERE THEY ARE RIGHT THERE.
SEE THAT BLACK AND WHITE ONE.
>> HE'S COMING, MALCOLM.
>> MALCOLM!
WE CAN CATCH 'EM BY HAND.
>> HOW?
>> IS HE CHASING A GOAT?
>> I GOT IT.
>> OKAY.
GIVE ME THAT.
[GOAT CRYING]
>> BE CAREFUL WITH THE HORNS.
>> I'LL GET ROPE.
MALCOLM, STAY WITH HIM.
GRAB THEM BACK LEGS OR
SOMETHING.
>> YOU GOT IT?
>> CATCHING A GOAT WAS NEVER ON
MY BUCKET LIST.
WE PICK IT UP AND START HEADING
BACK THE CAMP AND REALIZE THE
ONLY REASON WE CAUGHT IT WAS
BECAUSE IT WAS MAMA GET AND IT
DIDN'T WANT THE RUN AWAY FROM
ITS BABIES, SO WE DON'T HAVE A
CHOICE WE WON'T KILL HIM BECAUSE
WE HAVE A CONSCIENCE.
WE HAVE TO EAT, BUT I HAVE TO BE
VERY CAREFUL WHAT I SAY TO
SANDRA.
SHE DESPERATELY WANTS TO EAT THE
GOAT.
THERE IS NO NEED THE MAKE
ENEMIES OR CAUSED ANGST IN THIS
CAMP.
>> DON'T GET TOO ATTACHED
BECAUSE THIS IS GOING TO BE OUR
MEAL.
>> THE BABY?
>> SANDRA DON'T CARE ABOUT
KILLING THESE GOATS.
IN HER MIND IT'S JUST FOOD.
SHE WAS A VILLAIN FOR A REASON.
>> I WAS SO... IT'S A MOMMY
GOAT?
>> SO SAD.
>> I DON'T SEE ANYTHING WRONG
WITH KILLING AND EATING A GOAT.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE HERE, FOR
FOR HUMAN CONSUMPTION.
>> SHE'S NOT GOING NOWHERE WITH
THAT MAMA.
WE'RE GOING TO LET HER GO.
>> YOU MEAN LET THE BABY GO.
>> SHE'LL STAY WITH THE MAMA NO
MATTER WHAT.
>> EVERYONE WANTS THE ADD THEIR
TWO CREPTS IN.
I GOT TO GET EVERYBODY TO DO IT
AS A GROUP BECAUSE THAT'S THE
PLAN TO, CATCH IT, TO CATCH
SOMETHING AND KILL IT.
>> I CAN'T HARDLY EAT EITHER ONE
OF THEM.
>> WHAT YOU MEAN?
>> A BABY AND A MAMA.
>> IT IS THE GOAT VERSION OF
BAMBI RIGHT NOW.
>> I DIDN'T EXPECT THE CATCH A
GATE THIS QUICK.
THERE'S IN WAY I'M GOING TO KILL
THAT MAMA GOAT AND HER BABY.
I CAN'T DO IT.
>> IF I CAN CATCH ONE THAT DON'T
HAVE A BABY.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE IF WE CAN
CATCH A MALE AND LET THESE TWO
GOAT.
>> LET'S TAKE A VOTE.
>> SANDRA WANTS TO EAT A GOAT.
SHE'S RUNNING THE SHOW, BUT, YOU
KNOW, I'D RATHER LET THESE GOAT
GOSS.
SEE IF WE CAN CATCH ANOTHER
RANDOM GOAT THAT'S NOT A MAMA OR
A BABY.
I'M GOING TO TRY MY BEST TO SAVE
THE GOAT.
>> YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> I'M HUNGRY.
BUT I CAN'T.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE ANY
PART OF IT?
>> THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO KILL IT,
BUT I'LL HELP YOU CLEAN IT,
CLEAN THE CARCASS.
>> YOU CAN TELL WHO IS FOR IT
AND WHO IS AGAINST IT
IMMEDIATELY.
SANDRA DOESN'T GIVE A DAMN,
WHICH IS JUST SANDRA'S M.O.
ABOUT LIFE I'VE STARTED TO
REALIZE.
BUT EVERYBODY ELSE STARTS
TALKING IT THROUGH AND NO ONE
WANTS TO BE THE "SURVIVOR" THAT
ABANDONED A BABY GOAT MOTHERLESS
TO THE WILD.
>> MY HEART WANTS TO LET THEM
GO.
>> MINE, TOO.
I FELT BAD THE MOMENT I PUT IT
IN MY HANDS.
>> RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE FOUR
CHICKENS.
WE GOT CHICKENS RIGHT THERE, AND
THOSE ARE MEANT TO EAT, YOU
KNOW?
AND SO I DON'T SEE HOW IT MAKES
SENSE.
>> THERE'S ALL THIS MEAT AROUND.
WE'RE NOT EATING ANY OF IT.
IT'S CRAZY.
>> AMEN TO THAT.
>> SO YOU'RE ALL DOWN WITH
EATING A CHICKEN?
>> J.T., WE'RE EATING A CHICKEN.
>> THIS IS AN EASY DECISION
BECAUSE WE HAVE A HEART.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO KILL EITHER
OF THE GOATS.
SO WE ENDED UP LETTING THE GOATS
GO.
>> GO AHEAD, UNTIE HER AND LET
HER GO WITH HER BABY.
BYE, MAMA.
>> THAT INITIAL SURGE OF
ADRENALINE AND YOU MOUTHWATERING
SLOWS DOWN A LOT WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT ABANDONING A LITTLE BABY
GOAT.
SO IT MADE SENSE, LIKE IN OUR
HEARTS TO LET IT GO.
>> THEY'RE CALLING FOR EACH
OTHER.
THAT'S SWEET.
>> AND IT'S GOING TO BE MUCH
BETTER FOR THIS TRIBE MOVING
FORWARD.
>> THERE THEY GO.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AS A
NEW TRIBE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
J.T., I'LL TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
THANK YOU.
>> BY ALL MEANS.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, THREE
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL BE
TIED TOGETHER.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL WORK TOGETHER
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL THEN GRAB A BUCKET, FILL
IT WITH WATER, MAKE YOU WAY OVER
A GIANT TEETER TO TOTTER,
TRANSFERRING THE WATER UNTIL YOU
HAVE ENOUGH TO LOWER THE GATE.
THE THREE REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL THEN WORK TOGETHER
TO SOLVE A PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS GO THE TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, PLAYING FOR REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH, MAYBE THE MOST VALUABLE
THING IN THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH GETS THEIR CHOICE OF
COMFORT IN THE FORM OF...
>> OH.
>> Jeff: COMFORT FOR YOUR
BODY, OR COMFORT FOR YOUR TASTE
BUDS.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH GETS WHATEVER ONE IS
LEFTOVER.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
LET'S DO IT!
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
WE'VE GOT THREE PEOPLE AT THE
START ON THE OBSTACLES, THREE
PEOPLE AT THE END UNTYING KNOTS,
SOLVING THE PUZZLE.
>> THIS IDOL BEING HIDDEN ON
THIS TABLE MAKES ME WAY NERVOUS,
BECAUSE I'M IN CHARGE OF UNTYING
KNOTS.
SO I HAVE THE WAIT UNTIL AFTER
THE CHALLENGE ENDS IN ORDER TO
NAB IT.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO, FOR
REWARD AND IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
FIRST PHASE IS GETTING THROUGH
THIS WOOD BRAMBLE.
NUKU GOING UP TOP.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> Jeff: TAVUA GOING UP TOP.
MANA GOING DOWN BELOW.
AND RUNNING INTO TROUBLE EARLY.
CALEB, TAI, AND DEBBIE REALLY
STRUGGLING TO GET THROUGH THIS.
NUKU IS THROUGH.
OVER AND UNDER.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: GO, TAVUA.
TAVUA FLYING OVER IT.
NUKU IS NOT MESSING AROUND,
LAUNCHING THEMSELVES.
YOUR NEXT JOB IS TO UNTIE THAT
BUCKET AND START TRANSFERRING
WATER.
>> COME ON, DEBBIE.
>> I'M COMING.
>> Jeff: MANA NOW GETTING
THROUGH, BUT THEY'VE LOST TIME.
>> TOGETHER, GUYS, TOGETHER.
>> Jeff: SARAH SLOWING DOWN
NOW.
MANA'S GOT THE CATCH UP NOW.
>> HURRY, HURRY!
>> Jeff: NUKU HAS THEIR
BUCKET.
THEY'VE HAD THE LEAD FROM THE
BEGINNING.
MANA FINALLY BACK.
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: NUKU OVER WITH THEIR
FIRST BUCKET.
MICHAELA TAKING FALL.
TAVUA NOW HAS THEIR BUCKET.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: YOU NEED ENOUGH WATER
TO DROP THAT GATE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: NOT ENOUGH FOR NUKU.
TAVUA NOW HEADING OVER WITH
THEIR FIRST BUCKET.
MANA HAS THEIR BUCKET.
>> BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
>> Jeff: NUKU HEADING BACK
OVER WITH THEIR SECOND BUCKET.
MANA OUT WITH THEIR FIRST
BUCKET.
WILL THIS BE ENOUGH FOR THEM?
NO.
>> NICE WORK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: COULD THIS DO IT FOR
NUKU?
>> THERE WE GO.
>> Jeff: THAT'S GOING TO DO IT
IT DROPS.
GET THROUGH IT.
START UNTYING THE PUZZLE.
>> BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES TAVUA.
WILL THEY HAVE ENOUGH WATER?
MANA COMING BACK?
>> WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT, WE GOT
IT.
>> GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: TAVUA DROPS.
MANA DROPS.
START UNTYING THE PUZZLE.
>> GO, GO.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
>> Jeff: AUBRY'S DONE.
PUZZLE SOLVERS COME IN.
IT'S NOW VARNER AND SANDRA IN
THAT LAST PHASE FOR NUKU PUTTING
THE PUZZLE TOGETHER.
SIERRA MADE UP A LOT OF TIME FOR
MANA.
GO, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB, COWGIRL.
>> Jeff: IT IS NOW HALI AND
CULPEPPER.
TROYZAN HAS BEEN THE SLOWEST
WITH THE KNOTS.
IT IS NOW ZEKE AND CIRIE
SOLVING.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLES NOW.
>> TROYZAN, WE NEED A PIECE AT
THE END.
>> FIRST TWO TO FINISH ARE SAFE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
GAME CHANGERS."
YOU KNOW WHAT THE PUZZLE IT IS.
IT IS THE LOGO FOR THE SEASON.
HOW QUICKLY CAN YOU GET IT
TOGETHER?
SIERRA MADE UP A LOT OF TIME FOR
MANA.
THEY'RE BACK IN THIS.
TAVUA LOST A LOT OF TIME.
NUKU HAS BEEN IN THE LEAD FROM
THE START.
ZEKE AND CIRIE HAVE MADE UP A
LOT OF TIME ON THIS PUZZLE.
THEY'VE TIED VARNER AND SANDRA.
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO A
VERY CLOSE FINISH.
>> I'M MISSING ONE PIECE OVER
HERE.
>> Jeff: THIS IS GOING TO COME
DOWN TO SECONDS.
>> WE GOT IT!
>> Jeff: NUKU THINKS THEY HAVE
IT.
>> NO.
NO.
>> Jeff: AND THEY DO.
REWARD FOR NUKU.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
WHO WILL FINISH FIRST?
>> JEFF?
>> Jeff: NO, THAT IS NOT
RIGHT.
>> SWITCH IT, SWITCH IT!
>> Jeff: ZEKE AND CIRIE
THOUGHT THEY HAD IT, BUT THEY
WERE WRONG.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE CLOSE.
>> Jeff: VERY CLOSE.
IT'S A RACE TO THE FINISH.
>> WE GOT IT.
>> NO, NO, IT'S NOT.
>> JEFF, JEFF, JEFF!
>> DO THEY HAVE IT NOW?
>> Jeff: YES!
IMMONTI AND -- IMMUNITY AND
REWARD FOR TAVUA.
ONE BOARD SHY FOR MANA.
SO CLOSE.
>> WOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NICE WORK.
>> TALK ABOUT A STEAKOUT.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD, OH,
MY GOD.
>> TO FIND AN IDOL AGAIN IS
LIKE, I DID IT.
AND FINDING THIS CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
IT'S LIFE FOR ME.
IT GIVES YOU THE FEELING OF
POWER.
AND POWER IS HUGE IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: NUKU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
[APPLAUSE]
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
TAVUA.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
NOW WE HAVE THE REWARD.
NUKU, YOU'VE ALREADY WON THE
TARP THAT.
IS YOURS.
NOW YOU HAVE A CHOICE, DO YOU
WANT COMFORT FOR BODY OR COMFORT
FOR TASTE BUDS.
>> BODY COMFORT.
NUKU, COME GRAB YOUR REWARD.
>> WE FINALLY WON SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: TAVUA, IN ADDITION TO
IMMUNITY, YOU GET THE REMAINING
REWARD, COME GRAB IT, SPICES FOR
THE TASTE BUDS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
MANA, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> IN THIS GAME IT'S ALL ABOUT
NUMBERS.
THIS IS A DICTATORSHIP MAJORITY
RULES.
SO WE WILL HAVE A BRIEF
NEGOTIATION, WHETHER IT IS CALEB
OR HALI, AND I BELIEVE WE'RE
ROCK SOLID STICKING TOGETHER.
>> WE LOST THE CHALLENGE, LIKE
THE UNTHINKABLE OCCURRED.
SO A MIRACLE WILL HAPPEN IF I'M
TO BE HERE TOMORROW.
>> ARE YOU OKAY WHEN YOU FELL,
CALEB?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU FELL HARD.
IT LOOKED HARD.
>> I'M FEELING LIKE TWO AGAINST
FOUR AND CALEB'S A FREAKIN'
POWERHOUSE, SO IMMEDIATELY I
KNOW I'M IN HOT WATER.
>> SOMEBODY'S GOING TO GO HOME.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE GONE OFF THREE
TIMES NOW.
I'M SORRY FOR THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> I GOT MY HEAD KIND OF DOWN
BECAUSE I JUST HATE THE LOSE,
AND TODAY'S THE NINTH DAY, WHICH
I LEFT LAST TIME.
I GOT LIFE-FLIGHTED OUT ON A
HELICOPTER AND ALMOST LOST MY
LIFE, SO THE ONLY THING ON MY
MIND NOW IS, YOU KNOW, ARE THEY
GOING TO GO STRONG WITH WITH
THIS TRIBE AND KEEP ME AND GIVE
ME ANOTHER LIFE IN THIS GAME?
>> SO WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> WE WANT THE MAKE SURE THAT
YOU'RE COMFORTABLE WITH HALI?
>> I MEAN, SHE'S REALLY NICE,
BUT, YOU KNOW, CALEB AND I,
WE'RE FRIENDS, SO CALEB OR HALI,
HALI GOT TO GO.
CALEB, HE CAN HELP.
>> HE'S STRONG.
>> THE TWO NAMES THAT ARE ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK TONIGHT ARE HALI
AND CALEB.
I REALLY HAVEN'T TALKED TO HALI
SINCE I PLAYED WITH HER BEFORE
ON WORLDS APART SOME SEEING HER
HERE, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE NO
RELATIONSHIP, BUT TAI AND CALEB,
THEY SCARE ME.
THEY'RE CLOSE.
THERE WOULD HAVE TO BE SOME
UNDERLYING ALLIANCE THERE.
I MEAN, COME ON.
YOU KNOW EACH OTHER, SO, YEAH,
THERE IS A LITTLE CONCERN.
BUT OBVIOUSLY IF YOU TARGET A
STRONG PLAYER SUCH AS CALEB,
YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING
CHALLENGES GETS SMALLER AND
SMALLER.
>> WE DEFINITELY GOING TO KEEP
THE NUKU TRIBE STRONG.
>> GOOD.
>> SO IT'S GOING TO BE HALI.
>> MY LOGIC IS THIS: I GOT CALEB
AND TAI THAT I COULD POTENTIALLY
WORK WITH, BUT TAI AND CALEB HAD
A HISTORY, AND ONE THING I'VE
LEARNED FROM PLAYING BEFORE IS
PAST RELATIONSHIPS ABSOLUTELY
MATTER, AND YOU'RE A FOOL TO
DISCOUNT THEM.
>> I'M STICKING TO THE PLAN.
>> I FEEL PRETTY GOOD ABOUT WHAT
TAI IS SAYING ABOUT CALEB.
I THINK HE'S PLAYING THE GAME
FOR US RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> MAYBE GETTING RID OF HALI
WOULD BE A BETTER CHOICE.
BUT CALEB, DEBBIE, AND TAI
ABSOLUTELY HAVE A RELATIONSHIP,
AND IF THEY WANT TO TEAM UP,
IE-MAIL SURE THEY WOULD SEND ME
HOME FIRST, BUT RIGHT NOW I
DON'T WANT TO BE THE CHEAT, SO I
WOULD LIKE TAI TO MAKE THE
DECISION.
>> SIT DOWN A SECOND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HALI'S GOING HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT IF IT CAME DOWN TO HALI
OR CALEB?
>> WE NEED CALEB FOR CHALLENGES.
>> I GUESS.
I THINK SO.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM WITH CALEB,
YOU GO INTO THE MERGE WITH CALEB
AROUND, IT'S GOING TO HURT YOUR
GAME.
>> I HEAR THAT.
>> SO YOU GOT TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOUR GAME IN
THIS SEASON.
>> I SEE THAT, YEP.
>> OKAY.
ARE YOU IN IT FOR HIM, OR ARE
YOU IN IT FOR YOU.
>> NEW YORK I'M IN IT FOR
MYSELF.
>> HE GIVE ME SUCH VALUABLE
ADVICE.
IT MAKES SENSE.
LAST TIME I PLAYED WITH MY
HEART.
BUT THIS IS GAME CHANGER.
I HAVE TO THINK CLEAR.
>> IT'S IN THE A FINAL DECISION
YET.
>> IF WE GET RID OF CALEB, IT'S
VERY DIFFICULT, BECAUSE I'M A
FRIEND OF CALEB.
WE PLAYED TOGETHER BEFORE.
WE HAD SOME GREAT TIMES, AND
IT'S VERY, VERY DIFFICULT FOR ME
TO THEN WRITE HIS NAME DOWN.
BECAUSE IT'S SUCH A BETRAYAL TO
OUR FRIENDSHIP.
CAN I DO IT?
MY HEART SAYS, HE'S MY FRIEND.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LIVE WITH
IT.
YOU'LL KEEP WE WILL LIVING THIS
MOMENT OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
TONIGHT I HAVE TO THINK WITH MY
BRAIN WHO IS A BETTER PERSON THE
TAKE OUT, HALI OR CALEB.
>> Jeff: FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DON'T HAVE A TORCH, GO AHEAD AND
GRAB ONE.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE,
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
SO DEBBIE, IS IT COMFORTING OR
UNNERVING THAT YOU, TAI, AND
CALEB ARE ALL HERE TOGETHER AND
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU GUYS PLAYED
TOGETHER?
>> IT'S UNNERVING ACTUALLY.
YOU'RE RIGHT AWAY PERCEIVED TO
BE A TRIO.
YOU MUST HAVE A COMMON BOND.
>> Jeff: TAI, DID YOU FEEL
THAT WHEN WE DID THE SWITCH?
>> DEFINITELY, AND AUTOMATICALLY
I THINK THE OTHER TRIBE MEMBER
WOULD THINK, THIS IS THREE
PERSON TO WATCH OUT FOR.
>> Jeff: AND CALEB, NOT ONLY
DID YOU PLAY TOGETHER, BUT YOU
AND TAI HAD A FRIENDSHIP.
DO YOU FEEL THAT PRESSURE, AS
WELL, THAT PEOPLE ARE MAKING
ASSUMPTIONS?
>> YOU KNOW, YEAH, BUT THE
SIMPLE FACT THAT WE DIDN'T TART
THIS GAME TOGETHER, HE HAD
ALREADY BEEN WITH A WHOLE NEW
OTHER TRIBE FOR SEVEN DAY, SO
MAYBE IT'S NOT SOMETHING TO LOOK
DEEP INTO.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, IS THAT
FAIR THAT, YEAH, THERE MIGHT BE
A LITTLE SCRUTINY, BUT AS CALEB
SAYS, I DIDN'T EVEN START WITH
THESE GUYS.
>> I THINK WE'VE CONNECTED TAI
AND CALEB, BUT WE DID BOND, THE
OLD NUKU TRIBE PRETTY WELL, SO
MAYBE WE BRECK THAT BOND.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: SIERRA, IT'S REALLY
INTERESTING, BECAUSE "SURVIVOR"
IS A GAME OF SOCIAL POLITICS.
WHEN YOU'RE ALL STRANGERS, THAT
HAS ONE MEANING, BUT THEN WHEN
YOU PLAY TOGETHER, THERE IS THIS
ADDED LAYER THAT YOU HAVE TO
DECIDE HOW MUCH WEIGHT DO I GIVE
IT.
>> I MEAN, YEAH, ALL THESE
PEOPLE ARE SAYING THEY WEREN'T
REALLY CONCERNED WITH CALEB AND
TAI, AND THAT WAS A HUGE CONCERN
OF MINE AND STILL IS.
SO I'M NOT BLINDED BY THE FACT I
KNOW THEY HAVE A FRIENDSHIP.
LIKE ME AND HALI, WE HAVE NO
RELATIONSHIP FROM OUR SEASON, SO
IT'S DIFFERENT THAN THAT CASE
RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: HALI, DO YOU FEEL,
THAT AS WELL?
>> WELL, WHEN THE TRIBES FIRST
SPLIT UP, YOU WOULD EXPECT THAT
ME AND CALEB MIGHT BE AT THE
BOTTOM NUMBERS-WISE, BUT IF YOU
LOOK CLOSER, MAYBE CALEB HAS
MORE ANGLES TO WORK IN THIS
TRIBE THAN I EVER COULD.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE OF PAST
RELATIONSHIPS?
>> EXACTLY.
>> Jeff: CALEB, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT, THAT BEING ON THE
WRONG SIDE OF THE NUMBERS AFTER
THE SWITCH, THAT IT'S YOU OR
HALEY?
>> FOR SURE, AND IT'S THEIR
DETERMINATION.
THEY EITHER WANT TO TAKE A
STRONG PLAYER THAT'S GOING TO BE
LOYAL, KICK BUTT IN CHALLENGES
AND GIVE THEM ALL THEY GOT,
WHICH IS ME, OR THEY'RE GOING TO
GO WITH HALI, WHICH PROBABLY IS
EASIER TO MANIPULATE AND
POSSIBLY A LITTLE BIT EASIER TO
TAKE ALONG.
>> Jeff: WOW.
HALI, WHAT'S IT LIKE TO HEAR YOU
REFERRED TO AS THE EASY ONE TO
GET RID OF TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE SAID.
I THINK HE PUT HIMSELF OUT THERE
AS SOMEONE WHO IS
STRONGER-HEADED THAN ME AND A
BIGGER PLAYER IN THIS GAME AND
IN A GAME OF GAME CHANGERS, IS
THAT WHO YOU WANT AROUND?
>> CULPEPPER, SHE FLIPPED IT AND
SAID EVERYTHING CALEB JUST SAID
THAT MADE HIM VALUABLE IS WHAT
MAKES HIM A THREAT.
>> SHE'S A BUDDING ATTORNEY.
SHE'S DOING REALLY WELL.
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS TO
WEIGH.
WHAT PERSON IS REALLY GOING TO
MAKE THE TRIBE STRONGER IN OUR
NEXT CHALLENGE?
THEY BOTH BRING VALUE TO THE
TABLE, PHYSICAL, MENTAL.
IT'S A DIFFICULT DECISION.
>> Jeff: TAI, THERE WERE SO
MANY ELEMENTS TO THIS GAME,
WHERE ARE YOU GIVING THE WEIGHT,
TO THE NEXT CHALLENGE, TO THE
MERGE, TO THE END?
>> I THINK I HAVE TO LOOK INTO
THE BIG PICTURE, NOT JUST THE
NEXT CHALLENGE.
I'M LOOKING AT LOYALTY, TRUST,
AND PERSONAL RELATIONSHIP, AS
WELL.
THE BIG PICTURE OF THE GAME.
>> Jeff: SO CALEB, WHEN YOU
HEAR THAT, DO YOU THINK THAT
MEANS YOU'RE STAYING?
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, AGAIN, HALI
HAS HER ASSETS ABOUT HER, I HAVE
MINE.
I PEEVE THESE PEOPLE KNOW WHAT I
BRING TO THE TABLE.
THEY KNOW THE ASSET I AM TO THE
TRIBE.
AND I DON'T REALLY HAVE
RELATIONSHIPS ON THE OTHER SIDE
LIKE SHE DOES.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
I MEAN, I THINK THAT I'M A GOOD
PERSON TO TAKE FORWARD IN THE
GAME MORE THAN A BIG, STRONG
PLAYER IN A LOT OF MULTIPLE
DIMENSIONS.
SO BASICALLY MY CLOSING ARGUMENT
IS THAT I'VE JUST BEEN MYSELF
AND I INTEND TO CONTINUE THAT
WITH THESE PEOPLE, AND HOPEFULLY
THESE RELATIONSHIPS CAN TAKE US
PLACES THROUGHOUT THE REST OF
THE GAME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
HALI, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCILLARY
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE CALEB.
HALI.
CALEB.
THAT'S TWO VOTES CALEB.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CALEB.
ONE VOTE HALI.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT, CALEB.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> Jeff: CALEB, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, EVERY TIME YOU VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT, YOU CHANGE THE
DYNAMICS OF THE TRIBE, AND THE
QUESTION IS ALWAYS THE SAME: WHO
DOES IT BENEFIT, WHO DOES IT
HURT?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," J.T. STARTS AN
UPRIDING.
>> SANDRA IS DANGEROUS.
I CAN DEFINITELY CHANGE THE
COURSE OF THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: AND THE TWISTS NEVER
STOP COMING.
LOSERS, BOTH TRIBES GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> OH.
>> OH, OH, OH.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE FIREWORKS
TONIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> THE LAST TIME I PLAYED THIS
GAME, I WENT OUT DAY NINE.
AND THIS TIME, I'M GOING OUT DAY
NINE AGAIN.
LAST TIME I LEFT ON MY BACK IN A
HELICOPTER.
THIS TIME I'M WALKING OUT ON MY
FEET.
I'M MUCH HAPPIER ABOUT THAT.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH TAI IS
GOING TO REMAIN.
I STILL LOVE HIM TO DEATH AND I
WISH HIM THE BEST OF LUCK MOVING
FORWARD.