Previously on Survivor...
The minority was hopeless...
Six of them are thinking,
uh-huh, we got you.
and desperate.
I'm willing at any moment
to throw Brad,
Tai and Troyzan under the bus.
Until Andrea threw the
game off the rails.
Let's make a bigger move here.
But Michaela and Sarah wanted
to keep the majority intact.
At Tribal Council...
the minority voted for
one of their own.
And Andrea got her way.
Zeke, the tribe has spoken.
Nine are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
I thought myself, Sierra,
Troyzan and Tai
were on the bottom and one
of us was going home.
But come the find, there was
a plan to get rid of Zeke.
But unfortunately we all put Tai down.
So i don't know that i have Tai anymore.
It was just hard.
But i do think it was the right move.
Yeah...
Tribal Council was a
heartbreaker, for some reason
we decided to acquiesce to Andrea.
The majority turning on
each other after one
vote, just means there's nothing
solid in a big group.
If the pair of Brad and
Sierra stay together long enough
and they can convince enough
people to come back to that
side, we're back in trouble.
So we got to split that up.
So we are feeling
losing control in this game
and feeling like you're at
the botton, because
you have nothing to lose.
Sarah has been my
closest friend, not even alliance,
friend, while being out here.
And i feel like i really
got burned by her.
But she might be a key person
to get me further in this game.
I need to leave that
behind us and
somehow try to continue to work together.
I'm about to throw haly mary up here...
- Ok.
- And i maybe shouldn't.
What?
But...
I found something on the first day.
It's called the legacy advantage.
For real?
- What is that?
- It's an inmmunity idol.
But you can only play it at six.
- Ok.
- But...
if we can get to six, it can help us.
Right.
And if not, i get to will it
to someone, and you're
going to get a pretty present.
What if i'm gone?
- For real?
- Yeah.
Sarah is the first one
i've told about my advantage.
I want to use it as a way
to weasel in there.
"You still have me, girl."
I hope you don't have to
will it to me.
The door is not closed
for you, i'm just telling you.
I swear on everything, i will vote
where you guys tell me to vote.
And i'm willing to write
down anybody's name.
All right.
Brad and Sierra need
to be split up.
When Sierra told me
about this advantage,
it actually makes me
want to keep her now because
she's giving me information,
and she wants to work with me.
So the door is opening
for her to stay in this game
and Brad's game is over.
Subtitulado por: TwiNe
Come on in, guys!
All right, are you guys ready to
get to today's reward challenge?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
The winners of today's challenge
will have a good old-fashioned...
american barbecue.
Burgers...
- hot dogs.
- Oh, my god.
And cupcakes for dessert.
- Worth playing for?
- Yes!
There's more.
You are also playing for
your loved ones.
What?
Oh, my god.
All right, Sarah, clearly
you are ready for this.
You're up.
Sarah, who are you hoping to see?
- My husband.
- Wyatt.
Come on out, Wyatt.
Oh, my god.
Sarah, tell me about Wyatt.
Him and my son are the two
most important people in my life.
Anyone who has
kids knows it's not easy,
and then to have me just
completely sucked out of his life
and have to do it
100% on his own,
just the support he gives me,
i couldn't ask for anything better.
Wyatt, did you give her
an update on how the son is doing?
Just that he's doing great.
He misses her, he says mommy
every day, every morning.
We're ready for her to be home.
All right.
Give him a hug.
Damn, he's sexy, Sarah.
All right.
Andrea, you're up.
Let's bring mom Linda out.
Come on out, Linda.
Hi, mommy.
Andrea, what is it about your mom
that connects you so strongly to her?
I mean, she's just the
sweetest, most loving,
forgiving mom ever.
I was just a troublemaker growing up.
You were fine.
Yeah.
She...she had some hard things
that happened in high school, so,
you know, she lost her sister,
and so that's... i'm sorry.
But it's all because of your
sister that we're really here.
Really?
Yeah, she really encouraged me to apply.
I feel like every time
i come and play Survivor,
i feel more connected to her.
I just know she's proud of us
and she's just happy that we're
still like a loving family.
Well, i'm glad you're out here, Linda.
- Give her a hug.
- Thanks.
- I love you.
Aubry, you're up.
Who is here?
I think it's my sister Carrie.
Your sister Carrie.
Come on out, Carrie.
- This is everyone.
- Hi, everyone.
Aubry, outside of food,
in the hierarchy of need,
the trust, the love, the
affection your getting right now,
there's a bond with siblings
that's unlike any other bond.
Can you capture what that is?
I think it's just knowing that
that person has seen every single
shade of you and they still unconditionally
accept you for who you are.
And that means a lot.
Give her a hug.
Sierra, you were lucky enough
to have a loved one
visit first time you played.
It was your dad, and he's back.
Dan, come on out.
Sierra, this is the first time
in 30 days i've seen this body language
where you're at ease.
You feel safe.
Yep, this game is so hard.
I haven't been able to
let my guard down for one minute,
and just to have him here...
i mean, i'm shaking.
I'm really proud of her for playing
at such a high level of competition.
I hope she can keep thick skinned.
What made you say that?
Because this is a really great
piece of advice for everybody.
Life is so fragile.
And no matter how hard you
try to play anything in life,
there's always going to be
somebody trying to take you down.
And you have to just be
thick skinned and try to
climb the mountain to
the top and get there.
All right, give your
daughter a last hug.
Michaela.
Let's get your mom out here.
Candy, come on out.
There she is.
Michaela, what is it about your mom?
She works hard every single day,
and it's just one of those
people they do everything
they're supposed to do, but
sometimes life knocks you down
and you find yourself in a
situation where all you can do is work.
And so her just being able
to be somewhere like Fiji
and enjoy and not worry
about how much stuff costs or
who is going to pay
for it or what somebody else needs.
Me being able to give
her this opportunity,
that means more to me
than anything else right now.
All right.
Give her a hug.
- Troyzan.
- Oh, Troyzan.
Now, who are you expecting to see?
My brother Todd, but i'm
not sure if he made it.
Let's find out.
Come on out.
It's your bro.
God!
I can't believe it.
Troyzan, i'm trying to remember
if i've ever seen a
brother reunion like this.
There's no lack of affection
between you guys.
Zero, i mean...
we've been close since
we were this high.
And i feel more whole
family here, i have a big family.
There's six of us kids,
three boys, three girls.
We're like the brady bunch.
So... this is Peter.
We're glad you're out here.
Give him a hug.
Tai.
You look like you're
ready for some love.
Who do you want to see?
The love of my life, Mark.
Mark, come on out.
Mark.
Tell me about Tai.
He's an incredible person.
He's the best person i
think i've ever met.
He brings out the best in me.
And i think i do the same for him.
And i'm so lucky to have found him.
Give him a hug.
Culpepper.
Go get'em, buddy.
You have a very unique
situation in that you're the
only person out here
whose loved one, your wife,
has actually played this game.
She has.
Monica.
Now, Culpepper, anybody who is
a Survivor fan knows Monica.
But we know her in
the Survivor World.
She's tougher than me.
She's stronger than me.
And...
And i never realized how hard
it was on you to go all the way.
Thank you, sweetie.
Give him some last love.
One person left, Cirie.
You made a giant sacrifice this
time, what was it?
I have three boys at home.
The youngest graduated high school...
while i was here.
Shall we get him out
here and see how graduation went?
Jared, come on out.
Tell me about your mom, Jared.
I'm so lucky.
Some of my friends
can't even talk to their moms,
and me and her are just like
two peas in a pod.
Cirie, Jared just said something i
don't think i've ever heard
in an 18-year-old young man say,
which is i can talk
to my mom about everything.
This is typically the time they
tell their parents nothing.
No Jeff, we have a relationship...
that is like no other.
I wanted them to be able
to come and tell me anything.
We talk about some things i
might not even want to share.
Jared, give your mom some love.
All right, now you know
what you're playing for.
The loved ones will go with you
and enjoy that barbecue.
Here's what you have to do
to earn the loved ones.
For today's challenge, you'll
be tethered together
in groups of three.
On my go, you'll race through
a series of obstacles to a table
where you'll untangle
braided rope to release a key.
That key will open a
chest full of sandbags.
You will use them to
knock down a series of targets.
The first team to win
will go with their loved ones.
You'll have a nice barbecue,
nice afternoon.
Big stakes.
We're going to draw for
teams, we'll get started.
All right, we have our three teams.
It is Culpepper, Aubry and Andrea.
Cirie, Troyzan and Sierra.
And Tai, Sarah and Michaela
for an barbecue and love.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You're going to have to work
together to win this challenge.
Up and over that first obstacle.
We are dead even.
Everybody pushing hard.
Now you're going to crawl.
Sierra's out first.
Michaela right behind.
Here comes Andrea's team.
Troyzan is dragging Cirie.
Now you got to dig under
and get everybody under.
30 days you're already exhausted.
It's that love that's
powering you right now.
Andrea trying to squeeze through.
Andrea through.
Here goes Aubry.
Starting to pull ahead.
Tai going to go under
now for his team.
Go ahead, you got it.
Straighten your leg out.
I can't straighten it!
Sierra's leg stuck.
She's going to come back out.
Culpepper going to try
the shove that body through.
Can he do it?
Culpepper is through.
Move on!
Andrea, Aubry and Culpepper
in the lead right now.
Now you have to sthufl the
pieces on the table.
Untangle that rope and release the key.
Tai continuing to try
to get through this.
Here goes Cirie coming through.
Squeeze through, ma!
Cirie is through.
That's it, Andrea!
You got to let that key drop.
Once you're fully unbrainded.
There you go, release it.
Culpepper, Aubry, Andrea
moving on to the sandbags.
Unlock that box.
There goes Michaela face first.
She's through.
You're good.
Troyzan's through.
They're both pulling Sierra.
You're good.
Michaela, Sarah and Tai
trying to get the key.
Andrea, Aubry and Culpepper
in the lead right now.
Culpepper firing now.
Culpepper tosses and connects.
You got to knock all the
targets off the platform.
Culpepper with another big hit.
Culpepper on fire with another hit.
Great job, babe!
Culpepper knocks off another two.
He's down to three left.
One left.
Culpepper, Aubry and Andrea
win love and barbecue!
Loved one, come on
over and join them.
You will all share in the barbecue.
All right.
Big decision.
The three of you, Culpepper,
Andrea, Aubry, choose one player
and their loved one to join you
for this barbecue back at camp...
Brad, please.
and look already at the pressure.
Culpepper!
All right, who are you going to choose?
Cirie.
Come on over, Cirie.
Jared, come join.
You're sorry you all can't have love?
I am because i know
how they need it.
Aubry, Andrea, Culpepper,
put you through it again,
one last person...
- Please, y'all, come on.
- to join you.
Sarah.
Oh, my god.
Sarah, come on over.
Wyatt, come join.
Loved ones, have to say
good-bye to you.
Dan, Todd, Candy, Mark.
Time to say goodbye.
All right, everybody, grab your
stuff, head back to camp.
Have a good afternoon.
That was a very, very
difficult decision.
Michaela was completely defeated.
But Michaela is very
smart, and knows that
this is a game, so
we'll give Michaela a day.
She'll get over it, and
we'll be back on track.
- Burgers are ready.
- Hot dogs, too.
And there's steak and sausage.
Jared is like his mom.
He's not an island boy.
He's a city kid, you know,
he's never been anywhere.
It's huge to see him open
to different things.
The only thing that would
be better than that is
for me to make it to
the end and win for him.
I'm very fortunate that my loved
one is a former stud Survivor player.
She's a huge resource for me.
Michaela was angry after
she was not selected.
So hopefully Troyzan and
Sierra are back at camp
trying to convince Michaela to flip
and get in alignment with us.
Otherwise i have to win
immunity for me
to be able to make it another day.
I was really disappointed to
not get picked.
- But... but...
- I know.
Your mom is so cute, so sweet.
And you can see where
people's loyalties lie.
Like i'm a really loyal person,
but maybe people are
just taking advantage of that.
And they don't even
see me in their plans.
I was really pissed off
at the reward challenge,
because they didn't
care about me and my mother.
So i saw a huge opportunity to
move myself forward in the game.
Tai is awesome to work with,
because he has no one.
Maybe this is time to think about
who i actually connect with
and who i can trust.
And i feel like you could
be one of those people for me
and i could be one of
those people for you.
Definitely.
Uh... no, i love it.
You know, i'm ride or die
you and Brad.
I know.
I'm open to figuring out a way.
Listen, if we get two people,
let's just talk.
You, me, Brad, Michaela and Tai.
I mean, she's up and down.
I know, hey, if everything works,
we are in the majority again.
I don't want to turn my
back on Brad or Troyzan.
So i'm hoping that maybe
we can pull Tai back into our mix
and maybe have an
in with now Michaela.
Whom i've never worked with.
It's a great opportunity
because she's the kind of person
to get upset, feel disrespected and flip.
I'm trying to figure out how
to make these last nine days work.
And i've spent a lot of
time just being told
what to do in this game.
Right.
Look Zeke... they told me,
like, this is going to be our six.
This is going to be our six.
And the first vote you
vote out someone in the six.
That's what Andrea told us to do.
- Andrea is doing everything.
- Yeah.
I'm telling you right now.
If any of us in the end are
with Andrea, none of us win.
Yeah.
Right now, i feel like
we are all in agreement on Andrea.
Plus Brad.
I want you to know now
i'm on the exact same page as you, girl.
Like, in the same page.
I put Tai and me
in a wonderful position.
The stars aligned for us.
We've got options.
Be with the group that votes
Andrea, or be with the group
that votes Brad.
And we'll come to that decision
whenever it's time to come to
that decision, but at the end of
the day, this is about Michaela
and what Michaela is trying to
to in this game.
- Exciting.
- We don't need no steak.
Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to get
to today's inmmunity challenge?
Yes.
First things first, Andrea,
we'll take it back.
Thank you for meeting
me half way.
Once again immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to balance on a narrow
perch while holding a buoy
between two handles.
If at any point the buoy drops...
or you fall off the perch...
you're out.
Last person left standing wins
immunity, safe at the vote.
Losers, Tribal Council.
Somebody will be the twelfth
person voted out and become
the fifth member of our jury.
We'll draw to spots.
We'll get to it.
All right, everybody take your spots.
I'm going to count you in.
Here we go. Five, four,
three, two, one.
All right, everybody is in a good
spot and this challenge is on.
Already Sarah fighting to
balance but recovers quickly.
Brand-new Survivor challenge.
Somebody here will be
the first person to win it.
Aubry squirming, trying to hold on.
Aubry drops.
Aubry is first out of this challenge.
No shot at immunity.
And right behind Aubry,
Sierra drops.
There's not a lot of buildup.
It will just happen and you're out.
These buoys are going to
twist and turn a lot on you.
It's okay as long as you
keep those handles
in that center hole,
you're still alive.
Culpepper wobbling a bit.
Nice recovery.
Sarah starts to wobble
and another recovery.
Andrea out of nowhere squirming.
Andrea drops.
Andrea's out.
Sarah with another nice recovery.
Can she hold on?
Sarah can't hang on.
Sarah drops.
Andrea and Sarah are out.
We're now down to five.
Cirie squirming.
Cirie now pops out.
Cirie is now out.
And Troyzan drops.
We're down to three.
Just like that, in matter of 30
seconds we lose four people.
It is Michaela, Culpepper
and Tai fighting for immunity,
security at Tribal Council.
We've been out here 18 minutes now.
Michaela has not budged.
She's solid.
Tai now reajusting,
still looking solid.
Culpepper squirming.
That buoy starting to move,
but he's still fighting.
This is where the willpower kicks in
and the thought of wearing
that necklace, the prize,
the security.
Tai with more movement on those buoys.
Those handle starting to move.
The buoy starting to move.
Fatigue starting to hit
everybody now.
Michaela right on the edge.
Out of nowhere, Michaela drops.
We're down to two, Culpepper and
Tai, side by side for immunity.
Culpepper has been
struggling with his balance
and has hung in there
this entire time.
Tai squirming a little more now.
You've been fighting for
32 days, keep fighting right now.
Tai drops.
Culpepper wins individual immunity.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Culpepper, come on over.
Culpepper's first individual immunity
win in all your time on Survivor.
You are safe tonight at Tribal Council.
As for everybody else,
somebody going home tonight.
Should make for a lot of scrambling.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
Congrats.
Brad won inmmunity,
and saved himself.
And because of that, the whole
idea of splitting up Brad and Sierra,
i think Sierra is
in trouble, i think
Andrea is in trouble, and
it's funny because everybody
thinks i'm voting with them.
So a couple of people
going to be blindsided tonight.
- Congrats.
- Good job, Brad.
That is amazing.
I struggled the whole time.
Before the challenge, we were
planning on taking out Brad.
And Brad ends up winning inmmunity.
So it does kind of limit our choices.
The original five say Sierra
is the one to vote off tonight.
- Sierra.
- Ok.
We have to have the numbers.
We don't need to talk about it.
and strategically, both groups want us.
- Andrea.
- Ok.
Michaela and Tai told me
that my name is getting thrown around,
and i'm absolutely terrified,
but people have gave me their word.
And it's myself, Brad,
Troyzan, Tai, and Michaela
who are going to vote for Andrea.
So i'm hoping people are
looking at the big picture right now
and i'm not the biggest threat.
It's Andrea.
- Sierra.
- Is that how you feel?
- Yeah, i'm good.
- Cool, i'm good.
So, originally i didn't want
to vote Sierra out.
But Brad won immunity,
and if Sierra goes,
it is not all bad because
Sierra has told me
about this legacy advantage.
And that she would will
it to me if she leaves.
Now the only trick is, i need
to confirm that Sierra thinks i'm
good with her to ensure that
she gives it to me.
I don't want to vote her out.
But this isn't about making friends.
This is about winning one million dolars.
My lips are sealed.
So now according to Sierra,
Tai and Michaela might
be voting out Andrea,
which is news to me.
I need them to help me
vote Sierra out,
because i need that advantage.
I think we need to get Sierra out.
She told me she found
a legacy advantage.
And essentially what it is,
is it's an immunity idol.
So we got to get her out.
Initially it was get Andrea
because she might win everything.
But the fact that
Sierra has an advantage
further convolutes what's the best
move to make right now.
Let's get Sierra out because
she's got that advantange.
So she's got to be the
one to go no matter what.
Tai and i need to decide
which way to go tonight.
Sierra is a good person
to get rid of,
but we would like Andrea
gone sooner than later.
The question is:
Is now the best time?
It's a great thing when
the decision is in your hand
as long as you
make the right one.
Because if you make the wrong one,
you'll end up on the
jury looking stupid.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie,
and Zeke voted out at
the last Tribal Council.
All right, so let's start
with the loved one visit.
Andrea, you get to
choose two other people to go,
but you can only choose two.
Walk me through your decision
to choose Cirie and Sarah.
Yeah, it's such a hard decision.
We know how much love means out here.
You can enjoy hanging
out with your loved ones,
but in the back of your
mind, you're thinking,
are there going to be consequences.
So Sierra, that leaves you,
Michaela, Tai and Troyzan behind.
What kind of damage can
that do in this game?
I mean, well, you have us four.
Who just happen to be
the four who didn't get to go on
the reward last time,
so we just go to get
closer and figure out
if we want to move forward
in the game together or not.
Aubry, the game really
can turn on emotion.
You make one wrong decision,
and somebody doesn't
like it or feel good about it,
and the game pivots.
Absolutely, Jeff.
I think that holds true in
every single interaction.
Not just a big decision
like a loved ones visit.
But all those little
things can also add up.
Culpepper, let's talk about
the individual immunity challenge.
Really your first
big win on Survivor.
Yes, i mean...
This helps me, but it doesn't help
that the four are on the bottom.
So i can't revel in the glory
of my first immunity win.
Sierra, when you fall out
in an immunity challenge.
Are you wanting someone to win?
Are you thinking about your
pitch when you go back to camp?
I wasn't even concerned
who was going to win.
I see about myself, i'm in trouble.
But i'm still here,
i'm still a vote.
I think there are
bigger people in this game
that they need to be
worried about than me.
Like who?
There are people at
challenges who are stronger.
Who go longer than me, you know?
There's Andrea.
I don't feel like i'm the biggest threat.
Hands down.
Andrea, singled out.
I get what she's saying
that i've won two immunity
challenges, so that looks threatening.
But right now there are people
that are on the botton are big underdog.
So if one of them sneaks
by and get to the end,
they have a good shot
of winning this game.
Aubry, both have a point.
Yes, everyone sees Survivor
through a certain lens.
I think we're all seeing it
with ourselves at the center.
And each of us has to
decide what kind of threat
is the most threatening to me.
Sarah, is it hard to put
this season in its spot
right now, because it has been
so uneven and unpredictable.
Yeah, just when you think you
know what's going on,
you seem to not
know what's going on.
But we've got a solid
group, right now.
Hopefully we all stick together.
But has the deck reshuffleed?
Michaela, can you ever trust
anybody who says "we have a group"?
Isn't that often the phrase
said before somebody
in that we is blindsided and realizes,
guess i wasn't in the "we" after all.
We is relative to whoever feels
like they're the big W at the moment.
And that W can flip
upside down and be
a me if you ain't watching.
So it's just one of those things.
You stick with the we until it's
about to turn and bite you.
Then you run.
Andrea, maybe the
toughest thing
about tribal is you
can't believe a single word.
So what do you do?
Yeah, i mean, i've already
heard things tonight that have
raised a lot of red flags.
But then you're thinking, are
they really good and just bluffing?
You have to think about
the conversations you had
with the people you feel
good about earlier in the day,
and just hope that that
is sticking true tonight.
Sierra, you were nodding
your head at that.
Yeah.
The people who took the time
to speak to Sierra today,
i'm staying true
to what they said.
And i'm believing in them,
and that's how
i'm voting tonight.
But i probably have talked to
the same people Sierra talked to,
so they're lying to
either me or her.
Yep.
That's what it is.
And Michaela, that is exactly
what you were talking about.
It's fine as long as the We is a We,
and not a Me.
And it's about to
become a Me for somebody.
It is time to vote.
Cirie, you're up.
It's either you or me, girl.
I hope i'm a part of the real we.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the Tribal Council area inmediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Sierra.
Andrea.
We're tied.
Two votes Sierra,
two votes Andrea.
Andrea.
That's three votes Andrea.
Sierra.
We're tied again.
Three votes Sierra,
three votes Andrea.
Sierra.
That's four votes Sierra, three votes Andrea.
12th person voted out
and fifth member of our jury:
Sierra.
You need to bring me your torch.
Sierra, the tribe has spoken.
- Time for you to go.
- Yep.
Privilege, guys.
This is the Legacy Advantage.
Now that i'm out, i get to will
it to whomever i want.
It's a very hard decision.
I hope you didn't
vote for me tonight,
but i will be giving it to Saran.
She was honest with me
and real with me out here
and deserves to win this game.
So i hope Sarah gets to use it
as six and makes a huge move with it.
Well, with eight players left
and several seats still
open on the jury,
it might be time to
prepare for a storm,
because it's coming.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor...
Tensions are high.
Go fish.
I'm just making sure
he's not looking for an idol.
I'm not going to kowtow
to some diva's demands.
Forcing Cirie to make
a tought decision.
I'm never going to be
able to live with myself.
Damn, could i pull that off?
- Crazy.
- It turns everything upside down.
I thought i was part of the we.
And it looks like i was not.
I think i was too comfortable.
But i came in with
guns blazing,
gave it hell, and i made it
further than i thought i could.
Of course i wanted
to go further but
i couldn't be more proud
of myself right now.