>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," A SURPRISE SWITCH
SHOOK UP THE GAME.
WE ARE CHANGING FROM TWO TRIBES
TO THREE TRIBES.
AT THE NUKU TRIBE, J.T. WAS
OUTNUMBERED.
>> IT'S 5-1.
>> Jeff: AT THE TAVUA TRIBE,
TROYZAN HAD NO CONTROL.
>> IT'S TROYZAN VERSUS EVERYONE.
>> Jeff: AT THE MANA TRIBE,
BRAD HELD ALL THE POWER.
>> IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN TO
EITHER HALI OR CALEB.
>> Jeff: AND AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BRAD RALLIED THE TRIBE
TO VOTE OUT CALEB.
>> CALEB, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: 17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> Jeff:>> TAI, I KNOW THAT WAS
YOU.
>> IT WAS DIFFICULT, BUT IT'S A
GAME.
IT'S MY GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> THANK YOU FOR TRUSTING ME.
YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE ANY
SUSPICIONS.
>> ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER THAN
WORDS, ESPECIALLY ON "SURVIVOR."
>> YEAH.
I'M VERY CLOSE TO CALEB, SO THIS
VOTE WAS REALLY HARD TO ME, BUT
I WANT TO EARN MY TRUST FROM THE
REST OF MY TRIBE.
I'M NOT PLAYING WITH MY HEART
THIS TIME.
I'M PLAYING WITH MY HEAD.
>> I THINK WE'RE DOING WELL WITH
THE VOTE SO FAR.
>> WE'RE DOING GREAT.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> ME, TOO.
>> CALEB GOING HOME LAST NIGHT
INSTEAD OF ME WAS A BREAK IN
THIS GAME.
>> IF WE LOSE, WHO WOULD YOU GO?
>> I'D GO TAI.
>> I KNOW DEBBIE AND TAI DO HAVE
A COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP, SO
I'M TRYING TO SHOW DEBBIE THAT I
AM YOUR ASSET GOING FORWARD, AND
TAI IS A LIABILITY.
>> I MEAN, I'M TAI NEXT.
OH, MY GOD, AM I HIM NEXT.
BECAUSE IF WE LOSE, HEY, THEN WE
LOSE.
>> WE GOT A PLAN.
>> THIS IS MY SECOND TIME
PLAYING, NOT MY FIRST, SO I TELL
HALI JUST WHAT I THINK SHE WANTS
TO HEAR, BUT THE PHILOSOPHY FOR
THIS MANA TRIBE IS TO KEEP OLD
NUKU TRIBE.
>> IT OBVIOUSLY DOES, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, IF WE NEWS, WE KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING, EVERYBODY IS
LOCKED DOWN?
>> THAT'S THE ONLY WAY TO PLAY
IT.
>> IT'S TOO SOON TO MAKE TAI A
TARGET, SO HALI, YOU HAVE NO
OPTIONS.
YOU HAVE NONE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
NUKU AND TAVUA GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW MANA
TRIBE.
>> OH, WOW.
>> Jeff: CALEB VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: TODAY WE'RE DOING
SOMETHING A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
ONLY TWO MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE
WILL RUN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: HERE'S HOW IT WORKS:
THE FIRST PLAYER WILL RACE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES
WHILE BALANCING A BALL ON THE
END OF A POLL.
AT THE END OF EACH LEG YOU ADD
MORE POLE MAKE IT MORE
DIFFICULT.
AT THE END YOU USE A BALL TO
RELEASE A KEY.
THAT WILL OPEN A BOX.
YOU USE THE SANDBAGS INSIDE TO
KNOCK DOWN NINE BAMBOO TARGETS.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> OH, GOD.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> LOOK AT ALL THAT.
HOLY CRAP.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING YOU NEED
FOR A NICE CUP OF COFFEE
INCLUDING CHOCOLATE COOKIES.
>> CHOCOLATE.
>> WOW.
>> JEFF, WE LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH,ERER THIS MOUSE OF ICE
COFFEE.
LAST TRIBE TO FINISH, NOTHING.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU GUYS A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE, DECIDE WHO
YOUR TWO WILL BE, AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR PAIRS FOR EACH
TRIBE.
FOR NUKU IT IS J.T. CARRYING THE
BALL, MALCOLM THROWING SANDBAGS.
FOR TAVUA, IT'S OZZY CARRYING
THE BALL, TROYZAN THROWING SAND
BAGS.
AND FOR MANBACK TAI CARRYING THE
BALL, CULPEPPER THROWING
SANDBAGS.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> EASY.
>> Jeff: THIS FIRST SECTION,
THERE YOU GO, YOU'VE GOT TO GO
UNDER, BUT THE BALL HAS TO GO
OVER.
J.T. DROPS.
OZZY'S THROUGH.
TAI DROPS.
HE'S GOT DO GO BACK.
>> COME ON, OZZY.
>> Jeff: OZZY THROUGH THE
FIRST SECTION.
>> WAY TO BE, OZZY.
>> Jeff: OZZY WITH AN EARLY
LEAD.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, OZZY, GOOD
JOB.
>> Jeff: J.T. ONCE AGAIN
WORKING ON THAT FIRST SECTION
AND HE'S NOW THROUGH THE
TOUGHEST PART.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, TAI, FOCUS.
>> Jeff: OZZY NOW ON THAT
SECTION SECTION.
TAI TO THE SECOND SECTION.
HE'S GOOD.
>> GOOD JOB, OZZY.
>> OZZY MAKING FAST WORK OF THE
SECOND SECTION.
NO PROBLEM FOR OZZY.
TAI HAS HIS SECOND SECTION OF
POLE.
HE'S GOING TO START ON THE
BALANCE BEAM.
OZZY STILL WITH A NICE LEAD AS
HE HEADS OUT ON THAT THIRD AND
FINAL SECTION.
J.T. UP ON THE SECOND SECTION.
TAI ON THE SECOND SECTION.
>> SLOW AND STEADY, TAI.
>> Jeff: OZZY ON THAT THIRD
AND FINAL SECTION.
THE BALANCE BEAM ALONE IS
TRICKY.
J.T.'S MADE UP A LOT OF TIME.
CAN HE GET THERE?
>> GOOD WORK, J.T.
>> Jeff: J.T. IS GOOD.
OZZY STILL WITH A BIG LEAD.
OZZY DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
J.T. IS NOW BACK IN IT.
TAI IS ALMOST THROUGH THE SECOND
SECTION.
TAI, YOU'RE GOOD.
J.T. HAS HIS UNDONE.
IT'S NOW OZZY AND J.T. SIDE BY
SIDE AS THEY HEAD OUT ON THAT
THIRD AND FINAL SECTION OF
BALANCE BEAM.
>> SLOW AND STEADY, J.T.
SLOW AND STEADY.
>> Jeff: OZZY IS THROUGH.
TRANSFERS TO TROYZAN.
TROYZAN CAN NOW OPEN HIS CASE,
LOOKING FOR THOSE BAGS.
>> YEAH, J.T.!
>> Jeff: J.T. IS THROUGH.
MALCOLM CAN START OPENING THAT
LOCK.
TROYZAN HAS HIS BAGS.
CONNECTS IMMEDIATELY WITH ONE.
THERE ARE NINE TARGETS.
TROYZAN HITS HIS SECOND.
MALCOLM HITS HIS FIRST.
MALCOLM WITH ANOTHER.
>> FOCUS, TAI.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: TAI DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
>> SON OF A BITCH.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM IN THE LEAD
NOW.
MALCOLM WITH HIS FOURTH.
>> Jeff:>> COME ON, TROYZAN.
>> Jeff: ANOTHER HIT.
ANOTHER HIT.
WE'RE TIED.
BOTH GUYS HAVE FIVE TARGETS
LEFT.
TAI STILL ON THAT BEAM.
CULPEPPER WAITING FOR CHANCE TO
GET IN THERE.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME, TAI, RELAX.
I CAN CATCH THEM.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES MALCOLM.
MALCOLM IS DOWN TO THREE.
TROYZAN WITH FOUR.
TROYZAN SCORES.
WE'RE NEW TIED.
TAI IS ACROSS.
>> COME ON, CULPEPPER.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER QUICKLY
WORKING ON THAT LOCK.
CULPEPPER GOING TO TRY AND GET
MANA BACK IN THIS, AND HE DOES
QUICKLY WITH ONE.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: HE KNOCKS ANOTHER ONE
DOWN.
MALCOLM HAS THREE.
MALCOLM KNOCKS ANOTHER.
HE'S DOWN TO TWO.
MALL -- MALCOLM DOWN TO ONE.
CULPEPPER RACING TO GET BACK IN.
TROYZAN WITH TWO.
TROYZAN GETS IT.
>> COME ON, MALCOLM.
AWESOME.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM WINS REWARD
FOR NUKU.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR SECOND.
CULPEPPER KNOCKS ANOTHER ONE.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> CULPEPPER KNOCKS OFF A THIRD.
AND A FOURTH.
AND A FIFTH.
CULPEPPER ON FIRE.
>> CULPEPPER IS SMOKING THEM.
CULPEPPER HAS MADE UP A TON OF
TIME.
CAN HE CATCH TROYZAN?
TROYZAN MISSES.
CULPEPPER KNOCKS ANOTHER.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
BOTH GUYS WITH TWO.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER DOWN TO
ONE.
TROYZAN.
CULPEPPER!
CULPEPPER DOES IT!
MANA WINS REWARD WITH A HUGE
COMEBACK THANKS THE BRAD
CULPEPPER.
>> THAT WAS LIKE TERMINATOR.
>> Jeff: NUKU, NICE JOB, BIG
FINISH, GRAB YOUR REWARD.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY YOUR COFFEE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ENJOY.
WELL EARNED.
MANA, BIG COME-FROM-BEHIND
VICTORY.
NICER THERMOS OF ICE COFFEE.
GRAB YOUR REWARD, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
TAVUA, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
>> WE THOUGHT WE HAD IT.
BY TROYZAN DROPPED THE BALL.
HE WAS TERRIBLE.
HE ALREADY WAS THE ODD MAN OUT.
NOW TROYZAN'S LIFE IS HANGING ON
BY A STRING.
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> YOU WIN SOME, YOU LOSE SOME.
>> I WANTED TO WIN IT FOR YOU
GUYS.
>> AS A TRIBE, LOSING IS ALWAYS
HORRIBLE, LIKE WE ALL WANT TO
WIN.
BUT LOSING THE REWARD CHALLENGE
WAS GREAT FOR ME BECAUSE WITHOUT
REWARDS THEY NEED ME TO SURVIVE
IN THIS GAME.
I FEEL REALLY CONFIDENT I'VE
BEEN DOING AN AWESOME JOB BEING
THE ROCK OF THIS TRIBE.
NOT TO TOOT MY OWN HORN, BUT I'M
ABLE TO CATCH FISH.
I'M ABLE TO PROVIDE A CONSTANT
SUPPLY OF GREAT PROTEIN.
IF I DIDN'T BRING FOOD IN, MY
NAME WOULD COME UP A LOT MORE
THAN IT DOES.
BUT MORE THAN, THAT IT'S ALMOST
LIKE A MEDITATION, FISHING GIVES
ME A CHANCE TO THINK ABOUT THE
GAME AND COME BACK A LITTLE MORE
GROUNDED.
IT'S JUST EXTRAORDINARY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S A BIG OLD FISH, BRO.
>> DUDE, THAT THING LOOKS HUGE.
>> IT WAS UNDERNEATH A ROCK.
I SAW IT MOVE.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE HAVE BEEN
A BOTTOM FISH.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> OZZY IS NO JOKE.
AS FAN OF THE SHOW, JUST SEEING
HIM IN ACTION IS AMAZING.
HE CAUGHT THIS STINGRAY, SO
WE'RE GOING TO GET A MEAL, AND
HOPEFULLY THAT'S GOING TO GIVE
US MORE CONFIDENCE TO DO WELL IN
THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
>> I'M GOING TO GO BACK OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE AWESOME.
>> THANK YOU, J.T., AND MALCOLM.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> CHEERS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> CHEERS TO NUKU.
>> HOLY COW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH.
>> THIS TRIBE HAS GOT IT GOING
ON, LET ME TELL YOU.
THIS IS THE BEST TRIBE EVER.
I'M ECSTATIC HERE AT THE NUKU
TRIBE.
I PRETTY MUCH GOT EVERYTHING IN
LINE, ALL MY RELATIONSHIPS WITH
EVERYONE ARE PERFECT.
I'M THE QUEEN HERE.
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
I KNOW I'M RUNNING THE SHOW.
AND NOBODY REALLY KNOWS IT.
>> EVERYTHING LOOKS GOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT, IF WE GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, SANDRA'S
DANGEROUS.
I THINK WE GET RID OF SANDRA.
>> I'M STARTING TO THINK SO.
TOO.
>> THE LONGER SANDRA'S IN THIS
GAME, THE MORE TROUBLE WE'LL
HAVE GETTING RID OF HER.
SHE'S A TWO-TIME WINNER FOR MORE
THAN ONE REASON.
YOU CAN TELL BY THE ATTITUDE AND
THES ASs IN SANDRA'S VOICE,
SHE KNOWS SHE'S IN CHARGE.
>> IF ANYBODY SAYS YOUR NAME,
I'LL COME STRAIGHT TO YOU.
>> YOU GOT THE SAME.
>> MALCOLM AND I HIT IT OFF.
MALCOLM IS EXCITED.
I CAN SEE IT.
HE WANTS TO PLAY WITH ME.
I DON'T PLAN ON LOSING, BUT IF
WE LOSE AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
WING, BANG, MOVE, I CAN MAKE MY
MOVE AND GET RID OF SANDRA.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
FIRST THING FIRST, TAKE BACK THE
IDOL.
OZZY, AUBRY.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, ONE
PERSON WILL BE YOUR CALLER.
THE REST OF THE TRIBE WILL BE
BLINDFOLDED AND TETHERED
TOGETHER IN PAIRS, USING ONLY
VERBAL COMMANDS, A CALLER WILL
GUIDE THEIR TRIBE THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
WE'LL PULL ON A ROPE, WATER
ALONG WITH IT A BAG, ONCE YOU
HAVE ALL THREE BAGS, YOU'LL USE
THE BALLS INSIDE AND MANEUVER
THEM THROUGH A TABLE MAZE.
YOUR GOAL, GET ALL THREE BALLS
IN THEIR FINAL RESTING SPOT?
NUKU, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON,
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
SANDRA, YOU'RE GOING TO SIT OUT.
TAVUA?
>> TROYZAN.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN WILL SIT OUT
FOR TAVUA.
OH, BY THE WAY, THE FIRST AND
ONLY THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH
WINS IMMUNITY.
>> OH.
>> KIND OF A BIG BY THE WAY.
>> Jeff: LOSERS, BOTH TRIBES
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> SITOUTS, TAKE A SPOT ON A
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY,
GO?
>> HAUL ASS.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF LOUD VOICES.
>> TO THE LEFT, TO THE LEFT, TO
THE LEFT.
>> Jeff: BIG HIT BY J.T.
NUKU SENDING ALL FOUR OUT AT
ONCE TRYING TO FIND THAT FIRST
TOWER.
MANA SENDING ALL FOUR OUT AT
ONCE.
>> I CAN'T HEAR YOU, BRAD.
>> THE WAY YOU'RE FACING.
>> Jeff: CIRIE WITH A
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT STRATEGY.
SENDING HERS OUT IN TWO
DIFFERENT PAIRS.
>> STOP, OZZY!
STOP, OZZY.
>> Jeff: ZEKE HAS THE ROPE.
>> COME ON, OZZY.
>> Jeff: ZEKE AND OZZY FOR THE
FIRST BAG FOR TAVUA.
THEY CAN HEAD BACK.
>> THAT'S A TOWER.
WE'RE AT THE TOWER.
>> BEHIND YOU.
>> WE'RE LOOKING FOR A ROPE.
>> NO!
>> Jeff: J.T., RIGHT IN FRONT
OF YOU.
>> Jeff: J.T. HAS THE FIRST
BAG FOR NUKU.
>> SIERRA, BEHIND YOU.
>> Jeff: SIERRA AND HALI NOW
HAVE THE FIRST BAG FOR MANA.
EVERYBODY WITH ONE BAG.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THREE TOTAL.
>> RIGHT HERE, OZZY, DROP IT,
DROP IT.
180.
NOW BACK TO YOUR RIGHT.
>> Jeff: OZZY AND ZEKE HEADING
BACK OUT.
>> TO YOUR RIGHT, TO YOUR RIGHT!
>> MALCOLM, YOU GOT IT.
IT'S IN THERE.
>> HAUL ASS.
HAUL ASS.
>> Jeff: ANDREA AND SIERRA
WORKING TOGETHER TRYING TO FIND
THAT TOWER.
TAVUA AND NUKU WITH TWO BAGS.
MANA ONLY HAS ONE.
>> I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING BRAD IS
SAYING.
>> Jeff: TAI AND DEBBIE STILL
A BIG GOOSE EGG.
THEY HAVE NOTHING, WANDERING
AROUND.
>> STOP!
TAI, STOP.
YOU GOT IT.
J.T., IT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF
YOU, YOUR LEFT HAND.
THERE YOU GO.
>> LEFT?
>> GOT IT, GOT IT.
>> Jeff: J.T. AND MICHAELA
HAVE THE THIRD BAG.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE AND TAI HAVE
THE SECOND BAG FOR MANA.
>> J.T., HAUL ASS.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM AND AUBRY ARE
BACK.
J.T. AND MICHAELA ARE TRYING TO
GET BACK.
YOU GOT TO GET ALL THE WAY BACK
BEFORE YOU CAN HEAD OUT TO WORK
ON THE TABLE MAZE.
THAT'S ALL THREE FOR NUKU.
TAKE OFF YOUR BUFFS.
SPRINT OUT ONCE YOU'RE UNBELTED.
>> WE'RE WAY AHEAD OF THEM,
GUYS, WAY AHEAD.
>> Jeff: NUKU A GIANT LEAD.
MALCOLM WITH A BIG FALL.
>> OZZY, RIGHT THERE.
STOP, OZZY!
>> OH, BALLS.
>> Jeff: OZZY AND ZEKE HAD THE
THIRD BAG FOR TAVUA.
THEY'VE JUST GOT TO GET BACK.
NUKU WITH A BIG EARLY LEAD RIGHT
NOW.
IT IS J.T. ON THE MAZE FOR NUKU.
>> NOBODY IS BACK TO THEIR MAT
YET.
WE'RE WAY AHEAD.
>> NICE AND SMOOTH, BABY.
>> SIERRA AND HALI HAVE THAT
THIRD BAG.
THEY HAVE TO HEAD BACK.
OZZY AND ZEKE BACK WITH THE
THIRD BAG.
YOU'RE GOOD.
TAKE OFF YOUR BLIND FOLDS.
LET'S GO.
J.T. CONTINUES TO WORK IT FOR
NUKU.
>> RIGHT IN THERE IS WHERE YOU
WANT IT.
>> Jeff: MANA HAS THEIR THIRD
BAG.
THEY CAN START HEADING BACK.
TAKE OFF YOUR BLIND FOLDS.
OZZY GOING TO START WORKING ON
THAT TABLE MAZE FOR TAVUA.
THERE IS A BIG LEARNING CURVE.
ONCE YOU GET THE TOUCH AND YOU
LAND ONE, YOU'RE DONE.
THE NEXT PERSON HAS TO COME IN.
YASMINE DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
NOBODY IS GOING TO BE THE HERO
AND GET HOT AND DO ALL OF THEM.
IT'S GOING TO BE SIERRA FIRST ON
THE TABLE MAZE FOR MANA.
J.T. GETTING VERY CLOSE.
>> PERFECT.
YES!
>> Jeff: J.T. HAS THE FIRST
BALL FOR NUKU.
J.T. IS OUT.
HERE COMES MICHAELA.
EVERYBODY FEELING THE PRESSURE.
SIERRA DROPS.
IS SIERRA GOING TO GIVE IT UP TO
HALI?
>> YOU GOT THIS, OZZY.
>> Jeff: OZZY IS ONE TURN AWAY
FROM LANDING TAVUA'S FIRST BALL.
HE'S GOT IT.
OZZY HAS ONE FOR TAVUA.
TAVUA IS ONE, NUKU WITH ONE,
MANA WITH NOTHING, A BIG ZIPPO.
>> I DON'T THINK I'M A NATURAL.
SOMEONE ELSE.
>> Jeff: BIG STAKES.
ONE TRIBE AND ONLY ONE WILL BE
SAFE.
MALCOLM VERY CLOSE TO THAT INNER
CIRCLE.
>> GOT IT.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM.
VERY CLOSE.
MALCOLM HAS THE SECOND BALL FOR
NUKU.
THEY'RE DOWN TO ONE.
NUKU WITH TWO.
JUST ONE REMAINING TO WIN
IMMUNITY.
>> WE HAVE A HUGE LEAD.
YOU TAKE YOUR TIME.
IT IS VARNER, CULPEPPER AND
SARAH.
>> Jeff: RIGHT THERE, RIGHT
THERE.
STOP.
SARAH GETTING INTO THE INNER
PART OF THE MAZE.
>> THERE YOU GO SARAH.
AND SHE'S INSIDE AND SHE DOES IT
THIS TIME.
TAVUA WITH THEIR SECOND.
HERE COMES ANDREA FOR THE WIN
FOR TAVUA.
>> COME ON, VARNER.
>> Jeff: VARNER NOW GOING TO
FEEL THE PRESSURE BECAUSE IT'S A
SLOWDOWN BETWEEN VARNER AND
ANDREA.
TRIBAL COUNCIL LOOMING FOR TWO
TRIBES IN THE LATEST TWIST IN
"SURVIVOR" GAME CHANGERS.
>> I FORGOT HOW THE MOVE THIS
TABLE.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER VERY CLOSE.
CULPEPPER HAS FIRST FOR MANA.
SUDDENLY THEY'RE GETTING BACK IN
THIS.
CULPEPPER.
VARNER IS IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
MAZE.
VARNER GOT THEM TO THE MAZE.
NOW HE'S GOING TO BE THE HERO OR
THE MAZE.
>> JUST STOP.
>> Jeff: ANDREA RACING TO GET
BACK IN IT FOR TAVUA.
ANDREA VERY CLOSE, TWO MOVES
AWAY.
>> YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: VARNER IS VERY CLOSE.
>> VARNER'S INSIDE THE INNER
CIRCLE.
CAN HE DROP IT?
>> YOU GOT IT, ANDREA.
DON'T LISTEN.
>> Jeff: ANDREA SNAKES INSIDE
ONE MORE LEVEL.
VARNER VERY CLOSE.
CAN HE DO IT?
RIGHT HERE.
NO, VARNER FALLS OUT AT THE LAST
SECOND.
ANDREA IN THE INNER CIRCLE.
FOR THE WIN TAVUA WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SENDING MANA AND NUKU TO SEND
SOMEBODY HOME.
VARNER SO CLOSE.
TAVUA, NICE JOB.
VERY CLOSE FINISH.
ANDREA PULLED IT OUT OVER
VARNER.
TAVUA, NO TRIBAL COUNCIL, NOBODY
GOING HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, ENJOY
THE NIGHT OFF.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GREAT WORK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NUKU, MANBACK I'LL SEE YOU GUYS
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT AS ONE
GROUP.
YOU WILL VOTE OUT ONE PERSON.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> THIS TWIST IS SO DANGEROUS TO
ANYONE BECAUSE ANY FRACTURE IN
ANY RELATIONSHIP IS A REASON TO
SEND SOMEBODY HOME TONIGHT.
THIS TRIBAL IS GOING TO BE
INSANE.
>> IF WE'RE EVER GOING TO LOSE,
THIS IS THE ONE.
WE GET THE SAY WHO GOES HOME
BECAUSE WE HAVE MAJORITY.
>> I UNDERSTOOD CORRECTLY, BOTH
TRIBES WILL GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BUT ONLY ONE PERSON
WILL GO HOME.
>> THIS HAS NEVER HAPPENED
BEFORE.
I THINK WE HAVE TO SIT DOWN AND
TALK, GROUP DISCUSSION.
>> I'M STARTING TO THINK I NEED
TO BE READY FOR EVERYTHING IN
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS,"
BECAUSE WHO KNOWS WHAT PROBST IS
COOKING UP NEXT.
ME AND J.T. WANTED TO GET RID OF
SANDRA, BUT WE DO HAVE A NUMBERS
ADVANTAGE.
WE'RE UP 6-5 ON MANA.
SO IF WE STAY TOGETHER, IT'S
VERY SIMPLE ON PAPER, BUT ON
PAPER IS THE ONLY PLACE IT'S
SIMPLE.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO COME IN, WE
HAVE FIVE PEOPLE, TOO BAD, LIKE
ONE OF US IS GOING TO GO HOME.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE A PLAN.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO GET J.T. TO
VOTE WITH THEM.
>> YOU THINK THAT'S WHAT IT IS?
>> THEY WILL TRY TO GET ME,
SURE.
BUT I'M SOLID.
I'M SOLID WITH YOU GUYS 100% SO
WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> IT TAKES ONE PERSON TO FLIP
THE CHANGE EVERYTHING, BUT WE
HAVE TO VOTE SIX STRONG.
IF SOMEONE MESSES THIS UP,
THEY'RE GETTING THEIR ASS BEATEN
WHEN THEY COME BACK TO THIS
CAMP.
>> THIS IS THE PERSON I THINK WE
SHOULD VOTE OUT AND WHY, SIERRA,
BECAUSE THAT'S THEIR STRONGEST
FEMALE OVER THERE.
>> I DON'T THINK NOBODY HAS AN
IDOL.
>> I'M NOT WILLING TO RISK MY
LIFE THEY DON'T.
>> I SAY GET RID OF TAI.
HE'S SNEAKY AS HELL, END OF
STORY.
>> WE'RE NOT ON THE SAME PAGE.
EVERYBODY IS ON THEIR OWN PAGE.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
AND EVERYBODY PLAYS AS PART OF A
TRIBE.
BUT IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL GAME FROM
THE BEGINNING, REGARDLESS OF
WHAT ANYBODY SAYS.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK BRAD WILL
TARGET OVER HERE?
WHO DO YOU THINK THEY'LL TARGET?
>> I WOULD SAY ME, BUT I DON'T
KNOW.
>> THE MOST TRUSTWORTHY
RELATIONSHIP I HAVE ON THE MANA
TRIBE IS BRAD CULPEPPER.
IF I WAS A BETTING MAN, BRAD IS
SAYING, ALL OUR VOTES ARE GOING
FOR SANDRA.
I COULD BE A SWING VOTE AND VOTE
SANDRA, BUT THAT'S A BIG RISK.
I COULD JUST SIMPLY GO WITH
MAJORITY AND VOTE SIERRA OR TAI.
HMMM.
BUT I'D MUCH RATHER SEE SANDRA
GO.
IF I WANTED TO, I COULD
DEFINITELY CHANGE THE COURSE OF
THIS GAME BIG TIME.
GET A LITTLE JACKED UP.
>> I THINK WE NEED TO CONVINCE
THEM TO TAKE OUT SANDRA.
>> THIS TRIBAL CAN BE EXTREMELY
COMPLICATED.
NOW WE'RE GOING WITH THEM HAVING
SIX AGAINST OUR FIVE.
I KNOW THIS THAT FOUR OF US WILL
ALL VOTE ONE WAY.
WE HAVE ONE WILD CARD, HALI, WHO
USED TO BE ON DEATH ROW,
HOWEVER, NOW THE "SURVIVOR" GODS
SMILED ON HER AND SHE'S IN AN
ENVIABLE POSITION.
>> BLUE EYES, LOOK AT ME, ARE WE
GOING TO BE FIVE STRONG.
>> I'M ON THE MINORITY IF WE'RE
GOING AGAINST THEM, YOU KNOW,
LIKE FIVE VERSUS SIX.
>> THE BOND YOU BUILD HERE ARE
BETTER THAN THE BONDS YOU BUILT
AT THE OTHER PLACE, SO IF WE CAN
STAY FIVE UNANIMOUS, THAT WILL
SPEAK VOLUMES.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, OH, LOOK HOW
THE TABLES HAVE TURNED.
I MEAN, I HAVE OPTIONS.
I COULD GO WITH THIS TRIBE, BUT
I COULD ALSO FLIP.
THERE ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT
DYNAMICS GOING ON.
YOU NEED TO CONSIDER YOUR
SHORT-TERM AND LONG-TERM GAME AT
THE SAME TIME IN THIS VOTE.
>> I THINK J.T.'S GOING TO GO
SANDRA.
>> THEN WE SHOULD.
>> WE SHOULD, BUT I WISH WE WERE
GOING MALCOLM.
>> J.T. DOESN'T KNOW WHO WE'RE
GOING TO VOTE FOR.
>> HE DOES.
HE WOULD VOTE SANDRA.
>> FROM CONVERSATIONS...
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO VOTE
MALCOLM.
>> I KNOW WE HAVE TO VOTE
SANDRA, BUT IT'S SO STUPID NOT
TO GET MALCOLM OUT.
>> WE HAVE TO BE FIVE STRONG NO
MATTER WHAT WE DO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> IT'S J.T.'S VOTE.
>> IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN TO
J.T.
>> IT'S VERY TRICKY TONIGHT,
BECAUSE WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHETHER J.T. IS WITH US OR WITH
THEM.
AND THEY GOT THE NUMBERS, WHY
WOULDN'T THEY STICK TOGETHER?
SO I NEED TO LOOK FOR A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
MY MIND IS IDOL, IDOL, IDOL,
WHERE DO I GO?
IF YOU HAVE IT, IT'S PROTECTION.
I THOUGHT I'D FOUND THE IDOL.
BUT I FOUND THE CLUE.
WHOA.
OH, MY GOD.
THE CLUE TELLS ME TO COME TO A
CLEARING NEAR THE TRIBE FLAG.
THAT'S THE TREE WITH TWO MARKERS
LINED UP.
ANOTHER TREE WITH THREE MARKERS
LINED UP WITH A FIVE FLAG.
MAKE A CROSS, THAT'S WHERE TO
DIG.
I CAN CHANGE THE GAME AROUND.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP IN "SURVIVOR"
UNTIL YOUR TORCH IS OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IDOL WILL GIVE ME POWER.
THEY HAVE THE NUMBERS, WE HAVE
THE IDOL.
THE BEST KEY THE LIFE.
KEY TO A LIFE.
>> I'M SCARED.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
>> YOU HAVE BAD FEELING?
>>
>> HOLD ON.
>> WHAT?
>> I HAVE AN IDOL.
>> GOOD FOR YOU, TAI.
THAT IS FRICKING AWESOME.
>> RIGHT BEFORE TRIBAL, TAI HAS
FOUND AN IDOL.
>> IF ONE OF US FOUR IS GOING TO
GO, IT NEEDS TO BE PLAYED.
>> I'M EXTREMELY EXCITED BUT I'M
ALSO COMPLETELY TERRIFIED
BECAUSE WE DON'T KNOW WHO TO
PLAY IT FOR.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
THIS IS A HUGE GAME CHANGER.
>> HUGE.
>> A LOT CAN GO WRONG, BUT I'M
PRAYING WE CAN MAKE THIS HAPPEN
BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO BE A HUGE
MOVE.
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL HAS NEVER BEEN
DONE BEFORE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE CRAZY,
BECAUSE IT CAN BE ANYBODY
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: J.T. GO AHEAD AND
GRAB THE UNLIT TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE,
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
SO MALCOLM, NEW TWIST, WHAT WAS
THE FEELING WHEN YOU WENT BACK
TO CAMP KNOWING ALL OF YOU WOULD
BE COMING TOGETHER TO VOTE OUT
JUST ONE PERSON.
>> YOU KNOW, WHO CAN COUNT HOW
MANY TRIBAL COUNCILS THIS GROUP
HAS TO COUNT TOGETHER.
THIS ISN'T ANYTHING LIKE ANY OF
THOSE.
YOU HAVE TO RUN THROUGH EVERY
SCENARIO POSSIBLE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO PLAY IT.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, IT COULD
BE EASY TO SAY, THERE'S SIX
VERSUS FIVE, EXCEPT EVERYBODY
HAS THEIR OWN AGENDA.
>> WELL, WE IN THE BUSINESS CALL
A MEXICAN STANDOFF MOW TEACHLY.
WE HAVE OUR GUNS AGAINST THEM.
THEY GOT THEIR GUNS AGAINST US,
THE QUESTION IS ONE OF THEIR
GUNS POINTED AT THEMSELVES AND
IS ONE OF OUR GUNS POINTED AT
OURSELVES.
>> JEFF, ALL OUR GUNS ARE
POINTED AT THEM.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE, WHAT COULD
THE FIVE OF YOU DO TO UPSET THE
SIX?
>> WELL, WE HAVE SOMEBODY IN
THEIR SIX WHO USED TO BE REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY, REALLY CLOSE TO
US.
>> Jeff: WHO IS THAT?
>> J.T.
>> Jeff: SHE SAID THE MAGIC
WORDS.
"USED TO."
>> Jeff: J.T., IT IS A TOUGH
GAME THE PLAY.
YOU STARTED THE GAME WITH ONE
GROUP.
YOU NOW MIGHT BE ON A TRIBE WITH
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
WHERE ARE YOU WITH ALL OF THIS?
>> I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE ARE
EXPECTING ME TO DO SOMETHING TO
PUT MYSELF AT RISK WHEN IT WOULD
BE A SHOT IN THE DARK FOR ME TO
LAND IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
>> Jeff: LET'S LOOK BIG
PICTURE, THERE ARE A LOT OF
THREATS OUT HERE, AND I THINK
THERE ARE MORE THREATS ON THEIR
TEAM, YOU HAVE MALCOLM AND YOU
GOT A TWO-TIME WINNER OVER
THERE.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST THREAT HERE.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, YOU'RE NOT
SURPRISED BY THIS.
YOU ARE CLEARLY A THREAT IN THAT
YOU'VE NEVER LOST.
>> OH, I'M NOT WORRIED.
I KNOW I'M NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, CULPEPPER
MENTIONED SANDRA, HE MENTIONED
YOU.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THE SORT OF THING
YOU SCARED, BUT WHEN THESE
TWISTS HAPPEN, BUT IF IT SENT ME
HOME, I'D BE CUSSING MY NAME
DOWN THE RAMP.
>> Jeff: VARNER, HAS BE THERE
BEEN MUCH TALK ABOUT IDOLS?
>> YEAH, WE TALKED ABOUT WHAT
COULD HAPPEN, WHAT IF EACH
INDIVIDUAL ONE HAD THE IDOL, HOW
THAT WOULD GO.
WE RAN THROUGH EVERYTHING.
>> JEFF, AS MUCH AS THEY TALKED
AT THE BIG PICTURE, WE LOOKED AT
THE BIG PICTURE.
WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE.
IT'S JUST WHO DO YOU GO WITH
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE, WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING RIGHT NOW?
>> I HAVE TWO BIG QUESTIONS,
DOES HE FLIP, DOES SHE FLIP?
>> Jeff: AS FOR HALI, SHOULD
SHE NOT STAY FIRM WITH US, SHE'S
GOING TO BE PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER
ONE.
>> I DON'T KNOW, THAT'S NOT A
GOOD SPEECH TO GROOM ME IN.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> I JUST WANT TO THROW IT OUT,
THERE WE ARE IN A POTENTIAL
DRAWING ROCK SITUATION, SO MORE
INFORMATION COULD POTENTIALLY
AVOID THAT.
IF YOU DO HAVE CONCERNS ABOUT
YOUR ROCK-SOLID PLAN.
>> Jeff: NO, WE DON'T HAVE NO
CONCERNS.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THEY DON'T NEED
YOU, HALI.
>> WE NEED YOU AND WANT YOU.
>> ON THE OUTSIDE, RIGHT WHERE
THEY PUT YOU.
>> Jeff: J.T., THAT GOT A
REACTION FROM YOU.
ARE YOU GENUINELY DISTRESSED?
>> VERY MUCH SO, YEAH.
I HAVE A LOT OF THINGS GOING
THROUGH MY HEAD SINCE I'VE BEEN
HERE, BUT I GOT TO DO WHAT I GOT
TO DO TO STAY ALIVE.
>> AND AS YOU'RE TALKING, SIERRA
AND HALI ARE HAVING A
CONVERSATION THAT MALCOLM IS
JUST EAVESDROPPING ON.
>> I WANT TO SAY SOMETHING.
I THINK THIS IS A STUPID TIME IN
THE GAME TO BE THINKING ABOUT
ANYTHING EXCEPT PHYSICAL
THREATS.
THAT'S WHERE I AM.
YOU ASKED ME WHERE I STOOD AMONG
THIS GROUP, AND I WAS HONEST.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER, FOOTBALL
ANALOGY, AN AUDIBLE, PERHAPS A
CHANGE OF PLAN?
>> POTENTIALLY, ALL THEY CAME IN
LOCK, STOCK, BARREL ON THEIR
ORIGINAL PLAN.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, THIS IS
BECOMING ROUTINE AT TRIBAL WHERE
YOU COME WITH A PLAN, BUT IT
DOESN'T MEAN IT'S LOCKED IN.
>> I FEEL LIKE I JUST SHOWED UP
AT THE WRONG WEDDING OR
SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: EVERYONE IS STILL
TALKING.
>> DO YOU THINK THEY JUST
SWITCHED?
>> GUYS, NO CONFUSION.
>> NO CONFUSION.
JUST STAY.
>> OKAY.
>> STAY TO THE ORIGINAL PLAN.
>> ORIGINAL PLAN.
STICK TO THE PLAN.
>> STICK WITH THE PLAN.
STICK WITH THE PLAN.
>> Jeff: WOW.
SIERRA, YOU LOOK LIKE A DEER IN
THE HEADLIGHTS.
>> I WILL SAY ONE THING, JUST TO
SAVE MY OWN ASS, IF WE'RE
PLAYING THIS GAME THE WAY WE
STARTED, WE NEED TO CONTINUE
WITH THAT.
IF THAT'S HOW WE'RE GOING TO BE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> SWEAR?
>> SWEAR.
>> IT'S ON YOU.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> I'M SCARED.
>> I WET MYSELF.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON
HERE, JEFF.
>> LAST CHANCE.
TELL ME.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> THEY HAVE AN IDOL.
>> OKAY.
ARE WE STAYING?
SHOULD WE CHANGE IT TO BRAD.
I JUST TOLD BRAD ABOUT THE IDOL.
>> ARE YOU SURE IT'S NOT YOU?
>> Jeff: UNPRECEDENTED.
>> HE'S GETTING NERVOUS.
>> WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
ARE THEY TRYING TO CHANGE
EVERYTHING?
>> Jeff: NOW I'M THE ONE WHO
IS SPEECHLESS.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, WHAT JUST
HAPPENED?
IT WAS AS IF AN ENERGY FORCE
RIPPED THROUGH TRIBAL.
>> IT'S LIKE A BUNCH OF CARRIER
PIGEONS WERE GOING BACK AND
FORTH, OLD LINE, NEW LINES
STARTED CROSSING AND SHARING
INFORMATION.
IT'S STILL HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: I HAVE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT AND IT'S NOW
ROUND TWO.
>> Jeff: I THINK YOU JUST HAVE
PEOPLE WHO HAVE PERSONAL
RELATIONSHIPS WHO NEED TO
REALIZE THEY'RE PLAYING WITH A
TEAM RIGHT NOW.
BUT WE'RE GOOD.
>> NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
WE'RE JUST AM OKAY.
SOME SIDE NOTES.
>> Jeff: WOW.
ARE YOU GUYS READY TO VOTE?
I DON'T WANT TO BREAK THIS UP.
>> YES.
WE'RE READY.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> WE BETTER HUP.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: WE'RE READY.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS AS THE CONVERSATIONS
CONTINUE, TIME TO VOTE.
HALI, YOU'RE UP.
>> I DIDN'T CONSENT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE NOT READY?
>> Jeff: HALLIE, WE CAN VOTE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU MAY REGRET IT, BUT I'LL GO.
>> Jeff: TIME TO VOTE.
HALI'S UP.
>> WHO HAS THE IDOL?
>> NOBODY HAS NO IDOL OVER
THERE.
>> BEST PLAYER HERE, GOT TO SEND
YOU HOME.
>> IF YOU PULL OUT AN IDOL, I
WILL SOIL MYSELF.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> DO IT.
DO IT.
>> YES.
>> JEFF.
I FOUND SOMETHING THIS
AFTERNOON, A LITTLE NECKLACE.
I THINK I'M GOING TO GIVE IT
TO... WHAT WANTS IT?
PRETTY LADY.
HERE YOU ARE.
>> I'D LOVE TO WEAR IT.
>> THANKS, SIERRA.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR SIERRA WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE SIERRA.
DUDS NOT COUNT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: SIERRA.
DUDS IN NOT COUNT.
SIERRA, DOES NOT COUNT.
SIERRA.
DOES NOT COUNT.
MALCOLM.
ONE VOTE MALCOLM.
>> HOLY HELL.
MALCOLM.
THAT'S TWO VOTES MALCOLM.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> Jeff: FOURTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR: GAME
CHANGERS," MALCOLM.
THAT'S THREE, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I'M GOING TO VOMIT.
>> Jeff: MALL COME, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL
IS A SHINING EXAMPLE OF WHY
"SURVIVOR" IS STILL SO
ENTERTAINING AND DEF --
DEVASTATING, BECAUSE NO MATTER
HOW MANY TIMES YOU PLAY, NO
MATTER HOW CERTAIN YOU ARE, THE
GAME CAN STILL SMACK YOU IN THE
FACE.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.