Previously on Survivor...
In the Tavua tribe,
Troyzan was in the minority.
I'm sure Troyzan feels on the fringe,
because he is.
In the Mana tribe,
Tai found a clue leading to an idol.
Oh my God!
"You will have to wet a wooden board."
And Debbie lost her mind.
I was totally loyal to you.
And you broke my heart!
It's frustrating,
and I'm pissed!
In the Nuku tribe,
Aubry and JT attempted to rally the troops.
We'd be better off without Michaela.
But Sandra was leading the charge.
with you, me
and Michaela,
we can take out JT.
At the council,
Sandra got what she wanted. Again.
JT, the tribe has spoken.
And Aubry was kept in the dark.
There are 15 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Nice shot, friends.
You are there to play. I am impressed.
Really.
I thought at the council, Michaela was going to leave.
And they eliminated JT.
I'm always at the bottom of the ladder.
I think I put a lot of effort into building relationships
with these people.
But it blows my mind.
Why did you keep me instead of him?
It was because of betrayal.
When Malcolm left,
I took it very badly.
We lost someone because of him.
He had to answer for his actions.
Clearly,
Sandra is in charge.
And it's as if she sawed off my legs, like a slow death.
It was quite a blow.
Bravo.
Without a doubt, Sandra is the best here.
She is the queen of this game.
I have a thing or two to learn from her.
I found a clue just now.
"Look for a board."
I racked my brains, and I thought, the well.
It must be over there.
So I have to act.
I have to go get this idol.
But I have to hurry, before they wake up.
The clue says to wet the board.
Once you find the board with the tribe's logo,
you have to dig underneath, the idol is there.
At the last board that I wet, that's it!
White and shiny,
the anchor symbol.
This is so cool!
Oui.
I'm the king of the lucky guys.
I found the idol, the second in three days!
The last time I played one,
I changed the course of the game.
Malcolm is gone. Power has changed sides.
This one, I don't think I'll use it anytime soon.
We'll see. For now, I'm playing.
I am the game changer.
I couldn't be happier.
Survivor Game Changers Season 34 Episode 05 Stuff the Ballot Box
Over here, everyone!
Mana et Stavua,
discover the new Nuku tribe.
JT was eliminated
at the last tip.
Shit.
Glad to see that both tribes brought their idols.
I take them back.
Merci.
What the hell will happen? I do not know.
What's on the table, Jeff?
Glad to have them back.
even if they will not be used today.
Throw away your bandanas!
We are changing things again.
Goodbye, Mana!
Good. On s'y met?
Yeah! Go for it!
Yes sir!
Without opening it, take one.
What a crazy game!
My God, Jeff! Which is the correct one?
I don't know, but I'll have the one no one wanted!
I'm afraid.
Reveal your bandanas!
If you have orange, take a seat on the Mana mat.
Orange.
If you have blue, take a seat on the Nuku mat.
Debbie...
Debbie!
Debbie... ...has nothing.
...has no bandana,
because Debbie is without a tribe.
Debbie, take a seat in the middle.
I am Zeke. Nice to meet you.
Delighted. Enchanted, my friend.
Cirie! Nice to meet you!
Oh my God!
Three homos together!
We are very happy, on both sides.
The New Mana Tribe,
Troyzan,
Michaela,
Sierra,
Hali,
Aubry,
Cirie and Culpepper.
The new Nuku tribe,
Sandra,
Sarah,
Warns,
Andrea,
that,
Zeke
et Ozzy.
The game changes so fast!
Sandra and Varner
are now in the minority.
Sandra. You're in the back, hands in your pockets,
not very talkative.
What do you think?
I'm optimistic.
I hope they will get to know me
before deciding that if it goes one way, I'll finish the other.
Stuck in the middle, homeless, Debbie.
Let me explain to you.
You won't go anywhere
except...
on Exile Island.
You will depart from here for the island of Exile,
where you will live alone.
You will come back in the game
at the next council,
where you will join the tribe
which will lose one of its members.
The good news is obvious.
You cannot be eliminated on the next board.
The bad news is just as obvious.
You cannot bind.
With nobody.
It sucks.
What are you thinking right now?
What are you focusing your thoughts on?
When I was young, I often left alone,
with a pony.
I'm sure there aren't any on Exile Island.
But I'll get through this, alone.
And I will be optimistic about my future tribe.
Good, Debbie. Take your things,
head out to the ocean.
The boat is waiting to take you to the island.
Good. Mana, Nuku.
Take your things, return to camp.
The game has changed again.
I went from bottom to top in a split second.
I don't know how it happened,
but I'll go head first. I am not afraid.
But first I have to overcome the trauma.
Welcome back! Yes, welcome back!
It's changed a bit, but it still looks great.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Here we go, buddy!
"Throw away your bandanas!",
"Well, luck should turn for me."
Being 5 against 1 in Tavua,
it was rough, even though I have an idol.
I've been on my toes these past few days.
So I said to myself
that whatever happens now would be fine.
We live on coconuts,
but it keeps it going. That's all, just coconuts?
That's all.
Jeff has some surprises in store for us this season. Here's another one.
I fail in a tribe where I hardly know anyone.
I have Sierra, I've had her all along.
But when we were in the same tribe as Hali,
we weren't very close.
And I never had a connection with Cirie.
I don't know Aubry
is Michaela.
But there's Troyzan, who played with my wife Monica.
It should help bond.
And he's a man.
Like me.
We're the only two in the tribe.
Troy!
How do you see things?
I do not know. It's as if I was on my own.
But you are not.
I've been with Sierra since the beginning.
So you are...
Yeah. Friends.
You must stay with us.
Brad looks blunt to me from the necklace.
I also feel we are connected,
because we're the only two guys with five wives.
It brings me back to my season, One World.
The last thing I want is to get me
again bamboozled by women.
I tell you, look at me.
Don't be nervous with me.
Neither do I.
Tope is!
I see Troy
as an ally for the future.
I feel good with Sierra and Troy.
But that's only three.
And I need a majority of four.
So I still have work.
Do you have any coffee left?
Yes, but just coffee.
How many chickens are there left? Just three.
Where do you come from? I grew up in Oklahoma City.
I live in Brooklyn now.
Oh yeah? I lived in Manhattan.
Ah, super.
Sandra and I are on the fringes.
We find ourselves in the minority
because Andrea, Zeke, Sarah and Ozzy were together in Tavua.
And Tai was in old Nuku with them.
It is obvious that they are together.
It's weird to suddenly be at the bottom of the ladder, isn't it?
I'm not even afraid.
Varner and I are in trouble.
But when I find myself in the minority,
I stay calm and focused
because when I'm in the bath,
give me 1 or 2 days
and I will be in charge here too.
The queen remains queen.
So I think, uh...
To be clear, I want Sandra gone.
Me too.
She terrifies me.
We need to get Sandra out before the merge.
Otherwise, she will beat us.
"We can take it out whenever we want."
But what happened to everyone who said that?
They lost a million dollars to Sandra Diaz-Twine.
How do you want to play it with Sandra and Varner?
They have to be made to believe that they are safe.
Clearly, they have to be taken by surprise.
In case they have an idol.
You have to find a story to tell them.
It is to achieve the impossible.
No one ever took Sandra out. So it will be very hard.
We have to tell them a story.
Let them feel safe.
Then take Sandra out by surprise.
But I don't know what.
Us against Tai?
Tai is the perfect lure,
because it is dangerous.
He is very good at finding idols,
and he is very sneaky.
He goes in all directions.
Working with a guy like that makes me nervous.
So even if we're actually targeting Sandra,
dating Tai may seem plausible.
Sandra gives me the chips.
Oh, she scares me.
She should be the first to go.
Do not you think?
We are in a precarious situation.
On the one hand,
we give the name of Tai to Sandra and Varner,
so that Sandra feels safe.
However,
if Tai found out that his name was being mentioned,
it could blow us in the face.
Because Tai is known to switch sides.
So it's tricky.
If we merge, I don't want to deal with her.
If she leaves, I'm happy.
In the past, I found idols, changed sides.
I'm afraid they'll think I'm the most dangerous.
They say the plan is to get Sandra out,
but there is always a risk
let them surprise me first.
So I wanna go get another idol,
in case I'm the target.
I found the idol on the Mana camp,
"On my new camp,
we have the same well."
Then the same index
could walk here.
The cow! I know he's an idol.
I didn't even open it.
Survivor's god is really watching over me this season.
Having two idols, immense power.
Lots of flexibility.
It's crazy.
Come, chickens, chickens!
With two idols,
I'm actually more paranoid.
All these different levels, the complexity, the options...
Chickens, chickens!
I'm really, really nervous.
What to do with them?
Today I was at rock bottom.
"Debbie, you're going into exile."
My position couldn't be worse.
I'm going to be exiled on a ship?!
Oh my God!
What's going on?
"Welcome to exile"!
Exile is not a hell where I will freeze tonight
and starve to death.
It is a sumptuous yacht.
I play on velvet.
I have incredible luck!
Lord God, thank you!
"Enjoy your stay in exile!"
Count it!
"This ship's holds are full of meat,
salad, snacks,
sodas, liquor, wine and desserts."
Oh my God!
My God!
No one saw this coming.
A totally unexpected reversal in my favor.
Oh my God!
Never, ever,
they will only imagine this
is what happens to me.
They will all take pity on me,
because I would have endured that, I would have frozen.
Miam miam miam!
No one expects me to be treated like a queen.
I can do with that.
No tribe, it's true!
It's Debbie's tribe.
What happens now?
Can I join you?
Cochran?!
Oh my God!
It is perilous.
What are you doing here?
In addition to this most unexpected exile,
here comes Cochran!
I have met presidents, prime ministers,
it takes a lot to shake me up.
But meeting one of my favorite winners
was an honor and a privilege.
Literally,
I couldn't stop laughing, smiling, freaking out.
I am part of your exile experience.
Oh my God!
I'm here to help you think, talk strategy,
discuss the rest of the game.
It helps to have an outside perspective.
My God, this is the best of exiles!
We will never do better!
When I saw it was Debbie, I thought,
"Okay, if I'm here to advise her,
it's going to be hard."
Because what I saw of his 1st participation,
it's that she claims to be an expert in everything.
So I had my work cut out.
It must be a little scary
to be separated from the tribes
and ignore what is happening on the camp.
Actually no.
I am extremely confident.
From my perspective, if I were you...
You don't know what's going on. The game changes from day to day.
Hour by hour!
Yes, and you cannot participate in these changes.
Do you have fears, reservations about people?
Uh no.
At first sight,
it was obvious that one of his main faults
was overconfidence.
She seemed convinced that everything would be fine for her.
Overconfidence and sense of security
are poisons in this game.
For me, it's jumping off my couch into the TV,
"No, no, Debbie, don't say you're super good!
No, no, we are never in such a good position!"
Is there tension with anyone?
Only with Brad Culpepper. Really?
I ended up exploding on him.
It really screwed him up.
I saw its first season.
He looked like a hothead
who would perhaps internalize his annoyances.
So you blew up on her right before you cut them off
and he can now calmly sit down and say to himself,
"What is Debbie...? I'm Brad Culpepper!"
"They don't call me a wanker!"
So that would worry me.
I would try to fix things, not to overdo it.
You have to know how to swallow your pride and flatter people's egos.
That in itself is a strategy.
It will make you win.
Flatter his ego. I will follow your advice.
I'm talking with a guy
who has not only played 2 times. He went all the way, the 2nd time.
Cochran won.
I could tell her anything
and he really supported me.
That may well have been the greatest benefit
of this experience.
There is one last thing.
I have one last surprise for you.
Oh my God! In the context of your exile.
In this bag. Oh my God!
I present this to you. Oh my God!
A choice of advantages.
Oh my God! My turn to say it!
It's been a really tough two weeks, mate.
I understand.
I have to get up. Cochran, you know what it is.
What state are you in! You are going to be in a great place.
Everything will be alright.
You might be in the best position now, Debbie.
This may be the turning point for you.
I cry, because I impregnate you with my pestilence.
Do not worry. I will burn these clothes.
My God.
So I offer you this.
“You will soon join a new tribe.
Choose the perk you find most useful."
Just when I think it couldn't be better,
I can choose from this box a benefit
among three.
"Fake Immunity Idol Kit.
Everything needed to make a splendid, but false idol."
"Additional vote.
An extra vote can come in very handy."
"Advantage for the tribe in a test.
Your new tribe
will have an advantage at the next immunity test."
It's a big decision.
I take the extra vote. Good.
Go for the extra vote.
The additional vote is a certainty.
It's like having someone 100% reliable
who will vote for sure like me.
We're going to stuff the ballot box!
It has been an honor, a privilege and a pleasure.
And a pleasure for me too.
I'm excited to see the sequel.
It seems to me... You have this advantage,
you are determined, you are well placed,
you're going to go back and tear everything up. You will ensure.
If Debbie gets hold of what we talked about
and move forward with this new mindset,
I think she has the potential to go far.
Zeke...
When I pulled the minority bandana, yesterday,
I got a little over it.
I know it's scary. I experienced that.
Especially having played twice without ever reaching the jury.
It's the storm rumbling above my head.
I readily admit it,
I like Jeff.
I love her so much.
We got quite close.
And even if we're going to take Sandra out without him knowing,
I see in Jeff Varner
a potentially desperate person
whom I could trust and save.
But first, I have to convince him that Tai is leaving.
I'm all the way down
So I play dead hoping for the best.
I don't think you're all the way down, Varner.
Really?
I'll tell you.
If it was up to me,
Tai would leave.
I don't trust him.
You can't imagine my relief when I hear that.
He's too dangerous. Far too dangerous.
As soon as he finds one,
It's finish.
Zeke and I are going to lay down on the beach.
And within five minutes, Sandra and I,
we are no longer at the bottom of the scale.
Zeke is afraid of Tai,
for he would find an idol while sleeping.
We need to get rid of this as soon as possible.
I'm in 1000%.
Good, cool.
I didn't think it would be so easy.
And I'm still not sure I trust him fully.
But at this point,
I do not have a choice.
Good, see you later.
What did you talk about with Zeke?
We got closer.
And he said he wanted Tai out.
"I want to fire Tai now."
So...
We are calm.
warn me this
that they want to target Tai.
And as long as it's not me, I'll vote for Tai without batting an eyelid.
Most...
Inside me, I say to myself
that it doesn't stick.
They'd be stupid not to fire Varner or me.
Winning is the only way
to make sure that we are not being filled with slack.
We'll see what happens in the test.
But if they think I won't take control,
they don't know the queen.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for today's immunity test?
I have the idols, let's go.
Today,
you will dive into the water,
pass through a squirrel cage.
Then you will place heavy puzzle pieces in a sled.
You'll pull it down to the finish.
Three people will then solve a puzzle of barrels.
The first tribe to finish wins immunity,
is out of the vote.
The losers, on the board, someone will be the sixth person
removed from the game,
and his tribe
will host Debbie
as a new member.
Big stakes.
A minute of organization
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For immunity. Survivors, ready?
Go!
Ozzy is waiting for the end
to take a deep dive.
Everybody
must reach the platform.
Then, one by one, you will cross the squirrel cage.
Come on, friends!
The Nuku help each other.
Go on! Ahead!
The Mana help each other.
Culpepper takes off.
Mana takes the lead.
Culpepper quickly reaches the other end.
Go ahead, Sierra!
Like that.
This is Ozzy.
Its good!
Sierra passed.
Ozzy is in the water. Varner rushes forward.
Mana are very effective.
Here is Troyzan for Mana.
It passed quickly.
Sandra takes a lot of time for Nuku.
Come on, Sandra, it's good!
Hali crosses quickly.
There are many Nuku members left.
Mana still leads.
This is Michaela.
The Mana passed the squirrel cage.
Come on, friends!
Tai catches up quite a bit of time.
Culpepper et Sierra
are going to raise the coins for Mana.
Ready? One. Two...
Zeke is nearing the finish.
The gap is closing.
Brad, we have to go back up!
The Mana have their pieces.
Its good! Pull and push!
These parts are heavy.
Here, here!
The Mana are on the second set of coins.
The Nuku on the first.
Get ready to push!
Nukus are very fast
and efficient.
Get ready to push!
More than one for the Mana.
The Nuku are getting closer,
on the way to the 2nd series.
The advance evaporates.
We stick to them!
The Mana have all their pieces.
Nuku is hot on their heels.
Watch out for his foot!
Now you have to use
the logs
to move the sled
until arrival.
The sand is too hard
to move forward otherwise.
The Nuku have all their puzzle pieces.
Can they get there?
Can they go up?
I shoot, but it does not advance.
Nice teamwork of the Mana with the logs.
Carry on!
The Nuku close the gap.
We need the back log.
Nothing easy there!
This sled and these parts weigh their weight.
Good job!
We hurry, come on!
Oh my God!
Carry on!
Want it? This is where you deserve it!
Same here!
Nobody wants to go to the council.
1, 2, 3!
At the top of the slope, you may be able to pull it through the sand.
Let's go!
Oh, hisse!
Go on!
On continue!
Go on! Go on!
The Mana did the hardest part,
the steep part.
Its good!
Unload the parts!
On and go! On and go!
...three, come on!
The Nuku continue
to strive to reach the finish.
The council is watching.
PUSH!
Sierra, Cirie and Aubry
are going to solve the puzzle for Mana.
I need a back room here.
We are almost there!
This one goes here.
Oui.
It's good, Nuku! Unload the puzzle pieces!
Here, everything will be played on the puzzle.
Quick quick!
Yes yes!
Which trio will collaborate best?
Let's remove a few.
Yes! Jeff! Jeff!
The Mana think they are done.
It would be one of the quickest resolutions
of Survivor story puzzle.
And it's good!
Mana wins immunity!
Safe from the council.
What happened?
Mana, congratulations.
Immunity is yours.
Thanks, Jeff.
Good job.
Take your things, return to camp. Enjoy your free evening.
No one will leave Mana.
Move.
Advice.
Someone will be the sixth person eliminated from the game.
And immediately after, Debbie will join your tribe
and will return to camp with you.
Take your things, return to camp. See you tonight at the council.
I hated this test.
End to end.
But I'm not moving from here.
Tai is leaving tonight.
Unless he releases an idol.
I hope that will not be the case.
It was pretty bad.
The immunity test has knocked us down.
We got our asses kicked.
My only consolation,
is that we have an opportunity to eliminate Sandra.
She is perhaps the most dangerous player in Survivor history.
So she has to go.
And as long as Varner and her
think Tai is going out, everything should be fine.
We did well.
I will release it without hesitation.
In three participations,
This is the first time I feel like it could go wrong.
warn me this
that Tai is going to sort out.
But I do not believe it.
So I can't just hope for the best.
I have to assess the situation and work my magic.
You're smart, you know the game.
You know the game.
At the merger,
the last thing you'll need,
it's having Debbie, Tai and Aubry together.
I advanced the scenario of the trio of Kaôh Rông.
Aubry is still there,
Debbie is still there, Tai is still there.
You could say that they are not great friends,
but in the end,
these people have a unique bond. They were in the same season.
And when we participate in such a game, generally,
we stick to what we know.
I do not like it.
You are a very strong woman.
Sarah too.
You are a very strong man.
And if you need help, protection,
I keep my eyes open, I'll let you know what's going on,
where is the group, who is after you,
who says what about you.
Can I help you.
For now, everyone loves you.
But when it goes into a spin, it's every man for himself,
it is you who will jump.
It's always the same.
You know that. You lived it.
If Sandra won twice,
is that it does not appear
as the most dangerous.
It almost seems to me that by talking to people like this,
she coaxes us.
She doesn't pressure you
never raise your voice,
she is calm,
and little by little, it draws you in.
Sandra is so good
I was seriously considering it.
But we vote for Sandra. Sure.
Everyone votes for Sandra. OK.
Even Varner? No. He doesn't suspect a thing.
He thinks it's Tai.
I don't want her to go any further in the game,
but I agree with much of what he said.
Sur... Le trio de Kaoh Rong.
That they go too far is very...
We all know Tai is sneaky and unpredictable.
I'm starting to get very nervous.
I believe I am left out of certain discussions.
I'm not very smart
compared to all these dangerous people,
like Ozzy
and Sandra.
They are very good at plotting and scheming.
It's not my way of thinking.
So I get nervous when they walk away.
The friends...
I'm freaking out a bit. Why?
Everyone has disappeared. Don't worry.
I mean, easy voting.
It's easy.
Sandra.
You are not leaving. For sure.
That's what we decided.
She charms everyone.
I don't want her to merge.
Tai has put his foot in the dish.
He just told Varner that we all voted for Sandra.
"What the fuck is he doing?"
It was stupid.
It was useless.
It didn't make any sense.
Did you tell Varner we were voting for Sandra?
I didn't mention any of your names.
Everything is fine.
I have full faith in you.
But it's still a little stressful.
Sandra has won twice.
So we have to eliminate it.
But I feel that I run a risk.
But I can't get paranoid.
I have two idols,
then I should get away with it.
Did he say why he wanted me out?
Or just "Sandra"?
Queen Sandra.
Arriving,
I knew I was the biggest target.
And now Tai says they're after me.
I'm going to act like I'm going to leave.
At tonight's council,
it's about making Tai
or public enemy number one.
I'm going to trap him in the wide widths.
I will turn the situation around and he will leave.
If this is your first advice, take a torch,
immerse it in the fire
and turn it on.
Now here's Debbie,
who returns from the island of Exile.
She will join your tribe
after this advice.
Andrea.
Sixteenth day of Game Changers.
What is the state of the game?
so far,
it is above all a question of taking out the most dangerous.
"Well, that's how this season is going.
Let's find the next threat to come out."
And yet, Ozzy,
there aren't really any people here who aren't dangerous.
So are there people
who are you hesitating between?
Every day, I hesitate between people.
In the end, we can fit in
with a huge target, like me,
because others can jump before me.
The hesitation is permanent.
Sandra, he was watching your back.
It's been a great 16 days, Jeff.
But that's the end of the road for me.
Really?
I arrived in the new Nuku tribe
at the bottom of the ladder, and in three days,
nobody talked to me about strategy.
So you haven't heard any names, nothing at all?
I didn't hear any names.
I assumed they saw me as a big player.
This.
You were staring at Sandra
while she was talking.
What she said is pretty accurate.
So you think she's going to leave tonight.
I wouldn't say that,
because I'm also worried tonight.
Why?
I blew up Malcolm,
I did a big game changer.
So...
Yes I...
Tai. You seem lost in thought.
I am paranoid.
These are names of weight,
like Sandra and Ozzy.
And I'm nervous.
What was the question?
Sorry.
I believe you answered it. I do not know.
Everything is possible.
I just hope to be safe.
So Sarah.
Sandra says no one talks to her.
Didn't you hear any names either?
Yes, a few.
And I believe
that on arriving at the council,
some of us are undecided.
Tai, hence your nervousness.
I thought, only one name, Sandra.
But Sarah says others have been brought up
which I am not aware of.
So I don't know what's going on. I thought we were all together.
Now...
Who knows?
Sandra. That's what you want to hear.
If Tai wants to give a name,
as long as it's not me, I'll vote with you, Tai!
Can I do it secretly?
Whisper in my ear!
OK.
As long as it's not me. Don't whisper my name!
OK?
Yeah. I will do it.
Ozzy.
But we need one more person.
How to proceed?
We are only three.
We must be four. I need one more.
Wow.
Want to tell us? I am going to tell you.
I named Ozzy.
I remain in the tradition of coming out the strongest.
I am no match for him. It's a god!
He does everything so well. He knows how to dive
hold your breath, swim...
He knows how to do everything, so well!
I can't beat him in the test.
And the merger is coming soon.
In two votes, maybe.
This.
So it's time and...
Now everyone is talking.
Well, why not?
Do you agree to vote Tai?
We are small. He's a tough guy.
Let's act!
Finally, it's up to you.
You know me loyal.
Tai, I have a question for you.
Who do you trust?
'Cause you keep telling me you trust me
and Sarah,
in Andrea
and an Ozzy.
I may want to vote with you.
But how to trust you
if I don't know who you trust?
And I also know that you are always looking for idols.
It's not me looking for idols all the time.
I don't know Tai.
Can we just vote?
I am ready. I'm ready.
Looks like I'm ready. I am ready.
Good. It's time to vote.
Andrea, over to you.
For the love of God, what a tragedy!
Tai. You are an idiot.
You mentioned my name.
But to attack me is to sign his death warrant.
The queen remains queen. Bye!
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read, the decision is final.
The eliminated person will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Premier vote,
This.
Tai. Two Tai votes.
Sandra.
Sandra. Equality. Two Tai votes,
two votes Sandra.
Sandra. That's three Sandra votes.
Sixth person eliminated...
Sandra. Four is enough. Bring me your torch.
I wish you good luck.
It doesn't matter. Tear it all up!
Sandra,
for the first time in 94 days of Survivor...
The tribe has spoken.
Don't, Jeff, don't!
Good luck! The Queen!
It's time to go. Okay.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Sandra! Goodbye, Sandra!
One more time,
I have not got the faintest idea
of what just happened.
I'm starting to get used to this feeling.
Debbie.
A torch and a Nuku bandana will be waiting for you at the camp.
Others,
take your torches, return to the camp.
Good night.
Stay with us, to see a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The Mana are reaching their breaking point.
This game...
is hard.
Alliances implode.
I am furious. It might not be you.
And Varner sees an opening.
I have to shift the focus to someone else.
I want to take Ozzy out.
Maybe it's time to be done with Ozzy.
Jeff was finally able to extinguish my torch.
But I did fine during those 16 days,
considering I'm a double winner.
I owe a lot to Survivor.
I love Survivor, from the bottom of my heart.
I don't want to cry,
but I know why I have the life that I have.
It's thanks to Survivor.
There will never be another double winner,
only the queen.