Previously on Survivor...
Andrea. For victory.
The Tavua won their second immunity challenge.
And there was a surprise
for the two losing tribes.
In a single group, you will eliminate one person.
At the council,
it was total chaos.
What is this bronx, Jeff?
Oh my God!
JT leaked the Nuku plan.
They vote Sierra.
And Tai used it to his advantage...
I would like to give the idol to...
The pretty lady!
...saving the Mana tribe...
Sierra. Does not count.
...and eliminating Malcolm.
There are 16 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
How come
that Tai just gives the idol to Sierra?
I do not know.
I just said to Brad, "You're safe." Why Malcolm?
I would like to know.
But when Hali...
When she talked about physical threats,
it made me nervous.
No, Culpepper told you it was safe.
And I told him the same thing.
What else did you tell him?
I said fuck off Culpepper about our vote.
The advice couldn't have gone worse for me.
I told Brad Sierra was in danger.
And to play the idol, if they had it.
I saw it as a great opportunity to get Sandra out.
Alas, they took out our strongest player, Malcolm.
He was my closest friend in this tribe.
So I have to cut corners
my best, and move on.
Somehow that name got leaked,
for why would Tai have chosen her?
I freaked out when I thought Culpepper had an idol.
They can't prove what I said.
So I'm going to defend myself, thoroughly.
I will never tell them.
I'm here to make a million.
Tai turned around and Culpepper said, "Sierra."
Sierra did like that, took it and put it around her neck.
I told him he was safe. I'm pissed.
It's signed JT.
It's a dirty JT trick.
And if he knows me,
I'll turn around and send him home
right behind Malcolm, if I may.
He upset my plans. It's time for revenge.
The advice was very rough for me.
my biggest fear
is that if we lose immunity,
it might well be me.
I have to find an idol.
It's ugly, but it's true.
I'm afraid to stick my hands in here.
Name of...
I have a thing.
"Finding safety requires coordination."
Surprise, I found a clue!
He says, "Finding safety requires
to find the intersection of landmarks on your range.
Seek casually or desperately.
Your protection is at hand."
Great news!
I saw the marked trees.
As soon as they're all gone
in two minutes, it's over.
I got it.
We cover...
Surprise, I found the idol!
And no one knows. Perfect, that's what I need.
"Congratulations! You have found the Hidden Immunity Idol."
I won't tell anyone.
And she will allow me to stay.
Splendid! Thanks.
Oui!
Survivor Game Changers Season 34 Episode 04 Dirty Trick
Over here, everyone!
Tavua, discover the new Mana tribe.
Full!
Still intact. What is this bronx?
Byte, Discover la nouvelle tribu Nuku.
Quoi?!
Malcolm was eliminated at the last council.
Oh my God!
Ozzy. Why is Malcolm significant?
Malcolm is a huge, huge player.
That he left at this point,
it changes the game.
Ready for today's reward event?
Today,
each tribe will use a grappling hook to retrieve a bow.
Then you will dig up a bag containing a ball.
With the ball balanced on the arc, you will cross obstacles.
You will place the ball on arrival, and it starts again.
With the grappling hook, you will collect a bag containing a support.
You will dig up another ball.
The ball balanced on the support,
you will overcome the same obstacles.
Once the two balls arrive,
a person will solve a sliding puzzle.
The first two tribes to finish win a reward.
Want to know what's at stake? Yes!
Peanut butter and jam!
Peanut butter/jam sandwiches,
plus cookies and milk.
Oh my God!
For the second... My mouth is watering.
We don't forget you.
Just a sample.
Peanut butter and jam.
Oh my God!
For the last...
Nothing.
Tavua, you are one more. Who will not participate?
Troyzan.
Troyzan. Take a seat on the bench.
The others, a minute of organization and we begin.
I'm very quick with sliding puzzles.
I do it all the time on my phone.
Grapple or dig? Choose. You choose.
Choose. I will go. Where are you the best?
I'll dig up those fucking bags, come on!
I have a very good sense of balance.
OK, so you do this. You, the support.
You, the bow. You dig.
OK. Understood.
Well, on and go.
For a reward of peanut butter and jelly,
cookies and milk.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
It will be Sarah,
Warns
and Sierra
with the grapples.
First task,
hang that bow.
A bit short for Sarah. One should understand
how to use this rope.
Sierra has the bow, on her second throw.
Good job!
Tai will dig up the first ball.
Sarah hung up her bow.
Now Cirie digs up the ball for Tavua.
I got it! Tai has the ball for Mana.
It's Hali for the balance part.
Hali is in the lead.
She advances on the first obstacle.
She loses her ball and has to start over.
Varner is still trying to snag that bow.
Varner hooks it up for Nuku!
Now Michaela digs up the ball.
Michaela flips the beach!
Michaela, record time for Nuku's ball!
Go on, Cirie! That's it!
Cirie has the ball for Tavua.
JT takes off.
This is Hali,
progressing over the first hurdle.
Ozzy doesn't hesitate.
Like he grew up doing that in the jungle!
It gives Tavua the advantage.
Take your time, you're ahead!
Ozzy cleared the first hurdle very easily.
Ozzy is on the second obstacle.
Ozzy has passed!
Bring the ball to the finish, hook the next bag!
Tavua took the lead.
Nice throw from Sarah.
Sarah quickly grabs that bag for Tavua.
Cirie will dig up the second ball.
Hali has passed!
She attacks the second section.
JT made it through the first part.
Hali and JT face off.
JT loses his ball. He has to start over.
Hali took the hit.
It's not moving this time.
And it worked! Hali, drop the ball!
Go ahead, Mana!
Sierra attempts to grab the bracket.
Cirie is still looking for the ball.
Sierra l'a eu.
Tai goes for the second ball.
Both Tai and Cirie look for the second ball.
I got it!
Tai quickly finds the ball for Mana.
And here are the Mana in the lead!
Cirie finally has the ball for Tavua.
Debbie is on the course for Mana
with stand
and Andrea for Tavua.
Andrea passed the first section,
very quickly!
Debbie had taken the lead, but she lost it.
Big fall for JT.
Debbie is still struggling.
Go ahead, JT! Go ahead, my hen!
Come on, JT!
Well done, JT!
Andrea, it's good!
JT, it's good!
Go-y, the Nuku! Go-y, the Tavua!
The Tavua can attack the sliding puzzle.
And Varner can try
to hang this bag.
Varner snags the bag for Nuku!
Michaela digs again.
Can she do it as fast as last time?
Yes, I can! Yes, she can!
Go for it!
The door remains wide open for the Tavua.
That leaves Zeke plenty of time
to attack this puzzle.
He placed himself in the role of the hero.
Can he insure?
Debbie finally clears the first hurdle.
The pressure is on Aubry.
Debbie loses her balls. She has to start over.
Aubry...
It's good, Aubry! Aubry passed the first section.
Now,
Debbie and Aubry face off.
Together in their first season, they are now opposites.
Can they catch Zeke?
Come on, Aubry, come on!
Come on, Debbie!
Nope! Debbie has to start over.
Its good! It's good for Aubry!
In the hole!
So! Go for it!
Nuku can attack their sliding puzzle.
Sandra will take care of it,
confronting Zeke.
The Mana were leading, but they are dead last.
Debbie loses her ball again.
She wasted a lot of time.
Stay calm!
The Tavua are getting closer to victory.
Oui!
Zeke thinks it's good.
Zeke earns the reward for Tavua!
There is one place left.
Sandra is on the sliding puzzle for Nuku,
as Debbie still tries to clear the hurdle
for Mana.
Debbie fails again.
She insisted on doing it, right? I say.
It slips too much, damn it!
That's it! Sandra thinks it's good.
And it is!
Nuku wins the reward!
Mana will leave empty-handed.
Yes! You finished it!
I'm tired of losing again.
Me too.
Tavua, congratulations!
Come get your reward.
Peanut butter and jam, cookies and milk.
Nuku. Come get your reward.
As long as there isn't an even number, it would be an odd one!
Mana, I have nothing for you. Take your things, return to camp.
Once again we lost.
We don't organize.
It's a dictatorship, in which Brad
decides who will do what.
I have a very good sense of balance.
OK, so you do this.
Overall, I'm pissed off.
Nice job, friends!
To Tavua! Health! To Tavua!
Health! Good game!
Nice job, friends! Nice balance, Ozzy!
syllable,
literally gone
You're welcome,
knew how to make the mayonnaise take,
and there, we dominate.
Peanut butter in Survivor is gold.
But I don't want to be overconfident.
In case something crazy happens,
I need options.
What do you have in mind, Troy?
I do not know. I feel at the bottom of the scale.
Has anyone spoken to you? No.
I only trust you in this tribe.
Pretend to do something or they'll be suspicious.
At this stage,
Troyzan is alone against me and the other four.
But this concrete quartet,
it's stupid. It sucks. I do not like it.
Grandissons.
Go on.
I'm testing the waters, do we trust each other, you and me?
If you're talking about our discussion,
you are dead and so am I.
I'm playing like a delinquent this time.
I know how delinquents lie to me.
So I know how to lie to these people.
I will look for an idol.
But don't ever trick me!
No. Why would I? Good. I tell you, that's all.
I have an idol. And Sarah doesn't know.
And she says she wants to work with me.
It would be
a huge plus for my game
not to play my idol right away.
If I could work with her and keep my idol...
High five? Yeah.
100 %.
It would be...
Le ticket d'or!
Debbie, how are you?
Debbie, talk with us! Debbie!
Speak, you four,
decide some stuff and then tell me.
And when you kill me, give my clothes to Hali too.
Come here, Debbie! Come!
I think she is very angry.
She laughs?
No, I think she's pissed. I do not know.
Are you going to talk to him? Yeah.
Today, in the test,
Hali rocked on the beam.
But Debbie couldn't make it, we lost the peanut butter.
And she insisted on doing it.
But there, she is very angry.
So I don't know what she wants.
The only predictable thing about Debbie is her unpredictability.
How are you? I worry. Yep I'm fine.
Don't worry. It rolls between us.
I know, but... I'm fucked, bottom rung,
speechless for Brad,
so might as well close it
and listen to what I am told, what I will do.
Brad treats me with very little respect.
He's used to being the boss.
At football, in his law firm, in his family,
Brad is the boss.
It's just that, total disrespect to me.
What you want, you get it.
He licks your feet so much that you're only left with the bones.
Who, Brad?
If Hali wants to go on the beam,
even if she makes us lose the peanut butter/jam
hanging around for ten fucking minutes
and that I flew over this beam in 30 seconds,
it means you don't respect me.
It's disgusting, frustrating,
and I'm pissed!
What you want, you get it.
If I say something, I'm ignored.
Debbie's outburst about Brad
revolved around the fact of not having been listened to at the test.
It escapes me a bit.
I think Brad is great in events.
He's a leader, he brings people together.
But for her, I'm the princess who can do everything
and she the ghoul who has no right to anything.
It rolls between us.
It's him. I can't take it anymore.
Brad? Yeah.
I know, he doesn't show you much respect.
None! None!
None!
Not a little, none!
I wanted to comfort her,
but to see her get upset like this, I was really scared.
She's just different, I think.
She looks crazy.
Princess Hali, what she wants, she gets!
"She's good on the beam!" She cost us the reward!
Debbie thinks she's an expert in everything.
But Hali is better than her,
in terms of agility
in the trials.
When your word is not kept at all,
why not shut up and shut up?
I understand. No problem. OK.
I don't explode in anger.
I let off steam by doing my gym.
Hence that physique and those abs.
Because I don't get angry.
Now, and that's it. I evacuate, and it will be over.
I will make a strategic and thoughtful decision,
and it could be him.
I'd rather die fighting than live on my knees.
So it seems quite relevant to me.
to make Mr. Blah-blah-blah-Brad
my next target.
Debbie, excuse me.
I don't think you even realize it.
Used to being the boss,
you don't see that this is not a discussion.
At least not with me. It is a dictatorship.
And the funny thing is, I was supporting you.
I am loyal. I was totally loyal to you.
And you broke my heart!
Why not take out Brad? He's a wanker.
May the best remain.
Come on, Brad!
Come!
They make coffee.
Is there enough for me to take the leftovers?
Put seven drops of coffee with a spoonful of sugar.
Seven drops of coffee and a spoonful of sugar?
Sure!
Michaela would like seven drops of coffee
and a spoonful of sugar, to try.
Seven drops?
Ignorance, that's what it is.
Spoon, my ass.
Of ignorance.
Michaela begins to lose her bearings.
She is already a little perched, unstable.
Yesterday was a bit hard to manage, to the test.
No one likes babysitting in a survival situation.
And there she wants seven drops of coffee in a spoonful of sugar.
Is beyond me.
I like!
JT was unhappy with Michaela using
a spoonful of sugar for a mini-sip of coffee.
So I had a great idea.
I said to myself,
"I'm going to eat the rest of the sugar."
That's what's left of sugar? I will finish it.
It'll make things worse, he'll think it was Michaela.
Only JT and Michaela use sugar.
So I knew JT would blame Michaela
that the sugar pot is empty.
There is no more sugar!
I know who ate it.
And by the spoonful.
Michaela.
Where did he go? In his mouth!
Tongue cleaned.
I believe you.
The sugar is gone!
How could he disappear so quickly?
JT thinks it's Michaela.
But it's 100% Sandra!
I don't eat it, so...
I say. Neither do I. But someone is eating it.
Who could drink all the coffee with sugar?
Do you sweeten your coffee? I drank lots of coffee.
It must be you two.
Because Sandra doesn't drink it.
It's no secret, darling. It doesn't matter.
JT acted like I took the sugar.
I was furious.
And the problem, with me,
is that the more I try to contain myself,
the worse it gets, and in this environment,
we contain, contain, contain...
But I wanted to kill him.
I sense the tension in the Mana tribe.
Now I don't know where I belong.
I have to consider
what is best for me.
I used the idol on the board.
I think there must be a new one.
I want to be productive and go get her.
Even if they think I'm sneaking around, at least
I feel like I'm in control of my game.
It's so hard to find. The jungle is big.
Oh my God!
I found another clue.
"To find the idol that can save your game,
you will need to submerge a wooden board.
When your tribe's emblem magically appears,
dig underneath and see if you've hit the nail on the head."
I'm not going to look for her right away.
Maybe I've been gone too long already.
Finding the clue is hard enough. How will I find the board?
Over here, everyone!
Ready for today's immunity test?
First of all,
Andrea, I have to take her back.
One more time,
immunity is challenged.
Today,
you will climb a high wall.
Then you will collaborate
to advance a solid wood cube towards a post.
You will then release a set of keys.
With them, you will open a chest of sandbags.
You will carry them on a beam.
Upon arrival you will use a giant slingshot
to take down five targets.
The first two tribes to finish
gain immunity. The losers, on the board,
someone will be the fifth person
eliminated from the game.
Tavua, you are one more.
The same person cannot abstain twice in a row.
It was Troyzan, to the reward.
Cirie. Cirie will not participate.
The others, a minute of organization and we begin.
I think... Beam.
No, do you think so? You, rather. No.
You are strong?
I think I should.
And me, that I should do it.
Alright, you guys decide.
No matter. Good.
Debbie, let's all keep a good attitude.
I have a bad attitude, because I'm tired of defending myself.
I did gymnastics for ten years, damn it!
This beam took me two minutes. Nobody saw?
She, ten minutes!
Without disrespecting you.
I will not do it.
Here, I have decided.
Alright, here we go. For immunity. Survivors, ready?
Go!
You have to go over it.
Things go fast with the Mana.
Yeah! First down!
Everyone passed.
On the other side, Debbie. Mana quickly moves the cube.
Here is Troyzan,
Sarah et Zeke.
Varner is last among the Nuku.
It's Aubry, JT
and Sandra.
Once again!
The Mana come first.
A helping hand, JT?
Grimpe, JT!
Sierra is up for Mana.
Sarah pops up for Tavua.
It's JT for Nuku.
These keys must be freed by spinning them.
Did you see Brad? I was the first on the other side.
I love you. I don't know why you're mad at me.
Go on!
Sierra has them. Go ahead, Hali and Tai!
Sierra was quick.
Tai attacks the padlock.
JT has his.
Sarah has hers.
Michaela attacks the padlock.
Ozzy attacks the padlock for Tavua
and Tai for Mana.
And now how fast can you try the five keys
and find the right one?
Don't force.
Michaela a ses sacs.
Go for it! You have to transport
100 sandbags crossing the beam.
Michaela, take more than three!
If you drop the bags or fall,
like Michaela, you have to start over.
Varner rushes forward.
It will be Hali
and Tai on the beam for Mana.
Andrea et Ozzy
for Tavua.
Varner loses a bag. He has to start over.
Breathe!
Hali passed for Mana, it's good!
Tai has to start over.
This is Andrea for Tavua. Its good.
Michaela struggles to hold on.
Ozzy passed.
Michaela succeeds!
Tai falls again.
Luckily we didn't send the gymnast, really!
Seriously, I'm really tired of having to defend myself.
Here is Andrea again.
Its good.
Hali loses a bag. She has to start over.
Here comes Ozzy again,
with two full handles.
When you have them all, you can start shooting.
Andrea has the latest for Tavua.
The Tavua are impressive on the beam.
They have all their bags and a huge lead.
On and goes, on and goes! Allez-y, Tavua!
Tavua can now fire at targets.
Ozzy tire pour Tavua.
And just misses.
Here is Hali, with other bags for Mana.
Michaela and Varner, still on the bags for Nuku.
Ozzy shoots again.
Just too low!
It's the last!
Tai has the last bags for Mana. Its good!
Come, you people!
Go on! The Nukus all have theirs!
Go ahead and start shooting!
Someone else!
Sarah steps forward for Tavua.
Here is Sierra for Mana.
That's it!
Sierra scores the first point for Mana.
Mana leads with one point.
Sarah tire.
Just too short.
Sierra tire.
Sierra scores again!
That makes two!
Sarah scores for Tavua!
JT shoots one down for Nuku!
Culpepper takes over
for Mana.
Sarah se retire, Ozzy arrive.
Culpepper scores for Mana!
That's three for Mana.
Ozzy and JT are under pressure.
Culpepper seeks to hit a fourth target.
He shoots away.
Culpepper hits the farthest target!
That's four for Mana. more than one
and they take away immunity.
Ozzy hits the second target.
Culpepper succeeds for Mana!
Mana wins immunity!
Safe from the board!
There is one place left.
Ozzy hits the third target for Tavua.
Two more for Tavua.
Nuku needs to speed up.
And he touches! JT hits a second target for Nuku.
That's 32.
Tavua is looking to reach fourth.
Ozzy just misses.
JT marque!
Equality.
33.
The Nuku are back in the game.
Only two more targets for each tribe.
JT hits a fourth target.
Ozzy hits the Tavua's fourth target.
New tie, 44.
There remains one target per tribe.
You have to hit the bullseye.
JT, for the win!
Non! Ozzy...
Ozzy scores for Tavua!
Tavua wins immunity
and sends Nuku to the council.
You are amazing.
Mana, congratulations! Immunity is yours.
No one will leave Mana.
Tavua, congratulations!
No one will leave Tavua.
Mana, Tavua, get your things, go back to camp.
Enjoy your free evening.
Nuku, we'll see you tonight at the council,
where someone will be the 5th person eliminated from Survivor Game Changers.
Take your things, return to camp.
The last time I played
the ordeal that led me to the council where I left
ended with a slingshot.
Today, it ended the same.
But we are in Game Changers.
The same thing can't happen to me twice.
I hope.
Sorry, friends.
I should have... Come to think of it,
it would have worked better by alternating the shooters.
We lost the immunity test.
The Fijian gods aren't too fond of Nuka these days.
Nuku. I don't even know the name of this tribe!
This is to tell you where we are.
I have a lot more to offer than Michaela.
For me,
Michaela must be the next to go.
For JT...
We came to his camp. He did his part.
He is one of us.
I thought about it.
We'd be better off without Michaela.
Downright.
There would be a lot less babysitting,
much less bitterness, much less bad energy,
much less whining and much less sugar theft.
Of sugaring. Yeah, sweet food.
I do not see
any reason for anyone to keep Michaela
rather than me.
You better not make me laugh at the council.
As long as I know I'm not leaving, I'll tell the truth.
But if I'm afraid to leave, I'll close it.
Nope! Why would you be afraid?
No, it's obvious, I have much more to offer than her.
If I have to play my idol, I will.
But they need me to win events.
So it's sad for sugar,
but nothing will be sweeter than seeing Michaela leave tonight
and his torch be extinguished.
It's damp inside. So she licked it!
I swear!
Let's see that pot of sugar she licked.
I mean...
We no longer use this jar. Finished.
I told you, it's crazy, shit!
The immunity test of the day,
JT had to earn it for himself, except he didn't know
how badly he had to win.
I have to get revenge for what happened to Malcolm.
And I think
that between Varner, Michaela and me, we make a good team.
Do you think our tribe could survive without JT?
Oui.
I think so.
All JT needs is Aubry or someone else
and that would be bad for us.
I'll talk to Jeff, see what we can do.
Because I trust you more than those two.
Sandra, Varner and I,
that's three, that's enough to get out
JT.
I'm ready to see him go. He pisses me off.
I just want you to trust me, that's all.
The only thing that could go wrong for me,
it's if Sandra or Jeff Varner decided
that they would rather eliminate me than JT.
This is how you will go to the end with Sandra,
because all I know how to do is reach...? The 39th day!
Alright, here's the idea.
I spoke with Michaela.
As JT has a grudge against her, he will close it.
He will leave her alone.
With you, me and Michaela, we can hang out JT.
Tonight, my situation is perfect.
I can choose to vote with Sandra and Michaela
to eliminate JT,
where I can go with JT and Aubry
and eliminate Michaela.
I would like to do both at the same time, please!
What if JT has an idol?
Anyone can have an idol in this game.
But I want to keep winning.
So it's either eliminating an attitude problem,
or eliminate a big threat.
Good. At the last tip, Sandra,
you have arrived in the majority.
6 against 5.
Malcolm is eliminated by surprise, you are only five.
What happened when you got back to camp?
JT was blamed for it, thinking he could have told Culpepper everything.
The name leaked.
How Tai
would he have known to whom to give the idol?
JT, you must have felt pressure.
Because it's a bit you who started the movement.
Without a doubt.
And I felt very guilty.
Malcolm was the last one I wanted to see go.
I said two words to Culpepper.
He said, "Are we safe?" I said, "You're safe.",
"You all are.",
speaking of Sierra and him.
It wasn't sabotage.
But I talked too much and burned myself too.
Michaela.
What happens to the dynamics of the tribe?
I would say that we went from a tribe
where we were on an equal footing
to a tribe where someone thinks they're the fucking boss.
You are necessarily talking about JT.
Sure.
JT.
Does this surprise you or are you conflicted?
It doesn't surprise me at all.
It's clear, everyone is tired of babysitting.
Life in the camp is tough.
I have never been so excited to be on the board.
Sandra. Do you know what JT is talking about, "camp life is tough"?
Their argument started over sugar.
JT puts it in his coffee.
And there were no more.
He thinks Michaela licked the pot
where was the sugar?
It's for real!
That is to say if he is stupid.
I'm not going to put my tongue in a pot of sugar.
So it's been open conflict ever since.
Exactly.
So, Sandra, what are you basing your vote on tonight?
Knowing that you will only be four.
Because who you eliminate
is also important
than who you keep.
We will keep
the strongest player.
And with him, we will go forward.
Michaela.
This is a clear reference to JT.
No need to pretend, right?
No, I don't know why they act like I'm stupid.
It's an insult to my intelligence.
I'm not surprised.
But I'm like, "Damn!"
Jeff, frankly, we're sick of babysitting.
She remains lying in the shelter all day.
And she said, "You bring me seven drops of coffee and some sugar?"
I was joking.
And we bring him.
Pause. Have you ever seen me do the dishes?
No. She did it.
have you ever seen me
help cook?
She did it.
Have you ever seen me bring food on a tray?
She did it. So shut up.
We continue.
I haven't seen anything like it, Michaela.
It's as simple as that, Jeff.
As he said, he speaks for the whole tribe.
Warns.
Does JT speak for the whole tribe?
Most of the time, yes.
Aubrey. Does JT speak for you?
Are you sick of Michaela? Yes.
I made efforts, and there, I am perplexed.
Sandra. Does JT speak for you?
Are you sick of Michaela?
JT doesn't speak for me when it comes to Michaela,
but I listen to what JT says,
his arguments are valid
about our future in the game.
Jeff, some of us are game changers
and others are just there to fill in the gaps.
Aubrey. It seems to shake you.
Is it because you are worried about the tribe
that you don't like conflict?
Yeah, I really like Michaela.
I have great respect for his way of leading his life,
the fact that she is an intelligent and independent woman.
But this advice clearly shows
that we have a quality of life problem here.
Varner. How complicated is this vote?
Is it only?
It is incredibly complicated.
There are disputes on the camp,
arguments in the tests.
And it's unpleasant, very unpleasant.
Aubry.
Since the beginning of this council,
did you hesitate on your vote?
This vote, for me, has become crystal clear.
Is that very clear to you, Sandra?
JT? Yes sir.
And Michaela, is that for you?
It doesn't really matter.
Good. It's time to vote.
JT, over to you.
You have a lot to learn, child.
FYI, you don't think for me,
you don't speak for me. I'm not your friend.
Hi, Machin.
The queen remains queen.
Bye!
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read, the decision is final.
The eliminated person will leave the board immediately.
I will read the votes.
Premier vote,
Michaela.
JT. A JT vote,
one vote Michaela.
Michaela. Two votes Michaela.
JT. Equality. Two JT votes,
two votes Michaela,
one vote remains.
Fifth person eliminated from Survivor Game Changers...
JT.
Holy shit!
Bring me your torch.
And tell Malcolm you got him out!
I will do it.
JT, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Shit!
You are good!
And I didn't eat the sugar. I don't know where he went.
Was it you, Sandra?!
Hat!
This is the level of play we expect
in a season titled Game Changers.
Le hic,
as we have just seen, it is only a matter of time
before we play you.
Take your torches, return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
No one can let their guard down.
Throw away your bandanas!
Because the surprises never end.
What a crazy game!
You are going to Exile Island.
A castaway is abandoned.
And a former Survivor makes a surprise return.
I was a little overconfident.
I had not taken the idol. I didn't think I needed it.
I made a very, very stupid mistake.
I was not up to it, in this experience.
I will always love this game, but I hate that I played this way.
I passed up my chance to win a million.
It's that simple.