Previously on Survivor...
Sarah shared her
secret to get an ally.
And Sierra followed suit...
...but it backfired.
I need that advantage.
At Tribal Council,
Sarah's plan worked.
Sierra, the tribe has spoken.
And she was willed
the Legacy Advantage.
I will be giving it to Sarah.
Eight are left.
Who will be voted out tonight?
Hot water, put these in
hot water or no?
That was one of the
weirdest tribals i've ever...
it was weird.
She looked at Sierra,
and i'm like: what?
I don't know.
To make Sierra feel like...
There's little things that
Sarah does that kind of raises
some question marks, and this is
definitely one of them.
Sarah's lied to me before.
Maybe it's time to get
someone like Sarah out.
- Yeah.
- Do you know what i mean?
Sarah has been getting her
work in with a lot of people.
And fine for me.
I like to take it to the end and
all the people she screwed over
sitting right there to
decide who wins.
Last night at Tribal,
taking out Sierra
was good because she
told me about this
Legacy Advantage.
She said in the event
that she is voted out,
she's going to
will it to me.
So at Tribal Council, as her
name comes up,
i look at her in shock, like:
"i can't believe
you're going" and...
it worked.
And Sierra willed
me her advantage.
"You have found the Legacy Advantage".
"With this note in your
possession, you are guaranteed
immunity, but it comes with a twist."
"You may only use it once when
there are 13 people left in the
game or when there are only six
people left in the game."
Now i have two advantages.
The first one is a steal a vote,
which amounts to two votes.
And the second one is the Legacy.
So this time, Game Changers,
i'm shooting for
the stars here, and
if i had to pick, i want Andrea gone.
I cannot stand the girl.
However, it's got
to be the right time.
Subtitulado por: TwiNe
Come on in, guys!
All right, you guys ready to
get to today's immunity challenge?
First things first, Culpepper.
I have to take back the necklace.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Once again immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, with one
hand, you're going to steady a
balancing board while
simultaneously building a house
of cards with the other hand.
The first person to build their
house of cards high enough to
reach the finish mark wins
immunity, safe from the vote.
Losers, Tribal Council where
somebody will be the 13th
person voted out and the sixth
member of our jury.
We'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
All right.
Here we go, for immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
This is a Survivor classic.
Last won by Cochran.
Set a record.
17 minutes.
Got a little crush.
I don't know, Aubry, this could
be the beginning of a little
Survivor love affair.
You break this record,
you might win his heart.
Sarah slowly building her stack.
Lots of different
strategies out of the gate.
All you have to do is get a card
high enough to break that plain
of the red finish
and immunity is yours,
security at Tribal Council tonight.
Without it, you
could be in trouble.
Andrea off to a fast start.
Michaela off to a quick start.
Aubry off to a good start.
No sooner said that,
Michaela drops.
She has to start over.
It is now Aubry and
Andrea neck and neck.
Sarah quickly building.
Culpepper slow and steady.
Andrea drops, loses everything.
It is now Aubry in the lead.
That's how fast this challenge
can change hands, and every time
you move to reach for a card,
you have to keep
your base stable.
Culpepper drops.
He's got to start over.
Sarah drops.
She's got to go back.
Aubry taking her time.
Michaela right on her heels.
Tai still hovering
around the bottom,
trying to get something going.
And there it goes.
Cirie drops.
She's got to start over.
Aubry has not faltered
yet in this challenge.
She's been perfect.
Michaela now quickly back in this.
Chasing Aubry.
Who is in the lead.
Troyzan is in it now.
Michaela loses everything once again.
Leaving Aubry with nobody
close right now.
We're only five minutes
into this challenge.
Aubry is on a record pace right now.
It took Cochran 17 minutes.
Troyzan risky move
and loses everything.
Troyzan got to start over.
Aubry continues her ascent.
Now she's taking cards off.
Aubry did not have enough
cards to get to the top.
She's going to have to go
backward now and rebuild with a
different strategy.
Aubry's first mistake in this
challenge opens the door for
everybody else.
Andrea is now back in this.
Michaela once again
very quickly back in this.
Once again Michaela
loses everything,
will have to rebuild again.
It is now Aubry and Andrea.
Here comes the wind now.
Aubry getting closer.
Andrea loses.
She's got to restart.
That breeze is picking up.
Aubry tried a new strategy.
Will it be enough?
Aubry very close.
And Aubry has it!
Aubry wins individual immunity!
Ah, that's a good hug.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Will live to see day 34.
That was a record time
for this challenge.
Did that in six minutes.
No way!
First individual immunity win,
guarantees you to see day 34.
As for everybody else,
after 33 days,
somebody, sadly, going
home tonight.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, see you tonight at tribal.
Congrats.
For me both Troyzan and Brad
have voted for me twice, but
Sarah's so good at pulling
people in, she's very crafty.
We want the get to her when
she's not expecting it.
And i think that the next vote
would be the perfect time to do that.
Nice job, all.
Thank you.
All right, i need to know
how you do it.
- How you stacked it.
- I want immunity!
That felt really, really good
to have a high moment in a
33-day journey where i needed
something to kind of start a
resume.
Now i'm thinking a couple steps
ahead, and Troyzan is someone
who is likable, but Brad is
physically a big threat,
so the time is
nigh for Brad Culpepper.
Yeah.
Everybody, so we won't
have to talk about it.
So we can eat.
Because we ain't going
to have no more fish.
I will go...
Brad is nowhere to be found
because he's off in the forest,
so i volunteer to go find Brad
and kind of just make sure that
he's not looking for an idol.
And maybe we should
get Brad to go fishing.
Brad?
Brad!
Why you running away
over here?
My only suggestion is go fishing.
Like, like... go fish.
And bring back fish...
at low tide.
So... you're block mailing me?
No, it's not blackmail, it's
a genuine suggestion.
Michaela's trying to be a
princess and blackmailing me
into fishing for her.
I'm not going to kowtow
to some diva's demands.
I'm looking for a way for me to
get back into this game
and be able to make
it another day.
I don't know.
I'm really conflicted.
There something weird
about that... i mean...
the look at Tribal Council was weird.
I've been with Sarah
since day one.
I feel like i have a great bond
with her, but maybe Sarah is
pandering to the jury already.
Maybe Sarah is already pandering
to Sierra as she walks out.
Right now it looks like she
is playing the game the hardest.
Maybe it's not the time.
Yeah.
Luckily i have a little
solace tonight.
It's really weird to
have this feeling.
I feel like i can see things a
little more clearly.
Oh, wow.
They have a lot.
I am not acting on that gut
feeling with Sarah, because i
fully believe it's time to
send Brad home.
She's kind of worries me
more than anyone else.
I don't think right now we
have to worry.
Andrea is trying to work me
like i'm a cheap suit, trying to
hint around about Sarah, but i
need Sarah to stay in order for
me to make it
further in the game.
Because i think they're
trying to pit you against me.
Exactly, i know.
Everything out here is about
timing and when to make a move.
So at Tribal Council, should
Sarah and i get rid of Andrea
and drop our numbers down, or
keep our five strong and go for
Brad, because Brad is just too
dangerous to keep around.
He wins challenges.
It's a real difficult
position to be in,
but timing is key here.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie, Zeke,
and Sierra, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Aubry, at the last Tribal,
Sierra and Andrea felt
they were in trouble.
Did that signify a slight
turning point in the game where
people are a little more willing
to at least put a name up and
let them battle it out?
Yeah, i think there might be
a little bit more of a solid we
than we've had before.
Sarah, it's tricky, because
you have to account for
everybody else's best move
and figure out
where you fit within that.
Right, but if you
have your support
behind you, it ain't broke,
what's there to fix?
Troyzan, when you
hear Sarah say, if it's not
broken, don't mess it up,
what is your move?
You go to the bottom people
and say: "listen, here i am, and
if you get me now, you've got
the most loyal person in the planet."
Aubry, it's a pretty
good argument.
It's a really good argument,
but there are still eight people
left in this game,
and a lot can happen.
Cirie, what was the
vibe at camp after today's
immunity challenge?
Jeff, it's uncanny that it's
so quiet here.
there's not the scrammabling
that you see, deal-making
conversations, i've never
seen anything like this.
Andrea, you are
nodding your head.
Yeah, there was not really
any scrambling going on, or at
least no one came up to me.
Then you start the feel uneasy.
Why are these people
not trying harder.
It's really odd.
So Culpepper, if you
look at the number of players in
the game right now, there is a
move... what is yours?
I mean, quite frankly, i haven't
talked to Andrea, because i
wrote her name down twice, but i
talked to other girls here, and
at some point, maybe
it will click, thinking:
"you know what, this is the
chance for me to make my move."
"I got somebody who is
willing to go with me to the end."
I mean, i don't really
know what else to do.
Sarah, when it comes
to the jury, is your gut that
they are going to
respect game play?
This is Game Changers, and
it's about playing the game and
playing it hard, and
i've sat over there.
It sucks.
But at the end of the day, i
have rewarded game play, giving
credit where credit was due.
Aubry, do you agree with that?
I think that a lot of people
underestimate the emotions that
are involved, but when you're
voted out of the game, the first
thing you feel is something
that's human, people aren't robots.
Tai, on want hand you
have Sarah saying: "i think the
jury will reward great game
play, blindsides or not", and
Aubry is saying: "that's crazy,
you blindside somebody,
their feelings get hurt."
To me the game is personal relationships.
I think jury will reward
people who played the best game,
not because they're
best friends with them.
Andrea, where do you
sit on this in?
For this season i hope they
would award good game play, but
i think it's also not rubbing salt in
the wounds, if you're going to
blindside someone but be their
best friend that entire day,
that seems a little vicious.
And some people do that.
So i think it is the manner in
which you send those people off.
So big picture it for
me, Michaela.
Tonight's vote is about what?
Tonight's vote is about
advancing your group and keeping
yourself as safe as possible.
Without screwing your end game.
But, Jeff, here's an argument
against waiting until the end to
get rid of your big we.
When you're final five,
somebody's going to get got.
Okay?
And your going to wish when i
was at seven i could have got
who got me at five.
All right, it is time to vote.
Tai, you're up.
Let's hope the third
time is the charm.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a
hidden immunity idol and you
want to play it, now would be
the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area inmediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Andrea.
Brad.
That's two votes Andrea.
We're tied.
Two votes Andrea,
two votes Brad.
Andrea.
That's three votes Andrea.
Andrea. That's four votes Andrea,
two votes Brad.
13th person voted out and
the sixth member of our jury:
Andrea, that's five,
that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Andrea, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Well, even when all hope seems
lost, keep talking, because
somebody might be listening.
Grab your torches, head back
to camp, good night.
It's really frustrating
going out on day 33.
I thought that i was playing
better game and a smarter game,
and i thought that i had some
real relationships, but
it's Survivor, you can't
really trust anyone.
What a funny game, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It was a good play.
We sent Andrea to the jury,
but we still have a lot of
people in this
game that need to go.
And although Aubry is in our
group, i can't trust her that much.
Pretty standard day for me in Survivor,
up and down.
Really felt great at the
immunity challenge winning...
never happened before.
And i had a good
relationship with Andrea.
So naturally she's
going to get killed off, too.
Just my pattern in "Survivor"
seems to be really high highs
and really low lows.
I love you, and you know that.
- I love you too.
- Okay.
What was really bizarre,
when we came back from Tribal
Tai immediately
runs right to Aubry's side.
Tai was like Aubry's husband.
He was consoling her more than
anybody else, which was kind of
weird to me.
You're an amazing player.
You know what to do.
Tai works people, and he
works on their emotional side.
So the way he is moving around
with Aubry let me know that
they're some kind of pair
happening there.
Come on in, guys!
All right, first things frist,
Aubry, i got to take it back.
Spin and grin.
- Just win it again.
- Thanks, Jeff.
Once again immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you'll be
perched on top of a pole
in the ocean.
On my go, you'll use a
bucket to retrieve water.
You will pour that water down a
chute raising a key.
Once you have the key, you swim back
to shore, use that key to
unlock a bundle of
puzzle pieces.
You will then use those pieces
to solve a block puzzle.
First to finish wins immunity,
safe at Tribal Council.
Losers, somebody will become the
14th person voted out
and the seventh member of our jury.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
Why do i keep doing this.
All right, here we go.
For immunity, survivors ready?
Go!
That bucket has holes in it, so
that water will start leaking
out, the second you
start pulling it up.
You're tryingY to
pour it into that chute
to lift that key closer.
Michaela getting a lot
of water in her chute,
and that key is rising.
There's Troyzan doing a nice job.
Aubry now getting a
lot of water in her chute.
That key starting to move.
Michaela with more water.
That key getting very close.
Once you can reach it,
you can grab it.
Michaela has enough water.
She can reach for the key.
Michaela is in the water.
Troyzan has enought water.
He's got his key.
Cirie having to climb back down
to unhook her bucket,
which is tied up
now in the ladder.
Aubry has enough water.
She can reach her key.
Culpepper's got his key.
It is still Sarah and Tai
working for their keys and Cirie
just working to get back up to
get a shot at her key.
Michaela is first back.
Here comes Troyzan.
Aubry is out of the water.
Here comes Culpepper.
Tai has his key.
We got four people
in this right now.
We got to free up
all those pieces.
Michaela now starting
to work on her puzzle.
Culpepper working on the puzzle.
Sarah has her key.
Cirie has her key.
Is she going to jump or climb?
Do it, Cirie!
Cirie heading back now.
Sarah has her pieces unlocked.
Anybody can win this
challenge at this point.
Despite it taking a long time
for some people to get back
everybody is in it.
Sarah making some progress.
Here comes Cirie, last to get
to her puzzle pieces.
Tai adds another piece.
The puzzle starting to
come together now.
All of a sudden you start the
see that pattern, you know what it s.
Now it's just matter of finding
the right pieces
in a very complicated
design structurally.
Sarah making some nice
progress with her puzzle.
Tai making some progress.
Culpepper and Aubry, both
working methodically.
Cirie with her first piece.
Sarah getting closer.
Sarah down to two pieces left if
she's right it would be her
first individual win.
Sarah not sure.
Something is not right.
That opens the door for
somebody else to sneak in.
Tai down to a few pieces left.
Not only is this puzzle difficult,
you're on 35 days on Survivor.
Nobody's mind is
anywhere close to 100%.
Sarah now rebuilding.
Going the try something different.
Culpepper is making some progress.
Tai now taking pieces apart.
People feel like they're close
and then realize they aren't.
Culpepper down to his last piece,
but there's a hole he can't fill.
Now culpepper has to take
everything apart.
Michaela has figured out what
she thinks is wrong.
Michaela is racing to the finish.
- Good joob.
- Jeff, this is it.
- Thinks she has it.
- Is it?
Not right, Michaela,
is not right.
And kicks the puzzle,
which always helps.
Culpepper has been rebuilding his.
Culpepper very close.
Does he have it right?
Culpepper thinks he has it.
You seem pretty certain.
Culpepper wins individual immunity!
Wow, that went together fast.
Culpepper guaranteed
a spot in the final six.
Damn right, damn right!
Wow, got a little emotion going.
Pick somebody else, people.
- You clearly felt in trouble tonight.
- Clearly.
Culpepper, come on over.
Second win...
clearly based on the
emotion came at a big time.
Culpepper safe tonight at Tribal
Council, can't be voted out.
After 35 days, somebody
going home.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp, see you tonight at Tribal.
Congrats.
Brad is safe.
So now we have to recalculate
what our next
move is going to be.
And i'm ready to take out
somebody that is a threat to me.
Good job, Brad.
So at the immunity challenge,
Brad Culpepper wins.
So i'm going to
Tribal with my idol.
If i feel like i'm in trouble,
i'll play it.
Look at the people who you
think have made
the moves in the game.
You're sitting on the jury.
I'd say sarah.
It's scary time, big boy time.
And little Tai needs
to gain confidence.
And i know she's your friend.
I think Tai has been drinking
the kool-aid that he needs to
make a move in this game, but if
i want to make a big move for my
resume, if i don't get Tai out
of here before he gets me out of
here, my game is over anyway.
Tai sees Sarah as a threat.
Listen to me.
that Tai
For whatever reason, Cirie
wants to believe Aubry in
everything that's coming
out of Aubry's mouth.
I believe Tai over Aubry, i
really do, and you know what,
this is what i'll do.
I will give you my advantage,
because if i get voted out,
then at least you've got it.
Okay.
So i'm going to give Cirie
the advantage
of steal a vote to hold on to.
This way if this doesn't scream
loyal, i don't know what does.
If we all come back here and
nothing went wrong, i'll just
give it back to you and
i will never question
- your judgment again.
- Yes.
Sarah's so confident in Tai
that i can't even get her to use
her own advantage, so she wants
to give it to me because she's
that confident, but do i play it
tonight and save Sarah and risk
Sarah being pissed off at me?
I'm from the old school.
If you got it, play it.
So i'm going to use it,
believe that.
She going to give me the
advantage, because that's how
much she believes in Tai.
I told her: cool.
I think Sarah is confused.
If she's wrong about Tai, it
doesn't just screw up her game,
it screws up my game
and Cirie's game.
Once i get her advantage and
that's played, she'll see.
Me, you, Aubry. I'm going
to take Sarah's vote away.
Because Sarah's going
to vote for Aubry.
Once i take her vote, that
gives me her vote and my vote.
- So they're going to only have... hum...
- Three votes.
Exactly.
We have to take Sarah's vote
to our own advantage.
I have to, to keep her in the game.
The advantage is that you
can steal a person's vote
and utilize that for yourself,
which gives you
basically an extra vote.
However, once i do that, whoever
we voted for now after that
has the option to play
and idol if they have it.
And i think probably
Tai has an idol.
I need to get Tai comfortable
enough to trust me.
I may be able to tell Tai about
the advantage, and i'm willing
to use this to save him that
they try to pull fast one on
him, but i don't know if he
would believe that.
Damn, could i pull that off?
This is putting me at risk.
This could get me
voted out if i tell you.
So if i tell you this and you...
tell people and
get me voted out,
i'm never going to be able
to live with myself.
This is what i want to do.
I have an advantage.
They think that they're going to
get you out tonight, and i think
if i use my advantage,
i got to use it when Jeff
says... let's get to the vote.
I have to say: Stop, Jeff.
And i get to take
away a vote from them
and i'm going to
save you with this vote.
- But if i save you...
- But nobody is targeting me.
Everybody is targeting Aubry.
That's what they're
telling you, Tai.
- They told me.
- This is crazy.
It is crazy.
You just turned
everything upside down.
Which is completely
took me by surprise.
Can i believe you?
When you see me stand up and
play that advantage,
are you still can't believe me?
Okay.
Is there any reason why she
would lie to me?
Why would she make
up this weird thing?
I am completely freaking out.
Can i use my idol?
Maybe i should.
I have two to play with.
I don't know,
i'm terrified inside.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
Hali, Ozzy, Debbie,
Zeke, Sierra
and Andrea, voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Sarah, what happened when you
guys got back the camp?
Can't vote out Culpepper.
There's only six other people.
There was a lot of sneaking
around going on,
a lot of lies being told.
I know for me i had to get to
the bottom of who is telling me
the truth and who is
not telling me the truth.
We'll find out if i'm right or not.
Cirie, is this public
knowledge or are these things
happening in little
private pockets?
It's both.
There's several lies being told.
There's several untruth
stories going around.
And i think tonight is going to
show where the deception
is coming from.
Culpepper, did you
feel the same way that there
were a lot of lies, because not
everything can be true?
Absolutely.
You expect the lie, and
then you try the piece out
the truth in the lies.
I don't think everybody's
lying to everybody.
I think there are a couple
people in this group who get
caught in lies, and the problem
is sometimes when you start
telling the truth, people
remember you from your past.
Tai, the game is about deception.
How do you determine when to
trust somebody that you know is
deceiving you because
you now know they were
and you can come together?
I automatically give people
the benefit of the doubt first.
I'm scared, like all this
layering, i hope i'm on
the right vote tonight.
Troyzan, it sounds like
fear is what is leading this group.
If you say too much, people
always use it against you,
and even when you do
something good for someone,
the favor is rarely returned.
So my hope is that i stay and get
into a position where i have
more control of what my
game is going to be like.
So Michaela, which is
more likely to happen after
tonight's vote, that the deck
will be once again reshuffled
and it's a new game, or will the
deck start to stay intact?
I think that before we vote,
people need to decide what's best.
Is now the time to
try the make a big move?
So you can have a name and risk
going home next time,
or is now the time to be
happy for what you have,
play for a we and get
to the end of this game?
All right, it is time to vote.
Jeff.
I just have to say that
there is a rat in this group,
and the person that i save by
exposing this rat will thank me
tomorrow when they wake
up here on day 36.
So i would like the use this
advantage, and this advantage
will allow me to take away
someone's vote and utilize that
vote for myself,
including my vote.
So i am going to
steal Sarah's vote.
Well, actually,
that's my advantage.
And i'm letting Cirie
hold on to it,
and it says it
can't be stolen from me.
It wasn't stolen,
it was given to me.
It's non-transferable, it
says it on the bottom.
Cirie, why don't you
read the advantage
and the rules that go with it.
It says:
"You found an advantage
in this game, you now have the right
to steal a vote from
someone at Tribal Council."
"You will then cast a second vote
using that piece of parchment."
"This is non-transferable and
cannot be stolen from you."
Cirie, the key word
in there is non-transferable.
So she can't give it to me?
She can give it to you as a
sign of trust, but she can't
give it to you to use.
Sarah is the only person
who can use that advantage.
Can i have that?
So Cirie, things are
crazy now, because your
intention was revealed
but you don't have
the power to make the move.
Didn't read the rules.
So what are you
feeling right now?
I feel that i...
let me just tell Sarah something.
Look, Sarah.
No, back, back!
Back up!
- What the hell for?
- Back up!
- You have to back up.
- I'm not going to back up.
Move, slide to the side,
slide to the side.
No, i asked you 22 times.
Sarah, don't buy it.
I'm trying to tell you,
you got to listen to me.
It's out in the open.
This is it?
You know what Jeff, i'm
going the use my advantage.
All right, so whose vote
are you going to steal?
I'm going to take Tai's.
All right, so what this means is
Tai, you will not vote,
and Sarah, when
you go up to vote, you will vote
twice with the piece of
parchment that is up there and
with the extra vote you have.
Good, i'm ready to vote.
Another crazy,
unpredictable Tribal Council.
Time to vote.
Culpepper, you're up.
I should have read the fine print.
I hope you go home today.
You just caused way
too much drama for me.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, once the votes are
read, the decision is final.
Person voted out will be
asked to leave the Tribal
Council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Tai.
That's two votes Tai.
Aubry.
Michaela.
Two votes Tai, one vote Aubry,
one vote Michaela.
Michala.
That's two votes Michaela,
two votes Tai, one vote Aubry.
Michaela.
That's three votes Michaela,
two votes Tai, one vote Aubry,
one vote left.
14th person voted out and
the seventh member of our jury:
Michaela, you need to
bring me your torch.
I don't see how that
made sense, Sarah,
but do you.
Good luck the rest of you all.
Michaela, the tribe has spoken.
Well, tonight's Tribal clearly,
a game changer,
and with only six
players and four days left
and very little trust, i can't wait
to see how it finishes.
Grab you torches, head back to
camp, good night.
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
Next time on Survivor...
The final six...
and the biggest game-changing
move of the season.
I got no problem putting him
out with his own idol.
It's the two-hour
season finale
and live reunion show
next Wednesday night.
I'm kind of bummed.
But i'm excited to made it to day 35.
Like, it's been a wild experience.
It's a compliment to be voted
off because people think they
can't beat you.
Don't hurt my feelings.
I wanted to win a million dollars.
Maybe i have to come back and
play a third time to get to the end.