>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," ZEKE STARTED A
REVOLT AGAINST ANDREA.
>> I'M INTERESTED IN SEEING
ANDREA GO HOME.
>> Jeff: BUT ANDREA FOUGHT
BACK.
>> HOW DID HE THINK THIS WAS
GOING THE TURN OUT WELL FOR HIM?
I AM FURIOUS.
>> Jeff: AMID THE CHAOS,
DEBBIE SAW HER OPPORTUNITY TO
STRIKE, AND SARAH WAS LEFT IN
THE MID-LE WITH MAJOR DECISION.
>> THEY'RE VOTING FOR OZZY.
>> WE HAVE TO VET OUT ZEKE.
>> IT'S A REAL TOUGH POSITION TO
BE IN.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
DEBBIE GOT HER WAY.
OZZY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD
>> Jeff: 11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, GUYS,
KINDLING?
GET A POT OF TEA GOING?
WHAT I WANTED TO
HAPPEN HAPPENED.
WE HAVE COMPLETE CONTROL OF THIS
GAME.
THERE IS A LINE DRAWN IN
CONCRETE.
NOW THAT WE HAVE SARAH, MYSELF,
SIERRA, TROYZAN, BRAD AND TAI,
WE ARE A SIX THAT ARE NOT GOING
TO BE BLOWN AWAY BY THE WIND OR
THE TIDE.
AND NOW WE'RE GOING TO PICK OFF
FIVE THAT ARE LEFT
SYSTEMATICALLY ONE BY ONE.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS A SHOCKER.
I WAS COMPLETELY OUT OF THE
LOOP.
I THOUGHT WE WERE TRYING TO GET
OUT ZEKE.
SO I GUESS I'M SCREWED.
I'M IN THE MINORITY.
ZEKE, DO YOU WANT THE TALK ABOUT
WHY I VOTED FOR YOU?
>> NO, THAT'S FINE.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND WHY.
>> I WANT TO HEAR?
>> I DON'T THINK YOU EVER HAD
ANY INTENTION OF TAKING ME VERY
DEEP IN THIS GAME, AND NEITHER
DID CIRIE.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME TO CONTINUE
TALKING.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> CLEARLY SOME PEOPLE TRUST ME.
>> NO, I MEAN, THEY TRUST YOU
FOR A COUPLE VOTES, BUT EVERYONE
HERE...
>> THIS CONVERSATION DOESN'T
SEEM PRODUCTIVE.
SO I'M GOING THE TALK TO OTHER
PEOPLE.
>> OBVIOUSLY I WAS NOT INCLUDED
IN THE MAJORITY VOTE, BUT SINCE
I KNOW ANDREA IS COMING AFTER
ME, I NEED PROTECTION.
SO I FEEL LIKE I DON'T HAVE ANY
CHOICE BUT TO STAY WITH THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON RIGHT NOW?
ANDREA SAYING WHAT SHE SAID, HER
TRUE COLORS ARE SHOWN.
SHE TELLS YOU, GOOD LUCK.
YOU'RE WITH US.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO TALK TO
THEM.
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, I HAD TO
PICK A SIDE, BUT I STILL WANT TO
WORK WITH ZEKE.
HAVING ZEKE OPENS UP OPTIONS FOR
ME.
I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO BE
OKAY.
I JUST COULDN'T FILL YOU IN ON
EVERYTHING, BECAUSE I NEED THEM
TO TRUST ME.
SO I'M SORRY I LEFT YOU OUT OF
IT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> AS MUCH AS PEOPLE WANT TO
THINK THE LINE IS DRAWN IN THE
SAND, WELL, I HATE THE BREAK IT
TO PEOPLE, BUT THE TIDE COMES UP
PRETTY QUICKLY.
AND THAT LINE GETS WASHED AWAY.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY THE GET TO
TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, WE'LL BE DIVIDED INTO
TWO TEAMS OF FIVE.
ON MY GO, ONE PERSON AT A TIME
WILL RACE THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES TO THE PLATFORM.
AND THE NEXT PERSON GOES.
ONCE ALL FIVE ARE AT THE END,
WITH FIVE DOWN, GRAB A GRAPPLING
HOOK AND USE IT TO RETRIEVE FIVE
RINGS FLOATING IN THE WATER.
FIRST TEAM TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNING TEAM WILL
BE TAKEN BY SEA PLANE TO TRULY
ONE OF THE MOST STUNNING ISLAND
CHAINS IN ALL OF FIJI.
YOU'LL ENJOY A PICNIC WITH
ENOUGH VARIETY FOR EVERYBODY.
WE'RE GOING TO DO A SCHOOLYARD
PICK, WHICH MEANS ONE PERSON
WILL NOT PARTICIPATE.
ONE PERSON WILL HAVE NO SHOT AT
THIS REWARD.
WE'RE GOING THE DRAW FOR
CAPTAINS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> OH, BOY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
CULPEPPER WAS CAPTAIN, CHOSE
DEBBIE, SIERRA, ANDREA AND
AUBRY.
CIRIE WAS A CAPTAIN, SHE CHOSE
ZEKE, SARAH, TROYZAN AND TAI.
MICHAELA WAS NOT PICKED.
MICHAELA, TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
HOW YOU FEELING?
LIKE THEY SHOULD HAVE PICKED ME.
>> Jeff: ARE THEY MISSING OUT
ON YOU?
>> YEAH, PEOPLE PICKING ALLIANCE
MEMBERS TO PLAY WITH INSTEAD OF
PLAYING TO WIN.
I DON'T GIVE A [BLEEPED] WHAT
HAPPENS.
I'M JUST WATCHING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR THE BIGGEST
REWARD OF THE SEASON, SURVIVORS
READY?
>> DON'T MAKE NO DAMN SENSE.
>> Jeff: GO!
IT IS CULPEPPER AND TAI.
GOT TO GET UP THAT LADDER AND
DOWN THE SLIDE.
>> GOT IT, BRAD.
>> Jeff: CULPEPPER IS OVER.
TAI IS OVER.
CULPEPPER HITS THE SECOND
OBSTACLE.
TAI RIGHT BEHIND.
>> YOU GOT IT, TAI.
>> Jeff: 25 DAYS OUT HERE, AS
ALWAYS THEY TAKE A TOLL.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: MICHAELA FRUSTRATED
THAT SHE WAS NOT CHOSEN AGAIN.
TRICKIEST PART, THE BALANCE
BEAM.
CULPEPPER IS ACROSS ON HIS FIRST
TRY.
TAI REACHES THE BEAM, HAVING
TROUBLE EVEN GETTING UP ON THE
PLATFORM.
ONCE YOU'RE BACK TO THE MAT, THE
NEXT PERSON CAN GO.
GO, BLUE!
SIERRA IN THE WATER NOW.
TAI IS NOW GOING THE CRAWL
ACROSS THE BEAM, WHICH TAKES A
LOT OF TIME.
SIERRA HARD DOWN THE SLIDE.
BLUE STARTING TO OPEN UP A LEAD
NOW.
TAI'S ACROSS.
STILL GOT TO GET TO THE FINISH
PLATFORM.
SIERRA IS GOING TO BE CLOSE TO
CATCHING TAI.
>> YOU GOT IT.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: AN SHE IS QUICKLY
ACROSS ON HER FIRST TRY.
HERE COMES TAI.
GO, ORANGE!
NOW TROYZAN IN THE WATER.
>> GOOD JOB, TROY.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN UP AND OVER
AND LOSES HIS SHORTS.
SIERRA, YOU GOT TO GET ON THAT
MAT.
GO, BLUE!
IT'S AUBRY IN THE WATER.
HERE COMES TROYZAN.
>> COME ON, TROY!
>> Jeff: TRYING TO MAKE UP
SOME TIME.
>> GOOD JOB, AUBRY.
>> Jeff: AUBRY GOES OVER
AWKWARDLY.
TROYZAN BARELY KEEPS THOSE
SHORTS UP.
25 DAYS AND VERY LITTLE FOOD
SHOWING.
TROYZAN'S ACROSS.
TROYZAN PICKING UP THE PACE.
BLUE STILL WITH A BIG LEAD.
>> GIVE ME HAND.
>> Jeff: GO, ORANGE!
IT'S NOW SARAH IN THE WATER FOR
ORANGE.
HERE GOES AUBRY.
HER FIRST SHOT AT THE BEAM.
>> LET'S GO, GIRL!
>> Jeff: AUBRY CAN'T THIS IT.
SHE FALLS.
GOT TO GO BACK.
THAT WILL OPEN THE DOOR FOR
ORANGE.
HERE COMES SARAH.
CAN SHE CLOSE UP SOME OF THIS
GAP?
AUBRY STILL STRUGGLING.
SARAH CAN TAKE THE LEAD FOR
ORANGE HERE.
>> YOU GOT IT, AUBRY.
TACK YOUR TIME, GIRL.
>> Jeff: SARAH PUTS ORANGE IN
THE LEAD.
>> RUN, RUN, RUN, RUN, RUN!
>> Jeff: AUBRY'S ACROSS.
GO, ORANGE!
>> SIT ON THE MAT.
NO GO, BLUE!
WE ARE NECK AND NECK.
DEBBIE GOES OVER.
>> COME ON, ZEKE.
>> Jeff: ZEKE REACHES THE
SECOND OBSTACLE.
>> NICE, ZEKE.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE RIGHT ON HIS
TAIL.
HUGE REWARD ON THE LINE.
THE MOST DIFFICULT PART OF THE
CHALLENGE NOW.
DEBBIE IS GOING THE CRAWL.
SCEEK'S GOING TO CRAWL, TOO.
DEBBIE'S ACROSS.
ZEKE CAN'T MAKE IT.
GO, BLUE!
>> YOU CAN DO THIS.
>> Jeff: ZEKE FEELING THE
PRESSURE NOW ZEKE GOES BACK IN.
ANDREA NOW CATCHING ZEKE.
>> GOOD JOB, ANDREA!
>> Jeff: ZEKE GOING TO GIVE IT
ANOTHER GO.
ANDREA HEADING TO THE BALANCE
BEAM NOW.
CAN SHE LAP ZEKE IN ANDREA
CALLING.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: ZEKE NOT GIVING UP.
AN DEGREE YES'S ACROSS.
ZEKE CLOSER.
GO, BLUE!
IT IS CULPEPPER NOW WITH THE
MATT.
CULPEPPER DIVES DOWN TO RETRIEVE
THE GRAPPLING HOOK.
ZEKE'S FINALLY ACROSS.
ORANGE IS BACK IN IT.
GO, CIRIE.
IT'S NOW CIRIE IN THE WATER WITH
A BELLY FLOP.
CULPEPPER HAS THE GRAPPLING
HOOK.
BLUE CAN START TRYING TO
RETRIEVE THEIR RINGS.
SIERRA WITH A TOSS.
WON'T DO.
>> COME ON, CIRIE.
>> Jeff: CIRIE IS DOWN THE
SLIDE NOW, MOVING SLOWLY IN THE
WATER.
SIERRA HOOKS THE FIRST RING FOR
BLUE.
CIRIE REACHES THAT SECOND
OBSTACLE, AND SHE'S CLEARLY
EXHAUSTED.
>> COME ON, CIRIE.
>> CIRIE, YOU CAN DO IT!
>> Jeff: SIERRA SNAGS A SECOND
RING FOR BLUE.
>> CIRIE, EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
>> I CAN'T GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: CIRIE NOT GIVING UP.
THERE IS NOWHERE TO HIDE.
"SURVIVOR" EXPOSES YOUR
STRENGTHS AND YOUR WEAKNESSES
AND CAN MAKE YOU FEEL VERY
VULNERABLE.
SIERRA SNAGS A THIRD RING FOR
BLUE.
>> NICE JOB.
>> Jeff: SIERRA GOING TO SWIM
OUT TO HELP CIRIE, WHICH MEANS
SHE WILL HAVE TO RUN THESE TWO
PARTS OF THE COURSE AGAIN.
SIERRA PUSHING CIRIE UP.
SIERRA CAN NOW FOLLOW BEHIND
HER.
>> YOU GOT IT, CIRIE.
>> Jeff: UNBELIEVABLE THAT
MICHAELA IS ENCOURAGING CIRIE
GIVEN SHE WASN'T CHOSEN.
>> I CAN DO THIS.
>> Jeff: .
>> Sarah: NOT GIVING UP ON HER
TEAMMATE.
CIRIE GOING TO GIVE THE BEAM A
SHOT NOW, EXHAUSTED, WHICH WILL
MAKE IT VERY DIFFICULT.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: BLUE VERY CLOSE TO
WINNING THIS.
CULPEPPER SNAGS THE FIFTH RING
FOR BLUE.
BLUE WINS REWARD.
CULPEPPER, SIERRA, DEBBIE, AN
DEGREE -- ANDREA AND AUBRY.
CIRIE, YOU ARE THE WOMAN WHO
OVER A DECADE AGO GOT UP OFF THE
COUCH TO COME TRY THIS GAME
"SURVIVOR."
THESE ARE THE MOMENTS YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR.
THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER, BUT WE
WILL STAY HERE WITH YOU IF YOU
WANT THE TRY TO CONQUER THIS.
>> YOU CAN DO IT, CIRIE.
>> COME ON, GIRL.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY SUPPORTING
YOU, CIRIE.
[CRYING]
>> LOOK AT ME.
KEEP BREATHING.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO GET
THIS, CIRIE.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU CAN DO IT, CIRIE.
>> I GOT IT.
>> THERE YOU GO, GIRL!
>> YES!
>> YOU DID IT!
YOU DID IT!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: THAT IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
ONE OF THE MOST POWERFUL MOMENTS
ON "SURVIVOR."
>> SHE DID IT.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, DEBBIE,
SIERRA, ANDREA, BRAD, HUGE
REWARD, BUT BEFORE WE GET TO
THAT, CIRIE, YOU DIDN'T GIVE UP,
AN YOU PULL IT OFF.
YOU DID IT.
WHAT IS THAT FEELING?
>> I HAVE THREE SONS, JUST TO
SHOW THEM THAT IT'S GOING TO BE
TOUGH IN LIFE, AS LONG AS YOU
TRY, EVEN IF YOU FAIL, I'M PROUD
OF THEM, AND GRATEFUL TO HAVE MY
TEAMMATES EVEN THOUGH THEY LOST
A GREAT REWARD, TO STILL SUPPORT
ME.
IT'S A LOT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WINNING TEAM HUGE REWARD,
THEY'LL HEAD OUT, SEA PLANE WILL
PICK YOU UP, DROP YOU, SWIM OUT.
TROYZAN, SARAH, ZEKE, CIRIE,
TAI, I GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
CIRIE, I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE YOU
SWIM.
I'M GOING TO BRING A BOAT IN FOR
YOU GUYS AND PICK UP MICHAELA ON
THE WAY OUT.
BRING A BOAT IN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
HEAD OUT.
YOU'RE GOING TO PICK UP
MICHAELA, TOO.
>> I'M LOOKING OVER AT MICHAELA,
AND I SEE A ROD UP PIECE OF
PAPER THAT SAYS "SECRET
ADVANTAGE."
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE MICHAELA
DIDN'T SEE THAT.
WITH "SURVIVOR" TO BE A GAME
CHANGER, YOU GOT TO BE LOOKING
CONSTANTLY FOR IDOLS AND CLUES,
AND NOW I HAVE A SECRET
ADVANTAGE.
SO THIS IS A HUGE WIN FOR ME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
LET'S GET A FIRE GOING.
>> ALTHOUGH WE LOST THE
CHALLENGE, IF I DIDN'T TRY TO
COMPLETE IT, I WOULD HAVE FELT
LIKE A COMPLETE FAILURE.
>> FOR ME TO NOT EVEN BE MAD
RIGHT NOW, THAT'S HOW PROUD I AM
OF YOU.
YOU WON'T FORGET THIS.
>> I JUST COULDN'T LET FEAR OR
EXHAUSTION STOP ME OR BEAT ME
THIS TIME.
>> YOUR KIDS WILL BE SO PROUD OF
YOU.
YOU CONQUERED IT.
YOU DID GOOD.
>> THANKS.
>> THIS IS A ROUGH GAME.
WE'RE ALL VYING FOR THE SAME
PRIZE, BUT WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO
IT, THE PEOPLE THAT ARE PLAYING
ARE REALLY GOOD PEOPLE, AND IT
SHOWED IN THE WAY THAT THEY
HELPED ME TODAY.
I ME THAT I'M NOT A CHALLENGE
BEAST, SO IF I'VE ALWAYS JUST
DONE WHAT WAS NECESSARY TO GET
ME BY.
I DIDN'T WANT TO EVER PUSH
FURTHER THAN THAT, BECAUSE IT
WASN'T REALLY NECESSARY.
BUT DOING THAT, I'VE LIMITED
MYSELF IN A LOT OF WAYS.
I'M NOT LETTING MY MIND TELL ME,
BE AFRAID, DON'T DO IT, JUST
GIVE UP.
I CAN DO IT.
AND IF I CAN'T WIN THIS GAME BY
WINNING CHALLENGES, I'M GOING TO
DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO TRY TO
SOLIDIFY MY RELATIONSHIP IN THE
GAME.
IT'S GOING TO BE WHAT'S
NECESSARY FOR ME TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> WHEN WE WEREN'T LEADING THE
CHALLENGE, I LOOKED OVER AT
MICHAELA, AND I SEE A SECRET
ADVANTAGE RIGHT AT HER FEET.
THAT'S CALLED ATTENTION TO
DETAIL.
I'M A POLICE OFFICER, BUT THE
NORMAL PERSON THAT DRIVES DOWN
THE ROAD WOULD NOT KNOW IF THE
CAR IN FRONT OF THEM'S
REGISTRATION TAGS ARE EXPIRED OR
NOT.
I WOULD.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'VE FOUND AN ADVANTAGE IN
THIS GAME.
YOU NOW HAVE THE RIGHT TO STEAL
A VOTE FROM SOMEONE AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL."
HOLY --
HAVING THIS ADVANTAGE OPENS UP
OPTIONS FOR ME.
I CAN COMPLETELY FLIP THE GAME.
"THIS VOTE IS NON-TRANSFERABLE
AND CANNOT BE STOLEN FROM YOU.
THE LAST TIME THIS EXTRA VOTE
CAN BE CAST IS WHEN THERE ARE
FIVE PEOPLE LEFT IN THE GAME."
IN THE PAST THESE EXTRA VOTES
HAVE NOT BEEN PLAYED CORRECTLY.
I'LL BE THE FIRST ONE TO PLAY
THIS VOTE CORRECTLY.
>> OH, MY GOD, WE'RE IN THE AIR.
THIS IS SO AMAZING.
>> OH, MY GOD, I LOVE AIRPLANES.
>> I AM A CAPTAIN IN THE CIVIL
AIR PATROL, THE AIR FORCE
AUXILIARY, SO I AM A HUGE FAN OF
AIRPLANES.
>> LOOK AT THE WATER, YOU GUYS.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>> GORGEOUS.
>> THEY DON'T GET TO BE IN
AIRPLANES AS MUCH AS I DO.
SO IT'S REALLY FUN THE WATCH
THEIR FACES.
I APPRECIATE IT BECAUSE IT'S
LOOKING AT THE WORLD THROUGH A
DIFFERENT PERSPECTIVE.
YOU SEE EVERYTHING IN A WHOLE
NEW LIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
>> THE BROWN EYE IS SO GOOD.
>> IT'S HEAVEN.
>> I LIKE COLE SLAW.
>> CHEER, YOU GUYS.
>> CHEERS.
>> THANK YOU FOR PICKING US.
>> "SURVIVOR" 101, DON'T EVER
TAKE YOUR WHOLE CONTINGENCY ON A
REWARD.
SO TROYZAN GOT LEFT OFF ON
PURPOSE BECAUSE I NEEDED THEM TO
STAY TO BE MY EYES AND EARS BACK
AT CAMP.
YOU GOT FIVE ON THE OUTSIDE, ALL
IT TAKES IS ONE OR TWO TO FLIP
FOR THEM TO HAVE THE NUMBERS.
I NEED SOME PEOPLE I CAN TRUST
SO THE FIVE DON'T GET TOGETHER
AND CONTAMINATE OUR SIX.
>> HOW HAS YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH ZEKE GOING?
>> WHAT'S ALL THAT DRAMA ABOUT?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S TRYING TO
HIDE ANYTHING.
>> HE TURNED ON ME FOR NO
REASON.
FOR NO REASON.
IT DIDN'T MAKE SENSE.
I THINK WITH ALL THESE DIFFERENT
PLAYERS, HE'S NOT THE CENTER OF
ATTENTION, SO HE DECIDED TO TAKE
IT OUT ON ME.
IT WAS A WEIRD POWER PLAY, AND
HE... I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN CONFIDENTLY SAY I DON'T
KNOW IF LIFE CAN GET ANY BETTER
THAN RIGHT NOW TODAY.
AT THIS POINT THERE ARE 11
PEOPLE IN THE GAME.
IT'S KIND OF GREAT TO WATCH THE
FIVE PEOPLE WHO ARE FREE AGENTS
GET MAD AT EACH OTHER AND FALL
APART WHEN WHAT THEY SHOULD BE
DOING IS BECOMING STRONG AND
TRYING THE TAKE THE SIX OUT.
SO I NOW FEEL LIKE I HAVE
NOBODY.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE SIX IS SUPER
TIGHT.
I DON'T SEE WHY ANYBODY SHOULD
BREAK, AND I DON'T THINK WE
WILL.
AS OF NOW, I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
THE DRIVER'S SEAT, AND IT FEELS
GREAT.
>> TELL ME THIS: WHO DO YOU
THINK'S RUNNING THE SHOW?
>> SIERRA.
>> AND BRAD?
>> YEAH.
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS THEY'RE
RUNNING THINGS, AND IF THEY
CONTINUE, THEY'RE GOING TO PICK
OFF WHO THEY WANT UNTIL THEY GET
TO YOU, ME, AND WHOEVER ELSE,
AND THEY'LL GO TO THE END WITH
WHOEVER THEY CHOOSE.
I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH SARAH
TRYING TO GET HER TO SEE THAT
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE ON THE
BOTTOM OF BRAD AND CIERA'S
LITTLE GROUP.
I THINK DEEP DOWN SHE REALIZES
THAT, BUT IT'S JUST LIKE ME ON
THE BALANCE BEAM.
SHE KNOWS THE BEST THING FOR HER
TO DO IS TO CROSS THAT BEAM, BUT
SHE'S AFRAID.
>> IF I'M IN THE FINAL THREE
WITH THEM, DO STAND A CHANCE?
>> 100% HONEST WITH YOU?
NO.
I'M JUST BEING STRAIGHT UP,
BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT SARAH,
THEY CAN COUNT ON HER AT THE
VOTE, BUT THEN THEY'RE GOING TO
SAY THEY CARRIED YOU.
SHE DIDN'T DO NOTHING, I DID
EVERYTHING.
WHEN THE JURY HEARS THAT...
>> RIGHT.
>> I PROMISED MYSELF COMING OUT
HERE THATLY NOT MAKE THE SAME
MISTAKE I MADE THE FIRST TIME I
PLAYED.
WHAT I DID IN CAGAYAN WAS LOOK
FOR THE SAFEST ROUTE I COULD GO.
I SAT BACK, DIDN'T MAKE THE
MOVES, AND LET OTHER PEOPLE MAKE
THE DECISIONS.
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
IT GOT ME ON THE JURY.
AND NOT EVEN CLOSE TO A SHOT AT
$1 MILLION.
>> OKAY.
THIS IS US TALKING REAL.
SO IF IT WAS YOU, ME, MICHAELA,
AUBRY, THERE'S FOUR.
>> MAYBE ZEKE WOULD GO.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> HE WOULD GO WHERE WE WENT I
THINK.
THAT'S FIVE.
BUT ARE WE DONE WITH ANDREA OR
WHAT?
IS IT REPAIRABLE WITH HER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> THERE ARE SMALL WINDOWS OF
OPPORTUNITIES IN THIS GAME, AND
IF YOU MISS THEM, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO WIN.
HOWEVER, THIS GAME IS ALL ABOUT
TIMING.
AND I'M NOT SURE THE TIMING IS
RIGHT TO MAKE A BIG MOVE.
BUT I'M READY FOR IT IN THE
EVENT THAT IT IS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY IDOL?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAI, GOT THE TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO PULL ON A ROPE,
BALANCING A WOBBLY TABLE.
YOU'LL THEN RACE TO STACK WOODEN
BLOCKS ON THAT TABLE ONE LETTER
AT A TIME SPELLING "IMMUNITY."
IF YOUR TABLE WOBBLES AND THE
STACK FALLS, YOU GOT THE START
OVER.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED SAFETY AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
LOSERS, AFTER 26 DAYS, SOMEONE
WILL BE VOTED OUT AND BECOME THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS AND GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY?
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THOSE EIGHT
LETTERS.
ONCE YOU HAVE THEM, TAKE THAT
FIRST LETTER AND RACE UP AND GET
STARTED.
YOU'RE SPELLING THE WORD
"IMMUNITY."
BUT YOU HAVE TO DO IT WHILE
BALANCING THOSE BLOCKS ON A VERY
WOBBLY TABLE.
EVERYBODY BUT TAI WORKING ON
THEIR FIRST LETTER.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT TAI IS
STRUGGLING WITH.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ALL ABOUT
PATIENCE.
FASTER YOU GO, THE MORE RISKS
YOU TAKE.
ANDREA COMING BACK WITH HER
SECOND LETTER.
THERE GOES TAI.
TAI IS NOW DOWN ON THE GROUND.
HE'S REALIZING HE HEADED OUT
WITHOUT A BLOCK.
HERE COMES DEBBIE AND SIERRA
WITH THEIR SECOND.
CULPEPPER HAS HIS SECOND.
ANDREA PLACES HER SECOND LETTER.
TAI STILL STRUGGLING TRYING TO
MAKE SURE HE'S SPELLING
"IMMUNITY" RIGHT.
>> I CAN'T THINK.
>> Jeff: 26 DAYS ON SURVIVOR
CAN REALLY TAKE ITS TOLL.
TROYZAN HAS TWO LETTERS.
IT IS ANDREA IN THE EARLY LEAD,
HEADING BACK WITH HER THIRD
LETTER.
AUBRY WITH TWO.
HERE COMES MICHAELA WITH HER
SECOND.
ZEKE AND CIRIE MOVING SLOWLY.
TAI FINALLY HAS HIS FIRST
LETTER.
ANDREA PLACES HER FOURTH LETTER.
SHE IS HALF-WAY THERE.
HERE COMES TROYZAN RIGHT BEHIND
WITH HIS FOURTH.
CULPEPPER COMING OUT WITH HIS
FOURTH.
A LOT OF PEOPLE RIGHT BEHIND
ANDREA, TROYZAN AND CULPEPPER.
IT IS STILL ANYBODY'S CHALLENGE
TO WIN.
THE TALLER THAT STACK GETS, THE
MORE DIFFICULT IT BECOMES TO
BALANCE.
HERE COMES ANDREA WITH HER FIFTH
LETTER.
STILL IN THE LEAD.
TROYZAN RIGHT BEHIND HER, STEPS
BEHIND HER WITH HIS FIFTH.
ANDREA BIG SWINGS.
SHE HAS NOT DROPPED YET.
SARAH DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP IN THIS
CHALLENGE BECAUSE PEOPLE CAN
DROP AT ANY TIME.
ANDREA REACHING FOR THAT SIXTH
BLOCK.
AND THAT'S WHERE IT CAN GET
DANGEROUS.
YOU REACH BACK WITH YOUR RIGHT
HAND AND YOUR LEFT HAND DROPS.
AUBRY DROPS.
SHE'S GOT THE START AGAIN.
RIGHT NOW IT'S ANDREA AND
TROYZAN, AND THEY ARE NECK AND
NECK.
TROYZAN HAS CAUGHT ANDREA.
BOTH COMING BACK WITH THEIR
SEVENTH LETTER.
TROYZAN PLACES HIS FIRST, THEN
ANDREA.
>> YOU GOT IT, TROYZAN.
TAKE YOUR TIME, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: THAT STACK IS SO
HIGH.
IT DOESN'T TAKE MUCH TO DROP.
ANDREA DROPS EVERYTHING.
THE DOOR IS OPEN FOR TROYZAN
NOW.
HE'S GOT TO GET OUT, PLACE THE
"I" AND THEN GET ALL THE WAY
BACK WITHOUT DROPPING.
CULL PEPPER THE ONLY ONE WHO
MIGHT CATCH HIM, BUT HE WOULD
HAVE TO PICK UP THE PACE.
AND CULPEPPER DROPS EVERYTHING.
>> YOU GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN CAN REALLY
TAKE HIS TIME NOBODY IS CLOSE
RIGHT NOW.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: IT WOULD BE TROYZAN'S
FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN
THIS SEASON.
GOT TO GET UP ON THAT PLATFORM.
AND HE DOES!
TROYZAN WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
TROYZAN, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, TROYZAN.
>> OH, IT LOOKS IS GOOD ON YOU,
BUDDY.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
STILL HAVE A SHOT AT WINNING IT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 26
DAYS, YOUR SHOT AT WINNING
"SURVIVOR" WILL ONCE AGAIN FALL
SHORT.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME, TENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT, THIRD MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, IT WON'T BE YOU.
CONGRATS.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU GUYS TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> LUCKILY ONE OF MY POWER
STICKS WON IMMUNITY.
WE HAVE THE POWER TO CHOOSE WHO
GOES HOME.
THE SMART MOVE IS TO CHOOSE
ANDREA.
ANDREA IS SOMEONE WHO NEEDS TO
GO HOME.
SHE'S A HUGE THREAT IN THIS
GAME.
SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> GOOD JOB, TROYZAN.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> WOW, THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
I GUESS ON A SCALE OF ONE TO
TEN, WAS AN 11 BECAUSE I WON.
AND I SURPRISED MYSELF.
NOW THERE'S A ALLIANCE OF SIX.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO
IS GOING HOME.
>> WE NEED TO GET MORE COCONUTS.
WE'VE BEEN GOING THROUGH IT SO
FAST.
>> I'LL GO.
>> I'LL GO WITH YOU.
>> ALL DAY.
>> IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
>> AT THIS POINT I THINK THE SIX
OF US ARE SO SICK OF MICHAELA
THAT IT'S VERY TEMPTING TO VOTE
HER OUT, HOWEVER, I REALLY THINK
WE HAVE A BIGGER THREAT TO DEAL
WITH FIRST.
>> MICHAELA.
>> NO, NO, NO.
HEAR ME OUT.
>> I WILL.
>> I CAN'T STAND HER, BUT...
>> I KNOW.
>> ANDREA IS TOO GOOD.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY WE LOSE OUR
SIX IS IF ANDREA IS WINNING AND
SHE MOVES IN AND WE HAVE TO EAT
ONE OF OUR OWN.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO VOTE OUT
MICHAELA BECAUSE SHE'S HIGHLY
ANNOYING AND JUST HAS A BAD
ATTITUDE.
>> SURE WE CAN'T JUST GET RID OF
HER TONIGHT?
>> NO.
NO, NO, NO.
WE GOT TO DO IT TOMORROW.
>> HOWEVER, I'M A TEAM PLAYER.
SO IF BRAD WANTS TO TAKE OUT
ANDREA, I'M COOL WITH IT.
SHE'S THE BIGGEST STRATEGIC
THREAT.
SHE'S THE BIGGEST PHYSICAL
AND YOU TAKE THE SHOT THE MOMENT
YOU GET THE OPPORTUNITY.
THE BEST TIME IS RIGHT NOW.
GO!
>> I THINK WE GO US SIX, ANDREA,
AND WE TELL EVERYBODY ELSE
MICHAELA.
>> JUST IN CASE SHE HAS AN IDOL.
>> DON'T WORRY.
EVERYBODY WANTS THE WORK WITH
US.
EVERYBODY.
>> THE PLAN WAS MADE WITHOUT
EVEN ASKING ME, AND I REALIZED
AT THAT POINT, I'M NOT HIGH IN
THE PECKING ORDER IN THAT
SIXESOME.
SO IT MIGHT BE TIME FOR ME TO
MAKE MY MOVE.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> DO YOU THINK GOING WITH BRAD
AND SIERRA IS THE RIGHT MOVE?
BECAUSE YOU CAN MAKE A MOVE.
>> I'M ALWAYS READY TO MAKE A
MOVE.
>> THE THING ABOUT THE POWER
ALLIANCE IS I UNDERSTAND WHERE I
STAND WITH THEM.
I JUST HAVE TO STAND WITH MY
TAIL TUCKED BETWEEN MY LEGS AND
KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT AND VOTE HOW
THEY WANT ME TO VOTE.
THAT'S NOT REALLY HOW I WANT THE
MAKE THIS GAME.
>> WE'RE GOING THE NEED ANDREA.
>> GREAT.
>> HOWEVER, TO DO THIS, WE GOT
TO BRING IN ANDREA, WHO I HAVE
NO DESIRE TO WORK WITH.
BUT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO DEAL
WITH IT, AT LEAST FOR ONE VOTE.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
MY PLAY IS.
>> WELL...
>> I HAVE NOTHING RIGHT NOW.
>> SO WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO
FROM HERE.
>> I WANTED TO WORK WITH YOU.
>> YES.
WE STILL CAN.
I'M STILL GOOD WITH YOU GUYS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> IT'S OBVIOUS THERE'S A POWER
ALLIANCE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M IN THE THAT ALLIANCE.
>> BUT YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM OF
THAT.
>> I KNOW.
DON'T YOU THINK WORKING WITH THE
ENEMY COULD BE A GOOD THING?
>> IT'S GREAT.
IF SARAH'S WILLING THE MAKE A
MOVE, I'M TOTALLY ON BOARD.
BECAUSE I KNOW I HAVE A HUGE
TARGET ON MY BACK.
NOW, AS FAR AS ZEKE, WILL I
TRUST HIM AGAIN FULLY, OF COURSE
NOT, BUT RIGHT NOW I'M LOOKING
FOR ANYONE THAT WANTS TO PLAY.
>> DAY 26.
I ONLY MADE IT TO DAY 19 LAST
TIME.
>> CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
>> THAT'S HUNTING.
>> I THINK FORMING A
RELATIONSHIP IS SUPER IMPORTANT
IN THIS GAME.
AND ME AND SARAH ARE REALLY
CLOSE.
WE'VE REALLY CONNECTED.
SO I STILL FEEL SUPER CONFIDENT
IN SARAH, AND I THINK IT WILL BE
ABSOLUTELY AMAZING IF WE WERE AT
THE FINAL THREE TOGETHER.
>> THIS IS MY BIG PICTURE.
I DON'T CARE HOW WE GET RID OF
THESE PEOPLE, BUT AT THE END I
THINK IT'S ME, YOU AND DEBBIE.
>> WE'RE THE FINAL THREE.
>> I HAD THIS PLAN THE BLIND
SIDE THE POWER GROUP, AND THEN
SIERRA PROPOSES THIS IDEA THAT
ME, HER AND DEBBIE ARE A FINAL
THREE.
AN I WAS LIKE, HOLY CRAP, MAYBE
I'M NOT ON THE BOTTOM OF THE SIX
AT ALL.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
DOESN'T THAT SOUND GREAT?
>> YEAH.
AS LONG AS NOBODY FLIPS.
>> THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE GAME, SARAH.
>> RIGHT.
>> BASICALLY THE SIX OF US
TONIGHT ARE GOING TO AGREE ON A
VOTE, SARAH DOESN'T TRUST YOU.
THAT'S HER PROBLEM.
I DO.
BUT MICHAELA IS GOING HOME.
I TOLD AUBRY TO VOTE FOR
MICHAELA IN CASE ANDREA PULLS AN
IDOL, THEN MICHAELA GOES HOME,
PLUS I TOLD HER SIERRA DOESN'T
TRUST HER BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH
SHE SCREWED ME OVER THE LAST
TIME I PLAYED, I WANT AUBRY TO
THINK I'M WITH HER.
IF YOU WORK WITH ME, IF YOU
CONTINUE TO SHOW ME THAT I CAN
TRUST YOU, THERE'S A WAY IN.
>> OKAY.
>> IT WOULD BE STUPID TO.
>> AND YOU'RE NOT STUPID.
>> DOWN THE LINE I MAY NEED TO
USE AUBRY.
TO DO THAT I NEED HER TO THINK
I'M HER BEST FRIEND, AND I THINK
IT'S WORKING.
>> OKAY.
SO HERE'S THE DEAL, THEY'RE
TRYING TO COME AT YOU.
DEBBIE'S LIKE, YOU'RE SAFE,
AUBRY, AND THE WAY SHE SAID IT,
I'M LIKE, OKAY.
>> THEY'RE SO COCKY.
THEY'RE SO COCKY.
>> DEBBIE REMINDS ME NOW AS SHE
DID AROUND THE TIME I VOTED HER
OUT OF "SURVIVOR."
SHE STARTS TO GET COCKY AND THEN
MAKES MISTAKES.
>> DEBBIE'S LIKE, SARAH WANTS TO
CUT YOUR THROAT, I DON'T TRUST
HER, AUBRY, YOU'RE THE ONE I
WANT IN.
>> WHERE DOES THAT COME FROM?
>> THAT REALLY PISSES ME OFF.
I HATE LYING.
>> SHE'S A GRADE-A LIAR.
>> SO I WAS THINKING, I MIGHT
WANT TO SIT IN THE FINAL THREE
WITH DEBBIE, BUT NOW SHE'S
SPREADING LIES ABOUT ME.
>> WE HAVE YOUR BACK.
I SWEAR TO YOU...
>> AT THIS POINT, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
IF I CAN CONTROL DEBBIE, COULD
BE IN THE TOP SIX FOR SURE
POTENTIALLY IN THE FINAL THREE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THE PREDICAMENT
I'M IN?
>> YES.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO LEAVE
SAFETY FOR THE UNKNOWN.
HOWEVER, I SWORE THE MYSELF
COMING OUT HERE I'M GOING THE
MAKE BIG MOVES.
WHATEVER I DO, IT'S GOING TO
DETERMINE HOW FAR I GO IN THIS
GAME.
I'M GOING TO DECIDE AT TRIBAL.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
HALI AND OZZY VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO AS OUR JURY STARTS TO GROW,
THIS GAME GETS MORE COMPLICATED,
BECAUSE NOW YOU HAVE TO FIND A
WAY THE USE TRIBAL AS A WAY TO
START MAKING YOUR CASE.
SO WITH THAT IN MIND, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE REWARD CHALLENGE.
CIRIE, YOU ARE OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE OCEAN STUCK, AND THEN
SOMETHING AMAZING HAPPENED.
YOU DECIDED, I'M NOT COMING IN
UNTIL I FINISH THIS.
NOW THAT YOU'VE HAD A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME TO THINK BACK, WHAT WAS
THAT ABOUT?
>> THE FACT THAT I COULDN'T MAKE
IT ON THE PLATFORM WAS
HUMILIATING I GUESS.
AND THE FACT THAT ALL OF THESE
GUYS WERE WILLING TO HELP ME
INSPIRED ME MORE TO NOT WANT TO
END ON A FAILURE.
>> Jeff: SARAH, YOU WENT FROM
FRUSTRATED TRIBE MAID TO ANOTHER
HUMAN SEEING SOMEBODY TRYING
THEIR BEST AND FAILING, AND YOU
DOVE IN.
>> WATCHING CIRIE STRUGGLE OUT
THERE, I DON'T KNOW HOW ANYBODY
COULD LEAVE ANYBODY BEHIND LIKE
THAT.
BUT IT CAME DOWN TO HER
DECIDING, I CAN DO SOMETHING
THAT I THOUGHT I COULDN'T DO,
AND SHE PROVED IT TO HERSELF AND
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT STORY.
ANDREA, IT'S DEVASTATION THAT
THE ONE THING YOU NEED WALKING
INTO THIS GAME WAS WITHIN
MOMENTS OF BEING YOURS.
>> I MEAN, I'M ESPECIALLY
VULNERABLE TONIGHT, BECAUSE I'M
ON THE BOTTOM.
SO THAT CHALLENGE WAS SO
IMPORTANT, AND THOSE BLOCKS
FALLING COULD BE THE REASON I GO
HOME TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WHAT MAKES YOU
CERTAIN YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM?
>> AFTER THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, I FOUND MYSELF OUT OF
THE LOOP, SO DID A COUPLE OTHER
PEOPLE, AND THERE'S A VERY CLEAR
MAJORITY ALLIANCE AND A VERY
CLEAR BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: ZEKE, YOU ARE SHAKING
YOUR HEAD AS SHE WAS EXPLAINING
THAT.
>> OH, YEAH, TAI AND DEBBIE AND
BRAD AND SIERRA AND TROYZAN AND
SARAH, THE SIX OF THEM GOT UP,
WALKED INTO THE WOODS, AND I
GUESS THEY HAD MADE THEIR
DECISION ABOUT WHO WAS TO GO
HOME.
>> Jeff: DEBBIE, YOU'RE
SMILING VERY KNOWINGLY.
>> WELL, I WAS IN THAT SIX, AND
WE CAME TO A UNANIMOUS DECISION
THROUGH DIALOGUE, RESPECT,
EVERYBODY TAKES A TURN,
EVERYBODY SPEAKS.
IT TOOK TEN MINUTES.
>> Jeff: AND ANDREA, THAT
BRINGS US BACK TO YOU.
THIS IS YOUR FEAR, THAT THE SIX
HAVE DECIDED IT'S YOU.
>> SO THE WORD ON THE STREET WAS
IT WAS MICHAELA, BUT IF THE
ALLIANCE IS SMART, THEY WOULD
LEAK FALSE INFORMATION.
ALSO IT FELT LIKE EVERYONE WAS
CHEERING AS SOON AS MY BLOCKS
FELL AT THE CHALLENGE, SO THERE
ARE A COUPLE CLUES THAT IT'S
POSSIBLY NOT MICHAELA AND IT'S
MAYBE ME.
>> Jeff: SARAH, WHAT'S IT LIKE
TO BE PART OF THE GROUP THAT'S
BEING SINGLED OUT AS THE ONES IN
CHARGE MAKING THE DECISIONS?
>> WELL, "SURVIVOR" IS ALL ABOUT
BEING ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE
NUMBERS.
YOU CAN SEE CLEAR FRUSTRATION
FROM THE PEOPLE WHO ARE NOT ON
THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE NUMBERS,
BUT CAN YOU BLAME US FOR FEELING
SECURE?
>> Jeff: DEBBIE, IS THAT A
FAIR STATEMENT, THAT PERCEPTION
IS WHAT DICTATES WHETHER PEOPLE
ARE HAPPY ABOUT WAY THE GAME IS
BEING PLAYED OR FRUSTRATED?
>> IT IS INCONCEIVABLE FOR
ANYBODY TO CONCLUDE AT THIS
POINT THAT THERE IS ANYTHING
OTHER THAN A STRONG SIX SITTING
HERE TONIGHT.
SO IS PERCEPTION REALITY?
WELL, IT IS.
WE'VE GOT A SIX THAT HAS A VERY
ACCURATE PERCEPTION OF
THEMSELVES, AND WE JUST CLICK.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN, HOW DOES THE
SIX MANAGE TO STAY TOGETHER WITH
EVERYBODY BELIEVING THEY'RE AT
THE TOP WHEN THAT IS IMPOSSIBLE?
>> IF YOU'RE SMART ENOUGH TO GET
YOUR DAMN SELF TO SIX, TAKE IT.
I MEAN, THAT'S A HUGE PLUS.
COME ON.
I MEAN, ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN
AFTER THAT.
IT CHANGES ALL THE TIME.
>> Jeff: SO ZEKE, TROYZAN IS
SAYING, WORRY ABOUT SIX WHEN YOU
GET THERE, BUT YOU GOT TO GET
THERE.
>> THAT'S VERY TRUE.
I LIKE TO SAY THAT THE DECK
RESHUFFLES AFTER SOMEONE IS
VOTED OUT.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT I'M COUNTING
ON TONIGHT, IS FOR THE DECK TO
RESHUFFLE & WHO KNOWS WHO IS
GOING TO BE UPSET WITHIN
THE SIX TOMORROW AND MAYBE
THAT'S MYMOMENT TO STRETCH.
>> Jeff: SARAH, INTERESTING
WAY THAT ZEKE DESCRIBED IT.
>> SURE, PEOPLE COULD AGREE WITH
THAT, BUT LIKE TROYZAN SAID, IF
YOU ARE SIX, MAYBE YOU CAN GET
TO FIVE, TO FOUR, TO THREE.
SO I THINK IT'S WISHFUL THINKING
TO SAY THAT THE DECK RESHUFFLES.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA, YOU HAD A
REACTION TO THAT
>> SHE'S BASICALLY SAYING, Y'ALL
DON'T GO NO SHOT.
YOU CAN SIT HERE KEEP WATCHING
US WIN THIS GAME OR YOU CAN MAKE
A MOVE.
SO I DIDN'T GET NO MARCH NOTICE.
THEY THINK I'M ABOUT THE MARCH
MYSELF OUT.
I RATHER MARCH OUT SWING,
TELLING THE TRUTH, LIKE I ALWAYS
DO, THAN SIT HERE LIKE I DON'T
SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
WE ALL KNOW WHO IS RUNNING THE
SHOW, AND YOU CAN EITHER DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT WHILE YOU
HAVE NUMBERS, OR YOU CAN SIT
HERE LOOKING LIKE BOO BOO THE
FOOL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CULPEPPER, YOU'RE UP.
>> ACTUALLY IN OUR SIX, THERE
ARE NO PEOPLE WHO GIVE ORDERS
AND IN PEOPLE WHO TAKE ORDERS.
IT'S CALLED A DEMOCRACY.
>> YOU THINK YOU ARE RUNNING THE
SHOW, BUT I HOPE YOU'RE IN FOR A
REALLY RUDE AWAKENING.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND NOW WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED THE LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ANDREA.
DEBBIE.
ANDREA.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ANDREA.
DEBBIE.
TWO VOTES ANDREA, TWO VOTES
ANDREA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ANDREA.
DEBBIE.
THREE VOTES ANDREA, THREE VOTES
ANDREA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES ANDREA.
DEBBIE.
TIED AGAIN.
FOUR VOTES ANDREA, FOUR VOTES
DEBBIE.
ANDREA.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES ANDREA.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
FIVE VOTES ANDREA, FIVE VOTES
DEBBIE.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY:
DEBBIE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DEBBIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED ON THE
SHOCKED REACTIONS, MAYBE THE
DECK WAS RESHUFFLED.
GRAB YOU TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," THE TIDE HAS TURNED.
>> GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY.
>> SIX OF THEM ARE THINKING, WE
GOTCHA.
>> Jeff: BUT THE LINE IN THE
SAND...
>> YOU'D BE ON BOARD TO VOTE FOR
WHOEVER?
>> LET'S MAKE A BIGGER MOVE
HERE.
>> Jeff: IS WASHED AWAY.
>> ON THE NEXT VOTE WE
COSOMETHING INTERESTING.
>> NOW THE GAME HAS BEEN BROKEN
OPEN.
>> THAT WAS ABSOLUTELY A BLIND
SIDE.
THAT ONE I DID NOT SEE COMING.
I THOUGHT I HAD A LOCK, STOCK
AND BARREL SOLID SIX.
20 MINUTES AGO I WOULD HAVE TOLD
YOU THAT SIX IS NOT GOING THE
BREAK, BUT WHAT SURPRISES ME IS
THAT ANYBODY WOULD FLIP, AND NOW
IS GOING TO BE PROBABLY IN A
WORSE POSITION.
I'M STUNNED.