>> Jeff: OVER 17 YEARS AND 33
SEASONS, THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR"
HAS EVOLVED.
THESE ARE THE PLAYERS THAT
CHANGED THE GAME.
>> COMING INTO THIS GAME, I
ALREADY KNOW I'M A HUGE THREAT.
I CREATED THE SPY SHACK.
I FOUND THE SPECIAL IDOL.
I VOLTED OUT MY CLOSEST ALLY.
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> JUST WHEN YOU THINK YOU SEEN
IT ALL, YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHING
YET.
>> IN "SURVIVOR" PHILIPPINES AND
SURVIVOR CARAMOAN, I SWUNG FOR
THE FENCES MAKING SPLASHY,
FIREWORK-TYPE MOVES.
THIS IS THE OTHER IMMUNITY IDOL,
I'M GIVING IT TO EDDIE.
>> Jeff: THE LOOKS ON FACES.
>> I HAVE A REPUTATION TO
UPHOLD.
I'M GOING TO KEEP MAKING BIG
MOVES.
I'M SO EXCITED.
I CAN'T STOP BOUNCING IN MY
SEAT.
>> I'M THE ONLY PERSON TO EVER
WIN "SURVIVOR" TWO TIMES.
IT ONE JUST LUCK.
I'M AGAINST YOU, RUSSELL.
THAT'S WHAT I KNOW HOW TO DO,
MAKE IT TO DAY 39 AND NOT GET
VOTED OFF.
THE QUEEN STAYS QUEEN.
ADIOS.
>> I AM A BONA FIDE EX-COUCH
POTATO THAT SAW THIS GAME AND
LOVED IT.
IF YOU WERE TO GIVE UP IMMUNITY,
I WOULD BELIEVE YOU.
I'M A GANGSTER WITH A SOMETIME,
LIKE A WOLF IN SHEEP'S CLOTHING.
>> I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
SORRY.
I MADE IT TO THE END.
THE ONLY NEXT STEP FOR ME IS TO
WIN.
>> ANYBODY WHO WATCHED
"SURVIVOR" KAOH RONG WOULD NOVI
STRENGTH LIKE A GYMNAST AND A
TENACITY LIKE A GIANT SQUID.
I WANT HIM GONE.
>> OKAY.
>> WHEN I COME INTO THIS GAME,
IT'S GO FOR BROKE.
THIS IS THE KENTUCKY DERBY, THE
PREAKNESS AND THE BELMONT STAKES
ALL AT ONCE, SO YOU BETTER GO
FOR IT.
>> Jeff: THEY'LL BATTLE IT OUT
ON THE ISLANDS OF FIJI AS
"SURVIVOR" KICKS OFF ITS
500th EPISODE.
>> WE'VE ALL CHANGED THE GAME,
SO TO WIN THIS GAME, YOU HAVE TO
GO BIG OR GO HOME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS "SURVIVOR:
GAME CHANGERS," 39 DAYS, 20
PEOPLE, ONE SURVIVOR.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: WELCOME TO THE
34th SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
YOU WERE EACH HAND-PICKED
BECAUSE YOU SHARE ONE THING IN
COMMON: YOU HAVE PROVEN YOU ARE
WILLING THE MAKE THE KIND OF
MOVES THAT WILL CHANGE THE GAME.
SOME OF YOU MAKE BOLD MOVES.
SOME OF YOU MAKE QUIET MOVES.
SOME OF YOU HAVE MADE MOVES THAT
WERE SO SUCCESSFUL THEY'RE
LEGENDARY.
AND OTHERS HAVE MADE MOVES THAT
WERE A DISASTER AND GOT YOU
VOTED OUT.
BUT THAT'S THE NATURE OF A GAME
IN WHICH THERE IS ONLY ONE
WINNER.
MOST MOVES WON'T WORK.
IT'S HAVING THE GUTS TO MAKE THE
MOVE THAT GOT YOU HERE.
THIS SEASON IS CALLED "SURVIVOR:
GAME CHANGERS"
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
OZZY, HOW MUCH TIME WHEN YOU'RE
NOT PLAYING "SURVIVOR" IS SPENT
THINKING ABOUT THE MISTAKES I'VE
MADE?
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVE SOME CRAZY
DREAM, WAKE UP SWEATING WITH
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS SLIPPING
THROUGH MY FINGERS, BUT I ALSO
HAVE AMAZING MEN RISK AND
SOMETHING I WOULD NEVER GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: J.T., DOES IT MATTER
THAT THERE ARE HANDFUL OF
WINNERS HERE, THAT YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY PERSON THAT'S WON THE
$1 MILLION?
>> I THINK IT'S GREAT I'M NOT
THE ONLY WINNER HERE, BUT I
DON'T THINK IT MATTERS AT ALL.
SANDRA IS NOT GOING TO BE THE
ONLY TWO-TIME WINNER, I THINK.
>> Jeff: WOW.
CIRIE, IF J.T. IS RIGHT, YOU
HAVE NO SHOT.
>> WHO SAYS J.T. IS RIGHT?
>> Jeff: ZEKE, FRESH OFF
PLAYING IN MILLENNIALS VS. GEN
X, DO YOU FEEL SOME PRESSURE
KNOWING, WOW, I AM WITH A GROUP
OF PEOPLE WHO KNOW HOW TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR"?
>> YEAH, JEFF, I MEAN, AS A FAN,
I'M GEEKING OUT QUITE A BIT
RIGHT NOW, AND I THINK, YEAH,
YOU WONDER IF YOU BELONG ON THIS
BOAT, AND I INTEND TO PROVE THAT
I DO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET IT GOING.
THOSE OF YOU WITH AN ORANGE
BUFF, HALI, CALEB, TROYZAN,
SANDRA, AUBRY, TONY, CALEB,
VARNER AND MALCOLM, YOU'RE THE
MANA TRIBE.
THOSE OF YOU WITH A BLUE BUFF,
DEBBIE, TAI, ANDREA, CIRIE,
CULPEPPER, J.T., OZZY AND ZEKE,
YOU'RE NUKU.
THIS SEASON MAYBE MORE THAN ANY
OTHER, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
BE AWARE AND WILLING TO DO
ANYTHING, ANY TIME, TO ANYBODY
TO MOVE YOU FURTHER AHEAD IN
THIS GAME.
THIS BOAT IS LOADED WITH
SUPPLIES.
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT THE GRAB
EVERYTHING YOU CAN TO TAKE BACK
TO CAMP.
THERE IS ALSO A RAFT FOR EACH
TRIBE.
THERE IS MAP TO YOUR NEW HOME.
THIS IS THE SAME WAY WE STARTED
"SURVIVOR" IN OUR VERY FIRST
SEASON, WITH ONE TWIST.
YOUR FIRST GAME-CHANGING
OPPORTUNITY.
THERE IS A LIFE RING IN THE
WATER.
ON EITHER SIDE OF THAT RING,
THERE ARE TWO SETS OF
COLOR-CODED ROPES.
FIRST PERSON TO UNTIE THEIR
KNOTS WILL RELEASE A MASSIVE
TOOLKIT FOR THEIR TRIBE.
IT'S YOUR FIRST ADVANTAGE IN THE
GAME.
I CAN'T WAIT THE SEE WHAT THIS
SEASON BRINGS.
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS" IS ON.
>> GO.
>> Jeff: AND IT IS QUICKLY
CHAOTIC.
>> UNTIE THE RAFT, UNTIE THE
RAFT.
>> Jeff: AND WHO IS GOING IN
THE WATER?
IT'S GOING TO BE OZZY FOR NUKU.
HE'S OUT QUICKLY.
AND NOBODY IS GOING AFTER HIM.
UNBELIEVABLE.
A MASSIVE TOOLKIT AND CLEARLY
NOBODY FROM THE MANA TRIBE EVEN
CARES.
>> I GUESS WE'RE NOT GOING TO
HAVE A TOOLKIT.
>> NO.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT COMES WITH PLAYING THIS
GAME IS YOU NOW KNOW WHICH ITEMS
ACTUALLY HAVE VALUE.
>> GUYS, GOOD JOB.
>> KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING, KEEP
GOING.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> Jeff: CALEB NEW FINALLY IN
THE WATER FOR THE MANA TRIBE.
THOSE ARE OUR CHICKENS.
>> Jeff: PANDEMONIUM.
OZZY DIVING DOWN AGAIN.
CALEB HAS REACHED THE KNOT.
CAN HE MAKE UP THE TIME?
THIS IS WHAT YOU EXPECT ON A
SEASON CALLED "GAME CHANGERS."
30 SECONDS LEFT.
30 SECONDS.
OZZY HAS THE TOOLKIT FOR HIS
TRIBE.
>> TOSS IT.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO GET OVER,
MALCOLM, THIS IS IT.
LET'S GO, VARNER.
OZZY GOT THE TOOLKIT FOR NUKU.
>> I'LL BUILD US A MANSION WITH
THAT GUY.
>> Jeff: AND THEY HAVE THE
CHICKENS.
THIS IS MASSIVE HEAD START FOR
ONE TRIBE.
FOR ONE OF YOU THIS IS THE
BEGINNING OF A $1 MILLION
ADVENTURE.
GOOD LUCK.
>> IT'S "SURVIVOR: GAME
CHANGERS," SO YOU CAN'T JUST SIT
AROUND AND HOPE TO GET TO THE
END.
THE STAKES HAVE BEEN RAISED.
THIS IS GOING TO BE AN EPIC
SEASON.
SO GAME ON.
READY?
PADDLE.
JUST GO.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> SEEING THE FLAG WAS LAKE DEÀA
VU.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHEN YOU REALLY
FEEL LIKE YOUR ON "SURVIVOR"?
>> WHERE'S THE WATER?
>> HERE'S THE FLAG.
EVERYONE HERE IS A SNAKE IN THE
GRASS, AND I'M LIKE THE COBRA
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW IS SITTING
UNDERNEATH YOU, AND THEN ALL OF
A SUDDEN IT STRIKES AND YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT HIT YOU.
>> FIELD TRIP?
>> FIELD TRIP.
>> BAMBOO, BAMBOO.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
THIS SEASON I BELIEVE MY BEST
SHOT AT WINNING IS GOING TO BE
LITERALLY SCHMOOZING UP TO
EVERYBODY HERE AND MAKING THEM
FEEL AWESOME.
>> IS YOUR NAME TOYS FOR TROYZAN
>> I THINK IT IS.
>> IS THAT YOUR REAL NAME?
>> ANY TIME SOMEBODY STARTS
TALKING TO ME I'M GOING TO GO
LIKE THIS BECAUSE I CAN'T
CONTROL MY FACIAL EXPRESSIONS.
IT IS VERY DIFFICULT FOR ME TO
LIE.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF HUGE BAMBOO.
>> I IMAGINE WE'RE DOING IT LIKE
RIGHT HERE.
>> YEAH, LOOK AT THOSE LOW ONES
RIGHT THERE, YOU COULD...
>> OH, THESE TWO?
>> HEY, YOU GUYS DO NICE, NICE.
I'M OUT.
I'M LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
>> WHERE'S HE GOING IN
>> HE SAID, I'M OUT, I'M LOOKING
FOR THE IDOL.
>> HE'S SERIOUS, THOUGH.
>> I BET HE IS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO VOTE HIM OFF
FIRST.
>> SHOULD WE LET HIM GO?
>> YEAH, HE'S MAKING HIMSELF A
TARGET.
>> I THOUGHT THEY WOULD ALL BE
CHASING ME.
>> IF HE FINDS IT, AT LEAST
WE'LL KNOW HE HAS IT.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN THAT BIG BAD
MANIAC SCREAMS, I'M GOING FOR
THE IDOL.
>> YOU ALL GO KEEP AN EYE ON HIM
SO WE KNOW IF HE GETS IT.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO CALL A SEASON
ACCOUNT GAME CHANGERS" I THINK
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT FOR ME TO
GET A FOOTHOLD IN THE LION'S DEN
AND NOT BE PULLING A TONY WHO IS
FREAKING OUT EVERYONE AT CAMP
WITH ALL OF HIS IDOL HUNTING.
>> I JUST WANTED TO WALK AROUND
AND LOOK AT THE SCENERY AND THE
LANDSCAPE.
OH, MAN, THEY'RE REALLY NOT
COMING.
I WAS GOING TO RATTLE THEM A
LITTLE BIT.
SO I WAS THINKING THEY WERE ALL
GOING TO CHASE ME, AND IF THEY
WERE CHASING, I WOULD STOP AND
SAY, I'M MESSING YOU.
BUT THEY WEREN'T CHASING ME, SO
I SAID, LET ME TAKE ADVANTAGE
AND START LOOKING FOR THE IDOL
FOR SURE, YOU KNOW.
>> HE WASN'T GOING NOWHERE.
NOBODY WAS GOING TO VOTE HIS ASS
OFF OR NOTHING.
EVERYONE IS ALREADY TALKING
ABOUT WE CAN'T TRUST TONY, LOOK
AT WHAT HE'S DOING.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WE CAN HURRY UP
AND TAKE TONY OUT.
WE NEED HIM.
HE'S A PHYSICAL PLAYER.
WE NEED STRENGTH.
>> YOU GOT EVERYBODY PARANOID.
>> WHO THEY PISSED OFF AT, NOT
ME?
>> THEY'RE LIKE, SOMEONE GO
WATCH HIM.
OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU GUYS WATCH ME WHILE WE
LOOK FOR THE IDOL.
>> I LIKE TONEY.
HE'S GOT HIGH SPIRITS.
DAY ONE, PARANOIA, STIRRING UP
TROUBLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GRAB SOME BAMBOO AND GO
BACK.
>> ALL I CAN SAY, THAT'S TONY
FOR YOU, YOU WOULDN'T EXPECT
ANYTHING LESS, BUT HE'S GOT A
BIG TARGET ON HIS BACK.
>> GREAT JOB, MAN.
AWESOME JOB.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
>> I'M HERE THE SLAY EVERYONE
AND THE WIN A MILLION DOLLARS,
RIGHT?
BUT I HAVE LIKE THE GREATEST
TRIBE EVER.
I GOT THE GODDESS CIRIE.
>> CIRIE.
I'VE GOT OZZY.
I'VE GOT J.T.
I'M PLAYING SURROUNDED BY GAME
CHANGERS.
PART OF ME HAS TO KEEP SLAPPING
MYSELF AND BEING LIKE, YOU'RE
OUT HERE, TOO.
IF YOU BELONG OUT HERE, YOU NEED
TO ACT LIKE IT.
SO I WANT TO GET MY HANDS DIRTY.
I WANT THE LATHER MYSELF IN THE
BLOOD OF MY ENEMY, RIGHT?
LIKE I WANT TO CHANGE THE GAME.
THAT'S WHAT I LOVE ABOUT
"SURVIVOR."
>> LOOK AT THAT.
LOOK, A GOAT.
>> THERE ARE THREE GOATS OVER
HERE.
THREE GOATS.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN GET THAT
GOAT.
>> NO WAY.
>> THERE'S IN WAY.
YOU KNOW HOW FAST THEY GO.
>> LISTEN, LISTEN, I THINK TO
KILL A GOAT WE'D HAVE TO KILL
TAI.
>> THERE YOU GO.
SWEET.
>> WHAT'S IN THERE?
WE GOT TONS OF NAILS AND
HAMMERS.
WE CAN HAMMER AND NAIL.
WE GOT ALL THE TOOLS.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I PLAYED "SURVIVOR" CAGAYAN.
I HAVE A ME UNTIL NAL SOCIAL
GAME.
I'M A POLICE OFFICER.
SO I CAN READ PEOPLE, AND WITH A
SEASON CALLED "GAME CHANGERS," I
FEEL LIKE SOMEBODY WILL GET
ANXIOUS AND FEEL AS THOUGH THEY
NEED TO MAKE A MOVE, WHICH WILL
PUT A TARGET ON THEIR BACK, AND
THEN I'M GOING TO BE THE SILENT
ASSASSIN.
>> FINDING THE SECRET ADVANTAGE
IS JUST GIVING ME THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO DO SOMETHING BIG.
AND IT'S EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED
TO DO WITH MY GAME THIS TIME
AROUND.
CONGRATULATION, YOU FOUND THE
LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
WITH THIS NOTE IN YOUR
POSSESSION, YOU ARE GUARANTEED
IMMUNITY, BUT IT COMES WITH A
TWIST.
YOU MAY ONLY USE IT WHEN THERE
ARE 13 PEOPLE LEFT IN THE GAME
OR WHEN THERE ARE SIX PEOPLE
LEFT IN THE GAME, AND IF YOU ARE
VOTED OUT, YOU MUST WILL THIS
ADVANTAGE TO ANOTHER PLAYER
STILL IN THE GAME FROM ANY
TRIBE.
THE LEGACY ADVANTAGE OPENS UP A
LOT OF DOORS FOR ME.
I'M ALREADY A STRONG COMPETITOR.
I KNOW WHAT IT TAKES TO DO IT
SOCIALLY.
I'M A COWGIRL.
LIKE MY JOB IS WORKING WITH GUYS
EVERY DAY OF MY LIFE.
MY COMFORT IS HANGING OUT WITH
THE GUY, SO I GOT TO KEEP THEM
CLOSE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE ON MY TRIBE.
>> LISTEN, I HAVE TO PLAY WITH
PEOPLE LIKE YOURSELF.
>> HAVE YOU TALK TO THE OZZY AT
ALL?
>> HE'S GREAT.
IN BLOOD VS. WATER, IT WAS SO
DIFFICULT.
I HAD MY WIFE MONICA ON ONE SIDE
AND I HAD MY SIDE.
I WAS VERY AGGRESSIVE.
THIS TIME I'M TRYING TO LET
EVERYBODY COME TO ME, AND I FIND
MYSELF SAYING, W.W.M.D., WHAT
WOULD MONICA DO.
AND I PROMISE YOU, SHE WOULD BE
SLOW PLAYING THIS RIGHT NOW.
I GOT A LONG WAY TO GO, BUT I
THINK I'M OFF ON THE RIGHT FOOT.
>> OBVIOUSLY I WANT TO BE A TEAM
PLAYER, BUT YOU DO ALSO HAVE TO
HAVE WITHIN THAT TRIBE YOUR CORE
NUMBERS.
SURE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> FOR SURE.
>> I THINK MY COMPETITION IS
FIERCE.
IN "SURVIVOR," BIG MOVES ALWAYS
REQUIRE BIG RISKS.
A LOT OF TIMES THEY'RE NOT
SUCCESSFUL, BUT IF YOU DON'T
MAKE THEM, YOUR CHANCES OF
WINNING THE GAME ARE VERY SMALL.
>> THE ONLY ONE THAT I REALLY
GET A LITTLE BIT SCARED OF
HONESTLY IS CIRIE.
>> I DO, TOO.
>> CIRIE AND I PLAYED TOGETHER
ON FANS VERSUS FAVORITES, AND
CIRIE HELPED TO GET ME OUT.
I'M NOT SURE IF I CAN TRUST HER.
SO THIS TIME AROUND AS A GAME
CHANGER, I NEED TO BE THE MASTER
OF BLIND SIDES.
IF WE LOSE AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, CIRIE IS GOING TO GO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A HELL OF A
HOUSE WHEN YOU FINISH.
I THINK IT'S GOOD THE SAY YOU
CAN PUT THE PAST ASIDE, BUT I
KNEW IT WAS A PROBLEM WHEN I SAW
IVY ON THE SAME TRIBE AS ME.
I DIDN'T START THE BLIND SIDE.
I PARTICIPATED.
BUT THAT WAS EIGHT YEARS OR
SOMETHING.
GET OVER IT.
>> SO WE GOOD, OZZY?
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
YOU COMING IN HERE WITH BAGGAGE?
>> WHAT WAS IT?
EIGHT YEARS AGO?
>> I WANT A CLEAN SLATE.
I'M JUST SEEING WHERE EVERYBODY
IS.
IT FELT LIKE WE WERE SOLID, SO
MAYBE EVERYBODY WILL REMAIN
CALM.
>> I KNOW YOU GUYS HAVE
DIFFERENCES.
>> WELL, THE THING IS WITH ME
AND CIRIE, IT REALLY WASN'T
ANYTHING BECAUSE SHE WASN'T...
SHE JUST WENT ALONG WITH WHAT MY
ALLIANCE DECIDED TO DO, SO I
CAN'T HOLD THAT AGAINST HER, BUT
SHE'S JUST NOT A PHYSICAL
PLAYER.
SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE A REALLY
PHYSICAL PLAYER.
>> I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH
J.T., OZZY, HE KEEP BRINGING
CIRIE UP.
HE AND CIRIE HAVE HISTORY.
HE DOESN'T TRUST CIRIE, BUT I
LIKE CIRIE, SO I DON'T WANT TO
GET CAUGHT IN SOMETHING THAT
SUDDENLY THEY SAY CIRIE HAVE TO
GO.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
>> I'M NOT WORRIED.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE TO
WORRY.
>> SO WHEN YOU TALKED TO OZZY
THIS MORNING, YOU GOT A FEELING
THAT I STILL NEED TO WORK IT OUT
WITH HIM?
THAT PAUSE IS GIVING ME CONCERN.
>> IT'S JUST A VIBE.
I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS... IF
YOU TALK TO HIM, THAT'S WHY I'M
TRYING TO CONFER WITH YOU GUYS.
>> I KNOW, BUT WHEN YOU TALKED
TO HIM, YOU STILL GOT A VIBE
THAT THERE'S UNRESOLVED ISSUES
IS WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
SO JUST HEARING THE WAY OZZY IS
FEELING ABOUT ME, I KNOW THAT
IT'S GOING THE TAKE SOMETHING
MORE THAN JUST A CONVERSATION WE
HAD.
LISTEN, THE WAR IS GOING TO
START ANYWAY.
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE IF
THE WAR STARTS TONIGHT OR
TOMORROW?
THERE WILL BE BLOOD EITHER WAY.
>> ANYBODY NEED A REFILL OF
WATER?
I'M GOING TO GO GET SYSTEM
WATER.
>> PLEASE.
>> ANYBODY?
WATER?
>>WE'RE ALL GAME CHANGERS HERE,
WE KNOW WHAT THE DEAL IS.
SO WHEN ALL THESE BUMS ARE
TALKING, TONY IS ALWAYS WORKING.
I WENT TO DIG A BUNKER NEXT TO
THE WATER WELL SO I CAN GO UNDER
THE GROUND WHERE NOBODY IS GOING
TO EXPECT IT, BECAUSE THEY'RE
GOING TO BE LOOKING FOR SPY
SHACKS.
THEY AIN'T GOING TO BE LOOKING
FOR AN UNDERGROUND BUNKER.
THE BEST QUALITY I HAVE FOR THIS
GAME IS WHAT'S NEEDED TO WIN
THIS GAME.
AND THAT'S ADAPTABILITY.
IF THEY GET FOOLED AGAIN, THAT'S
SHAME ON THEM.
THIS GAME IS NOT WORTH IT IF YOU
LOSE.
I WOULD NEVER DO IT IF I DIDN'T
THINK I COULD WIN.
>> TONY IS THE BIGGEST THREAT
HERE.
HE'S PROBABLY THE NUMBER-ONE
GAME CHANGER, AND LOOK, I
ALREADY CAUGHT HIM DIGGING IN
PLACES LIKE THE IDOL WEASEL.
HE'S JUST OUT OF CONTROL.
>> WHAT'S UP, TONY?
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHT, BRO?
AND THEN HE ACTED LIKE, HEY,
BRO, WHAT'S UP?
I'M LIKE, I DIDN'T CONFRONT HIM,
BUT HE HAS... WHEN HE'S GUILTY,
HE HAS A FANTASTIC GUILTY FACE.
BUT I GOT TO BE VERY CAREFUL
WITH A GUY LIKE THAT.
>> RIGHT IN THERE DIGGING LIKE A
CRAZY MAN.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE FOUND
SOMETHING, BUT THAT'S ALL DUG
OUT.
>> YOU WOULD NEED A CLUE TO DIG
THERE.
HOW DID HE GET A CLUE?
>> HE'S DIGGING IN THE MIDDLE OF
NOWHERE.
>> WHAT DO WE EXPECT?
APPARENTLY TROY CAUGHT TONY
DIGGING IN THE IDOL IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
>> I PLAYED "SURVIVOR" A FEW
TIMES WITH WINNERS.
I PLAYED WITH TINA.
AND I THINK I HAVE THAT
ADVANTAGE WHERE I KIND OF KNOW
HOW TO NAVIGATE THAT.
>> TONY I GUARANTEE YOU IS
LOOKING.
TONY'S PLAYED ONE TIME AND HE'S
WON.
SO HE'S C&MING IN EXTREMELY
ARROGANT AND HE'S ALREADY PRETTY
CLOSE.
AND I AM SO EXCITED TO TEACH HIM
A LITTLE LESSON.
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
TONY.
LIKE JUST LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
>> YOU SAW THAT?
>> JUST NOW.
THE OPTIONS ARE GET RID OF HIM
OR GET RID OF CALEB.
>> I DON'T THINK WE CAN GET RID
OF CALEB, HE'S TOO STRONG
CHALLENGE-WISE.
>> I'M THINKING IF WE'RE IFFY
ABOUT TONY HAVING AN IDOL, WE
SHOULD GET RID OF HIS RIGHT-HAND
MAN.
>> IT'S OPEN SEASON.
NAMES ARE STARTING TO BE THROWN
OUT, CALEB, TONY.
THOSE ARE TWO PEOPLE I DON'T
WANT TO GO AT ALL, BUT I KNOW
THE PERSON THROWING THESE NAMES
OUT IS CIERA.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> CIERA SEEMS TO BE VERY GAMEY.
THAT'S MY GUT.
>> STRATEGICALLY FOR MY GAME,
I'M WHERE I WANT TO BE.
EVERYONE IS TALKING TO ME, BUT
IF CIERA IS GOING TO PUSH US OUT
OF ZEN MODE ON THIS TRIBE, IT
MAKES IT EASY TO TARGET HER
EARLY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOU'RE GOING TO RACE
TO A RAFT AND PADDLE OUT TO A
PLATFORM.
ONE PERSON WILL THEN SWIM OUT
THE RETRIEVE A SET OF KEYS.
YOU'LL ALL MAKE YOUR WAY OVER A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES BACK TO THE
BEACH.
YOU'LL DIG UP TWO BAGS OF PUZZLE
PIECES.
YOU'LL THEN USE THE KEYS TO
UNLOCK THE CHEST, WHICH WILL
RELEASE THE THIRD BAG OF PIECES.
YOU'LL USE THE PIECES INSIDE THE
BAGS TO FORM A SHIP'S WHEEL
PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO SOLVE THEIR
PUZZLE AND RAISE THEIR FLAG WINS
IMMUNITY.
THIS IS THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> OH, WOW.
>> WOW.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: WITH THIS IN YOUR
POSSESSION, YOU CANNOT BE VOTED
OUT.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
GAME CHANGERS."
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLIPGHT.
THERE IS A TWIST TO THIS SEASON.
THIS SEASON IN THE EVENT OF A
TIE VOTE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THERE WILL BE NO REVOTE.
WE WILL GO IMMEDIATELY TO A
TIEBREAKER.
THAT MEANS IF THERE IS A TIE,
YOU'LL HAVE AN OPEN DISCUSSION
AT TRIBAL IN FROM THE OF
EVERYBODY, AND IF YOU CAN
UNANIMOUSLY AGREE ON WHICH OF
THE TRIBE MEMBERS WHO ARE TIED
TO SEND HOME, THEY GO HOME.
IF YOU CAN'T UNANIMOUSLY AGREE,
THE PEOPLE WHO WERE TIED ARE NOW
SAFE, EVERYBODY ELSE DRAWS ROCKS
AND SOMEBODY GOES HOME.
ANDREW, WHAT IMPACT INITIALLY DO
YOU SEE THIS HAVING?
>> IT WORRIES ME BECAUSE THERE
MIGHT BE AN IDOL AND LET'S SPLIT
THE VOTE, BUT NOW SPLITTING THE
VOTE IS VERY DANGEROUS BECAUSE
YOU COULD BE THE ONE PULLING THE
ROCK.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
GIVE YOU GUYS A MINUTE THE
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD AND IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SEVEN FROM EACH TRIBE ON THE
RAFT FOR THE FIRST LEG.
GOT TO PADDLE OUT TO THAT
PLATFORM.
THESE RAFTS ARE HEAVY.
ONCE YOU'RE IN THE WATER, START
PADDLING.
LET'S GO.
EVERYBODY ON.
>> GO, GUYS GO.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET EVERYBODY ON
THE PLATFORM BEFORE THE SWIMMER
CAN GO.
>> RIGHT SIDE, RIGHT SIDE.
>> Jeff: NUKU VERY CLOSE TO
THEIR PLATFORM.
MANA IS NOW AT THAT PLATFORM.
EVERYBODY ON THAT PLATFORM.
OZZY'S IN THE WATER.
HALI IN THE WATER FOR MANA.
>> GREAT JOB, HALI, COME ON.
>> Jeff: IT'S OZZY AND HALI
RIGHT NOW IN A SHOWDOWN GOING
FOR THOSE KEYS.
>> LET'S GO, OZZY.
>> GOOD JOB, HALI.
>> LET'S GO, HALI.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT ON HIM.
YES!
>> Jeff: OZZY HAS HIS UNTIED.
HE'S HEADING BACK.
HALI HAS HERS UNTIED.
SHE'S HEADING BACK.
>> YEAH, OZZY.
>> Jeff: BIG STAKES OUT OF THE
GET.
BRAGGING RIGHTS AND YOU DO NOT
WANT TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
OZZY'S BACK.
UP AND OVER.
HERE GOES NUKU.
>> COME ON, HALI.
>> NICE JOB.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> Jeff: GO, MANA.
EVERYBODY OVER.
NUKU NOW WORKING ON THAT BARREL.
IT IS A LONG SWIM, A LOT OF
ADRENALINE.
NUKU TOSSING PEOPLE OVER.
THERE GOES MICHAELA ON HER OWN
IS MICHAELA AND AUBRY DOING ALL
OF THE WORK FOR MANA.
NUKU NOW HITS THE NET.
STILL WITH THE LEAD.
MANA HAS ONE PERSON LEFT.
THERE HE IS.
LET'S GO, MANA.
GOT TO GET EVERYBODY TO THE MAT.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> NICE JOB.
>> Jeff: GO.
START DIGGING, TWO PEOPLE.
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> Jeff: GO, MANA, GO.
>> AWESOME JOB, NOKOMIS.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
TWO BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES.
J.T. HAS THE FIRST BAG FOR NUKU.
CULPEPPER GOING TO GET OUT FOR
NUKU.
CIERA COMING IN FOR CULL PEPPER.
MANA WILL NOW SWITCH OUT.
LAST TIME CALEB DID THIS, HE WAS
EVACUATED FROM EXHAUSTION.
TAI HAS THE SECOND BAG.
GO!
>> OZZY.
>> Jeff: OZZY HANDS THE KEYS
TO DEBBIE, NOW WORKING ON THOSE
LOCKS.
CALEB HAS FIRST BAG.
HE'S GOING TO SWAP OUT.
MALCOLM BACK IN WITH TONY.
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: THEY'VE GOT IT.
LET'S GO.
MANA, YOU'RE BACK IN THIS.
DEBBIE STILL WORKING ON THOSE
LOCKS.
THAT HAS OPENED THE DOOR FOR
MANA NOW.
>> WE'RE RIGHT IN IT.
>> I GOT ONE.
>> THAT A BOY, JEFF.
>> Jeff: VARNER QUICKLY GETS
FIRST LOCK FOR MANA, AND JUST
LIKE THAT, MANA IS NOW IN THE
LEAD.
>> DON'T PANIC.
STAY CALM.
>> Jeff: NUKU HAD A HUGE HEAD
START.
>> DEBBIE FEELING THE PRESSURE.
>> Jeff: VARNER STARTING TO
PANIC.
>> I AIN'T PANICKING.
DON'T THROW THAT [BLEEPED] ON
ME.
I'M GOOD.
>> Jeff: NUKU HAS THEIR SECOND
LOCK OPEN.
NUKU BACK IN THE LEAD NOW.
START WORKING ON THE PUZ.
IT IS CIRIE AND ZEKE WORKING ON
THE PUZZLE FOR NUKU.
VARNER STILL TRYING TO OPEN THAT
SECOND LOCK FOR MANA.
FIRST PART OF THIS PUZZLE IS THE
OUTER RING OF THE SHIP'S WHEEL.
>> GOT IT.
>> GOT IT?
>> Jeff: VARNER HAS THE SECOND
LOCK.
THERE YOU GO.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
IT IS CIRIE AND ZEKE.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
>> Jeff: AND SIERRA AND
SANDRA.
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THIS.
CIRIE AND ZEKE HAD A BIT OF A
LEAD, BUT SIERRA AND SANDRA
QUICKLY CAUGHT UP.
SIERRA AND SANDRA HAVE BEEN
BEHIND AND HAVE HAD TO CATCH UP
THIS ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
CAN THEY DO IT NOW WHEN IT
REALLY MATTERS?
ZEKE AND CIRIE HAVE FIRST
SECTION.
SIERRA AND SANDRA HAVE THEIR
FIRST SECTION.
ONCE AGAIN WE'RE DEAD EVEN IN
THIS FIRST CHALLENGE.
NOW WORKING ON THE SPOKES, THE
SECOND SECTION OF THE SHIP'S
WHEEL.
SIERRA HAS DONE THIS PUZZLE ONCE
BEFORE AGAINST HER MOM AND LOST.
CAN SHE PULL IT OFF THIS TIME?
ZEKE AND CIRIE MAKING PROGRESS
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
YOU DON'T KNOW UNTIL YOU'RE
COMPLETELY FINISHED IF ALL THE
PIECE GOSS WHERE THEY NEED TO
BE.
ZEKE AND CIRIE THINK THEY HAVE
IT.
WILL IT FIT?
IS IT RIGHT?
>> YES, IT WILL.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> Jeff: IT'S NOT RIGHT.
SOMETHING'S OFF.
THEY HAVE TO GO BACK TO THE
DRAWING BOARD AGAIN.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR ONCE AGAIN
FOR MANA.
>> COME ON, HURRY.
>> THAT'S IT.
THIS IS IT.
>> Jeff: SAN DR. AND SIERRA
THINK THEY HAVE FIGURED IT OUT
NOW.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> YES, HERE.
>> Jeff: ZEKE AND CIRIE THINK
THEY FIGURED IT OUT NOW.
SUDDENLY BOTH PAIRS HAVE SOME
MOMENTUM.
ARE THEY RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: AND THEY ARE, ZEKE
AND CIRIE ARE MOVING ON TO THE
THIRD AND FINAL BAG.
THESE ARE THE HANDLES.
THIS WILL FINISH IT RIGHT HERE.
SAN DR. AND SIERRA NOW HAVE TO
MOVE QUICKLY.
IT WON'T TAKE MUCH TIME FOR THIS
LAST BIT.
>> YOU GOT IT.
GREAT JOB.
>> Jeff: CIRIE HAS THE LAST
HANDLE.
SANDRA GIVING IT A GO.
NUKU HAS IT.
THIS WILL DO IT.
>> SPIN THAT WHEEL, YEAH!
>> Jeff: REWARD AND IMMUNITY
FOR NUKU, AND THE FIRST
CHALLENGE IN "SURVIVOR: GAME
CHANGERS."
NUKU, CONGRATULATIONS.
OUT OF THE GATE IMMUNITY IS
YOURS.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: AND FLINT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: NICE CATCH, DEBBIE.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, MANA, LIKE IT OR NOT,
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
GAME CHANGERS."
GRAB YOU STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> THIS IS A PUZZLE I HAD DONE
BEFORE, AND I LOST THE PUZZLE TO
MY MOM, AND I TOTALLY LET
EVERYBODY DOWN.
AND IT'S JUST A CRAPPY FEELING
TO LOSE THE SAME PUZZLE TWO
TIMES.
I'M NERVOUS, YOU KNOW, I DON'T
WANT TO BE FIRST VOTE OUT ON THE
GAME-CHANGING SEASON.
>> THAT WAS A DOOZY.
LOSING THE FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE IS NOTHING NEW TO ME.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO ME EVERY TIME I'VE EVER
PLAYED.
>> ANYBODY REFILL?
MALCOLM, YOU NEED A REFILL?
>> NOBODY WANTS TO BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT.
TO EVEN HAVE TO GO TO THE FIRST
TRIBAL IS AWFUL F AWFUL.
AND EVEN THOUGH TONY IS A SNAKE,
NEW GUT IS TELLING ME TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG.
>> THIS SUCKS, BRO.
I'M SO PISSED RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION WHO WE DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH AND SAY WE HAVE
TO GET RID OF THE WEAKEST
THREAT.
>> I FEEL LIKE SIERRA.
>> SHE'S THE ONLY PERSON THAT'S
THROWN NAMES OUT.
>> THAT'S THE ONLY PERSON WHO
HAS SAID ANYBODY'S NAME.
>> WHOSE NAME IN.
>> YOU TWO.
>> THE VOTE IS BETWEEN THE TWO
OF YOU BECAUSE YOU WERE DIGGING
FOR AN IDOL.
>> WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT GAME
CHANGING, YOU TALK ABOUT SIERRA.
SHE VOTED HER MOTHER OUT.
THAT SAYS A LOT.
SHE'S FLIP-FLOPPED.
SHE'S FORCED TIES.
SIERRA IS LIT.
>> SANDRA?
>> I'M GOING TO DO WHAT YOU ALL
WANT?
>> WHOSE NAMES ARE OUT THERE AND
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I FEEL?
>> MINE.
>> WHO SAID YOU?
>> THE ONLY ONE THROWING NAMES
OUT IS SIERRA.
>> ONE PERSON.
FOR NO REASON.
>> HERE SHE COMES.
>> NO, HANG OUT, HANG OUT.
>> SAY MICHAELA.
SAY MICHAELA.
>> THIS SEASON THERE'S A LITTLE
TWIST HERE.
IN THE EVENT OF A TIE, THERE
WILL NOT BE A REVOTE, AND WE'LL
DRAW ROCKS RIGHT THEN AND THERE.
FOR ME IT'S A HUGE ADVANTAGE
BECAUSE I PLAY FEARLESSLY, AND
I'VE BEEN THERE.
SO I FEEL LIKE I WAS JUST HANDED
AN ADVANTAGE, BUT I KNOW I
DIDN'T PERFORM AT THAT
CHALLENGE, SO THE PRESSURE IS ON
FOR ME BECAUSE SOMETIMES EARLY
ON PEOPLE WANT THE KEEP THE
TRIBE STRONG.
>> WHAT DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
MICHAELA?
>> I THINK SHE'S
CONFRONTATIONAL.
>> I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> SHE'S THE OUTCAST.
>> EVERYBODY MAJORITY WANTS TO
GET RID OF MICHAELA.
I'M FINE WITH THAT.
AT THIS POINT I'D BE FINE WITH
ANYBODY BUT MYSELF.
>> WE'RE CHECKING YOUR
TEMPERATURE.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> WELL, THEY SAID CIERA.
>> GOING ENTER TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT IS AN EASY VOTE.
THE NAME CIERA CAME UP.
I'M PERFECTLY FINE WITH THAT.
THAT'S WHO I WANTED TO GO HOME
FIRST.
>> I'M STAYING UNDER THE SHADE.
I FEEL LIKE MY BACK IS BAKING.
>> BUT WHO DOES SHE THINK IS
GOING HOME?
WHAT?
>> SHE VOTING FOR ME?
>> YEAH.
>> REALLY?
>> OKAY.
>> SHE'S THE ONLY ONE.
>> I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> WHO DOES SIERRA THINK
EVERYBODY ELSE IS VOTING FOR?
AND THAT FOOL SAYS ME.
>> DOES SHE THINK THAT ALL NINE
PEOPLE ARE VOTING FOR ME?
MAN, WHY DID YOU ALL DO THAT?
>> SHE WANTED YOU SO WE SAID WE
AGREED.
>> I REACTED IN A WAY I
SHOULDN'T HAVE.
SO I'M NOT TRYING TO LET THEM
SEE HOW BIG MICHAELA CAN BE, BUT
SHE CAN'T CONTAIN GREATNESS, SO
IT CAME OUT.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> DO YOU FEEL OKAY?
>> NO.
WHO WANTS THEIR NAME...
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, HONESTLY, IT
MIGHT CHANGE TO SOMEBODY ELSE IN
THE COURSE OF THE AFTERNOON.
>> YEAH, I THINK IT NEEDS TO
CHANGE TO SOMEONE ELSE IN THE
COURSE OF THE AFTERNOON.
THAT WOULD BE IDEAL FOR MICHAELA
BRADSHAW.
>> MICHAELA IS DEFINITELY A
TRICKY ONE FOR US AS A TRIBE.
SHE HAS A BIT OF A HOT STREAK,
AND IF YOU IGNITE THAT THE WRONG
WAY, THE WHOLE PLACE IS BURNING
DOWN.
>> WOW, SHE'S SCARY, BREE.
>>FOR REAL, THAT'S SCARY.
MICHAELA IS FREAKING OUT.
>> I FIGURED MICHAELA WOULD BE
COOL.
LIKE I DIDN'T THINK SHE WOULD
BLOW UP ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH.
>> PEOPLE LIKE, THAT THEY GOT TO
GO.
>> THE PLAN IS CIERA IS GOING TO
GO HOME, BUT THE ONLY ISSUE IS
THE MINUTE THEY TOLD MICHAELA IT
WAS GOING TO BE CIERA BUT THAT
WE WERE GOING TO TELSEY SI IT
WAS MICHAELA, IT WAS A DIFFERENT
STORY.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> MICHAELA WAS POUTING, MAKING
THESE FACES LIKE SHE WAS PISSED
OFF.
>> YOU ALL TALK ABOUT ANYTHING
SINCE I BEEN GONE?
>> WHEN PUSH COMES TO SHOVE, WE
COULD EASILY TAKE OUT CIERA SOME
OTHER TIME.
IF MICHAELA IS SOMEBODY THAT WE
NEED THE TAKE OUT, WE NEED TO
TAKE HER OUT QUICK, FAST, AND IN
A HURRY.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH, DIP
IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THE
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
TONY, WHEN YOU HAVE A SEASON
CALLED GAME CHANGERS, THERE'S A
BIT OF AN EXPECTATION.
>> YEAH, IT'S A HUGE DIFFERENCE.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO DO MY
CRAZINESS AND THIS AND THAT.
THEY PUT THE BRAKES ON THAT REAL
QUICK.
IT'S NOT WHAT IT WAS IN CAGAYAN.
THESE ARE GAME CHANGERS, AND I'M
LIKE WHOA.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, DID YOU SEE
TONY RACING AROUND TRYING TO
PUSH THE PACE?
>> LITERALLY.
WE WERE HERE FOR ALL OF TEN
SECOND, AND HE SAID, I'M GOING
FOR THE ITEM AND TOOK OFF INTO
THE WOODS.
I'M SURE IF I FIND IT IN THE
FIRST TEN SECOND, GAME CHANGER,
BUT THERE HAS BEEN AN ELEMENT OF
WE'RE ALL REALLY ENJOYING
OURSELVES AND TAKING IT LIKE A
GAME.
>> Jeff: AUBRY, HOW BIG A PART
DO YOU THINK IMPRESSIONS FROM
THE PAST WILL PLAY IN THIS GAME?
>> I THINK WE'RE ALL LOOKING AT
EACH OTHER SAYING, OKAY, THIS IS
A PERSON I SAW ON TV AND TRYING
THE FIGURE OUT IF THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE THOUGHT THEY WERE OR IF
THEY MIGHT BE A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
>> Jeff: CALEB, YOU'RE IN AN
UNUSUAL SITUATION.
NOBODY REALLY KNOWS WHAT KIND OF
PLAYER YOU ARE STRATEGICALLY
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T GET A CHANCE
TO SHOW THEM.
>> YEAH, HONESTLY, JEFF, I THINK
IT CAN HELP ME BECAUSE THEY
DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF.
AND I CAN LOOK AT THE OTHER
SIDE, AND IT MAY FRIGHTEN THEM A
LITTLE BIT.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA, WHAT
IMPRESSION DO YOU THINK THEY
HAVE OF YOU OUT OF THE GATE?
>> I HOPE I'VE MADE A GREAT
IMPRESSION, BUT I'M NOT PLAYING
WITH PEOPLE THAT WANT TO BE MY
BEST FRIEND, LIKE SOMEBODY'S GOT
TO GO.
AND I THINK IT WOULD BE PUNKISH
FOR THE FIRST VOTE ON A SEASON
CALLED GAME CHANGERS TO BE TOO
EASY OF ONE.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, THAT'S THE
KIND OF ANSWER A VERY
EXPERIENCED PLAYER GIVES.
>> JEFF, MICHAELA HAS BEEN A
PLEASURE.
I THINK THE GROUP LOVES HER.
I CARE FOR HER.
YOU KNOW, LIKE FROM THE LITTLE
TIME THAT WE HAVE BEEN WITH HER,
SHE IS A PLEASURE.
>> Jeff: BUT SAUNDRA, IT SEEMS
IF YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE THE
EASY VOTE, IT WOULD BE YOU, THE
TWO-TIME WINNER.
>> EVERYBODY LOVES ME, JEFF,
WHAT CAN I TELL YOU?
I AM THE PERFECT PERSON TO GO TO
THE END WITH BECAUSE WHO WILL
GIVE ME ANOTHER $1 MILLION?
AND THESE PEOPLE ARE PLAYING FOR
THE SECOND, THE THIRD, THE
FOURTH TIME.
HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU HAVE TO
PLAY TO GET YOUR MILLION
DOLLARS?
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT, DO IT
NOW AND DO IT WITH SANDRA?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: SO VARNER, WHAT
HAPPENED TODAY WHEN YOU GOT BACK
TO CAMP AFTER THE CHALLENGE?
>> WELL, A GROUP TOOK OFF TO THE
WELL TO DISCUSS WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO, HOW ARE WE GOING TO
DO IT.
SOMEBODY COMES DOWN THE WAY,
THEN YOU SEE ANOTHER GROUP TAKE
OFF DOWN THE BEACH, AND IT'S
LIKE, OH, HELL, WHAT'S HAPPENING
NOW?
IS THIS WHAT WE JUST TALKED
ABOUT?
IT'S VERY UNSETTLING.
>> Jeff: SO HALI, WHAT WILL
THE CRITERIA BE FOR TONIGHT'S
VOLT?
>> I THINK TONIGHT'S VOTE HAS
TWO COMPONENTS.
WE HAVE A CHALLENGES WEAKNESS
WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT, WE WANT
THE KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG.
AND THEN ALSO PEOPLE GOT THEIR
FEATHERS RUFFLED BY SOME TALK
THAT WENT AROUND, AND I THINK
LOOSE LIPS SINK SHIPS.
I THINK THAT'S PART OF IT, TOO.
CIERA, WHY THE BIG REACTION?
>> I WASN'T SURE WHAT HALI WAS
TALKING ABOUT?
AM I IN THE MAJORITY?
WAIT A SECOND.
BUT I'M STILL GOING TO GO WITH
WHAT I BELIEVE TO BE THE
MAJORITY.
>> Jeff: SO MICHAELA, WE'RE
ABOUT TO VOTE.
ARE YOU NERVOUS THAT YOU MIGHT
BE THE MARK TONIGHT?
>> I'LL BE SURPRISED IF I GET
OUT OF HERE WITHOUT ONE VOTE
AGAINST ME.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, IF YOU HAD TO
PUT A CHAPTER TITLE ON THESE
FIRST THREE DAY, WHAT WOULD YOU
CALL IT?
>> THE UNKNOWN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CALEB, YOU'RE UP.
>> BYE, FELICIA.
>> A QUEEN STAYS QUEEN AND
ADIOS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE MICHAELA.
CIERA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CIERA.
ONE VOTE MICHAELA.
CIERA.
FOUR VOTES CIERA.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES CIERA, ONE
VOTE MICHAELA.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS,"
CIERA.
THAT'S SIX.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
CIERA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, EVERYONE.
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
WELL, NO MATTER HOW MUCH THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR" EVOLVES, ONE
THING ALWAYS REMAINS TRUE --
BLIND SIDES NEVER GO OUT OF
STYLE.
THE ONLY GOOD THING TO COME OUT
OF COMING THE TRIBAL COUNCIL,
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> JEFF, I WEAR GLASSES NOW.
>> LAST NIGHT'S TRIBAL WAS THE
SMOOTHEST TRIBAL I CAN REMEMBER.
IT WAS 9-1 UNANIMOUS.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
RIGHT NOW EVERYONE IS WAITING
FOR SOMEBODY TO MAKE THE FIRST
MOVE.
I'M BORED.
I'M TIRED OF JUST SITTING BACK.
I WANT TO GET INTO GEAR ALREADY.
THIS IS THE PART I SPECIALIZE
INCH I WANT THE JUMP INTO
ACTION.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO MAKE SOME
MOVES.
WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS?
>> I FEEL GREAT AFTER LAST
NIGHT.
>> FORGET THAT.
THAT'S HISTORY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I'M WILLING TO WORK FOR YOU.
>> I NEED YOU, BECAUSE YOU'RE A
BIG THREAT.
>> AND I NEED YOU BECAUSE I'M A
HOW ARE YOU WITH MALCOLM?
>> HE SEEMS COOL TO ME.
I TALKED TO TONY.
HE'S A THREAT IN THE GAME.
SO AM I.
AND I WANT THE PLAY WITH PEOPLE
WHO ARE THREATS BECAUSE I THINK
THAT'S THE BEST THING FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
>> THERE'S NINE OF US.
RIGHT NOW WE NEED A MAJORITY
ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
ME, YOU, TWO.
>> I THINK MALCOLM.
>> THREE.
CALEB FOR SURE.
FOUR.
SANDRA?
ALL THE THREATS THAT ARE AROUND,
I WOULD LIKE THE KEEP THEM
AROUND BECAUSE THEY'RE SHIELDING
ME.
SO THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'M DOING
HERE.
AUBRY IS A BIG THREAT FOR BEING
A STRATEGIC BEAST.
MALCOLM AND CALEB BOTH HUGE
THREATS, AND SANDRA, THE BIGGEST
THREAT OF ANY RETURNING PLAYER.
YOU DON'T WIN TWICE BY A FLUKE.
RIGHT NEW IT'S STILL PEACEFUL.
SO WE HAVE THE SEE WHO IS
WEAKER?
YOU KNOW IT'S GOING TO SPLIT UP.
IT AIN'T GOING TO BE NINE, EIGHT
STRONG.
IN FACT, THE VERY NEXT ONE WILL
BE A 5-4, BECAUSE THESE
NON-WINNERS WILL NOT AWARD A
WINNER ANOTHER WIN.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU THINK THAT'S
TRUE, BUT I THINK IT'S TRUE.
>> THE ONLY WAY A WINNER CAN WIN
IS THREE WINNERS AT THE END.
>> I WANT THE WORK WITH TONY.
HE'S A WINNER.
I'M A WINNER.
J.T. IS A WINNER.
WE HAVE TO PROTECT EACH OTHER
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
>> WE CAN'T START TAKING OUT THE
PHYSICAL PEOPLE BECAUSE WE'RE
GOING TO KEEP LOSING.
>> ME, YOU, AUBRY, MALCOLM,
CALEB.
>> IF YOU WANT ME AND IF WE CAN
BENEFIT EACH OTHER, THEN I'M IN.
TONY WANTS ME IN HIS ALLIANCE OF
FIVE.
MY GAME IS PRETTY SIMPLE.
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT ME, I DON'T
CARE WHO GOES HOME, WHICH I
REALLY DON'T.
>> IF I'M GOING TO GET TO THE
END, I'M NOT GOING WITH SOMEBODY
THAT DIDN'T WIN.
>> EXACTLY.
>> I HONESTLY BELIEVE TONY IS
GOING TO HELP MY GAME, AS LONG
AS OUR INTERESTS LINE UP,
THERE'S NO END TO THE DAMAGE WE
CAN DO TOGETHER.
>> THEY CAN TIE UP THE ROOSTER,
BUT THE HEN CAN RUN FREE.
EVENTUALLY WE HAVE TO LET THEM
LOOSE.
THEY HAVE TO GET USED TO THIS
BEING HOME.
THEY'LL STAY TOGETHER.
>> TAI AND CHICKENS HAVE A
HISTORY THAT'S SKETCHY.
THERE'S JUST GOING TO COME A
POINT WHERE THOSE CHICKENS START
LOOKING LIKE ANGUS CATTLE, YOU
KNOW?
SO WE SHOULD NOT BE GETTING TOO
ATTACHED TO THEM.
>> NOW WE LIVE WITH THEM FOR A
WHILE AND WE CAN NAME THEM.
>> GLORIA.
>> THAT LOOKS LIKE A GLRA.
>> MONICA IS THE WHITE ONE.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> THE IT WILL SKINNY ONE, OKAY?
>> THE KITCHENS BECOME MY
RESPONSIBILITY, KEEP THEM ALIVE.
NOBODY ELSE WOULD.
I'M THE CHICKEN GUY.
IT'S A BURDEN BUT IT'S A
RESPONSIBILITY.
I DON'T MIND TAKING IT ON.
>> CORN.
YOU HAVE THE SHARE THE WEALTH.
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME DON'T GET
ALL THE CORN OFF THE COB.
>> DON'T.
>> WE GIVE THE CHICKENS MORE
FOOD THAN WE HAVE.
COME ON, TAI.
>> BOTH OF US LOVE ANIMAL, NO
DOUBT ABOUT IT.
I'M A COUNTRY BOY FROM ALABAMA.
I'M LOOKING OUT FOR ME AND
MYSELF, AND TAI IS LOOKING OUT
FOR THE CHICKENS.
THERE'S A LOT OF CORN HERE NOW.
I THINK THE CHICKENS INEVITABLY
WILL HURT TAI.
>> WE GIVE YOU ENOUGH FOOD.
GET OFF.
>> IN THIS LEVEL OF COMPETITION,
ANYTHING CAN BE A REASON FOR
SOMEONE TO GET RID OF YOU.
>> I'M GOING TO HIDE THE RICE33
BEFORE HE GIVES THAT TO THEM.
HE HAS TO DECIDE WHAT HE'S HERE
TO DO, WIN A MILLION DOLLARS OR
MARRY THESE CHICKENS.
>> I CAME INTO THIS GAME CALM
AND COLLECTED.
NOW I HAVE SO MUCH ENERGY
BOTTLED UP INSIDE OF ME.
IT BURNS ME UP JUST TO SIT DOWN
AND LET EVERYTHING BE QUIET,
BECAUSE IN THIS GAME, ANYTHING
CAN HAPPEN.
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE THEIR MINDS.
PEOPLE COULD BE LYING TO YOU.
SO I HAVE TO GET SOME KIND OF
INTEL.
SO I NEED TO FINISH MY SPY
BUNKER AND GET CONTROL OF THIS
GAME.
YOU KNOW, I'M HERE FOR A REASON.
I'M A GAME CHANGER.
I'M GOING TO BE DOWN THERE
BUILDING MY BUNKER AND I'LL HAVE
ALL NIGHT TO DO IT BECAUSE
THEY'RE GOING TO BE SLEEPING.
SO I STARTED COVERING MYSELF UP
WITH DEBRIS TO SEE HOW IT WORKS.
WHILE I'M DOING THAT, I SEE
SANDRA AND TROYZAN WALKING UP MY
WAY.
I HAD THE BAIL OUT OF IT AND I
HAD TO HIDE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IS BETTER
TO GO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT ABOUT TONY?
>> YOU NEVER KNOW.
>> I CREEP UP ON THEM, THEY'RE
TALKING.
VERY INTENSE CONVERSATION.
I'M HEARING MY NAME.
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO STIR UP
THINGS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO PLOT AGAINST
ME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
THE PLATE.
>> SANDRA GIVES ME THE BIGGEST
LIE.
SO I'M STARTING TO THINK THAT
SANDRA IS AGAINST ME.
>> I'M TELLING YOU THAT I'M NOT
STEALING AND SCAMMING.
I KNOW I'M A THREAT.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING TO MAKE MY
TARGET BIGGER THAN IT ALREADY
IS.
I WANTED TO STAY WITH HER, BUT
THE MORE I SEE HER SNEAKING
AROUND DOING THINGS, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO PUT A STOP TO THAT.
>> FOR SOME REASON THERE'S
THINGS IN YOUR HEAD.
>> RIGHT NOW THERE'S NOTHING IN
MY HEAD I'M JUST CURIOUS TO WHAT
THE HELL IS GOING ON.
>> I THOUGHT I HAD ALIGNED
MYSELF WITH TONY, BUT HE'S
RUNNING AROUND ACTING CRAZY.
HE WANTS THE LOOK ME IN THE EYE
LIKE THE FUZZ, LIKE THE POPO
DOES, LIKE THEY'RE TAUGHT TO DO.
I DON'T WANT TO EVER DEAL WITH
THAT AGAIN.
THERE IS NO TELLING WHAT THIS
DUDE WOULD DO FOR $1 MILLION.
TONY NEEDS TO GO HOME.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE THE FIRST WEEK
OR TWO IS ALWAYS TOUGH.
LIKE FIRST SEVEN DAYS FOR ME.
>> DAMN RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE STRONG.
>> WE ARE.
>> ME, TOO.
>> I TRUST YOU 100%.
>> I DO, TOO.
I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO WORRY.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> I KNOW OZZY IS COMING FOR ME,
AND I SEE THAT OZZY AND J.T.
SEEM SUPER TIGHT, WHICH IS NOT
GOOD FOR ME.
MY WHOLE LIFE RIGHT NOW IS
HANGING ON LIKE BY A STRING.
IN THIS GAME.
I THINK THEY THINK CIRIE THE
LEGEND JEDI MIND TRICK PUPPET
MASTER IS TRYING TO GET ME.
THAT MIGHT BE SO.
IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT NOW.
SO I HAVE TO TRY TO WEED OUT WHO
I CAN PLAY WITH AND WHO I CAN'T.
I HAVE TO GET IN WITH SOMEBODY.
I CAN'T PLAY BY MYSELF.
I DON'T TALK TO YOU A LOT
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE IT
BLATANTLY OBVIOUS, BUT YOU KNOW
WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE SOLID.
ONLY TIME I'M GOING TO WRITE
YOUR NAME IS IF I'M NOT HERE AND
IT'S FOR YOUR BENEFIT.
>> OKAY.
SAME ON MY PART.
>> I TOLD CIRIE I'M GOOD WITH
HER.
BUT IF SOMEONE'S GOING TO THROW
HER NAME OUT, I'M GOING TO GO
WITH IT.
LAST TIME I PLAYED LIKE A COP,
LOOK WHERE IT GOT ME?
THIS TIME I'M PLAYING LIKE A
CRIMINAL, AND WE'LL SEE WHERE IT
GETS ME.
MY WORD IS NOT MY BOND IN THIS
GAME THIS TIME.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> I'M FEELING GOOD ABOUT YOU.
>> 100%.
>> YEAH.
I'M LIKE, DON'T SCREW ME, PLEASE
DON'T SKEW ME.
>> CIRIE, I'D NEVER SCREW YOU.
CIRIE IS A MASTERFUL PLAYER.
SHE HAS THIS MYSTICAL PLAYER
THAT DRAWS YOU IN.
>> YOU'RE A SMART PERSON, ZEKE.
I SEE YOU TALKING TO THESE GUYS,
AND I KNOW EVERYBODY HAS TO TALK
TO EVERYBODY, IF I HEARD YOUR
NAME, I WOULD TELL YOU.
>> WE'RE SOLID, DUDE.
>> I WANTEDING TO MORE THAN TO
WORK WITH CIRIE, BUT AS GAGA AS
I AM TO BE PLAYING WITH HER,
CIRIE IS ARGUABLY THE MOST
DANGEROUS PLAYER HERE, SO MY GUT
TELLS ME IT'S TOO EARLY IN THE
GAME TO ALIGN WITH SOMEONE WHO
EVERYONE IS GUNNING FOR.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO GIVE YOU A
PIECE OF ADVICE LIKE A GIFT.
>> OKAY.
>> THE IMPRESSION IS THAT YOU'RE
TALKING TO EVERYBODY.
>> AND EVERYBODY TALKS TO
EVERYBODY.
>> OKAY.
BUT THAT'S COOL.
>> EVEN THOUGH EVERYBODY TALKS
TO EVERYBODY, IF THEY LOOK AT
YOU AND IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
TALKING MORE THAN EVERYBODY
ELSE, THEN THEY'RE GOING TO SAY
YOU'RE SCRAMBLING.
I DON'T THINK I AM.
I DON'T FULLY TRUST CIRIE
BECAUSE SHE'S FEEDING ME WHAT
SHE THINKS IS
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE.
HEY, DEBBIE, I'M DOING YOU A
FAVOR, PAL.
I'M COMING TO YOU, AND I'M
TELLING YOU THEY'RE TRYING TO
GET YOU OUT.
I ASSESSED IT, I DON'T BUY IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF CIRIE
UNDERSTANDS WHAT KIND OF
TRAINING I'VE BEEN THROUGH.
I AM A CAPTAIN IN THE CIVIL AIR
PATROL, ALTHOUGH I DON'T GET
PAID IN DOLLARS.
I GET PAID IN MILITARY TRAINING.
SO IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LOT TO
OUTWIT ME.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LOT.
>> IN THE EVENT THAT SOMETHING
HAPPENS...
>> OR WE LOSE YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, THAT'S THE ONLY
SOMETHING THAT COULD HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE HAVE THE CLARIFY.
>> IN THE EVENT WE HAVE TO TAKE
SOMEONE OUT, I THINK WE SHOULD
GO FOR ONE OF THE GUYS.
THE ONLY WAY THAT BIG BOLD MOVE
WOULD BE SUCCESSFUL IS IF IT WAS
COMPLETELY QUIET.
>> I AGREE.
WE'RE COOL, GIRL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
OKAY.
>> ALL YOU REALLY HAVE AT THE
END OF THE DAY AS FAR AS WHO TO
TRUST IS YOUR INSTINCT, YOUR
INTERNAL RADAR, YOUR [BLEEPED]
DETECTOR, AND MINE SAYS CIRIE
WOULD BE ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
IF WE LOST, AND SHE'S LOOKING
FOR AN OPENING.
I ADMIRE IT, BUT MY B.S.
DETECTOR WAS EH, EH, EH WITH
WHAT SHE WAS TELLING ME.
>> YOU DOING LAUNDRY?
>> NO, I'M GOING TO WASH THE
POT.
SO HAS TONY APPROACHED YOU TO
JOIN HIS ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
>> TONY HASN'T TALKED TO ME THE
WHOLE TIME I'VE BEEN OUT HERE.
ARE YOU IN HIS ALLIANCE OF FIVE?
>> ACCORDING TO HIM I AM.
BUT I NEED YOU TO KEEP THIS
BETWEEN ME AND YOU, BECAUSE
WE'RE GOING TO TURN THE TABLES
ON HIM.
I DON'T LIKE WHAT HE SAID, LIKE
HE'S THE BOSS, AND HE'S NOT THE
BOSS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M DONE.
TONY CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
I THINK HE FEELS LIKE HE CAN
THIS WHATEVER, BUT HE'S TOTALLY
CONFUSED BECAUSE THIS IS MY
GAME.
YOU KNOW THAT SAYING, YOU'RE
ONLY THE KING UNTIL THE QUEEN
ARRIVES?
I'M HERE.
TONY TOLD ME THAT I'M A THREAT
AND AUBRY IS A THREAT AND IF WE
CAN GET CALEB AND MALCOLM ON
BOARD US FIVE CAN TAKE OUT THE
OTHER FOUR.
I WAS BEEN TO PLAY THIS GAME.
IT'S SO NATURAL TO ME THAT I
DON'T FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO PUT
TOO MUCH EFFORT.
HE WANTS TO GO FORWARD WITH FIVE
STRONG PEOPLE AND...
>> I AIN'T ON THAT LIST?
>> NO.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE I'M STILL
HERE, STILL ON TOP, STILL THE
QUEEN.
TONY IS GOING HOME AND THAT'S
IT.
>> SO HALI IS ON OUR SIDE.
I THINK SANDRA IS EASILY ON OUR
SIDE.
AND I HAVE A FANTASTIC FEELING
ABOUT JEFF VARNER.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> OKAY.
>> SANDRA PUT TOGETHER AN
ALLIANCE OF FIVE IN JUST 15
MINUTES.
I MEAN, THAT'S SCARY.
SANDRA KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
SHE'S WON THIS GAME TWICE FOR A
REASON.
>> IT'S ON, MAMA.
WHEN TWO WINNERS OF "SURVIVOR"
GO AFTER EACH OTHER FOR ANOTHER
MILLION DOLLARS, IT GETS UGLY
FAST.
AND I LOVE IT.
I CAN'T WAIT THE SEE THE
FIREWORKS.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> I FEEL LIKE SOMEBODY'S TRYING
THE PLAY ME.
THEY'RE PLANNING SOMETHING?
>> ARE YOU WORKING WITH SANDRA?
>> NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT SHE TOLD ME, WE'RE
JUST TALKING ABOUT MICHAELA, HOW
SHE MOVES THE CRATES CLOSE TO
THE FIRE.
COME ON, SANDRA.
I WANTED TO WORK WITH SANDRA,
BUT NOW I DON'T LIKE WHAT'S
BREWING.
I CAN FEEL IT.
I CAN SEE IT.
SHE'S SCHEMING AND SCAMMING.
AND I'M GOING TO HAVE TO PUT A
STOP TO THAT.
WE HAVE TO GET STRONG, ME, YOU,
MALCOLM AND CALEB HAVE TO GET
STRONG AND PULL SOMEONE ELSE IN,
BUT WE HAVE TO SOLIDIFY THAT.
I DON'T MIND SNAKES, BUT
WEASELS, NOT TOO FOND OF THEM.
IT'S TIME TO START GETTING
RUTHLESS.
>> WE HAVEN'T TALKED TOO MUCH.
OBVIOUSLY YOU KNOW EVERYBODY'S
GOING TO START THINKING ABOUT A
MAJORITY IN THIS TRIBE.
SO WE NEED TO THINK, YOU KNOW.
>> NO, I'M... MY THING IS
STRENGTH, STRENGTH, STRENGTH,
STRENGTH, STRENGTH.
>> 100%, BECAUSE THEY'RE TRYING
TO START TROUBLE.
I THINK IT'S SANDRA, SO WE GOT
TO KEEP THE STRONG TOGETHER.
>> YOU CAN'T LET SANDRA MOBILIZE
HER FORCES AND HAVE THEM AT HER
BECK AND CALL WHENEVER SHE WANTS
THEM BECAUSE THAT'S HOW SHE WON
THE GAME TWICE.
AS FAR AS ALLIES GO, TONY IS NOT
MY FIRST CHOICE, BUT HE'S
SOMEBODY I THINK I CAN WORK
WITH, NOT BECAUSE I TRUST HIM, I
DON'T TRUST HIM ANY FURTHER THAN
I CAN THROW HIS BIG, BALD BODY,
BUT IT BENEFITS ME TO HAVE ALL
THE STRONG PLAYERS AS LONG AS
POSSIBLE.
I NEED CALM -- CAMOUFLAGE.
>> I'M DOWN WITH THE DUDES.
I WANT TO BE STRONG.
SANDRA'S BEEN RUNNING AROUND
GRABBING DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
SHE HAD TO GRAB ME.
I WANT TO MOVE FORWARD.
>> SANDRA IS BAD NEWS.
THEY GET RID OF ONE OF US STRONG
GUYS AND THE REINS GO IN THEIR
HANDS AND THAT'S NO GOOD.
>> WITH SANDRA AND TONY, YOU
CAN'T TRUST EITHER ONE, BUT
RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE I CAN
TRUST TONY MORE THAN SANDRA.
BECAUSE HE'S GOT A BIG TARGET ON
HIS BACK, AND I FEEL THE SAME
WAY.
SO WE GOT TO TRY TO KEEP EACH
OTHER SAFE.
SOMEBODY OFFICIALLY KICKED THE
HORNET'S NEST.
>> IF SANDRA CAN PERSUADE
EVERYBODY TO SEND OUT ONE OF THE
STRONGEST PLAYERS, THAT'S
IDIOTIC.
SHE'S WON THE GAME TWICE.
I TOTALLY GET HOW SHE DOES IT.
SHE'S GOT EVERYBODY IN HER
POCKET IMMEDIATELY.
>> I KNOW HE'S A THREAT, BUT IF
TONY GOES HOME, WE'LL GET NICKED
OFF ONE BY ONE.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL IT'S GOING.
>> GAME OVER.
>> PLAYING WITH TONY IS
DANGEROUS.
BUT CHALLENGES, WE GOT TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG.
IT MIGHT BE A BLOODBATH LATER,
BUT FOR NOW WE GOT TO WIN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> Jeff: NUKU GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW MANA
TRIBE.
CIERA VOTED OUT AT THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> KNEW IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> FIRST THINGS FIRST, TAKE BACK
THE IDOL, ZEKE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, SIX
MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE ARE GOING
THE RACE OUT INTO THE OCEAN,
ACROSS A BALANCE BEAM, TO A
CAGE.
YOU'LL CRAWL UP AND OVER THE
CAGE, WHERE YOU WILL THEN UNTIE
A VERY LONG AND VERY HEAVY
SNAKE.
YOU'LL PUSH IT BACK UP OVER THE
CAGE, BRING IT BACK THE SHORE,
PUT THE SNAKE IN ITS CRADLE
WHERE THE THREE REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL THEN UNTIE NUMBERED
TILES.
YOU'LL USE THOSE TILES TO SOLVE
A COMBINATION LOCK.
THAT WILL RELEASE A SERIES OF
RINGS.
YOU'LL THEN ATTEMPT TO LAND
THOSE RINGS ON TARGET.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO SPELL
"IMMUNITY" WINS IMMUNITY.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FISHING KIT.
>> OH, WOW.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING YOU NEED,
TRAPS, NETS, HAND REELS, PLUS A
RAFT WITH PADDLES WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT CAMP.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: NUKU, YOU HAVE ONE
EXTRA MEMBER.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT SOMEBODY
OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> CIRIE.
>> CIRIE GOING TO SIT THIS ONE
OUT.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
CIRIE, YOU CAN TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
UP AND OVER THAT BALANCE BEAM
FIRST.
ALL THE WAY TO THE CAGE.
YOU CAN'T GO OVER THE CAGE UNTIL
EVERYBODY IS THERE.
>> WHOA, NUKU, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WE'RE NECK AND NECK
RIGHT NOW.
BOTH TRIBES VERY EVEN.
YOU CAN'T MOVE UNTIL YOUR
SLOWEST SWIMMER GETS THERE, GO,
NUKU, GO, MANA.
NOW EVERYBODY HAS TO GO UP AND
OVER.
THE NEXT STEP IS START UNTYING
THAT SNAKE.
>> TONY, RIGHT UNDERNEATH YOU,
BY THE NECK.
>> GET IT RIGHT, THERE RIGHT
THERE.
>> Jeff: VARNER BARKING OUT
ORDERERS FROM THE SAFETY OF THE
CAGE.
>> RIGHT AT YOUR HAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO UNDER.
>> Jeff: THE MORE PEOPLE UNDER
WATER, FASTER YOU WILL RELEASE
THAT SNAKE.
NUKU SENDING A LOT OF PEOPLE AT
ONCE.
MANA NOT.
NUKU ALREADY HAS THAT SNAKE
RELEASED.
MANA IS STRUGGLING TO GET IT
UNTIED.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: CALEB NOW GOING BACK
IN.
NUKU NOW STARTING TO LIFT THAT
SNAKE.
YOU CAN SEE THE EFFORT IT TAKES.
THIS IS NO JOKE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THAT SNAKE WEIGHS
OVER 400 POUNDS.
IT WILL TAKE EVERYBODY.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: TAI, ZEKE, SARAH ALL
WORKING TOGETHER FOR NUKU.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> AWESOME JOB!
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: NUKU MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS NOW.
MANA STILL TRYING TO UNTIE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> WE GOT IT.
>> Jeff: NUKU HAS THE SNAKE
FREE.
EVERYBODY OVER.
>> GO, GUYS, GO!
>> WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT, WE GOT
IT.
>> Jeff: MANA FINALLY HAVE IT
FREE.
CAN THEY CATCH UP.
>> WE'RE STILL IN IT.
>> Jeff: THEY STILL HAVE A LOT
OF CHALLENGE LEFT.
THIS GIVES NUKU A BIG ADVANTAGE.
THEY CAN DRAG THE SNAKE, WHICH
IS MUCH EASIER THAN CARRYING IT.
>> I DON'T HAVE THE STRENGTH,
DUDE.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO GO UP AND
OVER?
VARNER HAS BEEN USELESS SO FAR
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> PUT CALEB ON THE WALL.
>> Jeff: SOMEBODY GIVE ME THAT
HANDLE.
CALEB WORKING WITH TONY.
THEY HAVE THE HEAD OF THE SNAKE.
NUKU CONTINUES TO PULL AWAY.
IT WILL TAKE A GIGANTIC COMEBACK
FROM MANA, BUT ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN IN "SURVIVOR."
NUKU IS NOW OVER THE BEACH AND
IN THE WATER.
NUKU HEADING UP THE BEACH.
MANA NEARLY HAS THEIR SNAKE
CLEAR.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GET OVER.
>> GREAT WORK, GUYS.
GREAT WORK.
>> Jeff: THEY'RE NOW IN THE
SECOND STAGE.
J.T., SIERRA AND DEBBIE UNTYING
THE NUMBERED TILES.
MANA WILL HAVE TO HUSTLE TO GET
BACK IN THIS.
>> GO, GO, GO GO, GO, GO, GO,.
>> Jeff: NUKU HAS ALL SIX
TILES.
>> DEBBIE, STAY COOL.
>> Jeff: IT'S GOING TO BE
DEBBIE WORKING ON THE
COMBINATION LOCK.
HERE COMES MANA.
BIG DISASTER.
MANA LOSES THEIR SNAKE IN THE
WATER.
WOW.
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> Jeff: THAT IS A GIGANTIC
SETBACK.
DEBBIE HAS ALL THREE PAIRS OF
NUMBERS.
SHE CAN START WORKING ON THE
COMBINATION LOCK NOW.
MANA HAS TO HOIST THAT SNAKE
BACK UP.
AND THEY'RE BACK AT IT AGAIN.
HALI GOES IN.
TROYZAN GOES IN.
THIS IS WHAT YOU CALL A DISASTER
IN A "SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE.
DEBBIE RELEASES THE COMBINATION
LOCK.
START TOSSING RINGS.
>> YOU GOT THIS.
>> YOU GOT IT, GIRL.
>> Jeff: SIERRA LANDS THE
FIRST LETTER FOR NUKU.
>> Jeff: WE'RE ALMOST THERE,
GUYS.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: TROYZAN FALLS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK NOW.
ANOTHER SLOWDOWN FOR MANA.
>> THERE IT IS, BABY.
>> Jeff: J.T. SCORES THE
SECOND LETTER.
J.T. SNAGS A THIRD LETTER.
LET'S GO, TROYZAN.
SIERRA SNAGS A FOURTH.
NUKU EXTENDING THEIR LEAD.
HERE COMES MANA.
CAN THEY CATCH UP?
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WORK.
DROP IT AND GET OUT OF THERE.
MANA FINALLY BACK.
IT IS NOW SANDRA, MICHAELA AND
MALCOLM, AND THEY'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO WORK VERY FAST.
SIERRA AND J.T. HAVE DONE A NICE
JOB WITH THESE RINGS.
THEY'RE HALF-WAY THERE, BUT THEY
ARE NOT ALL THE WAY THERE, WHICH
MEANS THAT DOOR IS STILL OPEN
FOR MANA.
MALCOLM HAS ALL SIX.
MOVE OVER TO THE COMBINATION
LOCK.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THREE PAIRS
OF NUMBERS.
THIS CHALLENGE IS STILL ALIVE.
WHICH IS AMAZING GIVEN THE LEAD
NUKU HAD.
SIERRA SNAGS THE FIFTH LETTER
FOR NUKU.
THEY ARE THREE AWAY.
MALCOLM, HE'S GOT IT.
MALCOLM NOW GOING TO DO THE
TOSSING, AS WELL.
MALCOLM HAS THE FIRST LETTER.
J.T. HAS THE SIXTH LETTER.
MALCOLM SCORES THE SECOND
LETTER.
SUDDENLY MANA IS GETTING BACK IN
THIS.
MALCOLM SNAGS THE THIRD LETTER.
IT IS NOW 6-3.
MALCOLM IS SLOWING CLOSING THAT
GAP.
MALCOLM SNAGS THE FOURTH LETTER
FOR MANA.
>> COME ON, J.T.
>> Jeff: NOW IT IS J.T.
FEELING THE PRESSURE.
MALCOLM CLOSES WHAT SEEMED TO BE
AN INSURMOUNTABLE LEAD.
MALCOLM SNAGS THE FIFTH FOR
MANA.
IT IS 6-5.
>> YOU CAN DO THIS, MALCOLM,
COME ON, WASDY.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM FOR THE
SIXTH.
IT IS TIED NOW 6-6.
NOW IT'S ON.
MALCOLM WITH THE SEVENTH.
JUST MISSING.
>> YOU GOT IT, J.T.
RELAX.
>> Jeff: NUKU THOUGHT THEY HAD
IT IN THE BAG.
NOW WORRIED.
>> COME ON, MALL COMING.
>> SLOW AND STEADY.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM ON AND OFF
AGAIN.
J.T. SNAGS THE SEVENTH FOR NUKU.
NUKU NOW ONE AWAY FROM WINNING
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> YOU NEED A BREAK OR YOU GOOD?
>> MICHAELA BITING HER LIP,
WANTING IN SO BAD.
THIS TOSS COULD DO IT RIGHT
HERE.
>> BREATH, BABY, BREATHE.
>> Jeff: AND HE DOES IT.
NUKU PULLS IT OUT, WINS THEIR
SECOND CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
WOW.
THAT WAS EPIC.
>> YOU DID AWESOME.
WE WERE WAY BEHIND.
YOU CAUGHT UP WITH THEM.
>> Jeff: NUKU, CONGRATULATIONS
AGAIN.
ONCE AGAIN NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM YOUR TRIBE.
YOU CAN GRAB THIS PART OF YOUR
REWARD.
YOUR RAFT WILL BE WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT CAMP.
MANA, FOR THE SECOND TIME IF A
RE, I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
>> I CAN'T LOSE EVERY DAMN
CHALLENGE AND EXPECT TO WIN GAME
CHANGERS.
SO WE NEED TO KEEP THE STRONG
PEOPLE GOOD AT CHALLENGES AROUND
FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE OR ELSE
WE'RE DOOMED.
>> ALL I CAN SAY IS JEFF DIDN'T
EMPHASIZE HOW HEAVY THAT SNAKE
WAS.
I MEAN, THAT THING ALTOGETHER
WAS PROBABLY LIKE 600, 700
POUNDS.
THAT THING WAS HEAVY.
>> WE JUST FELL A LITTLE BIT
SHORT.
>> I DON'T LIKE TO LOSE.
>> NO.
NONE OF US DO.
>> THE CHALLENGE TODAY WAS
DEPLORABLE.
IT WAS SO FRUSTRATING BECAUSE I
AM A STRONG PLAYER.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON THAT I'M
HERE.
SO TO BE STANDING THERE DOING
NOTHING WHILE WEAKER PLAYERS
LOSE IT AGAIN.
IT PISSED ME OFF.
BUT THE OTHER PEOPLE ARE MAKING
DECISIONS FOR THE GROUP, SO I
GUESS I GOT TO SIT HERE AND DEAL
WITH IT.
>> TONY'S GOT TO GO.
EVERYBODY IS GOING TO BE HAPPY
ONCE TONY IS GONE.
>> BUT HE NEVER STOPS.
>> I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD LET
HIM GO OFF BY HIMSELF.
BECAUSE HE CAN FIND AN IDOL.
>> IS MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T GO
STRAIGHT UP AND VOTE TONY.
IF HE STARTS RUNNING AROUND
LOOKING FOR THAT IDOL, WE HAVE
TO SPLIT VOTES.
>> AT THIS POINT I'M ALMOST SURE
I HAVE THE NUMBERS THE VOTE OUT
TONY.
HE'S RUNNING AROUND ACTING LIKE
HE'S THE KING, SO HE'S GOT TO
GO.
UNFORTUNATELY TONY IS GOOD AT
FINDING IDOLS, AND THAT MAKES
HIM DANGEROUS.
SO WE GOT TO SPLIT THE VOTE.
WE NEED TO GRAB TWO MORE.
>> CALEB AND MALCOLM?
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT.
>> TONY IS SUCH A TARGET IN THIS
GAME, AND WE HAVE A WIDE-OPEN
DOOR RIGHT NOW IF WE WANTED TO
GO.
WHAT IF HE KEEPS RACKING UP THE
IDOLS?
WE HAVE A OPPORTUNITY RIGHT NOW.
>> TO DO SOMETHING RIGHT NOW?
AND TONY AND AUBRY ARE THICK AS
THIEVES.
>> THEY RUSSIA THEY'RE ALWAYS
GOING OFF TOGETHER.
>> SO LET'S SPLIT VOTES.
>> WHOSE NAME ARE YOU PUTTING
DOWN?
>> I THINK IT SHOULD BE AUBRY.
>> SANDRA IS SAYING THEY'RE
GOING TO PUT AUBRY'S NAME DOWN.
TO BE HONEST, I'LL DO WHAT I
HAVE TO DO TO NOT GET VOTED OUT,
BUT IF AUBRY GOES HOME, SANDRA
TAKES CONTROL OF THE GAME.
MY BACK IS AGAINST THE WALL.
I'M HERE TO WIN.
TO DO THAT I HAVE TO MAKE BIG
MOVES.
SO IF SANDRA IS GOING HOME, I
WANT THE THRONE.
WHEN I SET MY SIGHTS ON A
TARGET, I'M A HEAT-SEEKING
MISSILE.
THE QUEEN, SHE'S DANGEROUS, BRO.
>> SHE'S A TWO-TIME WINNER.
>> EVERYBODY SAYS, NEXT WEEK,
NEXT WEEK, DOESN'T HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S SOMEHOW SHE WINS.
SHE'S LIKE A HYENA.
>> I AGREE.
I AGREE WITH EVERYTHING YOU'RE
SAYING.
>> TONY WAS RIGHT.
SANDRA'S CONVINCED EVERYBODY
THAT TONY SHOULD GO.
AND NOW THEY'RE TRYING TO GET ME
TO BE PART OF IT.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT,
BECAUSE WHEN IT COMES TO STRONG
PEOPLE, WHEN YOU GET RID OF ONE,
IT EXPOSES THE OTHER, YOU SEND
TONY HOME, IT'S EXPOSING ME AND
MALCOLM.
BUT LOOKING AT NUMBERS ON WHO
WILL VOTE OUT SANDRA, WE ONLY
HAVE FOUR.
SO WE NEED ONE MORE PERSON.
>> MICHAELA WOULD GO WITH US
PROBABLY.
>> THEY WON'T SEE IT COMING.
SHE'S OUT.
>> WE GOT TO TRY TO DO IT, MAN.
>> SO TONY THROWS OUT LET'S TRY
TO FLIP MICHAELA AND IT MIGHT
JUST WORK, ONE THING ABOUT
MICHAELA, SHE JUST HATES TO
LOSE, SO MAYBE SHE'LL BE DOWN
WITH GETTING RID OF THE WEAKEST
LINK.
>> BANG, DONE.
GONE, SEE YOU.
>> I NEED YOU.
LET'S PLAY, LET'S DO THIS, MAN.
>> THE ONLY THING I'LL SAY IS
AFTER A CHALLENGE LIKE THAT, I
THINK SENDING A STRONG PERSON
HOME RIGHT NOW IS STUPID.
>> I KNOW EVERYONE'S GUNNING FOR
TONY, BUT I WANT THE GET FURTHER
IN THE GAME.
I WANT TO WIN CHALLENGES.
>> ME TOO.
>> TONY IS DANGEROUS, YEAH, HE
SHOULD GO, DO I THINK HE SHOULD
GO RIGHT NOW, HE'S STRONG.
>> I WANT TO WIN.
I WANT THIS TRIBE SUPER STRONG,
RIGHT?
IF WE LOSE ANOTHER CHALLENGE,
WE'RE SCREWED.
PEOPLE THAT KNOW ME KNOW THAT
LOSE IS NOT IN MY EVERYDAY
VERNACULAR.
SO TO COME OUT HERE AND DO IT
TIME AND TIME AGAIN WHEN IT
DOESN'T HAVE TO HAPPEN, IT
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
I DON'T LIKE LOSING.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
>> I LOVE SANDRA, BUT BOTH
CHALLENGES SHE'S THE WEAKEST
WOMAN HERE, THE SLOWEST WOMAN
HERE.
>> I KNOW THAT TONY IS A THREAT,
BUT HE CAN HELP US WIN
CHALLENGES.
BUT SANDRA IS USELESS IN JUST
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> I GET THE WHOLE ARGUMENT.
THAT WAS HELL.
I JUST WENT THROUGH HELL.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT AGAIN
WITHOUT TONY.
I'M IN HEAVEN, HAVING TWO
WINNERS GOING AT EACH OTHER IS
CHRISTMAS.
AND THE BEST PART OF IT IS WE
GET TO DECIDE WHICH ONE IS GOING
HOME.
>> YOU'RE PLAYING WITH FIRE.
YOU DON'T EVER PLAY WITH IT.
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW YOU CAN GET
BURNED, YOU KNOW.
>> YOU HAPPY?
>> THE ONLY REASON THAT I'M
HESITANT IS THAT THE GUYS.
I DON'T KNOW.
TONY HAS ALREADY BEEN EATING
AWAY AT CALEB'S BRAIN.
THAT'S WHY HE'S GOT TO GO.
THERE IS A CHANCE IT COULD GO
SOUTH AND THEN I END UP GOING
HOME, BUT LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, JUST BECAUSE TONY WON
ONE DOESN'T MAKE HIM A KING.
NO ONE HAS A TRACK RECORD LIKE
ME.
AND WE'RE GOING TO PUT THAT INTO
PERSPECTIVE TONIGHT WHEN TONY
GOES HOME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, TONY, IS
BACK-TO-BACK LOSSES, NOT HOW YOU
WANT TO START A SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
>> JEFF, WE WENT INTO THE
CHALLENGE FEELING STRONG.
WE DIDN'T GIVE UP.
WE DIDN'T SLOW DOWN.
WE WERE ALL FIGHTING AND WE'RE
ANGRY THAT WE LOST THAT
CHALLENGE, SO COMING HERE
TONIGHT, WE NEED THE STAY
STRONG.
WE NEED STRENGTH IN THE GAME.
WE GO BACK TO THE NEXT CHALLENGE
AND WE KICK SOME ASS.
>> Jeff: SO MALCOLM, GIVEN
THAT YOU'RE 0-2, SHOULD THE
PHYSICALLY STRONG PEOPLE FEEL
SAFER?
>> HAVE TO KEEP THE TRIBE
STRONG.
THERE ARE DIFFERENT LEVELS TO
WHAT MAKES A STRONG COMPETITOR
IN TERMS OF WHAT CAN HAPPEN IN A
CHALLENGE, BUT IF WE DON'T KEEP
PHYSICALLY STRONG PEOPLE, WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE PROBLEMS MOVING
FORWARD FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
>> Jeff: MICHAELA, WHAT WERE
YOU THINKING DURING THE
CHALLENGE WHEN MALCOLM THREW
RING AFTER RING AFTER RING WHILE
YOU DID NOTHING?
>> I'M JUST GOING TO SAY THIS,
I'M PHYSICALLY IN THIS GAME
BECAUSE I'M A STRONG PHYSICAL
PLAYER.
I KNOW THAT EVERYBODY WANTS TO
BE HERE AND WE'RE ALL PUT HERE
FOR A REASON, BUT IT DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE TO SEND STRONG
PHYSICAL PLAYERS HOME RIGHT NOW.
>> NOW I'M GETTING SCARED.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, WHAT DO YOU
MEAN WE THAT?
>> IF THEY'RE SAYING A WEAK
PLAYER SHOULD GO, MAYBE I SHOULD
BE AFRAID, BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IF YOU LOOK BACK, THEY'VE PUT
THE STRONGEST PLAYERS IN THE
RIGHT POSITIONS AND WE'VE STILL
COME OUT BEHIND.
SO WHAT DOES IT REALLY MEAN TO
BE PHYSICAL RIGHT NOW IN THIS
TRIBE?
>> Jeff: TROYZAN, IT'S TRICKY.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SO IF YOU SURVIVE
TONIGHT'S VOTE AND IT GOES THE
WAY YOU THINK IT'S GOING TO GO,
HOW WILL THIS TRIBE BE
DIFFERENT?
>> WE WILL BE AT LEAST 50% LESS
PARANOID.
THERE'S JUST CERTAIN PEOPLE THAT
MAKE PEOPLE ON EDGE, LIKE DO I
HAVE TO WAKE UP AT 4:00 A.M. AND
MAKE SURE SOMEONE'S NOT RUNNING
OFF DOING SOMETHING CRAZY?
THAT'S NUTTY.
>> Jeff: TONY, YOU WERE
SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
>> BECAUSE I CAUGHT HIM TALKING
TO SANDRA AT 4:00 A.M., SO I
DON'T KNOW WHAT HE MEANT BEING
UNEASY.
>> I'M IN THE SNEAKING OFF
ANYWHERE.
>> I CAUGHT YOU SNEAKING OFF.
>> IT WAS A TWO-SECOND
CONVERSATION, I TURN AROUND, AND
THERE'S TONY, WHAT ARE YOU ALL
TALKING ABOUT.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THE CRATES
IN THE FIRE, THAT WAS IT, BUT TO
TONY, EVERYTHING IS PARANOIA.
I DON'T PLAY LIKE THAT.
I'M CALM.
IT'S JUST A DIFFERENCE OF
OPINION.
IS SOMETHING IN MY DAMN HAIR.
DON'T PLAY WITH ME.
OH, THAT'S HUGE.
[SCREAMING]
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
RELAX.
GEEZ LOUISE.
>> Jeff: SO TONY, GOING BACK
TO SANDRA'S POINT, IN YOUR
SEASON, EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU
DROVE A LOT OF THE ACTION, A LOT
OF THE DECISIONS, DO PEOPLE LOOK
AT YOU NOW EXPECTING YOU TO BE
THAT GUY?
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE
LEADING PART PROCEEDING ME, BUT
I KNOW ABOUT THE LYING PART AND
THE DISLOYALTY AND THE
DISHONESTY AND THE BETRAYALS,
AND THEY'RE GOING TO BELIEVE
THAT BECAUSE THEY NOVI A HISTORY
OF LYING, BUT THAT'S NOT THE
GAME I'M PLAYING.
WE ALL GET CAUGHT SNEAKING
AROUND, BUT I CAN TELL EVERYBODY
RIGHT NOW, I HAVE NOT BEEN
SCAMMING NOBODY.
>> YOU KNOW, JEFF, I BELIEVE
HIM.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Jeff: SO VARNER, YOU'RE
SAYING YOU BELIEVE TONY.
>> I DO.
>> Jeff: AND CALEB, YOU
BEREAVE TONY?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: MALCOLM, YOU ARE
NODDING YOUR HEAD.
>> I DIDN'T THINK I WOULD LIKE
TONY.
I LOVE TONY.
>> IT'S PERCEPTION.
>> I'VE SEEN A TONY THAT'S
DIFFERENT THAN THE TONY FROM
CAGAYAN.
>> I'M NOT COMING OUTS HERE
COCKY OR CONFIDENT BECAUSE
THEY'RE A DIFFERENT CALIBER OF
PLAYER.
>> Jeff: SO VARNER, WHAT IS
YOUR PLAY RIGHT NOW AS WE GET
READY TO VOTE?
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THIS MANY
GAME-CHANGING PLAYERS?
>> WE ARE A ROUND HOLE, AND IT'S
TIME TO GET RID OF OUR SQUARE
PEG.
>> Jeff: WOW.
TONY, WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT
MEANS?
>> I'M NOT TOO SURE, JEFF.
>> JEFF, HE HOPES HE'S NOT THE
SQUARE PEG.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MALCOLM, YOU'RE UP.
>> AUBRY, YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME
TONIGHT, BUT I STILL HAVE TO
CAST THIS VOTE JUST IN CASE, AND
AS FAR AS TONY IS CONCERNED,
YOU'RE THE CLOWN THAT'S GOING
HOME, AND THE QUEEN STAYS QUEEN.
ADIOS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE AUBRY.
TONY.
AUBRY.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES TONY, TWO
VOTES AUBRY.
TONY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES TONY.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES TONY, TWO
VOTES AUBRY.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS," TONY.
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> SHEEP BEING LED TO THE
SLAUGHTER.
GOOD JOB, SANDRA.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR
PLOTTING AGAINST ME.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET, AND THE
QUEEN STAYS QUEEN.
>> YOU GUYS ARE SUCKERS IF YOU
ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET, TAKE
YOUR ASS HOME.
>> Jeff: TONY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> BYE, TONY.
SAY HI TO CIERA FOR ME.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S
INTERESTING THAT BOTH VOTES HAVE
BEEN DECIDED BY GROUPS, WHICH
MEANS IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE FINGER IS POINTED AT
YOU.
GAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> THANKS FOR THAT PARANOIA.
>> Jeff: MY PLEASURE.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," IT'S ONLY BEEN SIX
DAYS.
>> EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> Jeff: BUT THIS SEASON THE
GAME CHANGES FAST.
IDOLS ARE UP FOR GRABS.
ANIMAL INSTINCTS KICK IN.
>> IS HE CHASING A GOAT?
>> I GOT IT.
>> I'M HUNGRY, BUT I CAN'T.
>> Jeff: AND THE SURVIVORS GET
RUTHLESS.
>> I GOT TO TAKE THEM OUT.
I TOOK THEM OUT AS FAR AS I
COULD.
NOW I HAVE TO LOOK FOR AN IDOL.
>> I KNEW COMING INTO THE GAME I
WOULD HAVE TARGET ON MY BACK.
I KNEW I WAS THE MOST VICIOUS
PLAYER OUT HERE.
I TRIED TO OVERCOME THE
REPUTATION I HAD COMING INTO
THIS GAME, BUT APPARENTLY IT GOT
THE BEST OF ME.
AS FOR NOW SANDRA IS THE QUEEN.
SHE MANIPULATED EVERYBODY TO
BELIEVE I WAS SCHEMING OR
SCAMMING.
SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
SHE GOT ME TONIGHT.