Previously on Survivor...
In the Yawa tribe,
three Healers, one Hero
and a Fighter
remained undefeated.
Good game !
In the Levu tribe,
things were going well for Joe.
The idol!
Bon sang!
In the Soko tribe,
JP and Ali were in danger.
Ryan and I have to choose
which of the two leaves tonight.
At the council,
Chrissy and Ryan eliminated Ali.
Ali, the tribe has spoken.
There are 12 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
I didn't want to smile,
it was sad that she was leaving
and I felt sorry for her,
but I was happy for us,
it was hard not to smile.
She had to leave.
I play 24 hours a day.
I believe I dominate the social game
in this tribe.
The two guys are closer
to me than to each other.
Wow, we held one more.
Yeah.
The first two thirds!
It makes my position
very comfortable.
Perhaps the dominant position.
My current position
prepares me for a bright future.
If there is a test today,
we win.
I feel good
with my five from Yawa.
We fully trust each other
now.
Because we've been through
tough times together.
Ben's a good guy,
and Lauren should stay with us.
And with Mike and Jessica,
we come from the Healers.
We have this link
from the previous tribe.
If this group stays together,
we can accomplish a lot,
and I doubt the others
have the same unit.
I don't see the other tribes
staying so united.
Just.
So...
We are five.
And at the merger, we should be
able to recruit Joe and Desi.
We'll have to have a solid pact.
We gotta make a plan, execute it
and stick to it.
If, at the merger, we are five welded,
It will be alright.
But it's mostly Cole
that worries me.
Cole and Jess
have sex every night.
It makes trust difficult.
It has to improve.
There, we are the broken tribe.
We're two against two,
Devon and me against Joe and Desi.
But above all,
physically, we are exhausted.
Our stomachs are empty,
we can feel it.
We have nothing left to eat,
no more rice,
no chicken, no fruit,
no vegetables, nothing.
I'm too hungry.
Except for a small amount of sugar.
Sugar at breakfast.
Survivor is no joke.
We're not joking saying
that without food today,
we could die.
He struggles to move forward.
You can do it, Dev!
I'm spinning.
There are no longer any calories
my body can use.
My brain seems dead
and each of my limbs
weighs a ton.
It's the saddest moment
of my life.
Right here right now.
This game is way more real
than I thought
and at the next
reward event,
If we don't win,
I don't know what I'll do.
Over here, everyone!
Wow, Desi, that's laborious.
Yawa, Levu,
discover the new Soko tribe.
Ali was eliminated
at the last council.
Desi, to see you climb
these few meters of sand,
it looked
like you were climbing Everest.
Is this representative
of wear after 17 days?
Absolutely.
We have nothing to eat at the camp.
Not a single calorie.
I want to eat.
And how !
We are all there.
All tired, all hungry.
So what are we waiting for, Jeff?
All right, shall we get to it?
Yes.
Well, first of all...
Throw away all your bandanas.
It's fusion!
It is an indescribable pleasure.
We all want to achieve fusion.
This is where Survivor begins.
I am Mike.
How are you, Mike?
This is where you discover
your true allies,
but you have to
have your head in the game.
The merger is the first step
towards the million.
I really hope
it involves food.
Joe, delighted.
New bandannas!
Have you ever seen
so much love at a merger?
It's not bad, I like it.
Sweet music to my ears,
when Jeff said:
"Throw away your bandanas!"
I think I am in a good place.
I have people with the Healers.
The Healers are five.
There are only four Heroes
and three Fighters.
As a bonus,
everyone is unaware that I have an idol.
So there, I'm excited.
Where's the food ?
And the scary part?
There is a "but".
Doctor Mike, immediately
everyone says:
"And the feast?"
and "There is a 'but'!"
What is the dominant feeling?
Are you worried that things won't go
as usual?
35th season of Survivor.
You never know what will happen.
That's right.
And typically...
Oh, my God.
... At the merger, you are entitled
to a big feast at Survivor.
Yes !
But not today.
Do not say that !
Because we have better.
What what ?
We brought
Outback Steakhouse to Fiji.
Give me that steak!
Yes, the steak kings
are going to take care of the fusion feast.
And since Outback Steakhouse
operates the Australian way,
or "No rules,
just what's good.",
this meat cut on the bone,
these entrecôtes...
Entrecôte, entrecôte!
Sorry. Sorry, Jeff.
Do you like entrecote?
That's what I prefer.
They will be prepared
according to your wishes,
individually cooked the way you like it
.
In addition, potatoes
and all the accompaniment: salad...
And the chocolate fudge?
Are there any?
The authentic
Chocolate Thunder.
But yes !
Bonus: cold beer
and Gold Coast Rita.
Outback Steakhouse is waiting for you
right back there.
Good afternoon !
I needed this fusion so badly!
My tribe was a disaster.
We are only three.
Achieving fusion, we dream of it.
Here it gets serious.
Oh my God !
You believe in it ?!
Rib to bone.
I'll take it all.
Welcome to Outback Steakhouse!
Thanks.
Have a drink!
Oh my God ! It was ecstasy!
To the merger!
Achieving fusion
is such an accomplishment!
Going from this morning's depression
to the company of these great people,
and having this feast
was such a joy!
I feel like a king.
That is living!
Well, give me everything!
No, I...
What cooking, the rib?
Can I have two steaks?
Yes you can.
Give me two!
Thanks a lot.
I normally eat
8,000 calories a day.
So before the merge,
I was in "survival" mode.
"I want to eat !" And there, after
almost three weeks of hunger,
Wow !
The steak falls off the bone
and melts in your mouth.
This is a dream.
Oh my God ! Too good !
Best steak of my life.
Unbelievable.
If Survivor is a mountain,
I'm halfway there.
That's how you conquer
a peak: one step at a time.
Cole, I don't want
you to pass out. Eat more!
Can we recommend steaks?!
I ordered
three desserts and two steaks.
Sorry.
This is my first opportunity
to meet Joe.
And I'm really happy
to have spent all this time without him.
He is very noisy
and really unpleasant.
Tell us the advice.
I expected this question.
Well, I had to release an idol.
Where did you get it from?
Blue or yellow?
Yellow.
Really ?
You are the 1st to know it.
The cow !
Joe tells us there was
an idol that was played.
But does Joe have a second idol,
that of Levu?
Chocolate Thunder.
My God !
I believe that I love you.
This Aussie waiter
brings me a Chocolate Tonnerre.
I thought,
"You'll do me good down there."
Not the kind of thing
I often say.
Being a virgin, I try
to stay moral and holy.
Oh my God !
Came out of the joy
and excitement of the steaks,
the game quickly regains its rights.
The goal in the merger was to remain
the five Yawa until the end.
Namely Lauren, Mike,
Cole, Ben and me.
But the majority requires
at least two other people.
We should be able to recruit
the ex-Healers: Joe and Desi.
We'll see if it works.
As long as no
one leaves the alliance,
Everything will be alright.
Ah! Very good.
Fusion !
I'm glad to see you again.
I say. I was worried.
Yes everything is fine.
Only Joe worries me.
I'm afraid that in Levu,
he found another idol.
Yes. They are listening to us here.
They don't hear me.
Too much wind.
I say.
Before mixing,
Chrissy and I were close.
But no one knows
we worked together.
And she was talking to me
in front of everyone.
It's worrying,
because I don't want
to be seen as allies.
You are my number one.
We'll talk at camp.
In secret.
The merger being there,
everyone starts from scratch.
And we have to anticipate.
There are no more teams.
Only me and my family matter.
From now on, camaraderie is over.
It will be betrayals, lies,
and I'm sure
someone will crack.
Look at all this!
It's a new world.
It's incredible.
The goal was to achieve fusion.
And arrived at the camp, it is as if
we had received a new life,
a chance to start over.
We have hammers,
several machetes
and even huge nails.
We can build a great shelter.
But at this stage,
the cards are reshuffled.
People think of themselves first.
So I thought
we should look
a clue or advantage.
But I found nothing.
I have to keep looking.
Because people
will talk to each other,
plot, strategize,
create new alliances.
Did Joe talk
about all staying together?
Yes, he still wants it.
OK.
What do you think ?
Let's keep it as long as it serves us.
Exactly.
I spoke with Desi
and was delighted to hear
that she and Joe
were still working together.
So I have all the Healers
plus Lauren and Ben from Yawa.
And that's a majority.
I feel
like the queen bee.
Happy to see you.
I was worried the last time.
It was... unanimous?
I was nervous too.
I'm waiting to talk to Dev again
from the mix.
It's like
finding an old friend.
I wish
it was you, me, JP...
Ashley.
Are you close to JP?
Yes, we voted together both times.
Good.
So...
You, me, Lauren...
Us and the Heroes.
A Hero-Fighters alliance makes
sense to us,
because alas,
there are only three Wings left.
Lauren, Devon and me.
But I'm close
to two Heroes, JP and Chrissy.
So it would be a perfect match.
It's Heroes and Fighters
versus Healers.
It's okay with me.
Yeah.
Fusion Vote is
Survivor's crème de la crème.
It determines
who will control the rest of the game.
And a Fighter does not wait,
he will form alliances.
We are all good
at challenges.
Lord !
Without energy in reserve!
To see this group of 12,
I believe that they are the best
who have reached fusion.
But Healers and Heroes
see each other as antagonists
from the start.
We are well placed, know that.
We, the Fighters,
go a little unnoticed.
And at the merger, it is not negative.
You and me, we had to fend for
ourselves, but it turned out well.
We're in the minority
and they're all going to want us.
talk to people,
but don't give them
any idea what we're doing.
I had contact
with everyone.
Let's go with the Heroes.
Yeah.
We seven, get the five out.
Heroes and Fighters
want to take out the Healers.
No question for me.
I stay with the Healers.
I really like Doctor Mike
and I have a pact with the Yawa.
It makes sense
that the five of us stick together.
Devon's plan
is that he, Ryan and I,
with the Heroes,
we take out the Healers.
It's not good for me.
We're 1000% together, swear.
For our children.
Lauren tells me immediately
that Devon wants
all the ex-Healers out.
I made you a promise, Mike.
It worries me that Healers
might be the target
original Fighters and Heroes.
But in reality,
the five Healers are welded together,
and I bond with Lauren and Ben.
So the boundaries have been drawn,
and I expect a war.
For me, 3 Fighters
and 4 Heroes come out the Healers.
In my eyes, the best scenario
would be to take out Cole or Joe.
No problem for me.
I just know that I barely
endured a meal with him.
Yeah.
Joe knows how to play, which makes him
a threat to others.
Cole is a physical threat.
If he loses the first immunity,
it would be a good time
for him to leave.
It would be nice
to be able to be all seven.
For now,
I listen to everyone.
I can go with ex-Heroes
and ex-Combatants.
Let's pick up some wood,
like this...
Or I can see if it works
with the five Yawa.
The question is:
can I trust Cole?
How do you use cinnamon?
It's not bad if you bite it
rather than eat it.
He's selfish and I doubt
he respects anyone here.
He only respects himself.
He needs help
to get to the end, that's all.
But now, I need someone
I can trust.
Cole is munching
on cinnamon sticks.
What ?
Yeah.
Cole made some big mistakes,
especially with the food.
He doesn't think.
And he isolates himself, does not speak to
the group, eats alone.
We don't do that in Survivor.
But Cole is my number one,
I feel a connection with him.
We've built
something great together,
and I need him here.
It is therefore time for us to re-discuss.
You have to stop
eating cinnamon.
What are you talking about ?
We watch over you. Do not do it.
OK ?
Good. Did someone say something?
Yeah.
Here?
Well.
Ben. OK.
Devon is
in for taking out Cole or Joe.
So, well...
Leaving Cole would destroy
the trust between the five.
Yeah.
The Yawa tribe said,
"We stick together at five."
The problem
is that Ben is hesitant now.
It was just a theory.
OK.
Nothing definitive.
But Cole
is the biggest threat.
Let's see one vote at a time.
Sure.
Because here, Cole is one of your five.
The post-merger dynamics
are far from what I imagined.
I imagined being the only one playing.
But it turns out
that everyone is playing.
It greatly complicates my
life.
Everything we've been working on for
the past nine days,
we can forget
it if we take it out first.
It's not
because I arrived here
with a supposed alliance
of five...
... that everyone will stick to it.
They're all after you.
It's Joe or you.
All Heroes and all Fighters
are after you two.
Are you still with me?
Sure.
You are with me, huh?
100 %.
Now
that my name is mentioned,
I experience
Survivor paranoia.
Like in climbing,
when your gear doesn't hold,
you are at the top
and you will find yourself at the bottom.
And my allies are my gear.
Pray for them to extend
my life in Survivor.
Over here, everyone!
Good. Ready for your first
individual immunity test?
Yeah.
First of all, Desi and Mike,
I take back the idols.
Tribal immunity is over.
This is what you want
now.
The individual immunity collar.
With you are safe.
Without, you are not.
Today you will stand
on a narrow rail
and spin a marble
in a circular track.
Regularly,
you will descend along the rail,
increasing the difficulty.
If you lose the ball
or fall off the rail,
you are eliminated.
The last person standing
wins immunity,
is safe at the council.
The losers: someone will be
the seventh person eliminated.
Good. Take place.
Let's go.
Let everyone spin their ball.
All the balls spin.
Your first individual immunity test
is launched.
And now Ryan is eliminated,
after only
a few seconds.
Ryan, go to the bench.
This game can have you
in so many different ways.
This hypnotic trance
which is about to begin,
take over your mind,
this spinning ball...
Don't let her make you forget
what you're doing.
You are going to make
your first move.
You will put one foot
on the rail.
Things get
a little more difficult.
It is a delicate test.
You've probably
never done this.
How many people do that
on Sunday in their garden?
Not even me, Jeff.
Doctor Mike loses his marble.
Mike is eliminated.
More than 10 people.
A whole new test.
You will be the first person
to win it.
And the first protected person
on the board since the merger.
Alright, it's time to
take another step down.
The balance gets
a little more complicated.
Jessica loses her marble.
There are only nine people left.
Sweat
runs down Joe's face.
Yes sir !
No way to stop
to wipe it.
No sir !
You don't have to
get distracted.
The concentration needed
in the game
is also for this test.
Keep that marble
moving!
Alright, it's time to
take another step down.
You will put one foot
on the narrowest part.
Take small steps.
Ben is in trouble.
Ben does not manage
to finish advancing, it is lost.
JP loses his ball. He is eliminated.
Devon is eliminated.
More than six people.
Lauren loses her marble
right after Devon. More than five.
This third section
is wreaking havoc.
Nice recovery from Cole.
This sound should not mislead you.
He wants to seduce you, put you to sleep.
Joe loses his ball.
More than four people.
Fighting for immunity.
Tap into your last
reserves! Hold fast !
Your chances increase,
with each spin,
to be the person
who will win the event.
ELAPSED TIME: 10 Minutes
Cole struggles to stay in the game.
Cole loses his marble.
He is eliminated.
And immediately... Chrissy loses her marble.
More than two people.
Desi and Ashley
fight over immunity.
Desi's ball goes slow,
Ashley's twice as fast.
Different strategies.
Both are walking.
You just have to
keep your ball moving.
First
individual immunity test.
With a big tip on the horizon.
It's now been 30 minutes.
ELAPSED TIME: 30 Minutes
To put that into perspective,
Ryan was the first eliminated,
after two seconds.
Who is good at math?
How many times longer
did they last than Ryan?
It's been 30 minutes? 900 times.
And Desi and Ashley continue.
38 minutes.
ELAPSED TIME: 38 Minutes
Chrissy,
how many times has Ryan been?
1100 and some.
You lasted 1,100 times
longer than Ryan.
Put that on your resume.
I will do it.
Well, it's time
to move on to sudden death.
Both feet will be
on the narrowest part.
Three, two, one...
Ashley moves
inch by inch.
Desi wobbles.
Ashley fails and loses her marble.
Desi wins
first individual immunity!
Safe at tonight's council.
Well done, Ash.
Girls, you rock!
Great, girls!
Desi, come here.
First person
to wear this necklace.
Immunity is yours.
Safe at tonight's council.
You cannot be eliminated.
As for you guys,
after 19 rough days,
someone will be
the seventh person eliminated.
It won't be you.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight at the council.
Congratulation.
At the first merger vote,
it is crucial
to eliminate a threat.
And there are plenty of them.
It is time for this alliance
of Heroes and Fighters
assembles
and attempts to take out a Healer.
Wow, Desi and Ashley, that was...
Impressive.
Downright.
Good job.
I am very worried.
My name
has been maliciously mentioned.
I have a good chance
of leaving tonight.
Apparently, my eating habits
displease.
I'm looking for a way out.
I'll see what I can do.
I would like to apologise.
I know I've annoyed you
with food in the past.
Yes. I know you don't have
fat stores...
That's not an excuse.
Exactly.
That's what I was going to say.
I didn't want to say it
publicly and be the bad guy.
But I would have liked to.
'Cause I do this without thinking
how it is perceived.
I'm sorry, and never...
And the blow of the fish.
You bring it, you catch it,
and you eat it alone.
I don't think about it.
I know, friend. No problem.
Cole apologized,
and I played it:
"No worries, everything is fine."
He offended me the whole time
we shared on camp.
I appreciate that you have
the maturity to assume.
It's a first step.
But going against the ex-Yawa
and eliminating Cole
might hurt me later.
Cool ?
Yes, I said it all.
Okay, buddy. I appreciate.
I have to think tactically,
not emotionally.
Tactically speaking,
if I have to collaborate with Cole
to advance in the game,
I will.
My name is mentioned.
Yours or mine?
I heard both.
Without wanting to brag,
I should be worried.
In terms of strategy, I see things
before others.
So I understand.
I am aware that I
can be targeted.
I am a solid player,
strategy level.
I found an idol.
It terrifies people.
Please don't use it against me
.
But no.
Ben, Jessica, Mike,
Lauren and I, the red tribe,
we have a kind of pact.
We vote together.
Let me ask you a question.
Why include Ben, damn it?
He will betray you.
Ben is playing a double game.
My Healer tribe
has been compromised.
They get manipulated by Ben.
You never went to the council.
Joe goes wild, at the council.
This is where I excel.
But if I feel in danger,
I have an idol.
As for using it for me
or for someone else,
I will decide at the last moment.
Talk to me. I feel
awfully left out.
I heard Heroes
would target Healers.
I feel like...
...that we have to vote for Chrissy.
Having Chrissy in the game
is very dangerous.
She knows how to speak.
Yeah.
She is super smart.
She made these calculations
as if it were nothing.
Chrissy has to go first,
because in this game,
we must eliminate
very clever people.
The kings of manipulation.
So tonight
we'll be five Healers
against Chrissy.
And I think
Lauren will vote with us.
So now we are six.
Lauren approached us.
We were five
and we all became close.
We trust each other.
And then ?
Exactly.
He says he's with us, but...
He also found his Heroes.
The question becomes:
"Is Ben with or against us?"
We have to stick
to our five-way plan.
And I...
A Healer has to come out first.
You think ?
Oh yeah.
But we are fine with them.
We must not spoil this.
I don't trust Cole.
I say. Me too.
But listen to me, honey.
Look at me.
We are thought of.
Yeah.
OK ?
Ben and I
have been together since Yawa.
He was the only Hero
and I was the only Fighter.
But now
we are really in the middle.
Think about it and let me know.
OK.
The game starts from scratch.
There are so many things to consider
to make the best decision.
It's very hard.
You're thinking Cole, not Joe?
It's... It's Cole.
And Joe is our plan B.
But at the council,
let's pretend we're going to
vote Joe.
Like that, he will play his idol.
You don't think
Cole has one?
I do not know.
The discussion
revolves around who to eliminate: Joe or Cole.
Where it's tricky is that we
don't know if they have idols.
We need a plan B.
If Joe plays an idol
and Cole stands up
with something crazy...
Plan B
is next on the list.
Who would it be?
I ss.
I think so too.
It seems logical.
We have to do this.
Eliminating Jessica would be fine with me.
'Cause we think Joe
might have an idol
or give one to Cole.
it seems unlikely
that Jessica has one.
Also, Jessica and Cole
have become very close
and we want to separate them.
I applied for this game
for 16 years,
so i know the game well enough
to know
that a council is alive,
and that people change their minds.
I hope to be
on the right side of the votes tonight.
You don't talk to me '
cause you're playing it cool, huh?
It's true ?
Yeah.
Chrissy trusts me.
Will I betray her tonight
and eliminate it,
or break with the five Yawa
and release a Healer?
I'm in the middle,
and having to choose a side,
that's the worst you can do
in a million dollar game.
But one thing is certain, tonight
lines will be drawn,
alliances will be forged.
War sucks.
And it won't be pretty tonight
either.
Because tonight is war.
If this is your first tip,
take an unlit torch
and light it in the fire.
It's part
of the counseling ritual.
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears, so do you.
Well then. Fusion.
Significant, because we pass
to the individual part of the game.
Ryan, back
to our original theme.
There are five Healers left,
four Heroes and three Fighters.
How important
was it this afternoon,
considering
the options for tonight?
Yes, there are these original divisions,
but also the divisions
of the last eight days.
Dr. Mike, why
don't you just say:
"Let's agree
to bring out a Healer,
to rebalance the situation.
They are five."?
This is the most obvious blow,
but most here are already thinking about
the second and third shots.
I saw people scheming,
really nervous people.
Jeff, we can procrastinate,
play like, "Oh, I'm paranoid!"
In fact, I only heard
three names.
So for all 12 to
be nervous is bullshit.
Cole, there's an answer
we're giving to the board.
"I'm worried."
And then there is the truth.
"Actually, I have no worries
tonight."
We're actually trying
to tell our allies:
"I trust you."
Absolutely.
I did my best
to build strong alliances
and make sure those ties
are strong. So I say:
"I trust you
and am not worried."
Lauren, the definition
of what makes you a target
changes from board to board.
Did you perceive that everyone
assessed all types
threats to determine
who to vote for?
You have to consider everything.
Is this person
a physical threat?
Will she become
a threat later?
Or does she just piss you
off?
It's not just this evening at stake,
but also
all those which will follow.
Chrissy,
did you feel that too?
Yes. In general, in Survivor,
right after the merge,
it's the physical threats.
But in this season,
we consider
many other factors.
Joe, you seemed to nod.
I've been honest
since day one.
I am a strategist,
sporty and intelligent.
But there is
more dangerous than me.
Everyone talks about trust.
But is it real?
Because for me, yes.
I have already come to the council.
I said to Desi, "I've got you covered."
And we're both here.
So do you want someone
who throws names and says:
"I vote with you
to this advice, but to the next one,
ciao."?
And the people here, blah blah blah,
that's all they do.
Dr. Mike,
does that give you any comfort?
"If Joe is telling the truth,
that's good for me.
Because I'm also a Healer,
like Jessica and Cole."
Of course, if I weren't
the most misplaced Healer.
Because Joe has been saying since day 1:
"I'm telling you,
I've got you covered. Except Mike.
I say it: Mike, you're going to leave,
you are not
in my circle of trust.
Hi !"
He said I was looking for the idol,
but he found it.
But we settled
our differences.
And I have affection
and respect for Joe.
I'm sorry.
I said I found an idol?
No, I found idols.
Every camp I go to,
I find an idol there.
So let's change it.
Let's not talk about this vote.
Let's talk about the next one,
because names will be mentioned.
Now
everyone is worried.
Am I going to play it or not?
The other time, I almost played it
for someone you trust.
I let you admire it,
see what you want to do.
And there I am relaxed.
It's ridiculous.
Wow.
Cole, you reacted
when Joe pulled this.
What did you think?
I know that in the names
mentioned, there was Joe and me.
And Joe is protected if he wants it.
I don't have the same protection.
So that could be
my first and last piece of advice.
We'll see.
Jessica, you can see
how fast this game is changing.
A bomb has been dropped,
and everyone must say to themselves:
"It could be me."
Absolutely.
Idols change everything.
We wonder about his old
allies and his new ones.
Joe was in my first tribe,
and now I'm like,
"Are we still good? Or ciao?"
Jeff, Joe talks a lot, but
he's been covering for me since day 1,
when we found the 1st idol.
So in times like this,
I repeat to myself:
"I'm not worried,
I trust you."
The lines are drawn, Jeff.
What does that mean ?
We are going to know
who is allied to whom
and someone will leave.
You are right, because it is
time to vote. Jessica, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Might as well reset
the counters to zero.
It's for me.
This is
a hidden immunity idol.
Votes against Joe
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Chrissy.
Jessica. Equality.
Two votes Chrissy,
two votes Jessica.
Chrissy.
Jessica.
Three votes Jessica.
New equality.
Four votes Chrissy,
four votes Jessica.
That's five votes Chrissy.
New equality.
Five votes Chrissy,
five votes Jessica.
6 votes Jessica, 5 votes Chrissy,
one vote left.
Seventh person eliminated
from Survivor:
Jessica.
Bring me your torch.
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks, Jeff.
It's time to go.
In Survivor,
when boundaries are drawn,
what matters is not who leaves,
but who survives,
and the new boundaries
that are drawn.
Take your torches,
return to camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The future of the Healers
looks bleak.
Looks like the end of the world.
We were totally betrayed.
But they will not surrender
without a fight.
Come ! I got it ! JP!
Cole started digging.
An idol.
Before my eyes, it was chaos.
I believe it was
the worst betrayal of my life.
My heart is broken.
Who knew
a game could crush you?
I thought
only boys did that.
I was wrong.
But I will miss Cole.
I hope he goes far,
and maybe we go on a date
when Survivor is over.