>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT THE YAWA TRIBE,
COLE BROKE A HEALERS' TRUST.
>> JESSICA'S GOT AN ADVANTAGE
FOR THE NEXT TRIBAL.
>> Jeff: AND GOT CAUGHT.
>> IT'S MY PREROGATIVE ON WHO I
TELL.
KID -- DID I CHEW TO FORM A
RELATIONSHIP WITH SOMEONE I
SHOULDN'T HAVE?
>> Jeff: AT THE SOKO TRIBE,
RYAN HAD AN OLD ALLIANCE WITH A
HUSTLER AND BUILT A NEW BOND
WITH A HEALER.
>> SO YOU ANDRY GOING TO HAVE TO
BE FRIENDS.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: AT THE LEVU TRIBE,
DESI HELD ALL THE POWER.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, THE GAME
TURNED UPSIDE DOWN.
>> THIS IS BEING USED AGAINST
YOU TO BLOCK YOUR VOTE.
>> Jeff: AND JOE SEIZED THE
OPPORTUNITY.
>> I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU,
JEFF.
MAKING A BIG MOVE.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND SENDING A HERO HOME.
ALAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> I READ YOUR FACE.
THANK YOU, BABY GIRL.
>> Jeff: 14 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> THAT WAS WILD.
>> ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS WELL
PLAYED.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WHEN JOE
DECIDED TO PLAY THE IDOL FOR
HIMSELF, MY ENTIRE JAW DROPPED.
EVERYTHING IN MY WHOLE WORLD
JUST STOPPED.
I WOULDN'T SAY THEY WAS LIKE
100% TEAM ALAN, BUT HE WAS THE
ONE HERO ON MY TRIBE.
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ME AT THE
END?
>> I READ YOUR FACE.
THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
>> I CAUGHT MYSELF.
>> IT'S TOO LATE AT THAT.
>> Jeff: JOE MADE HIMSELF
TARGET ON PURPOSE.
HE TRICKED US ALL.
JOE IS A SCARY ONE.
HE'S GETTING CRAZIER AND
CRAZIER, BUT RIGHT NOW IT'S 2-2.
SO WHO KNOWS WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE CRAZY, BUT I
DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE CRAZY AND
SMART
>> I'M CRAZY AND SMART.
I HAVE COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED THE
ENTIRE TRIBE WITH THE IDOL.
I HAD TO PLAY THE NERVOUS ROUTE.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYONE THINKING I
WAS OVERCONFIDENT.
I PUT MY HEAD DOWN.
THAT WAS ALL AN ACT.
I HAD THE IDOL.
I'M NOT GOING HOME.
EVERY SINGLE TRIBAL IS SO SCARY.
>> DAMMIT.
>> OH, MY LORD.
>> OH, MAN.
MY BECOME HURTS.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YOU ALL RIGHT, BEN?
>> GOOD.
>> WHAT WAS IT THAT POPPED LIKE
THAT?
>> JUST THE BAMBOO.
[POPPING]
OH, YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
>> SORRY, BEN.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT, MAN?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> I THINK JUST THE LEAVES.
I THINK IT HAS A LITTLE HEAT.
>> IF YOU'RE A MARINE, YOU HEAR
A BANG LIKE, THAT YOU THINK MY
FRIENDS ARE DYING.
I FEEL BAD FOR HIM.
>> YEAH, THAT IS BAD.
>> THERE WAS A BAMBOO EXPLOSION
IN THE FIRE, AND I DON'T LIKE
LOUD NOISES LIKE THAT.
LIKE WHEN THEY'RE UNEXPECTED, IT
KIND OF PUT ME IN A BAD SPOT.
I WAS IN THE MARINES FOR THREE
AND A HALF YEARS.
WHEN YOU GO THROUGH COMBAT AND
YOU COME BACK, THERE IS NO WAY
TO ADJUST FULLY.
THERE'S THINGS THAT ARE THERE
FOREVER.
COMING BACK WITH THAT STUFF,
IT'S HARD, AND YOU FEEL LONELY,
AND YOU FEEL THAT NOBODY
UNDERSTANDS.
>> YOU SURE YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
OTHER PEOPLE, CIVILIANS OR
WHATEVER HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO BE SHOT AT OR HAVE
PEOPLE TRY TO KILL YOU.
YOU CAN'T COMPREHEND THAT
WITHOUT BEING THERE AND GOING
THROUGH IT.
AND SO THOSE REACTIONS ARE 100%
REAL FOR MEN AND WOMEN THAT HAVE
FOUGHT FOR OUR COUNTRY.
AND IT'S HARD TO BE AROUND OTHER
PEOPLE THAT DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT.
BEFORE I MET MY WIFE, THAT WAS A
MONKEY ON MY BACK.
MY WIFE AND KIDS HAVE DEFINITELY
SAVED ME FROM MY DEMONS, MY
NIGHTMARES, AND THE PAST.
I USED TO LIVE IN THE PAST.
THAT'S IN THE A GOOD THING FOR
ANYONE.
YOU HAVE THE LOOK FORWARD TO THE
FUTURE, BECAUSE THE PAST WILL
EAT YOU ALIVE, BUT THE FUTURE
WILL SAVE YOU.
YOU KNOW, WINNING THE $1 MILLION
FOR MY FAMILY IS MY GOAL, BUT
THERE'S A BIGGER PICTURE, AND
IT'S BIGGER THAN ME, MY FAMILY,
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
IT'S ABOUT JUST BEING ABLE TO
SHOW VETS WHO HAVE GONE THROUGH
BATTLE AND WAR AND DEPRESSION
AND P.T.S.D., THERE'S A WAY TO
LIFE OUTSIDE OF ALL THAT HELL.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YAWA, SOKO, GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW LEVU TRIBE.
ALAN VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE?
>> YES, SIR.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, YOUR FEET WILL BE
TIED TOGETHER.
YOUR ARM WILL BE BOUND TO YOUR
SIDE.
ON MY GO YOU WILL SLITHER
THROUGH THE SAND WHILE PUSHING A
BALL RELAY STYLE THROUGH THE
COURSE.
WHEN YOU REACH THE FINISH, THE
REMAINING TRIBE MEMBER WILL
SHOOT FIVE BALLS INTO A VERY
HIGH BASKET.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: IT'S AT HOT DAY IN
FIJI.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO COOL DOWN
WITH SOME ICED COFFEE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: ICED COFFEE, HUGE
ARRAY OF PASTRIES, PLUS COFFEE
AND TEA TO TAKE BACK TO CAMP.
FILL YOU UP AND PICK YOU UP.
>> IT'S GUN TO RUN RIGHT THROUGH
US.
I DON'T EVEN CARE.
>> Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH, ONE JUG OF ICED COFFEE.
LOSERS, NOTHING.
SOKO, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
CANNOT SIT OUT THE SAME PERSON
IN BACK-TO-BACK CHALLENGES.
WHOEVER SITS OUT HERE MUST
COMPETE IN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
WHO YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
CHRIS, YOU'RE GOING TO SIT THIS
ONE OUT.
YAWA, WHO YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
>> ME, I GUESS.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, LAUREN, TAKE
A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> Jeff: JESSICA, ROARK, AND
DESI OUT OF THE GATE.
DESI IS RIPPING IT UP.
DESI WITH AN EARLY LEAD.
GOT TO GET THERE WITH HER HEAD,
TOO.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, ASHLEY.
BLUE OUT THE A FAST LEAD THANKS
TO DESI.
>> COME ON, ROARK.
>> GET IN THERE, BABY.
>> Jeff: ROARK STRUGGLING.
>> COME ON, ROARK.
YOU GOT IT.
>> PUSH IT.
>> Jeff: AND IT IS JESSICA NOW
GETTING VERY CLOSE TO DR. MIKE.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
>> GET YOUR HEAD OVER HERE.
>> Jeff: GET YOUR HEAD.
THERE YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, DR. MIKE.
>> COME ON, MIKE.
>> NICE JOB, ASH.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY HAS THAT BALL
OVER THE HILL.
NOW SHE'S GOT TO GET HERSELF
OVER IT.
>> GREAT, ASH.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY SLITHERING
DOWN.
>> COME ON, ROARK.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE THERE.
GO, ALAN.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> YOU GOT IT, GIRL.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY, YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, JOE.
LEVU IS RIPPING THIS COURSE UP.
>> GO, JOE.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: LEVU WITH A HUGE LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
>> USE YOUR KNEES, MIKE.
>> Jeff: DR. MIKE STRUGGLING
TO GET ANY KIND OF A RHYTHM.
ALAN IS MOVING QUICKLY NOW.
SOKO BACK IN THIS.
>> USE THAT BODY.
ROLL IT.
>> Jeff: JOE IS ALREADY UP THE
COURSE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, BLUE, GO!
WOW.
LEVU WITH A HUGE LEAD RIGHT NOW.
>> I GOT YOU, ASH.
>> COME ON, MIKE.
>> Jeff: MIKE FACE FIRST.
>> COME ON, MIKE, YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD, ALI.
GO, RYAN.
>> NICE, RYAN!
YOU GOT IT
>>.
>> Jeff: DEVON ALREADY
SHOOTING FOR LEEFER LEAF.
THE OTHER TWO TEAMS WILL HAVE TO
MOVE VERY FAST TO HAVE A SHOT AT
THIS REWARD.
MIKE IS NOW IN LAST PLACE BUT
CONTINUES TO WORK.
YOU ARE ONLY AS FAST AS YOUR
SLOWEST.
RYAN DIGGING IN NOW.
RYAN LOSES THE BALL FOR SOKO.
A GIANT SETBACK.
>> LET'S GO.
PICK IT UP.
>> YOU'RE THERE, MIKE.
>> Jeff: OPENS THE DOOR FOR
SOKO.
DEVON WITH ANOTHER SHOT.
>> YOU GOT IT, DEV.
>> Jeff: FIRST ONE DROPS FOR
LEVU.
>> GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: IT IS NOW BEN WHO IS
TEARING IT UP.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT RIGHT
HERE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
YAWA.
GO.
>> K078 ON, COLE.
GOOD JOB.
>> DREW: THE DOOR IS STILL OPEN
FOR YAWA TO WIN THIS.
DEFERRED ACTION FOR CHILDHOOD
ARRIVALS -- DEVON MISSES AGAIN.
IT IS NOW RYAN TRYING AFTER
LOSING HIS BALL.
>> RYAN, YOU CAN DO THIS.
CONTROL, RYAN, CONTROL.
>> Jeff: RYAN LOSES THE BALL
AGAIN.
>> RYAN, DON'T GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: COME ON, COLE.
COLE IS SHOOTING FOR SOKO.
DEVON SHOOTING FOR LEVU.
THIS CHALLENGE IS WIDE OPEN
RIGHT NOW.
DEF WITHIN THE SECOND FOR LEVU.
RYAN'S TRIBE IS STILL IN IT.
TRYING FOR A THIRD TIME.
>> COME ON, RYAN.
YOU'RE STRONG.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
AND RYAN LOSES THE BALL AGAIN.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, DEV.
>> Jeff: DEVON WITH THE THIRD
FOR LEVU.
>> COME ON, COLE.
>> Jeff: COLE WITH FIRST FOR
YAWA.
DEVON WITH THE FOURTH FOR LEVU.
DEVON COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE,
AND HE DOES!
DEVON WINS REWARD, ICED COFFEE
AND PASTRIES.
LOOKING FOR SECOND PLACE.
>> WE CAN STILL COME BACK, RYAN.
>> THERE YOU GO, COME ON, RYAN.
>> Jeff: RYAN THE CLOSEST HE'S
BEEN TO GETTING IT OVER THE
HILL.
COLE MISSES AGAIN.
RYAN WORKING HIS WAY UP, USING
THAT FACE.
>> LET'S GO, MAN.
THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO.
-RYAN, YOU GOT THIS.
>> WE ARE DEFINITELY STILL IN
THIS, RYAN.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD, SOKO,
GO.
EVERYBODY GOT TO GET ON THE
MATT.
COLE WITH THE THIRD.
>> COLE, I NEED MY COFFEE!
>> Jeff: COLE SCORES THE
FOURTH.
J.P. HAS TO GET EVERYBODY TO
THAT MAT BEFORE HE CAN SHOOT.
WON'T MATTER, YAWA WINS REWARD,
SENDING SOKO BACK THE CAMP WITH
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
>> I'M SORRY, GUYS.
>> Jeff: LEVU, NEW TRIBE, NEW
RESULT, NICE WIN.
DOMINATING.
BIG REWARD.
ICED COFFEE, PASTRIES, AND
COFFEE AND TEA TO TAKE BACK THE
CAMP.
COME GET IT.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: YAWA, NOT AS BIG A
REWARD, BUT ON "SURVIVOR" ANY
WIN IS A WIN.
COME GRAB YOUR JUG OF ICED
COFFEE.
ENJOY IT.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SOKO, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> BRIAN DIDN'T THIS WELL IN THE
REWARD CHALLENGE, BUT CHALLENGES
ARE ONLY PART OF THE GAME.
I'VE BEEN ARE RYAN THE WHOLE
TIME, SO MY TRUST IS THERE.
I NEED TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO
HAVE HIS BACK.
>> WE GOT GOODIES.
>> THIS IS THE HAPPIEST I'VE
EVER BEEN.
WE WON THE SWEETEST REWARD SO
FAR, LITERALLY AND FIGURATIVELY.
NOT ONLY DID WE HAVE THIS HUGE
TRAY FULL OF PASTRIES, BUT A
COFFEE BREWING, TEA BREWING KIND
OF SETUP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MMM.
>> WE GOT THIS.
CHEERS, CHEERS.
>> TO THE FIRST AND BEST WIN
EVER.
>> FIRST OF MANY.
>> AFTER TRIBAL COUNCIL LAST
NIGHT, WE WERE CLEARLY DIVIDE,
BUT WITH THIS REWARD, IT'S TIME
FOR US TO COME TOGETHER AS A
TEAM.
SO I THINK WE CAN DO IT.
>> WHAT AN AMAZING DAY TO HAVE
AFTER LAST NIGHT.
>> WINNING THAT REWARD, IT WAS
JUST SO NICE.
SPIRITUALLY, PHYSICALLY,
MENTALLY, ALL OF IT.
BUT IT MAKES ME REALIZE MORE AND
MORE HOW IMPORTANT IT IS TO KEEP
MY MIND IN THE GAME.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR LETTING ME
STEP UP.
THANK YOU FOR TRUSTING ME.
>> NO EGOS, BRO.
>> I THINK THE BEST THING FOR MY
GAME IN THE END WOULD BE TO GET
RID OF JOE.
HE'S THE STRONGEST PLAYER I'VE
MET HERE AS FAR AS KNOWLEDGE OF
THE GAME, STRATEGY.
HE'S A GOOD PLAYER.
HE SCARES ME.
>> I'M GOING TO GO BATHE.
>> ASH, YOU GOOD?
>> ON WATER, YEAH.
>> SO ASH, THE SITUATION NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> JUST KNOW I'M WITH YOU.
I WANT US GO TO STAY TOGETHER.
>> TWO VERSUS TWO.
>> I'M STICKING WITH YOU BECAUSE
I TRUST YOU.
>> AFTER A NIGHT LIKE LAST
NIGHT, I'M FEELING INCREDIBLY
NERVOUS.
THE ONLY GOOD THING IS THAT I
HAVE DEVON.
WE ARE IN THIS TOGETHER.
>> I'M NOT VOTING WITH THEM,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
COOL.
I DON'T TRUST EITHER OF THEM.
>> I'D RATHER HAVE IT BE A TIE
THAN GO WITH THEM TWO.
>> YEAH.
SAME.
RIGHT NOW JOE THINKS HE'S
FINALLY IN CONTROL, BUT ME AND
DEVON ARE STILL IN THIS.
IT'S STILL 50/50.
THERE'S JUST NO MIDDLE MAN.
>> HOW DO WE GET DESI.
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT JOE IS
COMING.
>> DEVON AND I ARE REALLY GOING
TO WORK ON DESI.
WITH A TIE VOTE TO KEEP HERSELF
SAFE, I THINK SHE'D FLIP ON
SHOW.
IF NOT, THE NEXT VOTE IS GOING
TO ROCKS.
>> I'M SO FRICKING SORRY, GUYS.
>> IT'S A-OK, DUDE.
IT'S JUST A REWARD.
>> THANKS FOR CHEERING ME ON,
GUYS, I KEPT HEARING YOU.
>> I DID NOTHING IN, IN THIS
CHALLENGE, SO YOU DID WAY MORE
FOR ME.
>> AN ARGUMENT CAN BE MADE I DID
NOTHING.
>> THAT'S SO FUNNY.
>> THE REWARD CHALLENGE WAS AN
ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
I LOST THE CHALLENGE FOR MY
TRIBE.
>> LET'S OPEN A COCONUT.
>> WANT A SMALL ONE?
>> WANT ME TO TRY AND DO IT?
>> BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I JUST
HAVE TO CONTINUE TO CATER TO MY
SPECIFIC SKILL SET, WHICH IS MY
SOCIAL GAME, AND MY SOCIAL GAME
IS EVERYTHING.
IT IS BUILT UPON MAKING PEOPLE
LAUGH.
I'M A COCONUT OPENER WATCHER.
IF I CAN HELP PEOPLE GET THROUGH
THE DAY AND LAUGH, THEN IT'S
EASIER FOR THEM TO CRACK OPEN
THAT COCONUT FOR ME.
>> OH, THAT WAS GOOD.
>> AND PICK ME UP AFTER I LOSE A
CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY HAS FAILURE IN THE
GAME.
EVERYBODY.
YOU JUST DON'T WANT THAT FAILURE
TO BE GETTING VOTED OUT.
>> I HAVEN'T GRABBED WATER.
WANT A COUPLE OF US TO DO A
REFILL.
>> I CAN GO.
>> I'M OBJECTIVELY ON THE
OUTSIDE, AS I AM THE LONE HEALER
AT SOKO BEACH.
I LOVE A 2-2-1 SPLIT, AND I WANT
TO START DEVELOPING FRIENDSHIPS
WITH THESE PEOPLE WHERE THEY
FEEL SAFE WITH ME TO TALK GAME
WITH ME.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING, THE FACT
THAT YOU HAD SICK PEOPLE AND NEW
IT'S YOU?
>> OBVIOUSLY I HAVE FAITH THAT I
CAN RETURN WITH THEM FOR SURE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE ALWAYS
GOTTEN VERY GOOD VIBES FROM ALL
OF YOU GIRLS.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY GOOD TO
RECEIVE SOME SUPPORT FROM ALI,
SOME INTEREST IN WORKING
TOGETHER, AND WHEN WE MERGE, IF
SHE IS LOOKING FOR NUMBERS, I
CAN BRING SOME NUMBERS.
>> IT WOULD BE GIRLS AND THEN
WHAT, COLE?
>> COLE AND I BELIEVE I HAVE
MIKE.
>> REALLY?
I THINK I HAVE RYAN, BUT THE
THING IS IT'S HARD BECAUSE I
FEEL LIKE WHATEVER HAPPENS NEXT,
LIKE WE NEED STRONG.
>> I KNOW.
>> BUT RYAN DEFINITELY PLAYS THE
BEST SOCIAL GAME OUT THERE.
>> HE'S A TOTAL SWEETHEART.
>> I WANT TO KEEP HIM BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TO BE... THE HUSTLERS
WERE JUST A GROUP OF LOSERS, BUT
BEING HERE I CAN BUILD THESE
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS THAT I
KNOW WILL FURTHER MY GAME.
SO IF I CAN BUILD THIS RAPPORT
WITH ROARK, HOPEFULLY WHEN THE
MERGE DOES COME, SHE WILL TAKE
ME IN AS PART OF THEIR SIX,
SEVEN, BECAUSE AT THE BEGINNING
YOU NEED A LOT OF NUMBERS.
>> LET'S BE CAUTIOUS WITH
CHRISSY AND J.P.
>> I AGREE.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO KNOW TO
MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION, BUT I
THINK GOING WITH ROARK IS BEST
FOR OUR GAME.
THE NEXT TWO TRIBALS IF WE HAVE
TO GO, WE CAN VOTE OUT CHRISSY
AND J.P.
IF THIS WORKS OUT, WE CAN GO FAR
IN THIS GAME.
>> I HAD A GOOD TALK WITH ROARK.
>> ROARK?
>> YEAH.
SHE'S LIKE, I REALLY WANT TO
WORK WITH YOU.
I WAS LIKE, IF WE LOSE
CHRISSY,ER THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
>> I LIKE IT.
SO TELL ROARK THAT WE'RE ON
BOARD WITH HER.
THE GOOD NEWS IS I CONTINUE TO
BE IN POSITIONS WHERE PEOPLE
WANT TO WORK WITH ME.
>> I'M GOING TO STILL CHRISSY
THAT WE'RE ON BOARD WITH HER.
>> FOR SURE.
>> BUT UNFORTUNATELY MY TWO
CLOSEST ALLIANCE MEMBERS,
CHRISSY AND ALI, WILL NEVER WORK
WITH EACH OTHER.
SO I'M IN THE MIDDLE.
AND I NEED TO TREAD VERY LIGHTLY
NOT TO MESS THIS UP.
>> COLE'S EATING HABITS ARE VERY
BAD.
HE'S VERY INCONSIDERATE.
HE'S LIKE A PIG.
HE LICKS EVERYTHING.
HE IS LICKING THE SPOON.
THEN HE SCRATCHES BETWEEN HIGH
LEGS.
IT'S VERY GROSS.
>> ANYBODY ELSE WANT THE REST OF
MY RICE?
>> I'LL EAT IT.
>> BEN NOTICES IT.
HE'S ROLLING HIS EYES.
HE'S GETTING TICKED.
I HOPE COLE KEEPS DIGGING HIS
HOLE DEEPER AND DEEPER AND
DEEPER, AND MAYBE HIS LIPS WILL
STICK TOGETHER.
>> I'M GOING TO GET WATER.
ANYONE ELSE NEED WATER.
>> YEAH.
>> ADAM?
>> WHEN WE FIRST GOT HERE AFTER
THE SPLIT, I FELT LIKE COLE,
MIKE, AND I WERE IN CONTROL, BUT
AFTER SEEING COLE TELL SECRETS,
I DO BELIEVE THAT MIKE IS
PARANOID ABOUT COLE AS A NUMBER.
>> WE HAVE TO WIN TODAY.
>> YEAH, WE DO.
>> ON THE FLIP SIDE OF THAT,
MIKE CAN KEEP A SECRET, SO RIGHT
NOW IT WOULD BE TO THE BENEFIT
OF MY GAME TO FORM MORE OF A
BOND WITH MIKE.
DO YOU WANT THE DIG WHILE I
FILL?
>> OKAY.
ON OUR LAST ISLAND, JOE AND COLE
FOUND AN ITEM NEAR THE WELL, SO
THIS MORNING I GO TO THE WELL
WITH JESS CASH SHE SAYS, MIKE,
WHY DON'T YOU DIG SOME MORE.
SO I START DIGGING AGAIN.
>> I'M GOING TO START RIGHT
HERE.
>> COLE WOULD TELL US IF HE
FOUND IT, WOULDN'T HE?
>> I'M JUST DIGGING AND DIGGING
AND HOPING I FIND SOMETHING.
IF THERE IS AN IDOL, I'M GOING
THE FIND THAT IDOL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
>> I HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR THIS
IDOL NON-STOP.
THERE'S ALWAYS A DANGER IN
SOMEBODY ELSE KNOWING ABOUT THE
IDOL.
>> CONGRATULATION, YOU HAVE
FOUND THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I'M OKAY WITH JESSICA KNOWING
I HAVE THE IDOL.
SO AT THIS POINT I'M TRUSTING
HER.
>> CHA-CHING, BABY.
>> THIS IS FOR US.
IN REALITY, THIS IDOL IS MINE.
"SURVIVOR" IS ONLY ONE-THIRD
OVER.
BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGED IN GOING
FROM THE BOTTOM TO THE TOP.
THIS HAS BEEN THE STORY OF MY
LIFE, BUT YOU CAN NEVER
UNDERESTIMATE DR. MIKE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> SURE.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IDOLS.
THANK YOU, CHRISSY.
THANK YOU, JESSICA.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BECOME UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, WE'RE
GOING TO SWIM OUT THE A BOAT AND
RETRIEVE THREE BAGS OF RICE.
YOU MUST THEN PUSH THE RICE
THROUGH A HOLE, GET IT ACROSS
THE BALANCE BEAM TO SURE, WHERE
YOU WILL TEAR OPEN THE BAG
SEARCHING FOR THREE BALLS.
FINALLY YOU'LL MANEUVER THOSE
BALLS THROUGH A MAZE OF HOLES TO
THE TOP.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
SOKO, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
WHO YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
CHRISSY SAT OUT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE.
SHE MUST PARTICIPATE.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> ME.
>> RYAN GOING TO SIT OUT.
YAWA, ONE EXTRA PERSON.
LAUREN SAT OUT AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE, MUST PARTICIPATE.
>> MIKE.
>> MIKE GOING TO SIT OUT FOR
YAWA.
SITOUTS TAKE A SEAT ON THE
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, AND WE'LL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOUR FIRST STEP IS GET SOMEBODY
ON YOUR BOAT AND GET THOSE BAGS
OF RICE OFF.
YAWA DOING A NICE JOB.
ROARK DOING A NICE JOB FOR SOKO.
ASHLEY IS DOING A NICE JOB.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR BAGS OF
RICE.
NOW COMES THE FUN PART.
YOU'VE GOT TO SQUEEZE A
RECTANGULAR BAG OF RICE THROUGH
A VERY SMALL ROUND HOLE.
ASHLEY GOING OVER.
DESI IS OVER.
ALI GOING OVER.
CHRISSY GOING OVER.
LAUREN IS OVER.
AND VERY QUICKLY YAWA HAS THEIR
FIRST BAG THROUGH.
SOKO HAS THEIR FIRST BAG
THROUGH.
LEVU STILL WORKING ON THAT FIRST
BAG.
YAWA HAS THEIR SECOND BAG
THROUGH.
SOKO HAS THEIR SECOND BAG.
LEVU HAS THEIR FIRST BAG.
TRYING THE STAY IN IT.
SOKO WITH THAT THIRD BAG.
YOU'RE GOOD.
HEAD ON.
YAWA HAS THEIR THIRD BAG.
YOU'RE GOOD.
HEAD ON.
IT IS NOW LEVU, WHO DOMINATED IN
THE REWARD CHALLENGE, NOW
STRUGGLING IN THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
THEY CANNOT GET THAT SECOND BAG
THROUGH.
NEXT PHASE IS THE BALANCE BEAM.
YOU GOT TO GET THOSE HEAVY BAGS
OF RICE ACROSS THAT BEAM.
LEVU FINALLY HAS THEIR SECOND
BAG.
J.P. HEADING ACROSS THAT BEAM.
>> SLOW AND STEADY.
>> Jeff: HE'S THROUGH THE
FIRST THIRD.
LAUREN GIVES IT A GO.
SHE DROPS.
DEVON HAS THEIR THIRD BAG.
START MOVING, GUYS.
J.P. IS ACROSS.
>> THAT ABOY, J.P.
>> Jeff: DEVON MAKING IT LOOK
EASY.
LEVU IS RIGHT BACK IN THIS.
COLE NOW HEADING ACROSS FOR
YAWA.
ALI TRYING TO CARRY A BAG OF
RICE ON HER HEAD.
DESI DOING THE SAME THING.
ONCE AGAIN DESI IS MAKING A
CHALLENGE LOOK EASY.
J.P. NOW TRYING AGAIN WITH
ANOTHER BAG FOR SOKO.
YOU CAN GO AS OFTEN OF THE AS YO
WANT.
LEVU GOT OFF TO A TERRIBLE
START, BUT THEY HAVE NOW TAKEN
THE LEAD.
J.P. ACROSS WITH THE SECOND BAG.
BEN VERY CLOSE WITH THE SECOND
BAG.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
DEVON HAS THE THIRD BAG.
GO, LEVU.
COLE HAS THE THIRD BAG FOR YAWA.
IT IS NOW JOE WORKING ON
RECOVERING THOSE BALLS.
THEY'VE GOT A BIG LEAD.
LAUREN IS ACROSS.
GO, YAWA!
>> GO, GUYS.
YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: IT IS NOW SOKO IN
DEAD LAST.
THE LEAD IS OPENING NOW FOR LEVU
AND FOR YAWA.
IT IS NOW BEN RIPPING THROUGH
THAT BAG TRYING TO FIND THOSE
BALLS.
J.P. WITH THAT THIRD BAG FOR
SOKO.
JOE HAS THAT THIRD AND FINAL
BALL.
J.P. HAS CARRIED ALL THREE BAGS
IF HE CAN MAKE IT.
AND HE DOES.
BEN HAS THE SECOND BALL.
ASHLEY IS FIRST ON THE MAZE.
HERE COMES SOKO WITH THAT FIRST
BAG.
BEN HAS THE THIRD BALL.
THEY CAN START ON THE MAZE.
J.P. TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME LOST
TIME.
SOKO HAD A ROUGH GO OF IT ON THE
BALANCE BEAM.
>> SLOW IT DOWN.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY'S HAD A LOT OF
TIME TO LEARN THIS CHALLENGE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: HEAD STARTS MATTER IN
THIS GAME BECAUSE THERE IS A
LEARNING CURVE.
J.P. TRYING TO GET THAT THIRD
BALL FREE AND HE'S GOT IT.
THEY CAN START WORKING NOW ON
THIS MAZE.
IT'S GOING TO BE CHRISSY GOING
FIRST.
>> COME ON, CHRISSY.
>> Jeff: BEN IS DOING A NICE
JOB.
BEN GETS VERY CLOSE TO THE TOP,
AND BEN HAS THE FIRST ONE FOR
YAWA.
IT'S GOING TO BE JESSICA NOW IN.
>> DO I HAVE ENOUGH BALANCE BEAM
BEHIND ME?
>> Jeff: CHRISSY DROPS.
GOT TO DROP IT AND START AGAIN.
ASHLEY IS ONE BIG MOVE AWAY FROM
DROPPING THAT FIRST BALL FOR
LEVU.
AND THEY TIE IT UP.
LEVU HAS ONE.
>> I GOT TO TAKE MY SNEAKERS
OFF.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY DROPS AGAIN.
IT'S NOW ALI IN FOR SOKO.
DEVON ON THE MAZE FOR LEVU.
AS JESSICA INCHES CLOSER AND
CLOSER WITH THAT SECOND BALL FOR
YAWA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
TAKE A BREATH.
UP, UP, JESS.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS!
THAT'S TWO FOR YAWA.
THEY TAKE THE LEAD.
IT'S GOING TO BE COLE.
>> YOU'RE THROUGH, YOU'RE
THROUGH.
>> Jeff: ALI VERY CLOSE NOW TO
LANDING THAT FIRST BALL FOR
SOKO.
DEVON CLOSE WITH THE SECOND FOR
LEVU.
ALI HAS IT.
THAT'S ONE FOR SOKO.
CHRISSY GOING TO COME BACK IN.
DEVON VERY CLOSE WITH THAT
SECOND.
DEVON IS THERE WITH THE SECOND.
TIED AGAIN.
>> COLE, YOU GOT IT, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: COLE TWO-THIRDS OF
THE WAY UP FOR YAWA FOR THE WIN.
VERY CLOSE TO THE TOP.
CHRISSY IS HALFWAY THROUGH FOR
SOKO, WHO IS TRYING TO GET BACK
IN THIS.
AND DESI NOW ON THE COURSE FOR
LEVU.
COLE HAS PASSED THE LAST SPOT OF
DANGER.
HE CAN JUST GET THAT BALL TO
DROP, IT IS IMMUNITY FOR YAWA,
IN TRIBAL COUNCIL.
COLE CLOSER, CLOSER.
FOR THE WIN, YAWA HAS IT.
YAWA WINS IMMUNITY.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
THIS IS IT.
CHRISSY FEELS THE PRESSURE NOW.
GOT TO DROP THAT SECOND BALL TO
STAY IN IT.
CHRISSY FALLS AGAIN.
CANNOT FIGURE OUT THE BEAM.
>> DOES ONE OF YOU GUYS WANT THE
TRY?
>> DO YOU WANT ME THE TRY?
>> IT'S UP TO YOU.
I CAN TRY.
>> DO YOU WANT ALI TO TRY?
>> CHRISSY NOT GOING TO GIVE UP
HER SPOT.
DESI THREADING THE NEEDLE
NICELY.
CHRISSY IS TRYING TO CATCH UP.
>> I CAN'T STAY ON THE BALANCE
BEAM.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY DROPS AGAIN.
ANOTHER HUGE SETBACK.
DEAD VERY CLOSE FOR THE WIN WITH
LEVU.
SHE CAN DO IT RIGHT HERE.
IT'S OVER.
DESI WINS IMMUNITY, SENDING SOKO
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> NICE JOB, GUYS.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> Jeff: YAWA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IN TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> Jeff: LEVU, NICE JOB.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YAWA, LEVU, GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, ENJOY THE
NIGHT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, SOKO, GRAB JURY STUFF
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
HEROES V. HEALERS V. HUSTLERS."
>> TONIGHT IS MY FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I AM NERVOUS, BUT CHRISSY
DEFINITELY STRUGGLED IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
SHE NEEDS TO GO.
>> I DO NOT FEEL SAFE GOING INTO
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL.
AND I AM HAVING A HARD TIME
TRUSTING ANYONE, BUT I THINK
THAT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO
THERE IN ORDER TO MOVE FORWARD
IN THIS GAME.
>> YOU GUYS GOOD?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I WANT THE
GET WET AGAIN.
>> I AGREE.
>> I'M PROBABLY PRETTY GOOD.
>> YOU ALWAYS ARE NERVOUS IN
THIS GAME, AND I FEEL LIKE IF
I'M GOING TO PLAY, I WANT THE
PLAY BIG.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO DOWN?
>> OKAY.
>> SEE THAT BIG LOG THAT WASHED
UP, I WANTED TO GRAB THAT BEFORE
THE TIDE CAME BACK.
>> CAN WE JUST SIT FOR A SECOND?
I WANT THE HAVE A THOUGHTFUL
CONVERSATION.
>> OF COURSE.
>> I BELIEVE THAT ROARK IS IN T
NEXT MOST DANGEROUS PLAYER
BEHIND ME.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO PUT MY
FINGER ON IT.
>> YOU TO ME ARE THE MOST
STRATEGIC PLAYER IN THIS GAME,
AND I REALLY THOUGHT YOU AND I
TOGETHER COULD SIT DOWN HERE AND
TALK OUT OPTIONS.
IF WE SEND A BY HOME...
>> I COMPLETELY AGREE.
>> WE'RE HEADED TO TRIBAL AND
TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY CHRISSY
EVER FEELS THE NEED TO TALK GAME
WITH ME.
IN MY HEAD, I'M LIKE, ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
I WANT CHRISSY TO GO HOME.
>> THAT ALLOW, YOU, ALI AND ME
TO KEEP OPEN AN ALL-GIRL OPTION.
>> I PERSONALLY DON'T HAVE AN
OBJECTION.
>> IS THAT POTENTIALLY A
WORKABLE PLAN?
>> OF COURSE.
>> I WAS REALLY HOPING THAT
ROARK WANTED TO WORK WITH ME
GOING FORWARD, BUT I DON'T
BELIEVE ANYTHING SHE SAYS AND I
WISH I COULD STOP AND SAY TO
HER, YOU ARE NOT THE SMARTEST
PERSON HERE, BUT I DON'T WANT
THE RUIN MY GAME, SO MY PLAN IS
TO CREATE THIS IMAGINARY GIRL'S
ALLIANCE.
IF THERE IS A GIRL'S ALLIANCE,
THEN CLEARLY I WOULD NOT BE THE
ONE VOTED OUT, AND J.P. MIGHT
THINK HE WERE THE NEXT TO GO.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> THE FOUR OF US GET TOGETHER
AND VOTE OUT ROARK.
>> I THINK SHE'S GOOD IN
CHALLENGES, THOUGH, TOO.
>> ROARK WANTS TO DO AN
ALL-GIRLS ALLIANCE.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> OH, SHE'S GOT TO GO.
SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> J.P. AND I ARE TWO, SO NOW I
NEED RYAN.
I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT RYAN HAS
MY BACK.
>> I THINK ROARK IS TRYING TO
GET ALI AND ME.
>> SO THEY WOULD VOTE FOR ME,
BECAUSE THEY NEED THE KEEP J.P.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO WE WOULD NEED TO MAKE YOU,
ME, AND J.P.
>> RIGHT.
>> I BROUGHT IT UP WITH J.P., HE
REALLY LIKES ROARK, AND THEN I
SAID TO HIM, I HEARD SHE MIGHT
BE DOING AN ALL-GIRL ALLIANCE,
AND THEN HE'S LIKE, I'M DOWN
WITH THAT.
SO YOU, ME, AND J.P. AT LEAST?
>> PERFECT.
>> THE PLAN RIGHT NOW IS THAT
J.P., RYAN, AND MYSELF WILL
BLINDSIDE ROARK AND SEND HER
HOME.
>> CHRISSY SHOULD HAVE JUST
BACKED OUT AFTER SHE TRIED SO
MANY TIMES.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> CHRISSY'S PROBABLY GOING TO
SAY YOU.
>> LET'S KEEP WHITTLING THE
HEROES DOWN.
>> THE MAIN REASON FOR TAKING
OUT CHRISSY TONIGHT IS SHE COULD
NOT BALANCE ON THAT BEAM.
AND WITH HER, WE'RE NOT GOING TO
BE AS STRONG IN CHALLENGES.
AND SO I WANT CHRISSY TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
>> WHAT DID ROARK SAY?
>> ROARK SAID WE GET RID OF
CHRISSY.
>> CHRISSY?
ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW I TRUST YOU AND I
TRUST ROARK.
I TRUST YOU THE MOST.
>> I'M IN THE SWING VOTE
POSITION.
I SEEMINGLY HAVE THE CHOICE
TONIGHT ON WHO TO SEND HOME.
ME AND CHRISSY ARE SO TIGHT
BECAUSE THAT FIRST DAY I WENT TO
HER WITH THE ADVANTAGE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, ALI HAS ONLY
PLAYED THE GAME WITH ONE PERSON,
AND THAT PERSON IS ME.
AND WHOEVER I GO WITH, THERE'S
GOING TO BE ONE PERSON WHO IS
GOING TO HATE ME.
THIS IS A HUGE DECISION, BUT I'M
HERE TO TRY AND WIN THIS GAME TO
BUILD THE BEST SOCIAL GAME I
CAN, AND UNFORTUNATELY I'M
BREAKING THAT SOCIAL BOND WITH
SOMEBODY TONIGHT, BUT I STILL
THINK IT BEST ADVANCES MY GAME.
>> Jeff: ROARK, GRAB THE UNLIT
TORCH, DIP IT IN, AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
SO ALI, ONE OF THE THINGS ABOUT
"SURVIVOR" IS EVERYBODY BRINGS A
DIFFERENT APPROACH TO THE GAME.
HAVE YOU NOTICED ANY DIFFERENCE
IN HOW THE HUSTLERS OR THE
HEROES OR THE HEALERS ARE
PLAYING THE GAME?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I THINK TODAY'S LOSS
KIND OF SHOWED A LITTLE BIT,
WHERE IF I WAS UNABLE TO
COMPLETE THE TASK AT HAND, I
WOULD SAY, WE HAVE THREE OTHER
PEOPLE THE MAKE IT HAPPEN AND
MOVE OUT OF THE WAY.
>> WAIT.
I DID THAT.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ME?
>> I FELT THAT YOU STARTED IT...
>> I TURNED AROUND SO MANY TIMES
AND SAID, DOES ANYBODY WANT THE
TAKE OVER, AND YOU GUYS WERE
LIKE, NO, KEEP GOING, KEEP
GOING.
>> I BUT I WOULD HAVE SAID, YOU
GUYS TREE, WE NEED SOMEONE TO
GET US ON THE BOARD.
>> I REMEMBER TURNING SEVERAL
TIMES AND SAYING, WHO WANTS TO
TAKE THIS?
AND THEY ALL STOOD THERE AND
SAID, YOU GO AGAIN.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> IT'S HER SIDE, MY SIDE, AND
THE TRUTH, RIGHT?
>> Jeff: AND THERE IS A VOTING
BOOTH 20 YARDS FROM HERE ABOUT
TO GET USED.
RYAN, THESE ARE THE THINGS THAT
ULTIMATELY CAN DECIDE A VOTE.
>> A LOT OF THE TIMES THE TRUTH
IS WHAT YOU MADE OF IT.
I DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY GIVE UP OR
ANYBODY CONTROLLING.
I SAW US TRYING TO COMPLETE THE
TASK IN THE BEST WAY TO CATCH US
UP AN COMPLETE THE CHALLENGE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU GOT
BACK FROM CAMP?
>> I HADN'T TALKED ANY STRATEGY
AT ALL WITH ROARK AND I DIDN'T
WANT TO COME THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
AND NEVER HAVE HAD A
CONVERSATION WITH HER ABOUT WHAT
WE WERE GOING TO DO NEXT.
>> AND I HOPE WE CAN SPEAK MORE
CONSISTENTLY ABOUT IT, BECAUSE
ON THE DAY WHEN YOU NEEDED ME IS
THE DAY WHEN YOU CALLED, INSTEAD
OF SOUNDING BOARD WITH ME AS WE
WERE GOING.
SO THAT WOULD JUST BE A
PREFERENCE MOVING FORWARD.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, THAT'S TWO
STRIKES, CHRIS SIMILAR FROM ALI
ON THE CHALLENGE, CRITICISM FROM
ROARK, YEAH, YOU'RE MY FRIEND
NOW.
>> SHE DIDN'T TALK TO ME EITHER.
THIS IS A TWO-WAY STREET HERE A
LITTLE BIT.
I SPECIFICALLY TALKED TO ALI,
RYAN CAME TO ME.
I WAS TALKING TO J.P.
WE WERE ALL TALKING TO EACH
OTHER, SO I DON'T KNOW WHY THIS
HAS TO BE A CHRISSY HAS TO
APPROACH ROARK SITUATION WHERE
SHE COULD HAVE COME TO ME, AS
WELL.
>> SHE JUST SAID SHE
SPECIFICALLY TALKED TO ALI.
SHE NEVER SPECIFICALLY TALKED TO
ME.
>> I HAVE NO COMMENT.
>> Jeff: RYAN, WHAT DID YOU
SEE?
>> CHRISSY TOOK ROARK DOWN TO
THE BEACH.
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT THEY WERE
TALKING ABOUT.
YOU START RUNNING EVERYTHING
THROUGH YOUR HEAD BECAUSE IT
ONLY TAKES THREE TONIGHT.
>> J.P. WHAT WAS YOUR TAKE?
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN TWO GIRLS
WALK AWAY, YOU START RUNNING
THOSE SCENARIOS THROUGH YOUR
HEAD.
THERE'S TWO GUYS AND THREE GIRL,
SO THAT COULD BE ANOTHER WAY TO
GO WITH IT, AND THAT MAKES ME
UNEASY SITTING HERE.
>> Jeff: SO CHRISSY, IF IT'S
TRUE THAT MAYBE THESE ORIGINAL
LINES ARE BLURRED, ARE YOU MORE,
LESS, OR THE SAME IN TERMS OF
UNCOMFORTABLE ABOUT THE VOTE
TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I THINK I CAME HERE
TONIGHT EXPECTING THAT IT COULD
BE ME TONIGHT.
SO HEARING ALL OF THIS FROM ALL
OF THEM, IT'S SURPRISING AND
IT'S NOT SURPRISING.
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING TO BEAT
MYSELF UP OVER IT.
I'M DOING THE BEST I CAN.
>> Jeff: ROARK, HOW ABOUT FOR
YOU?
ARE YOU NOW MORE COMFORTABLE OR
LESS COMFORTABLE SINCE SHE SAT
DOWN?
>> CAN I FEEL THE SAME
COMFORTABLE?
>> Jeff: YEAH.
>> I FEEL THE SAME COMFORTABLE.
I'VE MADE BONDS I BELIEVE IN
THAT I CAN VOTE BASED UPON.
>> Jeff: SO ALI, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE SOMEBODY WHO BELIEVES THEY
HAVE BONDED WITH AT LEAST TWO
PEOPLE.
>> I THINK THAT YOU CAN'T REALLY
EVER EARN TRUST UNTIL YOU GET
HERE.
ROARK HAD A GREAT TRIBE WITH THE
HEALERS, BUT DID THEY REALLY
KNOW AND UNDERSTAND THE TRUST
THAT SAY ME AND RYAN KNOW
BECAUSE WE VOTED TOGETHER OR
CHRISSY AND J.P. KNOW BECAUSE
THEY VOTE TOGETHER?
ONCE WE GET HERE, THAT'S WHEN
YOU FIND OUT WHO YOU CAN TRUST.
>> Jeff: SO ROARK, TWO
HUSTLER, TWO HEALERS, YOU IN THE
MIDDLE.
ARE YOU THE SWING, OR ARE YOU
THE EASY VOTE?
>> I THINK TONIGHT I'M THE
SWING.
NOTHING I HEARD TONIGHT HAS
CHANGED MY VOTE FOR WHAT I THINK
WILL MAKE US A STRONGER TRIBE
MOVING FORWARD.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, IF THIS IS
TRUE, ONE OF THE TWOSOMES IS
ABOUT TO BE BROKEN UP.
>> I DON'T SEE IT AS A TWO, A
ONE AND A TWO AT THIS POINT.
I THINK THE RELATIONSHIPS HAVE
FORMED OVER THE LAST FIVE DAYS
THAT IT COULD BE ANY THREE
PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S FIND OUT WHERE THE THREE
GOES.
TIME TO VOTE.
ROARK, YOU'RE UP.
>> NEXT TIME DON'T COME FOR ME.
>> I'M OUTSMARTING MISS SMARTY
PANTS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE CHRISSY.
ROARK.
CHRISSY.
TWO VOTES CHRISSY.
ROARK.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES ROARK, TWO VOTES
CHRISSY, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: HEROES V. HEALERS V.
HUSTLERS", ROARK.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ROARK, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
GO.
WELL, THE STATED GOAL OF
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL WAS A STRONGER
TRIBE, BUT WITH A DIVIDED VOTE,
CLEARLY THE FIRST STEP WILL BE
REPAIR.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES AND HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
>> Jeff: TEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," TEXS ARE HIGH.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
YOU JUST WROTE CHRISSY'S NAME
DOWN.
>> BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED.
>> I SAID I WASN'T GOING TO CRY,
BUT IT'S ROUGH.
>> Jeff: AND IT ALL COMES
CRASHING DOWN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
COLE, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M NOT READY THE PLAY THIS
GAME WITHOUT COLE.
>> IT WAS A GREAT EXPERIENCE.
I WOULD TELL ANY SUPER FAN TO DO
IT, BUT I'M BUMMED.
I FELT LIKE I HAD A LOT MORE IN
ME, AND I SUPPOSE I TRUSTED THE
WRONG PEOPLE.
THE PROBLEM IS IT WAS MY FIRST
TRIBAL, SO I CAN'T TELL WHO
VOTED WITH ME.
I ALWAYS THINK THERE IS
SOMETHING SOMEONE CAN DO, AND
EVIDENTLY I DIDN'T DO THAT.
I OWN THAT.