SHE HAD IT RIGHT.
JOE, GET ONE BIG SHOT.
WE HAVE PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER THE
WORLD CAME OUT HERE TO BE WITH
US TONIGHT.
VERY COOL.
AND LET'S SAY HELLO TO OUR 18
PLAYERS THAT GAVE US SUCH AN
ENTERTAINING SEASON.
EVERYBODY NOW BACK.
SO, BEN IS STILL BASKING IN THE
GLORY OF HIS WIN.
BUT, BEN, EVERY HERO NEEDS A
WORTHY ADVERSARY, AND YOU HAD
ONE IN CHRISSY.
>> YES, YES.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, I GOTTA GIVE
IT YOU UP TO YOU, IT WAS REALLY
OUTSTANDING FROM-- TAKE ME BACK
BECAUSE 16 YEARS YOU APPLIED TO
BE ON THIS SHOW.
YOU FINALLY GET OUT THERE.
AND I REMEMBER STANDING AT THE
END OF THAT FIRST CHALLENGE WHEN
YOU WERE THROWING UP.
WHAT-- WHEN YOU FINALLY GOT THE
DREAM, WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU
GOT OUT THERE?
WAS IT OVERWHELMING FOR A
MOMENT?
>> YES.
THE FUNNY THING ABOUT DREAMS,
RIGHT, IS THAT IS IT BETTER TO
HAVE A DREAM THAT YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO TURNS OUT AND YOU CAN
IMAGINE IT OR ACTUALLY GET THAT
DREAM AND FIND OUT FOR REAL?
AND WHEN I FOUND MYSELF OUT
THERE, I WAS TERRIFIED.
AND I WAS SO TERRIFIED THAT IT
WASN'T GOING TO LIVE UP-- OR I
WASN'T GOING TO DO AS WELL AS I
POSSIBLY COULD HAVE.
AND SO THAT'S WHY I THREW UP.
I WAS-- I WAS SO SCARED.
>> Jeff: WELL, AND I WANT TO
REMIND PEOPLE, YOU GAVE UP A
LOT.
YOU KNOW, YOU GAVE UP YOUR JOB.
DID YOU GET YOUR JOB BACK?
>> NO, I ASKED FOR THE TIME OFF,
AND I ACTUALLY LOST MY JOB TO
PLAY THIS GAME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE
DAY, IT'S A GIFT.
RIGHT?
IT WAS A GIFT OF TIME THEY GOT
WITH MY FAMILY, AND I HAVEN'T
GONE BACK YET.
AND I'VE BEEN ENJOYING EVERY
MOMENT OF BEING WITH THEM.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Jeff: WOW, THAT'S
FANTASTIC.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: RYAN, YOU KNOW,
EVERYBODY JOKED ABOUT YOUR TINY
BODY, BUT THAT'S HOW YOU WERE
WHEN WE MET YOU.
YOU'RE A SMALL GUY.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: BUT DID THE FOOD, THE
LACK OF FOOD STILL SURPRISE EVEN
YOU?
>> OH, YEAH, THE DEPRIVATION OUT
THERE WAS A COMPLETE SHOCK FOR
ME.
I HAD NEVER SEEN MY HEART
BEATING THROUGH MY CHEST.
IT SHOWED PEOPLE I DO INDEED
HAVE A HEART AT LEAST.
IT'S SO REAL.
AND YOU SIGN UP FOR IT, AND I'VE
WATCHED IT FOR YEARS, DISECTED
THE SHOW WITH MY DAD.
BUT YOU DON'T DISSECT, YOU KNOW
NOT BEING ABLE TO EAT AND YOU
CAN'T PREPARE FOR THAT.
GETTING OUT THERE AND PUSHING
YOURSELF.
LIFE DOESN'T GIVE YOU MANY
OPPORTUNITIES TO PUT YOURSELF IN
SITUATION WHERE'S YOU CAN PROVE
IT TO YOURSELF AND, YOU KNOW, I
CAME UP SHORT, YEAH, BUT I
PROVED TO MYSELF THEY CAN HANG
WITH THE BEST.
>> Jeff: CONGRATS.
( APPLAUSE )
WELL, ONE OF THE THINGS THAT I
THINK KEEPS "SURVIVOR" RELEVANT
IS WE HAVE NEW PEOPLE PLAYING
EVERY YEAR AND THEIR STORIES ARE
OF THE MOMENT BECAUSE THEY'RE
CURRENT, AND SOMETIMES THEIR
STORIES BRING TO LIGHT SOMETHING
IMPORTANT THAT IS GOING ON IN
THE CULTURE RIGHT NOW.
WE SAW IT LAST YEAR WITH ZEKE
AND TRANSGENDER ISSUES.
IT WAS A CULTURAL MILESTONE.
WE HAD ANOTHER IMPORTANT STORY
THAT EMERGED THIS SEASON WITH
BEN.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I WAS IN THE MARINE CORPS.
>> DAMN IT!
>> I THINK HE HAS P.T.S.D.
>> I DON'T LIKE LOUD NOISES LIKE
THAT.
WHEN YOU GO THROUGH COMBAT AND
YOU COME BACK, THERE'S NO WAY TO
ADJUST FULLY.
THERE'S THINGS UPSTAIRS THAT ARE
THERE FOREVER.
COMING BACK WITH THAT STUFF,
IT'S HARD, AND YOU FEEL LONELY.
I DIDN'T SWEAR ON THE MARINE CO.
OTHER PEOPLES, CIVILIANS,
WHATEVER, HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO BE SHOT AT, TO HAVE
PEOPLE TRY TO KILL YOU.
SO THOSE REACTIONS ARE 100% REAL
FOR MEN AND WOMEN HAVE THAT
FOUGHT FOR OUR COUNTRY.
MY WIFE AND KIDS HAVE DEFINITELY
SAVED ME FROM MY DEMONS AND THE
PAST.
BUT THERE'S A BIGGER PICTURE,
AND IT'S BIGGER THAN ME, MY
FAMILY, THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
JUST BEING ABLE TO SHOW VETS WHO
HAVE GONE THROUGH BATTLE AND
P.T.S.D., THERE'S A WAY TO LIFE
OUTSIDE OF ALL THAT HELL.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK FORWARD TO THE
FUTURE, BECAUSE THE PAST WILL
EAT YOU ALIVE, BUT THE FUTURE
WILL SAVE YOU.
AND THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: SO, BEN, HAVE YOU
HEARD FROM A LOT OF PEOPLE?
I MEAN, YOU WERE PRETTY
VULNERABLE.
WE EVEN SAW YOU HAVE A MOMENT
WHERE SOME BAMBOO EXPLODED, AND
IT BROUGHT IT ALL BACK.
DID YOU-- DID PEOPLE REACH OUT
TO YOU?
>> YES, YEAH, THERE ARE A LOT OF
VETS WHO REACHED OUT AND SAID
THEY UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M GOING
THROUGH AND THANKS FOR, YOU
KNOW, BEING BRAVE AND SHOWING
THAT.
AND A LOT OF MY OLD BUDDIES THAT
I HAVEN'T SEEN FOR A WHILE, YOU
KNOW, HIT ME UP --
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, IT WAS AMAZING.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE EMOTIONAL
ABOUT THAT.
>> I LOVE THOSE GUYS, YOU KNOW.
WE WENT THROUGH A LOT TOGETHER,
AND IT'S JUST NICE TO BE ABLE TO
TALK TO THEM.
>> Jeff: SO YOU HADN'T EVEN
TALKED TO THEM IN HOW LONG?
>> PROBABLY FOUR, FIVE, SEVEN
YEARS, EIGHT YEARS-- WOW.
>> Jeff: IT'S KIND OF
INTERESTING, YOU WERE ONLY
PERSON I THINK UP THERE THAT
KEPT A SECRET THIS SEASON, AND
IT PAID OFF.
BUT WE'RE ALSO PRETTY GOOD AT
KEEPING A SECRET, AND I HAVE
SOMETHING I WANT TO SHARE WITH
YOU.
COME DOWN HERE WITH ME BECAUSE
WE HAVE THREE OF YOUR BUDDIES
WHO WANTED TO COME OUT HERE AND
REUNITE WITH YOU.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
BEN'S FORMER MARINE BUDDIES.
GUYS, COME OVER HERE.
GOTTA GET THE HAT, MAN.
BEN LOVES HIS HAT.
COME ON OVER, BEN.
NOW, THIS IS-- THIS IS A LEGIT
SURPRISE.
AND I'LL TELL YU-- WHY WE DID
THIS.
BECAUSE WE ACTUALLY JUST TRACKED
SOME OF YOU GUYS DOWN TO SEE
WHAT IMPACT IT WAS HAVING OW.
AND THE SECOND WE BROUGHT IT UP,
ALL THESE GUYS SAID, "CAN WE
COME?
CAN WE TELL BEN HOW MUCH IT
MEANS?"
GUYS-- WHO WANTS TO SPEAK-- BUT
WHY WAS IT SO IMPORTANT THAT BEN
WAS OPEN ABOUT THE P.T.S.D.?
>> MAN, WE HAVEN'T SEEN BEN IN
12 YEARS.
AND LAST TIME WE SAW HIM, HE
WASN'T IN A GOOD PLACE, SO TO
SEE HIM COME FROM WHERE WE LEFT
OFF TO NOW, COULDN'T BE MORE
PROUD OF YOU, BROTHER.
>> Jeff: IS IT PART OF IT
BECAUSE IT TAKES SOMEBODY TO
STEP UP AND SAY, "I'LL SHOW YOU.
I KNOW I'M A MARINE, BUT I'LL
SHOW YOU.
I HAD SOME HARD TIMES."
IS THAT PART OF WHY THIS IS SO
IMPORTANT TO GET WORD OUT.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
IT'S NOT JUST FOR US THAT WE
WATCH, WE SEE WHERE WE CAN GO.
BUT PEOPLE IF HE PULLS ONE VET
OUT OF THE GUTTER BY HIS STORY,
THAT'S HUGE.
>> RIGHT ON.
>> Jeff: A SUPER COOL REUNION,
AND THIS IS WHAT COMES FROM BEN
BEING BRAVE ENOUGH TO TELL HIS
STORY.
AND IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS
RIGHT NOW AND IT FEELS LIKE YOU,
YOU KNOW, YOU THINK YOU'RE
SUFFERING FROM P.T.S.D., REACH
OUT AND ASK FOR HELP.
THERE'S A U.R.L. ON THE SCREEN
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE THIS IS WHY HE
OPENED UP TO SHOW YOU THERE CAN
BE A LIGHT AT THE END OF THE
TUNNEL.
WE'RE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
WE'LL BE BACK FOR MORE FINALE
AFTER THIS.
>> Jeff: WELL, SO LIKE I SAID
AT THE TOP OF THE SHOW, ONE BIG
IDEA WE HAD WAS LET'S MAKE THIS
THE SEASON OF SECRETS.
AND EVERYTHING WAS GOING TO BE
CENTERED AROUND SECRET
ADVANTAGES AND SECRET IDOLS AND
THE PLAYERS THAT HAD THESE
SECRET ADVANTAGES WERE GOING TO
SHOCK ALL THE OTHER PLAYERS
BECAUSE THEY HAD A SECRET AND
THEN NOBODY COULD KEEP A SECRET.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SO I FOUND AN ADVANTAGE.
I HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE ELSE.
>> I GOT IT.
>> YEAH!
>> THE FACT THAT COLE KNOWS THAT
I HAVE THE IDOL COULD BACKFIRE.
BUT I DON'T THINK COLE HAS TOLD
ANYBODY.
>> JOE HAS THE IDOL.
WE FOUND IT PENTAGON.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> THIS ADVANTAGE IS YOUR SECRET
TO SHARE OR NOT SHARE WITH
ANYONE ELSE.
I FOUND A SECRET ADVANTAGE IN MY
CHIP BAG.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> JESSICA FOUND AN ADVANTAGE.
>> HOLY COW.
>> SO JESSICA FOUND AN
ADVANTAGE.
>> I WILL BE USING YOUR LITTLE
SECRET TO MY ADVANTAGE.
>> THEY KNOW ABOUT MY ADVANTAGE!
>>
>> I DON'T THINK WE'LL BE
SCREWED.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE I HAVE AN IDOL IN MY
PANTS.
>> SHUT UP.
>> LET'S GET IT ALL OUT IN THE
OPEN WHAT, DO YOU KNOW?
>> RYAN HAS AN IDOL.
>> AND I FOUND A SECRET
ADVANTAGE AND IT'S STILL IN
PLAY.
>> NOBODY AROUND HERE CAN KEEP A
DARN SECRET.
THANK YOU, FAMILY.
I NEED THE IDOL, AND I AIN'T
TELLING NO ONE ABOUT IT.
>> LAUREN HAS THE ADVANTAGE.
>> DON'T REVEAL THAT YOU HAVE AN
IDOL OR AN ADVANTAGE!
>> Jeff: LAUREN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> GOOD GAME, LAUREN.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING WAS OUT IN
THE OPEN, AND YET THE ONE THING
THAT HAD THE MOST POWER WAS THE
ONLY SECRET.
>> SECRET, SECRET, SECRET.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: SO, LAUREN, LET'S
TALK ABOUT THIS.
THIS IS THE-- CAN WE SHOW THIS?
THIS IS THE SHELL THAT MIKE
THREW IN THE FIRE BECAUSE YOU
TOLD HIM HUIT, AND THEN YOU GAVE
IT TO HIM.
ANY REGRETS?
OR IS IT-- AND I'M BEING-- I'M
NOT JOKING-- DO YOU REGRET THAT,
OR WAS THAT A MOVE THAT YOU MADE
AND IT JUST DIDN'T WORK?
>> NO, I REGRET IT 100%.
I CAN HAVE IT BACK?
CAN I HAVE IT BACK?
>> Jeff: NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE IT
BACK.
BUT I LOVE THAT YOU REGRET IT
BECAUSE THIS AND THIS-- DOES
ANYBODY HERE REMEMBER WHAT THIS
IS?
ANYBODY RECOGNIZE THIS?
EXACTLY, JAMES'-- JAMES IN
"SURVIVOR: CHINA" SEASON 15, SO
10 YEARS AGO, HE HAD TWO OF
THESE IN HIS POCKET.
HE GOT VOTED OUT WITH BOTH OF
THEM.
THIS AND THIS IS ANOTHER CLUE TO
WHAT WE'RE DOING NEXT SEASON.
BAD DECISIONS FROM FORMER
PLAYERS COMING BACK TO HAUNT.
ALL WILL BE REVEEM REVEALED WHEN
RETURN.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE BEST PARTS
OF THIS JOB IS WHEN WE COME UP
WITH A NEW IDEA THAT WE REALLY
THINK YOU'RE GOING TO DIG AND WE
HAVE ONE.
IT'S DIFFERENT, BIG, SUPER FUN
FOR OUR 36th SEASON WE
DECIDED TO DO SOMETHING THAT
SPEAKS TO THE PAST 35 SEASONS,
AND REALLY GETS AT THE HEART OF
WHY "SURVIVOR" IS SO FUN TO
WATCH AND SO DIFFICULT TO PLAY.
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR."
IT IS THE MOST COMPLICATED GAME
OF SOCIAL POLITICS EVER CREATED.
>> THIS ISN'T ABOUT MAKING
FRIENDS.
I NEED THAT ADVANTAGE.
IT WORKED.
>> Jeff: THERE IS NO ONE TO
RELY ON.
MICHAELA.
>> WHAT!
>> Jeff: NO ONE TO TRUST.
>> DID YOU DO THAT?
>> YEAH.
DIIT.
>> Jeff: EVERYTHING RESTS ON
YOUR ABILITY TO MAKE THE RIGHT
DECISION.
>> I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
>> Jeff: ...AT THE RIGHT TIME.
>> YOU'LL OFFICIALLY GO DOWN AS
THE DUMBEST IN THE HISTORY OF
"SURVIVOR" EVER.
>> Jeff: BECAUSE ONE BAD
DECISION... THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
...CAN HAUNT YOU FOREVER.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR," GHOST
ISLAND.
THE GRAVEYARD FOR BAD "SURVIVOR"
DECISIONS.
>> I ROLLED THE DICE TOO MANY
TIMES.
I HAD THE TWO IDOLS.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE PLAYED
THEM.
>> Jeff: AND AFTER 35 SEASONS
--
>> OOPSY.
>> Jeff: ...THERE HAVE BEEN A
LOT OF THEM.
THIS IS NOT A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER, A NEW
GROUP OF PLAYERS WILL HAVE THE
CHANCE TO REVERSE THE CURSE OF
SOME OF THE WORST DECISIONS IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
AN ENTIRE SEASON CENTERED AROUND
THE BAD DECISIONS OF PAST
PLAYERS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S NOT THE IDOL!
>> WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
>> Jeff: USING THE ACTUAL
ADVANTAGES AND IDOLS THAT DID
THEM IN.
>> HE GAVE ME A PIECE OF THE
IDOL.
DO THE "SURVIVOR" GODS MAKE HER
PAY FOR IT OR NOT?
>> Jeff: WILL THESE NEW
PLAYERS LEARN FROM THE MISTAKES
OF OTHERS.
>> IT'S THE STUPIDEST MOVE YOU
COULD EVER MAKE IN THE GAME.
I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE THAT
MISTAKE.
>> Jeff: OR WILL THE PAST COME
BACK TO HAUNT AGAIN?
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO LISTEN TO
YOUR GUT EVEN MORE THIS SEASON
THAN EVER BEFORE.
>> Jeff: JOIN US THIS SPRING
FOR "SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND" WILL
BE HERE IN JUST A COUPLE OF
Captioning funded by CBS
>> Jeff: IF THIS LOOKS LIKE
FUN AND YOU WANT TO BE A
CONTESTANT ON "SURVIVOR" GO TO
cbs.com/CASTING.
AND IF YOU WANT TO BID ON PROP,
GO TO SURVIVORAUCTIONS.COM.
ANOTHER GREAT SEASON.
ANOTHER GOOD ONE ON THE WAY.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
THANKS FOR ALL YOUR LOYALTY.
Captioning funded by CBS
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org