>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AFTER THE MERGE, THE
MAJORITY ALLIANCE WAS RUNNING
THE GAME.
>> WE NEED A HEALER GONE.
>> Jeff: BUT TRUST CAME INTO
QUESTION.
>> I THOUGHT I TRUSTED RYAN,
MAN.
>> Jeff: AND CRACKS BEGAN TO
FORM.
>> PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO FEEL
STEAM ROLLED BY YOU.
>> NO, NO, THEY ARE NOT.
>> AT THIS WAY IT'S BEN'S WAY OR
THE HIGHWAY.
>> Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
MIKE TRIED TO CHANGE THE GAME.
>> TRUST ME.
>> Jeff: HE CAUSED CHAOS.
>> I THINK YOU GUYS ARE SHOWING
POOR MORAL CHARACTER HERE.
>> DO YOU WANT THE BURY
YOURSELF?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO OPEN YOUR
MOUTH.
>> I'M PLAYING IT FOR ME.
>> Jeff: IN THE END, THE
MAJORITY STUCK TOGETHER AND SENT
COLE TO THE JURY.
COLE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> Jeff: NINE ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> MIKE, THAT WAS HILARIOUS.
THANK YOU FOR NOT INFORMING ME.
>> MY PLEASURE.
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING TO SPICE
IT UP A LITTLE BIT.
>> SPICE IT UP A LITTLE BIT, BUT
THAT WAS A STUPID REASON TO PLAY
YOUR IDOL, THOUGH.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS CRAZY AND
FUN.
THE SEVEN ACCOMPLISHED EXACTLY
WHAT THEY NEEDED TO ACCOMPLISH,
WHICH WAS MAINLY VOTE OUT COLE.
BUT THE BEST PART OF THE NIGHT
WAS WHEN OUT OF LEFT FIELD
DR. MIKE PLAYED AN IDOL, FOR IN
REASON AT ALL.
IT WAS ICING ON THE CAKE.
SO AT THIS POINT, WE HAVE TWO
HEALERS LEFT TO VOTE OUT.
JOE AND MIKE ARE DEAD MEN
WALKING.
>> IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
>> TELL ME LATER.
>> I'LL TELL YOU LATER.
I HAD TO PLAY MY IDOL FOR TWO
REASONS.
ONE, BECAUSE I'M NOT GOING TO BE
THAT IDIOT THAT GOES HOME WITH
AN IDOL IN HIS POCKET.
BUT I ALSO KNEW THERE WAS CHANCE
THAT THEY MIGHT WRITE JOE
INSTEAD OF ME, AND I NEED HIM
WITH ME.
SO I HAD THE MAKE SURE THEY WERE
GOING TO WRITE MY NAME.
NOW MY VOTE COMES ALONG WITH
ANOTHER VOTE, SO WE'RE A BLOC OF
TWO, VERSUS COLE STAYING HERE,
I'M STILL JUST A BLOC OF ONE.
SO MAKE SURE YOU'RE STILL HERE.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT, BUT...
>> NICE TRY, LADY LIBERTY.
>> IT DIDN'T GO ANYWHERE.
>> AT TRIBAL MAKE JUST EXPLODED.
HE WAS THE VILLAIN, WHICH I WAS
UPSET BECAUSE THAT'S MY ROLE,
THAT'S MY LANE.
BUT HE DEFINITELY MESSED UP WITH
THE IDOL, BECAUSE NO ONE KNEW HE
HAD AN IDOL, SO WE COULD HAVE
USED IT DOWN THE ROAD FOR A
BLIND SIDE FOR HIM AND I TO MOVE
FORWARD IN THE GAME.
NOW WE'RE JUST TWO SWING VOTES
WITH NO ALLIANCE, NO POWER, AND
NO IDOL.
>> IF YOU TRY TO DO SOMETHING AS
A TEAM THING, YOU HAVE TO LIKE
TALK IT OUT FIRST.
LET ME KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
I'M OVER THERE LIKE, WHAT?
>> IT APPEARS THAT I MIGHT HAVE
PUT A TARGET ON MY BACK AFTER
THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL, BUT THE
REALITY IS I ALREADY HAD A
TARGET ON MY BACK.
I NEEDED TO START PLAYING MY
GAME, AND MY GAME IS I'M GOING
TO CONVINCE YOU SEVEN WHY YOU
NEED TO CRACK.
>> NO, MAN.
>> WHERE DID MIKE GO?
>> HE'S LOOKING FOR ANOTHER
IDOL.
>> EVERYBODY THINKS I'M THAT
CRAZY DOCTOR, BUT I'M HERE TO
WIN THIS GAME.
I'M NOT HERE THE MAKE IT TO NINE
OR TO EIGHT OR TO SEVEN.
THE SEVEN HAS THE BREAK UP AT
SOME POINT.
NOW IS GOING TO BE THE TIME TO
ACT SOME, YES, IT MIGHT APPEAR
I'M ON THE BOTTOM RIGHT NOW, BUT
STAY TUNED.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TO GET REALLY
GOOD.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE YOUR FEET ONLY.
ON MY GO YOU'LL RELEASE A ROPE
THAT.
WILL DROP BLOCKS INTO A BIN.
YOU WILL THEN STACK THOSE BLOCKS
IN A CIRCLE AND PLACE A FLAG IN
THE CENTER.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> SURE.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL BE TAKEN ON A
SEA PLANE FOR AN AERIAL TOUR OF
THE SACRED ISLAND, TRULY ONE OF
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL PLACES IN
FIJI.
YOU WILL THEN ENJOY
CHEESEBURGERS.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: FRENCH FRIES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: ICE-COLD BEER.
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT'S WORTH
PLAYING FOR.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU ARE BAREFOOT USING ONLY YOUR
FEET.
THE FIRST STEP IS TO UNTIE THAT
ROPE, RELEASE THOSE PIECES.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR BLOCKS
RELEASED.
NOW YOU START BUILDING A
FOUNDATION.
YOU'RE GOING TO RELY ON THAT TO
GET YOU ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP.
ANOTHER METAPHOR FOR "SURVIVOR."
BUILDING FOUNDATIONS EVERY DAY,
TRYING TO GET AN ALLIANCE THAT
YOU CAN TRUST, KNOWING IT COULD
TOPPLE AT ANY MOMENT, WHICH WILL
HAPPEN OUT HERE.
LAUREN OFF TO A FAST START.
MIKE MAKING FAST WORK OF THIS.
ASHLEY GETTING SOME MOMENTUM
GOING.
ONCE YOU GET THAT BOTTOM LEVEL,
YOU START ON THAT SECOND LEVEL.
BUT YOU GOT TO KEEP IT STABLE,
BECAUSE THERE IS A THIRD LEVEL.
AND THEN A FLAG.
LAUREN WORKING ON THAT SECOND
LEVEL.
MIKE STARTING ON HIS SECOND
HERE GOES ASHLEY.
J.P. STARTING ON HIS SECOND
LEVEL.
RIGHT NOW IT IS LAUREN IN THE
LEAD.
MIKE RIGHT ON HER TAIL.
RYAN STILL WORKING ON THAT
BOTTOM LEVEL.
BEN TAKING HIS TIME.
DEVON TAKING HIS TIME.
JOE TRYING THE STAY IN IT.
YOU NEVER EVER KNOW WHAT SKILLS
WILL BE REQUIRED ON "SURVIVOR."
MIKE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
MIKE NOW WORKING ON HIS THIRD
LEVEL.
IT'S NOW MIKE IN THE LEAD.
LAUREN RIGHT NEXT TO HIM FEELING
THAT PANIC.
YOU COULD BE SO CLOSE TO A
CHEESEBURGER AND NOT TASTE IT IF
YOU DON'T WIN.
CHRISSY GETTING CLOSE TO
FINISHING THAT SECOND LEVEL.
ASHLEY NOW WORKING ON THAT TOP
LEVEL.
LAUREN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
MIKE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
AFTER A CRAZY TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WHO KNOWS WHERE MIKE STANDS IN
THIS GAME.
REWARD WOULD BE NICE.
MIKE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
HERE COMES ASHLEY WITH ANOTHER
PIECE UP TOP.
CHRISSY NOW AT THE TOP ROW.
IT IS NOW MIKE, THEN LAUREN,
ASHLEY, AND CHRISSY.
EVERYBODY HOPING MIKE WILL DROP
AND OPEN THE DOOR, BUT MIKE HAS
GOT A RHYTHM, AND IT IS WORKING.
MIKE DOWN TO ONE PIECE LEFT.
MIKE PLACES HIS LAST PIECE ON
THE TOP.
IF HE CAN GET IT TO STICK, A LOT
OF ACTION WITH THOSE TOES.
IT'S THERE.
MIKE NOW GOING FOR THE FLAG.
LAUREN TRYING TO ADJUST.
ASHLEY PICKING UP THE PACE.
MIKE COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE IF
HE CAN GET THAT FLAG UP AND OVER
NO!
MIKE DROPS A PIECE.
GOT TO PUT THE FLAG BACK IN THE
HOLE, GET THAT PIECE BACK IN
YOUR BIN, AND REPAIR IT.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR NOW.
ASHLEY CAN FEEL IT.
LAUREN CAN FEEL IT.
NOW IT IS LAUREN GOING FOR THE
FLAG.
CAN SHE GET THAT LAST ELEMENT, A
SKINNY LITTLE FLAG UP OVER THE
TOP AND INTO ITS SLOT?
LAUREN HOVERING.
HERE GOES MIKE TRYING AGAIN FOR
THE FLAG.
LAUREN DOES IT!
LAUREN WINS INDIVIDUAL REWARD.
SECOND CHALLENGE WIN IN A ROW.
>> THERE YOU GO, LAUREN.
>> NICE JOB.
>> NICE JOB, LAUREN.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, COME ON OVER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> FEELS GOOD.
>> Jeff: IT FEELS GOOD?
>> YEAH, IT FEELS REALLY GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAUREN.
SO TRICKY PART OF THIS REWARD IS
YOU'RE GOING TO BRING SOMEBODY
WITH YOU.
25 DAYS INTO THIS GAME,
ALLIANCES HAVE BEEN ALL OVER THE
MAP, NEVER KNOW WHO YOU CAN
TRUST, WHO ARE YOU BRINGING?
>> DEVON.
>> Jeff: DEVON, COME ON OVER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: THERE'S ROOM ON THAT
SEA PLANE FOR ANOTHER PERSON.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO BRING?
>> BEN.
>> Jeff: BEN JOINS DEVON.
ONE LAST SEAT, ONE FINAL CHOICE,
AND IN PICKING ONE PERSON TO
JOIN YOU, YOU SEND FIVE PEOPLE
BACK TO CAMP FOR RICE AND
COCONUT AND EXTREME HEAT.
>> ASHLEY.
>> Jeff: DIDN'T EVEN HESITATE.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: RYAN, DO YOU READ
INTO THIS?
IS THIS "SURVIVOR" AS USUAL,
SOMEBODY WINS AND THEY MAKE
THEIR MOVE?
>> NO, I DON'T READ INTO IT.
DEVON IS A BIG GUY, AND HE NEEDS
THAT SUSTENANCE, AND BEN AND
ASHLEY HAVEN'T BEEN ON A REWARD,
SO I SUPPORT LAUREN IN HER
DECISION.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LAUREN, DEVON, BEN, ASHLEY, NICE
AFTERNOON.
SEA PLANE, CHEESEBURGERS, FRIES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD OUT.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: J.P., RYAN, JOE,
MIKE, CHRISSY, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
>> I PICKED THOSE PEOPLE FOR
STRATEGIC REASONS.
THIS REWARD WOULD BE A GOOD
OPPORTUNITY TO CHANGE THE FUTURE
OF MY GAME TREMENDOUSLY.
THEY DO THINK THEY'RE A STRONG
GROUP OF SEVEN, AND IT'S IN THE
A STRONG GROUP OF SEVEN.
IT'S GETTING READY TO BLOW UP.
>> OH, MAN.
>> THIS IS FASTER THAN ANY
JET-SKI I'VE BEEN ON.
>> YOU CAN SIGH THE REEFS
PERFECTLY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT'S OUR HOME OVER THERE.
>> IS THAT IT?
THAT'S IT.
>> OH, WOW.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> THERE'S PEOPLE.
>> JOE.
HA, HA.
>> IT'S VERY LOW.
MY WIFE WOULD BE MAD AT ME IF I
WAS ON THAT THING.
I AM MAD.
THE REWARD CHALLENGE WAS MINE TO
WIN, AND I LOST IT.
IT SUCKS.
AND NOW I'M STUCK ON THE BEACH
WITH CHRISSY, RYAN, AND J.P.,
WHO ARE LITERALLY JUST BLINDED
BY THE SEVEN.
THEY JUST WANT TO PLAY A
COMFORTABLE GAME, LET'S GET JOE
AND MIKE OUT.
SO IT'S A DAY FOR JOE AND I TO
STIR THINGS UP.
WE'RE LIKE SISKEL AND EBERT.
>> IT'S LIKE AN EENIE MEENIE
MINEY MO SITUATION.
>> CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR AND GET
INTO ANOTHER FIGHT WITH CHRISSY.
>> MAYBE I'LL LEAVE WITH A BANG.
>> MIKE, YOU'RE IN RARE FORM
THIS AFTERNOON.
>> MIKE, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO
CALL OUR TABLE?
>> KIDS TABLE?
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO CALL IT?
I THINK WE SHOULD START OUR OWN.
>> THE COCOA NUTS.
IT DESCRIBES HIS DOMINICAN
ROOTS, WHICH IS SLIGHTLY COCOA,
AND IT DESCRIBES MY UROLOGY.
>> WE'RE THE COCOA NUT.
>> I LOVE CHEESEBURGERS.
I'M ABSOLUTELY STARVING.
AND NOW I HAVE TO CONTINUE TO
WIPE THE COCONUT COMEDY SHOW.
IT'S GETTING ANNOYING, BUT IT'S
BEEN SO BENEFICIAL TO HAVE
PEOPLE LIKE MIKE AND JOE ON THE
OUTSIDE WHO NOBODY WANT TO WORK
WITH, SO IT'S MAKING IT A LOT
EASIER TO GET TO THAT SEVEN THAN
IT NORMALLY SHOULD BE IN A
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
>> I DO THINK WE NEED TO GET JOE
OUT NEXT TO AVOID ANY SORT OF
WEIRD... I THINK THAT IS BECAUSE
HE'S A GOOD PLAYER.
>> I THINK SO, TOO.
>> SO WHO DO YOU THINK AFTER
NEXT TWO?
>> IF I HAD TO DO IT RIGHT NOW,
BEN SEVEN, LAUREN SIX, AND...
BEN'S GOT TO GO.
WE STILL HAVE TO GET OUT MIKE
AND JOE, BUT ME AND CHRISSY ARE
LOOKING DOWN THE ROAD.
OUR FOCUS AT THIS POINT IS ON
BEN HAS THE FIRST VOTE GOING
INTO THE SEVEN.
BEN'S A STRONG PLAYER.
HE'S GOING TO BE REALLY TOUGH
THE BEAT IN THE END, AND IT'S SO
FUNNY, BEN'S THE ONE THAT'S
SAYING, LET'S STICK WITH THE
SEVEN, STICK WITH THE SEVEN,
YEAH, WE'RE STICKING WITH IT,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO BE NUMBER
SEVEN.
>> I AM BEING STUPID THAT
THINKING THAT THE SEVEN OF US
WILL GET TO THE SEVEN?
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN,
TOO.
MY INTUITION TELLS ME THAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO IT.
>> 100%.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>> CHEERS.
>> BURGERS.
>> HEAVEN ON EARTH.
IT DIDN'T TAKE ME TWO SECONDS TO
EAT THAT CHOOSEBURGER.
I DROPPED MUSTARD ON MY PANTS.
I'M THINKING, I AIN'T HAD A BATH
IN 20-SOMETHING DAYS.
WHAT'S MUSTARD GOING TO HURT
NOW?
THE WHOLE TIME I'M THINKING LET
EVERYBODY EAT, FEEL GOOD, AND
THEN WE CAN START TALKING
SERIOUS BUSINESS.
>> THANK YOU, LAUREN.
>> YES, THANK YOU, LAUREN.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WE'VE ALL
WORKED REALLY HARD.
I HONESTLY, LIKE RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE ALL HERE INDIVIDUALLY
PLAYING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
BUT YOU HAVE TO HAVE A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF PEOPLE TO GET CONTROL
OF THE GAME, AND CHRISSY, RYAN,
AND J.P., THEY'RE FOOLING
THEMSELVES IF THEY THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO KEEP THE SEVEN TOGETHER
FOREVER.
THIS IS PERFECT TIMING.
THIS IS WHY I PICKED YOU GUYS.
I THINK THIS IS A GOOD GROUP,
YOU KNOW, AND I MEAN, YOU WOULD
BE HERO, HERO, HUSTLER, HUSTLER.
I'M GOING TO KEEP RIGHT ON
HUSTLING.
SEVEN IS A GREAT NUMBER TO GET
TO, BUT THAT SEVEN WILL NOT LAST
FOREVER.
AND IF YOU'RE STUPID ENOUGH TO
THINK IT WILL LAST, SOMETHING IS
WRONG.
J.P., CHRISSY AND RYAN FEEL A
LITTLE BIT TOO COMFORTABLE RIGHT
NOW.
SO TO ME IT'S THE PERFECT TIME
TO BEAT THEM TO THE PUNCH AND
BREAK UP THE NUMBERS BEFORE IT
BREAKS UP ON US.
LET'S GET ALL OUT IN THE OPEN,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW WHAT, DO I
KNOW, WHAT DO YOU KNOW, AND WHAT
DO YOU KNOW?
LET'S TAKE ALL THIS INFORMATION
AND USE IT AGAINST THEM?
>> RYAN HAS AN IDOL.
RYAN HAS THE MERGE IDOL.
RYAN TOLD ME I WAS THE ONLY ONE
HE WAS TELLING, AND HE TOLD ME
NOT TO TELL ANYONE, AND I HAVE
TRUSTED RYAN.
>> I FOUND A SECRET ADVANTAGE,
AND IT'S STILL IN PLAY.
OKAY.
AND WHAT IT IS IS BASICALLY I
HAVE AN EXTRA VOTE.
>> DAMN.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF TELLING OF
THINGS AND THIS GIRL HASN'T BEEN
TOLD ANYTHING.
>> LAUREN'S PLAN THE BREAK FROM
THE SEVEN EARLY IS AN AWESOME
IDEA.
AND IF I WANT TO BE IN ON THIS
STUFF AND REALLY BE THE ONE
MAKING DECISIONS AND NOT JUSTING
WITH TOLD WHAT TO DO, THEN I
NEED TO STEP UP THE AGGRESSION.
I NEED TO STEP UP MY GAME PLAY.
>> THEY'RE NEVER GOING TO EXPECT
BEN AND JOE TOGETHER.
IF YOU CAN PUT YOUR DIFFERENCES
ASIDE AND YOU CAN PUT YOUR
DIFFERENCES ASIDE AND PLAY THE
GAME THE WAY WE NEED TO GO AHEAD
AND PLAY IT, BECAUSE THIS IS NOT
PERSONAL, THIS IS BUSINESS.
>> HERE'S WHERE THE TRICKY PART
COMES IN.
>> WELL, THE TRICKY PART IS JOE
AND MIKE NEED TO STICK AROUND
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO LIVE WITH
JOE.
>> I'M SICK OF BEING CALLED KING
ARTHUR.
I'M SICK OF TRYING TO KEEP
EVERYONE IN LINE AND STRAIGHT.
BUT RIGHT NOW IF I NEED TO KEEP
JOE, I'LL DO IT.
>> WITH T WHOLE CIRCLE
ROUNDTABLE, THAT'S GOING TO HURT
YOU.
THEY'RE GOING TO AIM FOR YOU
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
>> THAT'S WHY I'M ON BOARD.
LY RIDE TO THE END WITH YOU
FOUR.
>> CAN WE SOLIDIFY THIS RIGHT
NOW?
>> OVER A BEER.
>> WE CAN TAKE CONTROL OF THE
GAME.
>> TO THE FINAL FOUR.
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
I LOVE IT.
>> LAUREN HAS BEEN SURPRISING
ME.
SHE CAME INTO THIS GAME TALKING
NO STRATEGY, AND NOW I'M SEEING
THIS OTHER SIDE OF HER, AND
SHE'S REALLY GOOD.
SHE'S LIKE AS GOOD AS ME.
AND I'M HAPPY SHE'S ON MY SIDE.
AND I THINK THIS PLAN IS GOING
TO WORK.
THIS IS WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS ALL
ABOUT.
THIS MOMENT.
>> ANYONE WANT ANY MORE BURGER
PATTIES.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT CAN HAPPEN
AT REWARDS.
>> OH.
OH, MY GOSH, GUYS.
THESE ARE LETTERS.
>> NO!
>> I GOT A LETTER FROM MY
DAUGHTER, AND IT JUST SAID,
"DEAR MAMA, AND THAT WAS IT."
I LOST IT.
I AM A SINGLE MOTHER.
I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR EVERY TIME
THAT I'VE GOTTEN.
AND IT'S A GOOD REMINDER THAT I
HAVE TO MAKE BIG MOVES FOR HER.
THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT OF ME
BEING HERE IS TO NOT GIVE UP ON
HER.
I'M NOT HERE JUST FOR MYSELF.
I'M HERE FOR HER AND FOR HER
FUTURE.
IT'S NOT FOR ME.
>> THANK YOU, LAUREN.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> YEAH, THANK YOU.
>> AND FOR THOSE GUYS TO GET IT
ALSO, I THINK IT MEANT A LOT TO
THEM, AND I THINK THAT IT
ACTUALLY BROUGHT US CLOSER
TOGETHER.
SO WE CAN ACTUALLY MAKE THIS
HAPPEN.
>> I REALLY AM GLAD THAT I WON
TODAY.
>> I AM, TOO.
>> THIS BONDED US EVEN MORE THAN
THAT CHEERS.
I'M IN THE WALKING AWAY FROM
THIS.
>> THIS IS WHERE WE FLIP THE
GAME.
BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT'S A START THE A NEW DAY.
WHAT BETTER WAY THE START THE
DAY THAN HEARING FROM YOUR
FAMILY?
SO SITTING UP THERE WITH MY WIFE
AND MY TWO KIDS, I KNOW IT'S A
LETTER, BUT YOU CAN HEAR HER
TALKING THOSE WORDS, YOU KNOW?
AND WYATT WROTE ME A LETTER,
TOO, AND HIS WRITING IS GETTING
BETTER.
AND I LOVE MY WIFE.
I LOVE HER TO DEATH.
SHE CHANGED MY LIFE.
SHE SAVED MY LIFE.
WHEN YOU GO THROUGH COMBAT AND
YOU COME BACK, A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE A HARD TIME DOING IT, AND I
QLOA HER THE WORLD.
SHE'S WHY I'M OUT HERE.
I'M HERE TO PLAY THE GAME.
MY FAMILY JUST GAVE ME THE GAS
AND THE FUEL I NEED THE PLAY
THIS GAME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OUT OF NOWHERE I SEE AN AX AND
IT SAYS "DIG."
AT FIRST I THINK THERE'S AN
IMMUNITY IDOL, BUT IT'S A CLUE
TO WHERE THE IMMUNITY IDOL IS
SITTING.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING SINCE DAY ONE
FOR AN IDOL.
I LOST IT.
NO WAY.
NO THE MARINE IN ME, WHEN THERE
IS A MISSION OR A TASK TO BE
DONE, IT IS GO TIME.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE MAP.
I HAVE AN OBJECTIVE, AND I'M
GOING TO GO GET THE JOB DONE.
MY MISSION NOW IS TO GET TO THIS
IDOL.
YOU KNOW, I'M SWEEPING THE AREA
LIKE I WOULD CLEARING A ROOM.
IT'S GOT TO BE RIGHT AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP A KEEN YOU OUT
FOR SOMETHING THAT LOOKS OUT OF
PLACE.
AND I HAVE TO FIND THIS, BUT YOU
HAVE TO KEEP A CALM AND COOL
HEAD, THINK QUICKLY, BUT THINK
CLEARLY.
A CLAY POT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
HOOK.
A BIG CLAY POT IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE HOOK.
A HOOK.
OH, MY GOSH.
THANK YOU, FAMILY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I FOUND AN IDOL ON "SURVIVOR."
I HAVE NEVER BEEN IN HAPPY IN MY
ENTIRE LIFE TO WEAR A DARN
NECKLACE OF SHELLS.
HUGE.
AT THIS POINT THE SEVENTH
BLOWING UP AND MY NAME HAS BEEN
THRUN AROUND.
I'M BEING CALLED KING ARTHUR.
SO I NEED THE IDOL.
AND I AIN'T TELLING NO ONE ABOUT
IT, BECAUSE NOBODY AROUND HERE
CAN KEEP A DARN SECRET.
OH, MY GOSH.
THIS GETS ME ONE STEP CLOSER TO
A MILLION.
OH, MY GOSH, I NEEDED THIS SO
BAD.
AND I BELIEVE MY WIFE HELPED ME
FIND THIS IDOL.
SO THANK YOU, HONEY, THIS ONE IS
FOR YOU, AND THIS ONE IS FROM
YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, LAUREN, GOT
TO TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHANG YOU'RE GOING
TO BALANCE ON A TRIANGULAR
PLATFORM WITH YOUR FEET PERCHED
ON VERY NARROW FOOTHOLDS.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS WE'LL MOVE
UP MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT YOUR HANDS TOUCH
THE STRUCTURE OR YOU FALL OFF,
YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WILL
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE TENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT AND BECOME THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
27 DAYS INTO THIS GAME, THERE'S
BEEN A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
ALLIANCES, A ROUNDTABLE, A
SECURE SEVEN.
WELL, IF YOU FEEL REALLY SECURE
WITH YOUR POSITION IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW, I'M GOING TO OFFER
YOU SOMETHING THAT MAY BE HARD
TO PASS UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN FOREGO THIS
CHALLENGE THAT'S GOING TO BE
CERTAIN PAIN AND INSTEAD INDULGE
IN SOMETHING THAT IS GUARANTEED
PLEASURE.
>> OH, GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN SKIP TODAY'S
CHALLENGE AND INSTEAD FEAST ON
PEANUT BUTTER AND CHOCOLATE.
>> OH, WOW.
>> OH, GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: I'LL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO THINK ABOUT IT, AND
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
DECISIONS HAVE BEEN MADE.
DEVON, BEN, AND LAUREN DECIDED
TO SIT OUT OF THE CHALLENGE AND
PARTICIPATE IN EATING CHOCOLATE
AND PEANUT BUTTER, GIVING UP
THEIR SHOT AT IMMUNITY, WHILE
MIKE, ASHLEY, RYAN, CHRISSY,
JOE, AND J.P. SAID, NOPE, I'M
NOT THAT SECURE, I'M GOING TO
TRY TO WIN IT.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS HEAVY.
THERE IS NO WAY YOU CAN EAT IT
ALL.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN EAT UNTIL THE
CHALLENGE ENDS.
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR FIRST
POSITION.
HOLD ON UNTIL YOU GET
COMFORTABLE, AND THEN I'LL COUNT
YOU IN.
>> COME ON, MIKE, WE GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE...
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY IS IN THEIR FIRST
POSITION.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
WE'LL BE HERE 20 MINUTES.
HANDS CANNOT TOUCH, BUTT CANNOT
TOUCH.
THIS WOULD BE ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO DO ON A FULLY RESTED, FULLY
FUELED BODY, LET ALONE AFTER 27
DAYS ON "SURVIVOR."
YOU'RE TESTED ON EVERY LEVEL,
AND NOW YOU'RE OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE OCEAN BALANCING ON A
TRIANGULAR PLATFORM.
MIKE, WHAT WILL YOUR KIDS THINK
WHEN THEY SEE THIS, YOU AND YOUR
FILTHY YELLOW SHIRT STILL
COMPETING ON "SURVIVOR" WITH
ONLY NINE PEOPLE LEFT?
>> I JUST HAVE TO CONVINCE THEM
I'M NOT CRAZY, JEFF, AND THEN
THEY'LL BE PROUD OF ME.
>> TOO LATE FOR THAT.
>> COCONUTS, MIKE.
>> YEP, WE'RE THE COCONUT.
HE'S COCOA AND I'M NUTS.
>> Jeff: A LITTLE WATER
MOVEMENT.
THERE AND J.P. ALMOST GOT CAUGHT
OFF BALANCE.
THAT'S HOW FAST YOU GET LULLED
INTO SLEEP.
YOU'VE GOT TO STAY LIMBER AND
LOOSE.
ANTICIPATE.
RYAN WITH A NICE ONE.
IT WILL CATCH YOU QUICKLY.
YOU FEEL IT.
IT COMES OUT OF NOWHERE.
JOE REALLY STRUGGLING.
IF YOU TOUCH, YOU'RE OUT.
J.P. WITH A BIG STRETCH, NICE
RECOVERY.
>> HEY, JEFF, DO YOU WANT TO GET
DOWN ON THIS?
>> NEW YORK I'M GOOD.
THAT'S FOR YOU GUYS.
THANKS, BEN.
A LOT OF FUN BEING HAD OVER
HERE.
IT'S AMAZING WHAT PEANUT BUTTER
AND CHOCOLATE DOES FOR THE
SPIRIT.
>> Jeff: J.P. ANOTHER NICE
SAVE.
J.P. HAS BEEN ALL OVER THE PLACE
BUT HAS NOT FALLEN.
>> HE'S GOING DOWN.
>> Jeff: J.P. CAN'T HANG IN
ANY LONGER.
J.P. IS FIRST OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
YOU'RE HALFWAY THROUGH THIS
SECTION.
THEN WE'LL MOVE UP.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME NOW TO MOVE ENTER
YOUR FINAL SPOT, WHERE YOU WILL
BE FOR THE REST OF THE
CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY IS SAFE.
YOU CAN TOUCH.
HOLD ON UNTIL YOU GET YOUR
BALANCE.
EVERYBODY MOVE UP ON TO THAT TOP
LEVEL NOW.
>> WHOA, THAT IS NOT EASY.
>> Jeff: NOW IT GETS FUN.
HERE WE GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
AND WE ARE BACK.
CHRISSY CAN ONLY HANG FOR A
SECOND.
MIKE ALMOST DROPS.
NICE RECOVERY.
JOE WITH A NICE SAVE.
JOE REALLY STRUGGLING TO STAY UP
THERE.
JOE CAN'T DO IT.
JOE IS NOW OUT.
WE'RE DOWN TO THREE.
THREE VERY DIFFERENT POSITIONS.
MIKE SIDEWAYS, TURNED AWAY FROM
EVERYBODY.
ASHLEY HEAD-ON LIKE SHE IS
SURFING, AND RYAN CROUCHED, ALL
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY 27 DAYS
INTO "SURVIVOR."
>> I'M IN THE HEAVING "SURVIVOR"
WITHOUT WINNING AN IMMUNITY.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY FLIRTING WITH
DISASTER.
RYAN PLAYING WITH FIRE WITH
THOSE HAND, BALANCING ON ONE
FOOT AND THEN THE TOES OF THE
OTHER, BUT HE DOESN'T WANT TO
TRY TO MOVE.
TOO RISKY.
ASHLEY REALLY STRUGGLING.
RYAN CAN'T HOLD HIS POSITION
ANYMORE.
RYAN DROPS.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO.
AND THEY ARE SIDE BY SIDE.
IT IS DR. MIKE AND ASHLEY, A
HEALER AND A HERO BATTLING IT
OUT ON DAY 27 FOR IMMUNITY ON
"SURVIVOR."
ASHLEY ROCK SOLID.
>> THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR.
>> Jeff: MIKE RIGHT ON THE
EDGE OF DISASTER.
FATIGUE NOW STARTING TO SET IN.
ASHLEY WITH A LITTLE BIT OF
MOVEMENT.
MIKE OUT OF NOWHERE DROPS.
IT'S OVER.
ASHLEY WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHAT A CHALLENGE.
ASHLEY, COME ON OVER.
[APPLAUSE]
ASHLEY SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
AFTER 27 DAY, WILL NOT BE VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, I KNOW
HOW HARD IT IS OUT HERE.
I KNOW 39 DAYS IS A GOAL.
FOR SOMEBODY TONIGHT THAT WILL
CUT SHORT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT, THIRD
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
SWIM OUT AND SEE YOU AT
SURVIVAL.
>> J.P., CHRISSY AND RYAN DIDN'T
WIN, AND THAT WORKS PERFECTLY
FOR OUR PLAN.
I'M LIKE A GIDDY LITTLE KID
ABOUT THIS VOTE TONIGHT.
NOW IT'S TIME TO PULL THE
TRIGGER AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> AWESOME JOB, ASH.
>> GOOD JOB, ASHLEY.
GOOD JOB, MIKE.
I WAS IMPRESSED, MIKE.
BALANCE ISN'T USUALLY YOUR
THING.
>> MIKE, YOU HAVE MANY MORE
SKILLS THAN YOU LET ON.
>> I WAS VERY SURPRISED THAT
BEN, LAUREN, AND DEVON CHOSE TO
EAT.
I THOUGHT WE HAD A JOB TO DO IN
TAKING OUT JOE AND MIKE.
WHAT AM I, A ROMANIAN GYMNAST,
LIKE I'M GOING TO BE DOING
BACKFLIPS ON THE PLATFORM?
THAT LED A BAD TASTE IN MY
MOUTH, AND LUCKILY ASHLEY WON.
NOW WE GET TO DECIDE WHO WILL
STAY BETWEEN MIKE AND JOE.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING FOR
TONIGHT?
>> I GUESS MIKE IS STARTING TO
BECOME QUITE THE COMMANDER.
>> I WOULD BE HAPPY WITH EITHER
ONE.
>> JOE IS MORE LIKELY TO FIND
THE IDOL.
>> I DON'T CARE.
JUST LET ME KNOW.
THEY'RE BOTH THE SAME.
>> I'M WITH YOU.
>> I FEEL VERY COMFORTABLE WITH
OUR ALLIANCE OF SEVEN.
WE'RE DEFINITELY UNIFIED IN
WANTING TO GET OUT JOE OR MIKE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET RID OF BOTH
OF THEM, BUT GETTING RID OF ONE
OF THEM WILL BREAK UP THIS NEW
COCONUT ALIKE, WHICH IS MAKING
US ALL BANANAS.
>> EVERYBODY EXPECTS JOE TO GO
NEXT.
I THINK IT WOULD BE A LITTLE BIT
FUN TO VOTE OUT MIKE AND LEAVE
JOEL UNTIL THE END.
I FEEL LIKE THAT WOULD BE FUN.
>> BOYS ON MIKE, GIRLS ON JOE?
>> OKAY.
>> I LOOK AT CHRISSY AND RYAN,
AND I SEE THE POWER BLINDING
THEM.
I SEE THE CLUELESSNESS IN HOW
CONFIDENT THEY'RE ACTING.
IT'S MIND BLOWING.
THAT NEEDS TO BE CHANGED, AND
MYSELF ALONG WITH MY ALLIANCE IS
GOING TO BE THE ONE TO CHANGE
THAT.
>> LOOK, THIS WHOLE TRUST IN THE
SEVEN ALLIANCE IS CRAP.
WE HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
OURSELVES.
THERE'S NO POINT IN GETTING RID
OF JOE AND MIKE.
WHO DO WE TAKE OUT FIRST?
RIGHT NOW IS THE POINT IN THIS
GAME THAT WE HAVE TO TAKE
CONTROL AND BREAK UP J.P.,
CHRISSY, AND RYAN.
THEY'RE ALL THREATS, IN MY
OPINION.
CHRISSY IS JUST A HUGE THINKER.
SHE IS SUCH A MASTERMIND.
J.P. IS A HUGE THREAT BECAUSE HE
MIGHT NOT BE GOOD AT BALANCING,
BUT HE IS GOOD AT EVERYTHING
ELSE.
AND RYAN IS A HUGE THREAT
BECAUSE HE HAS AN IDOL.
THIS IS A GREAT TIME TO FLUSH
THAT IDOL AND GET RID OF HIM.
STARTING TONIGHT, THE GAME IS
REALLY ON.
>> IT'S UP TO US TO TAKE CHARGE.
>> WE DON'T DO IT NOW, THEN
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
>> IT'S GOING DOWN TONIGHT, BUT
MOVING FORWARD, WE NEED THE
MAINTAIN CONTROL.
AFTER THE BIGGEST BLIND SIDE
YET, SO I'VE COME UP WITH A PLAN
TO DO IT VERY SUBTLY.
>> HEY, BIG GUY.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> THIS IS WHAT I THINK.
I THINK YOU SHOULD VOTE MIKE.
>> REALLY?
>> BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY BEN'S WITH
US.
WE DON'T WANT BEN TO KNOW.
WE DON'T WANT JOE TO KNOW.
WE DON'T WANT MIKE TO KNOW.
BEN IS WITH US, YET HE'S GOING
TO PRETEND LIKE HE'S NOT WITH
US.
SO AFTER TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CHRISSY, RYAN, OR J.P., WHOEVER
IS LEFT, WILL COME RUNNING TO
HIM.
THEY'RE IN FOR A RUDE AWAKENING,
AND IT'S GOING TO BE CLASSIC TO
SEE THE LOOKS ON THEIR FACES.
I MEAN, THIS IS WHAT "SURVIVOR"
IS ALL ABOUT.
BUT BEN'S VOTING WITH THEM, WE
NEED MIKE AND JOE TO VOTE WITH
US TO JUST KEEP NUMBERS.
>> IF THEY KNOW BEN IS A PART OF
IT, THEY COULD SWITCH OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
ARE YOU DOWN WITH THAT?
>> MY MISSION NOW IS TO STAY ON
THE INSIDE OF J.P., CHRISSY, AND
RYAN, AND INFILL TRAIL WHEN WE
GET BACK THE TRIBAL.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> I'M GOOD WITH MIKE.
>> WE'LL HAVE THE NUMBERS.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO BE LIVED.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL IS GOING TO BE
FUN TO WATCH.
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO PULL THE
RUG OUT FROM UNDERNEATH THEM.
SO I GOT TO GET ME ACTING SHOES
ON, AND THEY NEED TO GET MIKE
AND JOE.
>> WE WANT THE TALK TO YOU GUYS.
THEY STILL THINK SEVEN STRONG
AND YOU TWO ARE OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
>> US FIVE, AND BEN IS STILL
GOING TO THINK IT'S SEVEN
STRONG, AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE
ME, YOU'LL SEE AT TRIBAL, YOU'LL
BE HERE.
>> OH, MY GOSH, IT'S HAPPENING.
THE SEVEN HAS SPLIT, AS I KNEW
THEY WOULD.
>> JUST TALK TO ME.
>> I WILL VOTE WHOEVER YOU WANT
ME TO VOTE FOR.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN THE COURT
JESSER THE HAS BECOME MERLIN AND
I'M GOING TO MAKE THEM DISAPPEAR
ONE BY ONE.
>> CHRISSY, J.P., AND RYAN HAVE
NO IDEA THAT WE'RE ACTUALLY
TRICKING THEM, WHICH IS THE
FUNNY PART.
THEY THINK THEY'RE IN CHARGE,
AND I'M GLAD THAT'S THE PACE
THEY'RE ON, BECAUSE I'M A PAGE
AHEAD OF THEM.
YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT EVERY
LITTLE SCENARIO, BECAUSE ONCE
YOU MAKE THE PLAY, THERE IS NO
TAKING IT BACK.
TRIBAL IS GOING TO BE A HUGE
BLIND SIDE.
I MEAN, THE SEVEN IS GOING TO
GET BLOWN UP, AND IT'S GOING TO
BE FIREWORKS AT CAMP TONIGHT.
FOURTH OF JULY IS COMING EARLY.
>> Jeff: NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
DESI AND COLE VOTED OUT AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO DR. MIKE, LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
THE HEALERS WERE IN TROUBLE.
YOU PLAYED AN IDOL, COLE WAS
VOTED OUT.
WAS THERE ANY FALLOUT?
>> YOU KNOW, IT LOOKED LIKE I
WAS CRAZY AT THE LAST TRIBAL
THE REALITY WAS I NEEDED TO
REINVENT THE GAME.
I NEEDED TO SAY THE SAME THING
THAT JOE SAID BUT BECAUSE I'M A
DOCTOR HOPE THAT PEOPLE BELIEVE
IT BECAUSE I SAY IT.
>> Jeff: THAT'S CRAZY THAN
WHAT HE SAID LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THAT BECAUSE HE'S A
DOCTOR, PEOPLE WOULD BELIEVE
HIM.
IT'S AS IF MIKE AND JOE ARE JUST
THESE LITTLE TOYS YOU ARE
PLAYING WITH, BATTING BACK AND
FORTH.
>> WELL, WE'RE NOT NECESSARILY
PLAYING WITH THEM.
I THINK COMEDY ROUTINE STARTED
WITH THE TWO OF THEM, AND THEY
ARE GIVING US A SHOW.
ALL DAY LONG.
>> Jeff: MIKE, IS THAT AN
ANGLE, JUST TIR THEM ENTER
THINKING I'M SO NUTS THEY BECOME
CHARMED BY ME?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LOOK AT US, WE'RE TWO VOTES.
THAT WAS THE GOAL OF LAST
TRIBAL.
IT'S TO KEEP JOE AROUND FOR US
TO BE A TWO-VOTE BLOC, AND WE'RE
OUT THERE.
TWO VOTES.
>> RYAN, IS THAT PART OF THE
THREAT, THAT THEY'RE COCOA-NUTS.
>> IT'S A PACKAGE DEAL, BUY ONE
GET ONE FREE, BUT MIKE'S PITCHES
TO ME ARE COMPLETELY INACCURATE
ABOUT WHAT'S ACTUALLY HAPPENING
WITHIN THE SEVEN BECAUSE WE HAVE
BEEN SO STRONG.
YEAH, YOU COULD USE MIKE AND JOE
AS THE SWING VOTE, BUT IT JUST
DOESN'T MAKE A LOT OF SENSE, BUT
AGAIN, I GIVE THEM CREDIT FOR AT
LEAST TRYING.
>> Jeff: JOE, RYAN IS SAYING,
IF YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A PITCH,
THE PITCH HAS TO LINE UP WITH MY
VISION.
>> THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
ME AND MIKE MAY LINE UP WITH
SOMEONE ELSE'S VISION.
>> Jeff: WOW, DEVON, JOE JUST
SAID A FEW WORDS, BUT HE SAID
I DON'T HAVE TO LINE UP WITH
EVERYBODY, JUST SOMEBODY.
>> THAT'S ALL THESE TWO NEED,
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR CRACKS.
MAYBE ONE DAY THEY WILL FIND
ONE, MAYBE THEY WON'T.
THERE'S NO SAYING.
>> Jeff: SO LAUREN, IF IT IS
SEVEN STRONG, IS THIS THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM?
>> I HAVE A FEELING IT'S GETTING
READY TO BE A PERFECT STORM.
THIS CAN ONLY LAST FOR SO LONG.
YOU KNOW, I WISH THERE WERE
SEVEN SEATS AT THE VERY END,
THERE ISN'T, THERE'S ONLY THREE.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, THE SEVEN IS
ULTIMATELY STILL A MIRAGE, AS
LAUREN SAID, THE GAME DOESN'T
END WITH SEVEN.
>> WELL, CLEARLY WE ALL HAVE
DIFFERENT RELATIONSHIPS WITH
EACH OTHER.
SOME OF US HAVE JUST BEEN ON
TRIBES WITH EACH OTHER LONGER,
SO I DON'T THINK THAT ANY OF US
HAVE THE SAME EQUAL RELATIONSHIP
WITH EACH OF THE SIX OTHER
PEOPLE ON THE TRIBE.
THE QUESTION IS: HOW DO WE
MANAGE OUR OWN WAYS TO THE END.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: JOE, THAT'S THE
OPENING THAT YOU AND MIKE ARE
LOOKING FOR, IS WHEN ONE SMALLER
GROUP TRIES TO FIGURE OUT
ANOTHER SMALLER GROUP AND YOU
TRY TO GET RIGHT IN THERE AND
SAY, I'M THE MISSING VOTE YOU
NEED.
>> SHE SAID ONE OF THE OTHER
SIX.
WE'RE NOT IN THE TRIBE.
THEY DON'T EVEN CONSIDER US.
WE'RE THE TWO KIDS IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD, WE WANT THE PLAY
"SURVIVOR," BUT THEY DON'T LET
US PLAY.
THE SEVEN DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT
WE'RE TWO SOLID VOTES.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, YOU ALL HAVE
SAT HERE AND TALKED ABOUT THIS
SEVEN.
BUT THE MINUTE WE ACTUALLY GET
DOWN TO IT, EVERYBODY DOES SEEM
TO BE IN AGREEMENT, YEAH, I'M
PRETTY SURE THERE'S SOME
ALLIANCES WITHIN THE SEVEN.
>> LET'S JUST SAY WE'RE NOT ALL
SITTING AT THE FIRE AS SEVEN,
SAYING, OKAY, WHICH ONE OF US
SEVEN IS GOING TO GO NEXT.
WE'RE NOT DOING THAT, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
>> Jeff: RYAN, WHEN DOES THAT
MOMENT HAPPEN?
>> IT HAPPENS WHEN PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING.
IF YOU DON'T THINK IT'S
HAPPENING, THAT'S WHEN YOU KNOW
IT'S HAPPENING.
>> ON TOP OF, THAT YOU CAN'T GET
TO PLAN "B" UNLESS YOU GET
THROUGH PLAN "A."
SOMETIMES YOU GET CAUGHT LOOKING
SO FAR DOWN THE GAME YOU FORGET
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN FRONT OF
YOUR FACE AND BEFORE YOU KNOW
IT, YOU'RE THE ONE GOING HOME.
>> I DON'T THINK WE'RE PLAYING
THIS GAME AS POORLY AS JOE WOULD
LIKE TO THINK.
WE'RE NOT ALL THINKING THIS IS A
MAGICAL SEVEN, BUT IT TARTS
THERE.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, WHAT RYAN
SAID IS LATE TERRIFYING.
IT'S HAPPENING WHEN YOU DON'T
KNOW IT'S HAPPENING.
>> WHICH IS WHY YOU CAN NEVER
STOP PLAYING THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE TO PLAY IT WHILE YOU
SLEEP.
EAT.
WHO -- YOU HAVE THE PLAY IT
WHILE YOU PEE.
THE MOMENT YOU STOP PLAYING,
THERE ARE CONVERSATIONS BEHIND
YOU AND YOU'RE REQUEST IN THE
DUST.
>> Jeff: IT'S EXHAUSTING.
>> I THINK THE BEST WAY IS TO
FIND THE PEOPLE YOU TRUST IN
YOUR GAME.
THEY ARE YOUR EYES AND YOUR
EARS.
IT GIVES YOU A BREAK BECAUSE YOU
KNOW THEY'RE THINKING WITH YOU.
>> Jeff: BEN, HOW COMFORTABLE
ARE YOU THINKING THAT YOU COULD
LOOK AT SOMEBODY IN YOUR
ALLIANCE AND SAY, YOU IN
PARTICULAR, I BELIEVE I CAN
TRUST?
>> TRUST IS GOING TO GET YOU TO
THE END OF THE GAME.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST TWO OR THREE
OTHER PEOPLE.
THAT'S A FACT.
BUT FINDING TRUST IN A GAME OF
SO MUCH DISTRUST IS THE HARD
PART.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, HOW
CONFIDENT ARE YOU THAT YOU CAN
TRUST THE PEOPLE IN YOUR
ALLIANCE THAT YOU'VE ONLY KNOWN
27 DAYS AND THOSE 27 DAYS HAVE
BEEN ON "SURVIVOR"?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO BELIEVE THAT
I CAN FULLY TRUST THE PEOPLE IN
MY CLOSEST ALLIANCE, AND I FEEL
THEY HAVE COME THROUGH FOR ME IN
THE PAST AND HAVE PROVEN THEIR
LOYALTY AND THEIR TRUST.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
RYAN, YOU'RE UP.
>> SEE YOU LATER, COCOA-NUT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WILL BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL, PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL BE ASKED THE LEAVE THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MIKE.
JOE.
MIKE.
TWO VOTES MIKE.
ONE VOTE JOE.
MIKE.
THREE VOTES MIKE, ONE VOTE JOE.
J.P.
ONE VOTE J.P.
THAT'S TWO VOTES J.P.
WE'RE TIED.
THREE VOTES J.P., THREE VOTES
MIKE, ONE VOTE JOE.
J.P.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES J.P., THREE
VOTES MIKE.
ONE VOTE JOE, ONE VOTE LEFT.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY, J.P.,
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
J.P., THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> DAMN, THEY GOT ME GOOD.
>> Jeff: WELL, BASED ON THE
SHOCKED REACTION, IT SOUNDS LIKE
RYAN HAD IT RIGHT.
WHEN IS IT HAPPENING?
WHEN YOU DON'T KNOW IT'S
HAPPENING.
GRAB YOU TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> CAN SOMEONE PLEASE EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED?
SO HOW DID THAT PLAY OUT?
>> IF WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU,
ABSOLUTELY NOT WE'RE NOT GOING
TO TELL YOU.
DO WE LOOK LIKE IDIOTS?
WE'RE COCONUT, BUT WE'RE NOT
IDIOT.
JUST BE LUCKY IT WASN'T YOU.
>> IT WAS WELL PLAYED COMING
FROM A GUY WHO SAID HE WOULD
NEVER BE A PUPPET.
>> YOU COULD BE UPSET AND
BITTER.
ME AND MIKE HAVE BEEN IN THE
BOTTOM FOR HOW LONG?
WE'VE NEVER BEEN BITTER.
WE'VE BEEN HAPPY AROUND CAMP.
JUST BE HAPPY YOU'RE AROUND
CAMP.
>> I'M UPSET ABOUT THE BLIND
SIDE, BUT I'M MORE UPSET ABOUT
THE WAY THAT THOSE FIVE TREATED
US THREE WHEN WE GOT BACK TO
CAMP.
AM I ALLOWED TO ASK HOW LONG...
WHEN THE PLAN WAS CRAFTED?
AM I ALLOWED TO ASK THAT?
>> YOU CAN ASK, BUT I'M NOT
GOING TO ANSWER?
>> BLIND SIDES ARE PART OF THE
GAME, BEING SNARKY TO YOUR
FRIENDS IS NOT.
THAT IS THE PART THAT'S
FRUSTRATING TO ME.
CLEARLY THEY'RE NOT FRIENDS.
WHATEVER.
>> THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME, YOU
KNOW.
>> SO I TRIED TO BE VERY
GRACIOUS.
I JUST SAID, GOOD MOVE,
EVERYBODY, WELL PLAYED.
EVEN THOUGH I'M INFURIATED.
I THOUGHT I HAD IT MADE.
I'M JUST HAPPY TO BE HERE.
>> YOU'RE FINE.
>> IT'S A VERY NEW FEELING BEING
ON THE BOTTOM.
I REALLY NEED TO THINK HOW I'M
GOING TO RECOVER FROM THIS.
>> I NEVER MAKE A MOVE AND
SHARE.
>> YOU DIDN'T MAKE A MOVE.
YOU GOT DRUG ALONG.
>> GUESS WHAT...
>> THE GREAT PUPPET GUY WHO WILL
NEVER BE A PUPPET.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
>> IT WASN'T YOU, BEN.
>> MIKE AND JOE ARE PRETTY MUCH
IN THE DARK OF ME WORKING WITH
ASHLEY, DEVON, AND LAUREN, BUT
JOE IS WALKING AROUND LIKE IT
WAS HIS DAMN IDEA TO BLIND SIDE
J.P.
>> BUY ONE, GET ONE FREE.
YOU KEEP ME, MIKE STICKS AROUND.
>> HE DID WHAT A GOOD LITTLE
PUPPET WOULD DO.
YOU PULL THE STRINGS, YOU MAKE
SURE YOU WRITE J.P., AND HE DID.
WHAT WAS THE REASON FOR J.P.,
OUT OF CURIOSITY?
>> YOU GUYS ARE ASKING
CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION.
>> I SHOULD GET AN AWARD FOR THE
PERFORMANCE I PUT ON AFTER I GOT
BACK THE CAMP.
I'M DOING MY BEST DOUBLE AGENT
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT.
I'M PLAYING THE ROLE OF BEING ON
THE OUTS WITH CHRISSY AND RYAN
TO GATHER INTEL WHEN I KNOW THAT
I HAVE MY ALLIANCE OF FOUR IN
LAUREN, DEVON, ASHLEY AND
MYSELF.
>> J.P. GOING HOMEWORKED OUT AS
PLANNED.
AND IT WAS PERFECT TIMING
BECAUSE IT GAVE US THE UPPER
HAND.
IT JUST REVERSED THE ROLE.
CHRISSY, J.P., AND RYAN FELT
LIKE THEY WERE ON THE TOP.
NOW RYAN AND CHRISSY ARE SITTING
ON THE BOTTOM.
THEY KNOW IT.
>> WELL PLAYED.
>> THAT WAS REALLY WELL PLAYED.
>> THAT WAS GOOD.
CHRISSY AND RYAN THINK THAT I'M
IN WITH THEM.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I'LL GET RYAN TO PLAY HIS
IDOL.
>> AND YOU ARE GOING TO TELL US.
>> YEAH.
>> DUDE, I HAD TO DO IT, MAN.
>> YOU KNOW I'M IN THE MAD AT
YOU.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD HAVE
TO REPAIR MY TRUST WITH DEVON.
DEVON AND I HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
SINCE DAY ONE.
I HAVE GIVEN HIM EVERY SINGLE
OUNCE OF INFORMATION THAT I'VE
HAD IN THIS GAME.
AND HE BLIND SIDED ME.
HE COULD HAVE SENT ME HOME.
>> THE REASON YOU DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS VOTE WAS BECAUSE...
WELL, YOU TOLD ME THAT I WAS
GOING, YOU AND ME.
>>
>> NO, YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE I
TOLD.
>> EVER SINCE RYAN LIED TO ME
ABOUT HIM AND I BEING THE ONLY
ONES ABOUT THE IDOL, THAT LIE
CAUSED ME TO NO LONGER TRUSTED
HIM ANYMORE.
>> I HAVE NEVER WAVERED FROM ME,
YOU, AND LAUREN FROM GOING TO
THE FINAL THREE.
I VOTED THE WAY WE SAID WE WERE
GOING TO VOTE.
>> I TRUST ASHLEY AND I TRUST
LAUREN AND I WANT TO TRUST YOU,
BUT THAT SCARED ME.
TO BE HONEST, THAT REALLY SCARED
ME.
WE'VE HAD AN ALLIANCE SINCE DAY
ONE, BUT IT IS A SELFISH GAME IN
THE END.
AND I HAVE MY OWN PLAN TO GET ME
TO WIN THAT MILLION, AND HE'S NO
LONGER A PART OF IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
EVERYONE COME GET A SEASHELL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I GREW UP WATCHING
"SURVIVOR," BUT YOU DON'T
REALIZE HOW MENTALLY STRAINING
IT IS, AND MY WHOLE GAME UP
UNTIL THIS POINT HAS BEEN VERY
CLOUDY, BUT NOW EVERYTHING IS
BECOMING MUCH MORE CLEAR.
IS IT JUST ME OR ARE YOU FEELING
LIKE REALLY GOOD?
>> I'M REALLY GOOD.
>> YOU DID SO WELL.
BUT YOU REALIZE WE VOTE OFF ONE
MORE PERSON AND WE'RE GUARANTEED
FINAL FOUR, BECAUSE THEN WE HAVE
THE MAJORITY AND THEN WE CAN BE
OPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TO HIDE.
>> EVEN RIGHT NOW WE HAVE
LAUREN'S VOTE.
IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE ONCE WE HAVE US FOUR A
MAJORITY, WE'RE SET.
HAVING BEN BEING OUR SECRET
AGENT, I KNOW WHERE THE IDOL IS.
I KNOW WHERE THE ADVANTAGES ARE,
AND I KNOW WHAT EVERY SINGLE
PLAYER IS THINKING.
>> IT'S BETWEEN CHRISSY AND JOE
FOR SURE.
THE ONLY REASON I WANT THE KEEP
JOE OVER CHRISSY IS I THINK
CHRISSY'S MORE OF A CHALLENGE
THREAT THAN JOE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THIS GAME
I'M CALLING THE SHOTS, AND I
DON'T THINK ANYONE KNOWS THAT
I'M AS GOOD AT THIS GAME AS I
AM.
SO I'M SITTING IN THE BEST
POSSIBLE SEAT IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S REWARD
CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, WE'RE
GOING TO RANDOMLY DIVIDE INTO
TWO TEAMS OF FOUR.
ON MY GO, YOU'LL SWIM OUT THE A
BOAT, THEN PADDLE TO SHORE,
COLLECTING THREE BAGS OF LOGS
ALONG THE WAY.
YOU'LL THEN USE THOSE LOGS TO
PUSH PUZZLE PIECES THROUGH A
TUNNEL.
ONCE ALL THE PIECES ARE OUT, YOU
WILL USE THEM TO COMPLETE A
SURVIVOR PUZZLE.
FIRST FOUR TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YEAH.
>> THE WINNING FOUR WILL ENJOY A
SURVIVOR SPA.
YOU WILL ENJOY A NICE SHOWER.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: YOU'LL THEN ENJOY
MASSAGES.
AND THEN YOU'LL EAT CHICKEN,
VEGGIE WRAPS, FRESH FRUIT, AND
FOR DESSERT, KEY LIME AND PECAN
PIE.
>> NO, WAY.
YUMMY.
>> PECAN PIE.
I LIKE IT.
>> Jeff: LOSERS, NOTHING.
WE'LL DRAW FOR TEAMS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO THIS!
ALL RIGHT.
WE RANDOMLY DIVIDED INTO TEAMS.
WE HAVE LAUREN, RYAN, MIKE, AND
CHRISSY TAKING ON BEN, ASHLEY,
JOE, AND DEVON.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO GET EVERYBODY
IN THE BOAT.
MIKE IS TRYING TO GET UP IN THE
BOAT FOR RED.
DEVON TRYING TO GET UP IN THERE
FOR BLUE.
START PADDLING.
RED FINALLY HAS EVERYONE IN THE
BOAT.
IT IS BLUE OFF TO THE EARLY LEAD
NOW, WORKING TOWARD THAT FIRST
PLATFORM.
DEVON'S GOT FIRST BAG.
AND THEY ARE HEAVY.
BLUE WITH THE EARLY LEAD.
HERE COMES RED.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
>> PUSH IT DOWN, PUSH IT DOWN.
>> Jeff: CAN RYAN GET THAT BAG
OFF THE PLATFORM?
IT WEIGHS MORE THAN HE DOES.
HE'S GOING TO NEED HELP.
NOW IT'S IN THE WATER.
>> GIVE ME YOUR HAND, GIVE ME
YOUR HAND SO YOU WON'T FALL.
>> Jeff: RED FINALLY HAS THEIR
FIRST BAG.
BEN NOW HAS THE SECOND BAG FOR
BLUE.
THE BLUE BOAT NOW HAS PADDLED
AWAY FROM BEN.
HE CAN'T PUT THE PIECES IN NOW.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET BACK THE THAT
PLATFORM.
>> COME ON.
GET THE PIECES IN.
>> Jeff: BLUE STRUGGLING NOW.
>> COME ON, THEY'RE STRUGGLING,
LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: BEN MAKES IT.
YOU'RE GOOD, BLUE.
RED NOW HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
TIME.
MIKE HOPS OFF.
HAS THE PUZZLE PIECES FOR RED.
BLUE HEADING FOR THEIR THIRD AND
FINAL BAG OF LOGS.
HERE COMES RED.
MIKE IS GOING TO JUMP OFF FOR
RED.
BLUE WITH A MUCH EASIER TIME
THIS TIME.
PADDLE TO SHORE NOW.
RED HAS THEIR THIRD BAG.
PADDLE TO SHORE.
THEY ARE DEAD EVEN AGAIN.
BOTH TEAMS NOW TRYING TO CLIP
IN.
YOU'RE GOOD, BLUE.
YOU'RE GOOD, RED.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET ALL THE
PIECES UP THE BEACH.
CANNOT START UNTYING UNTIL YOU
HAVE ALL THREE BAGS.
LAUREN TAKING ONE BY HERSELF,
AND A LOT OF WEIGHT.
THIS IS NOW WHERE BLUE'S
STRENGTH IS COMING INTO PLAY.
THEY GET ALL THREE BAGS UP
QUICKLY.
START UNTYING.
>> I NEED HELP WITH THIS ONE.
>> RED REALLY STRUGGLING.
CHRISSY AND RYAN CANNOT GET OUT
THAT BAG.
BLUE, YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU CAN START SHOVING LOGS
THROUGH.
HERE COMES RYAN AND CHRISSY.
YOU'RE GOOD.
START UNTYING.
YOU HAVE TO GET ALL YOUR LOGS
THROUGH THIS TUNNEL, AND AS YOU
PUSH THOSE LOGS, YOU ARE PUSHING
YOUR PUZZLE PIECES OUT THE OTHER
SIDE.
THAT IS YOUR NEXT GOAL.
BLUE NOW EXTENDING THEIR LEAD.
DEVON AND BEN ALTERNATING
PUSHING THOSE LOGS THROUGH.
AND WITH EVERY PUSH, THEY
RELEASE MORE PUZZLE PIECES.
>> GO, LAUREN!
>> Jeff: RED HAS THEIRS FREE.
RED CAN START PUSHING.
BLUE HAS ALL OF THEIRS THROUGH.
YOU'RE GOOD, BLUE.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET ALL THE
PIECES UP ON YOUR PUZZLE TABLE.
LET'S GO, RED!
LAUREN USING HER WHOLE BODY TO
PUSH THESE LOGS THROUGH.
WOOD DIGGING INTO SKIN.
SHE DOESN'T CARE.
IT'S "SURVIVOR."
BEN AND ASHLEY STARTING ON THE
PUZZLE FOR BLUE.
LAUREN HAS BEEN A WORKHORSE IN
THIS CHALLENGE USING HER BODY TO
SHOVE THESE LOGS THROUGH.
THAT WILL DO IT.
GO, RED.
BEN AND ASHLEY HAVE HAD A LOT OF
TIME TO START GETTING USED TO
THIS PUZZLE.
>> TO THE LEFT OF IT.
>> Jeff: IT'S GOING TO BE MIKE
AND CHRISSY WORKING FOR RED, AND
THEY HAVE A BIG TASK AHEAD OF
THEM.
BLUE HAS HAD A BIG HEA START.
THIS WOULD BE A GIGANTIC
COMEBACK FOR MIKE AND CHRISSY IF
THEY CAN PULL IT OFF.
BEN AND ASHLEY NOW HAVE TO TRADE
PIECES AROUND.
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
THAT'S OPENING THE DOOR FOR RED.
DEVON SEES ITS.
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
PANIC STARTS TO SET IN AND THEN
YOU START THE MAKE MORE
MISTAKES.
MOMENTUM CAN SHIFT QUICKLY.
RED IS STARTING TO MAKE SOME
PROGRESS OVER HERE.
>> THAT WAY, THAT WAY, THAT WAY.
>> Jeff: THEY CAN SENSE
THEY'RE BACK IN THIS BECAUSE
ASHLEY AND BEN ARE SLOWING DOWN.
>> YOU GUYS GOT IT?
YOU GUYS GOT IT?
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT ON BLUE.
AND THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT RED WAS
HOPING FOR.
>> THAT WAY, THAT WAY.
>> Jeff: A MISTAKE.
>> HERE, HERE.
>> Jeff: BEN AND ASHLEY MAKING
QUICK MOVES.
THEY THINK THEY HAVE IT.
>> WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT, WE GOT
IT.
>> HEROES VERSUS HEALERS, VERSUS
HUSTLERS.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD!
REWARD FOR JOE, DEVON, BEN, AND
ASHLEY.
>> WE HAD A MINUTE LEFT.
>> WE COULD HAVE GOTTEN IT.
>> Jeff: JOE, BEN, ASHLEY AND
DEVON WAITING FOR YOU A SURVIVOR
SPA, WHILE THE OTHER FOUR,
LAUREN, CHRISSY, RYAN, AND MIKE
CAN DO NOTHING BUT WISH IT WAS
THEM.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
>> I FELT CONFIDENT WE WERE
GOING TO WIN, AND WE WON.
IT FEELS GREAT.
I NO LONGER AM ON THE BOTTOM,
AND I HAVE A TRUE ALLIANCE.
THE TABLES HAVE TURNED.
MASSAGE.
>> TO OUR WIN.
>> SALUDE.
>> GOOD JOB.
I'M SO PROUD OF US.
THIS IS GOING TO BOOST OUR GAME.
THE REWARD IS AMAZING.
TO HAVE A SPA DAY AND SHOWER AND
GET MASSAGES AND HEAT WRAPS.
IT'S LIKE HITTING A RESTART
BUTTON ON MY BODY.
>> TRY ONE OF THESE.
>> BUT THERE IS STILL STRATEGY
IN MIND.
SO BEN IS STILL PLAYING THE ROLE
OF THE DETHRONED KING, AND JOE
IS STILL EATING IT UP.
>> I LOVE LIVING THIS WAY.
LIKE A KING.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU SHOULD FEEL RIGHT AT HOME
THEN, KING ARTHUR.
>> YOU'RE A JERK.
>> TO KING ARTHUR.
>> CHEERS TO MY DISLOYAL
KNIGHTS.
>> IT WOULD BE NICE TO KICK BACK
AND RELAX WITH DEVON AND ASHLEY,
BUT I'M STILL PLAYING MY PART AS
BEING ON THE OUTS, BUT THAT IS
KIND OF FUN FOR ME NOW JUST
BECAUSE I'M MESSING WITH JOE AND
HE DON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
ANY TIME I CAN MESS WITH JOE,
I'LL TAKE IT
>> LIFE IS GOOD.
>> WHEN YOUR ALLIANCE TURNS ON
YOU, IT'S NOT SO FUN.
DID YOU HAVE THAT PLANNED FROM
THE GET-GO, OR WHEN DID... YOU
DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER, BUT...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
>> I'D RATHER NOT TALK ABOUT IT
HONESTLY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S FAIR.
>> THAT'S JUST A MOVE WE MADE
AND THE GAME MOVES ON.
>> BEN HAS BEEN THE LEADER OF
THIS PACK.
HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY THIS
GAME WITHOUT POWER AND CONTROL.
HE WANTS TO TALK ABOUT THE GAME
OBVIOUSLY, AND WE'RE JUST LIKE,
DUDE, WE'RE NOT GOING TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
NOW HE KNOWS HOW I FELT.
>> WELL, HOPEFULLY I'M NOT NEXT,
THAT'S ALL I'M GOING THE SAY.
>> YOU'RE A DANGEROUS MAN, BUT
THERE ARE A LOT OF DANGEROUS
PEOPLE OUT HERE.
>> BEN IS STILL PUTTING ON HIS
ACADEMY AWARD PERFORMANCE AS A
VERY DISAPPOINTED KING ARTHUR,
AND HE SELLS IT LIKE I'VE NEVER
SEEN A STORY SOLD.
IT'S AWESOME.
BUT HE'S PLAYING A REALLY GOOD
GAME, AND THAT'S PRETTY SCARY.
>> THAT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
>> HOWDY, PARTNER.
>> YOU'RE LUCKY WE GOT TO KNOW
EACH OTHER THAT WELL.
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
>> WE'RE GETTING TOGETHER.
>> LAST NIGHT WAS LIKE THE
TURNING POINT OF THIS ENTIRE
GAME FOR ME AND YOU.
>> YEAH.
BECAUSE WE FINALLY MADE A BIG
MOVE.
>> AND NOW EVERYONE IS
SCRAMBLING.
>> I'M FEELING LIKE THIS GAME
JUST UP TO A WHOLE OTHER LEVEL
FOR ME.
COMING INTO THE MERGE, I
DEFINITELY TOOK A BACKSEAT IN MY
OWN GAME, BUT MY GAME PLAY HAS
REALLY EVOLVED, AND I FEEL LIKE
I'M FINALLY PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
>> IT'S GOOD.
IT'S A GOOD FEELING.
>> BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL.
>> MAKING THAT BIG MOVE SET THE
PACE FOR SOME MORE BIG MOVES
DOWN THE ROAD.
I HONESTLY FEEL LIKE THIS IS MY
GAME TO LOSE.
>> IT WAS A FUN CHALLENGE TODAY,
THOUGH.
>> FUN?
WAS IT, THOUGH?
>> WHERE IS FUN IN THAT
CHALLENGE?
>> I FEEL LIKE NOTHING IS GOING
MY WAY.
I CAN'T WIN A VEGGIE WRAP.
THAT'S HOW BAD THINGS ARE GOING
RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE AN IDOL IN MY POCKET, BUT
I DON'T WANT TO JUST PLAY IT
ONCE AND THEN JUST GO HOME THE
NEXT TIME, SO I NEED TO TALK TO
MIKE, BECAUSE IF WE CAN WORK
TOGETHER AND WE CAN SHOW THAT WE
BOTH HAVE BEEN LEFT OUT OF
VOTES, WE HAVE BOTH WITHIN ON
THE BOTTOM, I THINK IT WOULD
ENDEAR US TO EACH OTHER AND JUST
MAYBE I COULD SWING HIM OVER AND
HAVE THE NUMBERS BACK ON OUR
SIDE.
>> "SURVIVOR" IS VERY
SITUATIONAL.
>> EXTREMELY.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT JUST FIVE, YOU,
LAUREN, DEVON, JOE AND YOURSELF?
AND AGAIN, I KNOW, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO...
>> I CAN'T SAY.
>> I GOT IT.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHERE I WAS
THREE TRIBALS AGO TO WHERE I AM
TODAY, I WENT FROM THE BOTTOM TO
THE TOP, AND NOW I HAVE A NICE
ALLIANCE OF FIVE.
WE HAVE A PLAN TO WORK TOGETHER,
AND I'M STICKING TO THAT PLAN.
>> I STILL WANT THE WORK WITH
YOU, MIKE.
>> YOU NEVER WANTED TO WORK WITH
ME.
I GAVE YOU SO MANY OPPORTUNITIES
TO WORK WITH ME.
>> NO QUESTION.
>> FOR A WEEK I GAVE YOU
OPPORTUNITIES TO WORK WITH ME.
>> THE GAME CHANGES, YOU KNOW
THAT.
>> UH-HUH.
THE GAME DOES CHANGE.
>> I WENT UP TO RYAN EVERY DAY
FOR AT LEAST A WEEK AND SAID,
LET'S WORK TOGETHER, AND HE SAID
NO.
I THINK I'M PRETTY GOOD RIGHT
NOW, UNFORTUNATELY.
WELL, UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW?
HE SAID TO ME RIGHT BEFORE
TRIBAL COUNCIL HE WASN'T VOTING
FOR ME, AND THEN HE VOTED FOR
ME, AND HE HAS THE NERVE TO COME
UP TO ME THE NEXT DAY AND SAY,
YOU KNOW, MIKE I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO WORK WITH YOU.
WELL, ISN'T IT JUST A BUCK LATE
AND A DOLLAR SHORT?
>> THIS MIGHT SOUND TOTALLY
BIZARRE, BECAUSE YOU AND I HAVE
NOT TALKED STRATEGY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> BUT RYAN AND I HAVE TALKED
STRATEGY PRIOR TO YESTERDAY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I EXPECTED CHRISSY TO TRY TO
WANT THE TALK TO ME, AND I JUST,
UH-HUH, UH-HUH, BUT THAT'S AS
FAR AS IT GOES.
IT'S VERY ANNOYING.
>> HE HAS TALKED ABOUT GOING
FINAL THREE WITH YOU.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S MENTIONED
IT TO YOU.
>> NO, BUT I MEAN...
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR SORT
OF PLAN IS, WHAT YOUR PERSONAL
PATH TO THE END IS...
>> I'LL LISTEN TO YOU ALL DAY
LONG, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M
GOING TO CHANGE MY MIND.
>> LET'S START HAVING
CONVERSATIONS.
>> WHO ELSE ARE YOU HAVING
CONVERSATIONS WITH?
>> WELL, IF YOU WANTED TO WORK
WITH ME YOU WOULD HAVE TALKED TO
ME SEVERAL WEEKS AGO AND NOT
TODAY.
>> I'VE JUMPED SHIP ONCE.
I'M NOT GOING TO JUMP SHIP
AGAIN.
>> I BELIEVE THAT BEN, RYAN, AND
I ARE THE NEXT ONES TO BE VOTED
OFF.
SO LAUREN DOES SOMEWHAT HAVE MY
FATE IN HER HANDS.
>> I OPENED THE TOPIC, BUT SHE
JUST DIDN'T WANT TO TALK
STRATEGY WITH ME.
>> THIS IS SO WONDERFUL.
>> ISN'T IT, THOUGH?
THEY DON'T WANT TO BE SEEN AS
DESPERATE, BUT THAT'S HOW I'M
FEELING TODAY.
THIS GAME IS KICKING MY BUTT,
AND IT IS A NEW FEELING FOR ME.
AND RIGHT NOW I AM DEFINITELY IN
TROUBLE, BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> NEW YORK I THINK THAT I'M
JUST... I'M JUST HUNGRY.
>> HUNGRY, TIRED OF SLEEPING ON
BAMBOO, WET, COLD?
>> DO YOU NEED A HUG OR
ANYTHING?
>> BEING OUT HERE, BEING
STRIPPED DOWN TO NOTHING IS WAY
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE, BECAUSE IN THE REAL WORLD,
I'M ALWAYS IN CONTROL OF
EVERYTHING.
AND IT'S HARD FOR ME TO NOT BE
IN CONTROL OF MY OWN FATE.
THAT IS WHY THIS GAME KICKS YOUR
ASS.
I REALLY DON'T WANT IT TO BE THE
END OF THE LINE.
>> THANK YOU FOR COOKING THE
RICE.
THIS HAS BEEN MY YEARS FOR 16
YEARS, AND WHAT I DO AS AN
ACTUARY IS COME UP WITH ALL OF
THE POSSIBLE OUTCOME, SO I WILL
ALWAYS KEEP THINKING OF
DIFFERENT COMBINATIONS AND
DIFFERENT WAYS THAT I CAN GET
MYSELF BACK ON TOP.
I HOPE THAT I CAN HAVE THE LAST
LAUGH.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> WOW.
>> HELL NO.
>> THAT LOOKS HARD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ASHLEY, GOT THE TAKE BACK THE
NECKLACE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> HARD TO GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: I KNOW IT IS.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHANG, YOU'RE GOING
TO USE A "SURVIVOR" DRIVING
WHEEL TO TRANSPORT A KEY THROUGH
A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
THAT KEY WILL UNLOCK A SET OF
BLOCK PUZZLE PIECES.
YOU'LL TRANSPORT THOSE TO THE
FINISH AND USE THEM TO SOLVE A
WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
SEVEN SHOT AT GETTING TO THE
END.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE 11th
PERSON VOTED OUT, THE FOURTHS
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
DRAW FOR SPOTS, GET IT ON.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMONTI, GUARANTEED SPOT IN
THE FINAL SEVEN, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
FIRST STAGE, TRANSPORT THAT KEY
THROUGH THESE OBSTACLES.
IF IT DROPS, YOU'VE GOT TO GO
BACK.
ASHLEY UP FIRST.
THERE'S BEN.
THERE GOES DEVON AND RYAN.
ASHLEY DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
BEN IS GOOD.
DEVON, YOU'RE GOOD.
RYAN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
LAUREN'S GOT TO GO BACK.
HERE COMES JOE.
HE'S GOOD.
MIKE DROPS, GOT TO GO BACK,
CHRISSY IS GOOD.
NOW YOU GOT TO GO ACROSS A
BALANCE BEAM.
BEN REALLY WORKING IT CAREFULLY.
IT IS DEVON, BEN, JOE, AND
CHRISSY NOW IN THIS SECOND
SECTION.
A LITTLE MORE DIFFICULT.
YOU HAVE SOME SPEED BUMPS.
BEN IS GOOD AGAIN.
BEN CAN NOW UNROCK HIS PUZZLE
PIECES.
DEVON IS ACROSS.
START UNLOCKING NOW.
JOE SLOW AND STEADY.
JOE IS ACROSS.
BEN RELEASES HIS PIECES.
ASHLEY COMING ACROSS NOW.
YOU'RE GOOD, ASHLEY.
NOW YOU GOT TO STACK YOUR PIECES
AND GET TO THE FINISH.
CHRISSY, YOU'RE GOOD.
HERE COMES MIKE.
MIKE DROPS AGAIN.
RYAN AND MIKE STILL BACK IN THE
FIRST SECTION.
LAUREN, YOU'RE GOOD.
BEN NOW HAS HIS PIECES FREE.
BEN TAKING THIS FIRST SECTION
WITH FOUR PIECES.
HERE GOES DEVON WITH FOUR
PIECES.
HE'S MOVING QUICKLY.
DEVON NOW IN THE LEAD.
IT IS DEVON AND BEN, DUMP THEM
IN AND GO BACK AND GET MORE.
YOU HAVE TO GET THEM ALL IN THE
BIN BEFORE YOU CAN GO BACK.
BEN RIGHT ON DEVON'S TALE WITH
FOUR.
DEVON IN THE LEAD, THEN BEN.
JOE DROPS.
GOT TO START AGAIN.
HERE COMES ASHLEY WITH FOUR.
IT IS NOW DEVON AND BEN RACING,
CARRYING THOSE DRIVING WHEELS.
GET THEM ALL IN THE BEN, ASHLEY.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
HERE COMES CHRISSY WITH FOUR.
DEVON WITH FOUR MORE.
LAUREN NOW WITH HER FIRST FOUR.
MIKE IS THROUGH THE FIRST
SECTION.
RYAN IS THROUGH THE FIRST
HE'S NOW IN THE SECOND SECTION.
DEVON IN THE LEAD, THEN BEN.
THEN JOE, CHRISSY, LAUREN AND
ASHLEY.
DEVON WITH HIS LAST FOUR PUZZLE
BLOCKS.
BEN GOING TO BE RIGHT BEHIND
HIM.
THERE'S ASHLEY NOW GETTING VERY
CREATIVE WITH EIGHT BLOCKS AT
ONCE.
DEVON HAS ALL HIS.
START WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
ASHLEY'S ACROSS.
JUST LIKE THAT ASHLEY IS BACK IN
THIS.
HUGE MOVE BY ASHLEY AND IT
WORKS.
SHE WON THE LAST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
WOULD LOVE TO WIN IT AGAIN.
AND DEVON, ASHLEY, AND BEN
ALREADY STARTING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
CHRISSY DROPS THREE MORE.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
CHRISSY IS TAKING A LONG TIME,
BUT TRYING TO GET BACK IN THIS.
WE'RE THIS CLOSE TO THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
YOU HAVE TO DIG IN RIGHT NOW.
THERE IS ONE WORD: YOU SOLVE IT,
YOU ARE SAFE IN THIS GAME.
IT WON'T BE EASY.
YOU KNOW THAT.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
>> NO IDEA.
>> Jeff: LAUREN COMING BACK
WITH HER FINAL FOUR PUZZLE
PIECES.
CHRISSY WITH HER LAST FOUR
YOU'RE STILL IN THIS.
LET'S GO!
WE ARE CLOSE.
ANYBODY COULD WIN THIS RIGHT
NOW.
CHRISSY PUTTING PIECES IN.
LAUREN PUTTING PIECES IN.
ONE WORD: WHAT COULD IT BE?
YOU CAN SEE THE WEAR AND TEAR OF
30 DAYS, NOT EASY.
EIGHT PEOPLE ALL FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY, SECURITY TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CHRISSY PLACES ONE LETTER AND
ANOTHER.
DEVON STEPPING BACK TO LOOK AT
CHRISSY'S PUZZLE, ALL IS FAIR IN
"SURVIVOR."
DEVON NOW QUICKLY RACES UP AND
THINKS HE HAS SOMETHING.
DEVON IS MOVINGS A FAST AS HE
CAN.
BEN LOOKING FOR SOME HELP.
BEN NOW HAS AN IDEA.
ASHLEY NOW GETTING IN ON THIS.
IT'S GOING TO COMING DOWN TO HOW
FAST YOU CAN SOLVE THIS PUZZLE.
CHRISSY ONE BLOCK AFTER ANOTHER,
DEVON THINKS HE HAS IT.
BEN THINKS HE HAS SOMETHING.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, SAY IT:
>> INVULNERABLE!
>> Jeff: CHRISSY PULLS IT OUT,
WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY, SAFE
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> GOOD JOB, BABY.
>> THANKS!
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, COME ON
OVER.
>> I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS
FOR 16 YEARS.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
YOU ARE BEAMING RIGHT NOW.
WHAT IS THIS DREAMING WHEN YOU
DREAM ABOUT PLAYING "SURVIVOR"
AND YOU PULL OFF ONE OF THE MOST
ICONIC MOMENTS, WINNING
>> I REALLY NEEDED IT TONIGHT.
IT'S AN INCREDIBLE FEELING TO
KNOW I'LL BE HERE TOMORROW ON
DAY 31.
>> Jeff: GUARANTEED A SPOT IN
THE FINAL SEVEN.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SADLY
FOR ONE OF YOU TONIGHT, 11th
PERSON VOTED OUT, FOURTH MEMBER
OF OUR JURY, IT WON'T BE YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF BACK AT CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT WON'T BE YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
I AM INVULNERABLE.
FINALLY WON AN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
I REALLY BELIEVE I WAS THE ONE
WHO WAS GOING TO GO HOME, SO
COMING HOME WITH THIS NECKLACE
IS JUST BEAUTIFUL IN SO MANY
>> GOOD JOB, CHRISSY.
>> I KNEW I WAS DONE.
>> A 12-LETTER WORD?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A 12-LETTER
WORD IN MY VOCABULARY.
>> AFTER THE CHALLENGE, EVEN
WITH CHRISSY WINNING, THERE ARE
THREE OTHER PEOPLE TO PICK AND
SEND HOME, SO NO HARM NO FOUL.
NOW WE JUST NEED TO GET TO
GETTING AND FIGURE OUT WHO IS
VOTED OUT NEXT.
>> NUMBER-ONE THING IS WHO WE'RE
VOTING OUT.
>> JOE.
WE DON'T NEED JOE ANYMORE, YO.
WE DON'T NEED JOE.
>> WE REALLY DON'T.
LET'S DO JOE.
EASY, SIMPLE, JOE.
DONE DEAL.
>> MY ALLIANCE OF FOUR IS GOING
TO VOTE JOE.
NOW, WE HAVE TO COME UP WITH
THIS WHOLE NEW PITCH TO JOE AND
MIKE.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST TELL JOE
AND MIKE WE'RE GOING TO USE YOUR
EXTRA VOTE TONIGHT, BUT WE'RE
NOT GOING TO USE IT SOME WE'LL
TELL THEM, ME, JOE, AND MIKE
WILL ALL VOTE RYAN, AND YOU'LL
SAY YOU, AND ASHLEY AND YOUR
EXTRA VOTE WILL VOTE BEN.
THAT WAY WE'RE SAFE, AND THEN
WE'RE ONLY VOTING JOE OUT.
I COME UP WITH THIS IDEA TO TELL
THEM TO SPLIT THE VOTES BETWEEN
RYAN AND BEN, BUT THE REALITY IS
MYSELF, ASHLEY, LAUREN, AND BEN,
ARE GOING TO VOTE JOER AND JOE
WILL GO HOME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A PLAN.
LAUREN'S GOT AN EXTRA VOTE.
>> WHENEVER I WANT THE USE IT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO USE IT
TONIGHT.
SO HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
DO.
YOU, MIKE, AND ME ARE GOING TO
VOTE RYAN.
LAUREN, HER EXTRA GEAUX VOTE
BEN.
RYAN PLAYS THE IDOL, THEY REVOTE
AND WE ALL VOTE BEN.
>> THEY DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE
EXTRA VOTE?
>> NO.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
LAUREN HAS AN ADVANTAGE WHICH
GIVES HER THE ABILITY TO
ACTUALLY VOTE TWICE.
SO RIGHT NOW I MEAN I'M
ECSTATIC.
I FEEL SO MUCH SAFER JUST
KNOWING THAT ADVANTAGE IS GOING
TO BE USED.
>> WE HAVE PLAN.
>> I'M SOLID, GUYS.
I AIN'T GOING NOWHERE.
>> HONESTLY, I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
BEN GO.
HE'S THE BIGGEST THREAT IN THIS
GAME.
I'M EXCITED FOR BEN TO GO HOME
BECAUSE BEN IS THE BIGGEST
THREAT OUT HERE AT THIS POINT.
HE WILL DO ANYTHING TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> SO WE DON'T EVEN NEED THE
TALK ABOUT IT ANYMORE.
IT'S SET.
>> AND BEN HAS BETRAYED ME
MULTIPLE TIMES.
FULL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU.
FOOL ME TWICE, SHAME ON ME.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET BEN FOOL ME
AGAIN.
>> LET ME SAY, THIS I THINK ANY
WAY THEY SPLIT THE VOTES IT'S
GOING TO BE YOU.
>> IF THEY'RE SMART.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, THEY HAVE TO KNOW THAT
WE WOULD VOTE AS A BLOC.
>> WHO WOULD YOU GUYS WANT TO
VOTE FOR?
>> I GOT TO GET ASHLEY AND DEVON
OUT.
DEVON SCREWED YOU, TOO.
AND ASHLEY SCREWED ME.
>> WHAT ASHLEY DID TO YOU...
>> HOW DID WE GET TRICKED BY TWO
25 YEAR OLD SURFERS?
>> GOSH DANG IT, THAT STINKS,
Y'ALL.
>> THIS WHOLE ACT THAT I'M
PUTTING ON, Y'ALL, IT IS LATE
EXHAUSTING.
BUT IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE TO
THIS POINT.
SO I JUST NEED TO GET THROUGH
ONE MORE TRIBAL AND PLAY THE
POOR ME, WHY ME, OH, ME CARD.
>> THEY NOVI THE IDOL.
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS.
>> I MIGHT PLAY IT.
I MIGHT NOT.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I WOULD.
IF I HAD ONE, I WOULD PLAY IT.
IT GETS YOU TO DAY 31.
>> YEAH.
>> WHATEVER HAPPENS, IT'S BEEN A
PLEASURE.
>> I STILL HAVE AN IDOL, BUT I
DON'T FEEL I NEED TO PLAY IT.
AND FOR TONIGHT TO ACTUALLY
HAPPEN THE WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN, PUT A SUCKER IN MY HAND
AND A BALLOON IN THE OTHER, AN
I'LL BE SITTING THERE LIKE A
LITTLE KID IN A CANDY STORE JUST
WATCHING JOE GET HIS TORCH
SNUFFED.
>> I'M JUST THINKING, WE WOULD
BE CRAZY TO TAKE HIM TO FOUR.
>> I AGREE 100%, CITIZENNING
NEXT TO HIM.
>> EVERYONE WOULD VOTE BEN.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S A STRONG, A LEADER, THE
KIDS.
SHOOT, I WOULD VOTE BEN.
>> TIMING IS EVERYTHING IN THIS
GAME.
AND IT COULD BE THE TIME TO VOTE
BEN OUT, BECAUSE HE HAS MADE BIG
DECISION, AND HE HAS BEEN THE
KING IN HIS ROUNDTABLE AND ALL
THAT STUFF.
YOU KNOW WHY DON'T JOE AND MIKE
USE THE VOTES WE NEED TO USE
THEM.
ME, AND YOU AND DEVON NEED THE
TALK ABOUT US THREE, VOTE BEN
OUT.
>> RIGHT NOW IT'S BEN, MYSELF,
LAUREN, AND DEVON.
AND JOE IS THE ONE WE'RE VOTING
OUT, BUT IT SEEMS LIKE BEN WOULD
BE A HUGE THREAT AT THE END, AND
I REALIZE THAT THIS GAME YOU
HAVE TO BE AGGRESSIVE, AND I'M
STARTING TO DO THAT.
>> IT'S NOTHING AGAINST BEN, BUT
HE'LL WIN.
>> TAKING OUT THE STRONGER
PLAYERS IS I THINK... BEN COULD
GO HOME TONIGHT.
THIS COULD BE OUR CHANCE TO MAKE
THAT HAPPEN.
>> I AM CONSIDERING AN
ALTERNATIVE PLAN ABOUT GETTING
BEN OUT.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YES.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WOW.
>> SHHH.
THAT'S A MOVE RIGHT THERE FOR
BOTH OF US.
>> YEAH.
>> BEN'S THINKING OF BIG MOVES.
BEN IS DANGEROUS.
>> AND IT WOULD HAVE TO BE 100%
A BLINDSIDE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S BETWEEN BEN AND JOE.
>> WHICH ONE DO YOU THINK?
>> THIS IS HARD.
THIS IS A DIFFICULT DECISION.
I'M HAVING A HARD TIME HERE
THINKING.
>>THIS VOTE IS NOT AN EASY ONE.
BEN IS INCLUDED IN OUR ALLIANCE,
BUT I REALIZE THAT BEN IS A BIG
THREAT.
I NEED TO MAKE BIG MOVES IN THIS
GAME TO SUCCEED, SO I GOT TO
KEEP DOING WHAT I'M DOING, AND I
GOT TO BE RUTHLESS, BUT ALSO I
HAVE TO BE SMART AND MAKE THE
RIGHT DECISION.
>> Jeff: WE NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
DESI, COLE, AND J.P. VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
MIKE, LET'S START WITH YOU.
YOU WALK INTO TRIBAL DOWN SILL,
DAY, 30 SMILING.
>> I'M JUST LOVING IT, JEFF.
I MEAN, I'M LIVING A DREAM.
I'M STILL HERE.
MY TRIBE VIBES ME.
I VIBE THEM.
I THINK I'M DOING PRETTY GOOD.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY, YOU HAD A
LITTLE BIT OF THAT EXCITEMENT
TODAY.
YOU WIN THIS CHALLENGE, AND YOU
SAID 16 YEARS BEEN WAITING ON
THIS MOMENT.
>> I STARTED TRYING TO PLAY THIS
GAME IN 2001.
I FINALLY GOT THE DREAM, AND
THEN I GOT TO WIN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY SOME YOU CAN'T HELP BUT
BE JOYFUL EVEN AT A TIME LIKE
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY
HAS TO GO HOME AND IT VERY WELL
COULD HAVE BEEN ME HAD I NOT HAD
THIS BEAUTIFUL NECKLACE ON MY
NECK.
>> Jeff: JOE, CAN YOU RELATE
THE CRISIS.
EVEN THOUGH TRIBAL IS WHERE
PEOPLE ARE VOTED OUT, BUT THERE
IS THIS EXCITEMENT THAT THIS IS
WHERE THE GAME IS WON AND LOST.
>> TRIBAL IS EXCITING BECAUSE WE
WANT TO SEE HOW STRONG OUR
ALLIANCES ARE AND HOW THIS GAME
IS GOING TO GO.
ARE PEOPLE GOING TO PLAY SAFE OR
BE RISKY.
>> Jeff: BEN, JOE REALLY SAID
SOMETHING INTERESTING.
AT TRIBAL IS WHERE YOU REALLY
TEST THOSE ALLIANCES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
LAST WEEK CHRISSY, RYAN, AND
MYSELF WERE BLIND SIDED.
THE THREE ROGUE NIGHTS AND THE
TWO JESTERS HAVE FORMED UP, AND
LOOKS LIKE I'M PROBABLY GOING
HOME TONIGHT, JEFF.
>> Jeff: RYAN, SO BEN IS BEING
PRETTY CLEAR THAT HE BELIEVES
YOU, HIMSELF, AND CHRISSY ARE IN
TROUBLE, AND NOW IT'S NOT A
SEVEN, IT'S A FIVE.
>> I THINK BEN PUT IT PERFECTLY.
YOU HAVE MIKE AND JOE IN THE
MIDDLE, AND THREE PEOPLE TOOK
ADVANTAGE OF THEM.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS
COMPLACENCY ON OUR PART OR JUST
COMFORTABILITY WITHIN THE SEVEN
THAT WE FELT.
>> Jeff: OWE IS ALREADY
SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
WHY ARE YOU SHAKING YOUR HEAD?
>> IT WAS NEVER A SEVEN.
BEN FAILED TO REALIZE HE WASN'T
KING BEN WITH SIX KNIGHTS.
HE WAS KING BEN WITH QUEENS AND
KINGS AROUND HIM.
HE PUT HIS GUARD DOWN AND LOOK
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> Jeff: SO DO YOU TAKE A
LITTLE JOY?
>> A LITTLE?
NO.
I TAKE A LOT OF JOY.
>> I THINK "SURVIVOR" IS ONE OR
LOST BY ALLIANCE MANAGEMENT.
I DON'T THINK THEY WERE MANAGING
THEIR ALLIANCE APPROPRIATELY.
>> TO ADDRESS JOE'S ANSWER
THERE, JEFF, HE CALLED EVERY ONE
OF US PUPPETS, A BUNCH OF GOATS
AND SHEEP AND STUFF LIKE, THAT
BUT NOW HE'S SITTING HERE
CALLING HIS ALLIANCE KINGS AND
QUEENS BECAUSE HE'S KNOWS HE'S
ON THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: MIKE, BEN IS
BASICALLY SAYING, NOW YOU'RE IN
A GROUP, BUT YOU'RE STILL ON THE
BOTTOM BECAUSE YOU AND THE OTHER
COCONUT ARE THE FREELANCERS.
>> YOU CAN SEE WE'RE ON THE
BOTTOM OF THE GROUP, BUT THERE
IS AN EQUAL EXCHANGE OF
INFORMATION FROM ALL FIVE OF US
EVERY TIME WE GET TOGETHER.
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE THE NEWEST
MEMBERS DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE THE
LEAST IMPORTANT MEMBERS OF THE
ALLIANCE.
>> HE'S RIGHT, LOOKING FROM THE
OUTSIDE IN, THEY'RE TRYING TO
FIND CRACKS.
BUT I FEEL THIS IS A TRUE
ALLIANCE AND RIGHT NOW WHAT'S
BEST FOR US IS TO STICK
TOGETHER.
>> BUT THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT WAS
CRITICIZED ABOUT OUR OLD
ALLIANCE, AND NOW THAT THERE'S A
FIVE-PERSON ALLIANCE INSTEAD OF
A SEVEN, IT'S A VERY TIGHT
DIVERSION FROM WHAT HAS BEEN
SAID BELIEVE TRIBAL COUNCILS BY
THESE EXACT PEOPLE.
>> I LIKE THEY TRY THE SAY THEY
DID IT WITH SEVEN AND WE DID IT
WITH FIVE AND WHY WOULD WE
EXPECT SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
I LOOK AT IT LIKE TWO SURGEONS
GO INTO THE OPERATING ROOM TO DO
THE SAME OPERATION AND THERE IS
A DIFFERENT OUTCOME?
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE?
THEY'RE DIFFERENT SURGEONS.
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T DO IT RIGHT
DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE NOT GOING TO
DO IT RIGHT.
>> Jeff: DEVON, IT'S LIKE
"SURVIVOR" IS A WHITE BOARD AND
YOU LAY OUT YOUR WHOLE PLAN AND
THE MINUTE YOU DO ONE PLAN, YOU
HAVE TO ERASE IT AND YOU HAVE TO
HAVE A BRAND-NEW PLAN HOUR BY
HOUR.
>> YEAH, EVERY TRIBAL COUNCIL IS
A COMPLETELY NEW PLAN.
AND EVERY TIME YOU VOTE SOMEONE
OFF, THAT COULD AFFECT YOUR GAME
PLAN AND TURN IT COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT DIRECTION.
>> Jeff: ASHLEY, ARE YOU
SURPRISED AT HOW MUCH OF THIS
GOES ON IN "SURVIVOR," OR WERE
YOU ABLE TO ANTICIPATE IT JUST
FROM BEING A FAN?
>> I THINK THE AMOUNT OF UPS AND
DOWNS IN THIS GAME IS IMPOSSIBLE
TO ANTICIPATE, BUT IT IS ALL A
TEST OF ALLIANCES, SO YOU HAVE
TO REALLY PAY ATTENTION BECAUSE
THE UPS AND DOWNS ARE CONSTANT
>> SO CHRISSY, WE'RE DOWN TO
EIGHT.
AT WHAT POINT DOES IT FEEL LIKE
MAYBE YOU CAN'T PENETRATE AN
ALLIANCE.
THERE'S JUST NOT ENOUGH TIME AND
NOT ENOUGH PEOPLE LEFT?
>> I THINK THAT EVEN IF AN
ALLIANCE IS STRONG, YOU ALWAYS
KEEP TRYING TO LOOK FOR THOSE
CRACKS.
YOU KNOW, I SUPPOSE THE TIME
THAT YOU CAN'T PENETRATE ANY
LONGER IS WHEN THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL BEGINS.
>> TRIBAL COUNCIL IS LIKE PROM.
YOU GO WITH SOMEBODY YOU THINK
YOU REALLY LIKE.
AT THE END OF THE NIGHT YOU MAY
LEAVE WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
NOW, I'VE NEVER BEEN TO PROM,
BUT I CAN IMAGINE THAT'S WHAT
IT'S LIKE.
>> Jeff: SO JOE, FOR MANY
TRIBALS YOU'VE BEEN HANGING ON
THE EDGE OF THE MOUNTAIN.
DO YOU FEEL MORE COMFORTABLE
TONIGHT?
>> YEAH, I THINK THIS IS FIRST
TIME IN TRIBAL I FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
YOU KNOW, AND TONIGHT I DON'T
HAVE AN IDOL, SO, YEAH, I MEAN,
I TRUST THE FIVE THAT I'M WITH.
>> Jeff: SO BEN, THAT'S A
PRETTY CLEAR STATEMENT THAT OUR
ALLIANCE IS BUILT BETTER THAN
THE OTHER ALLIANCE WAS BUILT.
AND THAT'S WHY IT'S MORE
POWERFUL AND GOING TO STICK
TOGETHER.
>> JEFF, THAT'S WHAT EVERY
COMFORTABLE ALLIANCE SAYS IN
THIS GAME, AND JUST LIKE US,
EVERY COMFORTABLE ALLIANCE GETS
BLIND SIDED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MIKE, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE A DANGEROUS PLAYER, SO
NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO
HOME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYONE HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I'M PLAYING IT.
IT'S FOR ME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR RYAN WILL NOT
COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE RYAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
RYAN.
ASHLEY.
TWO VOTES ASHLEY.
JOE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES ASHLEY, ONE
VOTE JOE.
JOE.
TWO VOTES ASHLEY, TWO VOTES JOE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JOE, TWO
VOTES ASHLEY.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JOE, YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> GOOD PLAY, Y'ALL.
YOU'RE GOOD PLAYERS.
>> GOOD GAME, JOE.
>> THAT WAS AN INCREDIBLY TIGHT
ALLIANCE.
>> Jeff: JOE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, THAT'S TWO
TRIBALS IN A ROW WHERE
EVERYTHING IS NOT WHAT IT SEEM,
WHICH IS WHY THIS GAME IS SO
MUCH FUN TO WATCH AND SO
DIFFICULT TO PLAY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," YOU WILL BE RUNNING
IN PAIRS WITH YOUR LOVED ONES.
LOVE BRINGS EVERYONE TOGETHER.
BUT IT'S EVERY MAN FOR
THEMSELVES.
>> SOMETHING IS DEFINITELY GOING
ON AROUND HERE.
COMMUNITY NECKLACE?
I HAVE TO DO WHATEVER I HAVE TO
DO TO KEEP MYSELF IN THIS GAME.
>> OH.
THEY DEFINITELY GOT ME.
IT WAS A GOOD CALL ON THEIR
PART.
WE HAD AN ALLIANCE OF FIVE, AND
OBVIOUSLY THEY REALLY DIDN'T
WANT ME IN THAT ALLIANCE.
THEY JUST NEEDED NUMBERS.
BUT I SAID LIKE I SAYS I WAS
GOING THE PLAY.
I PLAYED AGGRESSIVE.
I FOUND A COUPLE IDOLS.
I PLAYED MY GAME.
KUDOS TO THEM.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO SEEING
WHO IS IN THE FINAL THREE.