Previously on Survivor...
At the Naviti,
an alliance emerged that cut across
the old divisions.
Hello, Wendell and Donathan.
Wendell, sure.
And their target was clear.
It could be Chris.
I'm ready for it.
The Malolos were preparing for the council.
The minority alliance
thought itself lost.
It's gone badly.
Then Michael revived hope.
I found the original
James idol in Survivor China.
The worst mistake of any Survivor
is James leaving with two idols.
I feel responsible
for ending this curse,
to this legacy,
to play fair, this time.
Let's act!
At the council,
Michael bluffed
on the power of the idol...
She has the double power
to save two people.
...and carried out his plan.
All four of
us are going to vote Bradley.
If any of you want to join us, all
it takes is one vote.
Finally,
Michael made the wrong decision...
I play it for Steph.
...and couldn't
reverse the idol's curse...
...causing the departure
of his closest ally.
Brendan, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks, Jeff.
It was a real Survivor duel.
Naviti wins this round,
but the question is:
can this tribe get over it,
to avoid coming back here?
There are 16 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What party !
What a crazy first piece of advice!
And how !
I was certain to be cooked.
Tonight was an electroshock.
I thought I was leaving. I was sure of it.
Everyone was trying to save their skin.
Yeah.
Some
with a little more determination.
But I'm thrilled
with the original Naviti.
Because if they hadn't
followed the plan, I would have left.
Nice canard, Michael.
Yes, I only had that.
Sorry if I hurt anyone.
I hope you will understand
our point of view.
I was doing everything I could.
Michael has proven himself
as a tough player.
So far I only saw him
like a loving party animal
hanging out with Jenna and Stephanie.
I had it all wrong.
Now all my Naviti allies
see him as a huge threat.
And so, it was a coin toss.
He was a normal idol.
She could only save
one of us four.
Whatever I did
was hit and miss.
I appreciate your selflessness, Michael.
You could have kept it to yourself.
Yeah, you could have.
Yeah.
It was brave.
Very.
It didn't turn out the way I expected.
I did my best
to save the four
by lying about James' idol.
It was a bet.
This is my first big setback.
I doubt I have a trick to play
on every advice,
so let's avoid...
Yes, let's avoid!
I hope it's us who will have
a turn to play next time.
I don't believe I reversed
a curse.
I didn't play the idol well.
And I'm sorry.
But the council proved to me that
we are the 3 at the bottom of the ladder.
So after tonight,
I have my work cut out.
Over here, everyone!
Naviti,
discover the new Malolo tribe.
Brendan was eliminated
at the last council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today you will step over
a series of plateaus.
Then you undo
a pile of giant sandbags,
revealing a lever.
Pulling
it will release 60 smaller bags.
Collaborating,
you will bring them to the finish.
There you will throw them
at a series of targets,
spinning them
to release a flag.
Three flags released
and the reward is earned.
Want to know what's at stake?
Yes !
It's pretty straightforward.
Coffee and pastries.
Oh my God !
Lord ! Let's go!
Cinnamon rolls!
Wow, Domenick, what a reaction!
Food is scarce.
We have the fishing kit,
but we're struggling.
So it's all good to go.
Clearly worth it.
Moreover, the winning tribe
will send one of the losers
to Ghost Island.
The confrontation continues.
One minute of organization and here we go.
Fine, here we go!
For the reward!
Survivors, ready?
Everyone
must step over the plateaus.
Everybody !
Upright !
Come on, tough guys!
It's good, Naviti!
Malolo, it's good!
Now
we have to undo this stack
very heavy sandbags.
Looking for the lever.
Unleash them!
They are difficult to move.
Bend your legs more!
Coffee and pastries to be won!
Ghost Island in game!
The lever !
The Malolos see the lever.
Yeah Dom! Here is the lever!
It's neck and neck.
Prepare your arm!
Get ready to pull this thing,
we're running!
The lever released, pull it,
this will free the sandbags.
Michael is there! PULL !
Its good ! Go for it !
Malolo took the lead.
Naviti is there! Its good !
Naviti is right behind.
Two people collect the bags.
The others throw them.
The better organized you are,
the faster it will go.
For now, it's chaos.
Bags are flying everywhere.
They should all be
in the trash.
Only then
can you start shooting.
60 bags in all.
It's Stephanie and Jenna for Malolo.
Chris and Wendell for Naviti.
Its good ?
The Naviti have theirs.
One more, Jenna!
Chris will pitch for Naviti.
It hits the target straight away!
Jenna, one more!
Is there one missing !
Everyone should be there!
That's good, Malolo!
Come on, sea bass!
Chris for Naviti...
Chris touches again!
You have to hit the target
so that it unscrews
and releases the flag.
First flag for Chris!
Super know!
Right off the bat ,
Chris is wild for Naviti.
Sebastian tries to follow.
It is far from it.
Take your time, it's good!
...has velocity.
Second flag for Chris!
Lord.
He's on the third.
It seems easy with Chris
while Sebastian struggles.
It is an exceptional arm!
One last shot!
With Chris,
it turns to correction!
And that's it, it's over!
I want these pastries!
Naviti wins the award!
Coffee and pastries!
Cinnamon rolls!
A resounding victory,
thanks to the arm of Chris.
Chris, you clearly have
a sporting background.
It happened to me to throw mines,
in my youth.
That's to say ?
I played baseball in college.
And I was a pitcher.
Nice effort. Result:
a resounding victory for Naviti
and a great reward:
coffee and pastries
leave with you.
Additionally, you will send someone
from Malolo to Ghost Island.
Who ?
The stones ?
The stones.
Without hesitation. Well, the stones.
Without looking.
There is a white stone.
White Stone, Ghost Island.
Sebastian has what's left.
It really leaves it to chance.
Hold out your hands.
Reveal !
Stephanie has the white stone.
Take your things.
The boat will take you.
You'll be back in time
for the next immunity test.
Goodbye !
See you soon !
Naviti, well done.
Come take the reward.
Have a good time !
Prems for chocolate.
Well-deserved.
Take your things, return to camp.
Malolo, nothing for you.
I was just me.
And let's be honest,
I was pretty hot today.
I am a diamond in the rough.
Do you see me shine?
Come admire me, damn it!
No need to pay.
I always reach my goal,
in one throw.
That's all for me.
I almost cried
having to come here.
For now,
I'm at the bottom of the ladder,
with Michael and Jenna,
at the Malolos
It worries me a bit to be here,
separated from my group.
In Survivor, 24 hours,
it can change everything.
However, I really think
there is a reason for everything.
Go on !
And my goal, on Ghost Island,
is to turn the game around
and hopefully
gain an advantage.
Good. So. What do we have here?
"No, not today."
No game for me!
Thin !
I needed an edge!
When I got the message
that I wouldn't play,
let's be honest,
my heart sank a little.
Most...
In times
when I have to be brave,
where I can show my children
that I can do everything on my own...
These are the times
where I take a deep breath
and imbues me with the strength
that is within me.
Because I've been unhappy
in the past.
This is why
I left the Mormon religion
and that I got divorced,
all in six months.
It was there that I discovered
my true inner strength, and that...
I believe in myself no
matter what others do.
That's the real strength in life.
Now, single mother,
I can only rely on myself.
And I want to
channel this inner strength
Cause I'm ready to go back
and kick some ass,
with a clear vision
and a clear mind.
Are we grilling or what?
Yeah !
I would like chocolate.
Good.
But if someone wants us to share,
no problem.
Quick little war cry!
At three ! One two three...
Chris took a great victory
that impressed us all.
That's three straight wins.
Serve yourself !
Chocolate.
They must be collapsed.
Yeah.
Physically, he is an asset.
Moreover, he is
much more willing
to work with us,
the four Malolos.
Have Chris with us
means that now
we decide.
First cup!
Damn it !
My friends !
We have tough guys here!
Mission accomplished.
Let's enjoy this afternoon coffee!
First, the victory enchanted me.
But then this stuff
made me think of home.
It reminded me of
my mother and my grandmother.
Do you want company
or be alone?
Yes, sit down.
Good.
Can I tell you something?
Gladly.
Coffee and all that...
It really reminded me of home.
Reminds me of... home.
In fact,
I take care of my grandmother.
She had two strokes.
And today...
It worries me.
I am sorry.
Sometimes I feel guilty for being here.
Why ?
Because it's more work
for my mother.
Imagine watching this with them.
Yes, I rejoice.
They will be super proud of you.
My grandmother is my life.
She is sick
and my mother is disabled.
So I feel a little guilty
for being here.
I left them.
For my mother, it is heavy.
My family does not want to get
involved and help.
I don't drink coffee,
but since they like it...
It's a bit like home.
You're so sweet.
Don't feel bad about it.
I trust your discretion.
Lord, yes!
It was very tough.
Donathan was a little affected.
I saw the opportunity
to take a step towards him,
because it's probably with him,
of the four Malolos,
with whom I spoke the least.
I know you have a problem.
This is our first
face-to-face moment.
It's hard to be so long
away from my mother and my grandma.
My mother is in a nursing home.
For seven to eight years.
I have to go there
to take care of her.
At 15, I gave him his pills,
took him to the bathroom...
We want
to be a teenager, a young adult.
But at the same time, we have to
sacrifice some things to...
...Caring for those
who cared for you.
I told him about my mother,
thinking it was a good way
to get closer,
to build a real relationship,
real ties.
As a child, I didn't understand
much about it.
It was frustrating and hard.
But as soon as my mom was told
she had two months left,
that day, I was 17 years old,
I decided to become better.
Hear his story
that like me, he had to
take responsibility...
I can
only understand and sympathize.
I lived it.
Sacrificing what you have sacrificed
takes a lot of courage.
For that, I respect you.
Laurel wants to work with Wendell
and Domenick to get Chris out.
I want to support Laurel.
But I got closer to Chris.
I'm a little in the middle,
pulled from all sides.
I have to choose
what is best for me.
This is when I have
to start thinking about Donathan.
Over here, everyone!
And this is Stephanie,
back from Ghost Island.
Health !
Hello family !
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First,
I take back the immunity idol.
And here.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will cross a pontoon bridge,
carrying a bodyboard
tied to a rope.
You will take a bag
and you will hold on.
The others
will operate a giant wheel,
bringing you back to shore.
The 3 bags together, with the numbered discs
they contain,
you will solve a combination,
getting a key
which will release a sliding puzzle.
The first tribe that completes the puzzle
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers:
on the council, someone will be
the fifth person
eliminated from the game.
One minute of organization
and we get started.
Well, on and go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Come on Wendell!
Wendell pour Naviti,
Chelsea pour Malolo.
You have to go for it with this bodyboard
and manage the rope well.
Come on Chelsea!
Great !
You have to go get a bag,
then your tribe will bring you back.
Keep it up, Chelsea, great!
Come on Wendell!
Wendell leads,
but Chelsea is hot on his heels.
Wendell unties his bag.
Yeah, Wendell!
He has it.
And a bit of surfing at the Survivor!
Go on !
Wendell is in the water, ready.
The Navitis begin to spin.
Meet Wendell!
That's how we do it!
Go on !
We push !
We pump!
Wendell is back.
Chelsea has her bag,
she's in the water.
The Malolo begin to turn.
Come on, let's push!
Come on Chelsea!
Wendell
brings back the first Naviti bag.
Go ahead, Naviti!
Come on, Libby!
Go on !
Chelsea is here!
Course !
Come on, Chelsea!
You go-y !
Allez-y, Malolo!
Desiree rushes forward.
Naviti leads.
Come on, Libby!
Slowly and surely!
Take your time, stay straight!
Come on, Lib!
Libby slows down on the bridge.
Come on, Des!
An opportunity for Malolo.
Stay straight!
Come on, Des!
Desiree swallows the deck now!
Go, Libby, go!
Libby lost the lead
that Naviti had taken.
The two women
arrive at the same time.
On and go.
They untie the bags.
The tribes are ready to fire.
Hold on tight, Libby!
Libby is in the water,
she's leading again.
The Naviti bring her back.
Yes ! Yes !
Push hard!
That's good, Des!
Desiree loses her board!
She is under water.
She's on it?
Go on !
Can it hold underwater?
Wow !
Libby is back.
Real Survivor style surfing!
It's neck and neck
in this event.
Go ahead, Wendell!
Come on Wendell!
Wendell leaves for Naviti.
Desiree... Go ahead!
It will be Chelsea again.
Course !
Second round trip
for Wendell and Chelsea.
Both are out of breath.
The balance !
Come on Chelsea!
Yeah, Chelsea!
Come on, Wendell, it's good!
Wendell unties the third bag.
It's fine, don't worry!
Chelsea slows down.
She falls in the water.
An opportunity for Naviti.
Chelsea came back up.
Everything you have!
Wendell is ready,
start shooting him!
Go on !
Push harder!
Great job
from James, Domenick and Laurel!
Go on !
Great !
Wendell brings back the third bag.
Go ahead, Naviti!
They can attack
the combination lock.
Come on, Chelsea!
Chelsea has her bag, she's in the water.
Go on !
Chelsea is in the water,
pulled sideways.
Upside down, she loses the board!
New setback for Malolo.
Come on, Chelsea!
That's good, Chelsea!
James and Domenick
look for the combination.
It's good.
Go on !
Big advance for Naviti.
That's good, Chels, keep going!
Chelsea is back.
Course !
She has time to catch up.
Domenick and James
are still looking for the combination.
They failed to capitalize
on their big lead.
Kellyn and Bradley
try to catch up with them.
Huge effort
from both tribes so far.
Go on !
Domenick and James...
That's good for them!
They can unlock the puzzle.
Guys, it's "Ghost island".
The Naviti have the key,
you have to open the padlock.
They can attack the puzzle.
Well, what...?
36, 27, 18.
Pull out the handle!
Hey, take it out!
Kellyn and Bradley
found the combination.
It would be a hell of a comeback
for Malolo.
Slide the three!
Go on !
After a big setback
on the bodyboard.
[???]
Yes. Yes. Yes.
They can attack the puzzle.
Again there is a tie.
Bradley et Kellyn, James et Domenick,
side by side, for immunity.
At the very end !
Bring back the "N"!
These sliding puzzles are known
to pretend
we're almost there.
Any Survivor fan knows,
a puzzle is not finished
until the last piece is placed.
Yeah, come on!
Bring it back!
Bring them back, calm down!
The "H" is missing!
Bradley and Kellyn don't panic.
It goes all the way!
So !
They progress
slowly and methodically.
Keep it open!
Keep the "O" at the top!
The "A" at the top, to bring the "D" back!
Energy at Naviti.
Its good !
Domenick seems to have the chat.
He barks orders,
but James thinks he knows better.
Yeah yeah !
Raise the "I". Good, good.
Bradley and Kellyn are making progress.
It takes one of the "S".
Keep doing what you're doing!
Bring... Yes, to the "N"!
The Navitis are on full throttle.
They seem close.
So ! Close it!
They think it's good.
It's the case !
Naviti wins immunity!
They send Malolo back to the council.
We did it !
We did the puzzle!
Naviti, once again,
immunity is yours.
Thanks, Jeff.
Naviti, no advice tonight.
No one will leave your tribe.
Take your things, leave.
Kelly's.
We can say
that you are expressive.
We guess your feelings
by looking at you.
You lower your head
from the moment of defeat.
Yes, Jeff. I feel
like I let everyone down.
I wish I had succeeded.
We didn't want to
go back to the board.
But this is Survivor.
And yet, Michael, even if
Naviti assume defeat,
let's be clear:
will it be a Malolo tonight?
Is it Stephanie, Jenna and you
who are threatened?
Yes. There is little hope
for us.
I want us to stay
as strong as possible,
But the reality
is that only two of us
will return from the council.
We're gonna have to
figure out what to do today.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight at the council,
where someone will be the 5th person
eliminated from Survivor Ghost Island.
Having lost this immunity,
I was very disappointed
not to have been able to make the team win.
But unless the ex-Malolo
pull a trick out of their hat,
as in the last advice,
it's Stephanie, Michael or Jenna
who will leave.
I hate losing.
Me too.
It will be worse each time.
Yes.
To have lost that immunity
is overwhelming.
I am cornered.
I am one of the three
who are at risk of leaving.
So I think it's accepted
that it's every man for himself.
I don't want to
see Steph or Jenna leave,
but I'm ready
to vote for one of them tonight.
I was thinking of Jenna.
I would like to separate the two girls.
For me,
Jenna is one of the weakest here.
Whatever you decide, I will follow,
but it would be my choice.
The argument is good.
Going to counseling is going to be...
Depressing.
There is no doubt
that the five control the game.
They won't budge,
they're playing it safe.
So the game is 100% individual
at this stage.
I think
about the best strategy for me.
In this game,
you have to be sympathetic, appreciated.
I do my best, but...
Alas, I still have this absent,
almost angry look.
I find it difficult to leave
this defensive and aggressive air.
I am like this.
Does your hair still smell good?
Very vaguely.
Feel that!
A dead weasel!
I want to try
to sympathize with Sebastian.
I'll put my little wall aside
and hope
that Sebastian will protect me.
I make you braids?
You said you didn't know.
I never said that.
I do sick braids.
Bullshit!
You will see.
Jenna is in danger.
And I need a braider.
Otherwise,
I will only have a giant braid
instead of a small one.
So, as long as she's flirting
with me...
... It's cool, and I want
her to stay in the game.
What worries me more
about Stephanie than about Jenna,
is that Stephanie
is super strategic.
She's in the game.
Jenna, not really.
I agree.
But... As you feel it.
For me, it must be Steph.
Everyone changed their mind.
They think we should vote out Stephanie.
I don't know what to think about it...
Most...
If everyone
wants Stephanie, I am.
I know I'm a little freaked out,
but...
If you keep me, use me!
I know how to count, I know where I am.
No, I appreciate it, but...
If you...
I will see.
... do something...
But really. Because I would
really like to work with you. So...
I won't attack you
on the board, I promise!
Sorry !
It's someone else's turn.
With Bradley, I have to cook,
smile and blink,
because getting to the end
is all that matters to me.
I have two dependent children.
I imagine receiving the million
at the Reunion
and run to join my children,
then scream because mom
just won Survivor.
It makes me hallucinate
to think of this moment,
because I'm only 25 days away,
and I'm so close,
and I want it so badly, for all of us...
I have to keep my head in the game.
For me...Michael.
You can't trust him at all.
No, he's smart.
Nor to Stephanie.
But Jenna is harmless
and will do as Sebastian says.
So go for Michael.
Me too.
Yes, finally, we...
I am defenseless tonight.
You want me out, I'm out.
If you want to keep me...
...which would make more sense...
We can't keep losing.
True.
Even if you just keep me
for the trials...
If I haven't proven my loyalty,
get me out!
But I will prove it.
And win races.
So it's...
Winner winner.
I think so.
Yeah.
You understand, I have the impression
to have to sell myself.
Yes, I follow you.
Because I promise, my loyalty is yours.
I do my best to cut
corners, especially with Bradley,
but you never really know
what people think.
I may not have a chance.
I gave the best of myself.
I'm playing the game I've been waiting
to play for 10 years.
If I didn't give my all,
I would never forgive myself.
I'm only 18.
This game is the best experience
of my life so far.
And the fact that my options
seem limited,
it's hard, it's frustrating.
I have always been independent.
Someone
who wanted more for himself.
Getting away from my family
at a young age
to come and play this crazy game,
for me, it's...
I want to accomplish things
as young as possible and...
I really want it.
We have a few minutes,
we have to decide quickly.
It's who we want.
Voting Stephanie is the riskiest.
She may have brought something back
from Ghost Island.
So who, Michael?
I don't know what happened
to Stephanie on Ghost Island.
and so what she might have.
There is nothing here.
But I'm starting to think to myself
that nothing happened to him,
because I searched his bag
and there was nothing.
I don't know where she could have put it,
but she might have an advantage.
I am not sure.
Nothing.
Safe ?
Yeah.
As council approaches tonight,
a hundred different variables
go through your head.
It is therefore necessary to assess
who is the most trustworthy,
who is the most dangerous,
and which poses the least threat to
my own game.
But fortunately, we have the majority.
We have control and we lead the dance.
Kellyn. When we left the test,
it seemed clear that it was
Stephanie, Jenna or Michael
who would leave tonight.
Does it still feel?
Yes, the afternoon was busy.
Say we all agreed
all day on who to hang out with
would be lying.
To me,
that's the beauty of Survivor.
And it is also very painful
for the person who is going to leave.
Because a single sentence
said by one of us
it pu enough to change
collective opinion.
And that will make all the difference
tonight.
I look at the three faces
that hear that.
Stephanie. A sentence,
a comment,
can make the difference.
We feel a little helpless.
I was on Ghost Island.
It scares me: what did I miss
during my absence?
A lot can happen overnight,
when you're away from your tribe.
Bradley. Were there concerns
that Stephanie's stay on the island
could affect
this vote?
Sure. It would be silly
not to worry.
Has she played the game?
Didn't she play it?
I do not know.
But we have to approach this vote
as if she had an advantage.
So is it helping you, Stephanie,
or is it hurting you,
this potential benefit?
It can have both results,
depending on the nature of the advantage,
if I play it. Lots of "ifs".
Sebastian. What is particularly hard,
in Survivor,
we don't know
what the truth is
before it is finally revealed.
Yes, we cannot be sure of anything.
We learned that at the last council.
But that's pretty simple, Jeff.
We need to take out the three
who aren't our allies.
Can I intervene?
Yes.
I think when the merger comes,
you have to have the majority
For that, we must
win the next events.
I'm your best card
to earn them
and achieve majority merger.
Kellyn. What Michael points out,
it seems to me,
is that if you only want
to win the five against three,
it is done.
But if you want to go all the way
and keep coming out of the strong,
is this the trick to play
for a clever quintet?
It seems that we are
on a bad slope,
in terms of tests,
but there are so many ways
to consider
what is strength in this game...
Bradley. Kellyn says the force
has many faces.
Michael clearly showed
strategic skills
at the last council.
That must have alarmed you a bit.
Absolutely.
Coming to the last tip,
I didn't think I was in danger.
And for a moment,
I thought I was leaving.
So that's a valid argument.
to say that after what he did
to this council, especially to me,
I would like above all to eliminate it,
immediately.
Listen. My alliance with Jenna,
Steph and Brendan was real
and I did my best,
using my idol,
lying a little along the way,
to get my wedding ring
where we needed to go.
Now I have to change,
but I intend to show you
the same respect I showed
my original allies.
Stephanie.
If it's one of you three,
what is the meaning
of this journey in Survivor?
Why do you have to stay?
I want to be here because...
It's my dream, and I...
... Wanted to experience this
for so many years.
And every time
I come to the council,
either quite often,
which is frustrating,
it's harder, because I'm
on the brink of seeing it disappear.
And I want to keep having
opportunities to grow in this game,
personally,
and live all the experiences
that I've watched
all these years.
And if this is the end,
what will remain unfulfilled?
This question touches me
deeply because...
For me, I...
I play for my children, and...
It's my game, my moment,
but they're so close to my heart...
They're the only ones I'm afraid
of disappointing in life.
I am not ready to leave.
I truly believe
that some of the bonds I've made,
with Malolo and Naviti,
are very real.
The game is still long and I still have a
lot of game in me.
Jenna. And for you ?
What drew you
to Survivor?
Me, I always had this barrier,
that face that says, "I don't want to
be approached, to be vulnerable."
I open little.
When I know
they're going to have to eliminate me,
I always have that in mind.
It's hard, because I want to make
ties, I do my best.
I have work to do, this game will push me
to come out of my shell more.
For the rest, I hope not to
be in the category
what they want to
eliminate tonight.
Sebastian.
If we forget purple and orange
and we just listen to Jenna talk,
she is here to improve
on the social plan,
and she chooses the social game
hardest ever invented
to do it!
That must make it a bit difficult
to write his name.
Sure.
It kills me to write any name
in this game, it sucks.
I realize his experience,
I understand very well.
But there are
multiple angles for everything.
Michael.
What does Survivor mean to you?
I've been a fan all my life.
I've been following the show
since I was 13.
Coming, everyone imagines
their perfect game, sees themselves at the end.
It's very hard for my game not to
run as expected.
But I think I was able to show
that I am authentic.
I play my best.
I strive to be loyal to everyone
and to go far.
Desiree.
Was there a clear objective,
among the five Naviti,
on whom to eliminate, and why?
Clearly. There's always a good
reason to eliminate someone.
Just find it.
And I think tonight
we found the reason
to take out one of the three.
A good reason.
The future will show it.
Good. It's time to vote.
Chelsea, over.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Steph.
Two votes Stephanie.
Stephanie.
Three votes Stephanie.
Four Stephanie votes,
one Desiree vote.
Fifth person eliminated
from Survivor:
Stephanie. Five is enough.
Bring me your torch.
Stephanie, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Goodbye !
The five Naviti continue
to win as an alliance
and to lose as a tribe.
Something has to change.
Take your torches,
return to your camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
The demarcations are established.
Domenick and Chris
each want to kill the other.
The targets are clear.
I'm afraid I'll be next.
But a bomb explodes.
Throw away your bandanas!
A brand new start
in Survivor Ghost Island.
Why, Jeff? Why do that ?
I waited 36 seasons
to be able to play.
Leaving fifth,
without having the full experience,
it breaks my heart.
But I played my best.
I played hard and...
I still believe in myself.
At the end of the day, I go back
to the family that I know.
They will be proud of me.