Previously on Survivor...
There was a twist.
There will be two separate councils.
Oh my God !
And the ghosts
of past mistakes resurface
when Donathan played his idol.
Sorry, Jenna, I'm playing it for me.
But it was useless.
Jenna, the tribe has spoken.
Kellyn cast her
extra vote against Laurel.
But it was Michael
who joined the jury.
Michael, the tribe has spoken.
There are eight left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What happened ?
It was disturbing.
Six votes cast
in a five-man board.
Who had one more?
Not me !
Nor me.
It must be Kellyn!
Yeah. It was me.
Did you vote against me twice?
I did not understand.
Alright, I sit down.
I had one more vote, and tonight,
I thought there would be
one vote for me, one for Laurel,
that the three guys
would be quiet,
so I cast my two votes
against Laurel.
And I understand that
she is very hurt.
I passed
very close to the exit this evening.
And that Kellyn put
not one, but two votes on me
shows that it's every man for himself.
I have to adopt the same attitude.
Fortunately, Wendell and Dom have stuck with
me.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today you will have to
collect a bag of sand,
then overcome obstacles
until the finish,
where you should place the bag
on a very small table.
The first to finish
wins the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Yes !
The winner
will go to a very beautiful place
where he will taste ribs,
chicken, burgers,
pastries and ice cream
for dessert.
Is it worth it ?
Yes !
Do you know what the one thing
would make it even better?
It would be to share it
not only
with those you play against,
but to be able to share it
with those for whom you play.
I speak of love!
Wendell, what does it do?
Why is love so important
right now, in this game?
These are the people
we think about,
who we play for.
And I know...
I know that my father is not far away!
So, shall we start with you?
Well,
let's welcome Wendell's father!
Wendell, come here!
I'm proud of you.
You can do it, you know it.
You are my son.
Thank you dad.
Wendell. You are that tough guy
participating in a tough game.
But seeing your father,
you become the son.
This guy is everything to me.
He's... He's me!
It's the original Wendell, the senior.
Look at it, you will see me.
Look !
It's Wendell Senior,
the guy I told you about!
I told you !
He worked so hard.
All the things
I built on the camp,
he taught me how to do it
in my childhood.
He is everything for me.
Wendell senior.
Where does this pride come from?
He's saying
you're his hero!
He is ours.
He accomplished so much more
in every way,
than one could have imagined.
We are very proud of him.
Well, give him one last hug.
[???]
I love you.
It's him, it's my rock.
Kellyn, ready for some love?
This is your big brother, Clay!
Come here, Clay!
Oh, damn it!
You can do it ! You can do it !
We're in Survivor!
A big part of building
our relationship as adults...
We're opposites
on so many levels
except one or two things
we agree on,
Watching the show every week
cemented
rebuilding our relationship
in recent years.
Thanks to the Survivor family
for what they did for ours!
One last hug!
It's so good to see you!
Donathan.
Let's welcome your Aunt Patty.
Come, Patty!
She is cabbage!
I'm so glad
you came!
You're okay ?
Good.
Donathan. I've never seen you
so vulnerable,
and I saw you being.
What is the explanation?
What's going on for you?
It means everything to me.
I love being on the show,
but having this family contact,
it's something
I will never forget.
How are mom and grandma doing?
Perfectly.
Perfectly. Everything is fine, I promise.
Are you worried
about your family?
Clearly. They depend on me.
Come here, leave them alone,
it was risky, so hearing that
takes a big weight off me.
They are doing very well.
And she sends you lots of love.
She gave me this for you.
Oh thank you !
Alright, one last hug!
I love you !
I love you, Patty!
You will win !
Ready for a little love?
Yes !
Let's welcome your daughter, Paige.
Come on, Paige!
I'm proud of you !
Paige, tell me about your relationship.
Our norm is to be separated.
She served 21 years in the army, so...
We are used to being apart.
Manage it, manage
to put our emotions aside
and do what is necessary
to improve our lot
and brighten our future.
Angela, your daughter said
a very interesting thing.
You served in our army.
And in consequence,
you have sacrificed
your own family.
How do you feel
when your daughter says that?
Is it painful
or is it part of the bond?
A little...
A bit of both.
Because...
While being very proud,
I also suffer
from leaving my family behind.
Sometimes it feels like they've been
abandoned.
But then when you see
the amazing young adult that...
Everything she's become...
It's my family,
the real heroine
of all that, of my story.
Thank you, little sister!
One last hug!
I love you !
Chelsea! Ready for a little love?
This is your sister, Sydney. Come !
I told
you you would bring your butt here!
I miss you so much !
Sydney, you weren't here,
but you see your big sister
which is clearly vulnerable.
Yes. I am very proud of her.
She has always been very ambitious.
I try to be solid and strong
for her
when she's in trouble,
to give her love, and she...
everyone loves him.
And everyone is fine.
She may be
the most supportive little sister
never seen in Survivor!
Is not it !
One last hug!
I love you, my darling!
Me too !
Laurel, ready?
Yes !
Let's welcome your brother Franck!
Big brother !
It's really difficult !
Laurel, is this
the expected big brother welcome?
Is he your rock?
He is my rock.
He helps me through
the hard times,
because it is always strong
and resistant and...
It's very hard not to have him here,
because here you find people
you think you can trust,
but I can trust him 100%.
To have someone here who you know
is telling you the truth,
and vice versa, it's priceless.
One last hug!
Come on, come on!
You will win ! Go on !
You also have a little sister!
Welcome Grace!
I'm proud of you !
I miss you so much !
You are too pretty !
Between brother and sister, in general,
during childhood,
we are dog and cat.
And yet, when we come here,
it all flies away.
How does it feel
to kiss your little sister?
She is more than my little sister,
she is my twin.
Not for real, but check it out!
We are the same person!
It's my best friend,
the only one I like to talk
to at any time of the day.
If I had to choose one person
to spend the rest of my life with,
that would be Grace.
Honey, it's her.
One last hug!
I love you, sis!
More than one person. Domenick.
Your woman. The only relative
without blood ties.
You chose this woman
to build a family.
Kristin, over here!
I love you and hate you so much!
Can I see your face,
please?
Domenick.
Tell me about this relationship.
This woman, for giving up
what she gave up
so that I can
come here to experience this...
... crazy adventure,
something I've
been a fan of for ages...
What more can you ask of
a woman?
She is my life, my rock.
It's so painful.
I suffer so much,
I don't even recognize myself anymore.
Where does suffering come from?
Live without him,
without talking to him every day.
I hadn't gone a day
without talking to him in 20 years.
We're glad you're here.
Yes.
Thanks.
One last hug.
Now the stakes are known.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Well, on and go.
For a reward
in the form of love.
Survivors, ready?
Wendell quickly comes out of the water.
Sebastian on his heels.
Wendell passes. Sebastian too.
Come on, Chelsea!
Kellyn passes.
Come on, Donathan, good!
Donathan and Angela,
always at the start.
Domenick, it's good!
Everyone else
is on their sandbags.
You have to undo all the knots.
Donathan...
Oh, big drop! Its good !
Laurel has her bag, she's gone.
Chelsea has hers, she passed.
Chels, my baby! Go on !
Laurel and Chelsea are digging.
It's good for Sebastian.
Come on Sebastian!
Angela waddles forward.
Give it your all, Angela!
Good, mom!
Go ahead, you can do it!
Kelly's a son sac de sable.
Wendell a le sien.
Go, mom, go!
Go on !
Angela passed.
Domenick, Angela and Donathan
are on their sandbags.
Everyone else digs.
Keep on going ! Dig !
Bien, Kellyn, bien !
Everyone can win.
It remains to place the sandbag
on a very small table.
Domenick has his bag, he's gone.
Come on, Dom, come on!
This is Donathan.
He passed.
Angela is on her sandbag,
she is last.
Laurel will try to go
through a very small hole.
A little more, come on!
Not skinny enough!
You have to dig under this trunk.
Come on Sebastian!
Sebastian gives it a shot.
He passed!
He can start tossing his bag.
He has a good lead,
he can take his time.
Dig, mom, dig!
Angela digs now.
Chelsea tries to pass.
Everyone fights for love!
Sebastian can win now.
Still too short.
You are still in the game!
You go-y, you and it is!
Good, Donathan!
Donathan tries to slip out.
Domenick tries. As well as Wendell.
Everything remains open.
Go on !
Sebastian throws, for the win.
No, it falls!
Domenick has passed,
he can take his sandbag.
My God !
Domenick has a chance.
Domenick... It's falling!
Go on !
Come on, there you are!
Sebastian... It's falling again.
This is Domenick.
Oh, just not!
Sebastian succeeds!
Sebastian wins love!
Yeah !
Wow !
Well done, sea bass!
Everyone fought for it.
Sebastian.
We know how important it is.
We just talked about it.
And you know how it works.
Choose a person and their loved one
to accompany you.
He loves family life so much.
I have to choose Dom. Come !
Come, Kristin!
Alright, Sebastian,
pick another player .
and his relative to accompany you.
I promised Wendell.
It must be Wendell.
Wendell, come here!
Wendell senior, join us!
Good Sebastian.
Choose one last person
and their loved one to join you.
Donathan, come on, buddy!
Sorry, girls.
You deserve it, buddy!
Bien. Kelly's, Laurel,
Chelsea, Angela,
no more love for you.
Loved ones, it's time to go.
Good. One more decision to make.
Sebastian, you decide
who goes to Ghost Island.
And today there is a surprise.
Car awaits you on Ghost Island
an advantage in the game.
All you have
to do is land on Ghost Island
and the advantage is yours.
You can choose yourself.
You're the boss.
In this case, your sister would leave
and you would go to the Ghost Island.
If you offer it
to one of the other three,
his relative will leave.
But if you don't choose
one of you four,
power passes to these four,
who will decide.
Anyway,
I'm not going to Ghost Island.
But I offer it to you.
If you want to go there, you can.
Say it to me.
I will go.
Wendell, you give up
to a potentially unique afternoon
in exchange for an advantage in the game.
Good. Say goodbye to your father.
Make them drool!
Yes.
One of us could have gone.
Wendell senior, it's time.
Wendell, take your things
and on the way, the boat is waiting for you.
Take care of yourself !
Well, Sebastian, Domenick, Donathan
and your loved ones,
a beautiful afternoon awaits you.
On the way, enjoy!
Kellyn, Laurel, Chelsea, Angela,
nothing for you.
Take your things, leave.
These guys are so full of themselves
that they didn't even bother
to leave the four of us alone.
Get to work, girls!
Jeff said, "Go to Ghost Island
and you're guaranteed an advantage."
Although it was great
to be with my dad,
the best man in the world,
my mentor, my everything,
we agreed. He said,
"Go ahead and earn that money!
You have to go
all out and give it your all!"
And in my place, he would have done the same.
"Congratulation !
You have earned
the same “second chance” benefit,
for the same ordeal,
as Malcolm in season 25,
If you drop the ball,
you are not eliminated.
You will replace the marble
and start over."
Malcolm lost on the bill.
He is not eliminated,
he has a second chance.
"But he lost the ball...
twice."
And suddenly, Malcolm is eliminated.
"He lost the event
and was eliminated that night."
The tribe has spoken.
"He never reached
the final square again.
This tainted perk
has been living on Ghost Island for six years.
Only question: can you
reverse the curse?
At the next immunity,
I will have a second attempt
if the ball falls, like Malcolm.
Such an advantage, in this game,
at this stage,
we don't do better.
The end is in sight, we all know that.
It means to
seize, to catch, to grab
any advantage that can be found.
I have to be in the final.
And this brings me closer.
Dom, ready to eat?
God's goodness !
I am blessed to have my wife here.
But despite my desire
to be with her,
this is an opportunity
to talk to people
and say,
"This is our chance to unite!"
We're holding something here.
And with friend Wendell
working for us on Ghost Island,
we work well together.
And I tell you, Aunt Patty,
I will go to the end with them. Really.
I take you at your word!
It is said !
I am a country girl!
I know it !
Domenick and Sebastian
were drawing their plans,
now that we're together.
But they are the most dangerous.
And I don't know
if good old Donathan
can take on and defeat
these tough guys.
At the last tip,
I wasted my idol.
Now
I have to be more aggressive.
I must eliminate one of these targets.
Let's have a girls meal.
Shit, we can do whatever we want
without them
to give us orders!
The three guys got together
and left for the reward
or seek benefits
on Ghost Island,
and left us here
to do the dishes.
And guess what he's doing here?
He laughs at you
because he gets a new advantage.
He doesn't care if he
deprives someone of his family.
And it pisses me off!
Everything works for them.
They win immunity,
maybe have idols,
see their loved ones...
Wendell goes to Ghost Island,
assured that everything will be fine for him.
We can blame them, be sad
not to see our loved ones,
or seize the opportunity
to take full control of the game.
But their plan for the day has a flaw.
They left us here.
How many ?
Four. A majority.
If we can rally Donathan...
Yeah.
It's OK for me.
Who goes out first, then?
I would say: separate Dom and Wendell.
For us, there,
it's quits or double.
This is the only opportunity
to take the majority from them.
Dom and Wendell are in charge.
The four girls plus Donathan,
we can unite and break this duo.
We'll make you smile.
Take care, guys.
You will be entitled to it.
It will only work
if they don't suspect a thing.
They don't even have to consider it.
But targeting Wendell first
worries me,
because I think he potentially has
more tricks up his sleeve.
So, we leave Dom.
Yeah.
This is the shot to play.
Kellyn would want my trust after
targeting me at the last tip.
But it is of interest.
We can be mutually
useful to each other.
You can start
playing to win.
I agree. I agree.
The problem is that I know
that Domenick and Wendell
each have an idol.
So it's scary, but finding
another option is tempting.
I can join the girls
and target one of the guys.
Hoping
to avoid a backlash.
Over here, everyone!
And this is Wendell,
back from Ghost Island.
Hi.
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all,
I take back the necklaces.
Both.
Thanks, Dom.
Thank you, Chelsea.
Once again,
individual immunity is at stake.
Today,
using two handles,
you will balance a marble
on a wooden cylinder.
Regularly we will add
sections to the cylinder,
increasing the difficulty.
If you drop the ball,
it's lost.
Last to stand wins immunity,
makes sure to have a one in seven chance
of going to the end.
The Losers: On the council, someone
will become the sixth member of the jury.
Wendell, read us your advantage.
Yes, I have an advantage.
"If you knock the ball down,
you're not out.
You will replace the marble
and start over."
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Let's go. Grab your handles!
I'm doing the count,
the cylinder should be in the air.
Three...
... of them...
... and...
Everyone looks good
with their first section.
The test is on.
Three cylinder sections
that you are trying to hold
between two handles.
In the center, a small ball,
who wants to move,
one way or the other.
Domenick moves a little
but recovers well.
Things are moving a bit at Wendell.
It can move anywhere,
as long as it doesn't fall.
It will depend on your balance
and the pressure exerted
on the handles.
Kellyn loses his marble.
No immunity for her.
Go to the bench.
Kellyn is the first eliminated.
You are only seven.
We will stay ten minutes
on this section,
then we will continue,
and it will become
much more interesting.
ELAPSED TIME: 10 Minutes
Alright, next round!
Pose and relax.
Let's add a section
to your cylinder.
I count again.
You must have raised before zero.
Let's go.
Three...
... of them...
... and...
Lift up, Angela!
Angela couldn't lift in time.
Angela is eliminated.
Wendell loses his ball.
He has a second chance.
Everyone rest!
Everyone is quiet.
We start the round again.
Wendell uses his advantage,
takes his second chance.
Let's go. I count.
Three...
... of them...
... a... You have to lift!
Everyone is good, here we go again.
You are only six.
Wendell used his advantage.
But will it help him?
Things are already moving a little at Wendell.
But he recovers.
It is necessary to make sure
to exert equivalent pressures,
not to overtighten the cylinder,
or it will collapse.
Wendell loses his ball,
he is eliminated.
The curse is maintained,
the advantage did not help him.
Wendell is vulnerable on the board.
He sits on the bench.
ELAPSED TIME: 20 Minutes
Alright, round over.
Relax.
We go to the last round.
Good boy !
Replace your items.
Take back your handles.
Prepare yourself mentally.
On and go.
Three...
... of them...
... and...
The last round
of this event is launched.
We will only stop
when there is a winner.
Things are moving at Laurel. Well recovered.
If you're shaking,
you have to quickly regain control.
Big movement at Domenick,
but he recovers.
You jump a little,
squeeze too hard,
have the slightest contraction,
and it's done.
And suddenly, Sebastian loses his ball!
You are only four.
You can't get away
from this ordeal.
And the room for maneuver is small.
Laurel loses her marble,
she is eliminated.
You are only three.
It's accelerating.
Domenick, right next to Chelsea,
and at the very end, Donathan.
Stability, focus.
Stay in control at all times.
Domenick continues
to analyze the position of his hands.
Donathan
begins to shake a little.
Suddenly, Chelsea loses her ball.
His streak of immunity victories comes to an
end.
And it's face-to-face.
Domenick versus Donathan.
Domenick
begins to shake a little.
He's shaking more.
Donathan keep shaking
but continues
to stand the test.
Keep on fighting!
Donathan can't do it anymore!
Domenick wins
his second individual immunity!
Safe at tonight's council.
A guaranteed place
in the last seven.
That was a battle!
Domenick, come here!
Once again,
immunity is yours.
Safe on the board again,
you can't be knocked out.
Unfortunately for you,
after 32 very difficult days,
someone will become
the sixth member of the jury.
Take your things, leave.
Congratulation !
Naviti's happy family
is really over.
The Naviti girls
will attack the Naviti boys.
And Laurel and Donathan
are the most popular articles on Lavita.
Everyone needs
their votes. The game is started.
It's up to Laurel and Donathan to play.
Well done, Dom.
Cheer !
I was shaking.
Cheer.
Well done, sir!
I did not win immunity.
And not having
made fruitful the advantage,
I gave up seeing my father
for nothing.
But I trust my alliance.
We should be
able to take out whoever we want.
At the reward, yesterday,
it was Donathan, Sea Wolf and me.
I said, "We should work together,
and our friend Wendell
is on Ghost Island,
working for us."
So, the four of us plus Laurel,
we can do business.
What do you want to do ?
Let's eliminate Chelsea.
So that'll be five...
Five on Chelsea.
We act as if the Naviti
remained united,
but in reality, tonight,
we're going out Chelsea,
because it is important to remove
the people who dominate the tests
so that they don't worry us
afterwards.
Let's keep moving forward.
So what's the plan?
They form a block, let's separate them.
So, are we targeting Wendell?
I will follow your choice,
but I would prefer Wendell.
See Dom win immunity
comforted me in the idea
that the three boys
have too much power.
If I can pull this off with the girls
and get Wendell out,
this will be my sweetest victory
in Survivor so far.
We all know what to do:
play "welded Naviti".
I walk. Unless you tell me
something's changed,
I will follow the plan.
I'm 100%.
We can rally Donathan.
Donathan would follow us, do you think?
Yeah.
This is our plan.
We spoke to Laurel yesterday.
Hey, hi, Chelsea,
Kelly's...
...and Laurel.
Tonight,
the boys are not suspicious.
This is our chance. I mean...
Of course, you do
what you want tonight,
but I hope...
I'm in for Wendell.
Wendell is excellent
in the trials.
And he's smart.
For me, it is the most dangerous
at this stage.
We think our only chance
is to do it now.
It involves trapping him.
We must not alarm them.
It will happen.
It's gonna be fucking epic!
So tonight: Chelsea.
Yeah.
And then we will have the majority.
We'll take them out one by one.
Sebastian is in?
He told me.
As long as Don-Don is with us...
He is.
No worries.
He follows us.
I trust Laurel a lot,
and I need her tonight.
But I don't get
the usual good vibes from her.
So, I have the idol in my pocket,
unpacked, ready to go.
At the slightest glance,
I draw it and I shoot.
If we follow them and take out Chelsea,
we will have the opportunity, at the next move,
to attack Dom or Wendell.
They are the most serious
candidates for victory.
For me, tonight is an opportunity
to target one.
My worst regret would be not
having done it when it was possible.
It's a hell of a decision.
Laurel and I, we are well placed,
in the center of everything,
There's Wendell and Dom,
with Sebastian,
and the three Naviti daughters,
pulling us here and there,
Laurel and me.
I don't know how it's gonna turn
out tonight,
but I'm afraid that my choice
could turn against me.
I'm afraid we're out
of strategy, after that,
if Dom and Wendell
keep crushing everyone.
Want to follow them?
I do not know. I want
to play it all out.
Here, I don't know what to do.
On the one hand, I have the guys,
who I think I can trust,
but which I doubt I can beat.
On the other, the girls, whom I think I
can beat in the final.
But can I trust them
to get me there?
Plus, I know Domenick and Wendell
protected by a ton of idols.
This is probably the last opportunity
to target one of them
without them expecting it.
Donathan and I
both control this board,
and the direction of the rest of the game.
This decision is essential.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Michael,
eliminated at the last council.
Kellyn, after the last advice,
on the way back to camp,
are there any fallouts?
What's the vibe?
After this big double board
where two people left,
some were injured.
I put two votes on Laurel.
She didn't expect it.
So that kind of weighed down the mood a bit , I think.
Donathan.
Do you always feel
that Naviti still has the majority?
Laurel and I are at
the bottom again,
but there is a commotion
among the Naviti,
and she and I
realize that, so...
So there might be
an opening
among the six Naviti.
There's one tonight.
This assertion
has brought all Naviti
to squint at each other.
I see it, and I'm one of them!
To see how everyone
looks at each other,
I worry
about what will happen tonight.
Well, I do not know.
I'm shaken here.
Kellyn.
You too seem concerned.
What do you feel ?
Do you believe what he said?
uh well...
A bombshell of truth
came from that corner
to every advice
I made with him,
so my heart is racing.
Laurel. Donathan included you
in this discussion on:
"Oh yes, there is an opening!"
There is an opening, a fault,
and we have found the way.
We therefore hope to be
able to cash this check this evening.
Let's go !
Chelsea.
You also look around.
Yes. At the two previous councils,
I had a necklace around my neck.
There, I am more vulnerable.
So if I hear somebody say
there might be a rift
I'm trying to figure out
what exactly is going on,
if anything has changed.
I will be clear.
These girls approached me.
And these guys approached me.
This is the flaw.
Domenick. It was categorical.
But I would like to mention
one thing that we forget:
yesterday, during the
family reward,
these four women spent
an afternoon together.
And if these three
can speak to her, to her,
and that she is with him...
What's going on here
is a very confusing mess.
And this necklace
is very pleasant to me, there.
Wendell. Do you wonder
if Donathan
is just showing off?
I don't really know what he's talking about,
but we come to know
that Donathan hardly holds his tongue
and that he is ready to drop bombs
on the board.
We will have to live with it
and do what we have to do.
Kellyn. It would be unrealistic
not to imagine that everyone here
did not consider:
"What if I changed things?
What would it be?"
No?
Yes. It boils down
to a fairly small group
to be able to discuss by considering
each person, each test,
so all brains
must be on high alert,
and the visit of the families
deviated me a little from the path.
I was thinking of coming to play Survivor
thinking, "I'm home."
Then to see something
that really comes from home,
it's a huge...
An upheaval.
We all consider scenarios
with different people.
Chelsea. Are we at a stage in the game
where it's actually
to wait and see
who will switch sides first?
Yes. It's like
a giant bumper car track.
And you don't know who's loyal to you
and will get out of your way
and who's going to run into you.
Domenick. It's a great picture.
Do you have this feeling
that anything is possible tonight?
It's exactly that.
People act not only
to make sure to go further,
but can also consider a shot
which would enrich their CV.
So will I wait
for someone to come after me
or shoot first '
cause I don't wanna sit there
when I could have avoided
it at the right time?
Donathan. What are the odds
of a surprise elimination tonight?
If it turns out the way I believe
then there might be one.
Well, it's time to vote.
Angela, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Wendell.
Two votes Wendell.
Chelsea. Equality.
Two Wendell votes,
two Chelsea votes.
Wendell.
Three votes Wendell.
New equality.
Three Wendell votes,
three votes Chelsea,
two votes left.
Chelsea.
Merde.
Four Chelsea votes,
three Wendell votes.
One vote remains.
Thirteenth person eliminated
and sixth member of the jury:
Chelsea.
Bring me your torch.
Nice battle, sir.
Nice game, ma'am.
Chelsea, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
This advice answered the question:
there is indeed a fault.
The new question is:
what now?
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
When you're caught
in the bag...
What ?
I have to play it all out.
... the consequences
can be terrible.
We can target Domenick.
If Donathan wants to blow it all up,
maybe that's my ray of hope.
What is he going to do ?
He got out of control!
As a fan,
I'm super grateful.
I actually have no regrets
for this advice.
I wanted to make a big hit tonight
and I'm proud to have tried it.
Even though it didn't work out
in my favour,
I'll be gone with a bang
and fighting.