I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
Jeff: THIS IS NOT A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
Kris:
I HAD THE TWO IDOLS.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE PLAYED
THEM.
Jeff: FOR 35 SEASON,
"SURVIVOR" HAS CHALLENGED
PLAYERS WITH A GAME SO
COMPLICATED THAT WINNING
REQUIRES NEARLY PERFECT
EXECUTION.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT MAKING
FRIENDS.
I NEED THAT ADVANTAGE.
IT WORKED.
Jeff: ONE BAD DECISION CAN
HAUNT YOU FOREVER.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
THESE 20 AMERICANS WILL FACE THE
SAME CHALLENGE AS THEY BEGIN
AN ADVENTURE THAT WILL FOREVER
CHANGE THEIR LIVES.
THEY WILL BE ABANDONED ON THE
ISLANDS OF FIJI AND LEFT TO FEND
FOR THEMSELVES, BUT THIS SEASON
THERE'S A TWIST.
GHOST ISLAND, THE GAVE YARD FOR
BAD "SURVIVOR" DECISIONS.
AND AFTER 35 SEASON, THERE HAVE
BEEN A LOT OF THEM.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER WE'RE
BRINGING BACK THE ACTUAL IDOLS
AND ADVANTAGES THAT WERE FATALLY
MISPLAYED IN PREVIOUS SEASONS.
OH, MY GOD.
NOT THE IDOL.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
Jeff: THIS GROUP OF NEW
PLAYERS MUST FIND A WAY TO
REVERSE THE CURSE OF THESE
HAUNTED "SURVIVOR" RELICS OR
THEY WILL FACE THE SAME FATE.
IN THE END ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
THE CLAIM THE MILLION DOLLAR
PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR!
♪
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO THIS.
"SURVIVOR" IS ONE OF THE
GREATEST SOCIAL EXPERIMENTS EVER
CREATED.
IT REQUIRES DOZENS OF CRITICAL
DECISIONS EVERY DAY.
IT IS A GAME SO FRAUGHT WITH
PERIL THAT ONE BAD DECISION CAN
HAUNT YOU FOREVER.
WELCOME TO OUR 36th SEASON,
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND."
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
THIS SEASON, FOR THE FIRST TIME
EVER, YOU WILL HAVE THE CHANCE
TO REVERSE THE CURSE OF SOME OF
THE WORST DECISIONS IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
WHAT?
MY PROBABLY BIGGEST FEAR OUT
HERE IS MAKING BAD DECISIONS,
BECAUSE WE'VE SEEN IT SO MANY
TIMES THROUGHOUT "SURVIVOR."
THEY CAN BE SUCH A SPLIT-MOMENT
DECISION THAT CAN TAKE YOU OUT
OF THE GAME.
Jeff: AND IF YOU FIND
YOURSELF ON GHOST ISLAND, WHICH
MANY OF YOU WILL, YOU WILL BE
SURROUNDED BY REMINDERS THAT
EVERYTHING IN THIS GAME RESTS ON
YOUR ABILITY TO MAKE THE RIGHT
DECISION AT THE RIGHT TIME.
AND THAT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
OH.
Jeff: WEARING THE ORANGE
BUFFS, MALOLO, YOU DON'T KNOW
EACH OTHER, BUT YOU'VE GOT TO
MAKE YOUR FIRST BIG DECISION.
SELECT ONE PERSON TO REPRESENT
YOUR TRIBE.
ANY VOLUNTEERS?
Jeff: WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
WE GOT OUR GUY.
Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
BRENDAN.
Jeff: BRENDAN, COME ON OVER
HERE NEXT TO ME.
AS A TEACHER AND A COACH, I'M
RELIED ON FOR A LOT OF THINGS.
I KNOW SOMETHING BIG IS AT AT
STAKE.
IF I WANT TO HELP US, I WILL DO
IT.
Jeff: NAVITI, PICK ONE
PERSON TO LEAD YOUR TRIBE
I'LL DO IT.
Jeff: WOW, THAT DIDN'T TAKE
ANY TIME.
CHRIS, THAT WAS INSTANT.
I GUESS THEY SAW SOME GOOD
QUALITIES IN ME.
I'LL TAKE THE CHALLENGE.
Jeff: YOU GUYS WILL MAKE
YOUR FIRST BIG DECISIONS.
YOU'RE GOING TO DECIDE WHO RUNS
FROM YOUR TRIBE IN AN UNKNOWN
CHALLENGE.
WE'LL START WITH YOU, BRENDAN.
PICK THE PERSON YOU THINK MOST
CAPABLE OF HANDLING THE PHYSICAL
PART OF THE CHALLENGE.
I'M GOING TO TWO WITH BACK
ROW, RIGHT SIDE.
Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
MICHAEL.
Jeff: MICHAEL, COME ON UP.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW CHOOSE SOMEBODY TO HANDLE
THE PUZZLE PART.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH THE
WOMAN IN THE BECOME RIGHT.
Jeff: WHAT'S YOU NAME?
LAUREL.
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT NEXT TO
MICHAEL.
NOW WE GO TO NAVITI.
CHRIS, CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO
HANDLE THE PHYSICAL PORTION.
BACK LEFT.
Jeff: DIDN'T HESITATE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
SEBASTIAN.
Jeff: SEBASTIAN, TAKE A
SPOT RIGHT OVER HERE.
ALL RIGHT, CHRIS, CHOOSE
SOMEBODY TO HANDLE THE PUZZLE
PORTION.
NO.
Jeff: BEFORE YOU DO THIS,
WOMAN IN THE BACK WHO JUST
DUCKED, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
MORGAN.
Jeff: CLEARLY MORGAN YOU
ARE SAYING, NOT ME.
NOT ME.
Jeff: I ALREADY KNOW WHO I
WANTED, SO IT ALL WORKS OUT.
WHO DO YOU WANT?
FRONT LEFT.
Jeff: WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
DESIREE.
Jeff: WHY DID YOU CHOOSE
ME.
MAYBE I LOOK CREATIVE, BUT
PUZZLES ARE NOT MY STRONG SUIT.
Jeff: LET'S GET TO THE
CHALLENGE.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
THE FIRST PERSON WILL RACE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES TO
DIG UP KEYS.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THREE KEY, THE
PUZZLE SOLVER WILL USE THOSE
KEYS TO UNLOCK AND THEN SOLVE
THE PUZZLE.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS.
NOW LET'S GET TO THE STAKES.
FIRST A BIG PICTURE PERSPECTIVE.
THIS IS WHAT IS GOING TO BE
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
NOT MUCH.
WOW.
Jeff: A MACHETE, A POT,
RICE, AND TAKE NOTE, MUCH LESS
RICE THAN ANY PREVIOUS SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
YOU WILL ALSO START WITH A VERY
EXTENSIVE FISHING KIT.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL ALSO GO
BACK TO CAMP WITH SOMETHING
ELSE.
OH.
OH, I NEED THAT.
Jeff: A MASSIVE
SHELTER-BUILDING KIT.
THAT IS A BIG HEAD START.
THE LOSING TRIBE LOSES THEIR
FISHING GEAR.
AND HERE'S THE TWIST THAT MAKES
THIS REALLY FUN.
WHEN THE PUZZLE STARTS, I'M
GOING TO BEGIN A SAND TIMER.
IF AT ANY POINT BEFORE THE SAND
RUNS OUT EITHER ONE OF THE
LEADERS THINKS THEIR PUZZLE
MAKER IS NOT GOING TO WIN, YOU
CAN FORFEIT, AND BY FORFEITING,
YOU KEEP YOUR FISHING GEAR.
THERE IS A PENALTY FOR GIVING UP
ON YOUR TRIBE.
IN ADDITION TO THE
SHELTER-MAKING KIT, THE WINNING
TRIBE WILL START THE GAME WITH
20 EGGS AND A FLINT, WHICH MEANS
THEY WILL BE ABLE TO MAKE FIRE,
BOIL WATER, AND COOK THOSE EGGS
UP.
A LOT AT STAKE.
I HOPE YOU CHOSE THE RIGHT
LEADERS.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
OUR FIRST CHALLENGE, 36th
SEASON, BIG STAKES.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SEBASTIAN.
GO, SEBASTIAN.
Jeff: BOTH GUYS WHIPPING
THROUGH THIS.
DIGGING UP THAT FIRST KEY.
SEBASTIAN HAS IT.
MICHAEL HAS IT.
WE'RE DEAD EVEN OUT OF THE GATE.
ANOTHER HIGH STEP.
BOTH GUYS HAVE THEIR FIRST KEYS
HEADING BACK.
MICHAEL LEAPING THROUGH THAT
HIGH STEP THIS TIME.
SEBASTIAN RIGHT ON HIS TAIL,
LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND KEY.
GO, SEBASTIAN!
Jeff: THIS IS WHAT YOU
DREAMED ABOUT.
MICHAEL HAS IT.
SEBASTIAN HAS HIS.
IT IS ALREADY BRUTALLY HOT OUT
HERE.
WAY TO GO, WAY TO GO, GET IT!
Jeff: MICHAEL STRUGGLING
NOW.
SEBASTIAN HEADING BACK.
THAT ADRENALINE STARTING TO WEAR
OFF.
BOTH GUYS SLOWING DOWN NOW.
SEBASTIAN IN THE LEAD.
MICHAEL STRUGGLING TO STAY UP.
SEBASTIAN DIGGING.
LOOKING FOR THAT THIRD KEY.
HE'S GOT IT.
HUSTLE, HUSTLE, HUSTLE!
Jeff: MICHAEL IS LOOKING
FOR HIS.
MICHAEL HAS HIS THIRD KEY.
KEEP IT MOVING.
GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: THAT FIGHT OR FLIGHT
SURGE IS GONE.
THIS IS PURE WILLPOWER.
MICHAEL REALLY HAVING TROUBLE.
GREAT JOB, GREAT JOB.
Jeff: GO, DESIREE.
LET'S GO, DESIREE.
Jeff: KEEP HANGING IN
THERE, MICHAEL.
ALMOST THERE.
THERE WE GO.
GREAT WORK, MICHAEL.
GOOD JOB, DESIREE.
Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
LAUREL WORKING TO UNLOCK HER
PUZZLE.
DESIREE WORKING TO UNLOCK HER
SHE'S GOT IT.
THAT TIMER STARTS NOW.
LAUREL STILL WORKING TO GET HERS
FREED.
SHE'S GOT IT.
THAT SAPPED TIMER HAS BEGUN.
THAT IS THE TICKING CLOCK.
BOTH BREN DIDN'T AND CHRIS NOW
PAYING ATTENTION TO BOTH PUZZLE
SOLVERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DECIDE,
DO THEY STAY IN IT AND GO FOR
BROKE AND RISK LOSING THEIR
FISHING GEAR, OR AT SOME POINT
DO THEY PULL THE PLUG AND
SALVAGE THE FISHING GEAR BUT
GIVE UP THE ENDS AND FLINT?
I HOPE SHE KNOWS HOW TO DO
SLIDE PUZZLES.
YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: BOTH GUYS WATCHING
BOTH PUZZLES, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TO GAUGE WHAT YOUR PERSON IS
DOING IN RELATION TO WHAT THE
OTHER PERSON IS DOING.
DESIREE MOVING A LOT OF PIECES
QUICKLY.
LAUREL NOW STARTING TO GET SOME
MOMENTUM.
SHE'S GOT A PLAN.
COME ON, LAUREL.
COME ON, GIRL.
Jeff: IF AT ANY POINT
BRENDAN OR CHRIS GIVE UP ON
THEIR TRIBE MATE, THEY CAN PULL
THAT LEVER AND END THIS
CHALLENGE, AN WE'RE GETTING DOWN
TO IT RIGHT NOW.
NOT A LOT OF SAND LEFT IN THAT
BOTTLE.
THAT SAND BLOWING OUT JUST LIKE
THE TIME LEFT TO MAKE THIS
DECISION.
GO, DES.
Jeff: IF YOU OPT OUT, YOU
SAVE YOUR FISHING GEAR, BUT THE
OTHER TRIBE GETS THE SHELTER.
MALOLO WINS FIRST CHALLENGE.
HUNTING DECISION TO GIVE UP ON
DESIREE AND SAVE THE FISHING
GEAR.
THAT GAVE MALOLO A GIGANTIC
ADVANTAGE EARLY IN THIS SEASON.
OH, MY GOD, THAT LOOKED SO
HARD.
ALL RIGHT.
MALOLO IS GOING BACK WITH THE
SHELTER-BUILDING KIT.
20 EGGS AND FIRE.
HUGE ADVANTAGE.
CHRIS, WHEN IT CAME THE CRUNCH
TIME, YOU HAD A BIG DECISION.
DO YOU SALVAGE THE FISHING GEAR
OR GO FOR BROKE.
LOOK, OBVIOUSLY NO ONE WANTS
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL, BUT IT'S
MORE IMPORTANT TO GET WHAT WE
CAN AND IT WAS WORTH IT.
Jeff: ANYBODY FEELING A
LITTLE BIT, IF WE COULD DO IT
AGAIN, MAYBE WE'D MAKE A
DIFFERENT CHOICE?
I'M A TRUTH-TELLER, JEFF.
I DON'T LIE.
Jeff: FIRST BIG DECISIONS
OUT OF THE GATE, BAD NEWS FOR
NAVITI.
GOOD NEWS FOR MALOLO.
MAPS TO YOUR TRIBE CAMPS.
HERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
MALOLO, HEAD ON OUT.
NAVITI, HEAD ON OUT.
GOOD LUCK ON THIS ADVENTURE.
THANK YOU.
ONE BAD DECISION CAN RUIN
YOUR GAME, AND RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE CHRIS MADE THE WRONG
DECISION.
AND WE JUST GAVE A HUGE
ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME TO THE
OTHER TRIBE.
SO WE NEED TO PUT A STOP TO IT
QUICKLY BEFORE IT BITES US IN
THE BUTT.
ONE, TWO, THREE... MALOLO!
THIS IS LIKE THE BEST START
EVER.
YOU GET EVERYTHING.
LET'S GET NAMES AND LIKE
WHERE WE'RE FROM.
DO YOU GO BY MICHAEL OR MIKE?
EITHER ONE.
AT THE CHALLENGE, IT WAS SUPER
HUMBLING.
I'M ATHLETIC, BUT I'M YOUNGER.
I'M ACTUALLY 18 YEARS OLD.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL ANYBODY MY
AGE BECAUSE I THINK IT KILLS
CREDIBILITY RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
IT'S NOT ONLY BEEN MY DREAM TO
COME OUT HERE AND PLAY, BUT I
TOTALLY FEEL LIKE I CAN WIN.
WOW.
THERE'S A LOT HERE.
I GOT ONE AND THAT'S IT.
MY NAME IS STEPHANIE, BUT YOU
CAN CALL ME GONZALEZ.
OKAY.
THE BUG, THE ANT, THE
SPIDERS, IT DOESN'T PHASE ME
BECAUSE I GREW UP IN PUERTO
RICO.
SO I'M IN A GOOD SPOT.
I DO NOT WANT TO GET IN A
FIGHT WITH YOU.
JUST BY LOOKING AT ME, YOU
WOULD THINK SUPER GIRLIE GIRL,
BUT I THINK THEY'RE NOW SAYING,
WAIT A MINUTE, THERE'S A LOT
MORE TO THAT GIRL, AND THEY HAVE
SEEN NOTHING YET.
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
KENTUCKY.
RIGHT AT THE WEST VIRGINIA AND
VIRGINIA, YOU KNOW HOW KENTUCKY
IS?
THAT'S WHERE I AM.
RIGHT THERE.
OKAY.
COOL.
THAT'S AWESOME.
I LOVE THIS EXPERIENCE BECAUSE
I'M STARTING TO MEET PEOPLE I'VE
NEVER GOT TO MEET BEFORE.
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."
IT'S GOING TO BLOW A LOT OF
PEOPLE'S MINDS FROM EASTERN
KENTUCKY WHEN THEY SEE DONATHAN
HURLY IS ON "SURVIVOR."
ARE YOU MARRIED OR ANYTHING?
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
I'M NOT MARRIED.
ARE YOU DATING, MARRIED?
OH,, NO I CAN'T FIND A MAN IN
EASTERN KENTUCKY.
THERE'S NO SHAVE NOT NO GUY MEN
EASTERN KENTUCKY THAT'S OUT LIKE
I AM.
IT'S MY FIRST TIME OUT OF THE
COUNTRY.
MY MAIN GOAL BESIDES WINNING THE
GAME IS TO KNOW PEOPLE THAT I
WOULD NEVER KNOW BEFORE, LIKE
JAMES, HE'S EXOTIC, AND LAUREL,
SHE STOOD OUT TO ME BECAUSE
WHERE I'M FROM IS MAINLY
CAUCASIAN.
I DON'T HAVE CHANCE TO HAVE AN
AFRICAN AMERICAN FRIEND.
I DO LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
I LIKE YOU.
I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
I NEED TO HAVE PEOPLE I CAN
TRUST.
BECAUSE LOOKING AT ME, INOT THE
MOST BUILT OR MAYBE THE MOST
BRAINY.
IF YOU'RE TOO WEAK EARLY IN THIS
GAME, THAT'S DEFINITELY
SOMETHING THEY'RE JUST WANTING
TO GET RIGHT OUT HERE.
WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
SEBASTIAN.
I'M A FISHERMAN.
YAY.
PERFECT!
I'M WENDELL, A FURNITURE
DESIGNER.
HI, WENDELL.
AS YOU KNOW, I'M CHRIS.
I LIVE IN THE CITY OF DREAMS,
NEW YORK CITY, BUT I GREW UP IN
THE FLORIDA KEYS.
I'M KELLYN.
BEFORE "SURVIVOR" I WAS LIVING
MY LIFE LIKE I SHOULD, DOING
WHAT I THOUGHT I SHOULD DO.
I MADE THE DECISION TO SAY,
THAT'S NOT THE LIFE I WANT.
SO I GOT DIVORCED.
I FINISHED GRAD SCHOOL.
AND I REALLY HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
START LIVING MY LIFE FOR ME.
AND I'M A HUGE FAN OF
"SURVIVOR."
I MADE IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE AN INSANE
JOURNEY.
I'M READY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO CUT
SOME OF THESE.
SEA BASS, DO ME FAVOR.
DO YOUR FRIENDS CALL YOU SEA
BASS?
I DON'T KNOW.
FOR GOD SAKE, YOU'RE A
FISHERMAN AND YOU NAME IS
SEBASTIAN, SEA BASS IS YOUR
NAME.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED A LOT OF
ROOM.
THERE ARE TEN OF US.
WE NEED TO MAKE THE BEDS WIDE.
AS A CONSTRUCTION SUPERVISOR,
IT'S MY JOB TO MAKE SURE PEOPLE
WORK COHESIVELY ON A DAILY BASIS
TO MAKE SURE THE JOB GETS DONE.
WHAT'S GOING ON ON YOUR
STOMACH?
RIGHT HERE?
THE SHAPES, ALL THOSE SQUARES
YOU GOT.
WHAT ARE THOSE?
SOMETHING LIKE ROCKS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOOK AT FOOD AND I PUT
WEIGHT ON.
I USED TO BE 270 POUNDS.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT,
LIFESTYLE CHANGE?
YEAH, I JUST STARTED MAKING
BETTER DECISIONS, NOT JUST IN
FOOD, BUT IN LIFE.
I'M NOT A CRIMINAL, BUT BAD
DECISIONS.
I LIKED TO PARTY, DRINK, GAMBLE.
THOSE DAYS ARE OVER.
IN MY LIFE I'VE DEFINITELY SEEN
SOME ADVERSITY AND I HAD SOME
STRUGGLES, BUT WHEN MY FIRST
DAUGHTER WAS BORN, THAT
DEFINITELY WAS A CROSSROADS FOR
ME WHERE I CAN SIT THERE AND
SAY, IT'S TIME FOR ME TO STEP UP
AND BECOME MAN AND TAKE CONTROL
OF MY LIFE.
SO WHAT WAS YOUR TURNING
POINT?
I WANTED TO BE AROUND FOR MY
KIDS.
THAT'S IT.
LEAVING MY WIFE AND THREE KIDS
BEHIND HAS BEEN DIFFICULT FROM
THE SECOND I LEFT THE HOUSE, BUT
MY WIFE AND KIDS GAVE ME THEIR
BLESSING, BUT THEY GAVE ME THEIR
BLESSING WITH THE NOTION I HAVE
TO BRING HOME THE BACON.
THEY GOT ENGAGED.
MY PARENTS GOT MARRIED IN KEY
WEST.
WE'RE MORE ALIKE THAN WE
THINK.
I ALREADY KNEW WE WERE ALIKE,
DUDE.
WHO IS MISSING?
CHRIS AND SEBASTIAN.
CHRIS AND SEBASTIAN ARE
MISSING.
NOTHING TO BE WORRIED ABOUT.
WE MEAD THE TEAM UP.
WE NEED TO GET EACH OTHER TO THE
MERGE.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
WHEN CHRIS STARTED TELLING ME
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT FLORIDA, I
WAS IMMEDIATELY ATTRACTED.
WE BOTH LOBSTER IN THE FLORIDA
KEYS AND GO TO THE BAHAMAS AND
BACK AND FISH.
IT'S LIKE BEST FRIENDS IN A
CANDY SHOP, PICKING OUT WHAT
KIND OF GUMMIES EACH OTHER
WANTS.
SO IT'S GREAT TO HAVE A BUDDY
THAT IS SO CLOSE TO YOU.
WHO ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT
GUNNING FOR THE FIRST.
DON IS CRAZY.
WE NEED TO LIVE TO FIGHT
ANOTHER DAY.
THAT DUDE WILL BE THE ONE THAT'S
GOING TO TRY AND CUT YOU AND CUT
ME.
THERE ARE RED FLAGS WITH
DOMENICK.
WHEN JEFF ASKED PEOPLE, DID I
MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION, THERE
WAS ONLY ONE PERSON THAT CAME
OUT AND SAID, NO, HE DIDN'T.
BACK AT IT?
IT GOT ME ALREADY PLAYING THE
GAME.
I GOT TO GET RID OF THIS GUY
BECAUSE HE'S GUNNING FOR ME.
WASHING MY FACE A LITTLE BIT.
THEY GOT WASHED INCH I PUT MY
SHOES BEHIND ME, AND THE TIDE
TOOK THE SHOES OUT.
I'M DUNN A PAIR OF SHOES.
THAT WAS FIRST TIME SINCE I GOT
HERE THAT I FELT STUPID.
I THINK WHEN YOU LOOK AT OUR
OVERALL GROUP, ME AND DONATHAN
DON'T STAND OUT FOR OUR
PHYSIQUES.
THERE IS A DECENT POSSIBILITY
THAT THE FIRST BOOT WILL
PROBABLY BE ONE OF US BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT BRENDAN, WE'RE NOT
MICHAEL.
I'M A LITTLE AFRAID THAT ALL
THESE PRETTY PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
GANG UP ON ME AT SOME POINT IN
THE FUTURE IF WE DON'T WIN
IMMUNITY.
YOU GUYS THINK THERE IS AN IDOL
IN
OH, DEFINITELY.
IT'S NOT "SURVIVOR" WITHOUT
ONE.
PERHAPS, PERHAPS, PERHAPS.
SO I'M GOING TO GO SWIM RIGHT
NOW.
JACOB WENT EXPLORING,
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
I WAS THINKING HE WOULD.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THE
SUSPICIOUS DUDE WHO DISAPPEARED
FOR 30 MINUTES HUNTING THROUGH
ALL THE FAWNA FOR AN IDOL, BUT
THE LAST THING I'M GOING TO BE
IN THIS GAME IS COMFORTABLE.
I'M SURPRISED NO ONE'S COME DOWN
YET.
HE'S EITHER ON THE TRAIL OF
THE IDOL OR HE'S WORKING UP TO
IT.
WE ALL WANT AN IDOL, BUT WE HAVE
THIS "KUMBAYA" THING WE'RE WHERE
-- WHERE WE'RE NOT DOING
IT.
HE'S THE ONE THAT'S GONE.
JACOB IS PLAYING THE GAME TOO
HARD OUT OF THE GATE.
IT'S A BAD, RISKY DECISION TO BE
THE ONE THAT PEOPLE PERCEIVE AS
HE'S GOING OFF TO HUNT FOR AN
IDOL.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONE TO
STAND OUT FOR ANY REASON IN THE
EARLY STAGE OF THE GAME.
SO WE'RE JUST GOING TO GO OUT
AND LOOK FOR YAMS.
A YAM SEARCH PARTY.
I'LL GET THE FIRE GOING IF YOU
WANT TO GO.
NO PROBLEM.
NO WORRIES.
I GOT YOU COVERED.
I'VE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT THIS MY
ENTIRE LIFE.
YOU GOT TO REALIZE, "SURVIVOR"
AIRED THE FIRST TIME WHEN I WAS
FOUR.
AND I WATCHED EVERY SEASON SINCE
I WAS FOUR.
I'M EITHER ABOUT TO DO SOMETHING
REALLY STUPID OR REALLY
BRILLIANT.
IT'S LOVING THE SHOW SO MUCH
THAT MAKES ME WANT TO DO SO
WELL.
OH, THIS COULD BE REALLY STUPID.
SO I LITERALLY JUST POURED A
BUNCH OF RICE INTO MY DIRTY SOCK
HOPING THAT IT WOULD FREE UP
WHATEVER WAS INSIDE.
WHY NOT CHECK WHEN NO ONE ELSE
IS LOOKING.
THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE.
I WOULD BE DEVASTATED SO
HOPEFULLY THEY THINK THAT I'M
NOT BEING TOO SUSPICIOUS, BUT I
THINK I ALREADY SCREWED MYSELF.
THAT WAS STUPID.
GUYS, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
BUILDING A MASSIVE SPIDER NET.
THAT'S LOOKING GOOD.
WHEN DID YOU START DOING
FURNITURE DESIGN?
MY POP STARTED ME OUT
BUILDING, BECAUSE HE HAD ME
DOING DRYWALL IN THE BECAME AND
STUFF LIKE THAT GROWING UP.
NOW I'M DOING EXACTLY WHAT I
LOVE SO MUCH.
WENDELL, HOW YOU MAKING OUT,
BUD?
STARTING THE FRAMEWORK A
LITTLE BIT.
SO THEY COME IN, WE PUT SOME
GOODIES IN THERE FOR THEM TO
EAT, THEN WE COME FIND SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, 47 CRABS IN
HERE.
I LIKE THE NUMBER.
AND WE EAT THEM.
I WENT TO U. PENN LAW, TOP-TEN
LAW SCHOOL, BUT I WASN'T WHERE I
WANTED TO BE.
I TOOK OFF THE SUIT, AND NOW I'M
A FREELANCE FURNITURE DESIGNER.
SO I AM MORE THAN I APPEAR.
THERE'S THIS GUY DOM.
HE'S A CONSTRUCTION WORKER, AND
I TOOK TO THAT.
I JUST STARTED FEELING GOOD
VIBES FROM HIM.
HE JUST SEEMS LIKE A FRIENDLY
GUY THAT I WOULD WORK WITH.
IF WE DO LOSE, WHAT ARE WE GOING
TO DO?
UNLESS SOMEONE IS JUST HORRIBLY
HORRIBLE AT THE CHALLENGE?
I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS DOM.
WELL, I LIKE HIM.
SO JUST KEEP THINKING.
KEEP THIS THING MOVING AND WE'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
AS SOON AS I HEARD DOMENICK'S
NAME, I WAS LIKE, MAN, LET ME
GIVE HIM SOME INFORMATION,
BECAUSE I THINK I CAN SHOW HIM
MY LOYALTY AND I THINK IT'S
GOING TO RECIPROCATE IN THE LONG
RUN.
I ASKED, ACCEPT, HEY, WHAT'S
GOING ON, AND HE'S LIKE, ISN'T
IT DOM.
THERE'S SOMEONE THAT SAID
SEBASTIAN?
NO ONE THINKS IT WAS CHRIS?
OF COURSE IT COULD HAVE BEEN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I FEEL
LIKE HE'S CURSING ME OUT IN HIS
BRAIN.
I FEEL LIKE I'M AGGRAVATING ONE
SPECIFIC PERSON, AND I BELIEVE
CHRIS IS THE ONE LOOKING THE
TARGET ME.
I KNOW IT'S CHRIS.
AT THIS POINT HE MAY HAVE
ALREADY PUT SOME TYPE OF
COALITION AGAINST ME, BUT I'M
HERE TO PLAY THE GAME, AS WELL,
AND HE'S GOT A BIG BATTLE AHEAD
OF HIM IF HE THINKS HE'S GOING
TO ROLL RIGHT IN AND JUST VOTE
ME OUT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE ACROSS A NET
BRIDGE.
YOU'RE THEN GOING TO WORK
TOGETHER TO RETRIEVE TWO BAGS OF
ROPE.
YOU WILL USE THOSE ROPES TO PULL
A SLED FILLED WITH GIANT PUZZLE
PIECES.
WITNESS YOU HAVE ALL THE PUZZLE
PIECES, YOU WILL USE THEM TO
SOLVE A CUBE PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY.
THIS IS THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
WITH THIS IN YOUR POSSESSION,
YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THE
GAME.
WITHOUT IT LOSERS GO THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND."
IN ADDITION, NAVITI, BECAUSE YOU
DO NOT HAVE FIRE, YOU ARE ALSO
PLAYING FOR FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT.
ONE MORE THING, GHOST ISLAND IS
IN PLAY, AND SOMEBODY FROM THE
LOSING TRIBE WILL BE THE FIRST
TO VISIT.
BIG STAKES.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY HITS IT HARD.
CHRIS GOES DOWN HARD.
WENDELL GOES DOWN.
ALL THAT ADRENALINE.
YEARS IN THE MAKING.
IT'S NOW COURSING THROUGH YOUR
BODY.
YOU HAVE TO GO FAST.
NAVITI HAS ONE BAG.
CHELSEA WORKING ON THE SECOND
BAG.
DONATHAN HAS FIRST BAG.
LIBBY WORKING ON THE SECOND BAG.
SHE'S GOT IT.
GO, MALOLO.
GET YOUR FIRST THREE PIECES OF
PUZZLE IN THAT SLED.
WE'RE GOOD, GUYS.
Jeff: NAVITI DOING A NICE
JOB.
THEY HAVE THEIR PUZZLE PIECES.
MALOLO STILL WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES.
NAVITI NOW WITH A LEAD.
DESPITE HAVING NO FOOD.
NO SHELTER AND NO FIRE.
MALOLO HAS THEIR THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: GET EVERYBODY BACK
HERE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, MALOLO.
NAVITI NOW PULLING THAT SLED,
WHICH IS VERY HEAVY.
IT TAKES ALL TEN PEOPLE TO MOVE
THAT.
NAVITI WORKING TOGETHER REALLY
WELL.
MALOLO LOSES THEIR PIECES.
GOT TO GET THEM BACK IN.
MALOLO WITH A DISASTER OPENS THE
DOOR FOR NAVITI.
YOU'RE GOOD.
UNLOAD.
MALOLO BACK AT IT, BUT THEY'RE
STILL IN IT.
YOU HAVE TO GET ALL THREE PIECES
OVER THE HITCHING RAMP.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
NAVITI HAS THEIR THIRD PIECE.
HEAD BACK.
PULL IT BACK.
Jeff: NOW YOU'VE GOT TO
PULL THAT SLED BECOME AND LOAD
UP THREE MORE.
GOT YOUR THREE PIECES.
GO.
MALOLO NOW HEADING BACK.
RUN, RUN.
LET'S RUN IT, RUN IT.
LET'S GO!
Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
GOING TO EXHAUST YOU.
MALOLO TRYING THE STAY IN THIS.
NAVITI NOW LOADING THEIR FINAL
THREE PUZZLE PIECES.
YOU'RE GOOD, MALOLO.
NAVITI HAS THEIR FINAL THREE
PIECES.
YOU CAN HEAD BACK.
LET'S GO.
OH, MY GOD.
WE GOT THIS.
Jeff: YOU CAN SEE THE
FATIGUE SETTING IN.
THESE SLEDS ARE HEAVY.
IT TAKES TEAMWORK AND STRENGTH
BEYOND JUST PURE ADRENALINE.
MALOLO IS WORKING HARD TO GET
BACK IN THIS.
IF THEY CAN GET THAT SLED
MOVING.
NAVITI DOING A NICE JOB.
NOW HERE COMES MALOLO.
NAVITI GETTING CLOSER.
ONE MORE BIG PULL WILL DO IT.
THOSE LAST THREE PIECES, THERE
IT IS.
GO, YOU'RE GOOD.
NAVITI HAS ALL THEIR PUZZLE
PIECES.
NOW GET IT OVER THE HITCHING
RAIL AND START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
FOUR PEOPLE WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
LET'S GO.
THIS WAY, THIS WAY.
THIS IS THE TOP.
Jeff: ALMOST THERE FOR
MALOLO.
ONE MORE PULL WILL DO IT.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE GOOD.
IT IS BRADLEY, WENDELL, DOMENICK
AND KELLYN SOLVING THE PUZZLE
FOR MAF AND A HALF.
YOU'RE GOOD, MALOLO, STARTED
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
IT IS GOING TO BE JACOB,
MICHAEL, LAUREL, AND JAMES
SOLVING THE PUZZLE FOR MALOLO.
THIS IS IT.
THAT IS IT.
Jeff: KELLYN BARKING OUT
INSTRUCTIONS TO HER GROUP.
MALOLO SUDDENLY'S GOT SOME
MOMENTUM NOW.
HERE, HERE, HERE, HERE.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE BOTTOM.
Jeff: NAVITI NOW THINKS
THEY HAVE SOMETHING.
PUT IT IN THERE.
Jeff: AND NAVITI WITH
ANOTHER PIECE.
HERE COMES MALOLO NOW.
THIS IS YELLOW AND RED.
I DON'T KNOW.
EVERY TYPE OF DIFFERENT
COLOR.
GUYS, WE NEED TO DO ONE
PERSON TALKS.
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
Jeff: NAVITI THINKS THEY
HAVE ANOTHER PIECE.
COULD BE A BIG MOVE FOR NAVITI
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
MALOLO NOW FEELING THE PANIC.
THIS WAY.
ONE MORE.
IN, IN!
Jeff: NAVITI LOOKS SO
CLOSE.
ARE THEY RIGHT?
WE GOT IT, JEFF.
Jeff: NAVITI WINS IMMUNITY,
SENDING MALOLO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SORRY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NAVITI, DESPITE THE LACK OF
ADVANTAGE OUT OF THE GATE,
DIDN'T SEEM TO MATTER.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
PLUS FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
WE GOT FIRE!
Jeff: JACOB, WITH THE BIG
ADVANTAGE, LOSING TO NAVITI,
WHAT DOES THAT FEEL LIKE?
WE STILL KNOW WE'RE ONE OF
THE BEST TRIBES OF ALL TIME.
ONE LOSS DOES NOT MEAN A HISTORY
OF LOSSES.
WE'RE GOING TO COME BACK FROM
THIS.
Jeff: I THINK MOST PEOPLE
WOULD PROBABLY SAY IT'S A BIT OF
A STATEMENT TO SAY THAT ON DAY
THREE, WE KNOW WE'RE ONE OF THE
GREATEST TRIBES OF ALL TIME.
I THINK THERE'S NEVER BEEN A
TRIBE QUITE AS COHESIVE AS US.
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN A
DESCRIBE --.
Jeff: YOU'RE STICKING WITH
IT.
I AM.
GOT TO HAVE IT, OTHERWISE YOU
SHRIVEL UP AND DIE, MAN.
Jeff: SO, NAVITI, LET'S
MAKE THINGS A LITTLE MORE
INTERESTING.
YOU'RE GOING THE CHOOSE ONE
PERSON FROM MALOLO TO SEND TO
GHOST ISLAND, WHICH MEANS THEY
WILL NOT GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEY CANNOT BE VOTED VUT OF THE
GAME.
WOW.
Jeff: THIS IS A BIG
OPPORTUNITY AND A BIG DECISION.
HOW CAN YOU USE IT TO YOUR
ADVANTAGE?
JACOB WAS TALKING ALL THAT
TRASH.
LET'S SEND HIM.
OKAY.
Jeff: WHO IS IT GOING TO
BE?
WE'RE GOING TO SEND JACOB TO
GHOST ISLAND.
Jeff: JACOB.
IT'S GOOD WHEN YOU TALK BIG
SOMETIME, THEY FALL INTO YOUR
TRAP.
Jeff: SO THIS WAS ALL PART
OF A DESIGN.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT GHOST
ISLAND IS.
I WANT TO GO FIND OUT.
NICE TO BE IMMUNE FOR A MINUTE.
Jeff: SO YOU FRONTED BIG SO
THEY WOULD CHOOSE YOU TO KEEP
YOU SAFE.
BASICALLY, YEAH.
I'M NEUROTIC.
THIS IS HOW MY BRAIN WORKS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JACOB,
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD DOWN TO
THE WATER.
THE BOAT IS WAITING.
ENJOY GHOST ISLAND.
BYE, JACOB.
GOOD LUCK, Y'ALL.
BYE.
Jeff: THE BIGGEST DECISION
OF THE GAME THUS FAR.
NAVITI, LET'S SEE IF YOU CHOSE
WISELY.
NAVITI, YOU ARE SAFE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT FIRE.
ALL RIGHT.
MALOLO, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
GHOST ISLAND."
JACOB BEING ON GHOST ISLAND
DEFINITELY SCREWS US A LITTLE
BIT BECAUSE THAT'S WHO WE
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
NOW WE HAVE TO VOTE OUT SOMEONE
WE WEREN'T PLANNING ON.
STRATEGY-WISE, WHO IS IT GOING
TO BE NOW.
FOR THE PAST THREE DAYS MY
ENTIRE TRIBE HAS BEEN SITTING
AROUND TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THE HECK GHOST ISLAND IS.
IT'S A WEIRD FEELING I AM
WALKING TRULY INTO THE UNKNOWN.
I THINK THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING HERE THAT'S GOING TO
HELP ME.
I TRIED TO GET HERE IN THE FIRST
PLACE, BUT I WON'T KNOW UNTIL I
FIND WHATEVER THAT THING IS.
IS THAT A CHINA IMMUNITY IDOL?
WHAT IS THAT FROM?
I SEE ALL OF THESE ORIGINAL
"SURVIVOR" RELICS.
HUH, WAIT A SECOND.
I STARTED THINKING ABOUT ALL THE
PLAYERS GOING TO THE JURY OR
GETTING VOTED OUT EARLY, YOU
THINK ABOUT ALL OF THOSE MOMENTS
WHERE YOU SEE GREAT PEOPLE FALL.
A FEW STEPS TO THE SHELTER THERE
IS A ROW OF URNS.
SMASH THE URN.
OH.
OH!
GAME ON.
FOLLOW THE FIRE.
SO I FOLLOW THE ROW OF TORCHES
UP THIS LITTLE SLOPE TO A SMALL
CLEARING WITH SOME INSTRUCTIONS
FOR A GAME.
GHOST ISLAND GAME OF CHANCE.
I'LL WAGER A SECRET ADVANTAGE IF
YOU'LL WAGER YOUR NEXT VOTE.
IF YOU WIN, YOU'LL HAVE POWER IN
THE GAME.
IF YOU LOSE, YOU WILL NOT VOTE
NEXT TRIBAL.
SO I'M LOOKING AT THE GAME, AND
THERE'S TWO BAMBOO CHUTES.
IN THE MIDDLE THERE IS A THIRD
ONE WITH A LOCK ON IT.
I'M GUESSING THERE IS PROBABLY A
KEY IN ONE OF THE OTHER TWO
BAMBOO CHUTES.
IF I PICK RIGHT, I'LL GET THE
ADVANTAGE.
IF I PICK WRONG, I GET NOTHING
AND LOSE MY VOTE.
OH, BOY, I'M PRETTY SURE THAT MY
TRIBE IS LOOKING AT ME AS AN
EASY FIRST BOOT.
THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO AVOID
THAT, BUT IF THIS IS THE WRONG
DECISION, THEN LOSING MY VOTE
COULD JUST BE THE NAIL IN THE
COFFIN.
THAT'S RISKY, BUT IT FEELS LIKE
THE KIND OF RISK YOU SHOULD
TAKE.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH THE ONE ON
THE LEFT.
OKAY.
OH, MAN.
OH, MY GOD.
I OPEN IT UP, AND I'M FREAKING
OUT, BECAUSE I SEE "SECRET
ADVANTAGE."
THIS IS THE AUTHENTIC LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
THIS IS THE LEGACY ADVANTAGE
FROM "GAME CHANGERS."
IT HAS THEIR NAMES ON IT.
I'M TOUCHING A PIECE OF
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
SIERRA FOUND THIS ADVANTAGE ON
GAME ONE AND KEPT IT SECRET.
YOU ARE GUARANTEED IMMUNITY,
BUT YOU MAY ONLY USE IT WHEN
THERE ARE 13 PEOPLE LEFT IN THE
GAME OR 6 LEFT IN THE GAME.
ON DAY 30 SHE TOLD SARAH.
I FOUND SOMETHING ON FIRST
DAY.
IT WAS A LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
IT WAS A COSTLY MISTAKE.
Jeff: 12th PERSON VOTED
OUT, SIERRA.
THIS LEGACY ADVANTAGE HAS
LOST ITS POWER, BUT YOU CAN
RESTORE ITS POWER BY WILLING IT
TO SOMEONE ELSE ON THE OTHER
TRIBE.
CHOOSE WISELY, AND THIS COULD BE
THE BEGINNING OF A NEW ALLIANCE.
CHOOSE POORLY AND YOU COULD END
UP LIKE SIERRA.
SO NOW I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO
TO GIVE THIS TO ON THE OTHER
SIDE, SO WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS
GIFT IT TO MORGAN ON THE OTHER
TRIBE.
SHE'S GOT SPUNK.
SHE'S GOT ENERGY.
I THINK SHE'S GOING TO MAKE THE
MERGE, AND I THINK IF I'M THERE
AT THE MERGE WITH HER, THAT WILL
BE GREAT FOR US, BECAUSE WE'LL
HAVE THAT CONNECTION.
I HAVE TO BELIEVE THAT I CAN USE
THIS THING CORRECTLY, AND
REVERSE THE CURSE.
I THINK WE VISUALLY NEED TO
SET THE PUZZLE UP TO WHERE WE
CAN SEE A LOT OF PIECES.
A LOT OF PIECES ARE FLIPPED
UPSIDE DOWN.
MAYBE FLIPPING THEM ALL TO SEE
ALL THOSE COLORS.
AT THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, I
WANTED PEOPLE TO GET THE COLORS
TOGETHER, AND GONZALEZ, WHEN SHE
COMES BACK THE CAMP, THAT WAS
HER BIG IDEA.
ME, I'M PROBABLY THE WEAKEST
PERSON ON THE TRIBE.
I DON'T WANT THAT TARGET ON ME,
SO I'M GOING TO TELL MY TRIBE
MATES THAT GONZALEZ SHOULD BE
THE TARGET.
GONZALEZ MENTIONED ABOUT THE
PUZZLE, THAT'S WHAT I WAS TRYING
TO GET OUT, WHAT SHOULD GO
TOGETHER, AND SHE JUST KIND OF
TOLD ME TO SHUT UP, THAT THERE
WAS TOO MANY PEOPLE TALKING.
PEOPLE ARE VERY UNDERESTIMATING
ME WHEN IT COMES TO WHAT I THINK
IN MY MIND, AND I'M USED TO
THAT, BUT I HAVE MY OWN
THOUGHTS, AND MY OWN PLANS, AND
HOPEFULLY IT WORKS IN MY FAVOR
TONIGHT.
WHO DO WE FEEL LIKE IS ONE OF
THE WEAKER PLAYERS?
I THINK IT'S GOING TO COME
DOWN TO SIZE.
I MEAN, DONATHAN DID NOT PULL
BACK THERE.
WE NEED TO HAVE A STRONG
TRIBE?
WHO IS WEAK?
WHO DIDN'T PERFORM TO THEIR
BEST?
DONATHAN.
JUST VISUALLY.
IT KIND OF CRUSHES YOU IN A
SENSE BECAUSE HE DOES HAVE A
GREAT HEART, BUT AS MUCH AS I
DON'T WANT THE GET RID OF THE
GUY, IF SOMEBODY HAS TO GO, THEN
HE'S GOING TO BE ONE OF THE
OPTIONS TO GO.
BETWEEN DONATHAN AND
GONZALEZ?
WHAT ARE THE PROS AND CONS OF
EACH OF THEM?
BEING A SUPER FAN OF THE SHOW, I
KNOW THE FIRST VOTE SETS THE
TONE FOR THE ENTIRE GAME.
DONATHAN WILL BE SOMEBODY
THAT WE CAN USE AS A VOTE.
I THINK SHE WILL --
SHE WILL DO ANYTHING.
BUT THEN DONATHAN IS WEAKER.
IT'S EITHER GOING TO BE
DONATHAN OR GONZALEZ.
I THINK THAT DONATHAN IS
PROBABLY OUR WEAKEST LENGTH, BUT
I FEEL LIKE THERE IS A LEVEL OF
CONTROL THAT I HAVE.
HE'S GOING TO VOTE WITH US.
HE'S SOMEBODY THAT I CAN
NURTURE.
ONE OF THOSE TWO, THAT'S GREAT.
TO ME GETTING RID OF GONE IS
ABOUT GETTING RID OF A STRATEGIC
THREAT, BECAUSE HE'S GOT HER OWN
AGENDA, AND SHE'S WAY TOO
STRONG.
DONATHAN OR GONZALEZ?
I MEAN, I THINK SHE'S GOING
TO BE A HUGE THREAT.
I DO, TOO.
BUT THEN AGAIN SHE'S A REALLY
STRONG PLAYER, AND I FEEL
LIKE --
SHE IS, BUT IS SHE?
YEAH.
LIKE I FEEL LIKE DONATHAN
WORKS HARDER THAN HER.
HE DEFINITELY WORKS HARDER.
HE WORKS HARDER THAN HER AND
HE MIGHT BE GOOD IF WE NEED A
LITTLE PERSON TO SHOVE INTO
SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BUT THE THING IS, I'M
THINKING DONATHAN JUST TO KEEP
THINGS STRONG.
FOR ME PERSONALLY TONIGHT, I'M
BASING MY VOTE OFF OF STRENGTH.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S TO ME THE MOST
INTELLIGENT THING TO DO AT A
FIRST VOTE, BECAUSE WE ALL WANT
TO WIN.
WE WANT TO GET THE NEXT
CHALLENGES UNDER OUR BELT AND
MAKE IT THAT MUCH FURTHER AND
NOT HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ALL OF
THIS SO EARLY.
AND I THINK THAT GONZALEZ IS
SOMEBODY WE CAN EASILY DO WAY
DOWN THE LINE, BUT FIRST VOTE IS
HUGE BECAUSE IT COULD AFFECT OUR
ENTIRE GAME.
WITH THIS BEING GHOST ISLAND, I
FEEL LIKE IT'S A DOUBLE WHAMMY.
IF YOU MAKE A BAD DECISION, I
THINK THAT WILL HAUNT ME FOR
LIFE.
Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GRAB A TORCH, APPROACH A FLAME,
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNSEL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
STEPHANIE, I GOT TO ASK, YOU'RE
SMILING.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOU JUST WANT
THE TAKE EVERYTHING IN, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME, THE GAME GETTING
STARTED RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: WELL, LET'S GET INTO
IT.
GONZALEZ, WHAT'S THE TAKE ON
GHOST ISLAND?
IS IT EXCITING THAT THERE'S A
PART OF THE GAME THAT YOU DON'T
YET UNDERSTAND?
IT IS EXCITING.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE JACOB WILL COME BACK AND
TELL US HOW MISERABLE HE WAS,
BUT SOMETHING TELLS US HE'S
LOOKING FOR IDOLS, JUST BECAUSE
JACOB IS KIND OF SPECIAL.
Jeff: DO YOU KNOW WHAT
GONZALEZ IS TALKING ABOUT WHEN
SHE SAYS JACOB IS A LITTLE
SPECIAL?
HE DOESN'T SEEM TO CARE THAT
HE WILL LEAVE FOR THREE HOURS
AND AUTOMATICALLY HAVE A TARGET
ON HIS BAKE.
IT SEEMS LIKE HE'S MAKING A FEW
MISTAKES, AND THAT MIGHT BE WHAT
SHE'S REFERRING TO.
Jeff: LAUREL, WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN YOU GOT BACK THE CAMP.
IT SOUNDS LIKE JACOB WAS AN EASY
VOTE AND NOW YOU DON'T HAVE AN
EASY VOTE.
I THINK WE WANT TO KEEP THE
TRIBE STRONG.
THAT'S A QUESTION OF WHAT THAT
MEANS.
DO YOU WANT TO KEEP THE TRIBE
PHYSICALLY STRONG?
Jeff: WHERE DID YOU FALL?
I WANT TO KEEP THE TRIBE
PHYSICALLY STRONG.
I THINK WE STRUGGLED IN THE
OBSTACLE.
Jeff: DONATHAN, AS ONE OF
THE SMALLER GUY, DO YOU THINK,
PLEASE DON'T MAKE IT ME.
I'M DEFINITELY NOT THE MOST
PHYSICAL.
YOU SEE ALL THESE BUFF GUYS
PULLING THE WEIGHT.
I'M DEFINITELY NERVOUS TONIGHT.
Jeff: STEPHANIE, DOES THAT
MAKE SENSE TO YOU THAT DONATHAN
MIGHT FEEL HEAT?
IF IT'S BASED PURELY ON
PHYSICAL STRENGTH.
THERE'S STRATEGIC STRENGTH.
THERE'S SOCIAL STRENGTH.
SO WHAT IS THE CRITERIA FOR
TONIGHT.
Jeff: THAT WAS AN
INTERESTING ANSWER.
DONATHAN, DO YOU THINK THE
SOCIAL RELATIONSHIPS THAT ARE
ALREADY FORMED OR STILL MAY BE
FORMING WILL IMPACT TONIGHT'S
VOTE?
YEAH, THIS WHOLE EXPERIENCE
SO FAST HAS BEEN ABOUT BUILDING
RELATIONSHIPS FOR ME AT LEAST.
I'M FROM EASTERN KENTUCKY.
I DON'T GET TO SEE VERY MANY
DIVERSE AND DIFFERENT
BACKGROUNDS.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S JUST A BUNCH
OF EXPERIENCES THEY'VE HAD AND I
HAVEN'T HAD TO HAVE ANY REALLY
BIG EXPERIENCES IN MY LIFE, SO
IT COULD DEFINITELY PUT ME AT A
DISADVANTAGE.
Jeff: GONZALEZ, YOU WERE
VERY INVOLVED IN THE
PUZZLE-MAKING PART OF THE
CHALLENGE.
I WANTED TO BE IN THERE SO
BAD.
I CAN LOOK AT THINGS AND PUT
THEM TOGETHER IN MY BRAIN AND
JUST DO IT.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE SECOND NATURE
TO ME, SO I'M PRETTY STRONG AT
PUZZLES.
Jeff: AND YET, BRENDAN, SHE
WASN'T CHOSEN FOR THE PUZZLE.
WELL, I MEAN, PART OF IT IS
WE'RE THREE DAY IN.
WE DON'T KNOW EACH OTHER'S
STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES.
IF WE KNEW ABOUT GONZALEZ WHAT
SHE JUST SAID,'D BE ALL FOR HER
GETTING IN THERE.
Jeff: JENNA, OUT OF THE
GATE, DID YOU FIND GROUPS OF
PEOPLE MAYBE STARTING TO FORM
WHAT MIGHT BE AN ALLIANCE?
IT'S SO EARLY.
TODAY WAS THE FIRST DAY ANYONE
DID START SPHRAT JIEZING.
IT WAS BIGGER GROUPS.
YOU JUST WANTED TO BE PART OF
THE MAIN CONVERSATION.
Jeff: AT SOME POINT YOU
HAVE TO TRUST SOMEBODY,
OTHERWISE YOU HAVE NOTHING.
TOTALLY.
I AGREE.
BUT ALLIANCES HAVEN'T BEEN
FORMED AND LOYALTY HASN'T BEEN
PROVEN BECAUSE THIS IS OUR FIRST
VOTE.
I THINK IT REALLY BOILS DOWN TO
THE CONVERSATIONS WHO WAS THERE
AT THAT TIME.
AND IF YOU WEREN'T THERE, THEN
YOU KNOW YOU COULD JUST AS
EASILY BE WITH -- THE ONE OUT
TONIGHT.
Jennifer: GONZALEZ, YOU'VE
SHIFTED YOUR WHOLE REACTION TO
LOOK AT MICHAEL.
IT'S SCARY YOU CAN MISS OUR
ON ONE CONVERSATION AND THE
TARGET IS ON YOUR BACK.
Jeff: HAVE I MISSED
ANYTHING?
ANYBODY HAVE ANYTHING THEY WANT
TO TALK ABOUT?
YEAH.
JUST MAKING SURE WE'RE STILL
SOLID.
Jeff: DO YOUR THING.
IT'S YOUR TRIBAL.
WOW.
STEPHANIE, FIRST TRIBAL.
THROWING IT DOWN.
THIS GOING TO BE A CRAZY SEASON.
Jeff: IS THIS MAKING YOU
NERVOUS RIGHT NOW?
NO.
LAUREL IS CERTAINLY CURIOUS.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
SAYING.
Amaka: JENNA, ARE YOU
WORRIED IT DOESN'T INCLUDE YOU?
YEAH, IT DESTROYS THE UNITED
FRONT WE THOUGHT WE HAD.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
Jeff: DONATHAN, NOBODY
TALKING TO YOU.
NO.
Jeff: YOU ARE LEANING AWAY
FROM TALKING.
WHEN YOU GET NERVOUS, YOU GOT
TO MOVE A LITTLE BIT.
OKAY.
Jeff: BRENDAN, GAME IS ON.
THAT'S WHAT WE CAME HERE FOR.
WE'RE READY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JAMES, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE DONATHAN.
GONZALEZ.
THAT'S TWO VOTES GONZALEZ.
THAT'S THREE VOTES GONZALEZ.
ONE VOTE DONATHAN.
FOUR VOTES GONZALEZ.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND,"
GONZALEZ.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
GONZALEZ, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
SAD.
Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE ALREADY
BEEN FORCED TO MAKE A LOT OF BIG
DECISION, INCLUDING VOTING OUT
YOUR FIRST TRIBE MEMBER.
STILL A LOT OF DECISIONS LEFT TO
COME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD NIGHT.
FORTUNATELY WE DIDN'T HAVE TO
GO THE TRIBAL TONIGHT.
I TOLD MYSELF WHEN I CAME INTO
THIS GAME, I'M GOING TO HAVE A
HANDLE ON MY PAIR NOWBACK BUT
I'M JUST STARTING TO GET A BAD
FEELING AROUND HERE ABOUT NOT
FITTING IN.
I'M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT'S GOING
ON, BUT I NEED THE MAKE A MOVE
NOW.
COMING OUT THE LOOK FOR IDOLS
DURING THE DAY HAS NOT BEEN
WORKING OUT, SO I DON'T CARE
WHAT TIME OF DAY IT IS, I'LL
LOOK.
IT'S TOO DARK.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
SO AS LONG AS I'M IN THIS GAME,
I'LL BE LOOKING.
I'M HERE THE PLAY.
WE'LL SLEEP WHEN WE'RE DEAD.
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FOUND THE
IMMUNITY IDOL IN THE DARK.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW FOR ME PERSONALLY WITH AN
IDOL I CAN TAKE WAY BIGGER
RISKS.
I WANT THE TAKE RISKS.
I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME REALLY
HARD.
I JUST CAN'T READ IT RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL IT GETS
BRIGHTER.
OH, IT'S LIKE CHRISTMAS.
I FINALLY GET THE READ THIS
THING.
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
"THIS IS THE AUTHENTIC HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL THAT ANDREA WAS
VOTED OUT WITH IN "SURVIVOR'S"
26th SEASON."
YOU GOT IT.
NO WAY!
ON DAY 33 ANDREA HAD A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND WHAT SHE
THOUGHT WAS A TRUSTWORTHY
ALLIANCE, BUT SHE WAS WRONG.
OH, YOU GUYS.
ANDREA BECAME THE FIRST
FEMALE TO BE VOTED OUT WITH AN
IDOL IN HER POCKETS.
THIS TAINTED HOUR HAS BEEN
HAUNTED FOR FIVE YEARS BUT STILL
RETAINS ITS ORIGINAL POWER.
CAN YOU REVERSE THE CURSE?
I'M STARTING TO GET A HANDLE ON
THE ESSENCE OF GHOST ISLAND.
IT'S ALL ABOUT PAST PLAYERS'
MISTAKES.
ANDREA KEPT THIS IN HER POCKET,
AND IT WAS A HUGE BLUNDER ON HER
PART.
I HAVE NO INTENTION OF THE CURSE
GETTING ME.
LY REVERSE IT FOR SURE.
I THINK WE HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
IS MY GUESS IS THERE'S IDOLS TO
BE HAD AT GHOST ISLAND.
YOUR GUESS, BUT WE DON'T
KNOW.
WE HAVE TO BE CAREFUL WHO WE
SEND.
THIS GHOST ISLAND THROWS A
WRENCH IN THINGS, BECAUSE WHO
YOU SEND IS GOING TO IMPACT THE
GAME.
WE THOUGHT SEND THEIR WEAK
PLAYER TO GHOST ISLAND WHERE YOU
KNOW THEY'RE SAFE AND LEAVE THE
STRONGER PEOPLE THERE TO GET
VOTED OFF.
BUT IT SEEMS FOR ME THAT WAS A
REALLY GOOD MOVE, BECAUSE THIS
MORNING I LOOKED IN MY BAG AND I
FOUND THE MOST AMAZING,
UNEXPECTED SURPRISE.
THIS IS THE AUTHENTIC LEGACY
ADVANTAGE THAT SIERRA FOUND IN
"SURE CLIVER: GAME CHANGERS"
THIS IS THE LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
IT HAS SIERRA'S NAME ON IT.
I'M TOUCHING IT.
IT'S THE SAME ONE.
IT LOOKS LIKE JACOB FROM THE
OTHER TRIBE WILLED IT TO ME.
WITH THIS NOTE IN YOUR
POSSESSION, YOU ARE GUARANTEED
IMMUNITY.
YOU MAY ONLY USE IT WHEN THERE
ARE 13 PEOPLE LEFT IN THE GAME
OR WHEN THERE ARE ONLY SIX
PEOPLE LEFT IN THE GAME.
IF SIERRA HADN'T TOLD PEOPLE
ABOUT IT, SHE PROBABLY WOULDN'T
HAVE GOTTEN VOTED OUT, BUT THE
PROBLEM IS I HAVE A REALLY BIG
MOUTH.
SO I NEED SOME STAPLE GUNS TO
KEEP THIS THING CLOSED.
BUT THANK YOU, JACOB.
THIS MORNING I START
FORMULATING A PLAN ABOUT WHAT
I'M GOING TO TELL MY TRIBE ABOUT
WHAT GHOST ISLAND IS.
AND I DECIDE THAT SINCE I
ALREADY SENT THE LEGACY
ADVANTAGE TO MORGAN, AND SINCE
NO ONE KNOWS ANYTHING ABOUT THIS
PLACE, WHAT IF I JUST TAKE THE
TRUTH AND KIND OF STRETCH IT OUT
A LITTLE BIT.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO TELL THEM I
GOT THE LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
I'M GOING TO TELL THEM I GOT AN
IDOL OUT OF THIS.
THESE WERE THE BEADS ON OUR
TREE MAIL YESTERDAY, SO I TOOK
THEM AND PUT THEM IN MY BAG.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE NOTICED.
I HAVE A SHELL, SOME TWINE, THIS
MIGHT BE AN OPPORTUNITY FOR ME
TO BLUFF MY WAY THROUGH THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL IN CASE THINGS
ARE BAD, BECAUSE I'M NOT SURE
EXACTLY WHERE I STAND YET.
HANGS A LITTLE WEIRD.
THAT'S OKAY.
THAT'S FINE.
I'M IN THE LYING THROUGH MY
TEETH.
I AM TELLING BASICALLY THE WHOLE
TRUTH.
JUST ONE LITTLE DETAIL IS
DIFFERENT.
AND THAT LITTLE DETAIL COULD
POSSIBLY SAVE MY LIFE.
IT'S LIKE AN ASIAN DELICACY.
REALLY?
THEY'RE LITERALLY JUST SEA
SLUGS.
THEY'RE VERY CHEWY.
YOU GOT TO WORK FOR IT.
YEAH.
OH, GOD.
JACOB'S BACK.
HEY.
THERE HE IS.
JACOB.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHO'S MISSING?
GONZALEZ.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WE ALL NEED TO TALK.
I'LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING.
YOU'LL TELL ME EVERYTHING.
YEAH.
COMING BACK THE MY TRIBE, I
FELT LIKE I WAS IN A LOT OF
TROUBLE, FORTUNATELY I HAVE THIS
FAKE IMMUNITY IDOL, AND THE
TRUTH IS, I HAVE SOME DAMN GOOD
DECEPTION SKILLS, AN ANY
OPPORTUNITY TO BETTER MY
POSITION IN THE GAME, I'M GOING
TO TAKE.
IT WASN'T YOUR NORMAL EXILE.
THERE WAS A GIANT SIGN, ONE BAD
DECISION CAN HAUNT YOU FOREVER.
THEN I WALK FURTHER, AND THERE'S
LIKE 13 TINY LITTLE CLAY URNS,
AND IT SAYS, "SMASH THE URN."
SO I'M SHOWING YOU THIS BECAUSE
IT'S GOING AGAINST ALL MY
INSTINCTS TO SHOW YOU THIS
BECAUSE IT COULD PUT A TARGET ON
MY BACK AND GET RID OF ME NEXT
TIME, BUT I PULLED IT OUT OF A
BAMBOO CHUTE.
I PUT IT IN MY SOCK, A LITTLE
TINY IMMUNITY IDOL AND THE SHELL
HAS A LITTLE SKULL.
YOU GOT NO BELIEVE ME HERE, I'M
GOING TO PLAY THIS AT THE NEXT
TRIBAL NO MATTER WHAT, BECAUSE I
WANT THE STAY IN THIS GAME AS
LONG AS I CAN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE IDOL GUY.
I NEVER WANTED TO BE IDOL GUY.
DID YOUR IDOL HAVE --
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I DON'T HAVE IT UNFORTUNATELY.
I THINK I LEFT IT AT GHOST
ISLAND.
WELL, THANKS FOR SHARING.
I REALLY APPRECIATE THE HONESTY.
I DO, TOO.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE MY
TRIBE ISN'T SUPER SUSPICIOUS OF
ME, AND I THINK IT WORKED.
I BELIEVE MY TRIBE BOUGHT IT.
I BELIEVE MY TRIBE BELIEVES I
HAVE AN IDOL.
AND I BELIEVE MY TRIBE BELIEVES
I'M GOING TO PLAY AN IDOL AT THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL, SO I SHOULD
BE OKAY.
I THINK IT'S FAKE IDOL.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT THAT KID
FORGETS TO BRING THE NOTE.
HOPEFULLY IT'S A FAKE IDOL
AND WE CAN JUST PIN OUR VOTES ON
JACOB.
EVERYBODY WOULD BE ON BOARD
FOR JACOB.
YEAH.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE UP A
STORY, YOU BETTER THINK IT
THROUGH, BECAUSE JACOB'S
FANTASTIC STORY ABOUT WINNING
THIS IMMUNITY IDOL SEEMS
FAR-FETCHED TO ME, BECAUSE THERE
IS NO CHANCE IN THE WORLD THAT
THIS "SURVIVOR" NERD FORGOT THE
NOTE THAT CAME WITH THE IMMUNITY
IDOL BACK AT GHOST ISLAND.
IF THERE IS EVEN A REMOTE CHANCE
THAT HE HAS A REAL IDOL AND WE
PUTS ONE ON ONE OF US, WE'RE
GONE.
DO YOU WANT THE MAKE HIM
COMFORTABLE WHEREAS IF HE HAS A
REAL IDOL, HE DOESN'T PLAY IT.
THERE'S A LOT OF SPECULATION
ABOUT JACOB'S IDOL.
IS IT FAKE, IS IT REAL?
WE DON'T KNOW.
BUT WHEN SOMEBODY KNOWS THEY'RE
ON THE BOTTOM, THEY CAN CREATE
OPPORTUNITIES FOR SOMEBODY LIKE
ME.
I'M AS BIG OF A SUPER FAN AS HE,
IS AND I'M WILLING TO USE HIM TO
GET MYSELF FURTHER IN THIS GAME.
WE DO EVERYTHING.
USE YOUR HIPS.
YOU MUST BE A GOOD SQUATTER.
YEAH.
SNATCH.
THE POWER SNATCH?
YEAH.
YOU COME UP, YOU CLEAN IT.
GOOD?
IN THE BEGINNING I FELT WORRIED
ABOUT MY GAME, BUT I FOUND AN
IDOL AND I FEEL LIKE I'M REALLY
DEVELOPING A GOOD RAPPORT WITH A
SUBSTANTIAL AMOUNT OF PEOPLE IN
THIS TRIBE.
BUT I HEARD THROUGH THE
GRAPEVINE THAT CHRIS WAS GUNNING
FOR ME, SO I WANT TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH HIM TO LET HIM
KNOW I REALLY JUST WANT TO KEEP
THINGS COOL AND HOPEFULLY WE CAN
WORK TOGETHER.
I REALLY FEEL THAT WE MISREAD
EACH OTHER.
LET'S START FRESH.
I WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU.
FRANKLY, FROM THE BEGINNING I
THOUGHT YOU WERE GUNNING FOR ME.
100% NOT.
I LOVE YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE AWESOME.
I WANT TO JUST KEEP DOING WHAT
WE'RE DOING, SO JUST I'LL -- IT
WILL -- YOU'LL SAY, ALL RIGHT,
HE MEANS IT.
HAVE YOU FOUND THE IDOL.
NO ONE HAS EVEN LOOKED.
NO ONE HAS LOOKED.
NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
IT'S JUST GOOD TO KNOW,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU AND I ARE
TRYING TO DEVELOP A TRUST.
YEAH.
IF I KNEW YOU HAD IT, THEN WE
COULD WORK TOGETHER AND FIGURE
OUT A PLAN.
THE WAY CHRIS CAME AT ME OUT
OF THE GATE IMMEDIATELY MADE ME
THINK HE WAS DEFINITELY ON TO
ME, BUT I'M NOT GOING THE PLAY
DEFENSE.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE I HAVE
CHRIS IN MY CONTROL.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHO HE IS
MESSING WITH.
THE OTHER DAY I FOUND THE
MOST BEAUTIFUL SHELL.
I LOOKED AT IT AND SAID, THIS
WOULD MAKE A GREAT IDOL SOME I
DECIDE THE CREATE THIS FAKE IDOL
AND WRAP IT UP WITH THE
PAPERWORK THAT CAME WITH MY REAL
IDOL.
I BELIEVE I CAN EARN CHRIS'S
TRUST BY SHOWING HIM THE FAKE
IDOL.
IT'S GAMBLE, BUT I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO THROW IT OUT THERE AND
SEE IF HE BITES.
I HAVE AN IDOL.
CAN YOU SHOW ME?
YEAH.
I WANT TO GO TO THE END WITH
YOU.
OKAY.
READ IT.
IT'S SICK.
BY SHOWING HIM THE PAPERWORK
THAT GOES WITH AN ACTUAL IDOL,
IT DISTRACTED HIM FROM EVEN
LOOKING AT THE FAKE IDOL, AND
SEEING HIS REACTION, I KNEW I
HAD HIM HOOK, LINE, AND SINKER.
I EVEN TOLD HIM, ANY TIME YOU
THINK YOU'RE VULNERABLE, YOU ASK
ME, AND I WILL GIVE IT TO YOU,
NO PROBLEM.
IT'S NOT EVEN A REAL IDOL.
HE CAN TAKE IT HOME WITH HIM FOR
ALL I CARE.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM PLAYING AN
IDOL FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
DOMENICK SHOWED ME HIS IDOL
AND SAID HE WANTED TO TAKE ME TO
THE END.
SOMETHING ABOUT IT IS JUST OFF.
WE GOT TO START TO TALK
TRACT.
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T REALLY DONE
THAT.
I DON'T TRUST HIM.
IF MY INSTINCT TELLS ME
SOMETHING IS OFF, I HAVE TO GO
WITH IT.
LY NOT GET VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME GOING AGAINST MY INSTINCT.
KNOWING HE HAS AN IDOL SCARES
THE HELL OUT OF ME.
IT'S UP TO ME AS A LEADER TO
ELIMINATE IT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NAVITI GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW MALOLO TRIBE.
GONZALEZ VOTED OUT AT FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY IDOL?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
DOMENICK, TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL THEN RELEASE TWO SETS OF
BUOYS.
YOU'LL THEN GATHER ALL OF THE
MARKED BUOYS AND GET THEM TO THE
FINISH WHERE THE REMAINING TRIBE
MEMBERS WILL ATTEMPT TO SHOOT
THEM INTO A BASKET.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ALL EIGHT
BUOYS IN THEIR BASKET WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF GHOST
ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
YEAH.
Jeff: CHAIRS, PILLOW,
BLANKET, HAMMOCKS.
HAMMOCKS!
Jeff: EVEN WASH BOARDS FOR
CLEAN CLOTHES.
PLUS GHOST ISLAND.
THE WINNING TRIBE WILL SEND
SOMEBODY FROM THE LOSING TRIBE
TO GHOST ISLAND.
A LOT AT STAKE.
NAVITI, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
I'M NOT GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT GOOD AT SWIMMING?
Jeff: ANGELA, TAKE A SPOT
AT THE SIT-OUT BENCH.
EVERYONE ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT
HERE WE GO FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, GUYS.
Jeff: IT'S MIKE MIKE AND
LIBBY IN THE WATER FOR MALOLO.
NAVITI OFF TO A FAST START.
BRADLEY AND MORGAN.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO, WILL REST
GO!
Jeff: HERE COMES MICHAEL
AND LIBBY.
YEAH.
Jeff: NAVITI TO THE SEESAW
FIRST.
BRADLEY AND MORGAN NOW EXTENDING
THE LEAD.
BOTH BACK IN THE WATER.
THERE'S MICHAEL AND LIBBY RIGHT
ON THEIR TAIL.
GO GET IT.
NOW YOU'RE LOOKING TO RELEASE
THAT FIRST SET OF BUOYS.
MORGAN!
Jeff: MORGAN QUICKLY
RELEASED THE BUOYS.
MICHAEL RELEASES THEM FOR
MALOLO.
GOT TO SWIM IN.
GO, NAVITI!
WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE
GOOD.
Jeff: GO, MALOLO.
IT IS NOW CHELSEA AND SEBASTIAN
IN THE WATER FOR NAVITI.
DONATHAN AND JAMES IN THE WATER
FOR MALOLO.
NAVITI EXTENDING THEIR LEAD.
THEY WON THE FIRST CHALLENGE.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO DO IT AGAIN.
COME ON, GUYS.
Jeff: DONATHAN GOES DOWN
HARD.
JAMES IN THE WATER.
CHELSEA AND SEBASTIAN BOTH NOW
IN THE WATER FOR NAVITI.
HERE GOES DAWN DUNN AND JAMES.
NEITHER LOOKING VERY COMFORTABLE
IN THE WATER.
SEBASTIAN VERY QUICKLY HAS THAT
SECOND SET OF BUOYS.
CHRIS WAITING TO COLLECT THE
MARKED BUOYS.
CHELSEA HAS TO GET TO THE
PLATFORM.
GO, CHRIS!
JAMES IS GOING TO TRY TO GO
DOWN.
HE'S PUT THE MASK ON.
SWIM IN.
Jeff: DONATHAN IS SWIMMING
BACK TO THE PLATFORM, NO HELP.
HERE COMES CHRIS.
ALL THE PRESSURE IS ON JAMES
RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, MAN, YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: HE'S GOT TO GET DOWN
ABOUT EIGHT FEET.
AND HE IS CLEARLY STRUGGLING.
CHRIS WHIPPING THROUGH THE
COURSE FOR NAVITI.
CHRIS IS MAKING QUICK WORK OF
THIS.
CHRIS NOW GOING TO COLLECT EIGHT
MARKED BUOYS AS JAMES IS
TREADING WATER TRYING TO GET
ANOTHER BREATH.
DONATHAN ABSOLUTELY NO HELP.
JAMES REALLY STRUGGLING NOW WITH
NAVITI.
THEY HAVE A HUGE HEAD STARRED.
DONATHAN, DO YOU THINK YOU
CAN GET DOWN THERE?
CAN DO IT.
Jeff: JAMES QUICKLY POPS
UP.
DONATHAN, YOU NEED TO HELP.
Jeff: JAMES, BECKONING
DONATHAN.
DONATHAN, GIVE IT A SHOT.
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
GIVE IT A TRY, MAN.
Jeff: WENDELL SCORES FIRST
FOR NAVITI.
JUST TRY IT, DONATHAN,
PLEASE.
DONATHAN, YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
Jeff: YOU'RE STILL IN THIS.
MALOLO, YOU GOT TO GET DOWN.
THIS IS WHY YOU CAME TO
"SURVIVOR" RIGHT HERE.
DONATHAN NOW IN THE WATER.
HE'S GOING TO GIVE IT A TRY.
YOU GOT IT, DONATHAN.
Jeff: DESIREE JUST MISSES.
DONATHAN CLEARLY WANTED TO PART
OF THIS.
NOW HE'S FORCED TO.
MALOLO REMARKABLY IS STILL IN IT
AS NAVITI CAN ONLY SCORE ONE
BASKET SO FAR.
COME ON, DONATHAN, COME ON
BUDDY.
DONATHAN, THIS IS ABOUT PERSONAL
ACHIEVE.
RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
COMMIT AND GO.
DONATHAN GOES DOWN.
IT WOULD BE REMARKABLE IF
DONATHAN COULD PULL THIS OFF.
AND HE DOES IT!
DONATHAN AMAZES HIMSELF.
DESIREE SCORES.
NAVITI WITH TWO.
OUT OF NOWHERE, A HERO HAS
EMERGED FOR MALOLO.
DONATHAN, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, MY GOD.
GO, STEPHANIE.
COME ON, STEPH.
Jeff: WHEN THINGS LOOKED
OVER FOR MALOLO, DONATHAN DUG
DEEP.
WENDELL SCORES FOR MAF AND A
HALF.
THAT'S THREE.
IT IS STEPHANIE QUICKLY SWIMMING
THIS COURSE.
SHE'S STILL GOT TO COLLECT THE
BUOYS FOR MALOLO.
NAVITI WITH THREE.
THERE ARE EIGHT TOTAL.
WE STILL GOT A CHALLENGE GOING
HERE.
DESIREE SCORES.
THAT IS FOUR FOR NAVITI.
IT'S NOW WENDELL AGAIN.
WENDELL SCORES THE FIFTH FOR
NAVITI.
STEPHANIE, YOU'RE KILLING IT.
Jeff: MALOLO WORKING
QUICKLY.
THEIR SHOOTERS READY TO GET IN
ON THIS.
NAVITI WITH ANOTHER.
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE IN, YOU GUYS ARE OUT.
TWO PEOPLE IN THE WATER.
NAVITI NOW HAS SEVEN.
THEY ARE ONE AWAY.
IT'S BRENDAN NOW SHOOTING FOR
MALOLO.
THEY HAVE A LOT THE CATCH UP.
DESIREE FOR THE WIN.
SHE'S GOT IT.
NAVITI WINS THEIR SECOND
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IN A ROW.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ON ME.
YOU KILLED IT.
YOU DID GREAT.
I'M SO TIRED.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: NAVITI,
CONGRATULATIONS ONCE AGAIN.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
DESIREE, YOU STOOD UP AND TOOK
THAT.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
IN ADDITION, MASSIVE REWARD OF
COMFORT WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
BEFORE WE GET TO GHOST ISLAND,
DONATHAN, EVEN THOUGH MALOLO
LOST, ON A PERSONAL LEVEL, HOW
BIG OF AN ACCOMPLISH.
WAS THAT FOR YOU.
IT WAS HUGE.
WITH THE ENCOURAGEMENT OF MY
FRIENDS HERE, YOU KNOW, THEY
DEFINITELY WANTED ME TO TRY IT.
AND I DID IT.
NEVER IN MY WILDEST DREAMS WOULD
I HAVE IMAGINED I'D DO THAT.
Jeff: GHOST ISLAND.
ONCE AGAIN, NAVITI, YOU CHOOSE
ONE PERSON FROM MALOLO TO GO TO
GHOST ISLAND, WHICH MEANS THEY
CANNOT GO TO GHOST ISLAND.
YOU SENT JACOB LAST TIME, WHO
ARE YOU SENDING THIS TIME?
WE'RE SENDING DONATHAN.
Jeff: WE'LL RETURN BACK THE
CAMP TOMORROW AFTER TRIBAL.
GOOD-BYE, BUDDY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NAVITI.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
SWIM OUT AND CELEBRATE.
ALL RIGHT.
MALOLO, FOR THE SEEK TIME IN A
ROW, TRIBAL COUNCIL, SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE SECOND PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
HEAD ON OUT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
I WAS HOPING NAVITI WOULD
SEND ME BACK THE GHOST ISLAND.
FORTUNATELY I HAVE THIS FAKE
IMMUNITY IDOL AND EVERYONE
THINKS IT'S REAL.
I'M GOING TO TRY THE USE IT TO
TAKE CONTROL OF THE GAME.
WHEN I CHOSEN TO GO THE GHOST
ISLAND, I WAS DEFINITELY
NERVOUS.
THIS IS FIRST TIME BEING OFF BY
MYSELF, HAVING TO SURVIVE.
SO MY MIND IS RACING.
YOU KNOW, I DEFINITELY DON'T
WANT ANY GHOSTINGS AROUND ME.
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO GET MYSELF
TOO PARANOID.
IT'S A GAME.
THINGS ARE GOING THE HAPPEN THE
WAY THEY'RE GOING TO HAPPEN.
THE BIGGEST THING ABOUT
"SURVIVOR" IS YOU JUST HAVE TO
ADAPT AND GO WITH THE FLOW.
THAT'S MY MAIN GOAL OUT HERE.
HOPEFULLY IT GIVES ME A GREAT
REWARD IN THE END.
ONE BAD DECISION CAN HAUNT YOU
FOREVER.
SMASH THE URN.
NOPE, NOT TODAY.
NO GAME FOR YOU.
I GUESS NOBODY GOING TO SNOOP IN
MY BAG AND FIND ANYTHING.
UNFORTUNATELY I DIDN'T GET THE
CHANCE THE PLAY, BUT FOR ME THIS
WAS A CHANCE FOR ME TO PROVE
MYSELF.
GROWING UP PEOPLE ALWAYS WAS
WANTING TO PUT ME DOWN.
THEY WOULD SAY, YOU KNOW, WHO'S
THIS LITTLE KID OUT HERE
CHEERING AND DANCINGEN HE AIN'T
GOT NO TOUGHNESS IN HIM.
BUT TODAY WHEN JAMES WAS OUT
THERE STRUGGLING, YOU KNOW, I
HAD TO GO IN THERE AND MAKE
THOSE MOMENTS COUNT.
SO I WAS DEFINITELY INTIMIDATED,
BUT I KNEW I WAS COMFORTABLE
ENOUGH WITH MY SWIMMING TO BE
ABLE TO BE OKAY.
I JUST SEEN THEM BALLS COME UP,
AND I'M LIKE, HOLY HELL, I DID
THAT.
IT'S MY FIRST FIRE ON MY OWN.
PRETTY PROUD OF MYSELF RIGHT
NOW.
HOPEFULLY WHEN PEOPLE SEE ME
BEING OUT HERE AND BEING LIKE A
LITTLE MOUNTAIN MAN, IT'S GOING
TO BE SOMETHING THAT MAKES THEIR
EYES WIDE AND THEIR MOUTHS DROP.
BEING OUT HERE IS DEFINITELY
LIKE OPENING MY EYES AND GIVING
ME CONFIDENCE IN MYSELF THAT I
CAN, YOU KNOW, BE THE PERSON
THAT I ALWAYS THOUGHT I COULD.
I CAME OUT HERE TO PLAY.
I'M HERE TO WIN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THERE'S NO WAY AROUND IT, OKAY.
I GOT A JOB TO DO, I FAILED TO
DO IT, SO IT'S ON ME.
IF I'M LUCKY ENOUGH TO GET
ANOTHER CHANCE, I'LL DO
EVERYTHING I POSSIBLY CAN TO
REDEEM MYSELF, BUT I CHOKED.
IT'S COOL.
DON'T BEAT YOURSELF UP OVER IT.
SERIOUS.
MY IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
PERFORMANCE WAS PATHETIC.
MY PARENTS TAUGHT ME BACK IN
KOREA TO GIVE EVERYTHING, YOUR
BEST EFFORT, BUT INSTEAD I COST
US THE WIN TODAY.
THAT'S A FACT.
LIKE THERE'S IN WAY AROUND IT.
I FEEL LIKE HELL.
NOW PEOPLE MIGHT BE THINKING OF
LETTING ME GO BECAUSE HE'S TO
BLAME.
JAMES COULDN'T EVEN GO DOWN
THREE FEET.
AND I KNOW THAT'S ONE CHALLENGE.
YEAH.
BUT WE GOT TO GET JACOB.
I DON'T LIKE THE UNCERTAINTY OF
DOES HE HAVE AN IDOL.
BEST-CASE SCENARIO, HE HAS IT
AND HE DOESN'T PLAY IT BECAUSE
HE THINKS HE'S SENDING ONE OF US
HOME.
BUT THE QUESTION IS DO WE HEDGE
OUR BET AND ALSO THROW VOTES AT
JAMES?
I THINK WE GOT TO.
JAMES IS MUSCLED UP, BUT I DON'T
KNOW WHAT HE BRINGS.
EVEN THOUGH JAMES SKEWED UP
BADLY, HE'S PLAN "B."
THE REAL TARGET IS JACOB.
IF THE IDOL IS REAL, IT COULD
DEFINITELY BLOW UP IN OUR FACE,
SO WE GOT TO GET RID OF HIM, BUT
WE GOT TO BE-CAREFUL ABOUT HOW
WE DO IT.
IF WE CAN MAKE HIM FEEL ROCK
SOLID HE'S GOOD, THEN HE'S GOING
TO WANT TO HOLD ON TO IT AND
PLAY IT THE NEXT TIME.
RIGHT.
HE'S GOT TO FEEL REALLY
COMFORTABLE.
EXACTLY.
COOL.
I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE IF I WANT TO START PLAYING,
AND I FEEL LIKE NOBODY WANTS THE
PLAY YET.
I DO.
YOU DO?
I FEEL LIKE EVERYBODY'S LIKE
KUMBAYA.
THAT'S GREAT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE ON THE SAME
WAVELENGTH.
WE SLEEP BY EACH OTHER.
YOU ARE THE PEOPLE I WOULD LOVE
TO WORK WITH.
IT'S TRUE.
I'M LIKE YOU.
I'M USING MY LITTLE FLIRTATIOUS
WAYS TO GET TO THE TRUTH ABOUT
HIS IDOL, AND THE THING ABOUT
JACOB IS HE'S A STRATEGIC
SUPERFAN.
SO THE WAY TO GET IN HIS HEAD IS
TO TALK STRATEGY WITH HIM.
OKAY.
LOOK, WE KNOW THIS GAME.
THERE'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE A
TRIBE SWAP.
I WAS THINKING TO GET ONE OF
THE STRONG GUYS BEFORE THE SWAP,
AS MUCH AS I LIKE MICHAEL,
ANYONE WHO TELLS ME TRIBE
STRENGTH IS WORRYING ME.
TURNS OUT STEPHANIE IS A
HARD-CONSIDER FAN LIKE ME AND
SHE ALSO THINKS MICHAEL IS A
THREAT.
DON'T GET ME WRONG, HE'S A GREAT
GUY, EAGLE SCOUT, CREME DE LA
CREME, AND I BET WOMEN ARE ALL
OVER HIM BACK HOME IN L.A.
I'M SURE HE'S DOING GREAT FOR
HIMSELF, BUT I FEEL LIKE HE'S
GOING THE MAKE DIFFICULT FOR
THOSE OF US WHO AREN'T SUPER
STRONG.
SO I COULD PROBABLY PULL
JAMES NO PROBLEM.
I THINK ME, JAMES AND LAUREL
EVEN.
I THINK LAUREL PROBABLY WOULD GO
WITH US, TOO.
SWEET.
THAT'S A MAJORITY RIGHT
THERE.
WE'RE AN UNLIKELY PAIR, BUT
SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
IF I CAN GET IN THE GOOD GRACES
OF SOMEONE LIKE STEPHANIE, WHO
IS NOT ONLY BEAUTIFUL BUT ALSO
JUST REALLY GOOD AT THIS GAME,
WE COULD GO VERY FAR TOGETHER.
I'M PRETTY STOKED.
SO I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING, I
LIED ABOUT ONE THING AND I'M
ONLY GOING TO TELL YOU BECAUSE I
TRUST YOU.
OKAY.
IDOL IS NOT REAL.
SHUT UP.
I TELL YOU THIS, EVERYTHING
ELSE I SAID WAS REAL.
I DID WIN.
I OPENED THE DAMN THING, LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
THE NOTE SAYS YOU HAVE TO GIFT
THE ADVANTAGE TO SOMEONE ON THE
OTHER TRIBE.
SHUT UP.
WHO DID YOU GIVE IT TO
I GAVE IT TO MORGAN.
SHE SEEMS LEVEL HEADED AND THE
KIND OF PERSON THAT WILL RESPOND
TO LOGIC.
THOSE ARE THE KIND OF PEOPLE I
SEE MYSELF WORKING WITH.
I'M TELLING YOU THAT BECAUSE
I'M RELYING ON YOU.
WE'RE AN UNLIKELY COUPLE.
BEAUTY AND THE BEAST.
JACOB DIVULGED EVERYTHING TO
ME.
HIS IDOL WAS FAKE.
I KNEW IT IN MY BONES.
AND THEN HE TOLD ME THAT MORGAN
ON THE OTHER TRIBE NOW HAS HIS
LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
THAT'S HUGE.
THAT IS SOMETHING THAT I CAN USE
TO MY ADVANTAGE LATER ON IN THIS
GAME.
NOW I AM ACTUALLY REALLY
STRUGGLING WITH THIS JACOB VOTE.
HE TRUSTS ME.
AND THOSE ARE THE KIND OF PEOPLE
YOU WANT TO KEEP AROUND.
LONG STORY SHORT, HE'S LIKE, I
THINK I CAN PULL IN JAMES AND
LAUREL, AND, YOU KNOW, WE COULD
MAYBE LIKE THINK ABOUT ONE OF
THE BIG GUYS.
SO HE WANTS TO TARGET MICHAEL.
HE'S TOTALLY INTO LIKE YOU AND
I.
SO I FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD --
HE'S LOYAL LONG TERM.
YEAH.
STEPHANIE WANTS TO WORK WITH
JACOB AND START VOTING OFF THE
BIG PLAYERS.
I WAS SHOCKED AT FIRST.
JACOB IS NOT THE SMARTEST GUY IN
THE WORLD.
HE HAS A LOT OF KNOWLEDGE, BUT
HE HAS NO SOCIAL SKILLS.
AND HE'S JUST ANNOYING.
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO
DO.
YEAH.
HOWEVER, STEPHANIE AND I HAVE
BEEN CLOSE SINCE DAY ONE.
I WANT THE STAY LOYAL TO HER
SOME WHATEVER SHE WANTS TO DO,
I'LL GO ALONG WITH IT.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
I DON'T KNOW, HEY, PROBABLY.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE LIKE,
HE WASN'T REALLY GOOD IN THAT
CHALLENGE, SO WE SHOULD VOTE HIM
OUT.
EXACTLY.
SO STEPHANIE THROUGH OUT MICHAEL
AS A NAME.
YEAH.
SO FAR THE STRONG AND THE
BEAUTIFUL HAVE BEEN RUNNING THE
SHOW.
THEY'VE FORMED A LITTLE BIT OF A
CLICK WITHOUT ME, AND THAT
WORRIES ME, BUT SUDDENLY THE
PEOPLE ON THE BOTTOM HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO FLIP THE VOTE ON
THEM.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE IT'S THE
RIGHT TIME.
GUYS, DO YOU THINK EVERYTHING
IS AS IT SEEMS RIGHT NOW?
I'M REALLY HOPING SOME
HERE'S WHAT IT IS.
EITHER JENNA AND STEPH ARE
PULLING A DOUBLE CROSS ABOUT
JACOB, OR IT'S THE DOUBLE-DOUBLE
CROSS, AND THEY'RE GETTING ONE
OF US.
UH-HUH.
THAT'S WHY I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING THE
PLAY HIM, BUT, YOU NEVER KNOW.
JENNA AND STEPH ARE
SCRATCHING ME OUT, BECAUSE JACOB
IS A SHIFTY GUY AND FOR ALL I
KNOW HE'S TARGETING ME.
AND ALL IT TAKES IS A COUPLE
PEOPLE TO FLIP WITH HIM AND I
COULD BE GONE.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
I'M READY TO PLAY.
IF I GET VOTED OUT BY FRICKING
JACOB, I'M GOING TO BE PISSED
OFF.
Jeff: JACOB BEHIND YOU IS A
TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB IT.
APPROACH THE FLAME.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN THE FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
ALL RIGHT
JAMES, LET'S GET TO THE
CHALLENGE.
BECAUSE THAT IS WHY WE'RE HERE
TONIGHT.
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF DONATHAN,
AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
IS THAT FAIR TO SAY?
I'VE BEEN AN ATHLETE FOR MANY
YEARS, AND TODAY I DID ONE OF
THE WORST THINGS THAT AN ATHLETE
CAN DO, WHICH IS LET HIS OWN
TEAM DOWN.
I HAD A JOB TO CO, AND I FAILED.
I HATE MYSELF, BUT I REALLY WANT
TO PUT THIS LOSS ON ME, LIKE I'M
THE REASON WHY WE'RE HERE.
Jeff: STEPHANIE, JAMES IS
REALLY OWNING IT, WHICH IS
ADMIRABLE, BUT HE'S EXPOSED THAT
HE CHOKED.
THERE IS AN ELEMENT TO ME
THAT GIVES JAMES CREDIT FOR EVEN
TRYING TO DO IT.
BUT IT'S A BIG REASON WHY WE
LOST, AND IN THE END IT KIND OF
PUT US BACK A LITTLE BIT.
Jeff: JACOB, YOU WERE THE
FIRST PERSON TO GO TO GHOST
ISLAND, DID PEOPLE ASK YOU,
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
I WAS JUMPING OUT OF MY PANTS
TRYING TO GET THAT INFORMATION
OUT.
I PRETTY MUCH TOLD THEM
EVERYTHING.
I EVEN TOLD THEM ABOUT MY
OPPORTUNITY OF GETTING AN
ADVANTAGE.
Jeff: LIBBY, WHAT DID HE
SHARE REGARDING THIS OPPORTUNITY
FOR ADVANTAGES HE TALKED ABOUT.
HE SHOWED US THAT HE FOUND A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO THAT SURPRISED US.
Jeff: JAMES, THE OTHER
QUESTION IS YOU REALLY HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT GHOST ISLAND IS ABOUT.
THERE DEFINITELY IS SOME KIND
OF INFORMATION IMBALANCE.
JACOB HAS BEEN THERE AND SPENT A
NIGHT ON THE ISLAND, AND WE
HAVEN'T, BUT HE'S ONE OF OUR
ALLIES.
WE CAN TRUST HIM AND HIS STORY.
Jeff: GREAT PHRASE,
"INFORMATION IMBALANCE."
BECAUSE THAT IS WHERE "SURVIVOR"
OFTEN TIP, THE INFORMATION
IMBALANCE.
SO JACOB, WHEN YOU REJOINED THE
TRIBE, DID YOU FEEL WELCOMED.
I FELT WELCOME TO A
SURPRISING DEGREE.
I EXPECTED A LITTLE MORE
VITRIOL.
IT SAYS A LOT ABOUT MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH THIS TRIBE,
AND IT MAKES ME FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE MOVING FORWARD.
Jeff: SO STILL FEEL GOOD
WITH THIS TRIBE?
ABSOLUTELY.
I STILL BELIEVE 100% THESE ARE
SOME OF THE BEST PEOPLE THAT
HAVE EVER BEEN ON "SURVIVOR."
Jeff: STEPHANIE, WHERE DO
YOU SIT ON THIS IDEA THAT JACOB
HAS, GLASS HALF FULL.
Jeff: IN MY LIFE I AM GLASS
HALF FULL TYPE OF PERSON, AS
WELL.
I THINK THAT'S WHO HE IS AS A
PERSON.
Jeff: JACOB, IS THAT REALLY
THE WAY YOU ARE?
GOD, NO.
I'M A NEUROTIC PARANOID INDOOR
KID.
MAYBE WHEN I COME OUT WITH THAT
KIND OF BRAVADO IT'S SO I CAN
FEEL LIKE I'M NOT GOING TO JUST
DIE ON THE SPOT.
I HAVE A DREAM ACTED GETTING TO
THE END OF THIS GAME, AND TO DO
THAT I HAVE TO FIGHT ALL THE
FEARS THAT COME WITH IT.
Jeff: JENNA, WHERE IS THE
TRIBE RIGHT NOW IN TERMS OF
ALLIANCES?
THIS IS OUR SECOND TRIBAL.
I THINK THERE'S A LITTLE BIT
MORE THOUGHT IN ALLIANCES AND
STUFF LIKE THAT.
WE'RE KIND OF MOVING AROUND A
LITTLE BIT.
SO I THINK THIS ONE WILL BE A
LITTLE DIFFERENT.
Jeff: JACOB YOU'RE SHAKING
YOUR HEAD.
YOU AGREE?
THIS GAME IS BECOMING WAY
MORE ABOUT RELATIONSHIPS AND WAY
MORE ABOUT THE PEOPLE YOU TRUST
AND WAY MORE ABOUT LOYALTY.
Jeff: SO IS THERE ANY
CONCERN, EVEN THOUGH YOU GOT A
WARM WELCOME THAT YOU MIGHT BE
OUT OF A GROUP.
ABSOLUTELY.
FOR ALL I KNOW, THEY GATHERED UP
AND SAID, MAKE HIM FEEL GOOD AND
WE'LL GET HIM NEXT TIME.
I DON'T KNOW.
I HOPE IT DIDN'T HAPPEN, BUT IT
COULD HAPPEN.
ANY WORK I'VE PUT IN TO HELP
MYSELF AND MY ALLIES AND MY
FRIENDS, IT MIGHT ALL BE IN
VEIN.
Jeff: MICHAEL, HOW ABOUT
FOR YOU?
WHAT ABOUT RELATIONSSHIPS
FORMING AND GROWING.
THAT BECOMES A BIG PART OF THE
VOTE.
HE'S A HUGE PART OF IT.
LAST VOTE WAS PRETTY UNANIMOUS.
BUT TWO LOSSES BACK TO BACK, WE
GOT TO START DOING SOMETHING
DIFFERENT, BECAUSE WE DON'T WANT
TO KEEP THIS BAD MOMENTUM GOING.
Jeff: DO YOU TAKE SOME
MEASURE OF COMFORT THAT YOU'RE
OKAY BECAUSE THEY NEED YOUR
STRENGTH?
NO.
I DON'T.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS ALL ABOUT
PHYSICAL STRENGTH AT THIS POINT.
I THINK THOSE DAYS ARE OVER IN
"SURVIVOR."
SO, YEAH, I FEEL A LITTLE BIT
WORRIED.
Jeff: MICHAEL.
DOES THAT CONCERN YOU, BECAUSE
YOU'RE CLEARLY A PHYSICALLY FIT
GUY.
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
HEARING BRENDAN SAY THAT, I SURE
HOPE THAT'S NOT THE CASE, BUT
I'M TRUSTING THE ALLIANCES I'VE
MADE AND THE PLAN TONIGHT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JENNA, YOU'RE UP.
WE HAVE TWO EARS AND ONE
MOUTH FOR A REASON.
LISTEN MORE.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE MICHAEL.
JAMES.
JACOB.
ONE VOTE MICHAEL, ONE VOTE
JAMES, ONE VOTE JACOB.
JAMES.
THAT'S TWO VOTES JAMES.
JACOB.
OH, NO.
Jeff: TWO VOTES JAMES, TWO
VOTES JACOB, ONE VOTE MICHAEL.
JACOB.
THAT'S THREE VOTES JACOB, TWO
VOTES JAMES, ONE VOTE MICHAEL.
MAN.
Jeff: SECOND PERSON VOTED
OUT OF "SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND,"
JACOB.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BY, OH, BOY.
Jeff: JACOB, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
YOU ALL DID GOOD.
Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
Jeff: WELL, WE'RE ONLY SIX
DAYS IN BUT YOU'RE 0-2 AND DOWN
TWO TRIBE MEMBERS.
SOMETHING'S GOT THE CHANGE FAST
FOR "SURVIVOR'S" GREATEST TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR. A SUPRISE
TWIST CATCHES EVERYONE OFF
GAURD. DROP YOUR BOX YOUR
SWITCHING TRIBES. I KNEW I
WASNT GOING TO BE IN POWER THE
WHOLE GAME BUT YOU GOTTA RIDE
THE WAVE. WHAT HAS HAPPEND OVER
HERE? AND GHOST ISLAND IS BACK
IN PLAY. I AM FREAKING OUT.
I PUT SO MUCH WORK IN TO GET
HERE. AND AT THE FIRST TRIBAL
I ATTENDED, I WAS VOTED OUT. IM
EMBARRASSED. I DONT KNOW IF I
EVEN HAVE A GAME TO BE PROUD OF.
DONT GET ME WRONG, IT WAS ALL,
THERE BUT IT WAS ALLIANCES THAT
I MADE UP IN MY HEAD THAT DIDNT
ACTUALLY EXIST.
IT SOUNDS PATHETIC, BUT IT HURTS
ON A VERY DEEP LEVEL.