Previously on Survivor...
After a surprise mix...
Throw away your bandanas!
... Domenick was free
from his worst enemy.
Chris was always after me.
Getting away from him is a relief.
And he was armed
with a real idol, ...
Oh my God !
...of a false idol...
Terrible!
...and the Heir Advantage.
"You can only use it when
there are 13 or 6 people left in play."
And Domenick controlled the vote.
I have the choice
of releasing Libby or Bradley.
At the council,
Domenick made his choice
and broke the divisions by tribes.
Bradley, the tribe has spoken.
There are 13 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
This morning we received a message saying
that we had reached a new
phase of the game. Fusion!
Reach the point
where we're all together
and where the game becomes individual,
it's a real accomplishment.
Now
my efforts to bond
during the mixes, will pay.
I wish I could
do some damage!
Yes !
Seriously ?!
What's going on ?!
Welcome !
As soon as they arrived, I was happy
to see my friend Wendell.
It's good to have a reasonable and intelligent interlocutor .
Older sister !
And then there's Chris,
my nemesis.
He refuses to leave.
But I hope he doesn't want
to kill me at this stage of the game.
"Gather all
of you on the other side of the island,
a celebration awaits you there."
This stage of the game represents...
the hope that I can win.
Being 18, wanting to be
the youngest Survivor...
It's been hard for me so far.
So achieve fusion,
and an idol in your pocket,
for me, it's Christmas.
To eat !
Oh my God !
Oh yeah !
I know it's gonna be the apocalypse
but for me, at this stage,
we are all on equal terms.
Thank you, Survivor gods!
Everyone has a place at the table,
at random.
At each seat: a black bandana.
We are a family,
but as soon as the feast is over,
we will begin to devour each other.
I have something to say.
Yeah !
I have been at Naviti Hotel
since day one.
I cherish the new bonds
I've made,
but above all, I hope to strengthen
old relationships can
no doubt be stronger.
So play with the heart,
that's the main thing!
Health !
I have high hopes
for my second half.
And apparently I have options.
I have a four-way alliance
with Donathan,
I'm glad to see you.
Me too.
Bonus I can stick
with the original Naviti
and have the majority.
But Chris is too unpredictable.
“Life is precious,
use it.
Like LeBron in the Finals,
I will be relentless."
He's still a pain in the ass, sorry.
So if I can get rid of it,
what I've been trying to do
from the start,
That would take a hell of a weight off me.
I feel really bad.
I got back to my original weight!
I lay in the shelter,
and I ate so much
I can barely move or speak.
I put my bandana back on
and he looked different.
Something weird. Well.
I open it and it says:
"Hush! A secret awaits
at the mail tree."
Inside, I'm freaking out.
It's incredible.
Anyone could have
had this bandana.
I am blessed ! This is exactly
the remedy I needed!
Now that we've merged,
someone like me,
athletic and good in trials,
will be one of the first targets.
I must be smart.
People are walking everywhere.
I have to do this without everyone knowing.
"Congratulations, you have found
a clue for an idol,
valid at the next council
and maybe more.
But beware.
The idol is on Ghost Island.
Tonight, a boat
will come to exfiltrate you
for a quick round trip
to Ghost Island.
Will you risk being seen
to gain power?"
And how !
All my life I have found success
by taking risks.
So I'm going to look for the idol.
At this point, you have to put the package.
Especially when you're scary like me.
But at the same time,
can I really get there?
Leaving the island at night
for hours is very risky.
If I'm caught and questioned,
I'm fucked.
How does it feel, eight five,
Navigation contre Rest?
Yes, but can we
stay united between Naviti?
Yes, you know... As long as...
My problem is to settle
my conflict with Chris. Can we?
I'd like to mediate
between you two. Calm the game.
We had to do it before mixing.
Especially if it's just for a vote.
Is there a Malolo
we can all agree on?
Probably on Michael or Libby.
Yeah.
For this vote at least, I
'd love it to be quiet Navitou
and we take out Michael or Libby.
But alas, between Chris and Domenick,
it's the cold war,
the arms race.
And... These two can
blow it all up if they want to.
I just wanted to yell at you,
Dom and you, together,
to see if we could
target a common enemy.
I love Dom. He is my ally.
Maybe I can find a way
to be the bridge between them.
Maybe I'll find out
it's impossible
and only
the nuclear option remains.
Would you like... ?
Dom, what are you talking about?
All the time we've been here...
All this...
Whatever it is,
it goes back to day one.
Absolutely.
And that's unfortunate.
Because the three of us
could have collaborated.
For me, we could even
collaborate temporarily.
We can kill each other later
but right now,
Chris, it's important.
Yeah, I don't know.
If we can protect
each other
and fire someone...
I haven't decided anything at all yet.
And those who are there?
Would one of these three suit you?
Any of them ?
Tell me.
I don't know anyone yet.
I just named three people.
But if you can't say yes...
I can't.
So no agreement is possible.
I'm too sweet to walk.
They want to put me to sleep
to kill me better.
Do you have a mug for me?
We open the wine!
Go on !
I left this thread
as I entered it.
There's been too much turbulence
between Dom and me.
So for me, I have to eliminate
the one that threatens me the most.
I knew it would be
ten minutes of anything.
Let's organize his premature departure.
Let's drink to that!
The talks
came to an abrupt end.
I was ready to work with Chris,
but finished the soft method.
It's the war.
To season 36!
Domenick and Wendell
want me gone.
The only real protection for me
is an immunity idol.
And the idol is on Ghost Island.
Sneaking away without getting caught
is crucial.
It was dark night,
everyone crushed.
It was time
to take action.
Boots already on my feet,
fully equipped, I was ready.
But you gotta be smart,
make sure you do that
stealthily.
I live for these moments.
Fortunately, I left unscathed.
I'm pretty awesome, actually.
Ghost Island
is new to me.
I came
there but never arrived there at night.
Following these torches
is a bit scary.
A little weird.
But I'm ready to find out
what fate has in store for me.
"This is JT's authentic
immunity idol
in Survivor Game Changers,
in 2017."
Great news.
This idol will keep me in play.
"He went to the council
, leaving the idol at the camp.
It was a bad decision."
Damn!
"That night he was eliminated."
I made a very stupid mistake.
I was a little overconfident.
"This tainted idol
has lost some of its power.
It is only valid
at the next council."
It's crazy.
Most idols,
when you have them,
can be used
whenever desired.
But this one is
only good for the next tip.
And then I read something else.
"JT's idol is yours,
safe.
But if you're willing to risk
your vote at the next council,
you can increase its power."
Alright, I'm intrigued.
"Whenever you choose
the right bamboo,
you will prolong
the life of this idol with a council.
You can do this up to 5 times,
or until you lose your vote."
So the game has ten bamboos,
five on each side.
One in two chance every time.
"You can extend
the life of this idol."
If I'm lucky.
But beware.
If I play, it is also possible
that I cannot vote
at the next council.
It's crucial, because I'm trying
to orchestrate Dom's elimination.
I can win or lose.
I start, clearly.
Taking risks
is important in this game.
It's the only way to get to the end.
Alright, let's go! Number one !
Survivor is not designed
to take it easy.
"Congratulation !
Your idol has gained power."
Damn, yeah!
“She is now valid
for one of the next two councils.
Will you put your vote on the line?"
And how !
Let's go on !
I need
as much power as possible,
as long as possible,
in this game.
"No voting."
What a pity.
No voting.
But it does not matter.
I will not vote on this council,
but I have this idol,
usable
at either of the next two tips.
Thank you, Survivor gods!
JT was too sure of himself.
I don't want to be the one who leaves
without having played his idol.
I intend to
reverse the curse.
It will be in my pocket,
ready to turn everything upside down.
Lord !
Hot.
Dom, is this coffee coming?
He works hard !
Chris is grumpy and tired.
God knows why.
But he has no problem
barking orders
while he rests
and perks up.
It's these little things
that I don't understand about him
and hurt me.
Oh, and let's not forget:
he still wants to shoot me!
It is enough for me.
Even though he was super cool,
this rascal wants me dead,
he has to go.
This war,
when will it end?
Ah, very soon!
One of us is leaving.
Very soon. Don't worry.
We have to annihilate idol.
I don't know who has it.
Dom.
He showed it to me.
Really ?
I made the dumbest fake idol
in the world.
And although almost everyone
told her she was fake,
he still thinks
i have a real idol.
I do have a real idol.
And the Heir Advantage.
And also a false idol.
Even if my shell-string
is a bit of a joke,
Chris believes in it.
Are you sure he has it?
Why so many people,
so easily...
No no. Even if he has the idol,
you can only get rid of it
by taking it out by surprise.
You have no idea.
I tried twice,
but we always won.
The only time we could have
was on Ghost Island.
Dom and Chris have been rivals
since day one.
This beach is not big enough
for both.
As soon as one walks away,
the other speaks of him
to whoever is present.
Dom is a loser.
He's an idiot.
It's a joke, this guy.
Because some of the stuff he puts out
is totally ridiculous.
I would love to compare myself
to a Dwyane Wade.
I started from nothing,
and here I am!
Chris needs to show
his greatness to the world.
Life is full of opportunities.
Like D-Wade at his top,
I dive into it with both knees.
I tire. It becomes painful.
OK ?
Yeah.
We agree.
Cool.
Good discussion.
What do you think ?
Where are you, between Dom and Chris?
The only thing with Chris
is that he's a big target.
Yeah.
But after...
I don't think Chris will lie.
But Dom...
Chris, it's...
And you ask him for a trick,
what he will say, he will doubtless do.
Yeah.
That's the only thing. He is loyal.
OK.
And then Dom...
He is super dangerous.
Super dangerous.
Everything will be alright.
We will need a majority.
Yeah.
I believe we are well placed.
Yes.
Ideal day.
Dom and Chris go to war.
It distracts me.
Even from Michael and Libby.
It's incredible.
I've been so
low on the ladder.
Now that I have more power,
it's nice to know
that we have a
lot of control now.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for your first
individual immunity test?
First of all,
I'm taking up tribal immunity.
Merci Kelly, merci Domenick.
Tribal immunity is over!
This is what you want
now.
Attractive.
Individual immunity.
With that around your neck,
you're protected on the board.
Without, you are not.
Are we attacking this first test?
Yes !
Today you will stand
on a narrow beam,
now a statue in balance
on a long pole,
over your head.
Regularly,
you will advance on the beam,
running the thing.
If you fall
or lose your statue, it's lost.
The last person standing wins
immunity, is safe from the vote.
The losers: on the council,
someone will be the eighth person
eliminated from this game.
We draw the places at random
and we get started.
Everyone is in place.
Raise the poles
above your heads.
And this test... is launched.
Your first
individual immunity test
and already the air is hot.
You have
to balance on the beam
while holding
a pole carrying a statue,
with a million dollars at stake.
Things are already moving at Jenna.
It's finish.
Put down the pole, go to the bench.
Donathan suddenly loses his statue.
It's lost.
It can happen in the blink of an eye.
And the wind picks up.
It's lost on Desiree.
Mother Nature is always an obstacle
in Survivor.
Angela loses her statue,
it's lost for her.
You are only nine.
It doesn't take much.
The room for maneuver is zero.
You will stay five minutes
on the first section.
Then you will step on the beam
and it will be harder.
Elapsed Time: 5 Minutes
It's time
to move on to the next section.
You have to do it or it's lost.
You have 15 seconds.
You have to ask yourself:
"How to maintain the balance
advancing on the beam,
knowing that it is getting
narrower?"
Everyone arrived
on the second section, congratulations.
The ordeal continues.
Subitemant, Sebastian lost his statue.
You are only eight.
There is never certainty
on the board.
especially
to the merger.
The only certainty
that's when you have immunity
on the board.
Good. It's time
Elapsed Time: 20 Minutes
to skip to the last section.
Your foot
should touch the red paint
at the very end of the beam,
where it is very narrow.
I leave you time.
Chelsea, there you are.
Kellyn, inches away.
Domenick fails.
No immunity for Domenick.
The others continue to advance.
You have 30 seconds.
C'est bon, Kelly.
Michael fails, it's lost.
Chris fails.
It's lost, no immunity for him.
Wendell, you have to be at the end.
Wendell fails, he is eliminated!
Many eliminated at once.
You are only three.
Kellyn, Chelsea and Libby
are vying for immunity.
After 22 days, the first
individual immunity challenge.
Three women show others
how it's done!
The wind shakes your statues a little...
... forcing you
to work even harder
to balance them.
Things are moving a bit at Chelsea.
Well recovered.
She does not move.
Come on, Chelsea!
It's lost for Chelsea.
You are only two.
The face-to-face.
For immunity.
It is now !
It moves a little
for the statues of the two women.
Libby trembles.
Kelly's aussi.
Here comes the wind again,
who moves the statues
and remind you
to stay focused.
The flags are flying.
More wind, more instability.
And suddenly, Libby loses her statue!
Kellyn wins the first
individual immunity!
Away from the council!
And his legs give out!
Yeah, but you made it!
You won the first!
Kelly's !
In brutal mode!
Brute mode!
Kelly's, venez ici !
My God !
Well done, Kel!
Kellyn, safe on the board tonight,
can't be eliminated.
As for you, after 22 days,
someone will be
the 8th person eliminated.
It won't be you. Cheer.
Go away. See you tonight at the council.
Good job.
Thanks.
Miss Kellyn
brings back the trophy.
I hardly believe it.
So I'm not leaving tonight
but this vote still makes me
very nervous,
because Dom and Chris Noble
tear each other apart.
It is to this council that finally,
the demarcations
will be really clear.
Bravo, Kellyn!
Well done.
It was great.
Kelly won,
I'm happy for her.
But not having the necklace,
I have to come up with a plan.
Are we just gonna... sit embarrassed,
where to start playing?
I go to the well.
Des, are you coming?
Michael? Ready for action?
I decided to take the lead
and take everyone to the well
except Domenick and Wendell.
Question: what do you all think?
I spoke with some.
There is an idol in the game.
We could split the votes,
if you're interested.
Divide between...
Libby was their target.
Doing that would benefit
the whole tribe.
Can we all agree on this?
What do you think ?
We are open, of course.
The idol must jump.
Absolutely.
For me, it's personal, okay?
Dom must go.
Problem: I don't have a vote.
So I shield the plan.
It is very simple.
If Dom plays an idol, Wendell leaves.
If he doesn't play it, he leaves.
Isn't that a great plan
for everyone?
Let's blow up an idol and...
Do you think any of them have it?
Chris' plan is solid.
Domenick and Wendell
are a dangerous duo.
They are smart
and are threats to me.
But is it real?
What to believe? Dom has one
or is Chris lying
to make him a target?
The council will show the truth
of each other's positions,
and if it gets crazy,
I'm ready to play my idol.
Well, tell me, there...
I do not see anyone.
They scattered.
Let Chris go!
He fucks too much the bronx.
Yes.
He must go. Let him go!
When they return from the event,
Chris takes everyone to the pit,
except Dom and me.
So... I'm sick of it.
Enough, man!
Chris' ego is grotesque and out
of control. Let him go!
unite against him
and we'll see who doesn't follow us.
If we can get a majority.
Dude.
Okay, listen to me.
I have an idol.
A real ?
Yes.
If you want to see her,
let's go for a walk.
Useless.
I'm ready to play it today.
Let's do it!
Seen how Chris talks to people,
I can't believe
he can have enough people
to take out Domenick or me.
So maybe I won't have
to play my idol.
But if I feel threatened,
I'll take her out
and gain a few more days.
They're splitting the votes
between Wendell and you.
If we regroup,
we can surprise Chris.
Absolutely. 100 %.
Vote Chris.
OK.
There, we are only four,
but Libby and Jenna want to
vote with us, get Chris out.
No, don't tell them.
Don't tell Jenna and Libby.
They want him gone.
They bluff you.
I don't know who to trust here.
Apparently you could
split the votes on me.
It is an option.
But it shouldn't
be a dictatorship,
rather a democracy.
I swear, I'm voting Chris tonight.
We can take it out.
Then we can live
as civilized beings.
Tonight is war.
And people
have to choose sides.
Chris's or Dom's.
The friends.
Things are clear.
Choosing a side is hard,
but being safe
is very nice. Frankly.
How do you see all this?
Do the boys face each other or...?
Yeah, that's...
Looks like.
If the four of us Naviti girls
vote together,
we can take out one more Malolo.
Who would you target?
Me, Libby.
Because Michael is a blatant threat.
Eliminating Michael
is not very hard to plead.
For Libby, yes.
And she can bond
and go unnoticed.
There's a war going on,
and it's great for me,
because they lose sight of
what is really going on.
While everyone
votes for Dom, Wendell or Chris,
Naviti girls can date
who I want to date.
We have to play it carefully.
Yeah.
This is going to be the hardest part of the game.
If they target me, I play my idol.
Yeah.
I'm not afraid to do it.
I know I know.
It's the evening I've been waiting for.
This rivalry with Chris is going to end.
Again and again he refuses
to bury the hatchet.
This is our chance to release it,
which I've been waiting for since day 1.
There are definitely advantages.
Ghost Island offers a bunch of...
Not just benefits,
but arguably idols.
How many can there be?
I don't think Chris has anything.
I don't know how many relics there are
ready to be played,
but I have the Heir Advantage.
I can play it at 13 or at 6,
and we are 13 in play.
Fear sharpens the senses.
Keep the fear in your stomach,
all the time.
Whether it's me or Chris
leaving tonight,
this is the time
when i'll play it all out
and say, "I'm going to shoot this guy."
I'm a little worried
that not everyone will follow.
If in doubt,
maybe I should play the idol.
But at the same time, I could
stay much longer
if I can pass this advice
and use it on the next one.
Tonight is a war.
It's time to get Dom out.
The animal is injured,
it's time to finish it off.
Chris, take the single unlit torch
.
Light it in the fire.
It is part of the council ritual ,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears, so do you.
Chris. First time on the board.
Is this where the game
really begins for you?
Absolutely. Being here at the council,
I feel more alive than ever.
I know that at some point,
it can represent death,
but experimenting
takes the game to another level.
Donathan. What has changed
in recent days?
now that you are 13?
I was finally able to meet
those I didn't know.
There are the old bonds of the beginnings,
then those of the mixtures.
There are so many relationships
it's stunning.
Sebastian. It's interesting,
this game can be so complicated,
and yet, often,
be played on an impression.
In your normal life,
do you rely on your impressions?
Completely.
It feels like riding
on a fishing boat,
we say to ourselves: "He looks like a jerk,
he looks cool."
And it can be the exact opposite
when we go for a beer with them,
Domenick. It's essential.
Because in this game, you have to be able to
adapt and reassess,
and say,
"Maybe I should talk to him again."
It actually applies perfectly,
Jeffrey,
to the situation
I have been living for 22 days
with my good friend Chris.
Can I give my version?
Go ahead, I don't care.
On day 1,
I made a crucial mistake.
Right now we have a test.
You ask, "Would anyone
have made a different choice?"
I was the only jerk
to raise my hand.
I waited a day
and explained to Chris:
"Look, I said that without thinking."
And his response was,
"Do you have an idol?"
I went,
"Wow! What do you mean by that?"
Him:
"You seem to be after me."
It was almost an interrogation,
more than a conversation.
So, after this "conversation",
I went to find an idol.
What a coincidence !
That he looked for her and found
her right after that, I don't believe.
And shit! So there you go, Jeff...
I don't even hide it anymore.
The. Here it is, friend.
I'm going to put it on, because...
It's the shell.
So I show it to him,
but no way to convince him.
What should I do with him, Jeffrey?
I will say one thing:
tonight is an important night.
It's a showdown!
Yes, for me anyway.
So I put
on my finest attire.
Wow.
Domenick. You captivated
everyone.
Now the replica. Chris.
Yes, Dom showed me the idol.
But then,
returning from Ghost Island,
I find out that they tried
to eliminate Angela
because they wanted to get rid
of my closest ally.
When we were all Naviti.
Hold on. Immediately after mixing,
you went directly
to the Malolo side.
It's not "staying together",
what we wanted.
I was suspicious of him.
Why, when he told you everything?
I understand your frustration.
But it's mostly between Dom, me
and my instinct,
who tells me to beware of him.
OK.
It's crazy,
that everything is on the carpet.
Sorry.
But now that we're
finally here together,
let it be a showdown, fine with
me.
Domenick. Does that mean
one of you two is leaving tonight?
I know I'm in the hot seat,
no doubt about it.
It started when we got back to camp.
Eleven of them left.
Wendell and I were alone.
It was Dom and I in the living room.
What happened ?
Where were they all?
Apparently
they were all very thirsty.
Eleven, in single file,
left to fetch water.
Angela. Is it fair to say,
that we have been kept out
of discussions
that could impact this advice?
Very clearly, Jeff.
And it's easy to say,
"Let's go with this big plan!"
But I don't know how many
smaller plans there are.
So, if I see a majority
emerging, I follow it.
Libby. Who led the group?
Someone must have said, "I'm thirsty!"
Yeah, that guy!
Chris, so.
Chris, are you still the leader?
You were chosen on the first day,
and apparently you are still being followed.
I am at least someone
with whom we get along well.
Maybe they easily discuss
certain situations with me.
Domenick. It's a fear
that Chris and the whole band
do something without you.
Absolutely.
Fortunately, I have this object,
but my friend doesn't.
They could play it tricky.
I might have to decide:
protect him or protect myself?
I don't know more than you.
But I'm really scared tonight.
Libby. What is this revelation
about Dom and Chris
said about the stakes of this game?
So far we are 13.
We form bonds,
we experience alliances.
We all listened to Chris, listened to Dom.
We don't know who we can trust,
who we can no longer trust.
That's crazy.
The stakes are so high!
Kellyn. Only you, at this moment,
are completely safe.
What does it do ?
Everyone knows that in Survivor
the first vote after the merger
is crazy about crazy.
There may be idols,
benefits.
And with such an open council,
I'm glad to know
that it won't be my name
who will come out of the ballot box.
Chris. As the vote draws near,
there is talk of a group of 11,
but in fact, you do not know.
What can you do to make sure
it won't be you?
I try to develop
as much confidence as possible.
The frustrations, between Dom and me,
are frustrations.
It's like that.
At the end of the day, there are
key alliances, real links,
but above all,
you have to trust your instincts.
And I will do it again.
Well, let's see how it turns out.
It's time to vote.
Chris, over to you.
Tear it all down, man!
Thank you, friend.
Nothing against you.
I love you. Love !
It was a pleasure serving you
coffee for 22 days.
See you on the other side,
my brother.
We... have won a lot together.
For that, respect.
But socially,
you don't know what you're doing.
I hope you stop
saying "I" so much
and start listening to people.
Oh yeah, and finally,
someone had to say it,
it will be me:
stop rapping!
You are a shit.
A rap.
You're useless. You can't rap.
Your rhymes are creepy.
Put the mic down, man.
Put down the pencil, man.
Use an eraser.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
OK.
Jeff, Jeff, Jeff!
I have a better idea.
So...
This is the Heir Advantage
of Sierra Dawn Thomas.
In fact, Jacob won it,
first day.
He bequeathed it to Morgan,
who gave it to me.
He gives me immunity
when there are 13 people left in play
or six.
I'm playing it tonight for me, at 13.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
This is the Heir Advantage.
Votes against Dom
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Chris.
Two votes Chris.
Libby.
Two votes Libby, two votes Chris.
Chris.
Three votes Chris, two votes Libby.
Four votes Chris.
Chris.
Five votes Chris.
Six votes Chris, two votes Libby.
Eighth person eliminated
and first member of the jury:
Chris.
Good game.
Seven is enough.
Bring me your torch.
Good luck, brother.
No worries, man.
Good game.
You know I love you.
Oh, the torch!
Chris, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you, Probst.
I appreciate.
It's time to go.
If this advice is an indicator
the course
of the second half of the game,
everyone has an interest in playing
every moment, every day.
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
When you're left out...
I have an idol.
What ?!
Domenick and Wendell
have too much power.
...that we don't know who to trust...
I want to see the ultimate battle.
... you have to keep the objective in sight.
Now
let's move on to the delicacies.
Go ahead !
Wow !
I just got eliminated
with an idol in my pocket.
At least
I didn't leave her on the island.
Clearly, Dom organized this,
and some of my comrades
wanted me out.
JT and Chris Noble,
aka The Noble One: zero out of two.
This idol
is definitely cursed.
This little haunted thing
will give me nightmares for a long time.