Previously on Survivor...
The Malolo lost
their fifth immunity test.
Naviti wins immunity!
Sending Malolo back to the council!
Approaching the board,
Michael and James were in the minority.
I hope to survive this vote.
At the council,
Michael betrays an ally
to stay alive.
James, the tribe has spoken.
But he stayed away.
There are 14 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The advice was totally depressing,
to be honest.
I pulled James out to save myself.
I have to do what it takes
to get out of this.
I am now the last Malolo.
So I dread being next,
because the last three out
were Malolo.
So finding an idol is
the most important right now.
Mike's on the beach?
I believe.
He is surely looking for an idol.
At this point,
it doesn't matter if I'm surprised.
I will be aggressive and
flip the whole island if necessary.
I look
near the mail tree,
I dig under rocks,
one bit after another,
I try to search
every corner of the island
to find something.
He was looking, no doubt.
He is paranoid.
It shows, he runs in the jungle
in search of an idol.
It's three to one.
When I looked
at the foot of this tree,
I found that.
"Congratulations! You have found
an immunity idol."
Oh my God !
"This is the authentic
fake immunity idol
created by Ozzy in the 16th season,
Ozzy hid this carved staff
on the Isle of Exile."
Do your work!
"Jason found her."
And There you go !
I guess
it's the immunity idol.
Believing her to be true,
he promised to save Eliza.
When he showed it to her, Eliza saw
that it was a gross fake."
It's not the idol!
It's a fucking stick!
He's not an immunity idol.
"Eliza was eliminated that night.
And the bad luck continued.
Ozzy was eliminated at the next council,
an idol in his pocket.
Followed by Jason to the next council,
also with an idol in his pocket.
The only 3 players to have ever
touched this stick were eliminated.
But there is a secret
unknown to all.
For 10 years
this stick lived on Ghost Island,
slowly gaining power.
He has now become
a true immunity idol."
I feel
like I've plunged into my television
and taking it
from Ozzy's hands.
And I'm ready
to do some damage with it.
Over here, everyone!
Naviti et Yanuya,
discover the new Malolo tribe.
James was eliminated
at the last council.
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today
you will all pull on a rope,
supporting a disk.
You will collaborate
to stack blocks on it,
writing "reward".
If your stack drops,
you have to start over.
The first two tribes to finish
win a reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Yes !
For the first...
Oh my God !
Steaks, chicken skewers,
a grill to cook them,
spices to perfect the taste.
Lord !
For the second:
more rudimentary,
but not bad.
Chicken skewers.
For the latter: nothing.
In addition, the winning tribe will
send a person
from one of the other two tribes
on Ghost Island.
Big stakes.
Naviti, you are one more.
Who will not participate?
Me, Jeff.
Go to the bench.
Yanuya, who will not participate?
Me.
Get on the bench, Laurel.
The others, a minute of organization
and we begin.
Alright, here we go.
For a reward.
Survivors, ready?
Ready?
You write the word "reward"
with the Ghost Island logo
at the base and top.
And you start at the end of the word.
Backward !
Shoot more, Des!
Communication is the key.
I'm there !
Shoot well!
Slowly.
The more you collaborate,
the faster it will go.
Slowly and surely.
It's easy at first.
It gets harder
when the stack rises.
Let go of the rope a little.
You take it too much!
It's already starting
to look at Naviti.
Oh my God ! It moves !
Gently. Gently.
There you go, good.
Take your time !
Sebastian has Yanuya's "W".
Gently.
Like that !
Keep it tight!
Good, Kellyn.
You next, James.
Michael.
Uh, Michael.
No rush, Chelsea.
Chelsea have
the last two blocks from Naviti.
Gently.
Slowly but surely.
Chelsea, shoot more!
Chelsea places the "R".
It's starting to sway.
Let's go !
The Naviti must start again!
This is an opportunity
for Yanuya and Malolo.
Calm down, friends.
We have time, Wendell.
Take your time !
The Yanuya have a good lead
as Wendell places the "R".
You're there.
One more block to place for Yanuya.
The Ghost Island logo
that goes to the top.
Stretch more, I believe!
Come on, keep going!
You are not stretching enough!
More tense!
Oh my God !
All that Yanuya work!
And they lose it
and have to start over!
Well, we lead, we go smoothly.
It's now Malolo,
for the first time in a long time,
which leads into a test.
Kellyn, lève un peu !
The Malolo must start again!
Everything is still possible!
Bradley steps forward for Naviti.
It darkens.
A risky strategy.
Oh my God !
Will it pay off?
Drop the rope!
Good, Libby!
Chris, more tense!
Yanuya strives to communicate.
Naviti still leads at this point.
Any reward is pleasant.
More of these steaks...
It's grand!
And how, Jeff!
Yanuya tries to catch up with Naviti.
Faster !
The three tribes now know
that in the beginning, we can go for it.
The further the test progresses,
the more time you have to take.
Sebastian comes up with the "E".
It's neck and neck!
You can't beat Kelly.
Malolo takes a long time
with the first letters.
Kellyn, less tense!
It is not!
No need to shoot.
No voltage needed!
I don't strain!
They argue so much
that they do not progress.
You need to speed up a bit.
Yeah, come on!
Yanuya regained the lead,
Naviti on his heels.
Naviti must go
all out!
Over to you, Donathan!
The Naviti balance their stack
with only three people
stretching their ropes.
A risky strategy.
So.
Again, equality.
Wendell really takes his time.
Come on Wendell!
Donathan steps
forward with the last block.
They will try again.
Attention.
Donathan, don't stretch the rope!
Don't stretch the rope!
I don't hold it!
Donathan places the symbol.
Everything looks good,
just come back.
It would be a great victory
for Naviti.
That's it !
Naviti wins steaks
and chicken skewers!
There is one place left.
I adore you, my hen!
It is now
between Malolo and Yanuya.
Wendell has the last symbol.
Soft.
Gently. Its good.
Now the most difficult.
Come back.
Keep the rhythm.
This would mean
another defeat for Malolo.
Tell me when I can let go.
The story of the season, so far.
Slowly.
This tribe could be cursed.
Hold on !
She seems to be.
Malolo must start again.
Come on Wendell!
Wendell, one foot in painted area.
Everyone keep the tension!
A little more.
More than a foot.
Its good !
Yanua wins the reward!
Real food!
Malolo loses once again.
Good. Nice reward for Naviti
and for Yanuya.
A big decision to make.
Naviti, you decide
who goes to Ghost Island.
Either you unanimously choose
someone from one of the two tribes,
either each in the two tribes
will draw a stone.
That is, in theory, someone
from Yanuya could go to the island
without taking advantage of the reward
they have just won.
Very big decision.
Strategy is key here.
First, explain the reasoning.
Ghost Island
is still a bit of a mystery.
We want that to stay the case.
Someone who has been there before
would be a good choice.
The decision is unanimous?
Yes.
So?
Kelly's.
Take your things,
the boat is waiting.
You will come back
for the next immunity.
Naviti, Yanuya,
come get your rewards.
Thanks, Jeff!
It's well deserved.
Desiree, Angela, Michael,
nothing for you. Return to camp.
For the first time here, in this
ordeal, I had confidence in myself.
But Bradley was yelling orders at me,
and even though we won,
Oh my God !
I was boiling inside.
So let him do his thing
and dig his own grave!
I arrive on Ghost Island
for the second time,
in the land of the unknown.
But I have already come.
I just gotta stay calm,
take a moment,
follow my gut,
hoping this is
the best for my game.
"Let the game begin!
Follow the fire."
I open the urn and it says,
"Follow the fire."
My heart is pounding,
I want to vomit.
It's crazy, this feeling
that it's here
what the fate of my game is playing out.
ah ! Zut!
"The Ghost Island Game of Chance.
The odds have increased.
Two out of three hold a power.
Risk your vote to play."
Two out of three chances.
I'm so glad I
didn't play the other time...
On my first visit here,
I followed my gut
and decided to be careful,
not to gamble, to keep my vote.
Now the merge is approaching,
we feel that the game
has already almost become individual,
and being more proactive is essential.
Who risks nothing gains nothing,
I suppose, at this point.
I decide to play.
I just need the
Survivor gods to give me luck.
Please !
This one caught my eye
from the start.
I feel like I'm
unraveling my destiny.
Lord !
What a coward I am!
"You have gained an advantage.
This is the original "vote theft"
used to eliminate Michaela
in the 34th season."
This is the authentic parchment
who got Michaela eliminated.
It was in Game Changers.
"Not chosen
for the reward trial,
Michaela sat on the bench."
So ?
It's jerks.
"Blinded by frustration,
she does not live
advantage at his feet.
Sarah grabbed it and used it
to kill Michaela."
Fourteenth person eliminated and
seventh member of the jury: Michaela.
"This haunted perk
no longer allows stealing a vote.
But you can use
it as an extra vote."
Oh, that's huge!
Thank God I followed my guts,
because having a secret advantage
in your pocket, at this moment,
seems like the right time
where my life in the game will change.
This may be the key moment
where Kellyn goes from being the sweet girl
everyone loves
to the girl
smart enough and strong enough
to go all the way and win the game.
Boom!
For God Sake !
We smoked the other two tribes!
I am very proud of myself.
This is my best moment so far.
This team is indestructible!
Well ! We're eating steaks
tonight, my friends!
Can we free up the coffee table?
It makes me happy to talk about it,
to remember this moment,
because it was great for me.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks.
It was a...
Donathan, can you help me?
Donathan...
Donathan, can you help me move this?
Someone.
I do.
In my normal life,
I have no patience.
So today was:
"Lord, let's eat!"
It is supported on both sides.
So we have to put
those who start on the outside...
Hey, let's light the fire!
It made all the difference.
I thought you wanted to
prepare it first.
It's ready. Let's go!
Good.
For me the hardest part here
is not to
be a perfect asshole.
In my private life, historically,
that's what makes everything screw up.
And after, no way to catch up.
Do I season before cooking?
Just a little, we'll add more later.
Seen.
Is it okay if I put a little
on yours at the same time?
Go on !
It's getting serious.
In effect.
It's incredible.
He's a smart guy
a rather intelligent player,
but unaware
of being a big bastard.
He lets go.
Light.
He's still cooking, but he yells at
me because I didn't light the fire!
"You told me to wait!"
He force-fed me today,
being on my back like that.
He repeated it to me four times!
It pissed me off. I was like,
"Leave him alone!"
I was pissed!
There are three original Navitis:
Chelsea,
And then Libby and me,
original Malolo.
If the Naviti stay together,
she and I are way down.
But I think
we all agree on Bradley.
So if we lose
the next immunity,
I hope Bradley will be the target.
Let's say we lose. We go to the council.
For me, the question does not arise.
We all agree.
Bradley gets snappy,
and people take notice.
Maybe I can work with them
and take out Bradley.
But I don't know if it's worth
doing this now,
because I would like
to stay with the Naviti.
Glad we agree!
It's nice.
You were awesome.
Great job today.
It's better than nothing !
We collaborated well
and we got the job done.
We have to eat!
Yes, we were disappointed
not to be first.
We have the mindset
of a team that wants to win everything.
But at the end of the day, having something
different, appetizing
and nourishing, it's a victory.
Some onions !
Especially for big guys like me
who have to eat.
I love eating !
We won for Nicole.
Great day.
Yeah.
I only have one thing in mind,
every day: my girlfriend, Nicole.
He's
the most awesome person in the world.
Happy birthday, Nicole!
Happy Birthday !
Today
is Nicole's birthday.
So it's hard not to be
with her for the occasion
and to be here.
It's very difficult.
But it motivated me to take the time
to look for something
that will advance my game.
And the food
will tire a lot of people.
So when they sleep
it will be an opportunity to sneak away
in search of wood,
but in reality, of the idol.
As soon as I set foot
on this gigantic island,
I tried to pay attention
to the smallest detail,
to the places out of the lot where
an idol could be hiding, a clue.
There's a lot of driftwood
and dead trees,
but I see a tree
that I had seen before.
A normal tree, but surrounded,
tangled in the bark
of another tree.
I look at it and say to myself:
"If that, it doesn't stand out!"
God's goodness !
I find a small roll
wrapped in green.
Excited, I grab it and open it.
This is a clue for an idol,
with a very basic map.
God's goodness !
Excited by the clue,
I still have to find the idol.
So there's a pair of trees there.
With the mountain there.
And the water.
"Dig at the base
of the tree with crazy roots."
So...
It must be that tree.
Idols are what we want
in this game.
I need it. It is as if...
Now
I have to find her.
It can take me to the final.
Oh my God !
God's goodness !
I pull out this big green packet,
telling me: "That's it, that's it!
It's the idol!"
I open it...
My God !
I find this wonderful.
Thank you Lord !
This is perhaps
the most iconic relic
of the game's history.
"This is the authentic
immunity collar
that Erik gave to Nathalie
in the 16th season of Survivor."
Erik, once again,
immunity is yours.
"Arrived at the final quintet,
Erik won this immunity necklace
ensuring him the final square."
Do you think you can convince
him to give it to you?
Who would be silly enough?!
"But the remaining 4 women
bamboozled him...
Give it to me and...
... so that he gives up his necklace..."
I'm giving Natalie immunity.
"...Then promptly eliminated him."
13th person eliminated
and 6th member of the jury...
Eric.
Bring me your torch.
"But there is a secret.
This necklace lived
on Ghost Island for a decade.
He became an immunity idol
with the same powers
than another idol."
It is no longer
Erik's immunity collar.
He's an immunity idol.
When I saw season 16,
I thought Erik played
like a jerk.
Now, wow!
I have his necklace around my neck.
I could be
in his position at some point.
I will never do what he did.
I have one !
I won't make that mistake.
I'm super excited to have it,
super proud.
I worked hard.
The curse will be reversed.
I can't wait to use it.
Is it quills?
Oh, just hairs.
You just have to watch out
for the junk at the bottom.
Malolo is cursed.
We are the hungriest here.
We won no awards.
I'm starving.
My stomach is in my heels.
Et on perd.
All tests.
It doesn't matter who is in the tribe.
Even if there is a mix, we lose.
It is perhaps the tribe that loses
the most in the history of the game.
Tired of losing.
We should burn the Malolo tag.
You see ? The little banner?
Let's burn it. Lift the curse.
Now ?
Yes !
We have to reverse the curse.
I don't want any remains
of Malolo near me.
It brings bad luck. I do not want it.
There you go, there you go!
Let's lift the curse, seriously!
The curse is broken!
We had
a long series of defeats.
It's hard to get beaten
every time.
But if I keep the faith
through the hard times,
I hope to see the end of the tunnel.
And this is Kellyn,
back from Ghost Island.
Hi Kel.
Welcome !
And the smile?
Come on, lift your hearts!
Go on.
Michael. Seen that out of six councils,
Malolo has known five,
will the curse continue?
We feel good, we are happy
to have recovered Kellyn.
We burned the Malolo flag
this morning, in two pieces.
We are going to tear.
Desiree. Did you burn the flag?
Burned!
The curse is over, we burned it!
It is all good !
Okay, shall we go to the test?
Yes !
First, I take back the idol.
A half...
...and here's the other one.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will swim
to a floating platform.
You will climb it, jump from it
and collect
two sets of floating rings.
Then you throw them
at a floating target.
The first two tribes
to place all their rings there
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers: on the board,
a seventh person
will be eliminated from the game.
The Malolos hope very much
that it will not be them yet.
Yanuya.
Someone will not participate.
It was Laurel the last time.
It will be Jenna.
Naviti.
It was Domenick the last time.
Me.
It will be Chelsea.
You two on the bench.
The others, one minute and we'll get to it.
Alright, here we go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Kellyn is in the water for Malolo,
Sebastian for Yanuya
and Bradley for Naviti.
Sebastian takes the lead.
He climbs the platform and jumps.
Here's Bradley.
This is Kelly.
Go on ! Yes !
Sebastian has his rings, he's coming back.
Bradley has his, he's coming back.
Bradley started
with the furthest.
Seb, throw them!
It will be easier the 2nd time.
Sebastian arrives.
Kellyn brings her rings back.
Go on !
Sebastian is there, you have to go up...
Go!
Chris is in the water for Yanuya.
Bradley returns.
Throw them ahead!
Bradley et Kelly's reviennent
while Chris goes to the rings.
Hoist him onto the platform!
Go, Naviti !
Domenick dives for Naviti.
Kellyn came back for Malolo.
Go, Malolo !
Michael dives for Malolo.
This is Domenick for Naviti.
Neither a dive, nor really a jump.
Michael dives!
That's how it's done in Survivor!
Michael overtakes Domenick
with a superb dive
and reached the rings.
Chris came back.
It's good, Yanuya, go ahead!
Michael was amazing in the water
for Malolo.
The Naviti are dead last.
The Yanuya arrive.
and Chris. Everyone is in the water.
Michael came back.
Go ahead Malolo!
Malolo attempts
to reverse the curse.
Dom! Go on !
The Yanuya arrive. Everyone
must be there before untying.
Domenick came back.
Go ahead, Naviti!
The Malolo are at the top
of their platform.
Desiree is in the water.
The Yanuya untie their knots.
The Naviti are in the water. Domenic...
...jump into the ocean.
Oddly again!
The Malolos struggle
to win an event.
First ring for Yanuya.
The Malolos are there,
they can undo the knots.
The Naviti are there,
they can untie the knots.
Naviti and Malolo try to go up.
Donathan pitches for Naviti.
He places a first ring!
Chris sets up a second
for Yanuya.
Two for Yanuya, one for Naviti.
Malolo returns to his usual place:
the last.
Donathan just misses.
A third for Wendell.
And four for Wendell!
It is launched!
And five!
Yanuya can win now!
Michael scores for Malolo.
Donathan sets up a second
for Naviti.
And another from Michael for Malolo.
Go on !
A third for Michael!
It's disputed!
And three for Donathan!
Yanuya is at five.
And four for Donathan!
Come on, Donathan!
Wendell marque
et gagne pour Yanuya!
It is between Malolo and Naviti.
Fourth from Michael for Malolo.
Equality.
Fifth from Michael for Malolo.
Donathan just misses.
Malolo lost
eight out of nine events.
Michael can interrupt the series
now.
Come on, it's the right one!
And he does!
Malolo wins immunity!
Away from the council!
They erase
the curse that haunted them.
Naviti will go to council
where a seventh person
will be eliminated from the game.
I told you !
Yanuya. Immunity again.
No one will go.
Relax!
The curse is lifted!
Malolo. For the first time
in a long time,
we won't see each other at the council.
Enjoy the evening!
Go away!
Yanuya. No advice,
no one leaves, enjoy!
At the water !
Naviti. Tonight, at the council,
a seventh person will be eliminated.
Go away! See you tonight !
Losing was really tough.
But Bradley disrespected
everyone in the tribe.
Such a person
does not deserve allies.
So I want him out.
I want to apologize
for disappointing you.
I was so...
... exhausted, after swimming.
I was shaking.
I do not know.
We...
We win together,
we lose together, so...
You can't... It wasn't...
Maybe you drank too much coffee.
Lord ! I can't
believe this is happening.
Should I keep this guy?
Bradley constantly takes me high,
as if he was better than me,
than anyone here.
If the pot is empty,
I'd like to put this in it.
I would like to eat my rice first.
Bradley is a pain in the ass.
But apparently
he's ready to go all the way with me.
I need to figure out
what makes sense for my game.
I'm thinking... Libby.
Libby?
Yeah.
Did she have an idol?
So Libby, okay?
How are you, Donathan?
I will talk to Chelsea.
Tonight, we have to choose
which original Malolo
the original Navitis want out.
Donathan is just here
for a beach vacation.
Libby is incredibly attractive,
she smiles and urges you
to buy what she sells.
And it's very dangerous
in Survivor.
Libby worries me because she has already
betrayed the original Naviti.
When Morgan left,
she said,
"Beware of the blonde!"
In effect.
For me, it's very simple.
Everybody votes for Libby tonight.
It's fine with me if it's fine with you.
It was great talking with Libby,
but: "Nice, goodbye!"
I promise you.
It's him tonight.
It hasn't changed.
OK.
Chelsea and Don
tell me to vote for Bradley.
But I'm afraid it's me.
I'm still nervous though.
Have confidence.
I am protecting you.
Donathan and I
are at the bottom of the ladder.
It definitely makes you nervous.
I really want
to stay in the game.
This advice is critical.
Libby thinks we're voting for Bradley.
But we have a decision to make.
Because we are approaching the merger.
You have to start asking yourself
how to survive
and reach the end of the game.
And eliminate Bradley,
it is betraying the Naviti,
the original Naviti.
And it's huge.
Would you rather vote for Bradley or...
We have to think carefully
possible long-term repercussions .
It will be a
last minute decision,
but we must be ready.
Yes.
Here is my dilemma.
I have the choice
of releasing Libby or Bradley.
Libby might be a better choice
because she is very charming.
I've been taken in by Libby before.
I let go of her
and she ushers Morgan out.
The hour is approaching.
Yes.
So I don't trust Libby.
But after the merger,
Bradley 's attitude and irritability
could be disastrous
for me.
So here I don't know what to do.
I need to determine
whether to take this risk before the merger
will pay off.
Domenick. We had
this recurring story
of the original Naviti
against the original Malolo.
Is it still a factor?
Up to a point, I believe.
There was a lot of shuffling,
so new links have been created,
but it is possible
that the original Naviti
collaborate for the future.
Donathan. Does it worry you
that Libby and you, original Malolo,
risk not being able to do anything?
This is my main concern.
They could do it
again the other time
and target Libby or me.
Bradley.
What is the atmosphere of the camp,
with this underlying tension:
"We have the majority,
so it's one of you two." ?
You wouldn't guess
that there is any division
or tension.
The five of us get along wonderfully.
It's almost shocking,
from a Survivor fan's perspective.
We are a very tight-knit group.
Donathan.
Is it a big happy family?
Not that much.
Things have happened before.
We eliminated Morgan by surprise.
I'm sure Domenick
hasn't forgotten that.
Jeff, Donathan is not wrong.
I was totally
taken by surprise.
And it still hurts a little,
because Morgan was a good friend.
Libby. When Domenick says
it still hurts,
are you worried
that he doesn't trust you?
Yes, it's hard to hear that.
I hope I can always
work with him
and forget it,
but I was loyal
to my allies.
I had a connection with Morgan,
but my alliance
was stronger than this bond.
Therein lay my loyalty.
This loyalty, I can easily
give it to another alliance.
But I take my decision.
She seemed right to me then,
it always is,
and it's part of the game.
Bradley. Do you respect that?
She does not deny her vote.
Yes a lot.
But I could counter-argue,
say why Morgan
was not the best choice,
while knowing little
about the dynamics at work then.
It's interesting
that you counter-argue
about something
you admit you don't know!
I will discuss the color of the sky
if necessary!
Is it your nature?
Yes, it comes from the fact
that I love debating.
This is the best way
to have an exchange.
Sometimes it's positive.
Sometimes clearly negative.
But I don't wanna be the jerk
who constantly plays
devil's advocate,
because I hate it,
like everyone else.
Chelsea. Oh, pardon!
I mean, I don't think we
argue much about camp.
At least I don't think I'm a
quibbler.
If we discuss,
I like to bring all the arguments,
it feeds the debate.
But also, Jeff, it's hard to
disagree about something,
but at the same time, you don't want to
be the one causing the conflict.
So often, you have to hold back,
keep quiet,
listen to others even if you do
n't agree, but it's hard.
We want to have balanced people,
who listen to you,
with whom we can discuss,
and also have exchanges.
Chelsea. Is it a fear,
that the behavior on the camp
could cause problems?
Your behavior
always affects you in this game.
If you offend someone,
who knows what impact this will have?
Always be aware
of your attitude towards others.
Libby. As the vote draws near,
what's the argument?
Why
wouldn't the Naviti stay together?
Well,
we're getting closer to the merger.
It's time to start
thinking about the future.
And I want to help build it.
Domenick.
What's your criteria tonight?
There is a lot to consider.
The trust factor,
the compatibility factor,
and also the links that the person
was able to establish on the other side
and
how it can help you later.
Well, it's time to vote.
Bradley, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Two Bradley votes, one Libby vote.
Seventh person eliminated...
Good game !
Three is enough.
Bring me your torch.
Good luck for the future !
Bradley, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Thanks.
The adventure of a lifetime!...
Oh my God ! !
Wow !
That's crazy.
Based on tonight,
tribal divisions weaken,
personal ties grow.
And at only four,
it can be very interesting.
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Three tribes assemble.
Fusion !
For me, it's Christmas!
But a war is raging.
Dom is a loser.
Chris is an idiot.
Dom has always been after me.
But I'm too sweet.
These two can blow it all up
if they want to.
Finally, the limits are clear.
I was taken by surprise, 100%.
But being a super fan, I would
n't have wanted to go out any other way.
I am very confident, sure of myself.
And I can seem a little bossy
to some people sometimes.
I could have done much better.
I believe that...
If I had achieved
fusion, I would have won the game.
So hats off to them.