Previously on Survivor...
Approaching the board,
the Navivi, united,
had a plan of attack.
We divide the votes,
in case there is an idol,
between Michael and Libby.
At the council,
Michael played his idol.
This is not...
...no longer just a stick.
Votes against Michael
will not count.
And Libby was sent to the jury...
Libby, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving the seven Naviti
at the top
and Michael at the very bottom
of the four remaining Malolo.
There are 11 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Laurel, remind me to tell you about
this dream I had.
You and me having breakfast
in a kitchen
and Martin Sheen was your father.
We made great
egg bacon cheese sandwiches
and we ate like animals.
My God !
I'm too hungry !
Everyone is too hungry.
Food is scarce.
This morning, when I woke up, it hit me.
But having an empty stomach,
I know what it is.
I experienced this
when I was homeless.
This experience gave me
what I needed for Survivor.
I use it to hold on
day after day
in order to go to the end.
The plan is to stay united
between Naviti
and take out the remaining Malolo.
But it won't work for me,
because I'm down
at the Naviti.
So... This might
sound crazy to you,
but I'm ready
to take out the Naviti.
How ? We are all for it.
If I don't change anything now,
I will follow the "Welded Naviti"
and the others will control my vote.
I didn't come to Fiji
to do what I'm told
but to make big shots.
And my gut tells me
it's the right time.
We could use Michael
to take out Kellyn.
Then we would take out Wendell and Dom.
They have all the power and know it.
I already know I
can rally Ang and Chelsea.
We would have the majority.
I feel at a turning point
right now.
It suited me pretty well
to go with the Navivi,
to stay with Dom and Wendell.
I kept it a secret the whole time.
But now it is a question
of reversing them.
So I find myself
right in the middle again.
And the choice that I will make
will have a huge impact
on the direction the game takes.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for the reward test?
Today you will be split
into two teams of five.
On my signal, two members
of each team will paddle
to deliver their comrades
of three cages.
Then with the keys
you will release puzzle pieces,
with which you will solve
a giant Survivor puzzle.
The first to finish
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Yes !
The winners will leave by helicopter
towards a superb promontory...
No?!
...overlooking the Fiji Islands.
They will enjoy a picnic there.
Breads, meats, cheeses
and brownies for dessert.
Additionally, the winners will send
one of the losers to Ghost Island.
We're going to do it schoolyard style.
In other words, at 11,
a person will not be chosen
for the event,
can neither get the reward
nor be sent to Ghost Island.
We draw the captains
and we form the teams.
Good, the teams are formed.
An orange, Michael and Sebastian
will rescue Chelsea,
Kelly's
and Jenna.
A violet, Wendell et Domenick
are going to rescue Laurel,
and Angela
Donathan, not chosen,
will not be able to go to the reward
nor on Ghost Island.
On and go!
Survivors, ready?
First you have to free the boat,
front and back.
Then paddle
to the first cage.
Go on !
You have to detach to deliver.
Nice work from Sebastian and Michael,
who lead.
Once at the platform,
someone comes down
and can detach.
Chelsea have no right to help.
It's up to Sebastian to play.
Michael tries to
hang onto the platform.
Dom, get ready to go!
Wendell jumps on the platform,
but Domenick will have to come back.
He is in trouble
and the boat continues...
Come back !
... to move away from the platform.
Good !
Chelsea is free.
The Oranges
go to their second goal.
Laurel is free.
Domenick struggles to bring the boat back
to the cage.
The Oranges took the lead.
Again,
good strategy from the Oranges.
Michael tries
to hold on to the platform.
Chelsea and Sebastian are
working to free Kelly.
Straighten the boat!
Again, the Violets
are in trouble with the boat.
Go on !
The Oranges leave
more quickly this time.
Kelly's est libre.
Give everything, it's not over, come on!
The Violets are in the second cage.
Sebastian
quickly leads the Oranges
at the third and last cage.
Come on !
Quick !
Desiree is free,
she has to board.
Take an oar!
Jenna is free, the Oranges
can go back to shore.
The Violets still have
one person to deliver.
Come on, together!
On the right side !
The Oranges have a good lead.
You have to moor!
I stay on this side
to limit the tremors.
The Violets reach Angela.
Wendell will untie the knots.
Its good ! Now,
someone release the coins!
Michael has the three keys to the Oranges.
Stay calm !
The Violets are still trying
to free Angela.
We are almost there ! Down, down!
The Violets freed Angela.
They can go back to shore.
Michael opened
the third padlock.
Oranges can
start carrying
those very heavy puzzle pieces
to the arrival platform,
where they will complete the puzzle.
Here are the Violets,
collaborating to close the gap.
It must be moored!
It's good, go ahead!
A person with the keys
now.
Oranges are already carrying
puzzle pieces,
trying to build on
their lead.
Wendell opened
the third padlock.
It's now the race
to get the pieces.
Oranges are good!
Attack the puzzle!
The Violets still have
several pieces to bring.
Big lead for the Oranges.
There, this one goes!
Can the Oranges finally
reverse the curse?
The Malolo have won almost nothing
this season,
whoever their members are.
Upright.
Violets are good! Attack!
Exhaustion is already setting in.
It takes a long, narrow room.
Michael takes charge
for the Oranges.
If he is right, he will lead his team
to a great victory.
Yes, yes!
It... goes there.
Domenick
issues orders to the Violets.
He seems to know what he wants to do.
The Oranges
continue to place pieces.
Why does it say "trick" again?
Twice...
The Violets try to come back.
They move a lot of pieces.
Yeah, that's wrong!
But does this lead
to decisive actions?
There are unnecessary parts?!
It's a decoy!
There are decoys!
This one goes there. Bring her!
The Violets increase the pace.
They know they have to speed up.
"Dominate"! Look !
Why does it say "Survivor"
twice?
There is an extra piece!
There are two extra pieces!
Yes, it goes to the bottom right,
you're right!
The Oranges are close,
if they're right.
The Violets see
that it escapes them.
It would be the Oranges' first win
in a long time.
They think it's good.
And it is!
Reward for Sebastian, Jenna,
Kellyn, Chelsea et Michael !
Bien. Kellyn, Michael, Chelsea,
Jenna, Sebastian,
a beautiful afternoon awaits you.
Before leaving,
you send one of the five losers
on Ghost Island.
You know the music.
Or a unanimous decision,
or they pull the stones.
Donathan is not eligible.
The stones ?
Yes.
The stones.
Chance decides.
Good.
Reveal.
Angela goes to Ghost Island.
Throw the stone, take your things.
Angela leaves for Ghost Island.
Stay strong !
You will return in time
for the next immunity.
Bien. Kellyn, Michael, Chelsea,
Jenna, Sebastian,
a beautiful afternoon awaits you,
come and get the picnic.
Let's go, and have a nice helicopter ride!
Have fun !
Enjoy!
It is deserved !
Eat!
Donathan, nothing for you.
Take your things, leave.
After the last tip, I
clearly think I'm the biggest target.
And that won't change much,
unless I mess it up a bit.
This award
is the perfect opportunity
to identify flaws
in the Naviti
and get back into the game.
Is it me, or does it look like
we're coming to Jurassic Park?
Very cool !
I have never seen anything
so terrible!
Flying in a helicopter is incredible.
The doors were open,
we were talking,
we were joking all along.
I smiled ear to ear.
I still smile
just thinking about it.
No need for food
when you have a trip like this.
It was great.
Lord, look
at all that salmon, all that...!
My dream is coming true!
The biggest sandwich of my life.
A little toast?
Health !
A sandwich on a promontory!
The fact of having seen seven votes
at the last council
made the reward
even better,
because people are more open to rewards
talking strategy,
discussing options.
This may well be, seriously,
one of the best meals of my life.
That being said,
I know I'm
at the very bottom of the scale,
but now that I'm
essentially powerless,
I hope you will see
some value in me,
for the future, as a reinforcement.
I just wanted to say that.
I'm here, I'm a loyal vote.
One day after another.
Who knows what tomorrow will bring?
Michael says, "I'm ready
to work with you."
And Sebastian and Chelsea
were kinda...
"Mmh! Well, you never know!"
This is a strong sign
that the Naviti remain united
and that neither of them will deviate
from the plan that I want to apply
let Michael be next.
This sandwich
is as big as your head, Kellyn.
Everything continues to go well for me.
I feel my game
picking up speed.
So everything seems to be rolling,
on this promontory
in the middle of Fiji.
Go to Ghost Island
without knowing exactly where I'm going
increases my level of anxiety.
But at the same time,
I wanted to experience this island.
It wouldn't be Survivor
without experiencing every aspect.
And if I have a slight chance
of having an advantage,
so yes, of course I'd rather
be here than at camp!
"Let the game begin!
Follow the fire."
"The Ghost Island Game of Chance.
The odds have increased.
Two out of three hold a power.
Risk your vote to play."
Well... We have the majority.
Losing my vote
wouldn't matter.
To have a two out of three chance
of having an advantage is huge.
The original Naviti have the majority
and should stick together.
So it's trying.
I'm going for it.
Go for the third.
"No voting."
Well... It was a matter
of luck and I ran out of it.
I was really disappointed
to read "No vote".
I thought,
"Did I make a bad decision?"
Because if it speaks strategy
in my absence
and the alliance is cracking,
my "no vote"
could screw up my game.
Are you open
to what Des was talking about this morning?
It doesn't really excite me.
What do you think ?
I'm open to it.
Well... Seems safer
with Dom and Wendell.
I'm trying to decide if I want to follow
Des's plan to attack
the big threats from Naviti.
But in truth, I
trust Dom and Wendell much more.
than at Des.
So I decided to show them:
people at the bottom of the ladder
no longer want to be
and try to mount a shot.
Good. So...
I don't know what's going on with Des.
She tries to rally
the four Malolo against you.
Which I don't want to do,
of course.
So the plan...
She and Chelsea want to take you out.
Namely, me...
And Wendell and Kellyn.
Understood.
Oh my God !
Apparently
some of the Naviti girls
decided they wanted to
take their destiny into their own hands
and turn
against the most dangerous.
It does not surprise me.
Makes sense
that these weaker Navitis
be ready to take a hit.
And if they are ready
to act against the family,
I have to fix it.
Thank god you're here!
What's going on ?
So... I learn from Laurel,
believe it or not,
that Des and Chelsea
will work with the four Malolo
to take us out,
you, me and Wendell.
They realized
they had to make a CV,
start taking out the big players.
Impossible.
Why ?
I do not believe it.
I've been with Des since the beginning.
I come back
from the most beautiful day of my life
and Dom whispers to me,
"You're in danger."
The people I'm closest to
are after me.
If Chelsea is against me,
she made fun of me
all day.
We have to do something.
That does not make any sense.
Des, Chelsea and I
are rock solid.
They would never betray me like this.
Someone is clearly trying
to hijack Michael's target.
And I tell you,
it will never happen.
If only they broke up...
They want me gone at all costs.
If you have another idol,
it's time to tell us.
Eh not.
But there just might
be one here.
I would go get her.
You want ?
I'm at the bottom,
I'm not afraid
let it be known that I am looking for an idol.
Surely they all expect it.
And Donathan wanted to search too.
I didn't want
to search with him.
It's one of the worst mistakes
you can make in this game,
to share, with anyone,
that we have an idol.
But I'm at a point
where either I go to the next vote,
or I do my best
to find one.
It's not true !
Oh my God !
"Congratulations.
This is Scott's authentic idol
of Survivor 32, Intelligence vs.
Muscles vs. Beauty, in 2016."
Here, my friend!
"Scott trusted Tai,
thinking that he would combine the idols
to form a super-idol."
"A super idol can be played
after the votes are read."
"So Scott didn't play his idol."
Ninth person eliminated,
fourth juror...
"And Tai changed his mind."
You don't?
No.
Wow.
"It's considered one
of the worst betrayals in Survivor.
This tainted idol
has no more power in itself,
but combined with Tai's,
she becomes a true idol."
Tai's idol is hidden
under the center of your shelter.
Can you
reverse the curse?"
And then I'm freaking out!
I have to dig under the shelter
to find that other idol
which should be associated with it.
How the hell was I going to do that?
So I landed
right in the middle of the shelter.
What's up, big guy?
Do we make rice?
They have already started.
I felt
like everyone was looking at me.
I was trying to look around.
When will someone
come out of the woods?
get out of the ocean?
Should I
tie my hair or not?
It's good there.
Really ?
You'll tell me, otherwise, huh?
It was the most stressful thing
I've done so far.
There's a fucking idol there!
If I can have it...
I want to remain discreet.
Finally,
Laurel came to me.
Then Jenna and Michael.
We are there, and I say:
"You have to help me!"
There's an idol down there,
if I can reach it.
What is it?
An idol.
Did you find it?
I'm trying !
So I get up and go get
my canister so as not to look suspicious.
Fortunately,
Domenick ends up leaving
and we had a moment together.
And finally, I got it.
I was... Yeah!
I found something
that will help me,
to save the Malolos
or to save me.
These two beauties are assembled,
ready to serve!
Hoping
they reverse the curse!
Over here, everyone!
And this is Angela,
back from Ghost Island.
Welcome !
Are we going to the immunity test?
First of all, Desiree
brought your necklace back, Angela.
I take it back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will
balance a marble
on a disc attached to two strings.
Regularly, you will move
your hands back on the rope,
increasing the difficulty.
If your ball falls,
the event is lost.
The last person to hold
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
The losers: at the council,
a tenth person will be eliminated
and will become the third juror.
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Good. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go! This test is on.
You will stay in this position for
ten minutes.
From the outset,
everyone is very solid.
Nice recovery from Wendell.
Wendell loses his ball.
First eliminated, no immunity.
You are only ten.
Jenna loses her marble!
Things are moving at Des.
She loses her ball.
Could it be contagious?
Laurel loses her marble!
Angela perd sa bille!
Michael's ball moves quickly.
Can he save her?
Eh yes !
Wow !
Within seconds,
we lost half the group.
You are only six,
after less than a minute of testing.
It's a reminder not to be
swayed by the anxiety of others.
Donathan's ball moves.
She falls !
You are only five.
In the past,
this ordeal lasted a long time.
But maybe not today.
Chelsea, solid as a rock.
Suddenly,
Domenick's ball falls, he is eliminated.
In two minutes,
we have already lost seven of the ten players.
I have never seen that.
Il reste Chelsea, Sebastian, Kellyn
and Michael, for immunity.
You must remain present
in this ordeal.
Sebastian's ball
begins to move.
Nice recovery.
He refocuses her.
The closer you are to the center, the
more leeway you have.
Only one minute left in this round.
You just need
survive a little longer
and you qualify.
And suddenly, Michael's ball
moves, he is eliminated.
You are only three!
Wow !
Take this into account!
You can be eliminated very quickly.
Michael was perfectly still.
The slightest movement,
and this ball starts.
This first round
will last ten minutes.
Then we'll descend
along the rope,
increasing the difficulty.
ELAPSED TIME: 10 Minutes
The hands are now
further back on the rope.
It's much more difficult.
And it will last 15 minutes.
Someone is going to lose very quickly
now.
Chelsea's rope wiggles a bit.
Forearms hurt.
More movement
from Sebastian.
New beautiful recovery.
Tonight, someone will leave
and become the third juror.
Kelly's perd sa bille.
She is angry.
You are only two.
It's face-to-face.
Chelsea et Sebastian
are vying for immunity,
security on the board.
Bon sang!
Fatigue sets in.
The body begins to shake.
Sebastian's marble
suddenly begins to move.
He is on the verge of disaster.
But he holds on.
Sebastian moves again.
Can he still save her?
Yes ! It's the second time.
And three.
Sebastian perd said beetle!
Chelsea
win individual immunity!
Third woman in a row...
Well done, Chelsea!
...to wear this necklace.
Nice fight!
Chelsea, come here!
Good job.
Individual immunity is up to you.
The women continue
to dominate the individual events.
Third female victory in a row.
You are safe tonight.
As for you, alas,
after 27 very rough days
in this game,
the dream of going all the way
will fade away for one of you.
At the council, tonight, someone
will be the 10th eliminated and the 3rd juror.
It won't be you. Cheer.
Go away. See you tonight at the council.
The plan, from the start,
was to eliminate Michael tonight.
But I strongly believe
that the puppets
are getting together.
We must be prepared and anticipate,
before being had.
Well done, Chels.
It looked like a statue.
Brute mode. Angry.
Women provide.
Well done, ladies!
The immunity test
went perfectly.
Kelly's a perdu.
Now
I can apply my plan.
Because Kellyn is dangerous.
She has good relationships with
people, a great personality...
And she plays much deeper
than anyone imagines.
If I'm with Kellyn
in the final three,
she wins hands down.
So she has to go.
What happened yesterday ?
On the field?
Yes, something?
Dom makes me nervous.
He is perpetually paranoid.
I got this far
trusting my guts
rather than listening to others.
And Dom has been paranoid about every vote,
and he's trying to drag me into this.
It will not work.
Dom was freaking out
when I came back yesterday, and...
What about ?
That you and Chelsea
were after me.
This morning, I said to myself:
"It can't be
what Des and Chelsea want to do.
I've been with these girls
since day one."
Would it come
from Laurel or Donathan?
Laurel told Dom, who told me.
I think she's starting...
She wants to mess things up.
It was such a good plan!
I've been patiently waiting for this opportunity
and Laurel screwed it all up!
Why ?!
Kellyn would have been the best
surprise elimination in history.
But this plan
just blew up in my face,
and I'm furious!
So, I said the plan
would be to vote Kellyn out.
But you told Dom
I was after Kellyn.
Now everyone is freaking out
and looking at me because you mentioned me.
I was pissed!
I don't know if I can
trust them now.
At this point, the plan
is to take Michael out again.
But first I have to
cover my tracks.
I don't know why you say that.
I work with you.
Don't make up a story.
I'm not
trying to push you under the train,
but don't do it to me either.
I don't know how,
the shenanigans of Des
fall on me.
Des asked
why I was screwing up the plan.
And as soon as Wendell arrived,
she changed her story
and suddenly it was,
"We never had this discussion."
Why are you lying?
It is not known
if she proposed this move.
I was there, Wendell. If ever.
I got to the middle.
I don't know the context.
Suddenly, my game explodes in my face.
And it's his word against mine.
She yelled at me in
front of everyone, said...
Said I didn't have
a talk with her
where five people
wanted to release a Naviti.
Everyone know that I'm not lying.
OK.
Anything else on this?
Nope ? Good.
One of the Malolo leaves.
Just ? Good.
Hi, how are you ?
What she is doing makes no sense.
There is clearly something going on
with Des.
At this point,
I believe she intends to betray me.
So the big players have to react
before something happens.
The dynamic has clearly changed.
Yeah.
So it seems to me
that the strong must unite.
I'm ready to commit
to something, you know?
I'm worried again,
for tonight.
Having played my idol,
I am unprotected.
My worst nightmare.
Fortunately, things have changed.
The alliance of the seven Naviti cracks
and is about to fly apart.
The conversation took place.
What talk?
People saying they want to join us.
To eliminate whom?
Kelly's.
Merci.
Why ?
You are the most dangerous.
Bullshit !
Des, what's going on?
Honestly, I swear to God
I didn't say that.
Why would I leave
the majority camp?
I'm trying to determine the truth.
Hard when the story is changing.
Kellyn. I am loyal
and will vote as we always do.
Laurel tells me one thing.
Des told me another.
And I can't
figure out who's telling the truth.
But anyway,
my guts tell me
that now is not the time
to blow up Naviti.
I need
you to tell me something.
Do you believe Laurel or Des?
Because...
I want Des out.
You know, Dom, us girls,
we followed your plans, those of the guys.
And we want Michael out.
Good. This evening ?
Now !
Now.
Kelly's me met la pression.
"Dom, you're paranoid.
This time, it's up to us."
It pisses me off.
You say you won't make
an alliance of the big guys,
but here you are suddenly
great friend with Michael?
You see
how that can disturb us a bit?
It's going to go downhill here.
I have to trust my instincts.
And I feel
like Laurel is telling the truth.
Some here want
to take over the game.
Kellyn and I have to get together,
or we're all dead.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Libby,
eliminated at the last council.
So, 27 days!
Donathan. Is the pressure mounting,
the workforce shrinking?
Oh yeah.
Today was... Bam!
It was hot, ready to jump.
What ?
Desiree.
She learned something involving
Laurel from the Arabic phone.
and it was fireworks.
Desiree.
"Fireworks" is serious business.
When your name is mentioned,
when you feel your back against the wall,
there will be fireworks.
Did we mention your name?
Yes.
And I knew it was from Laurel.
So I didn't procrastinate.
I went to talk to the source.
She says she came to talk to me,
she actually yelled at me.
It was not a discussion,
but an attack, in front of the tribe.
Her back is against the wall
because she was caught lying.
Hence his reaction.
Lying about what?
Desiree approached
the four Malolos and said
que Domenick, Wendell et
Kellyn ménent la danse,
She and Chelsea and Angela
are down, don't wanna be
and therefore wanted to
do a hit with us.
I confirm.
Can I answer?
Still.
Not liking
endless discussions,
I will only say it once.
After that, I'll be done.
I never said I felt
at the bottom of the ladder. Never.
Hon-hon, darling.
You told us you
and Ang were downstairs.
That you were willing to work
with us to get Kellyn out.
Nope ! Are you listening to me or what?
Can you look Kellyn in the eye
and tell him that didn't happen?
Yes ! I've already done it !
Several times !
I haven't had the opportunity
to express myself, and I would like to say
that when Des came to Laurel,
it was just the Malolos.
She accused Laurel
of screwing up the plan.
And when Wendell arrived...
He was there from the start, next door!
That's crazy.
In the middle, Wendell arrived,
and she acted
like nothing had happened.
A player at the bottom of the ladder
trying to mount a shot.
You are at the bottom of the ladder,
and you are still there!
Chelsea.
You are also in the middle of it all.
It's fun, because I feel good
in my alliance.
I think they're trying
to destabilize the Naviti.
'Cause they can't hope to progress
only if the Naviti divide
and are no longer united.
Domenick. Desiree is adamant
she is telling the truth.
And Laurel, Jenna, Donathan and Michael
are categorical:
they tell the truth.
And the craziest
thing is that each of them
look you straight in the eye
and convinces you
that the truth comes out of his mouth.
Wendell, that's tricky, right?
Because you know
nothing but your truth.
It's difficult, because there are these people
with whom we have worked for a long time,
but comes this information
which leads you
to doubt your own family.
So I'm here, I'm listening,
I observe, I try to have
the end of the story.
Michael. Despite this attempt
to discover the truth,
someone is going to leave.
Yes. I am not reassured,
for some advice, already.
I'm glad something
blows it all up,
but my heart
is still pounding.
Donathan.
How do you feel ?
This may be the only opportunity
for the Malolo
to change something.
Exactly. Hence my annoyance.
Because I know what has been said.
These discussions have taken place.
So I'm going to say it: damn, yes!
The truth will set us free.
Saying that is fine,
but the result could be
let one of you four go.
Clearly.
Laurel. So you hope
they doubt their ties.
It's your only chance.
Yes, it would be great if the Naviti
listened to what was going on,
but they still have
this "sect" side.
And I'm frustrated,
because everything they said is true.
Kellyn.
It's kind of the perfect crime.
There are two versions,
both very plausible.
Only one can be true.
And if you betray Naviti,
you could
betray someone who was loyal.
All day
I played Sherlock Holmes
and I feel like Helen Keller.
But I understand
what the four Malolo are saying.
Whether it's true or not,
I approach it like a detective,
researching what happened,
listening to everyone,
to vote based
on who I think I am
best for me
and those I work with.
Desiree. At this point, your best
argument might be to say:
"Do you really want to
disturb the Naviti septet
based on speculation?
I said that all day.
I can only hope
that fate is on my side,
and let's vote!
Let's vote!
You are ready to vote.
Good. It's time to vote.
Jenna, over to you.
I hope it won't harm me.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Desiree.
Two votes Desiree.
Three votes Desiree.
Desiree.
Four votes Desiree.
Michael. Four Desiree votes,
one Michael vote.
Michael.
Two votes Michael.
Five votes Desiree,
two votes Michael.
Tenth person eliminated
and third member of the jury...
Desiree. Six is ​​enough.
Bring me your torch.
Desiree, the tribe has spoken.
Ladies,
better keep winning!
The lesson of this advice
is perhaps:
whether you lie or tell the truth,
if you do not have
a relationship of trust,
you will never finish.
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
A suprise...
Two people
will be eliminated tonight.
Oh my God !
... generates lies...
I love you.
I lied well.
Donathan is an idiot.
... and deceptions.
Michael would have an idol.
He does not have it.
If I do that,
that'll be really cool.
They knew I was lying.
Damn it ! I gave everything.
I tried
to play the comedy at best.
What a pity, I was almost there!
Kellyn was just the first.
I had plans, baby. Plans.
And Laurel screwed it all up.
My faith. I trusted
the wrong person!