Previously on Survivor...
Approaching the board,
Desiree was ready
to betray her alliance.
I'm ready
to take out Kellyn, Wendell and Dom.
But Laurel
warned Domenick of the mutiny.
Des tries to rally
the four Malolos against you.
Oh my God!
It's going to go downhill here.
At the council,
Domenick, Wendell et Kellyn
struck first.
Desiree, the tribe has spoken.
There are ten left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
The council was one hell of a show.
It was quite a challenge to determine
who was telling the truth and who was lying.
Laurel told me
that the Naviti girls
wanted to eliminate
Kellyn, Wendell and me.
Luckily she was there!
That damn smoke!
I want...
...just kiss you and thank
you for saving my ass.
Thanks for believing me.
Listen...
If you hadn't done
what you did,
she would have jumped,
then Wendell and me.
And I would be alone.
I wouldn't be here anymore.
I appreciate.
I am with you.
For the first time, I'm really
happy with my place in the game.
I think I've secured protection
of Kellyn, Domenick and Wendell
because I saved them tonight.
My apologies for doubting you.
You had your reasons.
Yeah. No, it seems to me
that even for this vote,
it solidified your position,
seeing how it went,
with a good group.
Even though Laurel saved me,
I'm still not sure I
want to work with her
for the sequel.
The good news is that Naviti
always has the majority.
And that's how I'll go to the end.
With the Naviti welded.
What a day!
If we find another ripe papaya,
we should make fruit rice.
Eleven days.
Much remains to be done.
The finish line is in sight,
Yeah, that's crazy.
We must not betray ourselves.
I promise.
Alright, my brother.
It will work for me
only if we think together.
But we can. We can.
My alliance with Domenick
is obvious to everyone.
It's obvious. It is known, we have already
been targeted, nothing new.
But I don't think people
realize that Laurel and Donathan
are also with us.
So we are discreet.
This is our best strategy
to go to the end.
Dom. If we take it out on each other,
we will both die.
Yes.
You understand?
I agree 1000%.
We agree.
It is unthinkable.
My relationship with Wendell is crazy.
We are very good friends,
but i am here to earn money
for my family.
So if it means
breaking that bond with Wendell,
it's a risk I'm
willing to take when the time comes.
I'm going to lie down for a moment.
Yes.
I already have an idol.
But Michael played one
a few days ago.
So if there's a new one here,
I plan to find it.
I can't give up.
I have to do this,
for my wife and my children.
I have lived on this camp
since day one.
So I know
the places on the beach
where I can look
for trees that look suspicious.
Or rocks
that seem to be placed abnormally.
This is my advantage
over some other players.
And, passing again next to this grove,
I lower my eyes...
I see this coconut with an emblem.
And I knew I had hit the nail on the head.
Its weight suggests that
it contains something solid.
I can't wait
to open it.
Oh my God!
I need to get rid of this quickly!
"Congratulations! This might
empower you,
but maybe not
the one you expect.
This is the real fake idol
David cheated on Jay with
in Season 33,
Gen Y vs. Gen X."
Wow! In fact, this grove
reminded me of season 33.
"Having reached the final sextet,
Jay did what you just did."
Those idiots didn't see her!
"He picked up a coco
and found David's false idol."
Thanks!
And here's another!
"Believing her true..."
You have to be faster!
"...Jay let his guard down.
A fatal mistake."
This is a work of art.
But... not an immunity idol.
"And Jay was eliminated that night."
Oh my God!
"But this tainted idol
did not become a real one.
Since she has no power,
the curse cannot be reversed.
Your chance to gain power
depends on your ability
to trick another player.
Are you smart enough
to do this?"
Let's plan this.
David cheated on Jay with this,
and Jay walked out. Very much.
I hope I can do the same.
Am I just gonna hide it somewhere
or find
out how to target a specific person?
No one can do that
better than me.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First, Chelsea,
I'm taking the necklace back.
Thanks.
Okay!
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today
you will support a bar,
jamming a bullet
between two jaws.
If you release the pressure,
the ball will fall
and it's lost.
And today
there is a twist.
Because it's not a...
...but two people...
My God!
...who will win immunity.
and two people
will be eliminated tonight.
Because there will be two separate councils.
Oh my God!
My God!
Here's how it will work.
We are going to draw lots for
two provisional tribes.
Five Oranges, five Violets.
The last Orange that stands
wins immunity,
is safe at the council of Oranges.
The Last Violet That Holds
wins immunity,
is safe in the council of the Violets.
So two people will leave.
And, further incentive
to hold on,
the last of you ten to hold
earns the right for his tribe
to go to the council last.
This tribe will therefore know
who left first.
Oh my God!
Good. Hit or miss.
No Ghost Island today.
There are enough issues.
We will draw the tribes by lot.
On and go.
Well, the two tribes are formed.
In one, in orange:
not Kelly's.
All clash,
one of the five will leave tonight.
In the other group:
Jenna and Donathan.
You too
only clash with each other.
One will win immunity,
one will leave.
Grasp your handles.
Lift.
Everyone is in place,
the test is launched.
New test
and new twist
for Survivor and its 36th season.
Everything rests on your arms.
If you release the pressure,
the handle will go down,
your ball will fall
and you will be on the bench.
Only five people per tribe.
Immunity is key tonight.
Kellyn's first foul.
The slightest relaxation
in the pressure,
that's all it takes.
Kellyn releases again.
First eliminated.
No immunity for Kellyn tonight.
It is a misleading test.
As long as you push,
you'll hold
those jaws shut.
Michael loses his ball,
he is eliminated.
No immunity for Michael.
Michael goes to the bench.
It can happen as quickly as that.
There are three Oranges left.
The five Violets are still there
and seem solid.
The pressure is going to intensify.
Because if you let go a bit
and the ball starts to go down,
it becomes all the more difficult
to maintain it.
And suddenly, Donathan,
a little movement and it's over.
More than four Violets
and three Oranges.
Laurel loses pressure,
ball gets closer
gradually from the end.
Laurel loses her ball,
she is eliminated.
More than two Oranges.
side by side, vying for immunity.
You won't beat me.
Whether.
I'm going to win.
It discusses!
A little further, in purple:
and Jenna
are vying for immunity.
I am in pain.
Hold on!
Shit!
Sebastian's first foul.
Jenna's first foul.
And another.
Sebastian and Jenna, a danger.
Sebastian is eliminated.
Jenna tries to adjust.
No, it falls, it is eliminated.
More than two in each tribe.
Immunity for Domenick or Wendell,
and for Chelsea or Angela.
She could
be worth a million dollars.
Damn, yeah!
You've been here 15 minutes.
Wendell's arms are shaking.
Domenick's forearms move.
did not move
at all.
Chelsea, all of a sudden,
his ball starts to move.
Chelsea struggles to hold on.
She stayed strong for
a long time.
Her whole body is moving now.
But she's holding on.
Suddenly, Angela loses her ball!
Chelsea
win individual immunity!
And There you go.
Cheer!
Finished for Chelsea.
In other words, the Violets
will go to the board first.
No big deal, Chelsea.
But she is safe.
And now
we have a face-to-face.
Not only
will you gain immunity,
but you will go to the council
second,
with the advantage of information.
I want this necklace!
You'll have
to last another hour then.
No problem.
We stay.
It's nothing. He is stubborn.
I am stubborn?!
My schedule is free.
Mine too, Jeff.
You've been there
for more than 30 minutes.
Wendell moves a lot,
but his ball doesn't.
Let it go, stop this nonsense!
I will not move.
Domenick tries to impose himself
by a verbal attack.
I have eight siblings.
We would kill each other
for the last nugget on the table.
You see?
Oh oh! It begins!
I am relaxed.
First start of movement.
Do not let go!
First movement at Domenick.
Wendell turned his head.
Hey! I've been watching the show
since day one.
I'll put that necklace on tonight.
He is for me.
My family
is watching me from that bench over there.
I will not lose.
Green brings me luck.
So much the better.
Domenick against Wendell,
to win the bet.
It is pure will.
Things are still moving at Wendell.
The body trembles,
the forearms burn.
Good luck, Dom!
Wendell laughs!
Domenick
wins individual immunity!
Safe at the council tonight,
and he earns the right
for the Oranges
to go to the board second
and see
what the Violets will have done before.
Chelsea, come here!
Bravo, Chelsea!
For the second time in a row,
immunity is yours.
You are safe tonight.
Domenick, come here!
Bravo, Chelsea!
Domenick,
safe at council tonight.
Neither Chelsea nor Domenick
can be eliminated.
Alas, Jenna, Sebastian,
Angela, Donathan,
you will go to the council first,
where one of you four will be eliminated.
Ensuite, Kellyn,
Michael, Laurel, Wendell,
one of you will be eliminated.
Two people eliminated tonight,
two dreams that will end.
Thank you for Chelsea, Domenick.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight.
Cheer. Cheer.
Thanks.
I had to win.
I don't know what happened.
Now
I'm up against three original Navitis.
I have to find something,
because I don't want to leave tonight.
Like a feeling of deja vu!
Cheer!
Thanks.
You are a warrior!
You are too kind.
Chelsea, Dom, great job!
Thanks.
It was hard
thanks.
For the council tonight
we have two groups of five.
The first is Chelsea,
Donathan, Jenna, Sebastian and Angela.
I had not anticipated
this twist.
It was creepy.
Without a draw at the start...
Survivor slapped us!
And in my group, apart from me,
Michael and Kelly.
Cheer.
A tiny mistake!
Finally I know that!
For tonight,
the plan is to vote out Michael.
It should be easy.
You can turn it off without a problem.
What is being said?
What's going on for you?
I would like not to
play my idol tonight.
I haven't decided
on that yet.
Coming back to the camp,
I know that I will probably be targeted.
I wanted to speak to Donathan
as soon as possible,
because he has an idol.
And to me,
that's one of my last options.
Can I ask you a favor?
What?
Since we're going to separate councils,
could I borrow
it for a few hours to show it?
That they believe her mine?
No.
Do not?
Do not.
Why?
It could be traced back to me
and screw up my plans.
But that won't happen.
No one suspects...
My bag is already made,
she's in it.
Even though we're allies, I can't
give my idol to Michael.
I'm here to win
a million dollars.
I have to
consider my interest first.
I don't want my idol
to be known before the council.
I do my Calimero.
I can participate?
Yes!
Donathan
gave me a clear answer.
I would have preferred another.
So even though lying is risky,
if I say I have an idol,
I might be able
to work this in my favor
and save me again.
To succeed would be pretty cool.
I have to trust you 100%.
Can I?
I know you won't say anything.
I have an idol and I will play it.
I'm not leaving tonight.
The cow! He has an idol!
Good blood wood!
Things seem
more dangerous than ever.
If it works, tonight
I'm with you...
And I...
I'm with you for good.
If it works. I'm super serious.
I think she thinks
I have the idol.
I convinced her
that I was going to play it tonight.
I did my best, I believe.
At this point, it's a last resort.
I hope it pays off
and I stay.
You don't tell Laurel about it, huh?
But no!
Good.
No problem.
Michael has already found two idols.
That there is another is possible.
I'm afraid he'll vote for me
and I'll leave.
He says he has an idol.
He does not have it.
Are you sure?
He wouldn't tell you.
Look at me.
I know when people are trying to trick me.
He does not have it.
He would have found her the next day...
Let him show it to us!
I do not want to leave.
Kellyn might be freaking out a bit,
because I doubt he has an idol.
So it's risky,
but I'm voting for Michael.
This guy refuses to leave!
We have to fire him.
I do not believe it.
I'm not... a genius.
But I know how to decipher people.
I vote Michael
because I don't believe him.
Domenick
assures me that I risk nothing.
But I fear
that gifted Michael
really have another idol.
Everything is fine?
I'm afraid.
It could be me tonight.
Why?
Michael, the idol finder.
I believe he has one.
I do not know. It really looks like.
So maybe I'll
vote for Laurel.
Voting Laurel seems safest to me,
because I doubt she has an idol.
So as long as Wendell follows me,
we can stay between Naviti.
He has an idol.
And he will play it tonight,
no matter what.
He acts like he has one.
It seems believable.
And I believe it.
If he does have the idol,
are we ready to sacrifice Laurel?
Kellyn, who gets super emotional,
wants to place votes on Laurel.
She doesn't know
that Laurel is my ally.
I need to talk to Laurel,
see what she has in mind.
Because we need a plan.
Today, it looks like Michael
has given up or has something.
If he releases an idol,
what happens?
If he votes Kellyn, she leaves.
And if I don't, it's me.
Michael has shown to
be a fierce competitor.
So voting for him makes sense.
But if he releases an idol,
I could leave.
It's frustrating to know that my game
depends on whether
he has an idol or not.
What should I do?
I don't think clearly,
I'm stressed.
Because you don't want
Kellyn out.
For me, she can leave
anytime.
Wendell and Domenick
are among my closest allies.
They have to protect me
for this next vote
you don't vote Kelly
because she might want to target me.
I'll probably vote Kellyn,
it's the safest for me.
Tonight should be easy.
I would like Michael to leave.
But if I have to vote Kellyn
to save Laurel, I'm ready for it.
I feel calm.
I don't even care.
The clock is ticking.
I've been thinking about it all day.
I have the secret advantage
gained on Ghost Island.
I have an extra scroll.
I can trace Michaela's name
and write another one.
An extra vote
is immense power.
I'll use my extra vote
tonight
and put two votes on Laurel,
in case Michael
has an idol.
It should be self-explanatory, right?
I don't plan on doing anything crazy.
We should just make
sure our allies understand.
The day was lively.
Full of discussions,
of people isolating themselves,
because there will be two councils tonight.
We have a few people
in sight.
I hope we can
get them both out at once.
But I'm ready to make
a big move, take risks,
to protect my allies.
I like sunny days.
Yeah.
If we want to do it...
I don't know what's going on there,
but we have the majority.
Yeah.
With me in my tribe,
there's Chelsea,
Angela, Donathan and Jenna.
Deux Rest, trois Navigation.
We've had the majority
since day one.
So all is well.
Nope?
Yeah.
We'll have to be super convincing.
On va voter Jenna.
And we'll tell him we're voting for Donathan.
So many things go through my head.
What are my chances
of leaving tonight?
I am in the tribe of Donathan,
which has the idol.
We are in the minority.
As Malolo,
we know we are in danger.
So I guess
it will be Donathan or me.
Ang is also coming?
She will come, I believe.
Would you consider voting Donathan?
That's what we do.
We vote for him.
It's the pivotal vote
that no one wants.
This is where personal connections
come into play.
Chelsea and Sebastian seem ready
to keep me again.
Donathan has to
believe it's me
so that he does not play his idol.
Because otherwise, I'm the one leaving,
and I don't want to.
Sebastian said:
We had to try.
I say. Finally...
That's the game.
It's frustrating, but...
Know that I love you.
Me too.
Glad we played together.
Sebastian says he will vote Jenna out.
I have my idol.
I can feel calm.
But I don't want Jenna to leave.
Maybe I can save her.
How are you?
Yes.
What's wrong?
I'm trying to convince Wendell
or Domenick to take action against Kellyn.
I'm taking my gear tonight,
but should I use
it for me or for Jenna?
I do not know. It's stressful.
Laurel is my closest ally.
But she's in the other group.
Apparently, she could
leave tonight. It terrifies me.
The Malolos
had to struggle all along.
I wouldn't like to
see Jenna go either.
This game, this game.
I know.
Vote Sebastian, tonight.
OK.
Why?
I will play it on you.
Would you play your idol on me?
If you are 100% with me.
Yes, I will vote Sebastian.
I will try to save you.
I lied well.
Donathan would play his idol on me.
He's an idiot.
I am ready to eliminate it.
I'll try to look surprised
when he joins the jury.
Great thanks for being willing to do this.
I told Jenna
I'd play the idol on her,
but there are so many variables
in this game.
It will depend on what
my gut tells me on the board.
It's a huge risk.
But I think back to Tai and Scott.
He did not save the friend
who could have helped him later.
I intend to reverse the curse
for Malolo.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Desiree,
eliminated at the last council.
Donathan.
Big twist today.
Clearly.
You have been divided
into two temporary tribes.
You will eliminate someone,
then the other five will come.
You shake your head,
you already know my question.
Yes, it definitely put
the animation on the camp.
Jenna and I
are with three Navitis, so...
It's back to square one.
Sebastian.
Is it a simple enough vote?
The Navitis are going to stay together
and the Malolos are in trouble?
Yes, the Malolos have been on the wrong side
of the handle from the start.
One can only sympathize
with their impotence.
So yes, it's pretty clear,
there are three Naviti and two Malolo.
And yet, see the jury.
That was not the case.
There are two Naviti and a Malolo.
Jenna. Did it seem like there was a loophole
for you to step into?
No flaw.
The Naviti remain united.
And I'm going to leave,
that's pretty clear, so...
I am ready to vote.
Wow! Are you giving up?
No, but I've
been at the bottom all along.
Today, the prospect
of both councils excited me.
But we found
"the welded Naviti".
Everyone has been pretty clear.
Sebastian.
Hearing this, do you say to yourself:
"Wow, aren't you fighting anymore?
We haven't voted yet!"?
Yes, her saying that is very
interesting. In this game, we fight.
It's pretty blunt
to say that out of hand.
Donathan, hearing Jenna say,
"It's me and I'm ready.",
"Well, at least I'm surviving."?
Yes, but people always have
more than one trick up their sleeves.
We never know. They might
tell me that I'll stay,
but Jenna would be surprised
to see me leave.
Chelsea. How would that
make sense, when there are 3 2?
Because of the fear of idols?
Yes. In case of division 3 2,
you can't do anything to
save yourself
if one of these two has an idol.
Basically, if you vote wrong,
one of the three Navitis
you thought was safe, leaves.
So, Donathan,
what did you do this afternoon?
to rock the Naviti
and cause something?
I believe
these three Naviti are scared
to make others look bad,
so...
Hence our desperation,
Jenna and I, tonight.
Jenna. It brings us back to you
and your feeling that
you don't have a chance.
Yes. It's clearly
a Malolo tonight,
and from the discussions
I've had, I believe that's me.
So is that really
all we needed?
Are you really ready to vote?
Wow. I don't think I've ever asked
so few questions of the board.
Well, it's time to vote.
Angela, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Oh my God!
So... That's...
Kaôh-Rong's super-idol.
That was Scott's.
And this, Tai's.
They ultimately didn't
form the super-idol.
I put them together now,
which creates...
a normal idol.
And I will...
say that...
Sorry, Jenna, I'm playing it for me.
Good. Thank you, Donathan.
Combined, these two pieces
form an idol.
Votes against Donathan
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Donathan. Does not count.
Sebastian. A vote Sebastian.
Jenna.
One vote Sebastian, one vote Jenna.
Two votes Jenna, one vote Sebastian,
one vote remains.
Eleventh person eliminated
and fourth member of the jury:
Jenna. Bring me your torch.
Jenna, the tribe has spoken.
Tonight, you can
immediately join the jury,
next to Desiree.
Hi!
It'll be OK.
Alright, you're done.
Take your torches, return to camp.
The following are coming.
Take place.
And we're going to start.
Let 's start
with the first big news.
You find out,
Jenna has just been eliminated.
Laurel,
what does this tell you?
It sucks to see her there,
because it shows that Naviti
is still playing the same game
only from the start.
We are back in the same position.
I feel like I'm repeating
the same story every day here.
And still today.
Yet Domenick,
by coin toss,
once again, on paper,
Naviti has the majority.
It was crazy.
We draw two teams,
and once again Naviti
was in the majority on both sides.
That's the whole story
of this season.
Wendell. Is it that simple?
It's Michael and Laurel,
are we doing it right?
Yes, it's the easiest.
Kellyn. So is this the right thing to do?
We play Survivor.
Is the easy shot ever
the shot to play?
I do not know.
It looks easy.
And then you think
of the king of idols sitting there,
you have to redo your calculations,
and that's scary.
Tonight, here, I am very, very afraid.
Wendell. Is it
like jungle animals?
The predator and the prey.
By dint, they come to feel
that something is wrong.
Are you talking about this?
The question is whether
or not you believe that a person has an idol,
then you study it to find out
whether it is telling the truth or not.
Absolutely, Jeff.
Eyes have been on Michael
since day 1.
I mean, watch it, first!
Finally, of course!
At least take it!
Thanks, Kellyn.
Domenick. You meant...?
I wanted to mention
to the people I work with
that I know Michael is known
for finding idols, but...
We shouldn't panic.
I stick to my plan,
because at this point, I haven't seen anything.
I don't believe he has it.
Michael. What logic would there be
to show him the idol,
knowing that there are five of you and
the only other choice is Laurel?
I do not know.
Maybe to influence the vote.
Otherwise, it wouldn't make much sense.
The prey
knows when there are predators.
It's something
I'd rather hide
and play to save me
once again.
It holds.
Laurel. Your position
becomes very interesting.
Because all eyes
are on Michael.
There is this question.
What if he had an idol?
You could attempt
to join Naviti and say:
"I walk with you."
But you might fall prey.
First, I'm jealous,
no one said I was pretty!
A few compliments
would be nice, but...
I saw Libby's spell
when they aimed for it
and failed, so...
It's the same.
My game hinges
on their reading of Michael.
Wendell. Do you fear
that if you are wrong tonight,
is that messing up your game?
Absolutely.
If we aim wrong
and an innocent onlooker is hit,
like a Libby,
it has implications
and that will have repercussions.
So we're trying
to aim for the best tonight.
Kellyn. These are the kind of moments
we dream of
when you dream
of participating in Survivor.
A big question arises.
If we are wrong, we fail.
And now Dom is talking to Wendell!
There is no certainty.
I hope
they recite the alphabet to each other,
because I thought everything was over
before I came here.
Does it make you nervous?
I was already before!
Of course I still am!
I have a one in four chance of leaving.
One in four.
And so far, you're not included
in the Naviti discussion.
Wow, Laurel, how do you feel?
That's what being Malolo is.
It's the same on the camp,
they discuss and make asides.
I imagine they're debating whether
to target Michael or not.
For me, they were planning to target him,
they talked and probably
changed their minds, so...
There, I think it's for my apple.
Kellyn. If Survivor
is a rollercoaster,
where are we on the journey?
For me, we are in the loop
and I'm hanging upside down!
Very unpleasant position!
And as long as no one comes
to make us go away,
I guess
we are waiting for this next vote.
Good. It's time to vote.
Laurel, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Kelly's.
Un vote Wendell, un vote Laurel,
un vote Kellyn, un vote Michael.
Michael.
Two votes Michael,
un vote Wendell, un vote Laurel,
un vote Kellyn.
One vote remains.
Laurel. Equality.
Two votes Laurel,
two votes Michael.
We will vote again. Here's how.
Laurel and Michael,
you're not voting.
Domenick, Wendell, Kellyn,
you can only vote
for one of them.
Domenick, over to you.
Come and take the ballot box.
There were six votes.
Someone had an extra vote.
I will count the votes.
I will read the votes.
Michael. One vote Michael.
Twelfth Person Eliminated
and Fifth Jury Member:
Michael. Two is enough.
Bring me your torch.
My brother.
You rock, you hear me?
I appreciate.
I love you.
Nobody kissed me.
Michael, the tribe has spoken.
It was exceptional. Vinaka.
Hello my brother.
Well, everyone
who could receive votes
have received them.
And with the rest of the tribe
waiting for you at the camp,
the discussions around the fire
should be interesting.
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Most are on dangerous ground.
He doesn't care, it annoys me!
Naviti's happy family
is over.
But blood ties take precedence.
If you could share this moment
with those you play for?
I speak of love!
Even if I failed,
I can be proud of myself.
I am the youngest here.
Unbeknownst to them, they were fooled
each time by an 18-year-old guy.
At 18, my life is just beginning.
I've been watching the show
for so long.
Living such an experience
is priceless.