Previously on Survivor...
After the merger,
the war
between Domenick and Chris broke out.
It's the arms race.
These two can
blow it all up if they want to.
But Angela and Desiree
had their own target.
Naviti girls can date
who I want to date. Libby.
At the council,
Domenick bluffed
with his fake idol...
I'm going to put it on, because...
It's the shell.
...and played the Heir Advantage.
I play it for me.
Libby received votes,
but Chris was sent to the jury.
Chris, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you, Probst.
There are 13 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Let's light this fire.
First council of the merger!
It's nothing!
Very delirious, huh!
But who voted for you?
I do not know.
No idea.
It's been three tips in a row
that my name comes out.
And I don't know why.
Emotionally, you wonder
what people have in mind.
But whatever I do
I have to make mistakes
to be noticed like this.
So I have to keep my eyes open,
looking for something
to help me a little.
I liked the shell necklace!
This guy wouldn't let me go.
What a relief
to finally be free from Chris!
It had been so long.
I can die in peace.
He was after me.
I'm not jubilant tonight.
I respect Chris a lot.
I know I did
the show, but...
I am not proud of myself.
What worries me
after my performance on the board,
it's that they think I'm
as dangerous as Chris thought I was.
I didn't mean to
sound pretentious or arrogant.
To do that is to become the target.
But if I can take a step back,
not be at the maneuver
these next few days,
I will have a little more flexibility
with them.
Besides, I still have
my real idol in my pocket,
and that's good,
because the war is anything but over.
Wendell cooks.
The advice went
as we wanted.
Chris finally left,
almost unanimously.
But the sequel
is much less easy to predict.
There are so many discussions.
Everyone talks to everyone.
So my plan
is to stick to the four
which no one knows anything about.
Me, Domenick, Laurel and Donathan.
And we go from there.
How are you ?
Yes.
You seem far away.
Of you ?
Yeah.
No, it rolls.
Yeah ?
I would tell you otherwise. You know.
I base many of my actions
on non-verbal elements.
I sensed Laurel a little hesitant.
She can be a bit paranoid.
So the safer she feels,
the better it is for our alliance.
So you know Dom has an idol?
Does he have a real one?
Yes.
This shell is a decoy.
I haven't seen it, but I believe it.
She is at our disposal.
We can go to the end.
I am with you.
If we are a close-knit quartet...
There are no others.
Are you 1000% top four with me?
Yes. At 1000%.
I don't want to work
with anyone else. Know the.
OK. I promise you
we're going to the top four together.
I also have an idol.
There, I know you're lying. Why ?
Why shouldn't I have one?
You would have told me before.
Domenick and Wendell have a lot
of power and influence.
And now
he tells me he has an idol.
I have once again been
left out, and I don't like it.
And of course, Dom hadn't told me
about the Heir's Advantage.
It's frustrating
that they still have something,
additional power.
You are the second to know.
I didn't tell anyone.
I'm telling you...
Wendell and I
tell each other every day that we cover ourselves 100%.
But he has shown to be loyal
only up to a point.
I'm hallucinating here.
Yeah. This is...
There, I downed my game.
Four people, two idols.
There is no more powerful.
Let's eliminate the others.
Yeah.
Good.
I distrust what Wendell tells me,
because he and Dom
share too much power.
She is 1000% with us.
Good.
At some point, I will have to shake
the coconut tree, change something.
Because after the merger,
you have to start making moves.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today
you will form two teams of six.
On my signal,
you will cross a pontoon bridge
up to a slingshot.
With, you will send sandbags
to targets.
The first team
to take down all six targets
win the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
Yes !
The six winners will enjoy
an afternoon... of tacos...
...of burritos,
of quesadillas...
Damn it !
My God !
... and about the pearls...
...in Survivor's taco shack .
Also, the winners
will send one of the losers
on Ghost Island.
We're going to do it schoolyard style.
Let's draw the captains
and let's go!
The teams are formed.
In orange:
Domenick, Kellyn, Jenna,
They confront
Chelsea and Donathan.
For the reward.
Survivors, ready?
Domenick and Wendell start.
Wendell... That's how it's done!
Come on Wendell!
Wendell is the first to slingshot.
Wendell backs up a lot.
He scores !
One for the Violets.
Wendell returns.
You have to cross the platform.
All must shoot at least once.
Laurel goes for the Violets.
We believe in you!
He hits and scores!
It's okay, Domenick!
Tie, 1 1,
with a giant reward!
This is Laurel.
Laurel shoots and scores
for the Violets!
The Violets lead 2 1.
Sebastian shoots high and very far.
Not too high! A little lower !
This is Donathan.
He could
extend the Violets' lead.
It goes too far!
Come back !
Sebastian fails,
he shoots too high every time.
Big setback for the Oranges!
Donathan...
This sling
is more powerful than him!
Back up a little harder!
He backs up and fires, but fails.
Come back !
Donathan gives up and leaves.
The Oranges
have the opportunity to equalise.
The management was good.
Just missed.
Angela, for the Violets.
Far too short.
Come back !
The Violets have a strategy.
Take out their weak players
as soon as possible
to be able to dismiss the forts.
We have to score here.
Straight to the target, it's good!
Equality, 2 2.
Chelsea for the Violets.
Come back !
Chelsea, their
participation goal achieved, returns.
I'm super ready!
This is Kelly.
Four more targets
for both teams.
The taco shack is in play!
She shoots. Too short.
Come on, come back!
Kelly's repartee.
The Oranges
adopt the strategy of the Violets.
Come back, Lib!
Libby fires a shot and comes back.
You're going to rock, Wendell!
Lots of strategy.
This is Wendell.
All the Violets have passed,
leaving the field open
to the best players.
This is Desiree.
Come on, Des, come on!
Nice shot.
She misses,
but the direction was good.
Come on Wendell!
Desiree could
give the advantage to the Oranges.
Wendell shoots for the Violets.
He scores again on the first try!
Three for the Violets!
Lord, he is unleashed!
Wendell needs to come back
and someone else go.
Come back, Des!
Desiree gives up and comes back.
Here comes Laurel again for the Violets.
Laurel proves to be strong
in this ordeal.
And that's it for Laurel! Its good !
Laurel takes down a fourth target
for the Violets.
Jenna's first shot.
Weak. In the sand.
Go on !
Jenna is called back.
Wendell is back.
The Violets took down
four out of six targets.
Oranges, only two.
Domenick must accelerate
for the Oranges.
OK ?
Yeah, and you ?
Good.
Come on, Dom!
Give tacos, Dom!
Everyone wants them!
Domenick scores,
three for the Oranges!
He knocks down the fifth!
One more for the Violets!
Come on, Michael!
Michael tries to close the gap
with this shot.
He must leave.
More than one target for the Violets,
two for the Oranges.
Laurel can win for the Violets.
Domenick returns.
Laurel begins to tire.
She is exhausted.
I'm ready.
Laurel backs up and shoots.
Too short.
She is exhausted. Laurel leaves.
This is the opportunity
the Oranges need.
Domenick just misses.
Come on, there you are!
Better not
let Wendell back!
Wendell and Domenick
are side by side again.
Everyone can smell these tacos!
Take your time !
Wendell can win for the Violets.
Come on Wendell!
Come on, miss!
Wendell takes his time,
for the victory!
And he succeeds!
The Violets win the reward!
Where to the tacos!
We've got it covered, friends!
How could we lose?
The Violets.
In addition to a beautiful afternoon,
you decide who goes to
Ghost Island. It's business as usual.
Either you make a unanimous choice,
or they pull the stones.
The stones, Jeff.
The stones.
Palms up.
Reveal !
White, and this is Ghost Island.
Jenna has the white stone,
she's going to Ghost Island.
Take your things,
the boat will take you.
Six people go to the reward,
five return to camp,
and Jenna goes to Ghost Island, alone.
You will return to camp
tomorrow morning.
Angela, Donathan,
take your things, enjoy!
Fill your stomachs!
Desiree, Sebastian, Domenick, Kellyn
, Michael,
nothing for you.
Take your things, leave.
I am very excited
about this award.
This is an opportunity to start
building stronger bonds,
and perhaps to strengthen some of them.
Hoping
to get the target off my back.
I am potentially
at the bottom of the scale.
So pulling the stone, it was
weird, I was almost happy.
I was told that we could play
for an advantage or a disadvantage.
I'll try to approach this
positively,
because at this stage,
we are all playing individually.
I will therefore
try to have an advantage,
it might help me.
Good.
Provided that there is something!
"No, not today.
No game for you."
I broke an urn, and...
No game for me.
It was disappointing.
When you come to the Phantom Island...
What's the point if we don't play?
People are talking, at camp, and...
Lots of things
will happen without me.
And I'm even more pissed off
not to share
the super Mexican feast.
My positive attitude
has evaporated today.
God's goodness !
Lord !
What do we have here?
Tiki Tacos!
Our team
couldn't seem to win.
All the tough guys were in front.
And we managed to win
this great reward.
Look at the margaritas!
And beer!
At work !
Burritos, nachos, enchiladas...
The total!
Guacamole!
Yeah !
And above all, guacamole.
I'd probably
even risk immunity for guacamole.
Congratulations to all !
We weren't the strongest,
but we got them anyway.
Let's enjoy!
Health !
On a personal level,
I'm glad Laurel is here.
Health !
She's been my ally
for two weeks
and she is super strong.
But she seemed
a little uncertain this morning.
It's good that she's here,
to strengthen our ties.
And there's also Donathan,
Laurel's right-hand man,
which I want to be very close,
because Domenick, Laurel,
Donathan and I,
that's my top four.
Last night was epic.
I did not see anything coming.
You obviously do.
But I do not...
I didn't see
my name coming either, yet.
I don't know what I'm doing wrong.
Tell me, if so!
The votes for you?
Yes.
I do not know. Easy vote,
I think, nothing else.
At first,
you were close to Michael.
I think it comes from there.
When we have
this label, this target,
it's hard to let go.
My name came out because of Michael.
They take us for a strong duo.
It sucks, cause I wanted
him to be my ally,
but at this point i have to act
and step up my game.
I think the sun will come out,
it will be great.
How do you feel the game?
Good.
That Chris is gone is good.
It was the right first shot.
I believe that is the consensus.
Yeah.
Chris was an easy vote.
There was no major division,
no demarcation drawn,
which is usually the case
at the first vote after the merger.
Chris gone,
it's more like every man for himself.
Now
I try to strengthen my alliances,
to make sure I prepare for
the best possible conclusion.
Guys make me nervous.
Just the duo, Dom and Wendell.
Both are strong.
Yes.
Wendell and Domenick,
the two, as a duo,
it is very dangerous,
because they work together.
This is why it seems important to me
to release the most dangerous of the two.
Who first?
Wendell. Dom has no power.
Angela has been worried
since Chris was eliminated.
So I was happy to hear
that it could strengthen our ranks
for the next vote.
Only you were out of it,
in the last vote.
Kellyn and Chelsea said they
couldn't trust you.
In my relationship with Chris,
he only listened to his own ideas.
Now I feel free
to play my way.
I'm definitely going to use
what I learned in the military,
with psychological operations,
in the civil affairs unit.
I'm going to mess things up,
stir up emotions.
Michael said
that I shouldn't
trust you, cause it's Chelsea and you
who didn't want to
share the info on Chris.
When people hear
their name being mentioned,
they go into "defense" mode
and the war begins.
And that's what I want to see.
The supreme battle.
I'm angry for the first time.
What happened ?
And the war is over, I want
to be triumphant, sword in hand,
all the victims on the ground,
and I stand proudly,
for they are my victims.
We will all agree.
For me, it's Michael.
I spoke with Michael.
He says he wants
to break the Dom Wendell alliance,
that you are too close
and everyone knows it.
I said, "Who come out first?"
But I like it!
"Wendell will continue to win,
he is strong."
Apparently
Michael brings up my name.
He makes a mess, walks around
and pushes people under the train.
So maybe we have
an easy joint vote again.
So let's fire it!
Over here, everyone!
Alright, let
's get into today's immunity challenge.
First, Kellyn,
I have to take the necklace back.
The best things have an ending.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will be playing
a Survivor classic.
It goes back to the first season.
This is the tasting test.
It is very simple
and in several rounds.
The last person wins
immunity, is immune to the vote.
The losers: on the council,
a ninth person will be eliminated
and will become the second juror.
The finish is in sight now.
Nothing as simple as
a psychological block
must come
between you and victory.
We draw the seats
and we go.
It's going to be good !
Well, on and go.
Reveal !
The most nutritious part
of the fish.
The eye.
Local fishermen
gave them to us.
Their families eat the flesh
and you the eyes.
Very simple. The first three
who eat both eyes
and show me an empty mouth,
qualify.
Survivors, ready?
It can go fast, someone
can swallow them all at once.
Open your mouth when it's good!
Michael, it's okay, step back!
There are two places left.
Libby tries to push them down.
Jenna is on it.
Come on, Libby!
Desiree, it's good!
Laurel, it's good!
And There you go ! Libby, no, too late!
are qualified.
The next six!
It's the same thing.
The first three qualify.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
Wendell is way off the mark!
Chelsea spits!
Do you see that!
Angela, you've qualified!
Sebastian too.
C'est entre Kellyn et Domenick.
One person will qualify.
Both chew fast.
Domenick, it's good! Qualified!
Oh, zu!
Kellyn, within seconds.
Wendell didn't even try.
Now that you're hot,
let's make this more interesting.
Go ahead, reveal!
Oh my God !
It would not be
a taste test without it.
beetle larva,
the one that Gervase couldn't swallow
in the first season.
Will she come between you
and your goal of reaching the end?
On and go.
The first three
to eat the three larvae
qualify.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Domenick shoves it.
Desiree chews,
Laurel tries to tear her apart.
There you go, one more!
Angela doesn't dawdle.
Come on, Angel! Come on, Laurel!
Michael, it's good!
Sebastian too!
And Angela too!
She narrowly beats Desiree!
Wow ! Fast !
We move on to the next round.
Il ya Sebastian,
and Angela
Now
we move on to the delicacies.
Reveal !
The yasawa sea slug.
The ocean is full of them.
You have probably come across some.
The first two to swallow both
and show me an empty mouth
play the last round.
Immunity is at stake.
Let's go. Survivors, ready?
Angela, from the start,
swallows a whole slug!
Wow !
Come on, one more!
Michael works hard.
Sebastian hangs on.
This is delicious !
Angela is stuck, she takes it out.
I do n't know
which is more disturbing.
It's good, Ang!
Angela is going to have to
tear her to pieces.
Come on, sea bass!
Michael is very calm.
He has slowly consumed the first
and is on the second.
No one wants to go to council
tonight without security.
Immunity is everything in this game.
Michael qualifies for the final!
Remain Sebastian and Angela.
Angela!
Sea bass !
Angela succeeds!
We have our face-to-face!
Michael versus Angela.
Congratulations to you !
Lots of protein!
It was for-vomit-able!
Last round. The confrontation
between Michael and Angela.
Reveal !
One of
the most popular delicacies in Fiji,
mother-of-pearl conch.
It's the flesh,
and there's a lot of it.
The issues are clear.
Let's go. For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Come on, Angel!
Both have the same strategy.
They start to bake
the flesh of the mother-of-pearl conch.
Angela is unleashed!
If she manages to swallow!
Endorse!
You go-y !
Angela continues to bake.
Michael tries to follow.
He will have to speed up
because Angela does not dawdle!
Angela still has a handful.
The last !
But she is
a bit ahead of Michael.
Michael can't afford
to take too long.
You want immunity? Accelerate!
Because Angela is launched.
Mode brutasse, you go-y!
Last track for Angela!
A ton of flesh!
Michael swallows another bite.
He only has one left.
Useless corn! Angela for purposes!
Angela wins
individual immunity!
Away from the council!
Attractive !
Oh my God !
Oh my God ! Brutal fashion!
Don't kiss me!
Lord !
I'll finish it, I want...
Really?
I want to have eaten it all.
Go for it !
Michael, explain to me.
The ordeal is over
and you wanted to finish.
I will never eat
stuff like this again
and
probably won't play Survivor again.
You have to do it when you can.
You were close, but not close enough.
Angela, come here!
Angela, immunity is yours.
You're safe
at tonight's council.
Others,
after 25 hard days
in Survivor,
someone will be
the ninth person eliminated
and the second juror.
It won't be you.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight. Congratulation !
It's always disappointing
to lose immunity.
But I trust the plan
that I put in place
these last days
to eliminate Wendell.
Wendell and Domenick
is the two-headed serpent.
So... we need to get Wendell out.
Angie,
the sea slug terror!
Gaining immunity is very nice.
But beating Michael
was clearly among my priorities.
Now voting seems easy,
because I had a plan to
mess things up, and it worked.
So I think I have
a bit of power right now.
It's clearly new,
challenging and fun.
What's going on ?
I do not know.
I think...
everyone agrees.
Michael.
Yes.
I haven't heard anything yet.
What's going on ?
I believe that...
... the consensus
is to eliminate Michael tonight.
Of course, it is decided as a group.
I'm not in a position
to influence that.
I don't want
you to have that impression.
Think about it.
In fact, you are the one...
We depend more on you
than you on us.
If Michael has the idol...
We should split the votes.
Yeah, have a backup plan, just
in case, like...
...five for Michael,
and then four for Libby.
Even if it's fusion,
it's still original Naviti and original
Malolo.
But if we can
rally Laurel and Donathan,
we can divide the votes,
in case Michael or Libby
have an idol.
Five votes on Michael,
four on Libby.
If we all follow the plan.
Hello.
How are you ?
So who for tonight?
I am between two waters,
to be frank.
If the Naviti split the votes
and that the Malolos vote together,
we can take out whoever we want.
I think the Naviti are welded,
but if they split the votes,
the five of us
can take anyone out.
We were demolished, shot down.
It's our turn to be strong.
And... If I decide
to play my idol tonight,
I know I'm quiet
for one more vote, but...
I would prefer
not to have to.
Who do you prefer?
Wendell.
My main allies
are Donathan, Domenick and Wendell.
But getting Wendell out
would be a big deal.
No doubt enough to fill a CV.
It's about whether I want
to continue working with him.
But if he smells something,
he could play his idol.
It will determine the course of the game
and my future in the game.
It's a very big decision.
I'm trying to decide if we should
be dangerous tonight.
The Malolos, we stay together.
Yeah.
The closer it gets,
the more my instinct tells me
to stay with Malolo
one more vote.
Our chances would be better
with more equal forces.
OK.
The longer I wait
the more I fear
that a Malolo will come out tonight.
I had this feeling
today
that i will never win
if there are too many Naviti.
But if I turn against them
and it turns out badly for us,
on the next tip,
it will probably be me.
For you, is this the best thing to do?
The one I always
trusted was Laurel.
But if I succeed
that would be great for my game.
Apparently it's Michael.
Voting with the majority.
It shows that you are.
It's smarter.
I spoke with Dom.
They vote Michael.
I have my back to the wall.
So I should
vote against my former ally
to save me.
Thanks.
You are quiet tonight.
It sucks. I hate doing this.
We are five. They are more numerous
and divide the votes.
Between whom and whom?
Mike and you.
Dom tells me that I risk nothing.
Then Don tells me that they are dividing
the votes between Michael and me.
Wait... what?!
Let's stick together one more vote.
Yes.
To equalize the forces.
We want to solder the Malolos.
If we vote together, without betraying,
it can be
a whole new start for me.
But I don't know who to believe anymore.
Who to trust,
who to be wary of?
Will the Malolos remain united?
I am torn.
I feel it well.
The only ones I can't decipher
are Laurel and Donathan.
Yeah. We will be fixed this evening.
The council is approaching.
I have Erik's idol,
and he made
the dumbest decision
in Survivor Micronesia,
Fans vs. Favorites.
I don't want to
prolong Erik's curse.
But now, in the game of Survivor,
I have to be
willing to take risks.
So I'm trying
to avoid having to play it tonight.
We cannot necessarily believe everything
on this island.
The board is the place to listen
and hear the clues.
There is clearly a danger.
But with any luck,
I'll spend the night.
Here is now the first juror.
Chris, eliminated at the last council.
Angela.
Let's start with today's test.
You looked
physically different today.
And your actions have confirmed it.
What happened ?
I was tired
of being at the bottom of the ladder,
to always be
excluded from discussions,
to learn everything at the last moment.
I knew I had to win,
take matters into my own hands.
Sebastian.
Angela took a sea slug
and swallowed it.
It was quite impressive.
I work
in seafood.
I was impressed to see
a woman do this better than me.
Donathan.
When you see such an effort,
do you feel the game
getting stronger?
Yes. The last days,
people do their own thing,
alliances are formed.
And it's no longer Malolo and Naviti.
It's Lavita,
it's a brand new game.
Desiree. Do you agree ?
Or do you still feel
that tugging?
"Naviti, Malolo...
Should I get rid of it?"
Are we at the stage
where we are considering big moves?
Who does not plan big shots
at this stage, does not really play.
And if it's staying with Naviti,
then it's staying with Naviti.
If it's joining Malolo,
it's joining Malolo.
In the end,
it all depends on your analysis.
Domenick. Will
the new final board format
favors those who strike
rather than followers,
because now,
we can boast of his game?
Absolutely. The new format
allows people to come here
and betray their best friends,
while being able to explain
at the end,
why it was necessary.
Wendell. Is the risk
that the smart follower
says to himself:
"Let the lions devour each other,
I will be the vulture that will come
and pick up the pieces."?
It's a huge risk.
The strongest is in the jury, there.
And once an alpha male is gone,
another seems to emerge,
but he becomes the new target.
So yes, very big risk.
Michael. How many moves in advance
do you envisage, for the moment?
Because that shouldn't
make you lose sight of this piece of advice either.
For me, only this advice counts.
I tell myself that some
may feel too sure of themselves
and do not consider
early blows
maybe they should do.
Laurel. Very interesting.
"Some people may be
too sure of themselves."
Yes. The Naviti
still have the power.
No matter what they say,
this division lives on.
That's what we, Malolo,
are trying to tell them.
They are not all at the top.
We're just trying
to get one of them to act,
to use us while we're here.
Chelsea. Laurel says, basically,
that if you are
in a real majority,
are you sure you're
not the bottom?
Frankly,
if you're last in the group,
you are stupid to stay there,
because, congratulations,
you are in the jury!
Wendell. It is therefore necessary to convince
the others that they are in a better position!
Basically, yes.
You preach what you want
others to believe.
“We dominate. You are calm.
Go to sleep."
It's very "cult", Jeff,
really!
And yet, Domenick,
everyone knows the lie.
Yes. It's no joke here.
Have all the conversations
you want,
you know you're being bullshit,
and, especially at this stage of the game,
we don't know if someone
will change sides, or when.
Kellyn. What would be the point,
for someone, of changing sides?
It would be a huge change
which would undoubtedly require
a masterful force of conviction,
because going from Violets to Oranges
wouldn't make much sense,
you'd stay at the very bottom.
It's time
to draw the lines
and one should know more
from this advice than from any other.
What's your criteria
tonight, Michael?
What move are you playing?
You have to do the right thing
when you have a majority for that.
For some, maybe it
's time to get out,
because they have the majority.
But it goes both ways.
Sit too long
on a bomb
and it can
explode in your face.
Everyone really needs to think
to blows at his disposal
and at the right time
to seize the opportunity.
Well, it's time to vote.
Desiree, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
I may be a bit paranoid
but I would hate to leave
with that in my pocket.
So it was
Ozzy's fake stick idol.
in Survivor Micronesia, 2007.
I dedicate it to Ozzy.
This is not...
...no longer just a stick.
He's a real idol.
Votes against Michael
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Michael. Does not count.
Libby. Two Libby votes,
one Wendell vote.
Ninth person eliminated
and second member of the jury:
Libby. Three is enough.
Bring me your torch.
Good luck to everyone.
Hi Libby.
It will be fine. Good luck.
Well done, sir.
Libby, the tribe has spoken.
Goodbye !
Hi !
Survivor is often compared
to a roller coaster.
After 25 days, two members of the jury
and Ghost Island still in play,
it's far from over.
Take your torches,
return to the camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
There is hope for Malolo.
I'm ready to take out the Naviti.
Properly armed...
Des tries to rally the Malolo
against you.
I have to make them paranoid.
...they could
blow up the game.
Everyone freaks out.
Who is telling the truth?
A Malolo is going to leave.
It's going to screw up.
For three councils,
my name came out for no reason.
And that sucks, because you
really trust people.
I did my best,
I won trials,
food rewards,
I made alliances.
I am proud of myself
and grateful
to have had this experience.