Previously on Survivor...
In the Malolo tribe,
a mix gave former
Naviti allies a 5 -4 advantage.
It couldn't have turned out better.
And Bradley was getting cocky.
And they are entertaining.
While we eliminate them!
The Naviti tribe
had to face the council.
And with Chris on Ghost Island,
were ready
to release one of their own.
Do you want to take Angela out?
But the four Malolo
saw the opportunity
to take out a major threat.
We can choose, Wendell or Morgan.
The four of us decide who goes.
At the council,
But they were taken by surprise
when Morgan was eliminated.
Morgan, the tribe has spoken.
I have the Heir Advantage.
I leave it to Domenick.
There are 17 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
What the fuck happened?!
Good game.
Good. You got me.
Do we talk about it a bit?
Not too much, no.
Let's say we decided to stay strong.
It succeeded.
This game is crazy.
Angela, sorry I voted for you.
The same.
Wendell and Dom betrayed me.
I thought I could trust them.
But even
if he wears a sheepskin,
below, a wolf remains a wolf.
Wendell, are we going for a walk?
Comfort yourself a little?
Wendell and I
had a neat little plan.
We were all going to vote for Angela.
But the old Malolo
took me by surprise.
Yeah. We had a good time.
We got everyone back together.
That's crazy.
They succeeded.
And we're burned out with Angela.
She wants us dead.
Chris still wants me dead.
And he doesn't know
what he's going to get into.
It will be...
A total and utter disaster.
I am with you.
At least there are two of us.
What do we do ?
I got passed, that's all.
But... Listen.
I have a real idol.
Mazette!
There is hope.
We may be at our lowest
but luckily
my buddy Domenick has an idol.
Wow. That's great.
We have a chance to stir things up.
Just as we left
our group,
maybe someone
will leave theirs.
It's playable.
We have to be
as smart as possible.
We are fine, we can do it.
This morning,
I looked at the bottom of my bag.
And... Damn it!
There is something !
It can be good or bad.
The council did not turn out
as I hoped,
I pray it helps me.
Oh my God !
Morgan, my girl! I love you !
The Heir's Advantage was given to me
by my girlfriend Morgan!
Just... Oh!
A big moment for me.
"With this advantage,
your immunity is guaranteed.
It can only be used
when there are 13 players left.
or when there are six players left."
There, we are 17. Okay.
Any help is welcome.
I already have the idol, but I want
everything I can get.
And there are lessons to be learned
from these relics.
It is important that I
truly reverse these curses.
I must not sink,
be eaten alive
like those previous players.
Oh my God !
Over here, everyone!
Malolo,
discover the new Naviti tribe.
Morgan was eliminated
at the last council.
Shit !
And this is Chris,
back from Ghost Island.
Chris discovers his new tribe.
Welcome !
Today
you will have to collect a ring.
Then you will return
to your flag,
the other tribe trying to stop you
by all means.
The first person
with one hand on the ring
and one on the mast
mark for his tribe.
Three points and it's won.
Like at home.
Peanut butter, jam...
Additionally, the winners will send
one of the losers to Ghost Island,
who will come back
for the next immunity test
and potentially risk
the board.
Big stakes.
Malolo, you are one more.
Who is not participating?
Not the same person
in two events in a row.
So ?
Go to the bench.
One minute of organization
and we get started.
First run!
Michael and Brendan for Malolo
against Chris and Wendell.
In place !
Well, on and go!
Survivors, ready?
Chris rushes off quickly.
He alone moves.
An interesting strategy, from the outset.
Chris quickly reaches the ring.
Go right!
Now comes the strategy.
Chris tries to throw,
he passes to Wendell!
This is for Chris!
Wendell tries to block Brendan.
Chris can free himself.
Can we stop Chris?
From the outset, it does not seem!
Naviti scores the first point!
New round. Angela and Laurel
contre Jenna and Kelly.
Survivors, ready?
Laurel goes ahead,
looking for the ring for Naviti.
Jenna leaves to challenge her a bit.
Catch her, Jenna!
Jenna goes after Laurel,
attempts to grab the ring.
We have a water battle!
Voici Kellyn et Angela.
Kelly's s'en prend à Laurel.
Angela is on the ring.
Everyone is struggling!
Laurel didn't give up,
not for a moment,
although they all cling to her.
But she is trained!
Jenna puts the package!
We feel that it is rocking!
Laurel strikes back!
Angela gives it all!
Angela's turn!
And she scores for Naviti!
New round.
against Domenick and James.
Naviti can win this time.
Survivors, ready?
This time, Sebastian
rushes quickly for Malolo.
Domenick sets off for Naviti.
It will be a fight for the ring.
He steps aside and throws it
to Bradley, whom James retains.
The Malolo hold the rope.
The Malolo must score.
It fights dry.
Bradley et Sebastian
pull James and Domenick
to their flag.
Can Sebastian and Bradley
make it happen?
Rest marque !
Naviti can win this time.
Malolo must score.
Survivors, ready?
Go !
Come on, Laurel!
Laurel, for the second time,
rushes towards the ring.
She draws on her reserves.
Stephanie arrives first.
It's a fight for the ring.
Des, to the left!
Do something, girls!
The Malolo
must score now.
The Naviti have the advantage.
They are getting closer step by step
of the arrival of the test.
Laurel makes the difference
for Naviti.
She is unstoppable.
Des, lift his feet!
No strangulation!
His feet !
Malolo gives
Naviti a hard time! Libby is getting closer!
Stephanie pulls her back.
Laurel continues to fight.
Libby, a few centimeters away!
For victory !
Go on !
Come on, Libby!
Lift his legs!
The Malolo are back!
Libby is trained!
Can she reach the goal?
And There you go !
Naviti wins the award!
Naviti, big reward
and big decision.
Which member of Malolo
will you send to Phantom Island,
knowing that he will return in time
for the next immunity?
I believe we are going
follow the consensus
and choose the stones.
The stones. Understood.
Yeah.
My biggest fear in Survivor.
Really ?
Kellyn, if the spirits listen to you,
you may go to the Island!
Palm up.
So. And... reveal!
Kelly's.
Stay strong.
What just happened?
I opened my mouth, that's all!
None of us
are here by coincidence.
We're all supposed to be here.
I have to be careful
about the wishes I express.
Kellyn, get your things.
The boat is waiting.
Off to Ghost Island!
You will return in time
for the next immunity.
See you soon !
Naviti, big win.
Take your reward,
go home and enjoy!
Malolo, nothing for you.
Take your things and leave.
Thanks, Jeff.
Come on, Survivor gods!
I knew they heard me.
I'm a little scared, but that's where
I'm supposed to be.
It's my biggest fear here,
to be alone on an island.
I can do anything
with people to talk to.
I am an extrovert.
My game is a social game.
But here,
now that I'm alone,
I try to avoid being hurt
by the idea of ​​Ghost Island.
I try to control my thoughts.
To just see what awaits me.
"Let the game begin!
Follow the fire."
I see that a game awaits me.
My mind is racing.
I get lost in the fire.
Not the best feeling
I had here.
"The Ghost Island Gambling Game."
“I put an advantage in play
if you bet your next vote.
Win and you will have power.
Lose and you won't vote
on the next board."
My stomach is in knots.
There, in Malolo, there are
five ex-Naviti and four ex-Malolo.
If I lose, we lose the majority.
Losing that vote is a huge risk.
Would the gods of Survivor have
given me the white stone
if I wasn't supposed to
come and earn that damn benefit?
In this game where one bad decision
can change your life,
you have to follow your gut.
How hard is that!
But I can't play this game.
I'll keep my vote
for the next tip.
The whole idea of ​​Ghost Island,
it's bad decisions
that haunt you.
So I wonder
if I chose well.
I'm not sure.
If it comes back to haunt me,
I can live with it,
because I did what I think is right.
It's crazy how fast this game...
... creeps into you,
affects who you are
where you want to go,
what you want to do.
I have been betrayed so often
in my personal life.
So in the last two years,
I've really changed my life,
trying to make the right choices
by following my gut.
Barely married, I decided
to end this relationship.
I branched off professionally,
went back to school, got an MBA
and found a great new job.
If I hadn't followed my gut,
I wouldn't be here today.
I believe in staying true to yourself
and following his gut
can get you far in this game.
You have won us food, my daughter!
Health !
Welcome back here, Chris!
I was super cold.
When I was sent to the Island,
I had a plan in the works
to take Dom out by surprise.
I'm eating this like I'm going
to the electric chair tomorrow.
But they chose Morgan.
So I have to understand
the truth about what happened.
Tell me everything.
Get rid of this guy!
My family slit my throat.
None voted Dom.
All three of us voted for me.
Clearly,
they were aiming at me through you.
Wendell and Dom took aim at Angela
to take my power away.
It was a big mistake.
And it will be Dom or Wendell.
It was an opportunity for me
to join the Malolo.
Do you think he has the idol?
He showed us the fake one,
with the shell and the string.
It's a string and a shell.
He is the king of manipulation.
It's Chris versus Domenick.
Between these two, it does not pass.
I like you, you, you and you.
And I like myself.
Chris wants us to take Domenick out.
He says he has an idol.
True or not,
that's what he tells us.
Would we split the votes?
What ? Yes that's it.
Do you like Wendell?
More than Chris.
I speak little with Chris.
Do you prefer Wendell to Chris
or the opposite?
I prefer Wendell.
It would be easy to follow Chris
and take out Domenick and Wendell.
Working with him means nothing to me.
I don't want
Chris leading the charge here.
Yeah, he's trying to dictate
what we all have to do.
In real life,
I was a student at Yale
and sportsman of the first division.
I like to be in charge.
But here it is something else.
I played under the radar.
But I want that to change,
to impose myself in the game.
I don't want you gone,
or Wendell.
The problem
is this whole thing with Chris.
I imagined him gone at this point.
He is always there !
I adore you and Wendell.
I prefer to work with you.
Three is still a good number,
with the right tools.
And I have a tool.
Mmh... I have the idol.
So is it true?
You really lied to us!
Yes. He's an idol.
We're not supposed to talk about it.
I'm telling you
because I want to play with you.
I think Donathan would vote Chris.
It could be Chris.
I want to target it.
Laurel flabbergasted me.
She's here to play hard.
I thought I only had Wendell.
We now know
that Laurel and Donathan
are willing to work with us
to get Chris out.
It changes everything.
That's great. I feel alive again.
Over here, everyone!
Good. Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, Malolo,
I have to take back the idol.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will swim
to a bamboo cage,
l'escalation,
dive down and release a door.
Then you'll pull a heavy chest
to the shore
and along a track.
With a rope, you will hang
the missing section of it,
Replace it
and continue moving the chest.
On arrival,
taking the balls in it,
you will try to place them
on a very narrow perch.
The first tribe that places the five
wins immunity,
is immune from voting.
For the losers: advice,
where a fourth person
will be eliminated from Ghost Island.
Malolo, you are one more,
who will not participate?
The others, a minute of organization
and we get started.
Fine, here we go!
For immunity!
Survivors, ready?
It's a sprint to the cage.
Chris and Wendell leave quickly.
Michael, nice dive!
Everyone must be at the cage
before they can climb it.
Chris and Michael
reach their cages.
Chelsea is there. Go ahead Malolo!
Go ahead, Naviti!
Now we have to go over
and start
releasing the cage door.
Its good !
The Malolos opened the door.
They may start dragging
the trunk, which is very heavy.
The Navitis waste a lot of time
on the gate.
The Malolos walked through the door.
They are progressing.
I can't
get my hands under.
The Naviti are still blocking
on their door.
It's a big lead,
from the start, for Malolo.
The Naviti
have finally opened their doors.
They can start
moving the trunk.
Big advance for Malolo.
You have a good lead, come on!
Here are the Naviti, they are starting
to find the rhythm.
The Malolos
put the safe on the track.
This is how we do it!
The Naviti reach the shore.
They strive to close the gap.
The Malolo are on the track.
Now we have to catch
the middle section
and bring it back to you.
On the first throw,
Sebastian hooks the section!
Now, teamwork
to place it and be able to continue!
So ! Its good !
No longer need the rope!
That's Naviti!
You have to put it on track.
Otherwise, it won't work.
The Naviti have a string of setbacks
in this event.
Huge advance for the Malolo!
Put it on the platform!
The Malolos undo the knots
to release the necessary balls
to finish the test.
Sebastian and Brendan
shoot for Malolo.
Wendell tries to hang his rope.
First throw: missed.
And one for Malolo!
You have to place all five.
Chris takes over.
Naviti has been struggling
since the start of the race.
And two for Malolo!
And another !
It turns to correction!
Naviti fails
to cross this section of track!
It's good, Naviti!
Naviti must place the section!
Everyone is needed!
Two is impossible.
Bring the rope behind!
So ! This time, Naviti is there!
Gently !
Brendan loses one!
This is the respite Naviti needs!
Get active, Naviti!
Ahead !
Let Sebastian shoot!
Brendan places third!
Naviti has to hurry
to open the trunk.
Come on, on the carpet!
Naviti has his balls, Chris rushes!
It's Chris and Wendell!
It would be
a spectacular comeback!
Its good !
Calm. Even if they place some,
everything is fine.
One for Naviti!
Brendan places fourth!
Sebastian could win!
And two for Naviti!
Naviti closes the gap!
Chris up one
but Wendell knocks one down!
Brendan shoots for Malolo.
Go on !
Come on guys !
And four for Naviti!
Here we are !
It's all here!
What a comeback from Naviti!
Everyone can win!
Just not!
Brendan... There he is...
It falls!
Chris succeeds!
Huge return from Naviti!
Naviti wins immunity
and send Malolo to the council!
That
's Survivor-worthy celebrations!
Naviti, what a comeback!
Immunity is yours.
Survivor reminds you,
again and again and again,
that you should never,
ever give up.
Because as long as there is life,
there is hope.
A superb ascent.
No one will leave your tribe.
Take your things, leave.
Enjoy your free evening.
Malolo, this evening, advice.
A fourth person
will be eliminated from the game.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight at the council.
Thank god I followed my gut
and haven't played on Ghost Island.
I still have my vote.
The original Naviti
approach the majority council.
We just have to choose who's going to go.
During nine tenths
of the race, we crushed them.
It was a good effort.
It confirmed what I knew:
we are better than them.
We didn't win, but you
were really good today.
Coming back from the event,
it was dark.
But I couldn't help
but smile,
telling me: "It's fantastic!
We have the power tonight."
I try to play like
a Boston Rob or a Kim Spradlin.
Someone who has a majority,
has control
and just needs to get the situation under control.
Walking around the ex-Malolo
seems to me to be the best tactic.
Talk to me.
I know, but I would like to stay.
We will see.
I can't do better
at this point.
Now, I don't think
these five are going to break up.
So one of us four
is leaving tonight.
And it's frustrating.
I still have so much game in me.
Single mother, my worst fear
is to disappoint my children.
So I hope to still survive.
But for now,
it's not up to me.
And it makes me sick that a guy
like Bradley stays in the game.
Hope
I worry about how much time is left.
We should decide.
So, do they have an idol?
I don't think so, but be careful.
We never know.
We need strength
but there,
in case they have one...
It would be safer
to take one of the guys out.
Yes, they will never see it coming.
We can not know
if the four original Malolo
have an idol.
We bet on the fact
that they'll think we'll want to
stay strong and date a girl.
But we're going to take one of the guys out,
because they won't be expecting it.
Even if they play an idol,
they will miss their target.
So, we vote for Michael?
Are you sure?
I would say Brendan.
They won't suspect it.
Brendan is not dangerous.
He's docile,
it's almost boring.
Brendan is an option tonight
because he likes to play chef.
He's like a dad giving
horrible pep talks.
It's okay with me. Let him be the leader.
The boss never wins.
On the other hand, Michael is strong,
and they won't see it coming.
I think of the smallest detail.
That's why
I'll be a great lawyer.
We are all safe,
Knock on wood, as long
as we don't do anything stupid.
The group has decided
to release strong people.
Michael and Brendan.
Two helpless penguins
on a tropical island.
It scares me
because I'm also a big guy.
But for now,
I follow the movement.
Because these funny Malolo
are completely soft.
High five !
What do you think ?
I'm as paranoid as you.
I have the impression that for the sequel,
strength, they don't care, and...
At least we have an idol.
And so: what do we do with it?
We are badly off.
But we have a card to play.
The idol we found.
But if we play it tonight, Stephanie
and Jenna have to find out first.
Otherwise, they will think they
are kept out.
Good news.
And.
Sworn. She's behind me.
Name of... !
He's James' idol
in Survivor China.
Oh my God !
We go from zero chance
to 25% chance.
Let's roll the dice.
We will get there.
I was just meditating on hope.
Let's act!
What I will do with the idol
will determine my future
and that of my allies.
It will be risky.
But I don't just want
to protect myself for a few days.
We will need luck.
The idol is not enough.
I'll take it out in full council.
I'll say, "I'm going to play
it for one of us four."
Maybe
one of them will turn around.
We have to vote for Bradley.
You agree ?
I'll write his name
on five pieces of paper!
Let's attack it!
Tonight is war
between the two groups.
We have work to
do to reverse the balance of power.
But maybe we could convince
people like Sebastian and Chelsea
that they are at the bottom of their covenant.
The worst mistake of all Survivor,
for me,
this is James leaving with two idols.
I feel responsible
for ending this curse,
to this heritage.
So even
though it's a classic idol,
I have a plan tonight:
lie and expand his power.
If you don't have a torch yet,
take one,
and light it in the fire.
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears, so do you.
Sebastian. First time on the board.
The Naviti seem to be in the majority.
Completely.
The 5 Naviti, we immediately knew
what we had to do.
And I think
we're sticking to it.
Desiree. If there are five solid Naviti
and only four Malolo,
was there discomfort?
Trop hit!
It's the only word that fits.
They know one of them is going out.
Stephanie. Were there attempts
to infiltrate the five Naviti?
Absolutely.
But Bradley made sure
to always know
where his little allies were.
Bradley. Did you feel
any irritation
when Stephanie
said "her little allies"?
Yes, I felt it all day.
I understand their point of view,
but that is what we have to do.
I tried to talk to some,
like a babysitter.
Michael.
He was apparently very tough
to identify a possible flaw.
First, the five Naviti are welded
for their loyalty
was not challenged.
But there are clearly people
at the bottom of the ladder at home.
It's obvious,
it's Chelsea and Sebastian.
Think about it. It's not hard to see.
Bradley is the point guard.
He made you all feel
like a united group,
a democracy.
But if I'm Sebastian,
I'm like, "Wait a second!"
Do you think Bradley
wants to take you further?
You're social, athletic,
no way Bradley will keep you.
But we're an alliance of five.
We all get along well, we like each other.
And we all intend to play together.
Kudos
for making them believe that!
Sebastian. When 4 people say,
"I'm telling you, it's you two.",
you say to yourself deep
down, "Mmh, that's interesting." ?
And how, how interesting!
Jeff, we knew
they were gonna try anything,
but it won't take.
We are not stupid. We know that in
war, when the other side wins,
you have to get your claws out.
It's a "them against us" mentality .
Desiree.
Is it really that simple?
"Sorry, but that's how it is."
Yes I...
It could be as simple,
but tonight it's not.
He's an idol
of Survivor China.
James's, actually.
He had two in his pocket when he left.
And what's cool about
this season,
I'm not going to read it all, but...
James has been cursed for 11 years,
having played neither idol.
I have the responsibility
to reverse the curse.
She has a double power.
She can save two people.
Double immunity.
I'm going to play
it for two of us four tonight.
And I can say that the four of us
let's all vote Bradley.
If any of you want to join us, all
it takes is one vote.
Two, even better.
I hope you will think about it.
Yes. It's hard to hear.
I'm a little surprised to have become
the big threat, the ringleader.
I don't have that impression.
But did I see it coming? No.
Chelsea.
It definitely changes things.
Yes. It's Survivor. You
never really know what is going on.
Of course,
that changes things a bit.
No kidding !
So Sebastian. Is it really
just a roll of the dice?
I do not know.
Who can you last with?
Big shots are respected.
We made it easy for you.
I challenge you: play the game
you came to play!
I agree.
Chelsea,
the hand is outstretched for you too.
But I don't believe
that if we changed sides,
one could advance socially
and break the bond between the four.
You know, we're together
because we don't have anyone else.
We're not a tight-knit quartet.
We were forced to unite.
I'm making this offer
to give you an alternative.
Sebastian.
In the end, it boils down to:
"Who does the best reading
in the other group?"
Pure instinct.
You know, you have to consider
all the scenarios
in her head.
Consider all options.
This is how I play.
I believe tonight is the one
you might think back to
once eliminated:
"Damn, I'm sorry I
didn't!"
With that, it's time to vote.
Kellyn, over to you.
I never in my life
heard a grown man
moan and complain
as much as you do.
I don't know
what just happened there.
I will count the votes.
I believe it's Stephanie.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
I play it for Brendan and me.
In fact...
I play it for Steph.
OK.
This is an immunity idol.
Votes against Stephanie
will not count.
I will read the votes.
Bradley.
Brandan.
A vote Brendan.
Brandan. Four Bradley votes,
three Brendan votes.
Brandan. Equality.
Four votes Brendan,
four votes Bradley,
one vote remains.
Fourth person eliminated
from Survivor Ghost Island:
Brandan.
Bring me your torch.
Hold the pressure.
You will find a way.
My God !
Bendan, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks, Jeff.
It's time to go.
It was a real Survivor duel.
Naviti wins this round,
but the question is:
can this tribe get over it,
to avoid coming back here?
Take your torches,
return to your camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
Build strong relationships...
As long as she flirts with me,
she stays in the game.
I bonded with Chris.
I'm a bit in the middle.
... will keep you level.
Is she there?
Go on !
Wow !
Bitterly disappointed.
It didn't turn out
the way we wanted it to.
That's life. Sometimes we win,
sometimes we lose.
But we defended ourselves well.
After 16 years of applications,
it's a bit hard to swallow.
But an experience rarely
lives up to the expectations we have.
This one was. It was awesome.
I am grateful
for every minute spent here.