Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT GHOST ISLAND,
JACOB WAS FIRST VISITOR TO
ENCOUNTER THE GRAVEYARD FOR BAD
"SURVIVOR" DECISIONS.
AND HE WILLED A CURSED LEGACY
ADVANTAGE TO MORGAN.
IT'S THE LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
I'M TOUCHING IT.
Jeff: AT THE NAVITI TRIBE,
DOMENICK USED HIS FAKE IDOL IN
AN ATTEMPT TO GARNER TRUST.
READ IT.
IT'S SICK.
Jeff: BUT IT BECOME FIRED.
LOOK, I DON'T TRUST HIM.
SOMETHING ABOUT IT IS JUST OFF.
Jeff: THE MALL OF AMERICA
TRIBE WAS FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND JAMES WAS ON THE HOT SEAT.
I COST US THAT CHALLENGE.
I CHOKED.
Jeff: BUT A BLIND SIDE WAS
BREWING.
WE GOT TO GET JACOB.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
JAMES RECEIVED VOTES, BUT JACOB
WAS SENT HOME.
JACOB, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
Jeff: 18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
AFTER THAT TRIBAL I'M FEELING
A LITTLE BIT DRAINED OBVIOUSLY.
IT WAS PRETTY MUCH A ROLLER
COASTER RIDE FOR ME AND MY
HEARTBEAT.
THAT WAS A GOOD PLAN.
I'M GLAD IT WORKED.
JAMES, FOR THE RECORD, PLEASE
DON'T HATE YOURSELF.
I'LL TRY.
TONIGHT I ENDED UP GETTING TWO
VOTES.
I DID DESERVE TO BE THE SECOND
TARGET.
BEING RAISED IN A
KOREAN-AMERICAN HOUSEHOLD HAS
TAUGHT ME TO TAKE OWNERSHIP OF
MY FAILURE, BUT I'M GLAD I'M
STILL HERE.
I'M READY THE FIGHT FOR ANOTHER
DAY.
IT'S TIME TO WIN.
I'M DONE LOSING.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
NAVITI GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW MALOLO TRIBE.
JACOB VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WE'LL BRING DONATHAN IN
RETURNING FROM GHOST ISLAND.
COME ON IN, DONATHAN.
WELCOME BACK.
DONATHAN ALSO GETTING HIS FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW MALOLO TRIBE.
LIB AGREE, TWO CHALLENGES IN,
YOU'VE LOST TWO TRIBE MEMBERS.
WHERE ARE WE RIGHT NOW IN THE
GAME WITH THIS TRIBE?
I STILL FEEL WE'RE UNITED.
WE'RE POSITIVE.
I CAN SAY WE'RE TILL GROWING
INTO THAT BEST TRIBE EVER.
Jeff: BRADLEY, WHERE'S
NAVITI RIGHT NOW?
I THINK WE'RE STRONG.
WE'RE GETTING ALONG REALLY WELL.
IT'S REALLY A COHESIVE BUNCH.
Jeff: SO IT SOUNDS LIKE
BOTH TRIBES ARE FEELING REALLY
GOOD.
WHICH MAKES IT A PERFECT TIME
FOR A SWITCH.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE SWITCHING TRIBES.
DANG IT.
DAMN.
IT'S BEEN REAL, GUYS.
OH.
Jeff: ANGELA, WHAT ARE YOU
FEELING RIGHT NOW BEFORE WE DRAW
BUFFS?
I FEEL A LITTLE BIT OF
ANXIETY, LIKE A BRECKEN FAMILY.
SO IT'S BAD.
Jeff: IS THAT A LITTLE BIT
OF EMOTION?
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVE THESE GUYS.
I DID TWO DEPLOYMENTS IN THE
MILITARY WHERE YOU BUILD STRONG,
LASTING RELATIONSHIPS IN A VERY
SHORT TIME.
TO ME THIS IS EXACTLY THE SAME,
SO I'M ABSOLUTELY NERVOUS ABOUT
THIS SWITCH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO IT.
DON'T OPEN THEM.
WAIT FOR ME.
I'M IN A BIT OF A POWER
POSITION RIGHT NOW, SO I'M KIND
OF FREAKING OUT.
BUT I KNEW I WASN'T GOING TO BE
IN POWER THE WHOLE GAME.
YOU GOT TO RIDE THE WAVE.
THERE'S WAVE THERE, YOU GOT SURF
IT.
Jeff: TWO BUFFS LEFT.
MICHAEL WILL GET TRULY THE LAST
SHOT.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY REVEAL YOUR NEW BUFFS.
SAY HELLO TO YOUR NEW TRIBE.
PURPLE.
WHAT ARE YOU, DOM?
I'M CONCERNED BECAUSE I STILL
HAVE TO DEAL WITH CHRIS ON THIS
TRIBE, SO IT IS CRITICAL TO ME
THAT I BUILD WITH RELATIONSHIPS
WITH EVERYONE OUT HERE IN ORDER
TO TAKE HIM OUT.
Jeff: IF YOU'RE PURPLE,
YOU'RE NAVITI.
HEAD OVER TO THE PURPLE MAT.
IF YOU'RE ORANGE, YOU ARE
MALOLO.
HEAD OVER TO THE ORANGE MAT.
I'M MALOLO.
Jeff: MAKE YOUR MOVE.
HEY, GUYS.
MICE TO FINALLY TALK TO YOU.
I KNOW.
HI.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ON THE NEW NAVITI TRIBE, THERE
ARE FOUR OLD MALOLO, DONATHAN,
LIBBY, LAUREL, AND JAMES.
AN WE HAVE FIVE OLD NAVITI,
DOMENICK, CHRIS, ANGELA,
WENDELL, AND MORGAN.
HOW YOU FEELING, MORGAN?
I'M FEELING GOOD.
PURPLE IS MY FAVORITE COLOR.
WE HAVE A LIVING ROOM.
WE HAVE THE COMFORT.
I'M FEELING REALLY GOOD.
Jeff: AND YOU STILL HAVE
THE NUMBERS.
AND WE STILL HAVE THE
NUMBERS, THAT'S FOR SURE.
Jeff: OKAY.
ON THE NEW MALOLO TRIBE, THERE
ARE ALSO FOUR OLD MALOLO WITH
JENNA, STEPHANIE, BRENDAN AND
MICHAEL AND FIVE NAVITI WITH
DESIREE, SEBASTIAN, KELLYN,
BRADLEY, AND CHELSEA.
KELLYN, IS THERE ANY PART OF YOU
THAT'S NOW WONDERING WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN TO THIS NAVITI
FIVE?
CAN WE ACTUALLY STAY TOGETHER?
I MEAN, JEFF, I FEEL REALLY
GOOD ABOUT PURPLE, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME, THINGS CHANGE.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN, AN I'M EXCITED TO MEET
MORE PEOPLE AND OPEN UP NEW
TREASURE BOXES OF LOVE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
MALOLO, NAVITI, GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD OUT.
THE GAME HAS CHANGED ONCE AGAIN.
FROM THE OUTSIDE IT LOOK LIKE
I WANT TO WORK WITH MALOLO, BUT
MY GAME PLAN IS TO KEEP US
TOGETHER BECAUSE IT WOULD BE SO
EPIC TOO JUST LIKE GO AND KNOCK
OUT THOSE MALOLO TRIBE MEMBERS
ONE BY ONE.
WELCOME.
DOES THIS WILL BE A LOT
DIFFERENT FROM YOUR CAMP?
YEAH.
WELL, MINUS THE PILLOWS AND
THE HAMMOCK AND STUFF.
MAJORITY IS KEY AN CRUCIAL IN
THIS GAME, SO WHEN I LOOKED
AROUND AND I SAW MY FOUR HOMIES
FROM THE OLD NAVITI TRIBE, I WAS
STOKED.
IT'S THE PERFECT SITUATION FOR
ME, SO RIGHT NOW I'M A HAPPY,
SMILEY, GIG LIE PIECE OF LAFFEY
TAFFY.
BANANA FLAVORED.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU JUST THROW
STUFF UP.
SO PROBABLY HALF OF WHAT WE'VE
DONE ISN'T RIGHT OR ISN'T GOOD.
IT'S A NICE BIG SHELTER.
IT'S JUST REAL BUMPY.
TO GO FROM NAVITI TO MALOLO,
I THINK IT WAS A BIT OF A SHOCK
FOR US BECAUSE THE SHELTER IS
JUST ALL TANGLED UP AND ONE BIG
HOT MESS OVER HERE.
THIS IS LIKE WHEN YOU'RE MEETING
A FRIEND'S NEW BABY WHO THEY
THINK IS SO CUTE AND IT'S THE
LOVE OF THEIR LIFE, BUT YOU'RE
LIKE, THAT BABY IS UGLY.
LIKE WHAT HAS HAPPENED OVER
HERE?
IT REALLY IS IMPORTANT TO
TAKE IN HOW BEAUTIFUL THIS IS,
MAN.
YOU GET LOST IN WHAT WE'RE
DOING.
IT'S EASIER THAN "TWO AND A
HALF MEN'S" CAMP.
I BET.
COMPARED TO THEIR BEACH.
THIS IS LIKE A GRASSLAND.
ONE THING THAT STRUCK ME
ABOUT NAVITI IS THEY HAVE DONE
NOTHING BUT COMPLAINING ABOUT
THE CONDITIONS OVER HERE SINCE
THEY GOT HERE.
AND BRADLEY SPECIFICALLY, HE
JUST CRIES ABOUT EVERYTHING.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR," IT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE HARD.
I DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND WHY
IT'S SHOCKING TO THESE PEOPLE.
ON TOP OF, THAT WE'RE DOWN 4-5.
ALL IN ALL, NOT A GREAT SWAP FOR
ME.
WELCOME TO NAVITI, GUYS.
WELCOME HOME.
THIS IS OUR LIVING ROOM.
WOW, YEAH.
THIS IS GREAT, GUYS.
IT GETS A LITTLE COLD OUT HERE
DURING THE EVENING.
TAKE IT TO THE BEDROOM.
WE WRAPPED UP OUR COMFORT
RIGHT HERE.
WE DIDN'T HAVE TOOLS LIKE YOU
GUYS.
WE HAVE OUR NIGHTTIME
FIREPLACE.
I'M DEFINITELY LIKE FLOORED
WHEN I ARRIVE HERE AT THE NAVITI
TRIBE, BECAUSE THEY REALLY GOT
IT GOING ON.
THEY GOT TWO FIRE PITS.
THEY GOT A GOOD SHELTER.
SURE ENOUGH, THEY GOT THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL VIEW THAT I HAVE EVER
SEEN IN MY LIFE.
FROM THE LOOKS OF IT, DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE THIS NEW TRIBE WILLING
GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL ANY TIME
SOON.
WE LOOK STRONG, YOU GUYS.
WE HAVE THE 5-4 ADVANTAGE,
BUT IT'S WAY MORE COMPLEX THAN
THAT, BECAUSE THREE OUT OF THE
FIVE I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE I HAD
HUGE CONNECTIONS WITH, AND DOM
HAS AN IDOL.
THAT SCARES THE HELL OUT OF ME.
I HAVE TO ELIMINATE IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GOING TO
HAPPEN?
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR US NOT TO
CARRY IT.
YOU NEED TO START PUTTING
YOUR ARMY INSTINCT ON AND TOP
THINKING WITH YOUR HEART.
OKAY.
YOU NEED TO --
IF YOU WANT TO WIN, YOU NEED
TO START THINKING LIKE THAT.
LIKE I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
LOOK.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU SOMETHING,
DOM TOLD ME HE HAS THE IDOL.
HE LOOKED FOR A LONG TIME.
YOU THINK HE DOES?
HE DOES.
THE ONLY WAY YOU AND I ARE GOING
TO SURVIVE IS IF WE HAVE EACH
OTHER BOTH.
IF IT'S JUST ME, WE'RE SCREWED.
I BELIEVE THE INFORMATION
CHRIS GAVE ME ABOUT DOMENICK IS
TRUE.
NOW THAT THIS SWITCH HAS
HAPPENED, WE HAVE TO CHANGE OUR
GAME PLAN.
WE NEED THE BLIND SIDE DOM.
I'M GOING ALONG WITH IT, BUT
WHEN CHRIS IS TELL ME STORIES,
I'M CRINGING, BUT CHRIS TALKS TO
YOU INSTEAD OF WITH YOU.
HE WAS GIVING ME ORDERS, FOLLOW
THIS AND STAY ON TRACK.
EVEN THOUGH I'M USED TO GUYS
BARK, ORDERS IN THE MILITARY, I
DON'T LIKE THAT KIND OF
CONFRONTATION AT ALL.
HOW ARE YOU ALL ON COCONUTS?
LET ME ASK YOU GUYS THIS, ALL
FOUR OF YOU ARE ALIGNED,
DOMENICK PROBABLY HAS THE IDOL.
YOU THINK SO?
YES, I KNOW SO.
AN WE NEED TO GET HIM OUT.
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
AND I GUARANTEE YOU HE'S GOING
TO TRY TO SWOOP EVERYBODY.
HE WILL.
YOU LIVE IN NEW YORK.
YOU GET IT.
HE'S NEW YORK E.
I'VE BEEN ON THE HIM SINCE DAY
ONE.
CHRIS STARTED TALKING ABOUT
HOW DOMENICK HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
WE HAVE TO GET HIM OUT.
AN I WAS LIKE, WOW.
WELL, WELCOME TO NAVITI.
WE GOT TO DO IT.
GOT TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
SERIOUSLY, LET'S SHAKE ON IT.
ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY.
CHRIS HAS A BIG PERSONALITY,
SO WHEN HE TALKS TO ME, I HAVE
TO NOD AND SMILE, NOD AND SMILE,
AN ACT LIKE I'M JUST THIS GIRL
THAT HE MIGHT THINK HE CAN TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF AND JUST LICK DRAG
ME IN AS A NUMBER.
WHEN WE GET BACK WE'LL PLAY
IT ALL COOL.
I'LL PLAY DUMB, BUT I'M NOT
GOING TO BE DUMB ABOUT IT.
THAT'S AMAZING.
I KNOW.
LOOK HOW PRETTY THAT IS.
THERE'S IN WAY THAT COULD EVER
GET OLD.
IT'S FREEZING.
I JUST WANT TO BE BACK AT NAVITI
YOU GUYS HAVE DIRT.
WE HAD SAND EVERYWHERE.
I FEEL DIRTY AND GROSS.
OH, MY GOD.
NAVITI PRETTY MUCH HATES
EVERYTHING ABOUT OUR CAMP.
THEY'RE A BUNCH OF COMPLAINERS,
BUT I'M IN THE MINORITY ON THIS
NEW TRIBE, AND I HAVE TO FIND A
CRACK.
SOMETIMES THIS GAME JUST LIKE
LITERALLY THE LUCK OF THE DRAW.
CRAZY, YEAH, BUT NONE OF US
ARE GOING TO FLIP ON PURPLE, SO
IT SUCKS FOR YOU GUYS TO BE 5-4.
WHEN YOU'RE ON THE BOTTOM,
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT IT OUT.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE AS MANY
CONNECTIONS AS YOU.
CAN IT'S FRUSTRATING THAT THIS
KIND OF LUCK CAN ALL OF A
SUDDEN, YOU GO FROM THE TOP OF
THE FOOD CHAIN TO THE BOTTOM.
NO, WE'RE NOT GIVING UP.
SO ME AND STEPHANIE NEED TO FIND
AN IDOL.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY WE CAN SWITCH
UP THE NUMBERS.
WE GO ON MAD DASH.
WE JUST RUN OFF INTO THE WOODS.
AN WE START SEARCHING UNDER
EVERY TREE.
EVERY ROCK, PEBBLE.
ANYTHING?
BRANCH.
THE WELL, TREE MAIL.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SEEING THINGS STARTING TO
JUMP.
WE'RE DIGGING OUR HANDS IN LOGS
COVERED WITH TERMITES AND ANTS.
WE'RE DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN TO
FIND AN IDOL.
IF YOU WANT TO TAKE ME OUT,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE ME
OUT FIGHTING AND SCREAMING
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO DO
EVERYTHING I CAN TO STAY IN THIS
GAME.
THIS COULD NOT HAVE WORKED
OUT MORE PERFECTLY.
WE VOTE THEM OUT.
I THINK IT'S HERE SOMEWHERE.
THERE'S A REAL IDOL SOMEWHERE IN
HERE.
NOW MORE THAN EVER THE OLD
MALOLO FOUR DECIDE WE NEED TO
FIND AN IDOL.
SO NOBODY SHOULD BE SURPRISED IF
A FEW OF US OLD MALOLO FOLKS ARE
OUT LOOKING FOR IDOLS.
THERE HAS TO BE A CLUE OR
SOMETHING.
WE GOT THE IDOL, BRO.
I AM JUST ECSTATIC.
I JUST FOUND THIS HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS FOR ME IS A HUGE SHRIVER
DREAM COME TRUE.
CONGRATULATION, YOU'VE FOUND THE
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS IS ONE OF THE AUTHENTIC
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS.
THIS IS GHOST.
AND THIS IS JAMES' ORIGINAL IDOL
FROM "SURVIVOR: CHINA" IN 20 OP
WHEN HE WENT HOME WITH TWO OF
THESE GUYS.
IT WAS A DECORATION ON THE
ENTRYWAY TO THE TRIBE CAMP THAT
NO ONE EVER SUSPECTED AS A IDOL.
HE PRIDE IT OFF, SURE ENOUGH,
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ON DAY 30 JAMES FOUND HIMSELF IN
A VERY STRONG POSITION.
HE HAD A TIGHT ALLIANCE OF FIVE
AND TWO IMMUNITY IDOLS.
THIS COMBINATION OF POWER LULLED
HIM INTO A FALSE SENSE OF
SECURITY.
AS HIS CLOSEST ALLIES SENT HIM
HOME WITH BOTH IDOLS STILL IN
HIS POCKET.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
JAMES.
JAMES IS THE ONLY PLAYER IN THE
HISTORY OF "SURVIVOR" TO BE
VOTED OUT WITH TWO IDOLS.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS CAN YOU
REVERSE THE CURSE?
AT EIGHT YEARS OLD, FIRST SEASON
I WATCHED WAS "SURVIVOR: CHINA"
AND JAMES WAS ONE OF MY FAVORITE
PLAYERS.
I WATCHED HIM WALK HOME WITH TWO
OF THESE.
TO BE SITTING HERE 11 YEARS
LATER HOLDING THE ACTUAL IDOL
AND BE GIVEN THE CHANCE TO
REVERSE HIS CURSE AND CHANGE HIS
LEGACY IS AMAZING.
THIS IS HUGE, MAN.
EXACTLY WHAT WE WERE LOOKING
FOR.
OH, THIS LITTLE SUCKER.
RIGHT HERE.
OH, WE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO
DO.
I'M WORRIED CHRIS IS GOING TO
TURN ON US BEFORE WE GET HIM.
I THINK HE'S GOING TO TAKE
ANGELA WITH HIM.
HIM AND ANGELA ARE TIGHT.
LIBBY, I LIKE HER.
CHRIS IS ALREADY TRYING TO
GET THEM.
THAT'S WHY WE GOT TO ROPE ALL
OF THEM IN, NOT JUST ONE OR TWO
OF THEM, WE GOT TO ROPE ALL FOUR
OF THEM IN.
THE EASIEST THING WOULD BE
THE FIVE OF US STICK TOGETHER.
I MEAN, AT LEAST ONE VOTE.
BUT I GET THE SENSE THAT CHRIS
DOESN'T WANT TO STAY FIVE STRONG
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T REALLY SEEM
TO HAVE A GOOD CONNECTION WITH
DOM.
SO WE MIGHT HAVE TO GO FOR
CHRIS.
I THINK PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO
GET A LITTLE PARANOID, BUT I
DON'T THINK YOU GUYS HAVE TO
WORRY AS OF RIGHT NOW.
I LOVE YOU.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
WE WERE STOKED WHEN WE SAW YOU
HAD PURPLE.
CROSS MY HEART.
US GIRLS GOT TO STICKING
TOGETHER.
I AGREE.
IMMEDIATELY I KNEW I COULD
BOND WITH MORGAN.
SHE WAS SUPER OPEN AND SUPER
FRIENDLY.
SO I FEEL CLOSER TO MORGAN THAN
ANYONE ELSE ON THE OTHER TRIBE.
I'M NOT SURE WE HAVE A SOLID
NAVITI FIVE.
THE GOOD PART ABOUT PEOPLE
COMING UP TO YOU WANTING TO
TRUST YOU, YOU CAN CHOOSE
BETWEEN WHICH ALLIANCE YOU WANT
TO BE WITH.
I DO FEEL STRONGLY ABOUT MORGAN.
WE CAN WORK TOGETHER.
WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
IT'S FINALLY FEELING LIKE A REAL
ALLIANCE.
I HONESTLY DON'T THINK YOU
GUYS HAVE TO WORRY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
ANGELA.
GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BECOME UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING THE RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF RAMP WALLS THE A SAND PIT
WHERE YOU'LL DIG UP A LADDER,
CLIMB IT, AND RETRIEVE A ROPE.
WE'LL USE THE ROPE TO GET YOU TO
THE TOP OF A TAL TOWER WHERE YOU
WILL SOLVE A PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LOSERS, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
YEAH.
[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: ONE SIMPLE LITTLE
TARP WILL PROTECT YOU FROM THE
RAIN AND THE SUN.
AND WINNING TRIBAL SENDS
SOMEBODY FROM THE LOSING TRIBE
TO GHOST ISLAND.
A LOT AT STAKE AS ALWAYS.
TAKE A MINUTE THE STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET IT ON.
LET'S DO IT!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AN
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
CHRIS AND SEBASTIAN FIRST.
BOTH GET THROUGH.
WENDELL GETS THROUGH.
BRENDAN JUST GETS THROUGH.
BRADLEY'S THROUGH.
JAMES DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
DESIREE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
LAUREL'S GOOD.
THERE GOES DONATHAN.
CAN HE GET THERE?
YES!
ANGELA GOT TO GO BACK.
ALL THE WOMEN OF MALOLO IN A ROW
ARE GOOD.
MICHAEL'S GOOD.
IT'S DESIREE STILL WORKING.
THERE GOES MORGAN.
LIBBY NOW STRUGGLING.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
DESIREE GIVES IT ANOTHER GO?
IS THIS THE ONE?
YEP, YOU'RE GOOD.
START DIGGING.
DOMENICK IS THROUGH.
JAMES GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
GO.
HE'S THROUGH.
HERE GOES ANGELA.
LIBBY WAITING.
ANGELA VERY CLOSE.
SHE'S GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD.
START DIGGING.
YOU'RE NOW DIGGING UP A VERY
TALL LADDER.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: MALOLO NOW HAS THEIR
LADDER OUT.
IT'S NOW MALOLO IN THE LEAD.
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: NAVITI STILL DIGGING,
AND THEY'RE SLOWING DOWN EARLY
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
RUNG TOWARD US.
Jeff: NAVITI HAS THEIR
LADDER.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO USE IT TO
GET SOMEBODY UP 15 FEET IN THE
AIR.
MALOLO TAKING A LONG TIME NOW TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO USE THIS
LADDER.
THAT END DOWN.
LET'S GET IT UP AND WE'LL
ROTATE IT.
Jeff: MALOLO HAS LOST THEIR
LEAD.
WE HAD IT RIGHT.
WHO'S UP.
Jeff: NAVITI NOW HAS CAUGHT
UP AND DONATHAN HEADS UP THE
LADDER.
IT'S NOW NAVITI IN THE LEAD.
A BIG LEAD THAT ORANGE HAD IS
NOW GONE.
CHELSEA HEADING UP THE LADDER
FOR MALOLO.
DONATHAN TOSSING THAT ROPE.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
WE'RE ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
Jeff: CHELSEA STRUGGLING
WITH THAT ROPE.
NOW GOING TO BE CHRIS WITH THE
ROPE FOR NAVITI.
WATCH OUT.
Jeff: CHELSEA'S GOT IT.
GET DOWN.
WAIT FOR CHELSEA.
Jeff: LET HER DOWN, LET HER
DOWN.
CHRIS FALLS SHORT.
MALOLO NOW TRYING TO CATCH UP.
IT'S NOW GOING TO BE SEBASTIAN
WITH THE ROPE FOR MALOLO.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
NOW YOU GOT TO PULL YOURSELF UP.
NICE, NICE.
Jeff: SEBASTIAN HAS HIS.
START PULLING YOURSELF UP.
GO, GO GO,.
Jeff: WE ARE NECK AND NECK
RIGHT NOW.
WENDELL'S UP.
SEBASTIAN'S UP.
LAUREL'S UP.
GOT TO GET EVERYBODY UP THAT
ROPE.
WE ARE DEAD EVEN RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GO, DOM.
HOLD THAT TIGHT.
YOU GOT IT.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: SOMEBODY'S GOT TO GET
UP TOP.
SEBASTIAN TRIES.
HE CAN'T DO IT.
I'M GOING TO GO UP.
Jeff: DOMENICK GETTING A
BOOST.
SEBASTIAN GETTING A BOOST.
IT'S DOMENICK AND SEBASTIAN THAT
ARE UP.
WHO'S NEXT?
GO, GO GO,!
GRAB MY HAND.
Jeff: GO, GO, GO.
SEBASTIAN NOW GETS BRADLEY UP
AND DESIREE.
DOMENICK PULLS LAUREL.
THIS IS TEAMWORK.
BOTH TRIBES WORKING VERY WELL
TOGETHER.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: THIS IS HOW YOU DO IT
ON "SURVIVOR" RIGHT THERE.
ON THE MAT.
Jeff: NAVITI'S GOOD TO
START ON THE PUZZLE.
WHERE'S THE FACE?
NO FACE, NO FACE.
Jeff: MALOLO TRYING TO GET
THEIR LAST GUY UP AND THEY'VE
DONE IT.
OKAY.
ON THE MAT.
Jeff: START ON THE PUZZLE.
Jeff: ALL THAT ADRENALINE
AND ENERGY TO GET YOU HERE.
NOW EXHAUSTED, YOU'VE GOT TO
SLOW DOWN AND USE YOUR BRAIN TO
SOLVE A COMPLICATED "SURVIVOR"
PUSS L.
WORK SLOW.
THINK ABOUT IT.
KELLYN AND BRADLEY FOR MALOLO.
WENDELL AND LAUREL FOR NAVITI.
THEY'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
FIRST WHAT THIS PUZZLE IS.
IT'S GOT TO START SMALL AT
THE BOTTOM AND GET BIGGER.
DON'T TELL THEM.
Amaka: TARP AND IMMUNITY ON
THE LIED.
-- LINE.
TARP GHOST ISLAND AND TRIBAL
COUNCIL AWAITING THE LOSERS.
KELLYN WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT.
MALOLO WORKING TOGETHER VERY
WELL AS A TRIBE.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
Jeff: WENDELL AND LAUREL
FALLING BEHIND.
DON'T SAY THAT, BRO.
Jeff: JUST CALLING WHAT I
SEE.
ANOTHER PIECE FROM BRADLEY AND
KELLYN.
NOW IT'S THE BIG PIECE MAYBE.
Jeff: ANOTHER PIECE FROM
BRADLEY AND KELLYN.
WENDELL JUST FLAT OUT LOOKING
TRYING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
HEY, BRADLEY, RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT HERE, THIS PIECE.
I THINK IT'S THE BIG GUY.
Amaka: ANOTHER PIECE BY
BRADLEY AND KELLYN.
THIS IS BECOMING A BLOWOUT RIGHT
NOW.
DECISIONS ABOUT WHO TO PUT ON
THE PUZZLE PLAYING OUT IN A BIG
WAY RIGHT NOW.
MALOLO MADE VERY GOOD DECISIONS
CLEARLY WITH KELLYN AND BRADLEY.
MALOLO WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD
SENDING NAVITI TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
MALOLO, CONGRATULATIONS.
A DOMINANT VICTORY OUT OF THE
GATE.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
IN ADDITION, NICE TARP.
COME GRAB YOUR REWARD.
ALL RIGHT.
NAVITI, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
AND SOMEBODY'S GOING GHOST
ISLAND, AND MALOLO, YOU'RE GOING
TO DECIDE WHO THAT IS.
IT NEEDS TO BE UNANIMOUS
DECISION, BUT IF IT'S NOT
UNANIMOUS, NAVITI WILL DRAW
ROCKS.
IF YOU CAN'T MAKE A DECISION,
YOU LEAVE IT UP TO CHANCE.
DOES ANYONE DISSENT AGAINST
DONATHAN?
I DISSENT.
DRAW ROCKS.
DRAWING ROCKS.
Jeff: WALK ME THROUGH THAT,
BRADLEY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING THAT THIS GROUP
CAN'T MAKE ONE DECISION?
WELL, THERE'S FIVE US FROM
FORMER NAVITI, AND WE OBVIOUSLY
WANT TO SEND AN ORIGINAL MALOLO,
SO IT MAKES SENSE THAT THE GUYS
DISSENT.
I DON'T BLAME THEM.
I'D DO THE SAME IF I WERE THEM.
Jeff: THERE ARE EIGHT BLACK
ROCKS AND ONE WHITE ROCK.
WHITE GOES TO GHOST ISLAND.
REACH IN AND TAKE A ROCK.
DON'T LOOK.
KEEP IT IN YOUR PALM.
EVERYBODY HOLD YOUR PALMS OUT.
EVERYONE REVEAL.
CHRIS.
Jeff: CHRIS HAS THE WHITE
ROCK.
CHRIS WILL BE GOING TO GHOST
ISLAND.
CAN NOT BE VOTED OUT OF
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THAT'S THE GOOD NEWS.
THE BAD NEWS IS YOU'LL BE OUT OF
THE SOCIAL POLITICS AND HAVE NO
SAY IN WHO DOES GO HOME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT THE
GHOST ISLAND.
BEST OF LUCK, GUYS.
SEE YOU LATER.
THAT SON OF A BITCH CHRIS IS
LUCKY, BECAUSE I WAS REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING RID
OF HIM AT TRIBAL TONIGHT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MALOLO, NO
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
NAVITI, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I AM FREAKING OUT.
BECAUSE SO MUCH OF THIS SEASON
IS ABOUT PLAYERS' PAST MISTAKES,
AND IT'S GOING TO BE 4-4
TONIGHT.
I'M WORRIED WE'RE GOING TO MESS
THIS UP.
DAY NINE JUST TURNED INTO A
NIGHTMARE.
WE LOSE OUR CHALLENGE AND I GET
SENT HERE TO GHOST ISLAND.
FRANKLY, I'M SPOOKED ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW, TONIGHT I'M MISSING A
HUGE TRIBAL COUNCIL IN WHICH I
WAS POLITICIAN A BIG ROLE IN
WHAT COULD HAPPEN.
I HOPE MY PLAN STAYS ELIMINATING
DOM IN A BLINDSIDE.
BUT YOU KNOW I'M SCARED WITHOUT
ME BEING THERE MAYBE IT MIGHT
NOT HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
NOPE.
NOT TODAY.
NO GAME FOR YOU.
AIN'T THAT A BUMMER.
I WAS HOPING I COULD WIN AN IDOL
OR SOME SORT OF ADVANTAGE, BUT
INSTEAD I'M BY MYSELF.
BEING OUT HERE, IT'S NOT EASY.
I'M HUNGRY.
I MISS MY FAMILY.
CRAZY.
I JUST -- IT'S JUST WHAT THE
GAME DOES TO YOU MENTALLY.
I EXPECTED THIS TO HAPPEN AT
SOME POINT.
THIS IS JUST -- THIS HAS BEEN
FIRST DIFFICULT DAY FOR ME.
AROUND THE TRIBE WHEN I'M
STRUGGLING, I HAVE TO BURY IT TO
BE STRONG FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
MY MOM WAS DIAGNOSED WITH M.S.
YEARS BEFORE I WAS EVEN BORN.
MY MOM IS MY HERO.
I SORT OF -- WHEN I HIT A MOMENT
OF WEAKNESS, I THINK OF HER.
SHE'S THE ULTIMATE SURVIVOR.
SHE WAS DIAGNOSED AT 27.
TEN YEARS AGO SHE WAS TOLD SHE
HAD TWO MONTHS TO LIVE AND SHE'S
STILL ALIVE.
EVER SINCE THEN I MADE IT MY
DUTY TO REMAIN STRONG FOR HER.
WHICH HELPS ME WHEN I'M IN A
TRIBE.
YOU HAVE TO DO THOSE THINGS.
BUT I'M HUMAN, AND GHOST ISLAND
IS GIVING ME A CHANCE TO LET OUT
ALL OF MY NEGATIVE ENERGY SO I
CAN REBOOT AND BE THAT AGAIN FOR
MYSELF.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW I WAS THIS
UPSET THINKING ABOUT MY MOM, IT
WAS AWESOME, AND THAT CONNECTION
REALLY HELPED ME.
IT'S CRUCIAL THAT I RECENTER
MYSELF, BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO
BETTER MY GAME GOING FORWARD.
THAT SUCKED.
I BET HE'S HAPPY.
HE'S GOT ALL THE RICE TO
HIMSELF, A BIG BED FOR HIS BIG
HEAD.
WHAT I SEE HAPPENING TODAY IS
THE FOUR MALOLO WILL VOTE FOR
DOMENICK BECAUSE THEY'RE KEEPING
TO CHRIS'S PLAN.
I GOT A TON OF SAND IN MY
DRAWERS AND THAT WATER LOOKED
REALLY NICE.
I GOT THE TAKE A DIP.
I DECIDED I WASN'T GOING TO
GO WITH CHRIS, I WASN'T GOING TO
GO AGAINST MY TEAM.
I WOULD RATHER HAVE LOYALTY
AGAINST DOING SOMETHING I'M
CONTROLLED AT AND NOT HAVING A
CHOICE IN.
HAVE YOU BEEN THINKING ABOUT
WORST-CASE SCENARIOS FOR TODAY?
CHRIS, TALK TO ME.
HE'S STILL ON DOM.
CHRIS SAID MAKE SURE YOU
STICK WITH THE PLAN, MEANING
VOTE WITH THE OTHER FOUR.
THEN THEY WILL SEND DOM HOME.
I DON'T WANT TO VOTE WITH
THEM.
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW, I'M
NOT VOTING ONE OF US OFF.
I'M EXPECTING A SPLIT VOTE, 4-4,
THAT WE'LL HAVE TO PULL ROCKS,
BUT I AM WILLING TO GO TO ROCKS
FOR OLD NAVITI.
I'M STAYING STRONG WITH MY TEAM.
SO WHO WOULD YOU THINK TO VOTE
OFF.
NAVITI.
SNOW SO WORST-CASE SCENARIO,
THEY ALL VOTE DOM, WE VOTE
LIBBY, IT WILL BE THE ROCK DRAW.
ANGELA WANTS TO STAY NAVITI
STRONG, BUT IT'S A LITTLE
SKETCHY TO ME.
SHE'S CHRIS'S RIGHT-HAND MAN.
SO WHATEVER OUR CONVERSATION
WAS, IT DIDN'T HOLD A LOT OF
WEIGHT TO ME.
I DON'T WANT THE DRAW ROCKS FOR
ANGELA, SO I'M GUNG HO ABOUT
GETTING HER OUT OF HERE.
I WAS SO READY TO PULL THE
TRIGGER.
CHRIS IS JUST A LOOSE CANNON.
TODAY WAS HIS DAY.
HE HAS NO POWER IF WE GET HIS
RIGHT-HAND MAN.
ALL RIGHT, COOL, ANGELA.
WELL, HE HAS LIBBY IN HIS
POCKET.
NO, SHE'S NOT.
YEAH, SHE'S WITH US.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL THAT'S EASY.
ANGELA THINKS THAT LIBBY IS
GOING HOME.
BUT I TRUST LIBBY WAY MORE THAN
I WOULD EVER TRUST ANGELA.
YOU WANT THE TAKE OUT ANGELA?
A COMPLETE BLINDSIDE AND
UNANIMOUS MOUSE.
WE ARE ON YOUR SIDE, WE'RE ON
YOUR TEAM.
I SWEAR.
THE PLAN IS TO GET ANGELA OUT
NOW TO SHOW THEM THAT WE'RE ON
THEIR SIDE.
ACT LIKE YOU'RE ALL TOGETHER.
I HAVE IN THE BACK OF MY MIND
THIS FEAR THAT THE FORMER MALOLO
FOUR WILL GO BACK TO THINKING
ABOUT ME BEING A THREAT TO THEM.
SO I MAY EXPOSE THIS FAKE IDOL
TO THE TRIBE SO THEY CAN GAIN
SOME TRUST FOR ME.
CHRIS DAY ONE AFTER ME.
CHRIS DAY TWO AFTER ME.
CHRIS DAY THREE AFTER ME.
AND ON LIKE DAY THREE OR FOUR HE
SAYS TO ME, DO YOU HAVE AN IDOL.
I GO, NO, I DON'T HAVE AN IDOL.
HE SAID, IF YOU DID, I'D SEE WE
COULD TRUST EACH OTHER AND I'D
BE OFF YOUR BACK.
SO I SAW THIS AT ONE OF THE
CHALLENGE, I BUNDLED IT, CHEESY
ROPE, BUT IT'S JUST TREE MAIL.
OH, MY GOD.
SO I MEAN, IT'S A REALLY NICE
SHELL, I EVEN TRIED IT ON FOR
HIM AND EVERYTHING.
I SHOWED IT TO HIM.
BUT IT'S WORTHLESS.
THIS IS THE NONSENSE HE'S BEEN
TALKING ABOUT FROM DAY ONE, ALL
RIGHT.
SO ARE WE GOOD?
NAVITI WANTS US TO VOTE
ANGELA OUT, BUT I SEE DOMENICK
AND I TRULY THINK HE'S CAPABLE
OF LYING STRAIGHT TO MY FACE.
I'M YOUR NUMBER.
IT COULD BE THE CASE THAT HE
HAS A REAL IDOL AND WANTED TO
THROW US OFF HIS PATH BY SHOWING
US THE FAKE IDOL.
FOR REAL ON MY CHILDREN I
WANT TO WORK WITH YOU GUYS.
I'M IN THE SAYING THAT.
I WOULD NEVER SAY THAT.
AIM WITH YOU GUYS.
100%.
IF ANYONE HAS TO GO, I SWEAR
ON MY CHILDREN AND FAMILY,
THAT'S A BAD SIGN.
IF DOMENICK IS VOTING FOR
ANGELA, WHOEVER VOTES FOR US
GOES HOME BECAUSE NAVITI ONLY
HAS THREE LEFT SOME WE CAN
CHOOSE ONE. ONE, THOUGH.
MORGAN.
BECAUSE OF THE IDOL.
I WASN'T KEEN ON THAT IDEA
BECAUSE MORGAN IS SOMEONE I CAN
TRUST, SO I'D RATHER NOT BRING
HER UP IN THIS VOTE, BECAUSE I'D
LIKE THE KEEP HER AROUND AS LONG
AS I CAN.
DOMENICK COULD'DLY HAVE A
REAL IDOL AND BE SHOWING US THE
FAKE IDOL TO THROW US OFF.
I DOUBT HE HAS AN IDOL.
YOU DOUBT IT, BUT WHAT IF HE
DOES?
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE'RE GOING
TO NEED WENDELL AND MORGAN IN
CHALLENGES.
WE DON'T NEED ANGELA.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS, THE
FACT IS ALL FOUR OF US NEED TO
HAVE THE SAME TARGET, SO WE NEED
TO AGREE QUICKLY BEFORE TRIBAL.
I DON'T WANT TO VOTE OUT
MORGAN.
I FEEL LIKE IT WILL BE A LOT
EASIER TO JUST VOTE OUT ANGELA
AND IT BE UNANIMOUS VOTE.
THE BIG QUESTION IS WILL WE BANK
ON THE ALLIANCES WE DID MAKE IN
THE ORIGINAL MALOLO, OR WILL WE
BLEND TOGETHER?
THIS DECISION REALLY TURNS THE
GAME.
EVERY DAY THE STAKES KEEP
GETTING BIGGER AND BIGGER.
Jeff: IF IT'S YOUR FIRST
TIME THE TRIBAL, BEHIND YOU A
TORCH.
GRAB ONE, DIP IT IN, AND GET
FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
ALL RIGHT, SO MORGAN, YOU GO
BACK THE CAMP WITH CHRIS AT
GHOST ISLAND 4-4.
YEAH, WE PRETTY MUCH SPLIT UP
INTO OUR GROUP OF FOUR, BUT AS
OF RIGHT NOW, BOTH TRIBES ARE
STAYING SOLID WITH THEIR GROUP.
Jeff: WENDELL, IS THAT
REALLY IT?
IT WAS JUST ONE GROUP OF FOUR
AND ANOTHER GROUP OF FOUR?
YEAH, WE WERE ON THE BED
PLOTTING TOGETHER.
THEY WERE OVER IN THE LIVING
ROOM PLOTTING SOME KIND OF
STRATEGY.
ALL YOU CAN HOPE FOR IS FOR
SOMEONE TO MAYBE CRACK, MAYBE
PULL SOMEBODY OVER.
Jeff: HOW ARE YOU GOING TO
PULL SOMEBODY OVER IF THEY'RE IN
THE LIVING ROOM AND THEY'RE IN
THE KITCHEN?
GOOD QUESTION.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GET OUT
OF THE KITCHEN AND GO TALK TO
SOMEBODY.
Jeff: DOMENICK, ARE YOU
SURPRISED THAT IT WAS SO
SEPARATED GIVEN THIS IS FOR
SOMEBODY A MILLION DOLLAR VOTE
TONIGHT.
YEAH, JEFF.
IF THIS GOES 4-4, I KNOW I DON'T
WANT MY FATE TO BE DETERMINED BY
A ROCK, SO I ACTUALLY DID STEP
OUT OF THE KITCHEN A LITTLE BIT,
AND I JUST EXPLORED THE
SITUATION TO SEE IF THERE WERE
ANY CRACKS, JUST TO SEE WHAT
EVERYONE'S THINKING.
Jeff: ANGELA, HOW ABOUT FOR
YOU?
WHAT DID YOU SEE WHEN YOU GOT
BACK THE CAMP.
I GOT OUT OF THE KITCHEN, AS
WELL, AND TALKED.
AND TONIGHT I'M ON THE FENCE.
I CAN GO WITH THE POPULAR
DECISION OR THE RIGHT DECISION
FOR ME.
BUT I'VE GOTTEN AN IMMENSE
AMOUNT OF PRESSURE, SO RIGHT NOW
I WANT IT TO BE MY DECISION FOR
ME.
I AM STUNNED BY WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING RIGHT.
NOW WHEN WERE YOU PRESSURED?
WHEN WE SWAPPED TRIBES, CHRIS
STARTED TRYING TO PULL MALOLO'S
MEMBERS OVER TO US.
AND IT WAS MORE PRESSURE VERSUS
ANYBODY ELSE HAVING AN OPINION.
CHRIS ISN'T HERE.
CHRIS IS GONE.
Jeff: SO MORGAN, DO YOU
THINK THERE IS CHANCE THAT
DESPITE CHRIS, THAT IT COULD
ACTUALLY MAKE THE FOUR NAVITI
HERE TONIGHT TIGHTER?
I THINK SO.
I FEEL LIKE WE ALL HAVE REALLY
GOOD RELATIONSHIPS.
BUT YOU KNOW, FOUR NEW PEOPLE
GOT ADDED, SO WE'RE TRYING TO
BUILD OUR RELATIONSHIPS WITH
THEM, AS WELL.
Jeff: DOMENICK, ARE YOU
FEELING THAT?
ARE YOU FEELING DIFFERENT
RELATIONSHIP, AS WELL?
ABSOLUTELY.
I FEEL REALLY COMFORTABLE WITH
THIS NEW FOUR.
I FEEL A SENSE OF NEW
POSSIBILITY.
AND I'M ALWAYS OPEN TO HEAR
PEOPLE OUT.
OKAY.
I WANT THE HEAR WHAT PEOPLE HAVE
TO SAY, AND I'LL MAKE A
DETERMINATION AS TO WHETHER OR
NOT I WANT TO GO AHEAD WITH THAT
OR NOT.
Jeff: JAMES, EVERYBODY HAS
WITHIN PAINTING THIS BEAUTIFUL
LITTLE PICTURE THAT ONE GROUP OF
FOUR ARE OVER HERE AND ANOTHER
GROUP IS OVER HERE, BUT THE MORE
QUESTIONS I ASK, THE LESS
ACCURATE THAT SEEMS TO BE.
YES, I AM KIND OF SURPRISED.
I MEAN, FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, IT
WAS A STRONG NAVITI FOUR.
MAYBE IT'S NOT THE CASE ANYMORE
ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW?
Jeff: OR MORGAN, MAYBE THIS
IS PART OF A PLAN.
YOU CAN'T EVER KNOW WHAT TO
TRUST AT TRIBAL.
YEAH.
RIGHT NOW WE COULD ALL BE
SITTING HERE COMPLETELY LYING,
OR WE COULD ALL BE TELLING THE
TRUTH.
ARE WE ALL GOOD ACTORS AND
ACTRESSES, OR ARE WE BEING REAL?
ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
LIBBY, HOW DO YOU DISCERN
WHEN IT'S OKAY TO LIE TO
SOMEBODY AND WHEN YOU NEED TO BE
HONEST?
I LIKE THAT YOU ASKED ME THAT
QUESTION.
Jeff: WHY DO YOU LIKE I
ASKED YOU?
PEOPLE THINK THE NICE GIRL,
THE SWEET ONE IS NOT OKAY WITH
LYING, BUT YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE
EVERYONE BELIEVES YOU IF YOU
WANT SOMETHING DONE, SO YOU HAVE
TO BE OKAY WITH FIBBING
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT'S JUST THE
GAME.
Jeff: MORGAN, EVEN AS LIBBY
WAS SAYING IT, THE SMILE WAS
GROWING BIGGER, THE CHARM MORE
BROAD.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HER.
YOU JUST WANT TO TRUST HER.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
IT'S LIKE HOW COULD THIS GIRL
EVER LIE, BUT THAT'S PART OF THE
GAME.
EVERYONE IS LYING.
EVEN LIBBY.
I'M SURE WILL LIE OR HAS LIED AT
SOME POINT.
Jeff: SO WENDELL, AS YOU
SIT HERE, WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
JUST BIG PICTURE?
I'D LIKE THE HOPE THAT
SOMEONE MAKES A MOVE AND THAT AT
THE END OF TONIGHT WE'RE A
STRONGER TRIBE AND WE WANT TO
WORK TOGETHER AND ACTUALLY START
WINNING SOME THINGS.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
LAUREL, YOU'RE UP.
Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE LIBBY.
ANGELA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ANGELA, ONE
VOTE LIBBY.
MORGAN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ANGELA, TWO
VOTES MORGAN, ONE VOTE LIBBY.
MORGAN.
WE'RE TRIED, THREE VOTES ANGELA,
THREE VOTES MORGAN, ONE VOTE
LIBBY, ONE VOTE LEFT.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND,"
MORGAN.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WHAT?
Jeff: MORGAN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
DON'T TRUST THE CUTE BLOND.
Jeff: WELL, TONIGHT'S
TRIBAL CENTERED AROUND WHETHER
YOU WERE LOCKED IN OR SOMEBODY
WAS GOING THE MAKE A MOVE.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY MADE A
MOVE.
THAT IS HOW YOU PLAY "SURVIVOR."
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN THERE'S NOWHERE
TO RUN --
WE MADE ENEMIES.
Jeff:  -- AND NOWHERE TO
HIDE.
IT'S FRUSTRATING BECAUSE I
HAVE SO MUCH MORE GAME TO PLAY.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO STAY
ALIVE.
WE CAN OPEN THIS GAME UP.
LET'S MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
I ACTUALLY HAVE THE LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO DO ME
GOOD.
OBVIOUSLY IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
SO THIS MIGHT BE CURSED NOW, BUT
I AM WILLING THE ADVANTAGE TO
DOMENICK.
HE WAS ALWAYS OPEN AND HONEST
WITH ME.
HOPEFULLY THIS ISN'T A CURSE.
IF IT IS I'M REALLY SORRY.