Previously on Survivor...
At the Naviti,
it was the war
between Chris and Domenick.
Between these two, it does not pass.
And the original
Navitis were tearing each other apart.
My family slit my throat.
All three of us voted for me.
Clearly,
they were aiming at me through you.
The Malolos were preparing for the council.
And the ex-Naviti were united
against Jenna, Michael and Stephanie.
Fortunately, we have the majority.
We have control and we lead the dance.
At the council,
the Naviti alliance remained united...
Stephanie, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Michael and Jenna
on their own.
There are 15 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
Over here, everyone!
Naviti,
discover the new Malolo tribe.
Stephanie was eliminated
at the last council.
Good.
Naviti string together victories,
Malolo the defeats.
Let's see what will happen now.
Throw away all your bandanas!
We change the tribes.
Throw them away !
Bon sang!
Michael, how are you feeling?
You chained defeats.
It's never good,
regardless of alliances.
From a game perspective,
it might save my life.
We, the Malolos, were in the minority
since the first mix.
Now that things
are changing again,
maybe there is hope
for Jenna and me.
James, what's going on now,
game-wise?
Well we all survived
to the so-called
first phase of the game.
Now it's a race
towards fusion and beyond.
This day can be decisive
for everyone's strategy.
Alright, shall we go?
Yes.
We do not have a choice.
New bandannas.
Don't open, wait for my signal.
Why, Jeff? Why do that ?
Depending on what I'm shooting,
I can be in trouble.
So I pray
that fate will play its part
and protect me.
Fate is my buddy.
This is my prayer.
Last one for you, Domenick.
Good. Everyone
unpack their bandana.
Let's see which tribes you are in.
Please...
Malolo.
Yes Naviti!
And you will quickly discover...
... a third color.
Green ?!
We go from two tribes...
... to three tribes.
If you have purple:
purple carpet.
Orange: orange carpet.
Green: in the center.
Do you have purple?
Hi.
It's booming?
Delighted.
Likewise.
Ma petite!
I was told about the legendary Sebastian.
Thin. Good luck to you.
That rascal Chris
was always after me.
Getting away from him is a relief.
For the first time, I have my hand.
I can decide
the direction of the game.
Wow. That's a mix!
There are three original Naviti
and two original Malolo
in each of the three Tirbus.
Bradley, at this point
it's really hard
to rely on purple or orange.
'Cause there's now been enough
interconnection between people
so that we no longer know
where is placed who.
For me, it remains: do the
original divisions persist?
Or are there new things?
I do not know.
I am delighted to discover it,
to see where everyone is.
Donathan, is this good for you?
Bad ?
Neutral ?
No idea !
I do not know these two,
I am delighted to discover them.
We have three Naviti 2.0s
and two original Malolos.
Will they stay together?
Libby and I have sex?
I do not know.
Sebastian, one thing goes
with a new tribe:
a new beach. No shelter.
Yes, we have to start from scratch.
But we have strength at hand.
It won't be a problem, Jeff.
It's a fact: in Survivor,
it's at pivotal moments
let the strong players shine
and the weak fade.
And whatever you feel
right now,
your chances of going all the way,
with 15 people still in play,
are better than at the beginning of the game.
Hold on to that!
A brand new start
in Survivor Ghost Island.
Yanuya is your name.
Here is a map leading to your camp.
Follow the beach.
Good luck with the new shelter!
Naviti, Malolo,
get your stuff, back to camp.
The game has changed again.
I was hoping for a better mix.
But even if I remain in the minority,
it may be a new start.
I have to make the most of this
opportunity, and that's my intention.
Damn, yeah!
Sweet hearth!
Rice !
Yeah !
The fishing kit!
We are never going to lose.
We have skills
in all categories.
I want to talk to you.
I moved.
We're going to talk about furnishings.
It shakes a little
to have to start from scratch.
But I was in a tribe
chaining defeats.
I want to know the victory,
the pleasure of having to eat,
not to go to every board.
It comes at the right time,
I'm excited.
Sea bass, I have something for you.
Stopped ! Did you save it?!
Thank you my brother !
I knew we would meet again.
My shell.
He schlings.
He is perfect.
I found him when he was alive.
I like to collect memories.
That's why
I still have these necklaces.
I kept this seashell
found on the old Naviti camp.
Wendell had the heart
to bring it this far,
her bag smelling of dead shellfish.
Wendell, I love you.
No problem. It was written !
I spent little time with Wendell
because he was friends with Domenick
and I worked with Chris.
He's the buddy
who was never my buddy.
But he knows who I am and
we barely know each other. Pretty cool.
Ready to merge?
Yeah, all right!
I'm glad we left.
You were seeing the wrong person
at the wrong time.
I know it. It's a new day.
I was more than ready
to throw off my bandana.
Because I found myself trying
to manage two oversized egos,
Domenick and Chris,
who each want to kill the other.
And even if I'm a little sad
not to have my friend Dom anymore,
I was excited
to be with Chris again.
He is an outstanding sportsman
with a terrible track record here.
Now
listen to Chris boast,
I don't like bragging and boasting at all.
Laurel, do you play volleyball?
Yes, I did.
I played beach volleyball.
To see you, I'm not surprised.
I did too.
Really ?
I played it in Cocoa Beach, actually.
Oh?
Two years ago.
That's where I was playing.
I played in Chicago once.
Our team won the tournament.
When you are a great
charismatic sportsman like me,
No lie, it's exhausting.
Some may settle down
and let the game evolve.
Me, I have to anticipate,
develop such and such a link,
because I've had an "X" on my back
since day one.
I see myself as an entrepreneur,
even if I currently have
few investments in progress.
I invest in myself.
I can see you
giving motivational seminars.
It's hard not to answer Chris.
He likes to listen to himself talk.
But I've been through
different situations
and have always managed
to adapt, to get along with everyone.
I have this ability to adapt
to the people around me,
to be what they need.
I'm also a model, actually.
Model ?
I didn't tell anyone.
In fact, I told Libby
I had been.
But you continue?
Yes.
I hesitate to call myself a model because...
For some crazy reason,
people see models
as self-centered, dumb...
Things that might
not work for me
as part of a tribe.
You know, I'm not saying it,
but I'm under contract
in Miami, Chicago, New York.
Obviously.
He must have thought to amaze
me by telling me to be a model.
The big reveal.
But I kinda don't care.
Athlete, model,
personal trainer, whatever.
It's good to have him,
he's a competitor.
He has the rage to win,
that makes him an asset.
But I think Chris
is starting to swell the tribe.
I don't know what to think of Chris.
Apparently, if you listen to him,
he likes you.
I'm having a little trouble closing it.
Yeah, it's tiring.
Yeah.
We're fine with letting
him do his thing,
dig his own grave.
As long as we win, don't worry
about smiling and nodding.
But if we lost,
Chris would be in big trouble.
Whoops !
I like this quintet.
I believe we will prosper.
Yes, we have a good mix of skills.
Our chances are good.
Yes.
Straight to the merge!
Exactly !
Mixing the tribes again
is crazy.
But everything is fine.
In my old tribe, Naviti,
there were five of us and we stuck to it,
taking out the Malolo one by one.
Now Ang, Kellyn and I
are still in the majority, 3 2.
The question is Angela.
She's been with James
for quite a while.
So I don't know what she has in mind.
It was not
a battle between tribes,
more of an internal battle
between Chris and Dom.
Basically, Wendell and Domenick
told us:
"Let's get out Angela,
she's Chris's right hand, she's dangerous."
And so, Domenick, Morgan and Wendell
voted Angela,
allowing the Malolos
to eliminate Morgan.
Turns out Dom and Chris
couldn't breathe a breath,
get along for a few votes
and maintain the strength of the Naviti.
Instead,
they attempted to take Angela out.
I'm starting to feel
like that might be a problem.
So back at camp,
I was seriously pissed.
When I saw it was
James and me against three Navitis,
I was afraid of being next.
But I found out that Angela
was betrayed by her own tribe.
And she is angry.
I'm here thanks to the Malolos.
Not because of my family,
but because you saved me.
But it's a new day!
Yes.
New tribe.
I am delighted.
It is enormous. There are cracks
in the Naviti group.
They've already betrayed Angela.
So maybe James and I
can work with her.
Dude, good to see you.
I was in danger non-stop!
Both of these tips
seem to have been awful.
How do you analyze Kellyn and Des?
Are they super close?
Inseparable. Believe me.
These five were welded,
you wouldn't believe it.
We had solid arguments,
but they did not flinch.
Bad mix for me.
Here I am again at the bottom of the ladder,
and as a bonus,
I'm not that close to Michael.
In fact, he voted for me
on the second board.
However, I still believe we
are on the same wavelength,
because we are only two Malolo.
So we have to work together
and I think he knows it.
How do you see Angela?
Is she close to them?
The thing is that we,
the four ex-Malolo, we saved her.
So let's hope
she feels indebted.
But we have work to do.
Welcome to the house !
The dump we came from,
you wouldn't believe it.
Returning to the Naviti camp
is like going from a hovel to a palace.
We have coconut, leftover rice,
coffee... We survive here.
Cushions, blankets...
Coffee?!
It was like
winning an award!
I'm so happy.
Strategically speaking,
Dom is a good ally.
And Chelsea was voting with me.
So in theory, the ex-Naviti
dominate, three against two.
But there are many unknowns
about this new camp.
I had no idea coffee
could make such a difference.
You cry ?
You look like you're crying!
It reminds me of home.
But yes !
In recent days, at Camp Malolo,
we didn't eat, or barely.
We had lost
four races in a row.
I was completely drained.
Coming here, having this amazing camp,
and then this coffee,
it made me feel at home
and made me think I had
the energy to survive here.
If you catch me smiling,
it's because of my relief.
Not having Chris on your back...
It's nice.
I feel like I
can finally let go.
For the first time,
I'm relieved
from Chris' constant monitoring ,
who repeated:
"Let's get out Dom, let's get out Dom!"
You would see
the shit I did!
A seashell on a string!
But it worked!
I can believe it.
Perhaps he still believes it to be true.
I feel like I'm
not on defense anymore,
and even to have control.
There are three original Naviti
and I'm comfortable with Donathan.
We are together.
At the same time,
they could manipulate me,
as I was the first time
by Libby.
So, no more half measures.
It's time to get your hands dirty.
Libby is a demon
in an angel body.
She is bloodthirsty.
Who does she think she is dealing with?
I see clearly in his game.
I can sit ?
Sure.
Every time I talk to her,
she remains evasive.
Libby? Not good. She has to go,
at least as much as Chris.
Where are you at with Donathan and Libby?
Libby is...
But she'll kill you right away.
She has a power of seduction.
She manipulates everyone
with her southern charm.
This is Parvati 2.0.
Thank you for the information.
Dom told me to beware of Libby.
She is really dangerous.
So if we go to the council,
Libby is strategically
the best person to eliminate.
As long as we are solid, we have Chelsea.
You do not have to worry.
I'm glad to be back here,
but also to play with you.
You are my closest ally here.
Reconnecting with Dom is great.
He's a great ally for me.
We are on the same wavelength,
it is excellent.
Game-wise, I may be
better than I thought.
Well, I thought I was fantastic,
but maybe I really am,
because I feel like I'm
playing at the top level.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for your first
immunity test
as new tribes?
Yeah !
First of all Libby...
I take back the idol.
This idol is no more.
Because now...
two tribes
fight for immunity.
Two tribes will be shielded from the vote.
Shall we do it?
Yeah !
Today
one person will be your voice.
The others will be blindfolded.
By verbal commands alone,
the voice will guide blind duos
to collect
three bags of puzzle pieces.
The three bags recovered,
the voice will guide a duo of blind people
to solve the puzzle.
The first two tribes
to complete their puzzle
gain immunity,
are shielded from the vote.
The losers: on the board,
someone will be the 6th person
eliminated from Survivor Ghost Island.
One minute of organization
and we begin.
Alright, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go for it !
Stay together!
Straight !
Not diagonally, straight ahead!
Desiree is the voice of Malolo.
Faster, there are no obstacles!
Wendell, Yanuya's voice.
Chris, straight ahead!
Laurel, well, keep going!
And Domenick, the voice of Naviti.
Straight ! Straight !
Who will communicate best
with his two duos?
That's the whole point of this test.
Laurel!
Yes ?
At the top ! Raise your arms!
Laurel is on the first sack.
Move! No no !
Both hands! Both hands!
I got it !
Kellyn is on the first sack.
Go on !
Chelsea! To the right !
Stop!
So ! Go under!
Chelsea, below!
On your right ! Dig ! Dig !
You are there! Michael and James!
Michael is on a sack for Malolo.
Dig!
Kellyn releases this first bag.
Come to my voice!
Pick it up!
Donathan and Chelsea are on a sack
for Naviti.
It's our bag!
Donathan, non! Donathan!
Do you have it, James?
What do I have ?
Why is he yelling my name?
Nope !
It's our bag! Go on !
We fight over the bag.
Chelsea, no!
Chelsea holds it, Michael too.
We have two duos
from two different tribes
fighting over the same bag.
Someone is wrong.
Let go!
It's our bag!
U-turn!
Chelsea and Donathan dropped the bag.
U-turn, under and to the right!
Come here ! Towards my voice!
Angela and Kellyn
brought their first bag.
Just there ! Move to the right!
You and it is!
Bring back the 3rd!
The Malolos have two bags.
Michael and James
go to find the third one.
Wendell, where are you?
Here !
Now
go back to your right.
Towards the left ! Left !
Still no bag for Naviti.
Two bags for Malolo.
All right, Michael!
A bag for Yanuya.
Sea bass, to the left!
And nothing at all for Naviti.
There you go, Chelsea and Donathan
have a bag for Naviti.
Follow me !
Below, Donathan!
There, go under!
Libby and Bradley
have Naviti's second bag.
Chris, five steps back!
Laurel! Laurel, turn right!
I am lost.
Laurel, all right!
Sebastian and Chris
would like to be guided.
Stuck in the middle of nowhere,
they search.
Chris, behind you!
To the left !
At your feet! At your feet!
Just there !
Get it!
Big fall from Michael.
He digs for Malolo.
Bradley! Follow my voice!
Watch out for the pole!
Big shock for Libby...
How are you, Libby?
... On the chin!
Sebastian and Chris
walk away with Yanuya's second bag.
Go to your left!
No, your right!
Michael and James
bring back Malolo's last bag.
They lead in a race,
for the first time in a long time.
Third bag for Malolo!
Desiree must now lead them
to the puzzle table,
eyes still blindfolded!
I protect you!
Donathan and Chelsea collaborate
for Naviti's third bag.
You are there! Go on !
Below!
Desiree issues orders
to her foursome.
Nope ! Here ! Follow my voice!
They have to cross the sawdust again,
still blind.
But they lead
and feel their wings growing.
Go on !
Huge advance for Malolo.
Go on ! Go on !
Go on !
Desiree and the Malolos
are at the puzzle table.
Now she must guide
two blind Malolo
to solve the puzzle.
Donathan and Chelsea
are on Naviti's latest sack.
Good teamwork!
Donathan rotates Chelsea.
He descended ! Let go!
Yanuya has all three bags.
Wendell goes down.
Follow my voice!
Here are Donathan and Chelsea,
with the third bag!
Oh ! Chelsea hits the post!
It's a race
to the puzzle table.
Grosse avance de Malolo.
They are already on the puzzle.
Yanuya arrives, led by Wendell.
And Naviti, led by Domenick.
Come on ! We are late !
Dom, slower!
We are late !
It's teamwork.
You need to get back up, and fast.
Stay on my ankles!
Two tribes
go through the central tunnel,
trying to reach the puzzle,
where Malolo is already hard at work.
The Malolos would love to win.
Kellyn and Angela are on the puzzle,
guided by Desiree.
Fit it into the triangle!
Wendell arrives for Yanuya.
And the 3rd bag?
Where is the bag?
Domenick right behind.
The 3rd...?
Where are their bags?
Wendell, the leader,
left without having all the bags.
A terrible setback
that will have a price for Yanuya.
Put it in the triangle!
Feel the hole!
In the triangle!
Desiree yells at her tribe.
No progress of Malolo
despite their huge lead.
Who are you talking to ?
To Eng.
The puzzle is a circle.
Domenick has the crucial place.
He will be a hero or a zero.
Here I am !
Wendell is under pressure to catch up
what he caused his tribe to lose.
First that, place it in the circle.
You need white...
But which one is it?
If you cannot guide
your blind companions,
you will go to the council.
Push it to the right!
Again and again !
Wendell, who caused
a major setback to his tribe,
quickly regain time.
In the circle! Hit the table!
Just there !
Desiree, who hadn't been able to
complete the puzzle on the first day,
is in charge of the puzzle on the 17th day.
Nope ! The round coin
you have in your hand, Kellyn!
It goes in the triangle.
Now put the round piece.
New piece for Yanuya.
Do you see that! The Yanuya
are back, they lead!
The Naviti are now fighting
against the Malolo.
The outer circle is finished.
The next one, turn it over!
The Malolo take the rhythm.
Yes ! Slide it!
This test
is based on communication
between the voice
and the duo taking care of the puzzle.
Return it!
It would be a huge comeback
for the Yanuya,
who were dead last
at their puzzle table.
Now they
are leading and close to victory!
Push it! Punch!
So ! They think it's good!
So Probst?
And that's the case !
Yanuya wins immunity!
There is one spot left!
Now it's Malolo and Naviti,
like in the good old days,
which confront each other.
The Naviti are progressing.
Perfect, good!
Only two more pieces for Malolo.
Two more for Naviti.
Which tribe will conclude?
Desiree screams for Malolo.
Reverse them!
Don't yell at me,
I'm doing my best.
In the other direction, turn!
Domenick screams for Naviti.
Put... Yes, it's good!
Is it right ?
That's a puzzle!
Naviti wins immunity!
Returning Malolo to the council
for the third consecutive time.
Wendell, in Survivor, the voice,
it's the hero or the zero.
Today you were both,
but in the end, the hero prevailed
for Yanuya.
Thanks, Jeff.
Immunity is yours.
No advice tonight.
Another victory for Naviti.
Good job.
Naviti, Yanuya,
take your things, return to camp.
Thanks, Jeff!
Have a good evening !
Malolo, for the fifth time
this season:
the council, where a sixth person
will be eliminated.
Take your things, leave.
See you tonight at the council.
The immunity test was
a total and utter failure.
I surrender once again
to a council.
This will be my fifth, out of six.
It sucks.
This is Survivor Ghost Island.
We want to reverse curses,
not create new ones!
I'm sorry.
The immunity test today
was probably
the worst moment of my life.
I wanted this to be the moment
when I proved myself.
In general, out of the game,
I feel like I
have to prove myself
and I usually
exceed expectations.
And... I failed.
I feel
like the worst loser.
Are you sorry for the test?
In case we can't
talk about it anymore: do we say James?
How are you?
Take out a strong man,
even if you want to win so much?
It's James or me.
Because of me, someone is going to leave.
And it sucks.
But I'm still
a player in this game.
So the plan tonight
is to eliminate James.
Nobody really has a connection
with him.
I feel like I
don't know him.
So even though it should be me,
James is going to leave.
Without wanting to judge too quickly...
Des screwed up.
Clearly. It was his fault,
not Kellyn's.
Yeah.
Have you spoken with Angela?
No.
Because... Without it, we're done.
Yeah.
At this stage,
the ex-Naviti are in the majority.
So Michael and I
are clearly off to a bad start.
But a strong player, in Survivor,
must be able to
receive bad cards
and get away with it.
Finish last...
Malolo seems cursed.
Yeah.
When I was two years old, my family
moved to South Korea.
And at 16, I decided
to come back to the USA alone,
to make my way
in a new country.
I had to adapt to a new life,
a new language,
a new school without friends,
and learn to relate to people.
This experience
prepared me for this moment.
Because the heart of Survivor
is to bond with other humans.
I don't want it to be
one of us tonight.
What do you think ?
Well...
Kellyn and Des
are really, really close.
So I'm probably
at the bottom of the scale.
See what happened
last time.
It's not you who voted
for me, but mine!
I assure you,
if you work with me,
you won't be down for anything.
I trust James.
And in this game,
relationships are everything.
In the army, it was like a family.
I was surrounded by great friends.
When I retired, I lost
this great piece of family.
Then my daughter
went to university.
Then I started my divorce.
And now I'm alone.
I don't know,
it's hard, that's all.
It's hard.
But it's positive,
because I grew up learning
to focus
on the happiness of others.
Now I'm...
Focused on me.
I try to know where I'm going,
what I want to do.
So... ?
Are you okay, Michael and you?
What do you think ?
We agree, we will act together.
Really ?
So...
If you're ready to vote Des...
We clearly need strength
to progress.
Yeah.
I want us
both to come back to camp unharmed tonight.
I had many
real discussions with James.
And while wanting
to remain loyal to Naviti,
I must first take care of myself.
So the only question is:
how to go further in the game?
What do you have in mind for tonight?
I am not sure.
The five of us stayed , Bradley, me,
Sea bass, Chelsea and Des,
all the way.
It was self-evident.
And what do you say now?
Well... I hope...
You want to work with me.
I thought Angela
was ready to work with Des and me.
Instead of which
she comes across as super paranoid,
which makes me very nervous.
'Cause I can see Angela
wanting to save James
and go after Des or me.
I feel great with Des.
Really ?
We've been together from the start.
We have the majority, seen like that.
Des and I will vote together.
I would love for you to work with us.
Stick together when it's chaotic.
This is where it gets tricky.
I'm more uncomfortable
before this advice
than ever before in the game.
From the start, I could never
trust Angela 100%.
She goes in all directions.
I doubt she fully understands
what's going on in her own head.
And that is dangerous.
I pray it works.
But tonight will tell us
if Naviti finally fractured,
if it's still
Oranges versus Violets,
or if everything has turned brown.
Good. So.
We all know the headline.
Malolo is perhaps
one of the worst tribes,
in terms of performance
in the tests,
we've ever had.
You may never win
an event as a team.
Desiree. What do you feel
when you're down,
advice after advice?
When we lose, when we are at the bottom,
when things are going badly,
it's an opportunity to reflect
on who we really are,
as if a mirror were being held up to you.
And I fully assume
today's defeat.
And above all, I blame myself.
What ?
I wanted this to be the moment
when I could say:
"I did it !"
And it was...
"I did that?! Oh, my God!"
But what makes a winner,
it's how you get up
after a fall.
So now
I just have to get up.
James. There was an ordeal
where you felt responsible.
You received votes and said:
"Yes, it is deserved."
Would it be fair to eliminate someone
for losing immunity?
Here it gets tough. Me, my tribe
gave me a second chance
despite a big mistake.
Everything will depend on people's priorities for
tonight's vote.
Kellyn. You must think about it,
considering who to eliminate:
the ability to win.
Because without winning, you will reach
neither the fusion nor the end.
Yes. To feel Yanuya win,
then Naviti,
it's horrible.
So imagine
that we didn't all think about it,
it would be a joke.
We all want to win.
Angela. What do you think ?
Because nobody wants to criticize
someone who gives the best.
Absolutely.
Someone has to carry the torch.
And if we think we have the strength,
we have to do it.
But if you propose,
we expect a hit on goal,
not a touchdown.
Desiree. It must not
be pleasant to hear.
No, indeed.
But if we anticipate
and think about the future of the game,
brute force is not
what we want to face
when
the individual events come.
James.
Desiree returns the ball to the group,
saying, "Strength, perhaps.
But Survivor is a long game
with multiple levels."
What do you read in his remarks?
His argument makes sense.
We saw physically strong people
become threats after the merger.
At the same time, I feel
that with this tribe,
we are very close to fusion,
and we know how to reach it.
Kellyn said it: with brute force.
Michael. You nod.
"Let's achieve fusion first!
Then we'll see who to eliminate."
Sure. You always
have to have an overview.
If we can't reach
the important milestone,
so what's the point?
I want to win,
like everyone here.
So, to achieve fusion,
we must have a goal:
keep the tribe strong.
But the other aspect
of the mixture of tribes,
and it's crazy that we haven't
talked about it yet tonight,
but there are three original Navitis
sitting here,
and two original Malolo.
So we play in his head,
we do the calculations,
and it did not escape me
that long-term relationships
are just as important
that brute force.
James. Do you dread
that ancient tribal alliances
are decisive tonight?
In that case, it would be
a little dangerous for Michael and me.
But these original divisions
into tribes,
they were random.
You can't be myopic like that.
You have to consider
different ways and people,
reach out to the opposite camp.
It's essential in Survivor,
I think.
Angela. What James
is saying is very interesting.
We were in different tribes,
but they were random.
We don't have Naviti or Malolo blood.
It's just a bandana."
It expands the field of
potentially lasting relationships.
It doesn't need to be done
on day 1.
Absolutely. That I was Naviti
was by chance.
And everyone from my original tribe
voted against me.
The Malolos
didn't save me directly,
but indirectly, that's why
I'm here today.
Out of curiosity, a question to all.
Be brief.
In life, do you rather follow
your head or your heart?
Angela?
Head.
Michael?
Heart.
Desire?
Head.
James?
Kelly's?
pour moi
your guts are the perfect blend
of your head and your heart.
When you find and follow
what your gut tells you,
it's because you let
your heart speak a little
and a little your head.
Find the balance
and decide on that basis.
36 seasons of Survivor
and players
always teach me this game.
And I love that. And that being said,
it's time to vote.
Desiree, over to you.
It was you... or me.
I hope it's you.
I got a second chance
and I really wish I
could give you one. Sorry.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Desiree.
One vote James, one vote Desiree.
James.
Two votes James, one vote Desiree.
Sixth person eliminated
from Survivor Ghost Island:
James.
Three is enough.
Bring me your torch.
James, the tribe has spoken.
Good game.
Playing with all of you was a pleasure.
Good luck.
Your heads, your hearts,
and ultimately your guts,
led you to eliminate
one of the strongest of the tribe.
Judicious? The future will tell.
Take your torches,
return to your camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
There is fire at Malolo...
Let's burn the Malolo flag!
It brings bad luck.
I'm next,
but I hope to see the end of the tunnel.
... and fury at Naviti.
Go on !
The hardest part is not being
a perfect asshole.
What rotten!
The fire raged inside me.
It was a great surprise elimination . I did not see anything coming.
Hats off to them.
But strangely, I am at peace,
because these 17 days, even if it was short
in the scale of my life,
really changed me.
I will return to the real
changed world,
with a new look.
I come away
more humble and grateful
to say that I played Survivor.