Previously on Survivor...
On Ghost Island,
Jacob was the first visitor
to uncover the graveyard
of past bad decisions.
And he bequeathed the
Cursed Heir Boon to Morgan.
It's the Heir's Advantage!
See, I touch it!
At the Naviti,
Domenick used his fake idol
to gain trust.
Lily. That's crazy.
But it backfired.
I do not trust.
Something is wrong in there.
The Malolo tribe
had to go to the council.
And James was threatened.
I caused us to lose.
I screwed up.
But a surprise elimination was
brewing.
We need to get Jacob out.
At the council,
James received votes.
But Jacob was eliminated.
Jacob, the tribe has spoken.
There are 18 left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
After the counseling,
I feel a bit drained.
It's been a roller coaster ride
for my little heart and me.
It was a good plan.
Glad it worked.
James, don't blame me.
Yeah.
I will try.
Tonight I got two votes.
I deserved to be the second target.
Growing up in a
Korean-American family
taught me to accept my failures.
But I'm happy to be here,
ready to fight.
It's time to win.
I'm tired of losing.
Over here, everyone!
Naviti,
discover the new Malolo tribe.
Jacob was eliminated
at the last council.
And here is Donathan,
back from Ghost Island.
Over here, Donathan!
Welcome !
Donathan also discovers
the new Malolo tribe.
Welcome. How are you ?
What's new ?
Libby, after two ordeals,
you have lost two limbs.
Where is this tribe in the game?
We are always united and positive
We will still become
the best tribe ever.
Bradley, where are the Naviti?
I believe we are strong.
We get on very well.
It's a tight-knit group.
So it looks like the two tribes
feel very good.
Now is the perfect time
for a change.
Throw away all your bandanas!
We change the tribes.
It was nice, friends.
Angela, how do you feel,
before we changed?
A little anxious, like
a separated family. It's sad.
Are you moved?
I do not know. I love them.
I did two deployments
with the army.
We forge strong and lasting bonds
in a very short time.
For me, it's exactly the same.
So this mix
makes me very nervous.
Fine, let's go!
Lord !
Do not open them yet.
I am rather in a position of strength.
So I'm freaking out a bit.
But I knew having the power
wouldn't last.
But you have to ride the waves.
There's a wave, ride it!
There are two left.
Michael will have the last.
Destiny.
Good. Reveal all
your new bandanas.
Greet your new tribe.
What have you got, Dom?
Purple.
I'm worried, because I still have
to deal with Chris in this tribe.
So it's crucial that I
connect with everyone
in order to get it out.
Violets, you are Naviti.
Go to the purple carpet.
Les Oranges, you are Malolo.
Go to the orange mat.
Je suis Rest.
Relax.
Go for it.
Glad to finally talk to you!
But yes !
Good. In the new Naviti tribe,
quatre ex-Malolo :
Donathan, Libby, Laurel and James.
And five ex-Navitis:
How are you feeling, Morgan?
Good.
I love purple.
We have a living room, comfort...
I feel very good.
And you are in the majority.
Absolutely.
Good. In the new Malolo tribe,
also four ex-Malolo:
Brendan and Michael.
And five ex-Navitis:
Kellyn, Bradley et Chelsea.
Kellyn.
Does a part of you wonder
what will happen to the five Naviti?
"Can we stick together?"
uh well...
Jeff, I smell the Violets,
but at the same time,
things change,
we never know.
I am excited
to meet new people,
to open new
treasure boxes full of love.
Good. Malolo, Naviti,
take your things, let's go!
The game has changed again.
Apparently,
I should be working with the Malolos.
But the Naviti are in the majority.
My plan
is for us to stay together.
'Cause that would be really awful
to release these Malolo
one after the other.
Welcome !
Rather nice.
Is it different from your side?
Yeah.
Without the pillows,
hammocks and all.
The majority
is essential in this game.
Around me,
I had my four friends
of the old Naviti. I was delighted.
It's ideal for me.
So there, I'm
a happy, bubbly candy cane.
Banana.
Alright, here...
You know how it is.
In the beginning, we do what we can.
We must have done
half the stuff wrong.
The shelter is large.
But there are plenty of bumps.
Going from Naviti to Malolo
was a bit of a shock for us.
Car l'abri...
...is just part
of the giant mess that is this camp.
It's like seeing your friends baby
that they find so cute,
the love of their life,
But this baby is ugly!
What happened here?!
It is important to appreciate
the beauty of the place.
Like...
We get lost in what we do.
It's easier at Camp Naviti.
Here, it's rotten, in comparison.
Looks like a meadow.
What surprised me with the Naviti,
it's that they
only complained about the conditions
since their arrival.
Bradley, in particular.
He constantly complains,
it's unbelievable.
It's Survivor, it's supposed to be hard.
I don't understand
what upsets them.
As a bonus, we are in the minority, 4 5.
All in all,
not a great mix for me.
Welcome to Naviti!
Welcome to the house !
Here is the living room.
Wow, yeah!
That's great !
And how !
Really cool !
It's a little cold here at night.
Let's go in the bedroom.
We put our comforts here.
We didn't have tools like you,
so...
And there, the hearth for the night.
Really ?!
I was sawed arriving at Naviti.
They assured. They have two homes,
good shelter,
and of course, the most beautiful view
I have seen in my life.
A priori, I doubt
that this new tribe
go to the council anytime soon.
We look strong!
Yeah, really!
We have the advantage, 5 4,
but it's much more complex than that.
Because with three of the five,
I hardly had any ties.
And Dom has an idol,
which terrifies me.
I have to blow her up.
What will happen, in your opinion?
We have the majority.
No reason to deviate from it.
But start thinking
with your military instinct,
not with your heart.
Yeah.
OK ?
I would follow Wendell.
If you want to win,
think like that.
I'm super serious.
I'll tell you something.
Dom told me he has the idol.
He searched for a long time. He has it?
He has it.
We will only survive
by acting together.
If I'm alone, we're screwed.
I believe the information
Chris gave me on Domenick.
After this mixture,
we must change strategy.
We have to get Dom out.
I follow the movement, but I get
a little stuck on Chris's stories.
Because he is a manipulator.
He talks to people, not with.
He was giving me orders:
"Do this, don't deviate."
And even though the army got me used
to guys barking orders,
I don't like
this kind of confrontation at all.
Where are you, level cocos?
I have a question for you.
The four, are you united?
Domenick probably has the idol.
Are you sure ?
Yes.
We have to take it out.
Find a way.
He will try
to rally everyone.
He will do it.
You're from New York, you understand.
He's a New Yorker.
I've watched him from the start.
Chris started
talking about Domenick having an idol
and we have to get it out.
And I was...
"Wow! Welcome to Naviti!"
We have to.
We have to get there.
Seriously...
Let's do it!
Absolutely.
Chris has a strong character,
so when he talks to me,
I have to nod and smile,
act like i'm a girl
which he could take advantage
of and use the vote.
On the way back, we play it cool.
I'll play dumb,
but I won't be.
This is exceptional.
I say.
Look how beautiful it is!
Impossible to get tired of it.
We freeze.
I want to go back to Naviti.
Yours is dirt.
We have sand everywhere.
I feel dirty and grimy.
My God !
The Naviti hate our camp.
A bunch of moaners!
But I find myself in the minority
in this tribe.
I have to find a loophole.
Sometimes
this game is a matter of luck.
But none of us
will betray the Violets.
So it sucks for you,
being at 5 4.
At the bottom of the ladder, it is necessary
to fight, to multiply the contacts.
It's frustrating,
because chance can make you
suddenly go
from the summit to the depths.
Let's not give up!
No.
With Steph,
we have to find an idol,
to change the balance of power.
Come on, let's run! Come !
We took off like rockets
in the woods.
Return that!
Digging under every tree...
Stands guard !
Every rock, pebble...
Something?
Every branch, near the well,
in the mail...
Lord ! These things
are going to jump out at me!
We put our hands in trunks
covered with termites and ants.
Nothing.
We did everything
to find an idol.
You want to take me out?
I will only come out
screaming and thrashing.
I will do everything to stay in the game.
We should be quiet.
It couldn't have turned out better.
And they are entertaining.
While we eliminate them!
I think she is there.
There's a real idol somewhere.
More than ever, the four Malolo
want to find an idol.
So no one should be surprised
that we're looking for one.
There must be a clue
or something.
Oh my God !
I watch.
We found the idol.
We got it, mate.
I'm so happy.
I found an idol.
It's a big Survivor dream
come true.
“Congratulations, you have found
the Hidden Immunity Idol.
This is one
of the true idols that James..."
It's the ghost!
This is the original James idol,
of Survivor China, in 2007,
when he came out having two.
She decorated the entrance to their camp.
Nobody suspected
that it was an idol.
He ripped it off, and indeed...
An idol.
I have two idols!
"By day 30, James was
in a strong position.
He had a close-knit covenant of five
and two idols.
Of this combination of powers,
he got
a false sense of security.
His allies eliminated him,
his two idols in his pocket.
Tenth person eliminated
and fourth member of the jury:
"James is the only one in Survivor
to have dated two idols."
"The question is:
can you reverse the curse?"
When I was eight years old, the first season
I saw was Survivor China.
James was one of my favorites.
I saw him go out with his idols.
Being here eleven years later,
with the real idol in hand,
and have a chance
to reverse this curse,
to change his legacy,
it's incredible.
It is enormous.
That's exactly what we were looking for.
This little rascal!
[???]
We have work.
I'm afraid Chris will betray us
before we knock him out.
And he'll take Angela.
They are close.
Libby. I like it.
Chris is already working on them.
We must therefore rally them all.
Not just one or two. The fourth.
Yup.
The easiest
would be to stay at five.
At least for a vote.
But I feel
like Chris doesn't want that,
because he does not have
a good contact with Dom.
So we might have to target Chris.
People are starting
to get a little paranoid,
but you have nothing to worry about right
now.
I love you, I'm on your side.
I was glad you were shooting purple.
Me too !
Wooden cross, iron cross!
Catholic girls,
we gotta stick together.
OK.
I knew right away
it would fit with Morgan.
She was super open and friendly.
We are two Catholics,
so I feel closer to her
than others of the tribe.
I'm not sure
that the five Naviti...
... are welded.
What's good when people come to you,
want to trust you,
is that you can
choose your alliance,
and I feel really good about Morgan.
We can work together, we understand each other.
I finally feel
like I have a real ally.
I don't think
you need to worry.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, Angela, I'm taking her back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today you will cross
a series of sloping walls
up to a sand pit,
where you'll dig up a ladder.
You will climb there,
retrieve a rope.
With the rope you will reach
the top of a high tower
where you will solve a puzzle.
The first tribe to succeed
wins immunity,
is shielded from the board.
The losers: someone will be
the third person eliminated.
Plus, you're playing
for a reward.
Yeah !
A single
small tarp.
It will protect you
from rain and sun.
And the winners send
one of the losers to Ghost Island.
Still a lot of issues.
A minute of organization
and we get to it.
Let's go!
Well, on and go!
For immunity and reward!
Survivors, ready?
Chris and Sebastian begin.
They pass.
Brendan just passes.
Bradley passes.
James falls and has to start over.
Desire too.
This is Donathan. Can it get there?
Angela has to start over.
All the Malolo women
follow suit.
Michael passed.
Desiree is still working there.
This is Morgan.
Libby is in trouble.
She has to start over.
Desiree tries again.
Is it the right one?
Yes it's good !
Start digging!
Domenick passed.
James tries again.
He passed.
Here is Angela.
Angela is almost there.
Its good !
Start digging!
You are now digging up
a very large ladder.
Go on ! One two three !
The Malolos have taken out their ladder.
The Malolo lead!
The Naviti are always digging
and slowing down,
at the start of the test.
The Naviti have their scale.
Use it
to get someone up!
At 4 m 50 high!
That's the basis!
That down! Put it down!
Malolo
take a long time
to figure
out how to use the ladder.
That end down!
We lift it and we turn it!
The Malolo lost the advantage.
It was right !
The Naviti have caught them!
Donathan climbs,
Naviti leads now!
The great lead of the Oranges
evaporated.
Chelsea climbs for Malolo.
Donathan throws the rope,
that's it ! Its good !
Chelsea are in trouble.
It's Chris, with the rope,
for Naviti.
Attention !
Chelsea has it! Come back down!
Wait for her!
Let her down!
The Malolo try to go up.
Sebastian
will throw the rope for Malolo.
Chris! Its good !
Now you have to pull yourself up.
Sebastian succeeded!
Pull up!
Him first!
It's neck and neck!
Wendell went up.
Sebastian came up.
Laurel came up.
Everyone must go up!
Perfect equality!
Come on, Dom! Hold on!
Someone has to reach the top.
Sebastian tries. He fails.
Domenick gets help.
Sebastian gets help.
Domenick and Sebastian are upstairs!
Who next?
Go on !
Take my hand !
Sebastian
brings up Bradley, then Desiree.
Domenick hoists Laurel!
Teamwork!
Good collaboration
in both tribes!
That's how it's done in Survivor!
Like that !
On the carpet !
Naviti, it's good,
start the puzzle!
Where is the base?
[???]
Come on, Mike!
Last man
for the Malolo, it's good!
Start the puzzle!
All that adrenaline
and energy to get here!
Now exhausted you gotta
slow down and use your brains
to solve a complicated puzzle.
Slowly. We think.
It's Kellyn and Bradley for Malolo.
Wendell and Laurel for Naviti.
They first try to figure
out what this puzzle is.
Small base, then bigger.
A tarp and immunity at stake.
The board and Ghost Island
for the losers.
It's not that.
Wendell, look at me!
On the table there!
To be ?
This is where the help of your comrades
is invaluable.
Bradley and Kellyn have a play,
if that's fair!
Another piece for Kellyn.
If that's right!
Very good collaboration
in the Malolo tribe.
Great !
It's good !
Wendell and Laurel lose ground.
Don't say that, Probst!
I say what I see.
New room
for Bradley and Kellyn.
There, the big one, maybe.
One more for Bradley and Kellyn.
Wendell looks at them to understand.
Hey, Bradley, there, that room!
It's the big one, I think.
New room
for Bradley and Kellyn.
It turns to correction!
The choice of who makes the puzzle
now turns out to be decisive.
Malolo has chosen very well,
clearly, with Kellyn and Bradley.
Malolo
wins immunity and the reward!
They send Naviti to the council.
Malolo, congratulations.
A clear victory, from the outset,
with the new tribes.
No advice tonight.
As a bonus, a nice tarp.
Come take your reward.
Good. Naviti. Tonight, advice,
where a third person
will be eliminated from the game.
And someone
's going to Ghost Island.
Malolo, you will decide who.
It has to be a unanimous decision.
Otherwise, the Naviti
will shoot stones.
If you can't decide,
chance will.
Does anyone
object to sending Donathan there?
I oppose it.
So the stones.
The stones.
Explain to me, Bradley.
Why
can't the group decide?
We are five
from the old Naviti.
And we want
to send a former Malolo there.
So it is logical that they oppose each other.
Normal.
I would do the same in their place.
There are eight black stones
and a white one.
The white one goes to the Phantom Island.
Pull one, don't look.
Keep it in the palm.
Everyone reach out.
Reveal !
Chris has the white stone.
Chris will go to Ghost Island.
He can't be eliminated tonight,
that's the good news.
The bad: you'll be
left out of the social game
and will not be able
to influence the elimination.
Pack your things,
head to Ghost Island.
Good luck to you.
See you later, Chris.
What a sloppiaud of Chris a de la veine.
I was really looking forward
to eliminating him on the board tonight.
Malolo, no advice.
Take your things, leave.
Enjoy your free evening.
Naviti, see you tonight at the council.
Take your things, leave.
I'm totally freaking out!
This season is very much
about the mistakes of the past.
It will be four against four
tonight.
And I'm afraid we'll screw it up.
The ninth day
has just turned into a nightmare.
We lose the race,
I'm sent to Ghost Island...
And frankly, that scares me.
Tonight I'm missing a crucial piece of advice
whose outcome
I greatly influenced.
I hope the plan remains
to eliminate Dom by surprise.
But I'm scared.
Me away...
It might not happen.
Alright, here we go.
"No, not today.
No game for you."
What a pity !
I was hoping that I could win an idol
or some benefit.
Instead,
I'm on my own.
Being here is not easy.
I'm hungry, I miss my family...
That's crazy.
What the game does to you, mentally.
I expected this to happen to me
at some point. It's just...
This is the first difficult day
for me.
With the tribe, when I'm having trouble...
I have to hide it.
You have to be strong
in the presence of others.
My mother has multiple sclerosis
since before I was born.
My mother is my heroine.
More or less, I...
In my moments of weakness,
I think of her.
She is the ultimate survivor.
She was diagnosed at age 27.
Ten years ago, she was given
2 months to live, and she's still alive.
Since then,
I make myself a duty
to stay strong for her.
It helps me,
when I'm in a tribe.
You have to do all that.
But I'm human, and...
Ghost Island offers me a chance
to evacuate all my negative energy,
in order to start off on the right foot
and be like this again,
for myself.
I didn't even know I was
so exhausted.
Thinking about my mom was awesome.
This link really helps me.
It's crucial that I refocus
because it will improve my game
for the future.
It sucks!
AIE Aie Aie !
Chris Noble must be happy
with rice just for him,
a big bed for his big head.
What I see happening tonight
it's the four Malolos
voting Domenick,
following Chris' plan.
I got a ton of sand
in my panties
and the water looks good.
I'm going to take a dip.
I decided not to follow Chris,
not to vote against my team.
I prefer loyalty
rather than being controlled
and having no choice.
Have you thought about
disaster scenarios for tonight?
No, but Chris talked to me.
He stays on Dom.
He said, "Follow the plan."
In other words:
vote with the other four.
So they'll take out Dom
and we'll be four against four.
I don't want to vote with them.
I won't release one of ours.
I expect a tie
and have to shoot the stones.
But I'm ready for it,
for the old Naviti.
I stay with my team.
So who would you date?
So at worst they all vote Dom
and us for Libby,
we'll shoot the rocks
or something.
We'll talk again, okay?
Angela wants
the Naviti to stick together,
but it's a bit dodgy.
She is Chris' right-hand man.
So for me, our "discussion"
had little weight.
I don't want to pull the rocks
for Angela, so...
The idea of ​​releasing it excites me.
I was ready to pull the trigger.
Chris is out of control.
He was supposed to go out tonight.
He's powerless
if you pull out his right arm.
Cool. Angela. Boom.
He has Libby in his pocket.
No.
Safe ?
Yes. She is with us.
Good. Great. Easy.
Angela thinks Libby is going to leave.
But I have much more confidence
in Libby
that I will never have in Angela.
Do you want to take Angela out?
With us, it would be
a total and unanimous surprise.
We are a team.
We are on your side
on your team, I swear.
The plan
is to get Angela out now
to show them that we are with them.
We have to talk, it's important.
Pretend to be with them.
Go for it !
I had in mind this fear
that the four ex-Malolo
start thinking of me
as a threat again.
So I could
show the fake idol to the tribe
to gain some confidence.
Day one, day two:
Chris was after me.
Third day, same.
And on the third or fourth day,
he said to me:
"Do you have an idol?" I answer no.
He said, "If I see that we can
trust each other,
I'll leave you alone."
So...
I found this purple fabric
at a proof.
I took it away...
A rotten string...
A mail scroll...
Oh my God !
My God !
So... It's a beautiful seashell.
I put it around my neck in front of him
and everything. I showed it to him.
Yeah.
But... It's worthless.
That's what he's been raving about
since day one.
Eh ? So... How's it going between us?
The Naviti
want us to take Angela out. But...
I almost see in Domenick
a Russell Hantz 2.0.
I believe he is capable
of lying to my face.
Count on me.
OK.
He could very well
have a real idol
and want to mislead
us by showing us the wrong one.
On my children,
I will work with you.
I would never say that in the air.
I am with you.
100 %.
If someone has to say, "I swear
on my children and my family"...
It's a bad sign.
If Domenick
really votes for Angela,
so we decide who leaves,
because the Naviti are only 3 left.
So we can choose,
Wendell or Morgan.
We need Wendell.
Morgan, then.
We vote...
Because of the idol.
I was not very hot,
because I can trust Morgan.
I'd rather not target her
and keep
it as long as possible.
Domenick
is a sort of Russell Hantz.
He could have a real idol,
showing us the wrong one
to deceive us.
I doubt he has an idol.
You doubt it, but if there is one...?
We will need Wendell and Morgan
in the trials,
no Angela.
Whatever we decide,
we all four have to
have the same target, then...
We have to decide quickly
before the council.
I don't want to eliminate Morgan.
It would be much simpler
to eliminate Angela unanimously.
The question is:
do we bet on alliances
spent in the old Malolo,
or do we mix?
This decision is a turning point.
Every day the stakes
get higher.
If that's your first tip,
behind you: torches.
Take one
and light it in the fire,
It is part
of the council ritual,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
If he disappears, so do you.
That's crazy.
Morgan. You return to the camp,
with Chris on Ghost Island,
four four.
Basically, we split
into two groups of four.
At this point, the two tribes
remain firmly between them.
Wendell, is that really the case?
Two groups of four?
Yes, we were on the bed,
them in the living room,
strategizing.
We can only hope
that someone cracks,
maybe recruit someone.
What if they're
in the living room and you're in the kitchen?
Good question.
You have to get out of the kitchen,
approach someone.
Domenick. Are you surprised
it was so separate,
since it's
a million vote for someone tonight?
Yes, Jeff.
If it turns to four four,
I don't want
a stone to decide my fate.
So I came out
of the kitchen a bit,
I explored the situation,
to see if there were flaws,
what everyone thought.
Angela. And you? What did you see
back at camp?
I also left the kitchen,
I discussed.
And tonight, I'm torn.
I can make the popular decision
or the one that is good for me.
But I feel enormous pressure.
So there, I want
it to be my decision, for me.
Your words amaze me.
What pressure?
When mixing,
Chris started trying to get
us Malolos.
And it was more pressure
than expressing opinions.
But Chris is not there.
He left.
Morgan.
Do you think there is a chance
that despite Chris,
this evening
unites the Naviti more?
I think so.
We have good relations.
But there are
four new people.
We try to build relationships
with them as well.
Domenick. Do you feel that too?
Different relationships?
Absolutely.
I am very comfortable
with this new quartet,
I sense new possibilities
and am always open
to listening to others.
I want to hear what they have to say
and I will determine
whether I want to follow or not.
Everyone paints this beautiful picture.
A group of four here,
another there.
But the more questions I ask, the
less accurate it seems.
Yes. In fact, I'm surprised.
For me,
there were four welded Navitis.
That may not be the case anymore,
in fact.
Or, Morgan,
maybe it's part of a plan.
We are always in doubt,
at the council.
Yes. We could all
be lying
or all tell the truth.
Are we all good actors?
Or are we sincere?
Only time will tell.
Libby. How to Determine
When Lying is Appropriate
and when to be honest?
I love that you ask me that.
Why is that ?
'Cause you'd think
the nice girl, sweet,
don't like to lie too much.
But you gotta make sure
others believe you
to achieve something.
So you have to be ready
to fabricate, sometimes.
But that's the game.
Morgan. When Libby said that,
her smile widened,
her charm spread.
But look at her!
We want to trust him!
She's beautiful, adorable,
how could she lie?
But that's part of the game.
Everyone lies.
Even Libby, I'm sure,
lie, or to lie, at one time.
So Wendell. Sitting here,
what do you think is going to happen?
On the main lines.
I'd like to hope
someone makes a hit,
that at the end of the evening,
we are a stronger tribe,
who wants to collaborate
and achieve victories.
Good. It's time to vote.
Laurel, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Good. Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Angela.
Three votes Angela,
a Libby vote.
Morgan.
Three Angela votes,
two Morgan votes, one Libby vote.
Morgan.
Equality. Three votes Angela,
three Morgan votes, one Libby vote.
One vote remains.
Shit !
Third person eliminated
from Survivor Ghost Island:
Morgan.
Bring me your torch.
Morgan, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
Do not trust
the pretty blonde!
This advice was centered
on one question.
Were things locked
or was someone
going to make a move?
Apparently
someone made a hit.
And that's how we play Survivor.
Take your torches,
return to your camp. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time in Survivor...
When we are cornered...
We got everyone back together.
...and exhibited...
It's frustrating.
I still have so much to give.
...we need protection...
I have the idol.
You can open the game.
... to survive.
I have an idol.
Lord !
Let's act!
I have the Heir Advantage,
actually.
I thought he would help me.
It clearly didn't work.
So it may be a curse,
but I bequeath
this advantage to Domenick.
He was always
open and honest with me.
I hope it's not cursed.
If so, sorry!