Previously on Survivor...
Approaching the board,
Kellyn saw an opportunity
to strike.
This is our chance to take out Wendell.
But Wendell and Domenick
had their own goal...
We take out Chelsea and then...
It's piece of cake.
Yeah.
...leaving Donathan and Laurel
in the middle.
What do you want to do?
Donathan and I
both control this board
and the direction of the rest of the game.
At the council,
Donathan and Laurel
stayed with Domenick and Wendell...
Chelsea, the tribe has spoken.
...leaving Kellyn without allies.
There are seven left.
Who will be eliminated tonight?
A rough evening for me.
A very close ally is gone
and my new alliance
clearly didn't work.
Finding myself at the bottom of the ladder,
I am open to discussion
and I wait
to see who will approach me.
I'm next
I don't believe.
That's why
I had to target Wendell.
When I see that going out next
is the goal of the two bosses,
it's very hard to get around that.
But after my divorce, I was
n't sure where I wanted to go,
but I had the idea that maybe,
if I followed my gut,
things would turn out well.
That's the impression
I have now.
So we'll see what I can
stir up tomorrow.
Any ideas this morning?
As for what's next?
No. I do not know.
On the one hand, I say to myself...
...that there's a game to be played
against the guys,
if we worked with Ang and Kellyn
for a vote.
But on the other hand,
I don't trust them.
If we keep
playing it too safe,
we will be even worse off
at the end...
I say.
...with no chance
of winning immunities.
I say.
This is probably the last chance
to release one
without them playing an idol.
Dom and Wendell
believe us 100% with them,
because last night I could have
attacked Wendell and didn't.
But I know I
can't beat them in the final.
And at seven, it's kind
of the last chance
to take out some of the guys,
blow up the idols
and position myself for the end.
If we act,
we need to target one of the forts.
That's... That would be my plan.
They are
two of my best friends here.
Dom and Wendell protected me.
They could have fired me
a long time ago and didn't.
So it's risky.
We have an opportunity
to take control.
To give it a try.
I would be sorry not to try.
Laurel and I have been together
since the beginning
and it hasn't changed.
We had chances
to take out Wendell and Dom,
but Laurel always changes her mind,
it's frustrating.
These guys dominated the whole game.
It's hard to watch.
So I would love
to take control of the game.
Well, I've reached the middle...
But that won't get me through.
And if Laurel keeps
changing her mind all the time,
I may have to
take matters into my own hands.
I am ready to take up the challenge.
So you and Laurel were
thinking of a plan
to fire these boys.
If we can be the four
and that they are only three,
we would have a better chance
of succeeding.
Donathan approaches me with an idea:
that he, Ang,
Laurel and I vote together
to take Wendell out by surprise.
You don't have to let anything slip,
if you want it to work.
No, I know, it's either...
I know, I know.
Tried to rally troops
to take action against Wendell before
and Laurel and Donathan screwed up
which seemed like
the best shot to me.
Nevertheless, that Donathan
wants to work with me delights me.
I'm telling you,
we're holding out an olive branch to you.
I felt
like I was underrated from the start
because Wendell and Domenick
were the dominant
and that they always
decided for me.
But I don't want to
let that happen anymore.
Over here, everyone!
What the fuck is that?!
...And then there were seven!
Ready for
today's reward event?
Today you will be separated
into three teams of two.
On my signal, you will drop
a wooden spool onto a track.
It will roll down.
You'll grab it there, pull it up,
and put it back on the trail.
Regularly,
you will add reels,
increasing the difficulty.
If a reel falls,
it's lost.
The last duo in play
wins the reward.
Want to know what's at stake?
The winners will serve
Survivor Goodwill Ambassadors .
They will deliver
much needed materials to a local school,
making students and teachers very happy .
Then you'll celebrate
with roast chicken...
Lord!
...and chocolate cake.
We will do so.
We will
draw lots for captains,
who will choose their partners.
So a person
will not be chosen,
who will not be able to go to the
reward, nor to the Ghost Island.
Big stakes.
We draw the captains
and we start.
We have our three duos.
Kellyn was captain,
she chose Sebastian.
Wendell was captain,
he picked Domenick.
Donathan was captain,
he chose Laurel.
Angela was not chosen.
No chance to go to the reward
or Ghost Island.
Let's go.
Survivors, ready?
We start with two.
Drop the first, and before it
gets to the bottom, drop the second.
Right off the bat, it's
all about spacing.
Tell me when.
Go ahead!
Sebastian drops his second.
Donathan drops his.
Domenick drops his second.
Let's go.
Perfect, Kelly.
Great!
If the reel drops, it's lost.
So if you drop her going
up the stairs,
or if the reels touch,
it is lost.
Take your time.
And... Coward!
We are two reels.
It gives you time
to take the hit.
After 33 days,
those simple stairs will wear you out.
It arrives quickly!
And that's just the beginning.
Go on!
You now have 15 seconds
to release a third reel.
Quick!
The person on top
can drop the news.
Wendell lets go.
Sebastian lets go.
Laurel lets go.
All now have three coils.
We have to speed up.
You have to run faster
and space out better.
Try to give
your partner time to get off
before coming back up to release it!
Come on, Laurel!
Always moving!
It's a big reward
after 33 days of adventure.
If you want it,
you have to earn it, now!
Hurry, she's coming.
Course!
I let her go, huh?
This test is not easy.
You go-y!
We go up and down these stairs.
Let her go!
Its good!
I can hear your breaths from here.
Fatigue
is really starting to set in.
You now have 15 seconds
to add a fourth coil.
Communication is essential.
Strive to space out those coils
as much as you can!
You do it?
Five...
...four...
...three...
...of them...
Let's all drop the fourth reel!
The race is gaining in intensity!
Dark!
Come on!
Quick!
The better you space out, the more time you have
on the stairs.
Kellyn, these two
are too close!
If you lose the rhythm,
you have to go for it to get back!
It goes down fast, Laurel!
One mistake and it's over,
no reward!
Don, you go-y!
Donathan is going to have to hurry.
Quick!
He has it!
There is no respite.
It's consistent.
This is coming fast!
It was right!
Everyone go for it,
everyone wants this reward.
It arrives quickly!
Only 15 seconds left
in this round.
Then we will add a fifth
and last reel,
and will continue until the end.
Come on, Laurel!
Come on, Don!
It's time to drop
a fifth reel.
Stay up there!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...of them...
...and...
Come down immediately!
Go on!
Don!
We have to replace them!
Everyone talks!
I let go when you catch.
Run, Dom!
Here we are, that's where it all happens!
Kellyn, they're too close!
So go for it!
Sebastian fails!
Sebastian and Kellyn are eliminated!
Only two duets left!
Course! Course!
Come on, Laurel!
Laurel can't!
This test is over!
Domenick and Wendell
win the reward!
It's difficult.
Lord!
Domenick, Wendell, come here!
Big win, big reward,
big decision.
You will be
Survivor's ambassadors,
bringing much-needed supplies to a local school,
a lovely afternoon with fried chicken
and chocolate cake.
Choose a person
to accompany you.
The others, if you want to
plead your case, now is the time.
No, we chose.
Yes?
Yes.
So?
Laurel.
Laurel, come here.
Now the other big decision.
Who goes to Ghost Island?
You two decide.
You have to agree,
otherwise they shoot the stones.
Easy.
Wow, it's simple!
So?
The pirate.
Sebastian goes to Ghost Island.
You applaud. Excited?
I love being called "pirate"!
Take your things,
the boat is waiting for you.
Take care of yourself!
Good. Wendell, Domenick, Laurel:
great afternoon,
be good ambassadors.
On the way!
Enjoy.
Thanks.
Kellyn, Donathan, Angela:
nothing for you.
Take your things, leave.
When Wendell and Domenick
chose Laurel,
I was pissed.
It becomes their game
and I no longer see myself
in this quartet.
It's time to rally people
and go after the big guys.
I want to prove to Domenick and Wendell
not to come looking for me.
Wendell and Domenick
sent me to Ghost Island
because they think
that I am their remora.
It's a sucker fish,
and one of the most abundant
in the ocean.
And they attach themselves
to the belly of these monsters,
great whites, mako sharks.
But this game is almost over.
And Ghost Island, so late in the game,
is decisive.
The benefits seem to
be ever more powerful.
So the remora might
just turn into a shark.
"Break the urn."
"Let the game begin!
Follow the fire."
“The odds have increased.
Three hold power.
Risk your vote to play."
There are four...
Three out of four
is a hell of a chance.
And that's Survivor.
You have to try everything.
I will play.
I choose this one.
Go on!
A key. It seems positive.
“Congratulations!
You have gained an advantage.
This is a genuine
"vote theft"..."
Owl!
"...which causes the elimination
of Michaela in season 34
and was poorly played by Kellyn
in this season.
He no longer has the power
to steal a vote,
but can be used
as an additional secret ballot."
Damn, yeah!
"But, agonizing question:
is this vote cursed forever
or will you finally reverse
the curse?"
Nothing could have happened to me better.
This is the authentic "vote theft"
of Game Changers.
Kellyn received it, this season,
as an extra vote
but misused it.
Now it is transmitted to me.
And having two votes
is great.
It's a chance
to show everyone here
that I can play Survivor
and win the game.
For the reward, Laurel,
Wendell and I were in a boat
loaded with school
and sports equipment as well as toys.
Balloons! Go on!
Their simple faces
reminded us
that it doesn't matter where we are.
I live in New York,
16 hours by plane from here.
My name is Domenick.
And to see that my kids,
when I give them a present,
react exactly like
those on the other side of the world...
It's just universal happiness.
I have two!
We all caught kids
Laurel played volleyball
with some,
Wendell you basket...
Everyone brought
their own particular scent.
We couldn't have had a
better trio for this award.
The people of Vanuya
welcome you.
Thanks!
Let's go!
Dom and I
have been collaborating since the beginning.
Most...
At times, Laurel still seems to
have a lot of doubts.
So we chose her
to accompany us
to show our alliance,
to reward her for her loyalty...
God's goodness!
...to show her
how much we care about her
and offer him this special moment.
That's the team. You see?
One, two, three, we're going all the way.
Who will win, in your opinion?
Who?
She's looking at me!
We've come a long way together.
We bonded on the 9th or 10th day
and we've been loyal to each other ever since.
My best hope is that in the final,
you split the votes.
So.
Clearly my best hope.
This is my argument.
"I am with you!
Going to the final with you makes sense.
You'll split the votes
and I'll get the rest."
And I think
they're counting on it, but...
I'm here to knock them out.
Top three, friends!
Three...
I love them, but the game first.
You understand that... We are solid.
100 %.
After Domenick, Wendell and Laurel
went to the reward,
I see what will undoubtedly be
the demarcations for me.
So my only option is to
destabilize them a bit.
Dom will be tough to beat in the end.
If you're both in the final,
I'm voting for him, not you.
Thank you, Donathan.
I'm trying to save you, so...
Since I think I'll end up on the jury anyway ...
Wow!
Strong statement, my friend.
Dom already knows
that I will vote for him.
Then I guess that'll inspire
him to put you on the jury.
I don't know what you're doing here.
I think my truth bombs
are paying off.
I hope I terrified Wendell.
It's my goal,
that they are afraid of each other.
It's good for me.
It's time
to pit them against each other.
What are you doing beautiful?
Routine.
Useful info?
He says you have his vote
and that it will encourage you
to send him to the jury.
Can I ask you a question?
If you've completely given up
on the final trio,
so what motivates you
to continue with us, as a quartet?
That is what I am saying.
No more motivation, then.
I don't know what my place is
in the game.
Good then.
I thought we worked together.
Donathan told us bluntly:
"I can't beat
either of you, so..."
Looks like he fired a suicide bomber.
And I know he's ready
for a big hit.
I know it's coming,
I can feel it.
He went from being a "good low-key guy,
I support you and hope
your story is good"...
...to "yo brother".
...To "I'm going to cut your throat
with a credit card".
I don't know what he will do.
He's going to ruin his game, mine,
everyone's game.
He scares me. He is
blowing up the game.
Over here, everyone!
Ready for
today's immunity test?
First of all, Domenick,
I'll take it back.
Once again,
immunity is at stake.
Today, you will collect
two piles of planks.
With it, you will build a bridge...
...which you will cross,
arriving at a tower.
There you will build a ladder
and climb it.
Once at the top,
you will solve
a Survivor sliding puzzle.
The first to finish wins immunity,
ensures a one in six chance
of reaching the final.
At the council,
someone will become the seventh juror.
Survivor is full of make
or break moments.
For one of you, that moment is here.
Who?
And can you rise to the challenge?
We draw the places at random
and we start.
Alright, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Donathan.
Full of energy,
he rushes towards the boards.
With, you have to assemble a bridge.
You have to lay one plank at a time,
in order.
Wendell attempts a first play.
It's the right one.
Laurel attempts a coin. Not the good one.
Sebastian's turn.
Not the good one.
First piece for Kellyn.
Sebastian has one now.
And one for Domenick.
And two for Wendell.
Everyone is exhausted. 35 days...
And now this!
Donathan is wrong again.
Angela and Donathan
are dead last.
Big fall for Kellyn!
We have Wendell and Sebastian,
side by side.
Sebastian cheated.
Both take turns leading.
New piece for Wendell.
New room for Sebastian.
New room for Laurel.
New room for Domenick.
We are starting
to move up a gear.
Last piece for Wendell,
it's good! He can chain.
And he leads.
Sebastian is finished, he can go.
Wendell and Sebastian
have a huge lead.
Wendell places
his first rung on the ladder.
You have to build from the bottom up.
Each piece must fit together.
It's good for Domenick and Laurel.
Laurel and Dom attempt to return.
Wendell has two bars
and is looking for the third.
I have three, Jeff!
And he has it!
First rung for Sebastian.
Wendell sets up another,
only three short.
This is Kellyn.
She can attack her ladder.
Wendell can climb to the top.
He moves on to the third
and final section.
Unbelievable!
Angela and Donathan...
This bridge doesn't have that
many pieces!
They try again and again
the same parts without finding!
Sebastian is done, he can go up.
Start at the top, Sea Wolf!
Wendell and Sebastian
are on the sliding puzzle.
Laurel tries to join them.
Donathan...
...finally finished the bridge!
It can go ladder.
Remain Angela,
all alone, dead last.
Laurel finishes her ladder,
she can climb.
She'll be happy to see
it's the same sliding puzzle
than that of the very first
moments of the first day.
She hadn't finished it,
but she was able to try.
Will she remember
anything useful?
Dom completed his ladder.
It quickly moves pieces.
Wendell progresses
to the top of the puzzle.
Sebastian slows down.
This is the
35 day effect of Survivor.
An otherwise rather simple puzzle
becomes literally
impossible to finish for some.
Dom moves more pieces.
It is launched.
Wendell quietly continues
his work
and made progress.
Laurel is doing well.
Donathan is coming, he's still fighting!
Kelly's Termine son échelle.
Angela
is still working on her bridge.
She's out of it.
Laurel, very methodical,
quietly moves pieces.
Dom, much more frenetic.
Wendell, dans sa bulle.
Wendell
still has the cards in hand.
He's been leading from the start.
He seems to have forgotten the others.
Who will finish first
and win immunity?
Jeff!
Laurel thinks she has it.
Laurel wins
individual immunity!
Safe at tonight's council,
she can't be eliminated.
I should have called your name,
I guess.
Did you call me?
No.
You must call.
You understand, right?
It's only over
when you say so.
I finished and did...
And I didn't say anything.
I could have called earlier too.
I heard Laurel calling but...
I clearly had it before,
but you called first.
So you won.
So you agree
that if you don't call,
I don't know if you still have
any doubts.
I agree.
So that suits you.
Well, it's maintained.
Laurel wins immunity.
This is how.
I appreciate.
Cheer. Sorry.
Well done, Laurel.
Laurel, come here!
Immunity is yours,
you cannot be eliminated tonight.
As for you others,
Angela, Kellyn, Domenick,
Donathan, Sebastian, Wendell,
after 35 days,
someone is going to leave tonight.
Take your things.
See you tonight at the council.
Cheer.
Thanks.
It's hard to lose,
I needed to win.
But Donathan approached me
to take out Wendell.
So I want to see words
translated into actions,
and I want it to happen tonight.
Laurel! You did it!
I've been considering taking Wendell out
tonight.
But I want to do it right.
He finished first today,
he could have won immunity.
It seems almost unfair
to eliminate it.
I don't like
the way it happened.
Yeah. Not serious.
I may win one
in the future.
If I'm still here.
I think the good move
is to stay with my allies
et de sortir Kellyn.
Tonight, I prefer
the good shot to the big shot.
It's tricky now.
Donathan...
We should
take out Kellyn first, right?
Yes, but... He's going to talk to her.
Yeah.
But we still have to
get Kellyn out.
Kellyn is super dangerous.
For trials as for the end,
where no one wants to take him.
She is super popular
and has lots of friends on the jury.
I think I know
the obvious answer, but...
Always Kellyn, for me.
Is that the obvious?
Yes.
The consensus is
that we'll do our best to get Kellyn out.
What is your suggestion?
We discussed ours,
we want to hear yours.
which one are yours?
For me,
you have to get Kellyn out. This is...
But if you're going to take me out
by surprise, let me know!
I'm nervous, I can't help it.
Without warning,
Donathan decides to freak out.
It seems
that as the end of the game approaches,
it implodes.
It baffles me.
Nobody's gonna take you out of the game.
Good.
Kellyn is more dangerous
because appreciated and all that,
but it is at least reasonable.
"If you're going to kill me..."
Laurel and I looked at each other,
"What the fuck are you talking about?!"
We're afraid
Donathan is trying something.
And suddenly,
I wish I could flex
my muscles tonight at council.
I have a real idol,
but moreover, i worked
on a good fake idol.
I just miss the paper.
Do you have the packaging?
So you want...
...the packaging and the message.
Yeah.
I have to look, but I have this.
Now, if asked,
I'm ready.
That, I keep!
So. Do whatever you want with it.
What was that?
What?
I gave him something.
OK.
Uh... Do you want...?
It has nothing to do
with tonight, I promise.
Do you believe me?
Look in my bags, go ahead.
No it's OK.
Will see.
I didn't know what was going on,
that's all.
I was saving something for him.
OK.
But if you have any doubts, go see!
You can
search my two bags thoroughly.
It's okay,
I'm not worried.
It's just...
You asked.
It was weird.
Wendell et Domenick, en gros,
were doing shady things,
near me, without my knowledge.
We're supposed to be super close,
we have to share information.
It made me uncomfortable.
Seriously, if you're playing an idol
on Kellyn tonight...
...I'm changing sides.
No one will protect Kellyn tonight.
She leaves, the plan has not changed.
I have to pull out all the stops
now.
Basically, that's my only option.
So I'm going to try to shake
the coconut tree before the board.
Donathan est parti voir Kellyn.
How do you feel?
Not very well.
Why?
I'm afraid that tonight
they try to take me out.
I gave Wendell something
in his bag.
Not an idol or anything,
just the wrapping of a necklace.
"What was that?!"
Donathan?
Apparently, Wendell
plans to play an idol tonight.
I saw Domenick
bring him something.
He wants to intimidate people tonight.
Donathan
is completely unpredictable, and...
He ends up doing
what he wants.
Like throwing a pinned grenade
to see who will catch it.
If Donathan wants to blow it all up,
maybe that's my ray of hope.
We can target Domenick.
We freaked him out.
He plotted for five minutes
then ran off to get water.
We take it out?
Boom. We did it?
We don't know
what he is capable of.
You never know,
with such a volatile guy,
able to rush to talk
to someone we are targeting,
what he could do.
But there is also Kellyn.
A super strong competitor,
a super threat,
and if we can blast
another threat at seven,
our chances increase.
Every move, every decision has to
be super strategic at this point.
That's what I try to do.
The end is coming. The sprint begins.
Now here are the members of the jury.
and Chelsea,
eliminated at the last council.
I would like to start
by talking about the test of the day,
compared to where we are
in the game.
You are on the 35th day of the adventure.
And it will always be
one of the most intense,
physically and emotionally exhausting,
experiences you will have.
What you feel is real.
You are on the kneecaps.
It's hard. And we saw it
in today's race.
Domenick, do you feel it?
Yes. I was completely shocked
by my mental abilities
today.
I couldn't,
I couldn't find it.
I can do a sliding puzzle
in 40 seconds.
I couldn't find the first piece,
the one in the upper left corner.
Surely we all agree
that blood,
sweat and tears are left here
and you start to crumble,
mentally and physically.
Wendell. To be honest,
I don't remember
have already seen
what happened today,
when you had that moment of...
"It's good, right? I think so."
...And Laurel double crosses you.
Yes. 'Cause we've been here
so long
the impact it had on us
physically
also affected our mental game.
I am far from being as lively
as on the first day.
You really feel it.
Absolutely.
It's good that I manage to smile about it,
but... everyone
wants to wear this necklace.
I'm very proud of Laurel,
but I'd rather have the necklace.
Domenick. What was the atmosphere
on the camp?
Well...
As the council approaches,
it's gone a bit of a spin.
At one time, Wendell and I
had this item of his,
I'll let him decide
if he wants to talk about it,
but Donathan saw it. I think
that freaked him out a bit.
And it may have made him
rise in the towers.
Wendell. It's very enigmatic.
Domenick transferred something
from his bag to mine.
"Oh! What's going on there?"
He puts something in my bag,
big deal!
But it was just the three of us. If we
're together, why the secrecy?
Why does
everything everyone says or does
should be public?
Because you depend on me
to get ahead in the game.
If you hide things from me,
I become skeptical.
We're not hiding anything from you.
You were sorry
for hiding your idol from me.
Because you absolutely want to
know everything and repeat and...
From those I work with, I expect
information, let's be clear.
Hence my frustration tonight.
Donathan.
Can I say something?
Kellyn. Your eyes are bulging!
I don't know what's going on,
what people have in mind.
I just know that after
the elimination of Chelsea, ...
...some were whispering...
Same.
...that after Chelsea, it would be me.
So...
Jeff.
It probably won't be Kellyn
tonight, but me.
You?!
Mmh.
I see the whispers.
They have full pockets.
They could play one
for Kellyn and get me out.
So I remain on my guard.
We don't change anything.
Ang, do you remember the hammock?
Stay on the hammock plane.
I don't know what the hammock is.
' Cause we don't talk anymore,
remember?
Laurel. This great sentence.
"We're sticking to the plan."
If only you were sure you
knew the plan!
Kellyn thinks it's her.
Donathan is sure it's him.
Yes. I believe I arrived tonight
with a solid plan A.
But I have a plan B and a plan C,
because you always have to have them.
And when something like that happens,
every word, every look has meaning.
And there, I try to be sure
that what I am going to do suits me.
And, Kellyn,
if you think you're threatened,
that's what you want to hear,
that there are disturbances.
Plans B and C?
Great news for me!
Here there are outsiders
and dominants.
Dominants can, through fear,
encourage others
not to attack them.
Nevertheless, I was approached
with plans today.
So, you never know,
in Survivor.
Domenick. Is it a little disconcerting
to say to yourself:
"Yes, of course, everyone has
plans B and C, it's Survivor!"?
Yes, because I'm campaigning
for "We stick to the plan", there.
And if a person is considering
switching to plan B, ...
...you don't know if the others...
We divide, 3 2.
...are considering it too.
So it's important...
Yeah.
...that a plan is followed.
Whether it is A, B or C,
everyone must follow the same.
Well, it's time to vote.
Donathan, over to you.
I will count the votes.
If anyone has an immunity idol
and wants to play it,
now is the time to do it.
Once the votes have been read,
the decision is final.
The eliminated person
will leave the council immediately.
I will read the votes.
Donathan.
Kelly's.
Un vote Kellyn,
one Donathan vote, one Domenick vote.
Kelly's.
Deux votes for Kelly.
Donathan.
Two votes Donathan,
Deux votes Kellyn, un vote Domenick.
Donathan.
Three votes Donathan,
Deux votes Kellyn, un vote Domenick.
One vote remains.
Kellyn. Equality.
Three Kellyn votes,
three Donathan votes.
This is what will happen.
We will vote again.
You can only vote
for Kellyn and Donathan.
Kellyn, Donathan,
you're not voting.
Domenick, over to you.
Come get the urn.
I will count the votes.
I will read the votes.
Donathan.
Kelly's.
Un vote Donathan, un vote Kelly.
Deux votes for Kelly, un vote for Donathan.
Fourteenth Person Eliminated
and Seventh Jury Member:
Kellyn. Three is enough.
Bring me your torch.
I will fight until the end!
I made you vote twice!
Hello.
Well done Kelly.
Kellyn, the tribe has spoken.
It's time to go.
It was really a pleasure,
from the bottom of the heart,
I wish you all good luck.
Health!
We're on day 35
and you're down to six.
And yet this game is still
far from over.
Take your torches. Good night.
Stay with us, to see
a preview of the next episode.
Next time,
in the Survivor finale...
They are only six.
If I'm wrong, it's over.
It would be epic.
I would love to reverse the curse.
With one last visit
to Ghost Island...
My chest is...
...and one final
million dollar decision.
Join us for the final!
This adventure came at exactly
the right time in my life,
when I needed to pass
of the person
I thought I should be
to whoever
I can dream of wanting to be.
I am very grateful
to have been able to
live this unique experience
that I will never forget.