Jeff: THE GREATEST SOCIAL
EXPERIMENT ON TELEVISION IS
BACK.
WITH A MODERN TAKE ON ONE OF THE
MOST INTRYINGING MATCHUPS OF ALL
TIME.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: DAVID VS.
GOLIATH."
THE DAVID TRIBE, TEN STRANGERS
WHO SHARE ONE THING IN COMMON --
OVERCOMING OBSTACLES.
THEY HAVE SPENT THEIR LIVES
BATTLING ADVERSITY AND ARE
ALWAYS THE UNDERDOG.
IVE BEEN INTERESTED IN
ROBOTS SINCE I WAS A WEE BABY
CHILD.
AND EVERYONE HERE IS GOING TO
ASSUME IM A HUGE NERD, WHICH IS
NOT ENTIRELY INCORRECT.
IM NOT EXACTLY THE KIND OF GUY
WHO CRUISED BY ON HIS GOOD LOOKS
THROUGHOUT LIFE, BUT NOW IM A
ROBOTICS RESEARCH SCIENTIST, AND
YOU MIGHT BE SURPRISED ABOUT
WHAT I CAN PULL OUT.
THERES EIGHT KIDS IN MY
FAMILY.
MY MOM HOME SCHOOLED ALL OF US.
WE DIDNT HAVE A WHOLE LOT, BUT
WE EARNED IT WITH BLOOD, SWEAT
AND TEARS.
I COULD THROW A BALE OF HAY
HIGHER THAN ANYBODY WHEN I WAS
12.
Jeff: THEYLL TAKE ON THE
GOLIATH TRIBE, TEN STRANGERS WHO
ALSO SHARE ONE THING IN
COMMON -- WINNING.
THEY HAVE SPENT THEIR LIVES
CAPITALIZING ON THEIR ASSETSS AN
ARE ALWAYS CONSIDERED THE
FAVORITES.
IVE BEEN AMAZING IN
BUSINESS.
EVERYTHING I TOUCH TURNS TO
GOLD.
I AM A PUBLISHER AND C.E.O. OF
THE LARGEST BLACK NEWSPAPER ON
THE WEST COAST.
IM A PROVEN LEADER.
IVE HAD PEOPLE WHO WOULD TAKE A
BULLET FOR ME.
IVE HAD A FAIRYTALE LIFE.
I STUDIED AT STANFORD YOUTH.
I GOT MY MBA FROM YALE.
THERES SO MUCH ABOUT WHO I AM
THAT PUTS ME AT SUCH AN
ADVANTAGEOUS POSITION.
AND I AM GOING TO BE A FORCE TO
BE RECKONED WITH OUT HERE.
Jeff: WHICH TRAITS WILL
MOVE MOST USEFUL IN THIS CUNNING
GAME OF SOCIAL POLITICS?
IM A FIRM BELIEVER THAT YOU
DONT JUDGE A BOOK BY ITS COVER,
BECAUSE LITTLE TINY SNAKES,Y,
LOOK AT THAT LITTLE SNAKE.
LITTLE DO YOU KNOW, HES
PROBABLY GOT THE BADDEST BITE IN
THE JUNGLE.
Jeff: FOR THE NEXT 39 DAYS,
THEY WILL BE ABANDONED IN THE
ISLANDS OF FIJI.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEYLL BE VOTED OUT.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
TO CLAIM THE $1 MILLION PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE, ONE SURVIVOR
AS IMEN -- AS IM ON THIS
BOAT TO START "SURVIVOR," I LOOK
AT EVERYONE ON THE BOAT AROUND
ME.
I WONDER, IS THIS MY TRIBE?
WE JUST LOOK STACKED, SO MUCH
STRENGTH, SO MUCH BEAUTY, SOME
CLEAR BRAINS.
AND AS I LOOK AT THE OTHER
TRIBE, I HAVE THE BIGGEST SMILE
ON MY FACE.
THE CARDS ARE JUST STACKED COME
WILL THELY IN OUR FAVOR, AND I
WANT TO TAKE FULL ADVANTAGE OF
THAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO THE 37th SEASON
OF "SURVIVOR."
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
"SURVIVOR" IS A GAME OF SOCIAL
POLITICS THAT OFTEN REVOLVES
AROUND THE STORY OF THE UNDERDOG
VERSUS THE FAVORITE.
IT COMES IN A LOT OF FORMS.
IT MIGHT BE THE PHYSICALLY WEAK
VERSUS THE PHYSICALLY STRONG.
SOMETIMES ITS THE SOCIALLY
AWKWARD VERSUS THE NATURALLY
CHARMING.
WHATEVER FORM IT TAKES, ITS AN
ENDURING MATCHUP THAT HAS
PROVIDED SOME OF OUR GREATEST
SHOWDOWNS.
BUT WHAT COMPLICATES "SURVIVOR"
IS THE UNKNOWN.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT TO EXPECT.
YOU DONT KNOW WHICH SKILL SET
WILL COME IN HANDY.
AND YOU KNOW VERY LITTLE ABOUT
THE OTHER PLAYERS.
SO THE QUESTION EVERY DAY IS THE
SAME.
ITS NOT WHO HAS THE ADVANTAGE.
ITS WHAT IS THE ADVANTAGE.
THATS THE THEME WERE GOING TO
EXPLORE THIS SEASON.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: DAVID VS.
GOLIATH."
LETS GO, BABY!
COME ON!
[APPLAUSE]
Matt: DAVID TRIBE, TAKE
YOUR BUFFS.
LETS GO, BABY.
YEAH.
Jeff: PASS EM OUT AND PUT
EM ON.
LETS GO.
ORANGE, BABY.
Jeff: GUY IN THE BACK IN
THE MIDDLE, WHATS YOUR NAME?
NICK.
Jeff: NICK, TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR UPBRINGING.
WERE YOU A DAVID FROM THE TIME
YOU WERE LITTLE?
ABSOLUTELY.
I GREW UP IN A TRAILER.
IF I WANTED TO MAKE SOMETHING
OUT OF MYSELF, I HAD TO GO AND
GET IT FOR MYSELF.
I MEAN, I WAS FIRST PERSON IN MY
FAMILY TO GO TO COLLEGE, SO I
LEARNED IT BY DOING IT.
I GREW UP POOR IN SOUTHEASTERN
KENTUCKY.
WE HAD FOOD STAMPS.
SO I ALWAYS TOOK TO SCHOOLING AS
MY WAY TO GET OUT, AND NOW IM
THE PUBLIC DEFENDER IN MY
COUNTY.
I HAD TWO DREAMS TO BE A LAWYER
AND TO BE ON "SURVIVOR."
HERE I AM WITH BOTH OF THOSE.
Jeff: WOMAN IN THE FRONT ON
THE CORNER, WHATS YOUR NAME?
GABBY.
Jeff: DOES THIS RING TRUE
TO YOU, THE STORY OF A DAVID,
MAYBE SOMEONE WHO HAS THE CLIMB
THE MOUNTAIN EVERY TIME IN.
BEING A DAVID, WE HAVE A LOT
MORE TO PROVE.
WERE NOT AT THE TOP WHERE WE
CAN LET PEOPLE DOWN.
WERE STARTING AT THE BOTTOM AND
WE HAVE TO CLIMB OUR WAY UP.
I THINK THATS A COOLER STORY.
YOU KNOW, DAVID NOT ONLY SLEW
GOLAITH IN THE BIBLE, HE ENDED
UP BECOMING A KING, TOO.
THE STORY DONT STOP WITH DAVID
VERSUS GOLIATH.
Jeff: I FEEL A MATCHUP
HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
GOLIATH, YOUR BUFFS.
GOOD CATCH.
BUFF ME.
Jeff: GUY IN THE BACK, DOES
THIS RING TRUE?
HAVE YOU ALWAYS FIFTH FELT LIKE,
I AM A GOLIATH?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY.
I WAS ON MY HIGH SCHOOL
WRESTLING TEAM BECAUSE I WANTED
TO GET INTO PRO WRESTLING.
ULTIMATELY ITS WHAT HAPPENED
FOR ME.
IVE BEEN A PRO WRESTLER FOR 15
YEARS.
PEOPLE CALL ME "THE MAYOR OF
SLAM TOWN."
AND "FRIDAY NIGHT DELIGHT."
I WENT TO U.C. DAVIS AND
GRADUATED WITH A DEGREE IN
GEOLOGY.
THE REASON IM HERE ISNT
NECESSARILY TO FIGURE OUT IF
JOHN IS THIS GOLIATH.
ITS REALLY TO FIGURE OUT WHO
JOHN IS.
Jeff: WOMAN IN THE MIDDLE,
WHATS YOUR NAME?
IM ALISON.
Jeff: DO YOU BELONG ON THE
GOLIATH TRIBE?
I HAVE NO DOUBT IN MY MIND.
I COME FROM FAMILY WITH A HUGE
LEGION OF SUPPORT.
I MAY NOT HAVE FACED THE SAME
ADVERSITY AS SOME OF THE PEOPLE
ON THE DAVID MAT, BUT I STILL
UNDERSTAND BEING AN UNDERDOG AND
WORKING HARD TO ACHIEVE WHATEVER
YOU PUT YOUR MIND.
TO.
Jeff: I GET THE WORK ETHIC,
BUT LETS PUT THIS TO THE TEST.
GUY IN THE BACK CORNER, WHATS
YOUR NAME?
PAT.
Jeff: PAT, LETS COMPARE
YOUR STORY VERSUS PATS.
OKAY.
YOU GREW UP WITH WHAT KIND OF A
FAMILY?
I WOULD SAY MIDDLE CLASS TO
UPPER MIDDLE CLASS.
MY DAD IS A PHYSICIAN.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
IM A DOCTOR TOO.
Jeff: OKAY.
PAT.
TELL ME ABOUT HOW YOU GREW UP?
WERE YOU UPPER MIDDLE CLASS?
NO, FAR FROM THAT.
I COME FROM A
PAYCHECK-TO-PAYCHECK FAMILY.
MY MOTHER WAS PARALYZED WHEN I
WAS NINE YEARS OLD.
MY FATHER WAS A FIREMAN AND A
POLICE OFFICER.
BUT EVERY PAYCHECK THAT HE
HAD HAD TO GO TO BILLS BECAUSE
HE WAS THE SOLE BREADWINNER.
Jeff: WAS MEDICAL SCHOOL AN
OPTION?
MEDICAL SCHOOL?
COLLEGE WASNT EVEN AN OPTION.
I WENT RIGHT OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL
TO THE WORKING FIELD.
Jeff: AS A GROUP HERE, DO
WE ALL AGREE ON THE PREMISE,
THIS ISNT ABOUT HARD WORK.
YOU DONT BECOME A DOCTOR
WITHOUT WORKING HARD.
THIS IS ABOUT HOW YOU LOOK AT
LIFE AN HUH LIFE HAS STARTED FOR
YOU.
OFTEN THE ADVANTAGE THE GOLIATH
HAS IS VISIBLE.
YOU CAN TELL BY LOOKING AT
SOMEBODY OR BY TALKING TO
SOMEBODY THEYRE A GOLIATH.
ON THE DAVID TRIBE, OFTEN THE
ADVANTAGE IS INVISIBLE.
BUT UNTIL YOU KNOW THE
SITUATION, YOU DONT KNOW HOW TO
DEFINE THE ADVANTAGE.
THE QUESTION THIS SEASON IS
WHICH ONE OF YOU IS THE BEST AT
TURNING EVERY SITUATION INTO ONE
THAT GIVES YOU THE ADVANTAGE.
THAT PERSON WILL WIN THIS GAME.
SO LETS START WITH A LITTLE
EXPERIMENT ON THIS IDEA OF
CAPITALIZING ON ADVANTAGE.
LETS GO WITH THE PREMISE THAT
OUT OF THE GATE THE GOLIATHS ARE
THE FAVORITES.
GOLIATH TRIBE, CHOOSE WHO YOU
THINK IS THE WEAKEST WOMAN AND
THE WEAKEST MAN ON THE DAVID
TRIBE.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
Jeff: BIG EARLY DECISION
TRYING TO MAXIMIZE A CHALLENGE.
WHO DID YOU DECIDE ON?
WERE GOING TO GO WITH PURPLE
HAIR AND BIG BANG THEORY.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, THATS
YOU, AND LYRSA.
LYRSA, TAKE A STEP UP NEXT TO
CHRISTIAN RIGHT THERE.
LIE -- LYRSA, HOW DOES THAT
FEEL?
IM NOT SURPRISED.
IM ALWAYS SEEN AS THE WEAKEST
PERSON BECAUSE IM TINY, BECAUSE
IM A LITTLE BIT CHUNKY, BECAUSE
IM NOT FROM HERE.
Jeff: WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
PUERTO RICO.
Jeff: AND CHRISTIAN, ARE
YOU SURPRISED THEY CHOSE YOU AS
THE WEAKEST MALE?
IT SEEMS LICK A LOGICAL
DEDUCTION BASED UPON WHAT THEY
SEE, BUT PERHAPS APPEARANCES ARE
DECEIVING.
Jeff: NOW LETS TRY TO
EXTEND YOUR ADVANTAGE.
GOLIATH TRIBE, NOW CHOOSE WHO
YOU THINK IS YOUR STRONGEST MAN
AND YOUR STRONGEST WOMAN.
YOU ARE LOOKING FOR MAXIMUM
DISPARITY IN THESE MATCHUPS.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO DID YOU DECIDE ON?
ALISON IS THE WOMAN.
WHO IS THE MAN?
MAYOR OF SLAM TOWN.
Jeff: JOHN, RIGHT HERE IN
THE FRONT.
FAIR TO SAY AT THIS POINT THE
GOLIATHS SHOULD HAVE THE
ADVANTAGE.
THEY HAVE CHOSEN THE WEAKEST
DAVID AND THE STRONGEST FROM
THEIR TRIBE.
THE ALLEGEDLY WEAKEST DAVID.
ALLEGEDLY.
Jeff: OKAY.
NOW PART TWO OF THIS EXPERIMENT.
LETS GIVE THE DAVIDS A CHANCE
TO TILT THE FAVOR TO THEIR SIDE.
WE ARE GOING TO RUN A CHALLENGE.
THE TWO PAIRS WILL COMPETE.
THE DAVID TRIBE IS NOW GOING TO
CHOOSE WHICH PATH THE GOLIATHS
HAVE TO TAKE AND WHICH PATH THEY
GET TO TAKE.
SO NOW THE DAVID TRIBE IS GOING
TO DO THE SAME THING.
YOU WANT TO PUT ALISON AND JOHN
ON WHAT YOU THINK WILL BE THE
MOST DIFFICULT THING FOR THEM TO
COMPLETE AND PUT YOURSELVES ON
THE EASIEST.
HERES HOW IT WORKS.
THE FIRST STAGE IS BALANCE.
YOU HAVE YOUR CHOICE BETWEEN A
BEAM OVER WATER, A PLANK BRIDGE
OR A TWO-PERSON TRACK.
THE NEXT STAGE IS AGILITY.
YOU HAVE YOUR CHOICE BETWEEN THE
NET TUBE, THE ROPE TUNNEL, AND
THE CRAWL UNDER.
THE THIRD STAGE YOU HAVE YOUR
CHOICE BETWEEN A 15-PIECE CUBE
PUZZLE, AN EIGHT-PIECE SLIDE
PUZZLE, OR TRANSFERRING 30
SANDBAGS FROM ONE PLATFORM TO
ANOTHER.
WHEN YOU REACH THE END, ONE
PERSON WILL CRAWL OUT TO RELEASE
A MASSIVE SHELTER-MAKING KIT.
FIRST TO RELEASE IT GETS IT FOR
THEIR TRIBE.
ALL RIGHT.
DAVIDS.
GET TOGETHER, FIGURE OUT WHAT
DECISIONS YOURE GOING TO MAKE.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
LETS HAVE A DECISION.
SO LYRSA, WHAT DID YOU CHOOSE
FOR THE GOLAITH TRIBE TO RUN?
SO THEYRE GOING TO DO THE
PLANKS.
Jeff: PLANK BRIDGE?
YES.
THEN THEYRE GOING TO DO
THE NET AND THE 15 BLOCKS.
Kris: Jeff: THE CUBE PUZZLE
YES.
Jeff: WHAT DID YOU CHOOSE
FOR YOURSELF?
WERE GOING TO DO THE BEAM.
Jeff: BEAM OVER THE WATER.
WERE GOING TO GO UNDER.
Jeff: THE CRAWL UNDER.
AND WERE GOING TO DO THE
OTHER PUZZLE.
Jeff: THE EIGHT-PIECE SLIDE
PUZZLE.
IT IS OUR FIRST REWARD
CHALLENGE.
LETS GET TO IT.
HERE WE GO, FOR REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
OUT OF THE GATE LYRSA AND
CHRISTIAN ON THE BEAM OVER
WATER.
LYRSA ALL THE WAY BACK, SO IS
CHRISTIAN.
THEYRE GOING TO FALL IN!
Jeff: ITS RISK KIM YOU
LEAN TOO FAR OUT, YOU CANT GET
BACK.
SLOW DOWN.
DONT FALL.
Jeff: LYRSA WAY BACK.
THERE GOES ALISON AND JOHN WITH
THE PLANK BRIDGE COVERING A LOT
OF GROUND FAST.
THE DAVIDS ARE MOVING QUICKLY.
LYRALYRSA IS THROUGH.
CHRISTIAN IS THROUGH.
JOHN AND ALISON WORKING TOGETHER
NICELY WITH THIS PLANK BRIDGE.
IT IS NOT EASY, BUT THEY HAVE A
GOOD MOMENTUM.
LYRSA AND CHRISTIAN NOW IN THE
CRAWL UNDER AND ITS TAKING THEM
MORE TIME THAN THEY MAY HAVE
ANTICIPATED.
PUSH WITH YOUR FEET!
PUSH WITH YOUR FEET, CHRISTIAN!
Jeff: ALISON IS THROUGH.
JOHN IS THROUGH.
GO!
YOU GOT A CHALLENGE.
THERE GOES ALISON.
LYRSA IS THROUGH.
BUT THE GOLIATHS ARE MAKING UP A
LOT OF TIME NOW.
CHRISTIAN IS NOW THROUGH.
GET THE PUZZLE PIECES.
Jeff: ITS GOING TO COME
DOWN TO THE PUZZLE.
CHRISTIAN WORKING ON THE SLIDE
PUZZLE.
THEY CAN BE TRICKY.
JOHN AND ALISON ON THE CUBE.
CHRISTIAN!
Jeff: OUT OF NOWHERE,
DAVIDS HAVE THE SLIDE PUZZLE IN
LESS THAN FIVE SECONDS.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER.
DAVIDS, DAVIDS, DAVIDS!
Jeff: LYRSA NOW GOING TO
CLOSE IT OUT.
DAVIDS WIN EARLY REWARD.
SEE THAT?
DAVID STOMPS GOLIATH ROUND ONE.
Jeff: THAT WAS A BLOWOUT.
CHRISTIAN, THE BIG DECISION YOU
MADE WAS NOT THE PHYSICAL PART,
BECAUSE THAT WAS PRETTY CLOSE,
IT WAS THE PUZZLE YOU CHOSE FOR
YOURSELF.
BECAUSE IVE BEEN ON "SURVIVOR"
FOR A LONG TIME.
IVE SEEN PEOPLE TRY TO DO A
SLIDE PUZZLE AND NEVER GET
ANYWHERE.
IN UNDERGRAD, I WROTE SLIDER
PUZZLE ALGORITHMS.
SO I FIGURED WE COULD GO THAT
WAY.
Jeff: GABBY, THIS IS REALLY
WHY THAT STORY OF DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH IS ONE OF THE GREATEST
METAPHORS FOR IMPROBABLE
VICTORY, BECAUSE WHO WOULD EVER
GUESS THAT SOMEBODY WOULD HAVE
WRITTEN ALGORITHMS FOR A SLIDE
PUZZLE AND THAT WOULD COME INTO
PLAY MINUTES INTO THIS SEASON.
YEAH, EXACTLY.
IM REALLY PROUD OF OUR DAVIDS.
THEY HAD THEIR SECRET WEAPON.
AND THIS WAS A GREAT FIRST
VICTORY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DAVID, OFF
TO FAST START.
HERES MAP TO YOUR NEW HOME.
[APPLAUSE]
THE RAFT IS WAITING FOR YOU.
THE ADVENTURE IS YOURS.
GOOD LUCK.
HEAD OUT.
GOLAITH TRIBE, NOT THE RESULT
YOU WANTED, BUT IT IS ONLY DAY
ONE OF A 39-DAY ADVENTURE.
HERES A MAP TO YOUR NEW HOME.
THE RAFT IS WAITING FOR YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
YOU KNOW, ITS FUNNY, ONE
COULD SAY THAT I SLIDE GOLAITH
WITH AN ALGO RHYTHM SLINGSHOT,
BUT I GO DIRECTLY TO THE THINGS
I DID WRONG, AND ITS SOMETHING
I NEED TO FIX ABOUT MYSELF, BUT
I DID MAKE A FEW MISTAKES MOVING
AROUND THE PIECES.
I COULD HAVE GONE A SECOND OR
TWO FASTER.
ITS A MATTER, THE LITTLE PIECES
AROUND IT, THERE WAS LIKE A
MOVE, LIKE A LEFT-RIGHT MOVE.
IT HAS TO MOVE AROUND THE BOARD.
I DID IT RIGHT.
WAS THAT GOOD?
I THINK IT WAS GOOD.
MAYBE IT WAS BAD.
ROW, ROW!
MY FIRST ASSESSMENT OF THE
TBLIET TRIBE, I WAS PRETTY
STOKED BECAUSE IT SEEMED LIKE WE
HAD A LOT OF STRONG GUY, A LOT
OF FIT WOMEN.
ITS LIKE, REALLY, THIS IS MY
TEAM?
I MEAN, I CAME TO HOLLYWOOD, AND
IM NOT ONE OF THE BEAUTIFUL
PEOPLE, LIKE I FELT LIKE I
REALLY HAD TO ALTER MY LIFE BY
WRITING, WRITE, WRITING,
WRITING.
MIKE.
DUDE, WHAT DO YOU DO?
IM A WRITER.
I FEEL LIKE I RECOGNIZE YOU.
WERE YOU ON "THE AMAZING RACE
HES A WRITER.
I KNEW I RECOGNIZED YOU.
IM A DIRECTOR SOMETIMES.
SOMETIMES ACTOR.
IM MOSTLY A WRITER.
I WROTE "SCHOOL OF ROCK" AND
"NACHO LEAK RAY."
I AM MORE SUCCESSFUL THAN I EVER
THOUGHT I WOULD BE, BUT FOR ME I
AM A "SURVIVOR" FANATIC.
EVERYBODY IN MY BUSINESS WANTS
THE OSCAR.
ITS LIKE, LOSERS.
I WANT TO WIN "SURVIVOR."
I FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD OWN
THEM IN EVERYTHING PHYSICALLY.
I USED TO BE A FAT KID.
I DIDNT SHOW UP LIKE THIS.
I WORKED FOR THIS.
I WORKED TO MAKE THE SWAT TEAM.
I WORKED TO BE A COP.
IT DIDNT JUST HAPPEN.
I WORKED MY TAIL OFF.
NOTHING JUST HAPPENS.
WHEN YOURE A BRAND-NEW COP,
22, OH, I GET HALF OFF AT
McDONALDS.
I GET FREE ICIES.
THIS IS PERFECT.
YOU DRINK SODA.
YOU GOT FAT BECAUSE YOU
BECAME...
I WAS BIG BEFORE THEN, BUT I
PUT ON 20 POUNDS MY FIRST YEAR
AS A COP.
AS YOU AGE NATURALLY YOU
START THE GAIN WEIGHT.
SO I WAS LIKE, THIS ISNT
GOING TO WORK FOR ME.
WHEN I BECAME A COP, I TIPPED
THE SCALES AT 320, 340,
SOMEWHERE IN THAT BALLPARK.
YOU COULDNT JUST BE ON OUR SWAT
TEAM AND BE AVERAGE, SO I MADE
THAT MY GOAL.
I COMPLETELY CHAINED MY WORKOUT
PROGRAM.
THE WEIGHT JUST SHED OFF.
I LOST CLOSE TO 100 POUNDS IN A
YEAR.
THEN I TRIED OUT FOR OUR TEAM
AND MADE IT.
YOU LOOK GREAT NOW.
THANK YOU.
YOU LOOK FINE, AS A MATTER OF
FACT.
ALL LEANED UP.
COME ON, GIRL.
YOU ALREADY SAID IT.
I BUFFED UP FOR THIS.
I PUT ON 15 POUNDS.
OLD DAN, FAT DAN, I NEVER WOULD
HAVE HAD THE CONFIDENCE TO WALK
AROUND HERE AND SAY, YES, IM A
GOLAITH, BUT NOW THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRL IS TELLING ME IM
VERY GOOD LOOKING, YOU KNOW, SO
I JUST CANT HELP MYSELF.
I CALLED YOU MY KRYPTONITE.
I WAS LIKE, SHES GOING TO GET
ME IN TROUBLE.
YOU KNOW NEW YORK SUPERMAN,
THE BLOND GIRLS NAME IS
KARA.
I NAMED MY DOG AFTER HER.
WHATS HER NAM?
KARA.
NO WAY.
KARA, SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
FIRST TIME I SAW HER, I WAS
LIKE, WOW, RIGHT UP MY ALI, LIKE
EVERYTHING I WOULD WANT IN A
WOMAN, LIKE PERFECT, LIKE WOW.
WHAT KIND OF GIRLS DO YOU
LIKE?
BLOND AND BEAUTIFUL.
SO YOURE SAYING IM BLOND
AND BEAUTIFUL IN.
ABSOLUTELY.
RIGHT UP MY ALI.
OKAY.
IM BLUSHING.
DAN IS ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE I
IMMEDIATELY CONNECTED TO.
I CAN TELL HES A GENUINE SOUL.
HES ONE OF THE NICEST PEOPLE
IVE MET.
HES HILARIOUS.
IN MY LIFE, I WAS AN N.F.L.
CHEERLEADER.
IM A REAL ESTATE AGENT NOW.
SO ITS PART OF ME TO BE
CHARMING.
ITS CLEAR THAT HES DRAWN TO
ME, WHICH, OF COURSE, MAKES IT
IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME NOT TO BE
DRAWN TO HIM, TOO.
IM SO HAPPY YOURE ON THIS
TRIBE.
DOES THAT MEAN WERE GOING TO
BE THE SHOW MANSLAUGHTER.
WE CANT PUT TARGETS ON OUR
BACKS.
WE JUST WONT MAKE IT
OBVIOUS.
YOU CAN KISS ME IN SECRET.
IM LIKE, DONT DO IT, DAN.
SHOW MANSLAUGHTERS SCREW YOU SO
HARD.
BUT THERE HAVE BEEN PEOPLE WHO
FOUND LOVE ON "SURVIVOR," SO WHY
NOT ME?
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
TO THE RIGHT SHOULDER AND OFF.
YEAH, WERE HERE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
REAL QUICK, WHOEVER KNOWS HOW TO
DO FRONDS.
I AM A PROPERTY MANAGER FOR 365
APARTMENTS.
I SWING A HAMMER EVERY DAY OF MY
LIFE.
OH, GOOD.
WELL HAVE SHELTER IN NO
TIME.
ITS A REALLY EXCITING MOMENT
IN SURVIVOR WHEN YOU FIRST GET
TO CAMP, BUT ITS ALSO A SIGNAL
THAT GAME ON, YOU GOT TO WORK.
SHOULD WE SPLIT IT DOWN THE
MIDDLE?
I THINK WE SHOULD GATHER
FIRST.
I THINK EVERYONE ON THE DAVID
TRIBE IS GOING TO BE WAY MORE
COHESIVE THAN THE GOLAITH TRIBE,
BECAUSE OUR ADVANTAGE IS WE ARE
SCRAPPY AND WE KNOW THAT TO
SUCCEED WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
AND USE EACH OTHER TO SUCCEED IN
THIS GAME.
I ALWAYS FOOD ITS ALWAYS A
TRICKY PART.
ITS A CHALLENGE TO EARN IT.
ITS GOING TO BE A CHALLENGE TO
OPEN THE SON OF A GUN.
YOURE NOT KIDLING.
SO IM THINKING WELL BUILD
OUR SHELTER OVER THERE BECAUSE
THERE IS NATURAL CANOPY.
I NEED.
THIS SHES WORKING ON THAT.
BEING ON THE DAVID TRIBE, THAT
MOST CERTAINLY FITS ME.
IM SELF-MADE.
I STRUGGLED MY WHOLE LIFE.
IM A BLUE COLLAR GUY.
WHAT IM THINKING HERE, WERE
GOING TO SPAN THIS TO THAT.
AND BEING BROUGHT UP THE WAY I
WAS, IT SEASONED ME TO PREPARE
ME FOR EVERYDAY LIFE.
THE OVERHANG ON THIS BEAM IS
GOING TO SUPPORT THAT END.
LET ME SEE HOW THEYRE GOING
OVER THERE.
CARL, WHERES THAT CORDAGE?
PAT IMMEDIATELY TAKES LEAD OF
THE SHELTER.
ILL MAKE A MARK HERE ON THIS
TREE.
NOW, PAT CAN BE A BIT --
EXTEND THIS CORNER OUT THE
THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
THATS WHERE WERE GOING TO PUT
THAT CLEAT.
-- DIRECTIVE WHERE HE WANTS
PEOPLE.
CHRISTIAN; WHERE YOU AT?
WERE GOING TO NEED MORE BAMBOO.
IN ENGINEERING AND SCIENCE THERE
ARE PEOPLE WITH STRONG
PERSONALITIES WHO CONFLICT, BUT,
MAN, I DONT THINK IVE EVER HAD
MY NAME SHOUTED LIKE THAT IN A
PROFESSIONAL SETTING.
PUSH DOWN ON IT.
THERE YOU GO, DONT SNAP IT.
BAMBOO IS WHAT WE NEED RIGHT
NOW.
I GOT THE SENSE THAT OTHER
PEOPLE FELT A LITTLE BIT BOSSED
AROUND BY PAT.
SWEATING LIKE A PREGNANT NUN
AT CONFESSION.
I ALSO WANT TO POINT OUT,
JOKES ARE INHERENTLY RISKY.
ONCE YOU SEE THE CRACK, YOU
NEVER GO BACK.
A JOKE CAN FAIL.
YOU DIRTY BITCH.
ID GIVE MY LEFT NUT TO BE 36.
I THINK PEOPLE WERE WILLING
TO PUT UP WITH IT AS LONG AS
WERE GETTING A SHELTER BUILT.
IS THAT LONG ENOUGH TO REACH?
I DONT HAVE GOOD DEPTH
PERCEPTION.
IF HE WERE NOT SUCCEEDING IN THE
SHELTER, HE WOULD BE IN REAL
TROUBLE.
I THINK THATS THE KEY, KID.
LETS GET THE SHELTER BUILT
FIRST.
WE KNOW ITS GOING TO RAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GO FIND SOME BIG TREE
LIMBS.
HERES ONE.
ITS FREEZING COLD.
WEVE GOT TO BUILD A SHELTER OUT
OF NOTHING.
WE GOT ONE MACHETE AND THATS
IT, BUT LOOKING AT THE BRIGHT
SIDE OF THINGS AND MAKING LIGHT
OUT OF A REALLY BAD SITUATION IS
THE QUALITY IN A GOLAITH.
WHAT ARE WE SITTING ON, PALM
FRONDS.
DO WE HAVE ANY MORE OF THESE?
I DONT KNOW IF THERES ONE
THATS THIS TALL.
I THINK WE HAVE THE KEEP THAT
OTHER ONE TO KEEP EVERYTHING
DRY.
ITS AN ADJUSTMENT OUT HERE
BECAUSE IM OLDER.
IM 57.
THEYRE 25.
SO LETS BUILD A BASE AND
SAVE BAMBOO FOR THE BEAMS.
WE CAN SAVE THE GREEN ONE FOR
THE BEAMS.
I RECOMMEND THAT WE DO IT
SMALLER BECAUSE WERE OUT OF
TIME.
I HAVE YOUNG PEOPLE WHO WORK FOR
ME, SO SIMILARLY WITH THESE
YOUNGER PEOPLE ON THE TRIBE, I
PUT OUT WHAT I THINK BECAUSE I
AM ACCUSTOMED TO BEING IN
CHARGE.
TWO BIG ONES GOING UP.
SO WE NEED A BASE HERE.
I JUST NEED YOU TO SLOW DOWN
A LITTLE BIT BECAUSE YOURE NOT
LISTENING TO PEOPLE.
YOURE JUST MOVING REALLY FAST,
AND I APPRECIATE THAT.
I AM AN INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER.
IM HERE TO BUILD A SHELTER AND
HELP OUT, HOWEVER, WE HAVE
NATALIE, WHO IS VERY STRONG, AND
SHE REALLY LIKES TO GIVE ORDERS.
WE NEED TO BIG A BIT OF A
HOLE AND THEN WE NEED TO GET A
ROCK WHERE WE CAN HAMMER THAT
INTO THE GROUND AND MATCH THE
HEIGHT OF THAT.
SHE IS NOT AFRAID TO TELL YOU
WHAT SHE IS THINKING.
LADIES, HELLO, I THINK YOU
WANT TO GET YOUR FRONDS AND PUT
IT BACK THERE.
CLEARLY BARKING ORDERS AT ME
AND ERR TRIBE MEMBERS.
SHES DEFINITELY PUT A TARGET ON
HER BACK.
LETS KEEP IT PUSHING, COME
ON.
PAT, YOU NEED HAND?
YEP.
GIVE ME THAT AX.
HES GOING TO DIE.
IM FROM NEW YORK.
THEY DONT HAVE TREES IN NEW
YORK.
TREES, WE GOT LOTS OF TREES.
WE GOT THE BEST COLOR FOLIAGE IN
THE NATION.
WATCH YOUR HEAD.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
TEAM DAVID!
LETS DO IT.
TAKE THIS ONE.
BEND IT LIKE THAT.
I WAS KIND OF NERVOUS, BUT BY
THE END OF THE DAY WE HAVE A
GOOD FOUNDATION.
WERE GOING TO HAVE SHELTER.
IT KIND OF GIVES ME A SIGH OF
RELIEF.
WHERE DID YOU LEARN HOW TO DO
THIS?
YOUTUBE.
IM 19 YEARS OLD.
NOBODY KNOWS THAT.
THEY THINK THAT IM 22.
SO MY BIGGEST CHALLENGE WOULD BE
MY AGE, JUST BECAUSE I DONT
WANT PEOPLE TO THINK THAT IM
NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
IM DOWN FOR WHATEVER.
IF WE MAKE ANY CONNECTIONS,
ILL LET YOU KNOW.
YEAH.
SO IM GOING TO TRY TO MAKE
AS MANY ALLIANCES AS I POSSIBLY.
CAN.
WERE GOOD 100%.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP IT 100
WITH ME, ILL KEEP IT 100 WITH
YOU.
IM NOT GOING TO GO BEHIND
YOUR BACK.
I HAVE A WIFE AND TWO
DAUGHTERS.
JESSICA REMINDS ME OF MY
DAUGHTER.
I KNEW I COULD TAKE HER UNDER MY
WING AND MOLD HER IN THE SENSE
OF HOW I WOULD LIKE THE PLAY THE
GAME.
WERE HERE.
WE CANNOT MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
ULTIMATELY WE HAVE TO WIN
CHALLENGES SO WE DONT GO TO
TRIBAL, BUT IF THATS NOT THE
CASE --
IVE EATEN WORMS FOR NO ODD
REASON, JUST BECAUSE THEY WERE
THERE TO EAT.
SOME PEOPLE ARE ALREADY
GETTING UNDER MY SKIN.
BUT RIGHT NOW, LET HIM PUT US
TOGETHER A SHELTER.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME THINKING
THAT I WAS GOING TO BE LAID
BACK, BUT I SEE EVERYONE ELSE
APPROACHING PEOPLE, SO THAT KIND
OF LETS ME KNOW, OKAY, THE DAVID
TEAM IS HERE THE PLAY THIS GAME.
DUDE, OH MY GOSH, WERE ON
"SURVIVOR."
WHAT?
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT, MAN?
HARDLY.
FROM ALL THE PEOPLE OVER,
THERE I LIKE THEM, THEYRE COOL,
BUT I TRUST YOU.
PEOPLE MIGHT NOT THINKING
THAT WED WORK TOGETHER.
I KNOW.
BUT THATS THE REASON.
WERE SO DIFFERENT.
EXACTLY.
THEY WOULD NEVER SUSPECT US.
THE STRONGEST CONNECTION I
HAVE IS ELIZABETH.
THAT KIND OF SURPRISED ME,
BECAUSE WERE SO DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, SHES A COWGIRL.
IM A PUNK ROCKER LESBIAN.
WERE SO DIFFERENT, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME I THINK WERE
CONNECTING ON THE SAME LEVEL OF
LOYALTY AND TRUST AND HONESTY
AND RESPECT FOR THE GAME.
ANYTHING YOU NEED, I WILL LET
YOU KNOW.
I WILL DO THE SAME FOR YOU.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
IM REALLY LOYAL.
IM A BIT OF A WEIRDO.
IF I DO -- IF I GET TOO SAUCY
WITH THE WEIRD STUFF, JUST TELL
ME.
I LOVE IT.
I THINK ITS ENDEARING.
I WILL.
ILL LET YOU KNOW IF YOURE TOO
MUCH, BUT IM NERDY, TOO, I GET
IT.
NERDS HAVE TO LOOK OUT FOR EACH
OTHER.
NOT TO CALL YOU A NERD, BUT I
CALL MYSELF A NERD.
IF THERE EVER WAS A MORE APT
TERM.
I FEEL LIKE CHRISTIAN AN I
ARE KINDRED SPIRITS.
I LOVE THAT GUY.
IM A TECHNICAL WRITER, WHICH
MEANS THAT I WRITE DOCUMENTATION
FOR SOFTWARE.
SO I CONSIDER MYSELF THE NERD
WHISPERER.
IF IT BENDS, ITS NOT DRY.
YOU PROBABLY KNOW THAT BECAUSE
YOURE THE SCIENCE GUY.
I LOVE INTELLIGENT PEOPLE.
I LOVE NERDY PEOPLE.
SO I DEFINITELY WAS DRAWN TO
CHRISTIAN.
WHO HAVE YOU TALKED TO?
IM STILL FEELING EVERYONE
OUT.
I LIKE YOU BECAUSE YOURE SMART.
I REALLY LIKE GABBY.
I LOVE THE LEVEL WE VIBE AT.
SHES NERDY LIKE ME.
SHES SOMEWHAT INSECURE LIKE ME.
SO WE GET ALONG WELL.
GIVE ME A LIST OF WHO YOU
VIBE.
WITH I THINK WE VIBE, SO WERE
COOL.
BUT LET ME KNOW.
OKAY.
ANYTHING ELSE?
NO, YOU GO BACK FIRST.
ILL STAY OUT HERE.
I HAVE TO HIDE HOW WELL WE
GET ALONG, BECAUSE I DONT WANT
IT TO BE A COUPLE THREAT.
A PLATONIC COUPLE THREAT, OF
COURSE.
FOR YOUR WORK, ARE YOU... DO
YOU TRAVEL A LOT OR IS IT...
DIFFERENT CITIES.
SOMETIMES IM GOOD GUY.
SOMETIMES IM A BAD GUY.
IN MEXICO IM DOING LIKE AN
AMERICAN GIMMICK OVER THERE,
WHICH IS SUPER FUN.
IN MEXICO?
YEAH.
DO YOU HAVE A MASK?
THEY HAVE MASKS, AND I TELL
THEM THEY HAVE MASKS BECAUSE
THEYRE UGLY AND AMERICANS ARE
SMARTER AND TALLER AND ALL THE
WOMEN WANT ME.
PEOPLE KNOW ME AS JOHNNY BLAZE,
JOHNNY NITRO, JOHNNY MUNDO,
JOHNNY IMPACT, JOHNNY ULTRA.
THE MONDAY NIGHT DELIGHT, THE
AMBASSADOR OF ABDOMINAL, THE
GEORGE BUSHY OF TUSHY,
MR. ABRAHAM LINCOLN.
IM DOING AMERICAN STUFF DOWN IN
MEXICO.
THEY HATE THAT.
BUT NONE OF THOSE CHARACTERS
THAT IM PLAYING IN A WRESTLING
RING ARE GOING TO WIN THE GAME
OF "SURVIVOR."
IM PLAYING AS JOHN.
IM PLAYING AS ME.
IM SO COLD, YOU GUYS.
HOW DOES NATALIE NOT EVER
HELP.
SHE JUST STANDS THERE AND STARES
AT EVERYBODY LIKE A STALKER.
ITS REALLY CREEPING ME OUT.
SHE JUST STANDS THERE AND STARES
AT EVERYBODY.
SHE DOESNT HELP OUT WITH
ANYTHING.
SHE DOESNT HELP OUT WITH A
SINGLE THING.
ONLY BARKING ORDERS AND SHE JUST
STANDS THERE AND STARES AND
COMPLAINS.
IVE NEVER SEEN THAT BEFORE.
IT PUTS A TARGET ON HER BACK.
I DONT CARE.
I AGREE.
GETTING AN IMMUNITY IDOL
WOULD BE PROBABLY ONE OF THE TOP
FIVE BUCKET LIST "SURVIVOR"
MOMENTS.
SO OF COURSE IM GOING TO GO
LOOK FOR IT.
IM GOING TO GRAB A ROCK.
WHERES MIKE?
HES BEEN GONE FOR A LONG
TIME.
CLEARLY EVERYONE IS SO CAUGHT
UP IN THEIR SOCIAL GAME RIGHT
NOW THAT THEYRE NOT AWARE THAT
I MIGHT BE SLIPPING OFF TO LOOK
FOR AN IDOL.
WHERE MIKE AT?
ILL BRING HIM BACK.
SERIOUSLY...
ARE WE JUST GOING TO LET HIM
LOOK FOR AN IDOL?
AT LEAST ONE OF US HAS TO GO
OUT THERE.
IM GOING TO GO LOOK FOR HIM.
IM A LITTLE DOWN FOR THE
COUNT.
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY, THESE
PEOPLE THAT KEEP DISAPPEARING,
THEYRE SETTING THEMSELVES UP
FOR FAILURE.
MIKE HAD A TARGET BECAUSE WE SAW
MIKE ON "THE AMAZING RACE" HE
WROTE "SCHOOL OF ROCK," WE KNOW
HE HAS MONEY.
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL GAVE PEOPLE
A GOOD REASON.
SO SOMEBODY SAID, WHO DO YOU
WANT TO TAKE OUT FIRST?
WHO IS GOING TO CAUSE MORE
PROBLEMS AT CAMP?
NATALIE.
SHES...
HES A LOT MORE SLICK THAN
NATALIE.
HES SCARY.
HES SCARY GOOD.
ITS SO EARLY.
I THINK THAT MIKE PUT A
LITTLE BIT OF TARGET ON HIS BACK
BY GOING OUT AND LOOKING FOR AN
IDOL.
I ALSO GET MIXED VIBES FROM
NATALIE.
WE DONT HAVE TO MAKE DECISIONS
YET, BUT WHEN WE DO, WE HAVE
OPTIONS.
CAN WE GO TO THE BEACH NOW?
I WANT TO GO TO THE BEACH.
YOURE PUTTING TARGET ON YOUR
BACK?
REALLY?
REALLY.
WHY DO YOU KEEP DISAPPEARING?
IF YOU DO, YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
TALK TO SOMEBODY ABOUT WHAT YOU
DID.
I WENT TO GET MY SHOES.
EVERYONES LIKE, WHERES
MIKE?
I FOUND OUT I PUT A TARGET ON
MY BACK WHEN I RAN INTO NATALIE.
SHE SAID, YOU HAVE A TARGET ON
YOUR BIKE.
YOUVE BEEN GONE TOO LONG.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOURE LOOKING
FOR AN IDOL.
I WENT FOR THE IMMUNITY IDOL NOT
BECAUSE I NEED IT, BUT BECAUSE I
WANT IT.
I JUST GOT CAUGHT UP IN THE
EXCITEMENT OF IT AND ENDED UP
BEING HOISTED BY MY OWN PETARD.
IT LITERALLY IS NOT STOPPING.
NO.
NO, NO, NO.
IM NOT DOING THAT.
SQUEEZE IN THERE.
HANG IT.
GOT IT.
YALL ARE AWESOME.
WE HAD A ROUGH FIRST NIGHT
WITH ALL THE RAIN.
IT WAS TERRIBLE.
WEVE GOT THE ROYAL TREATMENT
FROM THE ISLAND AS FOR AS THE
WEATHER GOES.
THERE IS NO INITIATION WITH
THIS.
HOLD THEM RIGHT THERE,
CHRISTIAN.
I THINK SOMETIMES THE STRUGGLE
IS WHAT MAKES SOMEONE WHO THEY
ARE.
WHAT ELSE DO I NEED FOR THE
SHELTER?
WERE JUST ADDING MORE AND
MORE FRONDS.
BEING A DAVID, WE CARE WAY MORE
ABOUT EACH OTHER WAY MORE THAN
GOLAITHS CARE ABOUT EACH OTHER.
DRYING UP NIGHT?
YEAH, IT FEELS REALLY GOOD.
WHEN YOUVE BEEN IN THE
STRUGGLE, YOU TEND TO EMPATHIZE
AND CARE DEEPLY ABOUT THOSE WHO
ARE AROUND YOU.
ITS INBRED INTO A DAVID TO CARE
ABOUT THE OTHER DAVIDS.
I FEEL LIKE TONIGHT WONT BE
AS BAD.
TONIGHT WILL BE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT STORY.
IT WAS ROUGH.
IT WAS REALLY ROUGH LAST NIGHT.
IT DOESNT LOOK LIKE THIS IS
STOPPING.
I PROMISE THEYRE NOT DOING
AS GOOD AS US.
I THINK THERE ARE A LOT OF
COOL PEOPLE ON THAT TRIBE, SO
IM NOT ROOTING AGAINST THEM.
I HOPE THEY GO THROUGH HELL.
YOU HOPE WHAT?
ITS VERY EASY TO AVOID WORK IF
YOURE GOOD AT IT.
I DONT WANT THE WASTE MY ENERGY
BUILDING A SHELTER.
HOLY CRAP.
I THINK IT STOPPED RAINING.
IM ON "SURVIVOR."
THE ONLY THING ON MY MIND IS
SCHEMING AND PLOTTING.
I HAVE TO FIND MY FLOCK OF
SHEEP.
THIS IS COOL.
ITS VERY EASY TO GET PEOPLE
TO TRUST YOU ON "SURVIVOR."
ITS ALMOST TOO EASY.
AS SOON AS I HEARD YOU SAY,
THAT I THOUGHT, SHES PROBABLY
FROM KENTUCKY.
IT DEFINITELY WORKED OUT IN
OUR FAVOR.
FOR REAL, FOR REAL.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO MAKE
THINGS OFFICIAL AND MAKE THAT
PERSON FEEL LIKE YOU GOT A GOOD
BOND, YOUR ALLIANCE HAS AN NAME.
WE NEED AN ALLIANCE NAME.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
ILL THINK OF SOMETHING.
OKAY.
THINK OF SOMETHING.
IM NOT REAL SMART.
IF I CAN IN THIS GAME, I WANT
THE NAME ALL THE ALLIANCE,
BECAUSE IM OUT HERE TO WIN $1
MILLION, BUT IM OUT HERE TO
HAVE FUN, TOO.
I THINK OUR SHELTER IS GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
I DONT THINK THATS IN OUR
CADS FOR TODAY.
WE DID AN AMAZING JOB.
PAT CAN BE A LITTLE BIT OVER
THE TOP, BUT PAT WAS A GIFT AS
FAR AS PUTTING THAT SHELTER UP.
BUT SINCE WEVE BEEN HERE, NICK
HASNT REALLY DONE MUCH OF
ANYTHING.
I CANT STAND MAN THAT DONT
WORK.
BEING A TRUCK DRIVER, THERES
TIME I COULDNT STOP TO GET
FOOD.
I MEAN, I HAD TO GET THAT LOAD
TO WHERE IT NEEDED TO BE, SO I
CANT STAND LAZY-ASS PEOPLE.
I CANT DIG THAT.
HES NUMBER-ONE ON MY LIST.
ME TOO.
WE GOOD WITH THAT.
SO HERES MY THING.
NOT ENOUGH WOMEN FIND ANGLES.
I CAME INTO THIS THINKING THE
SAME THING.
IMED A MAN WE NEED THE
CHANGE THAT.
WE TEND TO THE FIRE AND WE COOK
THE FOOD, AND WERE PUTTING
OURSELVES AT A DISADVANTAGE.
WHEREAS THE MEN GO OUT AND
EXPLORE AND FIND THE FIREWOOD
AND WHATEVER.
IDOLS ARE IMPORTANT IN THIS
GAME BECAUSE THEYRE A HUGE
ADVANTAGE.
AND WOMEN TEND TO NOT FIND
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS AS MUCH.
WE NEED TO DO THIS.
CAN YOU STAND AND WATCH WHILE
I LOOK AT THAT BRANCH OVER
THERE?
100%.
ITS IS HARD.
THERE ARE SO MANY DAMN TREES.
USE A STICK.
I WAS READING ONLINE THAT 15%
OF ALL HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS
HAVE BEEN FOUND BY WOMEN, AND WE
KNOW THAT "SURVIVOR" PLAYS MEN
AND WOMEN EQUALLY, SO WE SHOULD
BE FINDING IDOLS EQUALLY.
SO I WANT TO HELP BOOST THAT
STAT UP.
SO WE PROBABLY HAVE FOUR
MINUTES TO DO THIS.
I KNOW THAT EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF THESE TRIBE MATES HAVE LOOKED
FOR THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
I JUST GOT CAUGHT EARLY.
SO IM GOING FOR IT.
OF COURSE IM GOING TO GO FOR
IT.
IM ON "SURVIVOR: DAVID VS. "SUR
IM GOING TO BE LOOKING FOR AN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I FIGURE EVERYBODYS LOOKING
FOR AN IDOL, I SHOULDNT WORK.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
I SHOULD LOOK FOR AN IDOL.
IM WORKING ON THE SHELTER.
EVERYBODY IS LOOKING FOR AN
IDOL.
IM ONLY LOOKING FOR AN IDOL
BECAUSE EVERYBODY IS LOOKING.
ON TV ITS EASY.
IN REAL LIFE, ITS A NEED UNTIL
A HAYSTACK.
YOU GOT TO LOOK FOR IT.
THEY DONT COME UP EASY.
I FEEL LIKE ON THE GOLIATH
TRIBE EVERYONE IS HUNTING FOR
IDOLS BECAUSE ITS IN THE
GOLIATH D.N.A.
EVERYONE WANTS THE POWER.
AT THIS POINT IT FEELS LIKE ITS
A RACE TO THE IDOL.
EVERYBODY IS ALL WORKED UP ABOUT
THIS IDOL.
I THINK ITS FUNNY BECAUSE ITS
IN MY PANTS.
SO THIS BAD BOY RIGHT HERE MAKES
ME FEEL BULLET-PROOF.
I HAVE NEVER FELT BULLET-PROOF
BEFORE.
ITS A NICE FEELING.
THE SHORT OF THE STORY IS ME,
KARA AND NATALIA ARE ALL LOOKING
FOR IDOLS.
WERE LOOKING IN EVERYTHING.
I LOOK TO MY LEFT AND I SEE THIS
ROCK.
THIS ROCK JUST LOOKS COOL.
MAYBE THERE IS AN IDOL BURIED
UNDERNEATH IT.
I LOOK UP AND RIGHT THERE IN
FRONT OF ME IS PURPLE STRING
WRAPPED AROUND A ROCK.
HEY, GUYS, GUYS.
COME HERE.
YOU FIND IT?
I IMMEDIATELY GRAB IT, WHIP
IT OUT, OPEN IT, SUPER STOKED.
IM LIKE, OH, MY GOD, I CANT
BELIEVE I, ME, FOUND AN IDOL.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL."
FINDING THIS IDOL IS A GOLIATH
MOMENT FOR ME.
I SET MYSELF A GOAL AND I FOUND
IT.
I AM BECOMING THE PERSON I WANT
TO BE IN MY LIFE.
I FOUND AN IDOL WITH THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRLS IN THIS WHOLE
ENTIRE GAME RIGHT NOW.
IT CANNOT GET ANY BETTER.
WE FOUND IT.
YES!
I CANNOT GET OVER THIS.
FREAKIN AWESOME.
YES, YES.
I GOT AN OCTOPUS, A FREAKIN
OCTOPUS.
NO?
THATS CRAZY.
DAVY CROCKETT, KING OF THE WILD
FRONTIER.
WERE TAKING THIS SUMMER BACK
THE CAMP.
IM STILL COLD.
YOU GET ANYTHING, DAVIE?
I CAUGHT A FREAKIN OCTOPUS.
OH, MY.
AN OCTOPUS, DUDE.
LOOK AT IT.
CALAMARI FOR DINNER AND RICE.
HE CAUGHT AN OCTOPUS.
IVE ALWAYS BEEN SOMEONE WHO
DOESNT CONFORM TO SOCIETY.
IM ACTUALLY A BLURD, WHICH IS A
BLACK NERD.
IVE US A BEEN A FAN OF THE
ZOMBIE GENRE, CARTOONS,
NERD-TYPE THINGS.
DAVIE, SINCE YOU CAUGHT IT,
YOU WANT FIRST?
NO, ITS ALL YOU, BRO.
LOOK AT THIS.
I LOVE "SURVIVOR," SO TO BE
SITTING HERE ON AN ISLAND IN
FIJI, WAY TO GO.
IM STILL SLAPPING MYSELF IN MY
MIND, BECAUSE IS THIS REAL?
IT WOULD BE GREAT IF THE RAIN
JUST STOPPED.
IT JUST SUCKS WITH NO FIRE AND
NO SUN.
IM JUST GETTING THROUGH IT,
YOU KNOW.
THATS ALL RIGHT.
ITS HARD.
YEAH.
I FEEL PITIFUL THAT IM
CRYING ON DAY TWO.
ITS BECAUSE IN THOSE MOMENTS
WHENEVER YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE
NOWHERE TO TURN, I ALWAYS WANTED
TO BE THAT PERSON FOR OTHER
PEOPLE, THAT THEY FELT LIKE THEY
COULD GO TO, AND IT JUST SO
HAPPENED THAT THE PERSON I DID
THAT WITH WAS MY MOM.
MY MOM HAD A GUIDE IN HER LIFE,
AND THAT WHOLE RELATIONSHIP WAS
JUST REALLY NOT GOOD FOR HER,
VERBAL, MENTAL, VERY TOXIC.
IT WAS VERY TOUGH TO SEE THAT.
AND IT WAS LIKE I HAD TO BE THE
MOM IN SOME WAYS, AND HERIVAUX
THROUGH IT BECAUSE I NEVER
WANTED HER TO FEEL ALONE OR BY
HERSELF.
I WAS IN A RELATIONSHIP FOR
FIVE YEARS WHERE HE BEAT ME LIKE
EVERY DAY.
WOW.
I WAS IN THE HOSPITAL LIKE
EVERY MONTH.
IT WAS BAD.
YOUR MOM IS LUCKY, BECAUSE WHEN
I WAS IN THAT SITUATION, I
DIDNT HAVE ANYONE.
SO I STUCK WITH HIM.
IVE BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH,
LIKE COMING TO AMERICA AT A
YOUNG AGE FROM VIETNAM AS
VIETNAMESE REFUGEES, I
EXPERIENCED POVERTY.
I HAD AN ABUSIVE BOYFRIEND WHEN
I WAS YOUNG.
MY WHOLE LIFE IS LIKE 28 YEARS
OF FIGHTING, AND AS AN M.M.A.
FIGHTER, I SPEAK TO A LOT OF
DOMESTIC ABUSE WOMEN, AND I DO
LIKE FREE SELF-DEFENSE SEMINARS.
SO WHAT I WAS TRYING TO MAKE
SURE SHE TOOK AWAY FROM THE
CONVERSATION IS SHE SAVED HER
MOMS LIFE.
I DONT KNOW WHAT YOUR MOM
WENT THROUGH, BUT SHE WAS LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU IN HER LIFE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS TALKING
ABOUT THEIR PARENTS DOMESTIC
ABUSE, AND EVERYBODY IS CRYING.
ITS NOT REALLY HOW I USUALLY
TALK TO PEOPLE.
IM JUST A GUY THAT LIKE WONT
OPEN UP.
WELL, I HAVE THIS STORY, I
REALLY DIDNT FEEL COMFORTABLE
SHARING IT.
ITS PERSONAL, AND ITS FOR ME
AND MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS AND
MY FAMILY, BUT WHEN EVERYBODY IN
MY TRIBE IS TALKING ABOUT THEIR
MOST TRAUMATIC EVENT, I FEEL
LIKE I CAN LET MY GUARD DOWN.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU ALL
SOMETHING.
I DONT KNOW, ITS JUST HARD FOR
ME TO OPEN UP, AND SO LIKE, YOU
KNOW, WHEN WE WERE SAYING OUR
STORIES, YOU KNOW, THERE IS
SOMETHING ABOUT ME THAT I JUST
DIDNT TALK ABOUT YET, AND
BASICALLY WHERE I COME FROM,
LIKE WE ALL HAVE SOMEBODY CLOSE
WHO IS LIKE, YOU KNOW, HAD DRUG
PROBLEMS, AND I WAS JUST IS
SCARED TO TALK ABOUT IT, BECAUSE
I DONT WANT MY MOTHER TO LOOK
BAD, YOU KNOW, BUT TO LOSE MY
MOM TO SOMETHING LIKE THAT, ITS
SO SAD TO ME.
I MEAN, SHE... I MISS HER SO
MUCH.
I FEEL LIKE IVE BEEN KEEPING
THINGS FROM YOU ALL.
YOU COULD HAVE HELD THAT IN
UNTIL THE VERY END.
IM SORRY.
DONT BE SORRY.
DONT BE.
SINCE I HAVE SHARED MY STORY,
IT REALLY FEELS LIKE THERE IS A
WEIGHT OFF ME.
I REALLY NEED THE TALK ABOUT MY
PERSONAL STRUGGLES, AS WELL.
I DO.
BECAUSE I NEVER HARDLY CRY
ANYMORE, AND I THINK ITS
BECAUSE MY MOM ISNT HERE.
BECAUSE SHES ALWAYS THE PERSON
I WOULD CALL, AND BEING ABLE TO
OPEN UP TO MY TRIBE MATES, SHE
WOULD HAVE BEEN PROUD OF ME FOR
THAT.
I THINK THE STORM HAS BROUGHT
GOOD THINGS FOR US.
EVEN THOUGH WERE SUPER WET, IT
MADE US BOND.
THATS TRUE.
I THINK WHEN I OPENED MY HEARTED
TO THEM, IT REALLY MADE A
DIFFERENCE.
I THINK IT KIND OF FORMS A BOND,
AND IT WILL HELP ME GROW CLOSER
TO ALL THESE PEOPLE, AND ALL OF
THEM I NEED AT THIS POINT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR."
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
LETS GO, BABY.
Jeff: THIS IS WHAT YOU
COVET IN THE GAME, THE IMMUNITY
IDOL.
ITS PRETTY SIMPLE.
IF YOU HAVE THIS, YOURE SAFE.
IF YOU DONT, YOURE HEADING TO
TRIBAL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
VOTED OUT.
LETS GET TO IT.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO SPRINT THROUGH AN
OBSTACLE TO A SAND PIT WHERE ONE
PERSON FROM EACH TRIBE WILL RACE
TO DIG UNDER A LOG.
THE FIRST THROUGH HAS THE
MACHETE.
THEYLL USE IT TO CHOP A ROPE,
RELEASING YOUR LADDER.
THE SECOND TRIBE IS PENALIZED
AND MUST UNTIE KNOTS TO RELEASE
THEIR LADDER.
YOULL THEN CONFRONT THE
"SURVIVOR" POLE VAULT, WHICH YOU
MUST USE TO CROSS FROM ONE VERY
HIGH PLATFORM TO ANOTHER, MAKING
YOUR WAY TO THE FINISH WHERE YOU
WILL SOLVE A GIANT NUMBER
PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
IN ADDITION, YOURE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
IT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IN THE GAME, FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT.
PLEASE!
Jeff: LOSERS, TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"DAVID VS. GOLIATH."
BIG CHALLENGE AHEAD.
THIS IS WHAT YOU DREAMED ABOUT.
ITS HERE.
LETS DO IT.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND FIRE IN THE
FORM OF FLINT, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
CARL LEAPS.
AND EVERYBODY MIXED UP NOW
EARLY.
COME ON, GUYS.
Jeff: WOW.
THAT IS A BATTLE.
PAT GOING AFTER IT.
NOW CANT GO ANYWHERE UNTIL
EVERYBODY IS AT YOUR MAT.
PAT WILL NOT LET JOHN GO.
WOW.
JOHN, LETS MOVE.
LETS GO, LETS GO.
Matt: YOURE GOOD, GOLAITH.
IT IS ALEX VERSUS CARL.
ITS A SHOWDOWN RIGHT NOW
BETWEEN DAVID AND GOLAITH.
TWO DIFFERENT APPROACHES.
CARL IS USING HIS FEET.
ALEC IS DIGGING.
ALEC GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
CAN HE GET THROUGH?
ALEC IS THROUGH.
HELL GET THE MACHETE.
CARL IS STUCK.
GO, GOLIATH.
DAVID TILL WORKING.
CARL TRYING TO GET UNDER THAT
POLE.
GO, GOLIATH.
NATALIA IS FIRST.
SHES ACROSS.
THATS HOW YOU DO IT.
TEAMWORK.
CARL IS THROUGH.
AND EXHAUSTED.
CARL HAS NOW GOT TO UNTIE THE
KNOTS.
THE DAVID TRIBE QUICKLY FALLING
BEHIND EARLY IN THIS CHALLENGE.
THE GOLIATH TRIBE WORKING
TOGETHER.
ALEC HELPING EVERYBODY.
PULL IT, PULL IT, TO THE
RIGHT.
Jeff: THERE YOU GO, GO,
DAVID.
WE ARE STILL IN THIS!
Jeff: THE GOLIATHS ARE ALL
ACROSS.
GO, GOLIATHS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
Jeff: THERE GOES PAT.
HES FIRST ACROSS.
TAKE IT EASY.
BI IS ACROSS NOW.
GOLIATH HAS MASSIVE HEAD START.
THE GOLIATHS ARE ALREADY MOVING
PUZZLE PIECES.
11.
PUSH THIS ONE RIGHT HERE.
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE IT.
Jeff: HERE COMES DAVIE, THE
LAST DAVID.
YOURE GOOD.
GO.
GO, GO, GO!
CARL TAKES A BIG FALL.
HE HAS BEEN THROUGH THE RINGER
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
CHRISTIAN IS THE CALLER FOR THE
DAVIDS.
IT IS A REMATCH FROM THE EARLIER
SHOWDOWN, CHRISTIAN VERSUS
ALISON.
YOU ARE SOLVING THIS PUZZLE.
ONE THROUGH 25.
ROW TWO, ROW TWO.
Jeff: NUMBERS GO HORIZONLY
LEFT TO RIGHT, ONE THROUGH 25.
THIS IS GOING TO COME DOWN TO
TRIBE COMMUNICATION.
PUSH ROW TWO.
Jeff: HERE COMES THE RAIN
AGAIN.
17 COMES OUT ANYWAY.
Jeff: BOTH TRIBES
APPROACHING THIS THE SAME WAY.
THE ONE IS GOING TO GO THERE.
THEYRE GOING VERTICALLY EVEN
THOUGH THE PUZZLE IS HORIZON, SO
ITS NOT GOING THE LOOK RIGHT
UNTIL YOU HAVE EVERY ROW
FINISHED.
THE GOLIATHS HAVE THEIR FIRST
VERTICAL ROW.
THE DAVIDS HAVE THEIR LAST
THE DAVIDS HAVE CAUGHT UP IN
THIS CHALLENGE NOW.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK.
EXCELLENT.
CYCLE IT ONE MORE TIME UNTIL I
GET THE 24.
Jeff: GREAT COMMUNICATION
BY THE DAVID TRIBE.
NOBODY ARGUING.
PULL IT, PULL IT.
ONE IS DONE.
Matt: EVERYBODY YELLING ON
THE GOLIATH TRIBE.
THE GOLIATH TRIBE FINISHES A
SECOND ROW.
GOLIATH HAVING SUCCESS DESPITE
YELLING AT EACH OTHER.
PUT THAT IN ROW FOUR.
WE ARE DONE THERE.
Jeff: DAVIDS NOW HAVE THEIR
SECOND ROW COMPLETE AND WE ARE
BACK TIED AGAIN, JUST WENDELL
THE GOLIATHS PULL AHEAD, THE
DAVIDS ARE RIGHT ON THEIR HEELS,
AS EXPECTED.
ITS FOUR, ITS FOUR!
Jeff: WILL IT BE THE
GOLIATHS, OR WILL IT BE THE
DAVIDS?
THE GHIETS HAVE THEIR FOURTH
ROW.
ONE AND ONE?
ONE AND ONE.
Jeff: THE DAVIDS NOW HAVE
THEIR FOURTH ROW.
THIS IS IT!
[ALL YELLING]
THE GOLIATHS THINK THEY HAVE IT.
THE GOLIATHS PULL OUT THE FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, SENDING THE
DAVID TRIBE TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GUYS, WE DID OUR BEST.
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED ABOUT.
ITS OKAY.
WE GOT THIS, BRO.
Jeff: GOLIATHS,
CONGRATULATIONS.
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, FIRST
ONE.
ALSO FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CONGRATULATIONS.
SO, PAT, AS YOU WATCH THE
GOLIATHS WALK PAST WITH THAT
IDOL, WHAT IS THE FEELING
KNOWING TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
ONE OF THE TEN OF YOU, YOUR
DREAM WILL BE OVER THREE DAYS
IN.
ITS A SICKENING FEELING
FIRST AND FOREMOST.
THE RAIN IS COMPLETE MORALE
BUMMER, BUT ITS BROUGHT US
TOGETHER INSIDE OUR STRUCTURE.
AND ITS BROUGHT OUR HEARTS
TOGETHER AS A BIG HEART NOW.
WERE GOING TO LOSE AN ARTERY TO
OUR HEART, BUT WERE GOING TO
STAY STRONG.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
ONE OF THE DAVIDS WILL BE THE
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
ITS TOUGH TO LOSE.
NOW WE HAVE TO VOTE SOMEONE OUT.
AND I DONT TRUST NICK.
I HAVE NOT SEEN HIM PERFORM IN
THE GROUP AND IN THE CAMP, AND
ITS NOT ONLY ME.
THATS THE CONSENSUS OF THE
TRIBE.
I CANT SEE.
ITS OKAY.
SLOW, DEEP BREATHS.
YOULL BE OKAY.
YOU HAVE A FLAT SURFACE?
NOT YET, NOT YET.
OVER THIS SIDE.
CAN YOU TAKEVE THE HEAD AND
NECK.
DO YOU MIND BRINGING THE LINE
IN.
WHEREABOUTS IS YOUR PAIN AT
THE MINUTE?
WHERE?
MY BACK.
WERE GOING TO GIVE A SHOT
FOR YOUR PAIN.
WE GOT YOU.
ITS OKAY.
FOCUS ON THAT.
I CANT FOCUS.
ITS OKAY.
YOURE DOING A GOOD JOB.
WENDELL WE LEAVE THE
CHALLENGE, WE ARE ON A BOAT.
THE SEAS ARE REALLY ROUGH, AND
THE BOAT SLAMS DOWN ON ONE OF
THE WAVES, AND WE HEAR A CRACK,
AND AT FIRST I THOUGHT PAT HAD
JUST HURT HIS BACK, MAYBE
TWEAKED IT A BIT, BUT WE DONT
FOE WHATS HAPPENING, AND WERE
WATCHING, WERE HOPING FOR THE
BEST
PAT YOULL FEEL A LITTLE COLD
SENSATION GOING UP YOUR ARM.
OKAY, BUDDY.
IM SCARED.
DONT WORRY.
YOU JUST FOCUS ON ME.
TAKE NICE, DEEP BREATHS.
AND THEN JEFF ARRIVED, AND WE
ALL GROANED, BECAUSE IT MEANS
SOMETHING REALLY BAD HAS
HAPPENED.
THEY WERE ON A BOAT
TRANSPORTING BACK TO THEIR CAMP,
AND WHAT HAPPENED?
IT SOUNDS LIKE THERES BEEN
AN IMPACT ON THE BOAT WHICH HAS
HIT PAT PRETTY HARD ON HIS BACK,
CAUSING HIM A LOT OF PAIN.
ARE YOU STILL WITH US, PAT?
PAT, CAN YOU OPEN YOUR EYES THE
PAIN IS THE MAIN PROBLEM.
Jeff: JOE, THIS IS REALLY
UNUSUAL, EVEN THOUGH A BET RIDE
BACK TO CAMP IS VERY NORMAL,
WEVE NEVER HAD ANYBODY BEING
INJURED BEING TRANSPORTED.
WHATS THE CONCERN?
BECAUSE OF THE IMPACT TO HIS
BACK AND THE AMOUNT OF PAIN HES
NEW YORK WE ARE WORRIED THAT HE
COULD HAVE DONE SOME KIND OF
FRACTURE TO HIS BACK.
Jeff: PAT, CAN YOU HEAR ME,
ITS JEFF?
THIS IS SEVERE.
IS THIS A QUESTION RIGHT NOW OF
WHETHER HE CONTINUES?
YEAH, I THINK IT MIGHT BE.
YOU OKAY.
YOU CANT TAKE ME.
I CANT LEAVE.
BE STRONG.
WERE HERE FOR YOU, PAT.
I CANT.
JOE, IS THERE ANY WAY FOR HIM
TO CONTINUE, OR DO YOU NEED TO
GET HIM TO THE HOSPITAL?
HES A TOUGH GUY, SOMEONE AS
TOUGH AS PAT IN THIS MUCH PAIN
DOES MAKE ME CONCERNED THAT WE
DO NEED TO RULE OUT ANY SERIOUS
DAMAGE, WHICH WE CANT DO ON THE
BEACH.
Jeff: SO YOURE PULLING HIM
FROM THE GAME?
I DONT THINK WE HAVE ANY
CHOICE.
WE TO GET HIM TO THE HOSPITAL TO
MAKE SURE THERES NO SERIOUS
DAMAGE.
I JUST CANT.
Jeff: BROTHER, IM AFRAID
THERE IS NO OTHER CHOICE.
WE HAVE TO LOOK OUT FOR YOU,
PAT.
THATS THE NUMBER-ONE JOB OF OUR
MEDICAL TEAM IS TO TAKE CARE OF
YOU.
LETS BRING IN THE HELICOPTER,
GUYS.
LETS BRING IT IN.
THEYRE TAKING HIM OUT.
OH, MY GOSH.
SERIOUSLY, NOTHING CAN GO OUR
WAY, LIKE NOTHING.
I FEEL SO BAD FOR HIM.
Jeff: YOU JUST SAID AT THE
END OF THE CHALLENGE THAT THE
DAVID TRIBE WAS GOING THE LOSE
AN ARTERY BUT THE HEART WAS
GOING TO GO ON, YOU CLEARLY
DIDNT KNOW YOU WERE GOING TO BE
THE ARTERY.
I DONT WANT TO QUIT.
Jeff: YOU ARE NOT QUITTING.
DR. JOE IS PULLING YOU FROM THE
GAME FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY.
THERE IS NOBODY THATS GOING TO
QUESTION YOUR HEART.
COME ON IN, GUYS.
YOURE A BEAST.
IT WAS REALLY HARD TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO HIM.
HE WAS FIGHTING TO STAY IN.
AND THERE WAS TEARS ROLLING DOWN
HIS FACE.
WE LOVE YOU, PAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE GOT TO GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
BE STRONG.
ONE, TWO, THREE... LIFT!
I HOPE HE KNOWS HOW MUCH WE
LOVE HIM, AND I HOPE THAT HES
STILL GRATEFUL FOR THIS
EXPERIENCE, BECAUSE WERE
GRATEFUL FOR HIM.
OKAY.
WE NEED TO GO UP, FURTHER UP.
WE LOVE YOU, PAT!
STAY STRONG.
AS PAT LEFT, I FELT A SENSE
OF GUILT IN A WAY, BECAUSE I
THINK I REALLY MISJUDGED HIM.
I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO BE
THIS BOSSY JERK GUY FROM NEW
YORK.
I COULDNT HAVE BEEN MORE WRONG.
HE ORGANIZED HOW TO BUILD THE
SHELTER.
HE WAS THE LEADER FROM DAY ONE.
HE WAS THE CENTER OF CAMP.
AND ITS JUST A HUGE LOSS.
Jeff: MAN.
EXPECTED THE UNEXPECTED EVERY
DAY OUT HERE.
I CAN SEE THE EMOTION.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS FEELING?
TO LOSE HIM SO EARLY, ITS
REALLY HARD.
YOU GOT TO SIT BACK AND THINK,
IS ANYTHING GOING TO GO OUR WAY,
BECAUSE WE JUST LOST ONE OF OUR
STRONGEST PLAYERS.
Jeff: OF ALL THE TRIBES FOR
THIS TO HAPPEN TO, ITS THE
DAVID TRIBE.
YOU ARE CONSTANTLY THROWN AN
OBSTACLE EVERY DAY.
NONE OF US WOULD HAVE
EXPECTED THIS, AND IT FITS WHAT
WEVE ALL BEEN TALKING ABOUT SO
PERFECTLY IN THE WORST WAY.
BUT I FEEL LIKE PAT WOULD WANT
TO SEE US SUCCEED AND STICK
TOGETHER AS MUCH AS WE CAN.
Jeff: WELL, IF THERE IS A
SILVER LINING, YOU LOST A
CHALLENGE, YOU LOST A TRIBE
MEMBER, YOU WONT LOSE ANOTHER
ONE.
THERE WILL BE NO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: ONE LAST BIT OF GOOD
NEWS, EVEN THOUGH YOURE NOT
GOING TO TRIBAL, THERE WILL BE A
FLINT WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT
CAMP.
HOPEFULLY THE RAIN WILL BRECK
AND YOU GUY CAN GET TO WORK ON
STARTING FIRE.
ALL RIGHT.
THREE DAYS IN, DOWN ONE TRIBE
MEMBER, BUT WE ARE EARLY IN THIS
GAME.
THE FIGHT AINT OVER.
WERE GOING TO KEEP BRINGING IT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
GET TO CAMP.
THE GAME CONTINUES ON.
TODAY WAS PROBABLY ONE OF THE
MOST DRAINING DAYS OF MY LIFE.
THIS HAS BEEN CRAZY.
AND ITS TESTING YOU RIGHT OUT
THE GATE, ONE DISASTER AFTER THE
NEXT.
THIS IS TYPICAL OF WHAT A DAVID
HAS TO GO THROUGH TO ACCOMPLISH
ANYTHING IN LIFE.
BUT THIS AINT MY FIRST TIME
IVE BEEN KNOCKED DOWN, YOU
KNOW, AND SO I THINK THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT THE DAVIDS HAVE
GOING FOR US.
WE WILL KEEP FIGHTING.
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Matt: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," THERES NEW WAR.
IM GOING TO DROP A LITTLE
NATALIE NAPALM BEFORE ITS OVER.
SHES CRAZY.
SOME PEOPLE SAY ITS
AGGRESSIVE.
OH, WELL.
Jeff: A NEW TARGET.
THEYRE THROWING YOUR NAME
OUT.
EXCUSE ME?
AND A NEW MAN IN CHARGE.
AFTER HYPER PERSON LIKE ME IS
THE PERSON TO HANDLE IT ALL.
TO BE OUT OF THE GAME NOT BY
VOTE BUT BY PURE ACCIDENT IS GUT
WRENCHING, BUT ULTIMATELY I WILL
PICK MYSELF UP AND GET BACK ON
MY HORSE.
AS A DAVID, ITS WHAT IVE DONE
FOR 41 YEARS.
ITS THE STORY OF MY LIFE.