Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR", KARA, ALISON, AND
ALEC CONSIDERED WORKING WITH THE
DAVIDS.
WELL GIVE YOU FIRST THREE TO
CREATE AN ALLIANCE WITH THE
DAVIDS.
Jeff: BUT TRUST WAS AN
ISSUE.
THERES GOLIATHS IN MY FACE
AGAIN.
Jeff: AND THE DAVIDS
PREPARED FOR BATTLE.
WE HAVE THREE ADVANTAGES.
AND WE CANT SCREW UP THIS
VOTE.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THE POWER SHIFTED WHEN NICK
PLAYED HIS ADVANTAGE.
WHOSE VOTE ARE YOU GOING TO
STEAL?
I THINK ILL TAKE ALISONS
VOTE.
Jeff: WHICH CAUSED ALEC AND
KARA TO SAVE FACE WITH THE
DAVIDS AND COMPELLED DAN TO PLAY
HIS IDOL.
YOURE PLAYING THIS
FOR YOURSELF?
YES, SIR.
Jeff: BUT IT WAS BLOCKED BY
A NEW ADVANTAGE, THE IDOL
NULLIFIER.
THIS NULLIFIER WAS PLAYED
AGAINST DAN.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: BING.
SENDING DAN TO THE JURY.
DAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
ANOTHER EPIC TRIBAL.
TWO ADVANTAGES PLAYED
CORRECTLY.
HOW RARE IS THAT?
OH, MY GOD.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WELL PLAYED.
PLAYING THAT NULLIFIER AND
PLAYING IT TO PERFECTION FELT
GREAT.
HELL, I FEEL I SHOULD GO DOWN IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY FOR THAT ONE.
THEY NEVER SEEN IT COMING.
NOW THAT WE HAVE NUMBERS EVEN AT
5-5, HOPEFULLY WE CAN KEEP OUT
FOOT ON THEIR THROATS AND BURY
THEM AND RIDE OFF INTO THE
SUNSET.
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE SWITCHED THE NAME FROM THE
GOLIATH TRIBE.
I DIDNT VOTE TONIGHT.
OKAY.
AND?
ME?
YEP.
HAVING YOUR ALLIANCE STAB YOU
IN THE BACK DOESNT FEEL GOOD.
AND I WILL WITHOUT HESITATION
WRITE ANY OF THEIR NAMES DOWN AS
QUICKLY AND AS SOON AS I CAN.
THE ONLY REASON THEY CAST
THOSE VOTES FOR ME IS TO MAKE IT
LOOK LIKE THEY WERE STILL WITH
YOU GUYS SO THEY COULD COME
BECOME AND HAVE A STORY TO TELL.
IM IN THE A SCORNED WOMAN,
BECAUSE I CAN HANDLE VOTES AND
BLIND SIDES AND BACKSTAB, BUT
THAT IS WHAT I NEED YOU TO KNOW.
GOT IT.
THE GOLIATH TRIBE IS DEAD AS
DEAD CAN BE.
I DONT THINK THEY KNOW HOW
VICIOUS I CAN, BE BUT THEYRE
GOING TO FIND OUT VERY SOON.
THE ONLY PEOPLE AWAKE ARE ME
AND DAVIE.
COME ON, SOMEBODY PLAYS AN IDOL,
ITS VERY LIKELY ANOTHER ONE IS
OUT THERE.
I FEEL LIKE IT WOULD BE IN
THIS AREA BECAUSE NOTHING HAS
BEEN HIDDEN HERE YET.
ME AND NICK WANT TO HAVE AS MANY
ADVANTAGES AS WE CAN IN THIS
GAME, MANLY FOR ME BECAUSE I
SUCK AT THESE DAMN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
MOST OF THE CLUES HAVE BEEN
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE ISLAND.
AT FIRST WE CONTINUE TO SEE
ANYTHING AND WERE GETTING
NERVOUS BECAUSE THE GOLIATHS ARE
GETTING READY TO WAKE UP.
HOLY CRAP.
IM SO STOKED.
ALL IM THINKING IS FINALLY I
FOUND AN IDOL.
BUT ITS NOT AN IDOL.
ITS AN IDOL CLUE.
SO IT SAYS, "CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND THE CLUE TO A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT WILL REQUIRE YOU TO BE
DARING.
TONIGHT WHILE THE OTHERS SLEEP,
YOU MUST SNEAK OUT OF CAMP.
YOUR IDOL AWAITS AT THE ISLANDS
FURTHEST POINT.
LOOK FOR THE FLAME.
GOOD LUCK."
THATS SO FRUSTRATING.
I HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL TONIGHT.
ITS GOING TO BE HARD TO SNEAK
OUT OF CAMP.
ITS GOING TO TAKE SOME
CREATIVITY.
ILL DO WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO,
EVEN IF IT MEANS STAYING UP ALL
NIGHT TO FIND THIS THING.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS REWARD
CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOULL BE
DIVIDED INTO TWO TEAMS OF FIVE.
ON MY GO, YOULL RACE OUT TO A
ROPE BRIDGE AND CROSS IT.
WHEN YOU REACH THE FINISH,
YOULL ATTEMPT TO LAND THREE
RUNGS ON A LADDER TARGET.
FIRST TEAM TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOURE PLAYING FOR.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: THE WINNING FIVE WILL
ENJOY A "SURVIVOR" PICNIC.
YOULL HAVE FRESH WRAPS, SALAD,
AND WINE.
LOSERS, ANOTHER HOT AFTERNOON
BACK AT CAMP.
WORTH PLAYING FOR IN.
OH, YEAH.
DEFINITELY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WERE GOING TO DO A RANDOM DRAW
FOR TEAMS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
WE GOT THIS, RIGHT?
WE GOT THIS.
Jeff: GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH
THAT WATER.
STAY STRONG, STAY STRONG.
Jeff: ACROSS THE ROPE
BRIDGE.
GO, PURPLE.
GO, ORANGE.
ITS GOING TO BE NICK OUT FIRST
FOR PURPLE.
ALEC FOR ORANGE.
YOU GOT TO BALANCE WITH YOUR
FEET ON THE BOTTOM ROPE USING
THE TOP ROPE TO KEEP THAT
BALANCE AND MOVE YOU ACROSS.
ITS A NEW "SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE.
ALEC MAKING QUICK WORK OF IT AS
HE HAS DONE ALL SEASON.
ALEC IS GOOD.
GO, ORANGE.
NICK NEARLY ACROSS FOR PURPLE.
GOT TO GET IN THE WATER.
GO, PURPLE.
ITS GOING TO BE ALISON HEADING
UP FOR ORANGE.
HERE COMES KARA FOR PURPLE.
YOU GOT IT, KARA.
YOU GOT IT, ALISON.
TALK YOUR TIME.
Jeff: ALISON STRUGGLING ALL
AROUND.
CAN SHE GET IT BACK?
NO, ALISON GOT TO START AGAIN.
HUGE SETBACK FOR ORANGE.
TAKE YOUR TIME, KARA.
ALISON, WIDE.
Jeff: YOU DO NOT PRACTICE
THIS AT HOME ON THE WEEKEND.
THESE ARE THE "SURVIVOR" GUINEA
PIGS RIGHT HERE.
KARA NEARLY THERE.
YOU GOT IT, GIRL.
Jeff: GO, PURPLE.
ITS GOING TO BE ANGELINA UP
NEXT.
ALISON STILL STRUGGLING, COSTING
MORE TIME.
HERE COMES ANGELINA TRYING THE
THE -- TO LAP HER.
BUT ALISON IS FIGHTING.
ALISON NEARLY THERE FOR ORANGE.
ALISONS GOT IT.
GO, ORANGE.
GABBY HEADING UP FOR ORANGE.
ANGELINA NOW AT THE FOURTH ROPE
FOR PURPLE.
ANGELINA STRUGGLING TO GET THAT
FIFTH ROPE.
SHES GOT IT.
YOU GOT IT, GABBY.
Jeff: GABBY STRUGGLING.
SHES ALL TWISTED UP.
YOU GOT THIS.
GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: ANGELINA IS THERE.
GOT TO GET IN THE WATER.
GO, PURPLE.
IT WILL BE CARL NOW FOR PURPLE.
CARL THE ONLY OTHER PERSON ALONG
WITH ANGELINA TO NOT GO ON A
REWARD SINCE THE MERGE.
HE CAN TASTE THOSE WRAPS.
HERE GOES GABBY NOW KICKING IT
INTO THE NEXT GORE.
CARL MAKING FAST WORK OF THIS.
GABBY, YOURE GOOD.
GO, ORANGE.
CARLS AT THE PLATFORM.
GO, PURPLE.
HERE GOES MIKE FOR ORANGE.
DAVIE QUICKLY UP THE LADDER FOR
PURPLE.
DAVIE IS THE LAST PERSON FOR
TAKE YOUR TIME.
Jeff: MIKE MOVING SLOWLY
WHILE DAVIE CONTINUES TO RIP
THROUGH IT.
VERY FAST TIME FOR DAVIE.
GO, PURPLE.
PURPLE HAS EVERYBODY ACROSS.
MIKE STILL WORKING FOR ORANGE.
PURPLE GETS TO THE PLATFORM.
GO, PURPLE.
NICK GOING TO JUMP OUT NOW FOR
THE FINAL STAGE OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
PURPLE WITH A BIG TIME
ADVANTAGE.
START THROWING THOSE RUNGS.
MIKE IS ACROSS.
GO, CHRISTIAN.
CHRISTIAN THE FIFTH AND FINAL
MEMBER FOR ORANGE.
NICK TOSSES.
THATS NO GOOD.
ITS GOT TO BE LEVEL.
CHRISTIAN GOING VERY
AGGRESSIVELY, TRYING TO MAKE UP
SOME TIME.
NICK LANDS THE FIRST LADDER
RUNG.
COME ON CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: PURPLE DOWN TO TWO
LADDER RUNGS.
CHRISTIAN ANEN CREDIBLY FAST
TIME.
GO, ORANGE.
NICK GOING TO TRY AGAIN.
JUST MISSES.
IT IS ALEC IN THE WATER FOR
ORANGE NOW.
NICK WITH A ONE-RUNG LEAD.
THERE ARE THREE RUNGS TOTAL.
HERE GOES ALEC.
NO, THAT WONT WORK, ALEC.
NICK ANOTHER CONNECTION, BUT
ITS LOPSIDED.
ALEC HAS THE FIRST LADDER RUNG.
WE ARE TIED 1-1.
IT WOULD BE A HUGE COMEBACK FOR
ORANGE.
GO GET IT, GO GET IT, GO GET
IT.
Jeff: NICK NOW GOING TO
SWAP OUT.
HERE COMES DAVIE.
ALEC GOING TO TRY AGAIN.
OH.
YOU ALMOST HAD IT.
Jeff: IT IS DAVIE FOR
PURPLE AND HE LANDS IT ON HIS
FIRST ONE.
IT IS 2-1.
ALEC SCORES HIS SECOND.
WE ARE TIED AGAIN.
ALEC CAN WIN IT AND HE DOES.
ORANGE WINS REWARD.
WHAT A COMEBACK FROM ORANGE.
ALISON, GABBY, MIKE, ALEC,
CHRISTIAN, NICE AFTERNOON, PLANS
FOR YOU, "SURVIVOR" PICNIC.
HEAD TO THE BEACH.
THE BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP.
THANK YOU.
DAVIE, CARL, CARBACK ANGELINA,
NICK, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
I HAD A CHANCE TO PROVE RIGHT
THERE IN MY GRASP AND IT GOT
AWAY BECAUSE OF ALEC.
HES A CHALLENGE KING.
HES PROVEN THAT TIME AND TIME
AGAIN.
SO FIRST CHANCE YOU GET TO GET
HIM OUT OF HERE, YOU GET HIM OUT
OF HERE.
WINNER, WINNER, WINNER.
OH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
OH.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR ALL THE
SUPPORT.
ESPECIALLY ALEC.
REWARD CHALLENGE COULDNT
HAVE GONE ANY BETTER.
WE ALL CONTRIBUTED.
EVERYONE DID SO WELL.
IM SO GRATEFUL WE HAD ALEC ON
OUR TEAM.
I WAS THE STAR OF THE SHOW.
SO RIGHT NOW IS A CHANCE TO
CAPITALIZE ON THAT.
WE DONT HAVE THE NUMBERS RIGHT
NOW, AND ANGELINA IS PLAYING
WITH THE DAVIDS.
I NEED TO GET THIS RELATIONSHIP
GOING WITH CHRISTIAN AND GABBY
AGAIN.
WITH YOUR NAME POPPING UP AT
TRIBAL, I WAS NOT A PART OF THAT
AT ALL.
OKAY.
WHEN IM BAR TENDING AND IM
FLIRTING WITH A GIRL, E-MAIL
WORKING FOR THE TIP.
RIGHT NOW CHRISTIAN AND GABBY
ARE SITTING ACROSS THE BAR.
THEYRE THE TWO HOTTEST GIRLS
IVE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
IM PUTTING THE CHARM ON AND IM
WORKING FOR THEIR FREAKIN
NUMBERS RIGHT NOW.
IM OVER THE DAVID-GOLIATH.
I WAS STRADDLING ONE LEG IN
ONE CAMP AND ONE LEG IN ANOTHER.
NOW I FEEL LIKE IVE TOTALLY
COMMITTED.
ITS EXCITING.
ITS REALLY EXCITING.
NOW THAT THE TABLES HAVE
TURNED, OF COURSE THE GOLIATHS
WANT TO WORK WITH US.
THEY HELD ALL THE POWER BEFORE.
AND THEY COULD KIND OF JERK US
AROUND AS LONG AS THEY WANTED.
BUT NOW THE DAVIDS HAVE THE
POWER.
SO IT ALMOST FORCES THEIR HAND
IN A WAY TO PLAY WITH US, WHICH
IS GREAT, BECAUSE I HAVE MORE
OPTIONS NOW.
HOW MUCH DID YOU EAT?
OH, MY GOD, E-MAIL SO FAT.
NO, WAY.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE THERE LETTERS?
OH, MY GOD, I LOVE MY FAMILY.
THANK YOU FOR WINNING THIS.
I KNOW THAT YOU FEEL
EMBARRASSED WHEN WE SAY IT, BUT
WE LOVE YOU, AN WE ARE VERY
PROUD OF YOU.
IM PROUD THAT YOU DECIDED TO
DO SOMETHING AND STUCK WITH IT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE JUST THINK
AND TALK.
YOU ACTUALLY DO.
I AM WRITING TO MY SON, WHO
HAS ACHIEVED ONE OF HIS GOALS TO
PLAY THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
GREAT JOB.
MY DAD SAID, HEY, FIND AN IDOL,
WIN A BIG FEAST, MAKE JEFF
LAUGH.
I THINK IVE DONE ALL THREE OF
THOSE THINGS ALREADY.
READING THESE LETTERS REALLY
DOES SORT OF ADD MOTIVATION FOR
ME TO SAY, HEY, LOOK, I CAN WIN
THIS, ITS GOING TO BE HARD,
JUST KNOW WERE HOME PULLING FOR
YOU AND TAKE SOME OF OUR
STRENGTH.
ITS GOING TO REQUIRE ME TO
BURN PEOPLE.
ITS GOING TO MEAN I HAVE TO
MAKE HARD DECISIONS.
I WANT TO PROVE NOW PEOPLE
SHOULDNT UNDERESTIMATE ME, THAT
IM A FORCE IN THIS GAME.
NEVER IN MY LIFE DID I THINK
NOT CATCHING FISH WOULD BE MORE
THAN JUST A BAD DAY.
ITS STARVATION.
STARVATION FOR REAL.
ITS FRUSTRATING TO GO FROM A
HIGH FROM TRIBAL TO, YOU KNOW, A
HE OF YET ANOTHER DAY OF NO
FOOD, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, ITS TOUGH, MAN.
26 DAYS, IT AINT EASY.
AND YOU CAN BE A MILLIONAIRE, A
BILLIONAIRE OR A HOMELESS PERSON
ON THE STREET.
IN FLOOD IS IN FOOD.
YOU CANT PREPARE FOR THAT.
BUT I CAME HERE TO WIN.
I GUESS TODAY IS MY MOMENT, BUT
IT WILL JUST MAKE ME STRONGER.
IT JUST MAKES ME STRONGER.
CHEER, GUYS.
LOSER CHEERS.
SORRY WE DIDNT COME BACK.
KARA, DO YOU THINK HE HAS AN
IDOL?
WHO?
ALEC?
WHY?
IF ALEC DOESNT WIN, THEN I
WANT TO GET HIM OUT.
HE IS A CHALLENGE BEAST.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
HES A THREAT.
CARL MAKES THE PLAN THAT ITS
GOING TO BE ALEC.
IM LOOKING AT THEM, AN IM
LIKE, WERE REALLY JUST TALKING
ABOUT THIS OUT LOUD IN FRONT OF
ME?
LIKE YOU KNOW THAT IM CLOSEST
WITH ALEC AT THIS POINT.
CARL IS VERY CONFIDENT AFTER
THAT LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, BUT
WHEN YOURE OVERCONFIDENT IN
THIS GAME, I KNOW FOR A FACT, AS
A GOLIATH, THAT IT DOESNT
ALWAYS GO IN YOUR FAVOR.
IM GOING TO WIN JUST TO PUT
THE CHERRY ON TOP.
CARLS COMING AFTER ME.
IS THAT A SCARY THING?
YEAH, ITS A SUPER SCARY THING.
SO ALL THATS ON MY MIND IS I
MOST LIKELY NEED TO WIN THIS
NEXT IMMUNITY.
ITS ANEN SETTLING KIND OF
FEELING JUST TO KNOW THAT YOUR
PRIMARY TARGET NUMBER ONE RIGHT
NOW.
AND THEN ON TOP OF THAT, WHEN I
WAS AT THE REWARD, I ATE TOO
MUCH.
I FEEL SUPER FRICKING SICK, MAN.
OH, MAN.
I JUST CANT WAIT FOR EVERYBODY
TO GO TO BED, BECAUSE TONIGHT I
HAVE TO GO GET THIS IDOL.
THANK GOD.
SO PEOPLE THAT WENT ON THE
REWARD ARE COMPLAINING ABOUT
THEIR TOM Mac, AN THEY ATE TOO
MUCH TOO FAST, LIKE ALISON IS
THROWING UP EVERYWHERE.
SHE OVERDID IT.
SHE EALT TOO MUCH.
-- SHE ATE TOO MUCH.
SO THERE IS A BIT OF DISTRACTION
ALREADY.
[SNORING]
IN MY REAL LIFE, IT IS FUN TO
GET OUT HERE AND BE MISCHIEVOUS,
BE A CRIMINAL AN SNEAK OFF.
I DONT WANT TO PUT MY GAME IN
JEOPARDY BY DOING MISCHIEVOUS
STUFF, BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I
WANT AN IDOL.
I GOT TO GET IT DONE QUICKLY.
I CANT TAKE ALL NIGHT.
LUCKILY DAVIE IS LOOKING OUT FOR
ME.
OH, MY GOD.
IM JUST KEEPING GUARD.
ALISON IS HAVING REACTIONS FROM
HER REWARD.
IM LIKE, HURRY UP, GET YOUR ASS
BACK HERE.
I CAN ONLY COVER YOU FOR SO
LONG.
IM TRYING TO GET THERE AS
QUICK AS POSSIBLE.
I DONT KNOW HOW FAR AWAY THIS
THING IS.
I WALKED FURTHER DOWN THE BEACH
THIS WHOLE TIME IVE BEEN HERE.
FINALLY OFF IN THE DISTANCE I
SEE A LIGHT.
SO, YEAH, MY HEART IS POUNDING.
FIRE REPRESENTS LIFE.
YOUR LIFE IN THE GAME JUST GOT A
BIT MORE SECURE.
HURRY BACK.
THATS SICK.
MY FIRST IMMUNITY IDOL ON
"SURVIVOR."
THIS IS AWESOME.
I GOT POWER IN NUMBERS RIGHT
NOW.
BUT EVENTUALLY PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO RECOGNIZE, HEY, NICKS TAKEN
OUT A LOT OF TARGETS.
HES GOT A SOLID RESUME.
SO WEARING THIS IDOL FEELS
AMAZING.
IM GOING TO BE IN THE BEST
POSITION IN THIS GAME FOR A LONG
TIME.
I WANT TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
EVERY SECOND OF THIS GAME AND
PLAY AS HARD AS POSSIBLE, AN
THATS WHY I TAKE A RISK AND GO
FOR THESE IDOLS.
AND I PLAY HARD.
THATS WHY IM TRYING TO WIN
THIS GAME MORE THAN ANYTHING,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU HAVE CHANCE AT
$1 MILLION AND THERES TEN
PEOPLE LEFT AND IM ONE OF THEM.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, ALEC.
ILL TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY BACK UP FOR
GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO BALANCE ON A VERY
NARROW PERCH WHILE HOLDING A
HANDLE BEHIND YOUR HEAD.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU LET GO OF
THE HANDLE OR FALL OFF THE
PERCH, YOURE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
NINE SHOT AT GETTING TO THE END.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE FOURTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
OKAY.
SO ITS DAY 27.
IF YOU FEEL SECURE ENOUGH THAT
YOU DONT NEED IMMUNITY AT
TONIGHTS TRIBAL COUNCIL, YOU
CAN OPT TO SIT OUT OF TODAYS
CHALLENGE, GIVE UP YOUR SHOT AT
IMMUNITY AND INSTEAD FEAST.
ON NACHOS.
OH, MY GOD.
NACHOS.
AND BEER.
Jeff: GIANT PLATTER, GUAC,
JALAPENO, PLUS MARGUERITES AND
ICE-COLD BEER.
BEER.
Jeff: BIG DECISION ON DAY
27.
ILL GIVE YOU A MOMENT TO MAKE
YOUR DECISION AND WELL GET
STARTED.
OKAY.
EVERYBODYS MADE THEIR DECISION.
ANGELINA, CARL, AN NICK HAVE
OPTED TO NOT COMPETE, GIVE UP
THEIR SHOT AT IMMUNITY SO THEY
CAN FEAST ON NACHOS.
YOU GUYS START EATING.
YOU CAN EAT UNTIL THIS CHALLENGE
ENDS.
NICK, IM POURING YOU A BEER.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: EVERYBODY IS IN
POSITION, AND THIS CHALLENGE IS
ON.
VERY SIMPLE CHALLENGE.
YOUR FEET ARE ON A VERY NARROW
PERCH.
YOUR HANDS ARE HOLDING ON TO
HANDLE.
IF EITHER ONE OF YOUR FEET COME
OFF OF THAT PERCH OR YOUR HANDS
COME OFF OF THAT HANDLE, YOURE
OUT.
THATS IT.
SEVEN PEOPLE COMPETING FOR
CERTAINTY TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHILE THREE PEOPLE DIG
IN TO ONE OF THE LARGEST
PLATTERS OF NACHOS EVER MADE.
[BURPING]
[LAUGHTER]
11 MINUTES INTO THIS CHALLENGE.
ANYBODY WANT TO ADMIT THEYRE
FEELING A LITTLE DISCOMFORTABLE?
YEAH, SURE.
E-MAIL -- IM WILLING.
Jeff: MIKES FEET REALLY
SHAKING.
MIKE DROPS.
HES FIRST OUT.
AN DAVIE LETS GO.
DAVIE DROPS.
AN WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
ALISON, CHRISTIAN, GABBY, KARA,
AND ALEC STILL FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY.
ALEC WIGGLING AROUND A LITTLE
BIT.
HE HAS TO WIN THIS.
Jeff: KARA NOT MOVING.
I THINK KARA CAN OUTLAST HIM.
ALEC DOESNT LIKE TO BE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE HEARD HIM DURING
THE RAINSTORM.
Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
PURE PAIN, TOLERANCE.
THIS HURTS EVERYWHERE.
IM MISERABLE.
Jeff: YOUVE BEEN UP THERE
ONE HOUR.
WAY TO GO, GUYS.
Jeff: YOU CANNOT LOSE
FOCUS.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS IS
THAT NECKLACE AROUND YOUR NECK.
ALEC TRYING THE REARRANGE THOSE
HANDS.
I THINK ALEC IS HURTING.
HES TRYING THE MASSAGE THOSE
FINGERS.
HES HURTING.
KARA IS SOLID.
SHE LOOKS SOLID.
DAMN.
BOMB.
Jeff: KARA JUST STEPS OFF,
AN WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
YOU HAVE TO BE FEELING IT
EVERYWHERE NOW.
THERE IS NO RELIEF OUT HERE IN
THIS FIELD, NO BREEZE, JUST
DONE, THE SUN POUNDING DOWN.
IF YOU NEEDED ANY EVIDENCE OF
HOW HOT IT IS, MIKE AND NICK
HAVE RETIRED UNDER THE BENCH FOR
SOME SHADE.
CAN I OPT OUT OF THE OPTING
OUT.
Jeff: IT IS DEAD HOT.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: ALISON REALLY
STRUGGLING NOW.
ALISON CANNOT HANG ON ANYMORE.
ALISON STEPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE, AN WE ARE DOWN TO
THREE.
YOURE A FIGHTER, BOBBY --
BABY GIRL.
YOURE A FIGHTER.
Jeff: HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
THIS IS GOING TO GO, ALEC?
UNTIL I WIN?
UNTIL HE WINS.
Jeff: ONE HOUR AND 35
MINUTES.
IM NOT LETTING GO.
Jeff: THE SEASON CONTINUES
TO BE A BATTLE.
I THINK WERE GOING TO BE OUT
HERE A LONG TIME.
THE MUNTZ CONTINUE TO TICK BY,
AND AT A SNAILS PACE.
THE CHANCES OF ANY ONE OF THE
THREE OF YOU BEING COMFORTABLE,
0.0.
LETS JUST END IT, JEFF.
YEAH.
YOURE REPORTING IN EXCESS OF
PRECISION THAT YOU DONT
ACTUALLY KNOW.
Jeff: TWO HOURS.
AWESOME JOB.
WOW.
Jeff: THIS IS WHERE YOU ARE
REALLY FINDING WHATS INSIDE YOU
IM GOING TO WIN THE
CHALLENGE.
OH, MY GOSH.
Jeff: GABBY HAS BEEN
STRUGGLING, CONTORTING HER BODY,
AND STILL NOT GIVING IN.
ITS SO HARD.
Jeff: GABBY, WHATS GOING
ON?
WHAT IS IT?
PAIN?
I JUST REALLY WANT TO... THIS
IS THE ONE THAT I CAN WIN, AND
ITS KILLING ME, BECAUSE I DONT
KNOW WHEN ITS GOING TO END.
Jeff: WHAT YOU DON KNOW IS
HOW CLOSE THEY ARE.
EXACTLY.
Jeff: DOES ALEC HAVE
ANOTHER HOUR OR IS HE DOWN TO A
MINUTE LEFT?
IM NOT GOING TO STEP OFF
UNTIL I WIN.
I WONT STEP OFF.
Jeff: GABBY, KEEP FIGHTING,
YOURE THERE.
YOURE A WARRIOR.
IM GOING TO WIN IT.
OH, MY GOSH.
BEAST MODE, GABBY, BEAST
MODE.
YOURE STRONG, GAB.
IM GOING TO STEP OFF.
GABBY, DONT LET GO.
OH, MY GOSH.
DAMN.
Jeff: GABBY FALLS OUT AND
TO THE GROUND.
OH, GABBY.
TWO HOURS AND 30 MINUTES INTO
THIS CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO A SHOWDOWN, DAVID
VERSUS GOLIATH.
CHRISTIAN VERSUS ALEC FOR
IMMUNITY.
DUDE, YOU ARE A BEAST, BY THE
WAY.
YOURE AMAZING.
YOURE NOT GOING TO WIN.
Jeff: WERE WAY PAST PAIN
THRESHOLD.
YOUR BODIES ARE NUMB NOW.
THREE HOURS.
[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: WE ARE DEEP ENOUGH
INTO THIS CHALLENGE NOW THAT
YOURE GOING TO START TO LOSE
FOCUS.
SO WHATEVER YOURE DOING TO STAY
MENTALLY CONNECTED, YOU BETTER
DO IT.
JEFF?
YES.
IS IT OKAY IF I TELL A STORY
TO PASS THE TIME?
SO I WAS WORKING ON A PROJECT
THAT WAS ABOUT PLANT ROOT
GROWTH.
STAY FOCUSED, CHRISTIAN.
THIS HELPS ME FOCUS, CARL,
THANK YOU.
GOT YOU, BABE.
SO ITS MY JOB TO QUICKLY
THROW TOGETHER A PLANT ROBOT.
SO IM TAKING A BUNCH OF
PARTS... BASICALLY I HAD TO TELL
PEOPLE... ITS ONE THING TO HAVE
A ROBOT... WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
EXEO SKELETON RESEARCH.
WHO IS UP FOR 20 QUESTIONS?
I START TO LOOK AT THIS AS A
DIFFERENT KIND OF OPPORTUNITY.
YOURE MY CAPTIVE AUDIENCE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT A REUBEN
SANDWICH IS, JEFF?
I NEVER GREW A BEARD IN MY LIFE.
JEFF, NOW YOU KNOW WHAT ITS
LIKE TO HEAR MY VOICE FOR HOURS.
TORTURE.
Jeff: BEEN UP THERE FOR
FIVE HOURS.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
OH, MY GOD.
I DONT FEEL GOOD.
WHAT ON EARTH?
THATS INCREDIBLE.
CHRISTIAN?
YOURE SAFE.
IM NOT.
I KNOW.
I KNOW HOW YOU MUST FEEL IN THIS
MOMENT, AND I HEAR YOU.
I JUST... I MIGHT NEVER GET THIS
OPPORTUNITY AGAIN.
IM SORRY.
Jeff: ALEC JUST DROPS OUT.
CHRISTIAN CANT BELIEVE IT.
CHRISTIAN HAS JUST WON
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY AFTER FIVE
AND A HALF EPIC HOURS.
NO IDEA WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
WHAT A STRANGE TURN OF EVENTS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
ALEC JUST STEPPED OFF.
Jeff: CONGRATULATION,
CHRISTIAN.
WELL EARNED.
WELL FOUGHT.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, GET OVER
HERE.
GOOD JOB, CHRISTIAN.
DAY 27, INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS
YOURS.
YOU ARE SAFE IN THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, YOU HAVE
TONIGHT AND TOMORROW TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IS GOING TO BE THE NEXT
PERSON VOTED OUT.
TOMORROW NIGHT, TRIBAL COUNCIL,
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE FOURTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
THE GOOD NEWS IS IT WONT BE
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
I WON IMMUNITY, AND IT HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH ALSO UMS.
IT WAS JUST I WANTED IT MORE
THAN ALEC.
ALEC IS SUCH AN OBVIOUS TRAR GET
FOR THIS VOTE BECAUSE HES SUCH
A STRONG IMMUNITY THREAT, BUT
WHEN YOURE SITTING AROUND FOR A
FULL DAY, THATS A LOT OF TIME
FOR PLANS TO CHANGE.
THE IMMUNITY IDOL -- IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE YESTERDAY WAS NOSE
FRUSTRATING THING.
I STEPPED UP ON THAT PERCH AND I
SAID IM NOT LETTING GO UNTIL I
WIN.
MENTALLY I COULDNT HANDLE IT.
PEOPLE SEE ME AS A PHYSICAL
THREAT.
ME STANDING ON THE PERCH FOR SIX
HOURS SEALED MY OWN FATE.
I SHOULDNT HAVE LET GO.
YOU BODY COULDNT GO ANYMORE,
AT LEAST MEDICALLY.
I AM THE ONLY ONE THAT PEOPLE
ARE TALKING ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
IT SUCKS.
I DIDNT COME OUT HERE TO BE
LIKE SOME UNANIMOUS VOTE.
I DIDNT COME OUT HERE TO HAVE
PEOPLE JUST SAY, HIM.
NO, IM NOT GOING TO GIVE UP.
ALEC IS WHO WERE GOING
AFTER, 100%.
100%.
HES A BEAST.
YOU KNOW, IM NOT OF COURSING
TO SUGAR COAT THINGS.
THE NEXT VOTE IS ALEC.
IT SHOULD NOT BE NO TURNS, NO
DETOURS, ALL GO TO TRIBAL, WRITE
DOWN ALECS NAME.
LET JEFF READ THE VOTE.
WE CAN ALL COME BACK TO THE
BEACH AND RELAX.
HES A BEAST, WE DONT GET HIM
OUT, WE DONT STAND A CHANCE.
WHAT DID YOU TALK ABOUT FOR
SO LONG?
ARE YOU GOING TO TRUST THIS
BRAND-NEW GIRL?
CARL HAS SHOWN HIMSELF TO BE A
CONTROLLING PLAYER.
I CALL HIM THE GODFATHER BECAUSE
I FEEL LIKE WITHIN THE DAVIDS HE
LIKES TO CALL THE SHOTS.
THIS VOTE SHOULD BE VERY,
VERY SIMPLE.
WHATS HAPPENING?
HES DISCUSSING THE VOTE.
WHATS HE DISCUSSING?
WERE GOING TO VOTE FOR ALEC.
OKAY.
ONE OF US GOT TO GO HOME, WE
SHOULD BE THANKFUL IT AINT NONE
OF US.
SO THATS IT.
YEAH.
ITS LIKE DONT TELL KARA,
WHO IS AN ALLY OF THE PERSON
WHOSE NAME YOURE THROWING OUT.
THATS INFURIATING.
DO YOU NOT KNOW WHAT GAME WERE
PLAYING.
WERE IN "SURVIVOR."
I DIDNT THINK WE WERE TELLING
KARA.
I FELT SO STUPID WALKING UP ON
THAT.
THE ONLY SMART THING IS TO
USE THEM.
DUDE, IM CURIOUS WHY KARA
HAD TO KNOW.
ITS BEEN DISCUSSED ALREADY.
THAT MAKES ME FEEL EVEN
STUPIDER BECAUSE THATS FIRST
TIME IVE HEARD OF IT.
YOURE TOO EMOTIONAL AND TOO
PARANOID.
IM NOT BEING PARANOID TO
WALK UP ON A CONVERSATION.
SHE DIDNT FEEL LIKE SHE KNEW
WHAT SHE WAS WALKING INTO IN
THAT CONVERSATION, AND SO AS A
RESULT SHES LIKE, THE THINGS
THAT SHE THOUGHT --
CHRISTIAN, YOU WERE IN THE
CONVERSATION.
GABBY IS ONE OF MY CLOSEST
ALLIES.
SO MUCH OF MY JOB IS MAKING SURE
THAT GABBY IS HAPPY, BUT RIGHT
NOW SHES QUITE UPSET.
I REALLY CANT WORK WITH HIM.
GABBY...
HE JUST FREAKIN BOSSES ME
AROUND.
HES ALLOWED TO GO TALK TO OTHER
PEOPLE BUT IM NOT?
IT PISSES ME OFF.
I FIND CARL TO BE COMING
INCREASINGLY PROBLEMATIC.
HES BOTH AN ALLIANCE LIABILITY
AND PERHAPS A PERSONAL LIABILITY
BECAUSE CARL AND GABBY ARE ON A
COLLISION COURSE.
ITS JUST HARD KNOWING ITS YOU,
BUT IF THERE IS ONE THING I
REALIZE, WHEN EVERYONE WANTS YOU
OUT, ITS NEVER THAT EASY.
YEAH.
I THINK THERE ARE BIGGER
THREATS THAT ARE USING MY
PHYSICALITY AS LIKE A SCREEN FOR
THEM.
YEAH.
WHO IS IN CHARGE OF ALL THE
DAVIDS?
CARL.
CARL WAS THE ONE WHO CAME
BACK TO CAMP AND SAID, IT NEEDS
TO BE ALEC.
CARL IS THE ONE WHO CAME UP WITH
THE PLAN TO VOTE ME OUT.
CARL WAS THE ONEHWHO GOT DAN OUT
WITH THE IDOL NULLIFIER.
I THINK HES RIGHT NOW BLINDED
BY POWER.
WHEN YOU GET COCKY, YOURE GOING
TO GET BLINDSIDED.
I THINK SOMEONE LIKE CARL, HE
WOULDNT BE EXPECTING IT.
IM JUST SAYING, HE WOULD
NEVER EXPECT IT.
PEOPLE AT THIS POINT KNOW IM
GOING HOME.
WE NEED TWO VOTES, CHRISTIAN AND
GABBY.
IM IN.
IF I DONT PULL SOMETHING OUT
OF THE HAT, IM GOING HOME.
SO IM GOING TO DO WHAT I NEED
TO DO TO KEEP MY BUTT IN THIS
GAME.
WE SHOULD VOTE OUT CARL.
WHY CANT WE?
HES THE REAL THREAT.
BUT WHY CANT WE?
I TOLL KARA, ALISON AND MIKE,
IF WE CAN TAKE OUT CARL, WOULD
YOU BE ON BOARD, AND THEY ALL
LOOKED AT ME AND SAID, 1,000%.
WE WOULD LOVE TO SEE A BIG
THREAT LIKE HIM GO OUT.
CARL IS A DIFFICULT ALLIANCE
MEMBER TO WORK WORK SO ID BE
LYING IF I SAID I DIDNT THINK
ABOUT THAT.
THE THING I WORRY ABOUT IS THAT
IF YOURE GONE, ITS GOING TO BE
A TOUGH ROAD FOR ME INCH A
SELFISH WAY, HAVING YOU AND ME
AROUND IS WAY SORT OF DIFFUSING
THE TARGET.
TO GET RID OF ALEC NOW TAKES
ONE MORE THREAT OFF THE BOARD,
BUT IVE ALWAYS BELIEVED THAT IN
ORDER FOR ME TO SURVIVE, I HAVE
TO KEEP THREATS AROUND OR ELSE I
WILL BE THE ONLY THREAT
REMAINING.
AS OF TODAY, IT SEEMS LIKE HE
HAS THE POWER TO CHOOSE WHICH
ALLIANCE WE GO WITH.
ITS A CRITICAL TIME TO DO
IT.
AT THIS POINT OF THE GAME TRIBAL
ALLIANCES ARE FINALLY BLURRED TO
THE POINT WHERE ITS LIKE TWO
LIQUIDS THAT JUST MIX.
AN YOU HAVE TO START FIGURING
OUT WHATS BEST FOR YOUR OWN
GAME GOING FORWARD.
ITS YOU AND ME.
WERE IN THIS BECAUSE WE HAVE TO
DO IT TOGETHER.
AND WE HAVE TO PENDULUM SWING
TOGETHER AND IT WILL BE
STRESSFUL AS HELL.
THIS IS MAKE-OR-BREAK POINT
IN MY RELATIONSHIP WITH ALEC FOR
SURE.
EITHER IWILL BE VOTING WITH HIM
OR SENDING HIM HOME.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT TO GET VERY
DYNAMIC VERY QUICKLY.
Jeff: WE NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH, JOHN, AND DAN VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS START WITH THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
ITS BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE WE
HAVE HAD A CHALLENGE GO NEARLY
SIX HOURS.
CHRISTIAN, ON YOUR WAY TO
ULTIMATELY WINNING, YOU WERE
VERY OPEN AND VULNERABLE IN
SAYING, I COULD ACTUALLY MAYBE
WIN THIS ONE, SO IM JUST NOT
GOING TO EVERY GIVE UP.
WELK BACK HOME I
SELF-SACRIFICE ENDLESSLY TO
PLEASE PEOPLE.
I HAD TO REMIND MYSELF THAT IM
IN A GAME THAT ILL PROBABLY
ONLY GET ONE CHANCE TO PLAY, SO
WHEN IM IN THAT DLEM MARKEY
LOOK BACK AT THE TIME I WAS
TALKING TO JEFF FOR FIVE AND A
HALF HOURS AND HE WAS MY CAPTIVE
AUDIENCE, I CAN REMEMBER THAT
MEMORY.
Jeff: I WAS CAPTIVE.
YOU WERE CAPTIVE, YEAH, YOU
WERE CAPTIVE.
CAPTIVATED.
Jeff: I COULDNT GO
ANYWHERE.
AND ALEC, YOU WERE TOE TO TOE
WITH CHRISTIAN.
CHRISTIAN TALKED THE ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
YOU BARELY SAID A WORD.
WHEN DID IT START TO KICK IN
THAT YOU WERE ACTUALLY HURTING.
I TOLD YOU ALL FROM THE
BEGINNING IM NOT STEPPING OFF
UNTIL I WIN BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
IM AT A REALLY VULNERABLE PLACE
IN THIS GAME.
THAT WAS MY MENTALITY GOING INTO
IT.
NEXT THING I KNOW, HOUR FIVE,
AND I REMEMBER JUST TRYING TO
FOCUS ON SOMETHING AND CLOSING
ONE EYE AND SHAKING MY HEAD.
AN I REMEMBER BEING REALLY
DIZZY.
Jeff: NICK, ONE OF THE
OTHER ELEMENTS WAS YOU HAD
CHANCE TO SIT OUT AND NOT
COMPETE FOR IMMUNITY AND HAVE
NACHOSSEN STEAD, WHICH YOU TOOK
PART IN ALONG WITH CARL AND
ANGELINA.
WAS THERE ANY IMPACT?
NO, THERE WASNT AT ALL.
IF ANYTHING THERE WAS OTHER
PEOPLE SAYING, MAN IF, I HAD
KNOWN THAT WAS SIX HOURS, I
WOULD HAVE SAT OUT AND HAD SOME
NACHOS TOO.
SO THE DECISION WE MADE LOOKED
BRILLIANT.
I THINK IT SAYS SOMEONES
ABOUT SOMEONES CHARACTER IF
THEYRE GOING TO OPT OUT.
JEFF, HES EATEN THREE
REWARDS.
I HAVENT EATING ANYTHING BUT A
SCOOP OF RICE HERE OR.
THERE THAT WAS THE ONLY
OPPORTUNITY I HAD TO GET SOME
FOOD, SO ALL I CAN DO IS HOPE MY
TIMING WAS RIGHT THAT I CHOSE TO
SIT OUT AND GIVE MYSELF SOME
NOURISHMENT, HAVE THE STRENGTH
PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY TO
CONTINUE ON WITH MY ALLIANCE AND
ILL ROLL WITH IT.
IM CALLING A SPADE A SPADE.
YOU WERE CONFIDENT ENOUGH TO EAT
NACHOS.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
IM SORRY, JEFF.
"SURVIVOR" IN EVERY WAY IS ABOUT
CALCULATED RISKS.
YOU KNOW, EAT A NACHO IS A
CALCULATED RISK.
TO NOT EAT THE NACHOS IS A
ALSO WHAT THAT RISK REVEALS
ABOUT YOUR CALCULATION.
I THINK THATS WHAT WERE
TALKING ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF, THE
CONCEPT OF CALCULATED DECISIONS
IS REALLY SALIENT RIGHT NOW.
EVERYTHING IS DONE WITH
INTENTION, YOU KNOW, SHOULD I
GET THIS FOOD, AND AM I FEELING
IN A GOOD PLACE WITH THE PEOPLE
THAT SAY THAT THEY TRUST ME AND
WHO I SAY I TRUST?
THAT WAS SOMETHING PART OF MY
CALCULATION, AS WELL.
Jeff: ALISON, BUY THAT IN
I DONT BUY A LOT OF WHAT
ANGELINA IS SELLING ANYMORE.
TO BE HONEST, JEFF, ITS
HYPOCRITICAL FOR ALSTON SAY THAT
WHEN THE THREE PEOPLE WHO WERE
CHIMING IN, THESE THREE GOLIATH,
THEY MADE A VERY CALCULATED
DECISION LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
Jeff: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHATS THE DECISION THEY MADE?
YES, ILL GET THERE.
Jeff: MIKE COVERING HIS
FACE.
NO, NO, NO, SO ITS OKAY,
MIKE.
IM GOING TO BE DELICATE ABOUT
IT.
BUT ID RATHER MUCH TALK ABOUT
HOW THE TRIBAL ALLIANCE HAS
FALLEN AND THERES NEW ALLIANCES
AND NEW RELATIONSHIPS THAN TALK
ABOUT A DECISION TO EAT NACHOS
BECAUSE I THINK THERES SO MUCH
MORE THAN THAT, JEFF.
Jeff: SO IS THIS MOMENT
THAT ANGELINA TALKING ABOUT THAT
GOES BACK TO LAST TRIBAL, IS IT
STILL RELEVANT RIGHT NOW?
I DEFINITELY THINK WEVE
CROSSED TRIBAL ALLIANCES NO
QUESTION THERE.
NEW ALLIANCES HAVE BEEN FORMED.
BUT I DONT THINK THEYVE TRULY
BEEN TESTED YET.
Jeff: AND THATS THE TRICK
IN "SURVIVOR" IS LIKE, ARE WE
GOING TO JUST TALK ABOUT IT OR
ARE WE GOING TO DO IT?
Jeff: ALISON, REALLY, THE
NUMBERS ARE SMALL ENOUGH NOW
THAT YOU BETTER BE PLAYING YOUR
OWN GAME.
RIGHT.
WE KEEP CIRCLING AROUND THESE
TRIBAL LINES ARE BLURRED, BUT
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO THE VOTES,
IT DOESNT SEEM LIKE THE
BLURRING IS HAPPENING.
ITS INTERESTING HOW EVERYONE
SORT OF KNOWS THE MOST LIKELY
PERSON GOING HOME TONIGHT IS THE
PERSON WHO IS ON THE BEAM FOR
FIVE AND A HALF HOURS.
Jeff: ALEC?
ALEC.
WE ALL KNOW ITS SOCIAL
POLITICS, ITS STRATEGY, ITS
NOT PHYSICAL.
CHRISTIAN STOOD ON THE BEACH AND
BEAT ME.
NUMBER TWO, MAYBE THESE PEOPLE
THROWING MY NAME ARE USING ME
BECAUSE IM AN EASY VOTE RIGHT.
NOW ONCE IM GONE, WHO ARE THE
EASY VOTES.
THE THREATS ARE GONE.
I BELIEVE IF IM A THREAT, KEEP
ME AROUND.
MAYBE IM A SHIELD FOR SOMEONE.
Jeff: ITS ALWAYS
INTERESTING WHAT ONE PERSON SEES
AS A REASON TO GET RID OF
SOMEONE IS WHAT ANOTHER PERSON
MIGHT SEE AS A REASON TO KEEP
SOMEBODY.
THATS FUNDAMENTAL TO HOW THE
GAME WORKS AND WHY THERES THIS
DICHOTOMY WHERE EVERY STRENGTH
CAN BECOME A WEAKNESS.
Jeff: CARL, THATS WHERE
ITS INTERESTING TO CIRCLE BACK
TO THE BEGINNING THAT YOU,
ANGELINA, AND NEW ENGLAND SAT
OUT OF THE CHALLENGE, BECAUSE IN
THESE LAST 24 HOURS, THE GAME
HAS SHIFTED, THAT COULD HAVE
BEEN A MILLION DOLLAR PLATTER OF
NACHOS YOU FEASTED ON.
IF IT WAS WRONG AND I GET
CANNED, BUT ITS SOMETHING I
HAVE TO DEAL WITH.
BUT I FEEL IVE MADE THE RIGHT
CAN CONNECTIONS AT THIS
PARTICULAR TIME OF THE GAME TO
SAY THE DECISION I MADE THE EAT
NACHOS WAS A GOOD DECISION FOR
ME AT THAT TIME.
Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
MIKE, YOURE UP.
IM PUTTING MY TRUST IN MY
ALLIANCE.
HOPEFULLY THEY PUT TRUST IN ME.
IM DOING THIS FOR THE
BENEFIT OF MY GAME AND NO ONE
ELSES.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE ALEC.
CARL.
ALEC.
TWO VOTES ALEC.
ONE VOTE CARL.
ALEC.
THREE VOTES ALEC.
ONE VOTE CARL.
ALEC.
THATS FOUR VOTE ALEC.
THATS FIVE VOTES ALEC.
ONE VOTE CARL.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ALEC. THATS SIX.
THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
ITS BEEN REAL.
NO WORRIES.
LOVE YOU.
YOURE A STUD.
THATS IT, BROTHER.
Jeff: ALEC, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
GOOD LUCK, ALEC.
BYE, ALEC.
Jeff: WELL, THE LINES ARE
CLEARLY BLURRED AND THIS GAME IS
WIDE OPEN.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
OF YOU, MAN, BUT IM GLAD YOU
WERE ABLE TO REALIZE, THAT
PHYSICAL THREAT STUFF IS REAL,
MAN.
HES A BEAST.
WATCHING ALEC WATCH OUT WITH HIS
TORCH SNUFFED, MAN, THAT JUST
MADE MY WHOLE TIME OUT HERE,
BECAUSE I KNOW THERES FIVE
DAVIDS AND FOUR GOLIATHS.
WE OVERTOOK THE POWER AND
THEY DONT EVEN REALIZED IT.
THATS THE BEAUTY OF IT.
ONE AT A TIME.
THE DAVIDS HAVE SWUNG THE
GAME COMPLETELY IN OUR FAVOR.
AND WE HAVE ALL THE POWER IN THE
WORLD NOW.
I JUST WANTED TO FIGHT
HARDER.
WHY AM I FIGHTING HARDER?
IVE BEEN TRAINED TO SEE THIS
THING FROM YOUR PERSPECTIVE AS
WELL AS MY OWN.
YEAH.
IM EXCITED.
YES, YES.
I WANTED TO FIGHT FOR ALEC,
AND I DID, BUT AT SOME POINT I
REALIZED THAT JUST LIKE IN THE
HOSPITAL, I CANT SAVE EVERY
LIFE.
THERES A POINT IN TIME WHERE
SOMEONE IS IN TOO CRITICAL A
CONDITION.
I THINK THAT WITH HIM OUT OF THE
PICTURE, E-MAIL PROBABLY NEXT
BIGGEST PHYSICAL THREAT THERE
IS.
SO THEYRE PROBABLY GOING TO
TARGET ME, AND I TAKE BLAME FOR
THAT.
THANK YOU FOR COMFORTING ME.
ITS HARD.
I KNOW.
IVE BEEN TALKING WITH THESE
DAVIDS ABOUT MAKING A MOVE, AND
I DIDNT DO IT.
NOW LOOK AT WHERE I AM.
NOW IM JUST PRAYING THAT
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY WILL WANT TO
WORK TOGETHER OR DID I MISS MY
OPPORTUNITY?
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAYS
REWARD CHALLENGE?
YEAH, LETS GO, BABY.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE YOURE
GOING TO BE DIVIDED INTO TWO
TEAMS OF FOUR.
ON MY GO YOULL SWIM OUT THE A
TALL LADDER, CLIMB IT, AND LEAP
OFF.
YOULL THEN DRIVE DOWN TO
RELEASE TWO LINES OF BUOYS WITH
AN ATTEMPT TO LAND THOSE BUOYS
IN A SERIES OF TARGETS.
FIRST TEAM TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR?
THE WINNING FOUR WILL BOARD THE
"SURVIVOR" SPEEDBOAT FOR A FUN
AFTERNOON CRUISING THROUGH THE
FIJIAN ISLANDS.
FRIED CHICKEN, POTATO SALAD,
CORN ON THE COB, ICE-COLD
BEVERAGES AND CHEESECAKE FOR
DESSERT.
WERE GOING TO DO A SCHOOLYARD
PICK THERE IS ONE EXTRA PERSON.
THAT MEANS SOMEBODY WILL NOT BE
CHOSEN THAT.
PERSON WILL NOT PARTICIPATE AND
HAVE NO SHOT AT REWARD.
WELL DRAW FOR CAPTAINS.
WELL GET STARTED.
WOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
KARA WAS A CAPTAIN.
SHE PICKED CARL, DAVIE, AND
MIKE.
ANGELINA WAS A CAPTAIN.
SHE PICKED NICK, GABBY, AND
ALISON.
NOBODY CHOSE CHRISTIAN.
CHRISTIAN HAS TO SIT OUT.
NO SHOT AT REWARD.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO GET TO THE
LADDER.
THAN YOU WILL GO UP THE LADDER
ONE AT A TIME AND LEAP OFF.
YOURE GOOD.
MIKES GOING TO GO UP FIRST.
GO, PURPLE.
GREAT BRITAIN YESS GOING TO GO
UP FIRST FOR PURPLE.
MIKE CLIMBING THE TALL LADDER.
LEAPS.
CARL HEADING UP NOW.
HERES GABBY FOR PURPLE SLOWING
DOWN.
GO.
CARL GETTING TO THE TOP.
HES GOING TO JUMP.
ALISON TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME
TIME.
GO, ALISON.
DAVIE NOW SCAMPERING UP THAT
LADDER.
HERE COMES ANGELINA.
KARA UP QUICKLY.
THERE GOES NICK.
NICK WITH A BIG LEAP.
ORANGE, YOURE GOOD TO DIVE
DOWN.
NICK GOT TO GET TO THE RING.
PURPLE IS GOOD NOW.
YOU ARE NOW TRYING TO PULL TWO
LINES OF BUOYS TO RELEASE THEM.
GO.
Jeff: NICK GOING TO HEAD
DOWN FOR PURPLE.
ITS GOING TO BE KARA NOW FOR
ORANGE GIVING IT A GO.
KARA HAS THE FIRST BUOY FOR
ORANGE.
SHES GOING BACK DOWN.
NICE JOB BY CARA.
PURPLE STILL WORKING ON THEIR
FIRST SET OF BUOYS.
ANGELINA GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
THATS WHAT IT TAKES.
ANGELINA RELEASES THE FIRST
LINE.
THATS IT.
NO DAVIE DOES IT FOR ORANGE.
THEY HAVE BOTH SETS OF BUOYS.
START SWIMMING THEM IN.
ONE MORE PUSH.
Jeff: ITS ALISON GOING
DOWN TO FINISH THE JOB FOR
PURPLE.
CAN SHE DO IT?
YES, SHES GOT IT.
START SWIMMING THEM IN.
YOURE LOOKING FOR THE FIVE
MARKED BUOYS.
ORANGE IS GOOD.
YOU CAN START SHOOTING.
ITS GOING TO BE DAVIE.
DAVIE JUST MISSES.
NOW YOU GOT TO SWIM THAT BUOY
BACK BEFORE ANYBODY ELSE CAN GO.
HERE COMES PURPLE TRYING TO STAY
IN THIS.
HERE GOES MIKE FOR ORANGE.
STILL TRYING TO SCORE THAT FIRST
BASKET.
OH, IN AND OUT.
MIKE JUST MISSES.
ALISON IS UP.
HERE COMES ANGELINA.
YOURE GOOD.
START UNTYING.
YOURE LOOKING FOR FIVE MARKED
BUOYS.
THATS IT.
CARL GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
CAN HE SCORE THAT FIRST POINT?
NO.
PURPLE IS GOOD.
YOU CAN START SHOOTING.
ITS GOING TO BE NICK.
NICK SCORES FIRST SHOT.
IT IS NOW PURPLE IN THE LEAD.
HERE GOES DAVIE TRYING TO TIE IT
UP.
DAVIE, WHOA.
DAVIE SCORES FOR ORANGE WITH
AUTHORITY.
HERE GOES ALISON.
NO, HERE GOES CARL FOR ORANGE.
HES BEEN CLOSE.
THIS TIME HE GETS IT DONE.
ORANGE BACK IN THE LEAD NOW.
HERE GOES NICK, NOT MESSING
AROUND.
NICK SCORES.
WERE TIED AGAIN.
2-2.
IT IS BECOME -- BACK AND FORTH.
HERE GOES DAVIE.
IT IS NOW ORANGE IN THE LEAD,
3-2.
YOU HAVE FIVE BUOYS TOTAL.
ANGELINA JUST MISSES.
CARL COULD EXTEND THE LEAD RIGHT
HERE.
AND HE DOES.
ORANGE HAS FOUR.
THEY ARE DOWN TO THEIR LAST ONE.
IT WOULD BE CARLS FIRST REWARD
EARNED IN THIS GAME, AND HES A
PART OF HELPING THEM WIN IT.
HERE GOES DAVIE FOR THE WIN
RIGHT HERE.
AND HES GOT IT.
ORANGE WINS REWARD.
DAVIE, MIKE, KARA, AND CARL
WITHIN REWARD.
THE DROUGHT IS OVER FOR CARL,
AND IT CONTINUES FOR ANGELINA.
STILL HAS NOT WON A REWARD IN
THIS GAME.
MIKE, KARA, CARL, DAVIE, FUN
AFTERNOON.
FRIED CHICKEN, COLD BEVERAGES,
INCLUDING BEER.
BRING IN THE BOAT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
HEAD OUT.
ENJOY YOUR AFTERNOON.
ALL RIGHT.
NICK, ALISON, GABBY, ANGELINA,
CHRISTIAN, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
HAVE A FUN AFTERNOON BACK AT
CAMP WITH A LITTLE BIT OF RICE.
WINNING THIS REWARD WAS SO
CRUCIAL BECAUSE I REALLY DO
THINK THAT THE DAVIDS VERY WELL
COULD FROM HERE ON OUT JUST PICK
OFF THE GOLIATHS ONE BY ONE.
SO ITS A GREAT TIME TO
RECONNECT WITH CARL AND DAVIE,
WHO I CAME BACK FROM VUKU FROM,
AND IF WE COULD GET EVEN CLOSER,
NO MATTER WHAT, IT WOULD TAKE ME
FURTHER IN THE GAME
PUT THIS BOAT IN GEAR AND
LETS GET IT.
LETS GO, BABY.
WINNERS!
I LOVE IT.
I LOVE EVERY BIT OF IT.
THE BEERS ON THE BOAT GO
ROUND AND ROUND, ROUND AND
ROUND.
CARL, YOU NEED A BEER?
[BURPING]
DAMN.
WINNING REWARD WITH CARL,
DAVIE, AND KARA WAS A TRIUMPH,
BECAUSE CARL AND DAVIE ARE KIND
OF IN POWER NOW.
IM TRULY A FREE AGENT, AND I
FEEL LIKE I CAN USE THEM TO MY
ADVANTAGE, SO IT WAS A GOOD TIME
TO KIND OF SUCK UP TO THE KING,
AND KARA AND I DID A LOT OF
SUCKING UP.
THIS IS MY FIRST REWARD, MAN.
I KNEW THAT YOU NEED IT.
I COULD LITERALLY CRY RIGHT
NOW AT THIS MOMENT.
THIS IS CARLS FIRST REWARD.
HES STOKED.
ITS APPARENT THAT HE LOVES BEER
AND HES JUST NOT WORRIED ABOUT
A THING.
SO WE GOOD.
WE GOOD, MAN.
I NEED YOU TO TRUST ME.
ALISON HAS TO GO NEXT.
THE ONLY PERSON WHO IS GOING TO
BE HURT BY THAT IS GABBY.
NO ONE ELSE.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS, SO NOT A
PROBLEM.
I DONT KNOW IF IT WAS A SLIP
UP, BUT HES COMFORTABLE WITH ME
AND HE DECIDES HE WANTS TO GET
ALISON OUT, WHICH IS
UNBELIEVABLE THAT YOU REALLY
THINK THAT IM GOING TO BE FINE
WITH YET ANOTHER GOLIATH, YET
ANOTHER PERSON ON MY ALLIANCE TO
GO HOME.
IM JUST GOING TO PRETEND LIKE
WERE GOING TO WORK TOGETHER
MOVING FORWARD AND IM VERY GLAD
THAT I HAVE MIKE HERE WITH ME.
DAVIES DRUNK.
ADVANTAGE QUICKSAND.
CARL WITH HIS BEER IN HIS
HAND.
I SEE FOOD.
WE GOT BISCUITS, POTATO
SALAD.
OH, MY GOD.
THATS ICED TEA WITH LEMONS
IN IT.
AND PLATES AND ACTUAL FORKS.
THANK YOU, GOD.
THIS IS THE BEST REWARD, NOT
ONLY GETTING TO EAT, BUT BECAUSE
I WAS ABLE TO PROVE TO MYSELF
THAT I AM AN ATHLETE, MAN.
I CONTINUOUSLY BY MY HOMEBOYS
GET MY BLACK CARD TAKEN AWAY
FROM ME.
YOU ALL KNOW WHAT A BLACK CARD
IS?
THATS WHEN THEY TRY TO TELL YOU
YOURE NOT BLACK.
YOUVE GOT TO BE ABLE TO PLAY
SPORTS.
YOU GOT TO WATCH SPORTS, AND I
NEVER BEEN ABLE TO DO NONE OF
THAT, AT LEAST IN MY MIND, BUT
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW...
YOU NAILED IT.
YOURE SHAQUILLE ONEAL.
FINGER ROLL.
THEYRE NOT TAKING MY BLACK
CARD NO MORE.
THE FACT THAT I WAS ABLE TO DUNK
ON FIRST ONE, IT WAS LIKE, COME
ON, MAN, YOU GOT THIS STUFF IN
YOU, DUDE.
IT WONT BE A PIECE OF
CHICKEN LEFT ON THAT PLATE.
I CAN PROMISE YOU.
IM HAPPY.
IM SO HAPPY THAT ITS US
FOUR.
BECAUSE THERES SOME PEOPLE AT
THAT BEACH THAT ARE SHADY,
SHADY, SHADY.
JUST KNOW IF YOU NEED TO GET
ALISON OUT OR SOMETHING, WERE
HERE TO HELP.
WERE HERE TO HELP.
EXACTLY.
ITS JUST MATTER OF TIME.
WERE DOING IT.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
LOVE YOU, TOO.
CARLS ERROR IN THIS GAME AT
THIS POINT IS THIS CONFIDENCE
THAT HE CAN SAY WHOEVER HE WANTS
TO AND THAT EVERYONE WILL GO
ALONG WITH IT.
ITS REALLY SOLIDIFIED THE FACT
THAT IM JUST A PAWN IN CARLS
GRAND SCHEME, AND I DIDNT COME
HERE TO PLAY A PAWN.
HE IS JUST GETTING DRUNK ON THIS
REWARD.
HES LIKE DRUNK OFF POWER IN
THIS GAME.
HIS CONFIDENCE IS BLOWING OUT OF
HIS BEER BOTTLE.
AND IT WAS GREAT FOR MY GAME,
BECAUSE NOW I KNOW WHERE HIS
HEAD IS AT.
YOU REALLY THINK ITS FIVE?
I REALLY DONT KNOW, GABBY.
IM NOT SOLD ON THE FIVE.
I THINK IT WOULD BE FOOLISH.
CARL IS PERCEIVED AS CALLING ALL
THE SHOTS.
SO THERE -- THEYRE GOING TO
PERCEIVE IT THAT WE WENT ALONG
AS THE GODFATHER.
AS LONG AS HE IS PERCEIVED AS
CALLING ALL THE SHOTS, WE WONT
GET CREDIT.
WE HAVE TO REMOVE THE GOD FARE
SO PEOPLE KNOW WE HAVE AGENCY IN
THIS GAME.
I THINK ITS TIME TO MAKE A
MOVE, AND IM READY.
MY JOB AS A TECHNICAL WRITER IS
TO LOOK AT A WHOLE BUNCH OF
INFORMATION, SYNTHESIZE IT AND
FIGURE OUT WHAT IS ACTUALLY
NEEDED.
AND THATS WHAT IVE BEEN DOING
WITH CARL.
IVE BEEN GEARING INFORMATION,
HOW HE TREATS ME, HOW HE TREATS
OTHERS, HOW HE ACTS IN THE
ALLIANCE, AND IM NOT GOING TO
JUST SIT ON THAT INFORMATION.
IM GOING TO ACT ON IT.
THIS IS WHAT IM HOPING HAPPENS
IN FULL CANDOR, BECAUSE HONESTLY
AT THIS POINT I SEE YOU AND
CHRISTIAN AS MY CLOSEST ALLY.
I WANT IT TO BE A BLINDSIDE OR
CARL, BECAUSE IM TELLING YOU,
CARL, NICK, AND DAVIE THINK ITS
DAVID STRONG.
SO I HOPE THAT ME AND CHRISTIAN
CAN WALK IT DOWN, GET MIKE AND
WE FREAKIN DO IT, BECAUSE NOT
ONE EXTRA PERSON CAN KNOW.
IT IS MUSIC TO MY EARS THAT
GABBY WANTS TO VOTE TOGETHER AND
TAKE OUT A THREAT IN THIS GAME.
WEVE BEEN DOING THIS SONG AND
DANCE FOR FIVE TRIBAL COUNCILS
NOW, BUT THE TIMING FEELS RIGHT.
THE CLOUDS ARE PARTING.
THE SUN IS SHINING.
THERE IS AN HALLELUJAH CHORUS.
WE ARE GOING TO DO THIS.
HEY THERE.
WELCOME BACK.
WAS IT GOOD?
THE REWARD WAS AWESOME.
I MEAN, I ENJOYED EVERY BIT OF
IT.
AND I FEEL AS THOUGH MY GAME IS
IN GREAT SHAPE.
AND I HAD BEER.
CHICKEN AND BEER.
WE FOUGHT HARD TO GET THE
NUMBERS, WE DONT PLAN ON GIVING
IT BACK.
WE CAN PICK THEM APART ONE AT A
TIME LIKE THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO
DO TO US.
SO WE DONT HAVE TO DO A WHOLE
LOT OF SCRAMBLING.
IM READY TO GET ALISON ASS OUT
OF HERE.
SHES THE BIGGEST THREAT THATS
LEFT.
ALISON.
WERE NOT GOING TO WALK AROUND
HERE SCRAMBLING.
THAT WERE NOT GOING TO DO.
THE ONLY BACKLASH WERE GOING TO
GET FROM THAT --
CHRISTIAN SEEMS REALLY SOLID.
US FOUR AND CHRISTIAN FIVE,
THATS ROCK SOLID.
I THINK ITS GOING TO BE
GABY.
ITS GOING TO BE YOU.
ESSENTIALLY I HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO REPLACE GAB YESS POSITION
WITHIN THE HISTORIC DAVIDS AND
PUT GABBY ON THE OUTS.
GABBY HAS BECOME SO CLOSE WITH
ALISON, AND SHES GOING TO GO
RIGHT DOWN WITH HER.
LISTEN, TOMORROW THE VOTE IS
GOING TO BE FOR ALISON.
ALISON IS THE BIGGEST THREAT.
I KNOW.
TO ME CARL IS THE GODFATHER.
HE BRINGS ME OVER, AND HES
LIKE, WERE VOTING ALISON, AND
THEN WERE SUPPOSED TO KISSs
THE RING AND HEAD OFF TO THE
BEACH.
BUT FOR NOW, IM KIND OF OKAY
WITH THAT.
I THINK THE DAVIDS HAVE THEIR
PECKING ORDER, AND ALISON IS
NEXT UP, SO I HAVE TO GET ON MY
LIFEBOAT AND LIKE SWIM AWAY FROM
THE ALISON SHIP.
WE DONT WANT TO BE
SCRAMBLING, SO, WE ALL DECIDED
ITS GOING TO BE ALISON.
ALISON?
YEAH.
IF GABBY ASKS YOU, WERE VOTING
FOR ANGELINA.
THE PLAN HANDED DOWN BY
GODFATHER CARL, WHEN I WAS
BECKONED TO HIS BEDSIDE, HE
TELLS ME, CHRISTIAN, THE VOTE IS
ALISON.
WERE LEAVING GABBY OUT OF IT.
IT WILL PISS OFF GABBY, BUT
WHAT YOU GOING TO DO?
COOL WITH THAT?
CARL, IM COOL WITH IT.
ABSOLUTELY.
I ALWAYS LOVE TO DEFER ALL MY
MAJOR STRATEGIC DECISIONS TO
SOMEONE WHO IS STILL HALF
SLOSHED.
WE DONT HAVE TO DO NO
SCRAMBLING TOMORROW YOU GUYS.
ITS THAT SIMPLE.
GABBY IS MY CLOSEST ALLY.
ILL MAKE SURE SHE THINKS
ITS ANGELINA.
THERE YOU GO.
THATS ALL WE NEED TO DO.
SO THAT MOMENT WAS A FINAL
DATA POINT FOR ME THAT CARL MUST
GO.
LETS SAY CARL MAGICALLY WENT
AWAY.
HE HAS POWER IN A MORE LITERAL
SENSE THAN IVE EVER SEEN.
THERES SOMETHING SLIGHTLY
MENACING ABOUT IT.
I WOULD BE WORKING WITH
ALISON, KARA, GABBY, AND ME.
THATS FIVE.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY ARE READY
TO FLIP.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY ALONG WITH
KARA AND ALISON ARE READY TO
VOTE FOR CARL, AND THEY NEED A
FIFTH AND THEY NEED ME.
TO BE HONEST, IM WILLING TO
SWING LEFT OR RIGHT, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
THATS WONDERFUL TO HEAR,
MIKE.
I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE IM IN
THE MIDDLE RIGHT NOW.
THERES FOR ON ONE SIDE, FOUR ON
THE OTHER, BUT ITS A WIN-WIN.
LIKE IF CARL GOES HOME, THEN,
YOU KNOW, THE GODFATHER IS GONE.
AND IF ALISON GOES HOME, THEN
WONDER WOMAN IS GONE AND I CAN
MAKE THE DECISION WHICH WILL
SERVE MY GAME THE BEST.
THERE IS THE SUN.
OH, THERE IT IS.
AWESOME.
THATS A BEAUTIFUL SIGN.
YEAH.
GABBY AND CHRISTIAN ARE OUT
THERE WATCHING IT.
SO RIGHT NOW IM TELLING YOU,
THE REAL PLAN, WEVE DECIDED TO
VOTE ANGELINA.
SO THEYRE REALLY LYING TO ME
AND NOT TELLING ME ITS ALISON.
I CANT WAIT FOR TONIGHT.
BECAUSE THAT PROVES THAT IM
NOT WITH THEM.
AND THEYRE USING ANGELINA
INSTEAD OF ME.
THATS GOOD.
IM SO GLAD IM MAKING A MOVE.
IM NOT STUPID.
THE REAL TARGET IS ALISON, AND
THE REASON THE DAVIDS ARENT
TELLING ME IS BECAUSE THEY THINK
THAT IM CLOSE TO ALISON.
THATS SO FUNNY.
DO PEOPLE SERIOUSLY THINK IM
STUPID.
I DONT KNOW HOW YOU CAN SAY
YOURE IN AN ALLIANCE AND NOT
TELL ONE OF YOUR ALLIANCE
MEMBERS WHO YOURE VOTING FOR.
WERE NOT IN AN ALLIANCE, ARE
WE?
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
IM ONE STEP AHEAD OF YOU.
WE SHOULD COUNT OUT HOW MUCH IS
LEFT.
I KNOW ITS LOW.
I KNOW WEVE ALREADY HAD WAY TOO
MUCH.
WERE IN A BAD SPOT RIGHT NOW.
THE RICE HAS JUST QUICKLY
BEEN DEPLETING.
BASICALLY AT THIS RATE, WE WILL
BE OUT OF RICE WITHIN ONE OR TWO
DAYS.
CURRENT SITUATION IS THAT WE
HAVE 15 OF THE SMALL SEASHELLS.
SO WERE LESS THAN ONE-THIRD OF
WHAT WE WOULD NEED TO JUST
SUSTAIN WHAT WEVE BEEN EATING
SO FAR.
AND I IMMEDIATELY IDENTIFIED
THIS OPPORTUNITY AS MY CHANCE TO
START A NEGOTIATION WITH JEFF AT
THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
SO MY IDEA IS WE START WITH
FIRST OFF ALL OF THE FISHING
GEAR.
SECOND WOULD BE MAJORITY OF THE
COOKING GEAR.
DURING MY COURSE OF STUDY WHEN I
WAS GETTING MY MBA AT YALE,
THERE IS A REQUIRED NEGOTIATIONS
CLASS, AND I LOVED IT SO MUCH
THAT I ACTUALLY ELECTED TO TAKE
ADVANCED NEGOTIATIONS.
SO ITS AN AREA THAT I JUST LOVE
TO DO.
ITS FUN TO ME.
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT THE
HAMMOCKS.
YOU WANT TO START WITH ALL
THAT STUFF?
ANGELINA IS LIKE SHE KNOWS
EXACTLY HOW MUCH RICE WERE
SUPPOSED TO EAT EVERY DAY FOR
THE REST OF THE THING, AND SHES
LIKE DONE AN INVENTORY OF
EVERYTHING AT THE CAMP, THE
FISHING GEAR, THE LUXURIES, THE
BLANKETS, AND SHES READY TO
SELL IT DOWN TO GET SOME RICE.
IN A WAY, SHES RIGHT, BUT SHES
STILL AGGRAVATING EVERY STEP OF
THE WAY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, CHRISTIAN,
GOT TO TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
TURN AROUND, PLEASE.
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
YOURE NOT BEING ARRESTED AT
THIS POINT.
WELL SAVE THAT FOR LATER.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BECOME UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO RACE OVER AN OBSTACLE.
THEN AROUND A POST, AND THEN
CROSS A BALANCE BEAM, CHECKING
THREE BUNDLES OF PUZZLE PIECES
ALONG THE WAY.
YOULL THEN USE THOSE PIECES TO
SOLVE A WORD PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE AT THE VOTE, GUARANTEED A
1-8 SHOT AT GETTING TO THE END.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
BIG STAKES.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO IT?
YEAH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU
BEFORE WE GET TO THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
Jeff: YEAH, GO.
SO THE TRIBE WAS WONDERING IF
YOU WERE OPEN TO A NEGOTIATION
REGARDING RICE.
Jeff: WHATS UP?
SO WERE GETTING CRITICALLY
LOW.
WERE AT THE POINT NOW WHERE WE
HAVE AT BEST TEN OF THESE SHELLS
REMAINING, AND SO WERE PREPARED
TO MAKE AN OFFER TO YOU UNLESS
YOU WANT TO PUT THE FIRST OFFER
OUT.
NO, GO AHEAD.
OKAY.
Jeff: THIS IS FUN.
SO OUR STARTING OFFER, AND
THIS WAS DISCUSSED AS WHOLE, IS
WE WANT TO START WITH AN OFFER
OF ALL OF THE FISHING GEAR, THE
MAJORITY OF ALL OF THE COOK SETS
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF A SMALL
POT AND A LARGE POT AND ONE
KNIFE AS WELL AS TWO OF THE
COMFORT CHARITIES AND THE
HANGING SWING FROM THE COMFORT
AS WELL AS THE REMAINING TEA AND
COFFEE.
THATS OUR STARTING POINT.
YOURE HOPING IF YOU HAVE A
COUNTER WERE ALL EARS.
Jeff: ANGELINA, THAT WAS
THE MOST WELL-LAID-OUT
PRESENTATION OF A LOWBALL OFFER.
YOU ALWAYS START LOW.
IF YOU KNOW NEGOTIATION, THATS
WHAT YOU DO.
Jeff: HERES MY THOUGHT.
IF SOMEBODY HERE IS WILLING TO
RISK THEIR SHOT AT IMMUNITY,
ILL PROVIDE ENOUGH RICE TO GET
YOU THROUGH THE END, RATIONED
RICE, NOT AN ABUNDANCE.
SO IS THERE ANYBODY THAT WANTS
TO SACRIFICE THEIR SHOT AT
IMMUNITY, MAYBE YOU FEEL SAFE?
YOURE GOING TO DO IT?
ILL DO IT, JEFF.
Jeff: ANGELINA IS GOING TO
SACRIFICE.
SHES GOING TO GIVE UP HER SHOT
AT THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IN
THE GAME SO EVERYBODY ELSE CAN
BENEFIT WITH RICE.
WE DONT HAVE A SITOUT BENCH.
PHI F FIND A SPOT IN THE GRASS.
-GOOD LUCK.
GOOD LUCK.
GREAT NEGOTIATION.
I WANTED IT TO BE ME, BECAUSE
ITS A BIG MOMENT FOR MY
SURVIVOR STORY AND FOR MY
RESUME, BUT IT WASNT WITHOUT
RISK AND VUL -- VULNERABILITY.
MY NAME IS THE DECOY NAME THATS
BEING GIVEN, BUT IT SHOWS IM A
RISKY PLAYER WHO IS WILLING TO
MAKE BIG MOVES AND BIG
SACRIFICES TO MAKE THINGS
HAPPEN.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU GOT TO GET UP AND OVER THAT
FIRST OBSTACLE WITH YOUR FIRST
BUNDLE OF PUZZLE PIECES.
EVERYBODY UP QUICKLY.
EVERYBODY UNTYING.
ITS GOING TO BE CARL COMING
DOWN.
HERES KARA.
DAVIE JUMPS.
CHRISTIAN JUMPS.
CARL JUMPS.
NICK JUMPS.
A HUGE LEAP.
GABBY IS ACROSS.
THERES ALISON.
KARA.
AND MIKE.
EVERYBODY ACROSS.
YOURE SPINNING NOW.
YOU GOT TO KEEP BOTH HANDS ON
THAT POST AND YOU ARE GOING TO
GET DIZZY, BUT THE FASTER YOU
GET DONE, THE FASTER YOU RELEASE
THAT SECOND PUZZLE OF PIECES.
OH, MY GOSH.
Jeff: WHO IS IT GOING TO
BE?
EVERYBODY CONTINUES TO SPIN.
DAVIE HAS HIS.
CARL HAS HIS.
CHRISTIAN HAS HIS.
NICK HAS HIS.
NOW YOUVE GOT TO TACKLE THE
BALANCE BEAM WHILE CARRYING TWO
BUNDLES OF PUZZLE PIECES AND
BEING DIZZY.
CHRISTIAN ALL TURNED AROUND.
THERE GOES KARA.
DAVIE IS OUT.
HERE COMES CARL.
KARA FALLS OFF.
GOT TO START AGAIN.
MIKES GOT TO GO BACK.
DAVIE HAS HIS THIRD BUNDLE.
GOT TO GET ACROSS THE BEAM.
DAVIE FIRST ACROSS.
HE CAN START SOLVING.
GOT TO PUT 11 BLOCKS IN THERE,
DAVIE.
HERE COMES CARL.
CARLS ACROSS.
KARA IS ACROSS.
ALISONS ACROSS.
CHRISTIAN IS GOOD.
NICK IS GOOD.
HERE COMES MIKE.
MIKES GOOD.
GABBY NOW ACROSS.
ITS AN 11-LETTER WORD, BUT YOU
HAVE 13 LETTERS.
THOSE OTHER TWO LETTERS WILL BE
IN YOUR HAND AS YOU START TO
SWAP LETTERS OUT TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT THIS WORD IS.
ALISON IS SWAPPING OUT LETTERS.
ANGELINA HAS ALREADY GIVEN UP
HER SHOT AT IMMUNITY, INCREASING
EVERYBODY ELSES ODDS.
YOU WANT THE SEE DAY 31 RIGHT
NOW.
THATS ALL THAT MATTERS.
KARA STEPPING BACK THE TAKE
ANOTHER LOOK.
CARL SWAPPING OUT LETTERS.
IS HE ON THE SOMETHING.
MIKE STICKING PUTTING HIS
LETTERS IN.
GABBY PUTTING HER LETTERS IN.
NICK GIVING IT ANOTHER LOOK NOW.
CHRISTIAN HAS HIS 11 LETTERS IN.
EVERYBODY NOW TRYING TO SOLVE.
CARL GETTING CLOSE TO SOMETHING.
ALISON TRYING SOMETHING ELSE.
WHO HAS THAT BIG VOCABULARY?
CARL THINKS HE HAS IT.
PERCEPTION, THAT IS NOT RIGHT.
CARL GOT TO GO BACK AT IT.
THE WORD WASNT RIGHT, BUT THAT
SHOWS YOU WHAT A LITTLE FOOD
DOES.
CARL GETS HIS FIRST REWARD, AND
FIRST ONE TO SOLVE A WORD.
WERE LOOKING FOR ONE SPECIFIC
WORD, AND IT IS NOT
"PERCEPTION."
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: ALISON WITH A BIG
REACTION.
SHE LOCKED IN ON SOMETHING.
NOW ITS DAVIE TRYING TO CATCH
ALISON.
DAVIE AND ALISON MOVING PIECES
LIKE THEY KNOW.
ITS GOING TO BE CLOSE IF
THEYRE RIGHT.
JEFF, JEFF,.
Jeff: DAVIE THINKS HE HAS
IT.
AND HE DOES.
PERSPECTIVE.
DAVIE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
WORDSMITH.
I WAS, THERE I WAS THERE.
YOU WERE RIGHT THERE.
WOW.
Jeff: DAVIE, COME ON OVER.
NICE JOB.
THANK YOU.
SMARTY PANTS.
Jeff: DAVIE SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CAN NOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 30
VERY, VERY TOUGH DAYS IN FIJI,
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE FIFTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
IT WONT BE YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
GOOD JOB, DAVIE.
THANK YOU, ANGELINA.
THIS IS BEST-CASE SCENARIO.
SOMEONE IN MY ALLIANCE WINS THE
IMMUNITY.
ALISON IS WITHOUT THE NECKLACE.
SO IM LEAVING FEELING LIKE I
WON, BECAUSE I WAS ABLE TO CLOSE
THE DEAL WITH JEFF AND WE CAN
TAKE ALISON OUT.
OH, WERE GOING TO BE GOOD TO
GO.
OH, YEAH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR THE SACRIFICE.
ITS OKAY.
I DONT WANT TO MAKE A BIG DEAL
OUT OF IT.
IT IS A BIG DEAL.
LET ME JUST COUNT IT.
AND ALISON HAS TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
BUT I SAY WE DO A FEAST OF RICE.
ITS A CELEBRATION.
COOL.
I DONT THINK ITS A TOUGH
DECISION TONIGHT.
WE VOTE ALISON OUT AND WE ALL
LIVE TO SEE TWO MORE DAYS, AS
LONG AS THE DAVIDS STICK
TOGETHER, THE LAST THING WE WANT
TO DO IS MAKE A DUMB MOVE AND
GIVE THE GOLIATHS THE NUMBERS
BACK.
WHILE THIS GROUP IS TOGETHER,
WERE SOLID.
UH-HUH.
YES, MAAM.
ANGELINA RIGHT NOW ON OUR
SIDE IS WORKING IN OUR FAVOR AS
WELL AS MIKE, SO WERE USING
THEM FOR AS LONG AS WE HAVE TO.
I MEAN, I KNOW IVE PLAYED MY
HEART OUT.
YEP.
BUT I ACTUALLY THINK THEYRE
WRITING MY NAME.
I THINK IT WILL BE BECAUSE
YOU DIDNT WIN IMMUNITY.
THE MARGINS HEADING INTO
TONIGHTS TRIBAL COUNCIL ARE
RAZOR THIN.
ITS GOING TO BE A 5-4 VOTE.
MOST LIKELY, AND THE FATE OF MY
GAME RESTS IN THE HANDS OF KARA,
CHRISTIAN,, GABBY, AND MIKE.
SO I OBVIOUSLY HAVE THAT FEAR
TODAY THAT ANY OF THE PEOPLE
THAT I THINK ARE WRITING DOWN MY
NAME AND IM GOING TO BE THE
FIFTH MEMBER OF THE JURY.
OUR NEXT CONVERSATION NEEDS
TO BE WITH MIKE.
YEAH.
RIGHT NOW THERES TWO CAMPS,
AND IM IN THE MIDDLE.
IVE MADE REALLY STRONG
ASSURANCES TO BOTH GROUPS THAT
IM WITH THEM.
AWESOME.
YEAH.
IM A WRITER AND DIRECTOR,
BUT IM ALSO AN ACTOR, AND I
HAVE TO DO LIKE MY GREATEST
ACTING IVE EVER DONE TO JUST
GET THROUGH THIS DAY.
I KNOW WE HAVE FOUR VOTES.
SO WHAT?
ANY ONE THING GOES WRONG.
WELL, IM DEFINITELY -- EVERY
PERSON IVE TALKED TO IS ALL IN.
AT THIS POINT ITS EVERY
GOLIATH FOR HIMSELF.
AND EVEN THOUGH ALISON AN I
WORKED TOGETHER FROM THE
BEGINNING, ALISON IS THE MOST
COMPETITIVE PERSON OUT HERE, SO
IT WOULD ACTUALLY BE EASIER FOR
MY GAME IF ALISON GOES HOME.
AND I THINK CARL, HES KIND OF
BECOME THE DON MAFIA OF THE
CAMP, AND ITS ANNOYING.
SO ITS GOING TO BE A HARD CALL
TONIGHT, BECAUSE IM GOING TO BE
BURNING SOME BRIDGES ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER.
IM FULL OF DIRT.
I KEEP PULLING OUT SAND.
UH, THIS IS THE THING I HATE THE
MOST BEING OUT HERE.
I HAVE NO PARANOIA, I JUST HAVE
BEARD HATE.
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I LOVE MIKE, AND I THINK MIKE
WANTS TO TAKE OUT CARL.
BUT MIKE IS A PROFESSIONAL
ACTOR.
HE WORKS IN HOLLYWOOD.
I MEAN, THIS IS HIS JOB.
HE VOTED FOR ME TWICE.
WERE BOTH STILL COOL WITH
TODAY?
OH, YEAH, IM 100% IN.
AN YET IM TRUSTING HIM ON
THIS VOTE TO VOTE WITH ME.
BUT I HAVE TO TAKE THE SHOT.
I JUST WANTED TO TOUCH BASE
ONE LAST TIME.
CARL?
SOLID.
WERE ALL SET, AS LONG AS MIKE
DOESNT [BLEEPED] US.
I THINK HE ALMOST IM STOKED.
OKAY.
WELL PICK UP THE PIECES WHEN
WE GET HOME.
THEYLL BE APOLOGIZING TO US,
OR THE ME.
AT LEAST TO YOU, THATS TRUE.
IF CARL GOES HOME TONIGHT,
IM GOING TO FEEL SO VINDICATED
THAT THIS WHOLE TIME IVE BEEN
SEEN AS AN EMOTIONAL YOUNG
WOMAN, SEEN AS HYSTERICAL, ALL
THESE INSULTS SLUNG MY WAY, AND
IM GOING TO FEEL SO PROUD THAT
I BROKE FREE FROM THOSE
PERCEPTIONS AND SHOWED THAT IM
NOT GOING TO BE AN UNDERDOG IN
THIS GAME ANYMORE.
BUT THE PLAN REALLY HAS TO BE
EXECUTED FLAWLESSLY, OTHERWISE
IM WRITING DOWN CARLS NAME AND
HES COMING BACK TO CAMP WITH ME
AND ALL WILL BE EXPOSED.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH, JOHN, DAN, AND ALEC,
VOTESSED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO KARA, LAST FRIDAY EVERYBODY
VOTED FOR ALEC.
WAS THERE A SHIFT IN THE
DYNAMIC, OR DO YOU THINK IT WILL
BE THE SAME THING AGAIN,
EVERYBODYS GOING TO VOTE FOR
ONE PERSON?
LAST TRIBAL WAS TOUGH.
IT WAS BASICALLY LIKE A
SACRIFICE TO SHOW THAT WE WANTED
TO WORK WITH THE DAVIDS, AND
TONIGHT IF I CAN RELATE IT TO
REAL ESTATE, YOU SAY YOU WANT TO
WORK WITH SOMEBODY,
IS OFFICIAL UNTIL YOU SIGN THAT
CONTRACT THAT PROVES WHERE THE
LINE REALLY ARE DRAWN.
Jeff: ALISON, IT SOUNDS
LIKE THE LAST VOTE WAS A SHOW OF
GOOD FAITH.
CERTAINLY DEMONSTRATING THAT
I WAS WILLING TO VOTE OUT
SOMEONE WHO WAS SO CLOSE TO ME.
I WAS SAYING, IM HERE TO PLAY
THIS GAME.
LET ME PLAY WITH YOU.
Jeff: SO NICK, WHAT IS THE
DYNAMIC AT CAMP NOW?
WELL, I THINK WHEN THERE WERE
SEVEN GOLIATHS AND FIVE DAVIDS
THE BEACH WAS LIKE A FRYING PAN
AND THERE WAS SCRAMBLED EGGS
EVERYWHERE, BECAUSE EVERYBODY
WAS SCRAMBLING, AND NOW ITS A
LOT LESS HECTIC.
PERHAPS MORE OF A POACHED
EGG.
YOU TAKE A BIG BOILER BOWL AND
DROP THE EGG IN.
THERES LITTLE PIECES SWIRLING
AROUND, BUT EVENTUALLY THEY
COALESCE INTO ONE WHOLE, WHICH
IS PRESUMABLY THE PLAN YOU THINK
IS GOING TO GO DOWN AT TRIBAL
TONIGHT.
THATS AWESOME.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
AND ILL ADD JUST ONE THING,
JEFF.
THIS THERE IS A REALLY JOVIAL
SPIRIT AT CAMP, BUT TRIBAL IS
LIKE A COLISEUM.
WERE ALL GLADIATORS, BUT WERE
GIVING EACH OTHER PERMISSION TO
PLAY THIS GAME HARD AND NOT TAKE
THINGS TOO PERSONALLY.
Jeff: MIKE, YOURE NODDING?
I THINK THAT ANALOGY IS GOOD.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED VOTING
PEOPLE OUT, I FELT GUILT
STRICKEN.
AS THERES MORE BLOOD ON THE
FLOOR, OKAY, LETS GET ANOTHER
PERSON OUT OF CAMP.
I DONT KNOW, ITS THE ONLY WAY
I CAN SAY IT.
Jeff: ALISON, WHAT DID YOU
NOTICE AT CAMP TODAY?
WAS IT CALM?
OR WAS THERE A LEVEL OF TENSION?
IT WAS SURPRISINGLY CALM TO
THE POINT THAT IT WAS
DISCOMFORTING TO ME.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT LAST TRIBAL
WOULD LIBERATE MY GAME, AND THEN
MAYBE IM JUST THE NEXT ONE.
I THINK WHATS HAPPENING WITH
ALISON IS SHES HAD SCRAMBLED
EGGS FOR SO LONG, AN NOW ITS
SWITCHED UP AND HER BREAKFAST
TASTES DIFFERENT.
IT HAS HER WORRIED.
ITS A DIFFERENT TASTE IN HER
MOUTH.
ITS JUST DIFFERENCE.
Jeff: CARL, DID YOU FEEL
THAT SAME THING?
PEOPLE WERENT TALKING TO YOU?
FOR ME HONESTLY, CAMP DIDNT
SEEM ANY DIFFERENT.
I KNEW WHO I HAD SPOKE WITHIN
PREVIOUSLY, IF THEY WANT TO TALK
TO ME, ALL THEY HAVE TO DO IS
COME TO THE SHELTER.
SO IM OKAY WITH THE WAY THE
VIBE WAS AT CAMP TODAY.
Jeff: GABBY, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF CARLS ANSWER?
WHAT I HEAR HIM SAY, IF ANYBODY
FELT VULNERABLE, THEY KNOW WHERE
I AM, SET AN APPOINTMENT.
SET AN APPOINTMENT.
THATS WHAT I WAS THINKING.
I DONT KNOW IF ITS LIKE, YOU
APPROACH ME OR I APPROACH YOU,
BUT I FEEL LIKE THE
CONVERSATIONS THAT HAVE BEEN HAD
OVER FAST COUPLE DAYS HAVE BEEN
VERY DELIBERATE.
YOU MAY NOT CHECK IN AGAIN WITH
EACH OTHER, BUT WERE LOCKED IN.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE TRUST IN THOSE
PEOPLE THAT THATS WHATS
HAPPENING.
Jeff: MIKE, YOU HAVE TO
MENTION THE FACT THAT THE LAST
THREE PEOPLE VOTED OUT WERE
GOLIATHS.
SO IS TONIGHTS VOTE AS SIMPLE
AS DAVIDS JUST PICKING OFF A
GOLIATH?
HONESTLY, NO, TRIBAL LINES
HAVE BLURRED.
I WON THE REWARD CHALLENGE WITH
CARL AND DAVIE AND KARA.
ILL REMEMBER THAT DAY FOR THE
REST OF MY LIFE.
SO MOMENTS LIKE THAT CHANGE
RELATIONSHIPS.
Jeff: ANGELINA, CONCERN YOU
AT ALL THIS WHEN PEOPLE GO ON A
REWARD IT CAN BE SO POWERFUL
THAT IT COULD ACTUALLY IMPACT A
VOTE?
I THINK THERES A LITTLE BIT
OF NERVOUS ENERGY, BUT I THINK
THERE ARE CLEAR EYES AND FULL
HEARTS FOR CERTAIN PEOPLE HERE,
AND MAYBE NOT FOR OTHERS.
FOR ME SECURING THE RICE WITH
YOU WAS PROOF THAT THERE IS A
STRONG GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO I
TRUST.
HAD I NOT HAD THAT BACKING, I
WOULDNT HAVE BEEN ABLE TO HAVE
THE CONFIDENCE THAT I DID TO
MAKE THE DEAL WITH YOU TODAY TO
GET RICE FOR THE REST OF THE
GAME.
Jeff: ALISON, DO YOU CONCUR
WITH ANGELINA THAT THERE IS A
CLEAR PLAN FOR TONIGHTS TRIBAL?
NOT NECESSARILY.
I HAVE A LOT MORE APPREHENSION
ABOUT THE PLAN, BUT I JUST HAVE
TO PUT FAITH AT THIS POINT
BECAUSE I WAS TWO LETTERS SHORT
FROM HAVING PERSPECTIVE.
Jeff: VERY CLOSE TODAY.
DAVIE, YOU GOT A CLEAR PLAN?
DEFINITELY FOR THE VOTE
TONIGHT THERES A CLEAR PLAN,
BUT EVERYONES GOT THOSE THINGS
IN THEIR MIND, LIKE IS THIS
GOING TO HELP ME MOVE FORWARD OR
IS THIS GOING TO HELP ME MOVE
BACKWARD.
Jeff: MIKE, DAVIE JUST HIT
IT.
THERE MIGHT BE ONE OR TWO CLEAR
PLANS FOR TONIGHTS VOTE, BUT
THERE ARE NINE UNIQUE PLANS TO
GET TO DAY 39.
THATS WHAT KEEPS US ALL UP
AT NIGHT, ALL THE DIFFERENT
ITERATIONS OF HOW WE COULD GET
TO THE END AND WHO DO WE TRUST.
LIKE WHATEVER STRATEGIZING IS
GOING ON OR HAS BEEN GOING ON,
IT CAN GET YOU HEADY, YOU KNOW?
Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KARA, YOURE UP.
SORRY, GIRL.
I LOVE YOU, BUT THIS IS A I GOT
TO GET YOU BEFORE YOU GET ME
VOTE.
YOURE THE GODFATHER NO MORE.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE ALISON.
ALISON.
TWO VOTES ALISON.
CARL.
WERE TIED, TWO VOTES ALISON,
TWO VOTES CARL.
ALISON.
THREE VOTES ALISON.
THATS FOUR VOTES ALISON, TWO
VOTES CARL.
CARL.
THATS FOUR VOTES ALISON, THREE
VOTES CARL.
CARL.
WERE TIED.
FOUR VOTES CARL.
FOUR VOTES ALISON.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
12th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
CARL. YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
Jeff: CARL, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
TONIGHTS VOTE MAKES ONE THING
VERY CLEAR: THE LINES HAVE
DEFINITELY BLURRED.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," FAMILY BRINGS
EVERYONE TOGETHER.
ITS TIME FOR SOME LOVE.
YES!
Jeff: BUT THE ULTIMATE
BETRAYAL --
OH, MY GOSH.
I COULDNT BELIEVE IT WAS COMING
OUT OF HER MOUTH.
Jeff: BREAKS THE GAME WIDE
OPEN.
I WANT THE PLAY MY NUMBER-ONE
ALLY.
IM CONFUSED. I NEVER SEEN THAT
ONE COMING
WE HAD A PLAN IN PLACE BUT
I PUT MY GUARD DOWN AND THEY
SWITCHED THE PLAN AND IM THE
ONE WHO IS GOING HOME.
ITS NO DIFFERENT THAN DRIVING
MY TRUCK.
I WAS ON CRUISE CONTROL, MOVING
A LITTLE FAST, BUT IN THIS GAME,
YOU JUST CANT DO THAT.
IT WAS A GREAT MOVE ON THEIR
PART AND THEY GOT THE BETTER OF
ME.