Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," DESPITE WINNING THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, THE DAVID
TRIBE HAD YET ANOTHER SETBACK.
I SPRAINED MY LEG.
Jeff: THE GOLIATH TRIBE WAS
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL AND
NATALIE WAS RUBBING SOME THE
WRONG WAY.
NATALIE IS USED TO BEING THE
BOSS BITCH.
Jeff: BUT ANGELINA SAW A
BIGGER PROBLEM.
JEREMY IS A MANIPULATOR.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ANGELINA GOT HER WAY WHEN THE
TRIBE VOTED UNANIMOUSLY FOR
JEREMY.
JEREMY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
17 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
COME ON IN, GUYS.
DAVIDS GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW GOLIATH TRIBE.
JEREMY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ITS BEEN A TOUGH TEN DAYS.
BI, YOUR KNEE IS WRAPPED AN
YOURE LIMPING.
WHATS GOING ON WITH YOU?
I ACTUALLY HAVE TO MAKE A
REALLY SAD ANNOUNCEMENT.
I SPRAINED MY MCL YESTERDAY, AND
IM AN ATHLETE, SO I HAVE MADE
THE DECISION TO LEAVE THE GAME.
THATS OKAY, BI.
THATS OKAY.
IM SO SORRY.
ITS ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT TO DO WHATS BEST FOR
YOU.
THATS REALLY SAD.
ITS OKAY.
Jeff: WHATS THE EMOTION,
ANGELINA?
WE WORKED SO HARD TO BE OUT.
ITS A DREAM FOR MOST PEOPLE,
AND TO SAY I CANT MOVE FORWARD
HAS TO BE ONE OF THE HARDEST
DECISIONS TO MAKE.
I HAVE RESPECT FOR HER DECISION.
I WISH THIS WASNT ONE SHE HAD
TO MAKE.
Jeff: IS IT CRAZY WHEN WE
THIS A SEASON CALLED DAVID
VERSUS GOLIATH, ITS NOT THE
GOLIATHS THAT HAVE SOMEBODY
EVACUATED.
ITS NOT THE GOLIATHS THAT HAVE
SOMEBODY QUIT.
ITS THE DAVID TRIBE, ONE
OBSTACLE AFTER ANOTHER.
YEAH, JEFF, YOU KNOW, WE
DOUBT OURSELVES HERE AND, THERE
BUT THE THING ABOUT DAVIDS IS
OUR ENDURANCE.
I THINK AS A TRIBE, YOU KNOW,
THIS WILL CONTINUE TO MAKE US
STRONGER.
Jeff: SO BI, WHEN YOU GO
BACK HOME AND YOU REFLECT ON
THIS EXPERIENCE, WHAT WAS IT?
I MEAN, THESE ARE A BAND OF
MISFITS.
IM GLAD THAT I WAS FORCED TO
GET TO KNOW THEM, BECAUSE
THEYRE AMAZING HUMAN BEING,
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
I KNOW THEYRE GOING TO ROCK IT.
BUT SAD TO SAY IT WONT BE WITH
ME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
BI HAS MADE HER DECISION.
BI IS QUITTING THE GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD DOWN TO THE WATERS EDGE.
WELL GRAB A BOAT FOR YOU, PICK
YOU UP.
GREAT WORK, BI.
REALLY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER UNPREDICTABLE MOMENT IN
WHAT SO FAR HAS BEEN AN
UNPREDICTABLE SEASON THAT IS
ABOUT TO HAVE ANOTHER
UNPREDICTABLE TWIST.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
OH, MY GOD.
I FREAKIN KNEW IT, JEFF.
Jeff: WE ARE SWITCHING
TRIBES.
LETS PLAY THIS GAME, BABY.
HEARING "DROP YOUR BUFFS" IS
TERRIFYING TO SOME, BUT THEN TO
ME IT WAS LIKE, NOW ITS REALLY
TIME TO PLAY THE GAME.
IM HERE FOR THE PART WHEN ITS
TIME TO BACKSTAB AND LIE AND
TURN OTHER PEOPLE AGAINST EACH
OTHER.
THAT DEVIL IS DAVIE.
IM READY TO DO ALL THAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY REVEAL YOUR NEW
BLUFFS.
PURPLE.
ORANGE.
I HAVE A NEW COLOR.
PURPLE.
Jeff: AS YOU START TO OPEN
THEM, YOU WILL SEE THERE IS A
THIRD COLOR.
GREEN.
Jeff: WE ARE SWITCHING FROM
TWO TRIBES TO THREE.
THE MOST DISAPPOINTING PART
FOR ME WAS WATCHING KARA OPEN
HERS.
I WAS LIKE, WHAT IS HER, WHAT IS
MINE.
OH, THAT WAS ROUGH.
CARL AINT GOT ONE.
Jeff: AND IF YOU DONT HAVE
A BUFF, IT MEANS YOU DONT HAVE
A TRIBE.
CARL, THAT IS YOU.
IF YOURE ON THE ORANGE TRIBE,
MOVE TO THE ORANGE MAT.
IF YOURE ON THE PURPLE TRIBE,
MOVE TO THE PURPLE MAT.
IF YOU ARE GREEN, GO IN THE
MIDDLE.
CARL.
YOU DONT HAVE A BUFF.
COME RIGHT OVER HERE.
ANGELINA.
NATALIA.
IT WILL BE GREAT.
WELL HAVE A GOOD TIME.
SLAM TOWN.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
THE OBVIOUS FIRST REACTION IS
THE GOLIATHS HAVE THE ADVANTAGE
IN EVERY SINGLE TRIBE.
LETS START WITH THE ORANGE
TRIBE.
YOUR NAME NOW IS VUKU.
WE HAVE THREE FORMER GOLIATHS.
WE HAVE NATALIA, KARA AND ALEC.
WE HAVE TWO FORMER DAVID, DAVIE
AND ELIZABETH.
IN THE MIDDLE, THE GREEN TRIBE,
YOUR TRIBE NAME, TEVA.
YEAH.
Jeff: AND WE HAVE THREE
FORMER GOLIATHS WITH JOHN, DAN,
AND ALISON, AND TWO FORMER
DAVIDS WITH CHRISTIAN AND GABBY.
DOWN ON THE PURPLE TRIBE, YOUR
NAME IS JIBINI, THE SAME
BREAKDOWN, THREE FORMER GOLIATH,
NATALIE, MIKE, AND ANGELINA, AND
TWO FORMER DAVIDS WITH LYRSA,
HANDS ON HER HIP, AND NICK.
THAT BRINGS US TO YOU, CARL.
HERES WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN TO
YOU.
YOURE GOING TO EXILE ISLAND.
WOW, WOW.
Jeff: YOU WILL RETURN TO
THE GAME AT THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, JOINING THE TRIBE THAT
LOSES THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AND HAS TO VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT.
SO WHOEVER LOSES GETS CARL AS
THEIR REPLACEMENT.
CARL, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD DOWN
THE BEACH.
BOAT IS WAITING.
THERE IS MAN -- MAP TO EXILE.
GOOD LUCK, CARL.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
EN THE DAYS IN.
ONCE AGAIN THE GAME HAS CHANGED.
VUKU, JIBINI, GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
TEVA, NEW BEACH, NO SHELTER,
STARTING OVER.
HERES A MAP TO YOUR NEW HOME.
THANK YOU.
.
Jeff: YOURE WELCOME.
BASICALLY THE ENTIRE TRIBE
SYSTEM HAS BEEN GERRYMANDERED
AGAINST THE DAVIDS.
THATS NOT GOOD.
WE WERE ONLY DOWN 9-7, BUT CARL
IS OFF ON AN ISLAND, AND
EVERYONE IS EVENLY DISTRIBUTED
INTO A MINORITY.
SO THE DAVIDS ARE COLLECTIVELY
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
NO WAY.
THIS IS SO SICK.
THIS IS SO MUCH BETTER.
WE HAVE CHAIRS.
WE GOT HAMMOCKS.
YOU GUYS ARE SO HAPPY.
OUR CAMP SUCKS COMPARED TO
THIS.
WHEN JEFF SAID DROP YOUR
BUFFS, I WAS LIKE, THIS COULD BE
TROUBLE.
FORTUNATELY FOR US, WE GOT THREE
GOLIATHS, SO MYSELF, KARA AND
NATALIA, AND THEN TWO DAVID,
DAVIE AND ELIZABETH.
SO WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
SO IM SUPER PSYCHED ABOUT THAT.
IM MARRIED.
I HAVE THREE KIDS.
YOU CHEER?
IM RETIRED.
ILL CHEER FOR US.
WE HAVE A REALLY STRONG
TRIBE.
WE DONT HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
ANYTHING ELSE, JUST WIN.
THIS IS REALLY MESSED UP.
EVERY SINGLE TRIBE HAS GOLIATH
AS THE MAJORITY.
SO THAT ABSOLUTELY CHANGES OUR
STRATEGY.
IM STOKED WITH THIS NEW
TRIBE, BRO.
ME, TOO MAN.
WERE ALL FINDS CAL.
WE HAVE A GREAT BALANCE.
WE GOT THE FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET IN WITH THESE GOLIATHS.
IM ASHAMED TO SAY I HAVENT
BEFRIENDED TOO MANY CAUCASIANS.
ITS IN THE THAT I HAVENT
WANTED TO, BUT IVE JUST BEEN
AROUND BLACK PEOPLE MY WHOLE
LIFE, BUT I AM BLACK NERD.
LIKE I DRIVE A FREAKIN P.T.
CRUISER.
IM THE BLACK GUY THAT WHITE
PEOPLE LOVE TO APPROACH, HEY,
NICE CAR.
SO HOPEFULLY ILL BE ABLE TO FIT
IN.
IM NOTHING LIKE THE REST OF
MY FAMILY.
THEYRE NOT REDNECK LIKE I AM.
I WAS EXTREMELY CONSERVATIVE.
I WAS RAISED REALLY
CHRISTIAN.
I THINK FAITH IS SO IMPORTANT TO
HAVE OUT HERE.
FOR SURE.
I WAS LITERALLY QUOTING
SCRIPTURE IN MY HEAD THE WHOLE
BOAT RIDE OVER HERE.
THEY HAVE US OUTNUMBERED, SO
GETTING OUT OF THIS ALIVE IS
GOING TO BE HARD, BUT IM NOT
AFRAID OF HARD WORK.
ITS DEFINITELY TIME TO PULL OUT
ALL THE STOPS.
IM GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO FIND COMMON GROUND.
I USED TO HAVE HORSES AND
TRAIN HORSES.
DID YOU EVER COMPETE?
I USED TO WHEN I WAS LITTLE?
WESTERN PLEASURE?
SADDLE SEAT.
NO WAY, SO YOU HAD THE SAME
ENGLISH GETUP THAT I DID IN.
YES.
THATS HILARIOUS, MAN.
THE LONG COAT.
AND THE TOP HAT.
THATS AWESOME.
MY FIRST HORSE WAS AN
ARABIAN.
THEN WE GOT A SEATTLE BRED.
THATS AWESOME.
I LOVED IT.
I WISH I HAD A REPORTS.
YEAH.
CAREBACK MY BEST ALLY IN THIS
GAME, MY MOST IMPORTANT ALLY IN
THIS GAME, IS GETTING ALONG WITH
ELIZABETH WAY TOO MUCH.
THEY HAVE TOO MANY THINGS IN
COMMON.
IM GETTING NERVOUS.
IM LIKE, THESE TOO ARE WAY TOO
CLOSE AND IM NOT OKAY WITH IT.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
IM NOT GOING TO LIE.
IM SCARED, BECAUSE YOU GUYS
HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
I DONT WANT YOU TO FLIP ON ME.
OH,, NO IM TRYING TO MAKE
CAMP LIFE EASY.
YOU KNOW ME, IM SO LOYAL TO YOU
GUYS.
ALL OF A SUDDEN NATALIA IS
NERVOUS.
SHES WORRIED I MIGHT JUMP SHIP.
IT CONCERNS ME.
SHES FREAKED OUT THAT I WOULD
FLIP ON ELIZABETH.
I WOULD NEVER FLIP.
WHAT WOULD BE THE POINT OF THAT.
THERE IS NOTHING THAT NEEDS TO
BE QUESTIONED.
IT WOULD NOT MAKE SENSE.
IM NOT SURPRISED AT ALL.
I KNEW THAT FOR WHATEVER REASON
ITS HARD FOR HER TO TRUST
PEOPLE.
BUT WE HAVE A FOOL-PROOF PLAN.
SCREWING THIS UP WOULD BE DUMB.
HELL, IM STUCK HERE ON EXILE
ISLAND.
NOBODY TO TALK TO.
OF COURSE, E-MAIL A TRUCK
DRIVER, SO IVE BEEN ALONE, BUT
IM ABLE TO PICK UP THE PHONE OR
STOP AT A TRUCK STOP AND GO TALK
TO SOMEBODY OR WHAT NOT.
SO AS FAR AS BEING ON EXILE, I
HAVE NEVER BEEN ALONE LIKE THIS
BEFORE.
OH, BOY.
FROM A TREE BY A ROCKY POINT I
FELL AND ROLLED THROUGH THE SAND
AND NOW HERE I AM, SOON TO BE
WASHED AWAY WITH THE TIDE.
IF YOU CATCH ME IN TIME AND
RECOGNIZE MY MARK, YOUR TIME ON
EXILE WILL BE WORTH IT.
A TREE.
AS I READ THE RIDDLE, IT STARTED
COMING TO ME THIS A COCONUT THAT
WAS IN THE OCEAN BY THE SHORE
MIGHT HAVE AN ADVANTAGE INSIDE
OF IT.
SO I IMMEDIATELY GET UP AND RUN
TO THE BEACH.
ONCE I GET OUT THERE, I SEE THAT
THERES TONS AND TONS OF
COCONUTS.
SO I START GOING CRAZY TRYING TO
GATHER AS MANY COCONUTS AS I
COULD.
THIS OCEAN AINT NOTHING TO PLAY
WITH.
IM GETTING BASHED AROUND THE
ROCKS BY WAVES.
AND I CANT FIND THAT DAMN
COCONUT TO SAVE MY LIFE.
ITS LIKE A NEEDLE IN A
HAYSTACK, BUT THERES NOTHING
THAT IVE EVER DONE IN LIFE THAT
I JUST SAID I QUIT.
AND THEN I SEE IT.
WOW.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND AN ADVANTAGE IN
THE GAME.
THIS IS AN IDOL NULLIFIER.
IT BLOCKS THE USE OF AN IDOL BY
ANY OTHER PLAYER.
HERES HOW IT WORKS: YOU WILL
LAY THIS IN SECRET WHEN YOU VOTE
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WRITE THE NAME OF THE PERSON YOU
WANT TO BLOCK FROM USING AN
IDOL.
IF AN IDOL IS PLAYED FOR THEM,
THIS ADVANTAGE WILL NULLIFY THE
IDOL.
SWEET.
SO THIS IS THE NULLIFIER.
IF I GUESS CORRECTLY WHO IS
PLAYING AN IDOL, I CAN PLAY THIS
NULLIFIER, PUT THEIR NAME DOWN,
AND THAT IDOL BASICALLY BECOMES
NULL AND VOID.
I GUESS I NEVER THOUGHT COMING
TO EXILE WOULD BE REWARDING.
FINDING THIS ADVANTAGE IS HUGE,
BUT I HAVE THE PLAY IT IN THE
RIGHT MANNER.
SO WHEN THE TIME COMES, IM
GOING TO USE THIS NULLIFIER JUST
LIKE THE SLING THAT SHOT GOLIATH
IN BETWEEN THE EYES AND TOOK HIM
OUT.
WELCOME,.
WELCOME.
IM NATALIE.
NICK, NICE TO MEET YOU.
I FEEL LIKE THIS NEW TRIBE IS
THE DAVIDS OF THE DAVIDS OF THE
DAVIDS.
I THINK EVERYONE ON THE JIBINI
TRIBE WOULD BE THE LAST FIVE WER
TEAMS, AND WERE ALL NOW ON ONE
TRIBE.
IM GOING TO BE SEEING TRIBAL
COUNCIL A LOT THE NEXT COUPLE
DAYS.
SO YOURE A SCREENWRITER?
I AM.
STUFF WEVE SEEN BEFORE?
PEOPLE KNOW ME FROM THE MOVIE
"SCHOOL OF ROCK."
I KNEW IT!
IT FEELS WEIRD TO HAVE THE
DAVIDS IN MY CAMP.
I WANT THEM GONE.
I DIDNT FEEL LIKE GOING
THROUGH THE WHOLE INTRODUCTION
AND GETTING TO KNOW THEM,
BECAUSE THE GOLIATHS ARE STILL
IN CONTROL.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
SO NICK WOULD YOU AND
ANGELINA START THE FIRE, AND IF
YOU DONT MIND, THE POT IS
LOOKING A LITTLE --
I THINK NATALIA CLEANED IT
THIS MORNING BUT ILL GO DOWN
AND TOO IT.
THE PRIORITY IS TO GET THE
FIRE DOING, BECAUSE ONCE THE SUN
FALLS, IF YOU DONT HAVE YOUR
THINGS IN ORDER, YOU JUST WONT
HAVE THEM FOR THE NIGHT.
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
YOU GOT TO PUT SOME WOOD.
YOU GOT THE FEED IT RIGHT AWAY
ORITS GOING TO GO OUT.
SEE HOW FAST ITS GOING.
PUT THAT LINEN BY YOUR HAND,
YOUR RIGHT HAND, PICK UP THAT
LINEN PIECE BY YOUR RIGHT HAND.
PUT THAT ON THERE.
THAT BURNS QUICKLY.
THE TYPICAL NATALIE STYLE IS
TO KIND OF SIT ON HER THRONE,
LOOK AT HER PEASANTS AND TELL
THEM WHAT TO DO.
KEEP FEEDING IT, ANGELINA.
YOU HAVE TO BLOW.
FEED WITH IT THE SMALL PIECES OF
WOOD, THE REAL THIN ONES.
SEE HOW ITS SITTING ON THE
SIDE.
LIKE THAT.
I THINK WE NEED A COUPLE OF
BIGGER PIECES THAT ARE THICK.
I DONT THINK SO, NICK.
HOW ABOUT THAT WHITE ONE OVER
THERE, NICK?
ANGELINA, THIS IS YOUR FIRE.
KEEP FEEDING IT.
YEP.
IT WASNT A FEW HOURS INTO
THIS TRIBE WHERE I SAW A CRACK,
AND ITS NAME WAS NATALIE.
SO EVEN THOUGH NATALIE IS
BOSSINESS IS TOUGH TO LISTEN TO,
ITS ALMOST LIKE SWEET MUSIC TO
MY EARS, BECAUSE I KNOW ITS NOT
JUST TOUGH ON ME, ITS TOUGH ON
EVERYBODY.
SHE DRIVES ME CRAZY.
YEAH.
YOU FEEL LIKE SHE COULD GO
NEXT?
ITS A LONGER CONVERSATION.
WELL HAVE TO TALK ABOUT IT.
WELL, I GET A GOOD VIBE FOR
FROM YOU FOR SURE.
I GET A GOOD VIBE FROM YOU.
MY INITIAL GOAL WAS TRY NOT
TO PLAY TOO FAST OR TOO HARD,
BECAUSE THATS WHAT I LOVE TO
DO.
I KNOW A THERE IS NO WAY A DAVID
IS GOING TO WIN THIS GAME ONLY
PLAYING WITH DAVIDS.
I SEE THE OPPORTUNITY TO BUILD A
RELATIONSHIP WITH A GHIET.
ID LOVE TO START AN
ALLIANCE.
ID LOVE THAT.
OKAY.
AWESOME.
I REALLY LIKE NICK.
HE SEEMS VERY UNPRETENTIOUS,
VERY SALT OF THE EARTH.
YOU WANT TO NAME THE
ALLIANCE.
WOULDNT THAT BE AWESOME?
LETS TAKE A SECOND TO THINK
ABOUT IT, THEN WELL HAVE TO
COME UP WITH A GOOD ONE.
I WAS THINKING THE ROCK
STARS, IF YOU LIKE IT?
WE CAN DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO IM HAPPY THAT WE CREATED
THAT BOND.
YOU REALLY DONT THINK ANYONE
ON YOUR SIDE HAS AN IDOL?
I REALLY DONT.
THE PERSON WHO HAS AN IDOL ON
MY SIDE IS DAN.
YOURE PRETTY SURE?
I KNOW HE DOES.
NOTHING WOULD MAKE ME
HAPPENNER WITH THAN IF THIS ROCK
STAR ALLIANCE BORE FRUIT.
BUT I HAVE MORE AT RISK THAN HE
DOES.
THE GOLIATHS DO HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
WELL SEE IF WE CAN LIVE UP TO
THAT ALLIANCE.
THE ROCK STARS.
YOU NEED ME TO BRACE IT ANY
WAY OR JUST STAY OUT OF YOUR
SWINGING RADIUS HERE?
THERE IS A DIFFERENT VIBE WHEN
YOU HAVE THEE OF THESE
STEREOTYPICAL GOLIATHS WITH US.
WHEN JOHN JUST SWINGS HIS
MACHETE AND JUST SORT OF SMASHES
THROUGH THIS PIECE OF BAMBOO,
THATS A NEW THING.
THATS NOT HOW I CHOP BAMBOO,
THATS JUST A STYLISTIC
DIFFERENCE.
CHRISTIAN, LET ME HELP YOU.
I WILL WALK AND LEARN.
YOU WANT TO CHOP THINGS AT AN
ANGLE.
CHRISTIAN, HE WANTS TO HELP.
HE WANTS TO BE INVOLVED.
AT THE SAME TIME, HES WILLING
TO PUT DOWN THAT EGO AND LISTEN
TO OTHER PEOPLE, WHICH IS GREAT.
I GOT FIRST PART RIGHT.
NOW ILL ROTATE A LITTLE BIT.
IM DOING WHATEVER I CAN IN
ORDER TO CONTRIBUTE AS MUCH AS I
CAN, BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I
HAVE TO MAKE SURE IM AT THE TOP
OF MY SOCIAL GAME, SO I GOT TO
GO ON A CHARM OFFENSIVE HERE,
AND THATS REALLY UNDERSTATING
IT.
I REALLY NEED SORT OF CHARM
NUCLEAR WARFARE, SO TIME TO
BRING ABOUT THE CHARM POCOLYPS.
I WAS CURIOUS ABOUT SLAM
TOWN.
SLAM TOWN IS THE PLACE I SAY
IM GOING TO TAKE MY WRESTLING
OPPONENTS SOME SLAM TOWN IS
POPULATED BY PEOPLE WHO YOU HAVE
SLAMMED?
CHRISTIAN IS A QUICKIE GUY?
I FOR SURE HAVE A TON OF
QUICKIENESS IN ME.
I HAVE A CONFIDENT PUBLIC PER
SEW NAP.
IM USED TO PERFORMING IN FRONT
OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE, BUT
SOMETIMES IN SMALLER GROUPS LIKE
THIS.
I DO GET A LITTLE BIT AWKWARD.
I RUN OUT OF THINGS TO SAY,
SELF-DOUBT, INSECURITY, ALITTLE
BIT OF SOCIAL AWKWARDNESS, FOR
SURE I GOT, THAT BIG TIME.
SO I WAS MOSTLY CURIOUS ABOUT
THE AVAILABILITY OF A
COMPTROLLER POSITION.
WERE CONSTANTLY FIELDING
INTERVIEWS.
YOU HAVE A PORTAL?
I DONT HAVE ACCESS TO IT.
I ALREADY FEEL LIKE CHRISTIAN
HAS A SPECIAL BOND WITH HIS DUDE
BROS.
IT MAKES ME WORRY A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT MY PLACE ON THE TRIBE.
I ALWAYS STRUGGLE KNOWING THAT
PEOPLE PROBABLY LIKE ME BUT
HAVING THAT LITTLE VOICE OF
SELF-DOUBT THAT SAYS, WELL, WHAT
IF THEY DONT.
IM NOT HAPPY WITH HOW THINGS
TURNED OUT.
GIVE YOURSELF A LITTLE TIME.
YOURE DOING OKAY.
I DONT KNOW.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHOA, WHOA.
WERE TOGETHER.
YOURE DOING FINE.
I FEEL LIKE IM ON THE
BOTTOM.
IM AFRAID TO OPEN UP TO
PEOPLE.
THEYRE SO INTIM DATING.
YOURE DOING GREAT.
YOURE SO CHARMING.
I FEEL LIKE IF WE LOSE IM GOING
TO GO.
GABBY AND I ARE PEAS IN A
POD.
WERE IN THIS TOGETHER.
WHEN I AM AT MY LOW, SHES
STRONG.
WHEN SHES AT HER LOW, IM
IM THERE TO DRY HER TEARS.
IM THERE TO TRY TO KEEP HER
HEAD IN THE GAME.
I DO MUCH BETTER WITH
VULNERABLE PEOPLE AND WEIRDOES.
I DONT WELL AROUND LIKE THESE
GOLIATHS.
THEY HAVE THEIR
VULNERABILITY, TOO, THEY JUST
DONT LIKE THE SHOW IT.
I FEEL LIKE CHRISTIAN IS SO
MUCH BETTER AT BEING CHARMING
AND BEING LIKABLE AND BEING
HIMSELF.
AND I ENVY HIM FOR THAT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THEYRE THE
COOL KIDS AT THE LUNCH TABLE.
AN IM STANDING THERE ASKING IF
I CAN SIT WITH THEM.
RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE THE ONLY
PERSON I CAN LEAN ON IS
CHRISTIAN, AND I DONT KNOW IF
THATS ENOUGH.
I FEEL LIKE IM IN A DESPERATE
POSITION BECAUSE IM SCARED OF
GOING HOME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AS NEW TRIBES.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, CARBACK --
KARA, GOT TO TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
AND TODAY TWO TRIBES WILL WIN
IMMUNITY.
HERES HOW IT WORKS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, ONE
PERSON WILL BE YOUR CALLER.
THEY WILL SIT ON A SURVIVOR
DRIVING WHEEL WHILE TWO
BLINDFOLDED TRIBE MEMBERS PUSH
THEM THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES RETRIEVING A BALL
ALONG THE WAY.
WHEN YOU REACH THE FINISH, THE
CALLER WILL GUIDE TWO MORE
BLINDFOLDED TRIBE MEMBERS AS
THEY ATTEMPT TO MANEUVER THAT
BALL THROUGH A TABLE MAZE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY.
IN ADDITION YOURE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: TODAYS REWARD IS A
WINNER-TAKE-ALL.
ONLY THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH
GETS IT, AND I THINK YOURE
GOING THE LIKE IT.
BROWNIES, PASTRY, COFFEE AND A
"SURVIVOR" DRIP, ICED COFFEE IF
YOU PREFER.
LAST TRIBE TO FINISH, TRIBAL
COUNCIL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
IMMEDIATELY GET CARL AS THEIR
NEW TRIBE MEMBER, A LOT GOING
ON.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD FOR THE
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
TO THE RIGHT, TO THE RIGHT,
TO THE RIGHT.
Jeff: EVERYBODY OUT QUICKLY
THROUGH THE FIRST OBSTACLE.
GREEN, TEVA, MAKING QUICK WORK
OF IT.
PURPLE RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
IT IS GREEN AND PURPLE.
YOURE THROUGH THE FIRST PHASE.
ORANGE REALLY STRUGGLING.
THE VUKU TRIBE WITH KARA AS THE
CALLER TAKING A LONG TIME
THROUGH THE EASIEST PART OF THIS
COURSE.
IT IS NOW TEVA AND NOW DANS GOT
TO CLIMB OVER.
I GOT IT.
STOP, STOP.
Jeff: THIS IS WHERE
COMMUNICATION IS KEY.
IT IS KARA LEADING ALEC AND
DAVIE.
HARD RIGHT.
BACK UP.
TURN RIGHT.
Jeff: GABBY TALKING TO JOHN
AND DAN.
ANGELINA TALKING TO NICK AND
NATALIE, TRYING THE MANEUVER
AROUND THE CORNER WITHOUT
FALLING OFF.
IF YOUR FEET TOUCH, YOUVE GOT
TO GO BACK.
STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
THERES A POLE HERE ON THE
RIGHT.
NATALIE, YOU OKAY?
ANGELINA, NATALIE, AND NICK
ARE STUCK.
TELL US WHAT TO DO.
STOP, STOP, STOP.
Jeff: KARA PICKING UP THE
PACE FOR VUKU IN ORANGE.
GREEN IS THROUGH THE SECOND
PHASE.
STRAIGHT.
Jeff: GABBY CONTINUES TO DO
A NICE JOB AS CALLER.
HERE COMES KARA WITH DAVIE AND
ALICE DOING THE PUSHING.
THEY ARE THROUGH THE SECOND
PHASE NOW.
GABBY NOW GETTING TO THE LAST
PART OF THE THIRD STAGE.
YOU HAVE TO UNTIE THE BAG
CONTAINING THE BALL THAT WILL
SOLVE THE TABLE MAZE.
IF ANGELINA COULD JUST GET
THROUGH THIS SECOND PHASE, THEY
CAN GET BACK IN IT.
WERE GOING TO GO OFF THE
RAMP.
Jeff: TWO TRIBES ARE
WINNING IMMUNITY.
THE REWARD IS THE BONUS, BUT
WHAT YOU WANT IS IMMUNITY.
STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
Jeff: YOURE GOOD!
GABBY IS THROUGH ALL THREE
PHASES FOR TEVA.
YES!
Jeff: GABBY IS GOING TO
LEAD CHRISTIAN AND ALISON
THROUGH THE TABLE MAZE.
SO YOUR GOING TO GO TO THE
LEFT SIDE.
ALISON DOWN.
GO STRAIGHT A LITTLE BIT.
Jeff: KARA GETTING CLOSER
TO THAT BALL, FINISHING THE
THIRD SECTION.
WATCH OUT FOR THAT POLE.
WERE THROUGH.
WERE THROUGH THIS PART.
Jeff: PURPOSELE IS THROUGH
THE THIRD PHASE, BUT THEYRE
HEADING THE WRONG DIRECTION.
ONCE AGAIN COSTING THEM TIME.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
ITS COSTING US TIME.
NATALIE, STAY CALM.
OKAY.
Jeff: KARA SITS DOWN.
SHE HAS THE BAG WITH THE BALL.
GOT TO GET ACROSS THAT FINISH.
GO.
Jeff: YOURE GOOD!
KARA CAN NOW MOVE ONED TO TABLE
MAZE.
FINALLY PURPLE IS ON THE FINAL
BEAM.
OKAY.
WE ARE AT A TRICKY PART NOW.
GO TO THE LEFT.
DO NOT DO ANYTHING OTHER THAN GO
TO THE LEFT.
Jeff: IT IS GREEN IN THE
LEAD ON THE MAZE.
ORANGE RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
PULL FORWARD.
Jeff: ANGELINA, NATALIE AND
NICK TRYING THE STAY IN IT.
WAIT.
GUYS.
IF WE CAN STAY STRAIGHT, WE GOT
THIS.
WHATS UNDER MY FOOT?
YOUR FOOT IS FINE.
Jeff: IF THEY DROP OFF THIS
BEAM, THEY HAVE TO GO BACK.
STOP.
STOP RIGHT HERE.
Jeff: ANGELINA HAS DONE A
GREAT JOB NOT GIVING UP.
GABBY CONTINUES TO PATIENTLY
LEAD CHRISTIAN AND ALISON.
BOTH PULL UP.
YEP.
Jeff: KARA DOING A NICE JOB
WITH ELIZABETH AND NATALIA.
ANGELINA HAS THE BALL.
SHES GOT TO GET ACROSS THAT
LAST LINE.
PUSH, PUSH.
Jeff: YOURE GOOD.
GO!
NOW TO THE RIGHT.
Jeff: THIS IS ALL ABOUT
TRIBE COMMUNICATION.
GREEN CONTINUES TO MAKE GREAT
PROGRESS ON THE MAZE.
ORANGE RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
ANGELINA HAS THE BALL IN THE
MAZE.
PURPLE NOW CAN GET INTO IT.
PURPLE HAS GOT TO MAKE UP SOME
TIME QUICKLY.
YOURE GOING TO GO TO THE
RIGHT AND FORWARD.
Jeff: TEVA AND GREEN VERY
CLOSE NOW ON THIS MAZE.
THEYRE IN THE FINAL SECTION.
THEYVE JUST GOT TO DROP THAT
BALL IN THAT LITTLE HOLE.
WHERES ALISON?
WATCH OUT.
Jeff: ORANGE DROPS AND HAS
TO START OVER.
A HUGE SETBACK FOR ORANGE.
THAT IS THE BREAK PURPLE NEEDED.
IT IS NOW PURPLE IN SECOND.
IT WOULD BE AN AMAZING COMEBACK.
STOP, STOP.
Jeff: GABBY TRYING THE USE
THAT FINNESS, THAT FINAL MOVE IS
SO TOUGH ON THIS TABLE MAZE.
ITS THERE, ITS THERE, ITS
THERE!
Jeff: THERE IT IS.
TEVA PULLS IT OFF.
TEL AVIVY WINS IMMUNITY AND A
HUGE REWARD.
ONE MORE IMMUNITY UP FOR GRABS.
A NICE MOVE BY PURPLE.
GETS THEM WITHIN STRIKING
DISTANCE.
IT WOULD BE A HUGE WIN FOR THE
TRIBE THAT EVERYBODY THOUGHT
WERE THE UNDERDOGS TO COME OUT
AND WIN IMMUNITY OUT OF THE GATE
WOULD SEND A BIG SIGNAL THAT
THEY ARE HERE TO PLAY.
ANOTHER NICE MOVE BY PURPLE.
THEY ARE NOW IN THE FINAL
SECTION.
CAR CRA WITH A NICE MOVE FOR
ORANGE.
WE NEED TO GO RIGHT AND THEN
FORWARD.
PERFECT, PERFECT.
Jeff: IN AND OUT FOR
PURPLE.
NATALIA, GO.
PULL!
Jeff: BIG MOVE BY ORANGE.
NATALIA DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
Jeff: VERY CLOSE THERE.
ALL AROUND IT.
CANT GET IT TO DROP.
OPENING THE DOOR FOR ORANGE TO
SLOWLY GAIN ON THEM.
ORANGE IS NOW THROUGH TO THE
FINAL SECTION.
PURPLE HAS BEEN UNABLE TO CLOSE
THE DEAL, AND WE NOW HAVE A
SHOWDOWN.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
Jeff: BOTH TRIBES WITH
THEIR BALL IN THE LAST SECTION
OF THE TABLE MAZE.
WHICH ONE WILL GET IT TO DROP
FIRST?
THROUGH.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
GO TO THE RIGHTS.
RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE,
RIGHT THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
NATALIA, DOWN.
STOP, STOP.
FORWARD.
WERE ALMOST THERE.
Jeff: PURPLE DOES IT!
JIBINI WINS IMMUNITY, SENDING
VUKU TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WOW.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
YOU GUYS DID SUCH A GOOD JOB.
Jeff: TEVA, NICE WIN OUT OF
THE GATE.
IMMUNITY.
BIG REWARD FOR TEVA AS WELL.
WELL BE WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT
CAMP.
JIBINI, CONGRATULATIONS.
JIBINI, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
THANK YOU.
THANKS, JEFF.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, VUKU, GRAB
YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THE GAME,
YOU WILL THEN INHERIT CARL,
WHICH WILL BRING YOU BACK THE
FIVE MEMBERS.
THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE DIDNT
GO AS PLANNED, BUT WE HAVE THREE
GOLIATHS AND TWO DAVIDS.
TONIGHTS TRIBAL COUNCIL IS
REALLY JUST PICK DAVIE OR
ELIZABETH.
IM SORRY, YOU GUYS.
ITS ALL RIGHT.
HONESTLY, IF I WAS CALLING,
WE WOULD HAVE STILL BEEN AT THE
FIRST PART.
I DONT THINK I WOULD HAVE
STAYED THAT CALM.
I THOUGHT WE HAD THE BEST
CHANCE OF WINNING.
I WAS SHOCKED THAT WE LOST.
COMING BACK FROM THE CHALLENGE,
I WAS THINKING, NOW THAT WE
LOST, ITS A 50/50 CHANCE I
COULD BE GOING HOME, SO ITS
REAL DISHEARTENING, BUT IM NOT
QUITTING YET, EVEN THOUGH IM
OUTNUMBERED.
YOURE NOT GOING TO GET RID OF
ME THAT EASY.
SO IM LIKE, GET YOU BUTT IN
GEAR AND GO TRY TO FIND THAT
IDOL.
ELIZABETH WAS LIKE, DAVID, WE
HAVE TO GO RIGHT NOW, I THINK I
KNOW WHERE THE IDOL IS.
SHE DOESNT KNOW WHERE THE IDOL,
IS BECAUSE I HAVE THE IDOL.
IVE HAD IT SINCE DAY FIVE.
THEYRE GOING TO BE UNITED.
I DONT TRUST THEM AS FAR AS I
CAN THROW THEM.
IT WOULD BE MY VOTE TO GET RID
OF NATALIA.
THAT WORKS FOR ME.
ELIZABETH WANTS TO TRY TO GET
RID OF NATALIA.
BUT MY GUT IS TELLING ME THOSE
THREE GOLIATHS ARE SOLID RIGHT
NOW.
LUCKILY WITH MY IDOL I DO HAVE A
SAFETY NET, BUT I DONT WANT THE
USE THAT THIS EARLY IN THE GAME.
I DONT KNOW, MAN, ITS
LOOKING LIKE PLAN "B."
AS SOON AS YOU GUYS WENT DOWN,
THERE SHE TOOK OFF.
SHES LIKE, DAVID, I GOT TO GO,
I THINK I KNOW WHERE THE IDOL
IS.
THERE WAS NOTHING THERE.
HE THINKS THAT ME AND HER ARE
STILL TOGETHER.
OUR PLAN IS FIND THE IDOL.
THATS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
PLAN "B" WAS TO VOTE YOU OUT
BECAUSE SHE DOESNT TRUST YOU.
SHES A THREAT.
I KNOW.
I ALREADY KNEW SHE WAS A THREAT.
AND I DONT WANT YOU GUYS TO
FEEL LIKE IM JUST TELLING YOU
ALL THIS INFORMATION BECAUSE IM
DESPERATE.
NO, NO, NO.
IM TRYING TO WORK WITH YOU
GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
AWESOME.
IF THERE WAS ANY DOUBT WHO
NEEDS TO GO, ITS GONE.
ELIZABETH IS A THREAT TO ME.
SHES GETTING CLOSE TO KARA, MY
ALLY.
SHES ALSO TALKING ABOUT VOTING
ME OUT.
SO IM LIKE, GET THIS GIRL OUT.
SHE NEEDS TO GO.
ITS TIME TO TURN THIS GAME
ON ITS HEAD.
I NEED SOMEBODY THATS SMART ON
THIS SIDE, SO IN ORDER TO WIN
THIS GAME, YOU HAVE TO HAVE A
RESUME, IF YOU CHOOSE TO STAY
WITH THE FLIETS, YOU GOT A LOT
OF MUSCLE AND A LOT OF BRAIN TO
GO THROUGH.
YEAH.
WITHOUT AN IDOL, I NEED TO
FLIP WAS ON THOSE GOLIATHS.
I FEEL LIKE ALEX MIGHT BE MY
BETTER OPTION.
IF YOU WERE TO VOTE OUT ONE OF
THE GOLIATHS, THAT COULD BE YOU
SAYING, HEY, I LED THAT CHARGE,
I HAD THE BALLS ENOUGH TO JUMP
SHIP.
YEAH.
ITS HARD FOR ME, BECAUSE IF
I WERE TO MAKE A MOVE AND FLIP,
THAT SAYS A LOT TO THE PEOPLE ON
THE OTHER TRIBES.
AND I KIND OF SHOW MY CARDS.
IM WILLING TO DO ANYTHING
HONESTLY.
OR EVEN IF WE JUST VOTE OUT
DAVIE.
SO YOU WOULD JUST PUT DAVIE.
YEAH.
ILL PUT DAVIE.
ALEX IS VERY CARE INFORMAL WHAT
HE SAYS OAR WHAT HE DOESNT SAY.
I DONT KNOW WHATS GOING ON
INSIDE HIS HEAD.
AT THIS POINT TO SAVE MY AS, IT
BECAME CLEAR I HAD THE WRITE
DAVIES NAME DOWN TONIGHT.
HERES WHAT I WAS THINKING
ABOUT.
IF WE VOTE DAVIE OUT, IM JUST
SAYING, WEIGHING OUR OPTIONS --
ITS WORSE FOR HER TO STAY IN
THE GAME.
SHE WOULD BE PRETENDING TO WORK
US WITH.
DAVIE, WE CAN MOLD HIM TO WORK
WITH US AND HELL BRING IN CARL
BECAUSE THEYRE ON THE OUTS,
THEY DONT HAVE ANY OTHER
PEOPLE.
NO MATTER WHAT, WE STILL HAVE
THE MAJORITY.
ITS GOOD TO THINK THROUGH
THINGS.
FOR SURE.
IN MY OPINION, DAVIE IS A
BIGGER THREAT.
BUT NATALIA, SHE HAS TO HAVE IT
HER WAY, SO I FEEL LIKE IM NOT
HAVING MY OPINION HEARD.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW, WE HAVE
EACH OTHERS TRUST, RIGHT?
YES.
DO YOU THINK OR NO?
YEAH, I AGREE.
I THINK --
I NEED CONFIRMATION, ALEC.
I JUST FREAK OUT IF I DONT HEAR
IT.
I GET THE FEELING THAT
NATALIA DOESNT REALLY TRUST ME,
WHICH MAKES WORKING WITH HER
DIFFICULT.
SO I DONT KNOW.
ITS TOUGH.
DAVIE, DO YOU SWEAR YOUR WITH
US?
YEAH.
BECAUSE IF YOU DONT VOTE
WITH US, YOU HAVE NO FUTURE IN
THIS GAME.
SO YOURE GOING TO VOTE FOR HER,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU TWO SHUT UP.
SHE DOESNT NEED TO BULLY
DAVIE INTO VOTING.
I KNOW.
SHE THINKS SHES SO SMART.
ALL THREE OF THEM TOGETHER
DONT SEEM AS TIGHT AS THEY WANT
US TO THINK THEY ARE.
SO NOW IM WONDERING IF ALEC
MIGHT LISTEN TO ANOTHER PLAN.
YOU THINK THIS IS THE RIGHT
MOMENT.
, BRO?
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE.
ELIZABETH WANTS TO VOTE FOR
NATALIA.
VOTING OUT NATALIA, ITS A
BIG RISK, BUT THE THING IS,
NATALIA IS REALLY BOSSY.
SHES BEEN BARKING ORDERS AT
CAMP.
AND HONESTLY, ITS PISSING ME
OFF.
YOU TOTALLY TRUST THESE
GIRLS, RIGHT?
IM WITH YOU.
IS YOU GET A FUNNY FEELING
DURING TRIBAL, YOU NEED TO MAKE
SOME EYE CONTACT WITH ME AND LET
ME KNOW.
I HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION, DO
I STICK WITH THE NUMBERS AND GET
RID OF LICKS, OR DO I MAKE A BIG
MOVE?
THE THING IS IF I FLIP, CARL
WILL COME BACK AND THEN THE
DAVIDS WOULD HAVE THE NUMBERS.
SO I DONT KNOW.
ITS EXACTLY LIKE SURFING.
IF YOURE PADDLING FOR A WAVE
AND YOURE NOT FULLY COMMITTED,
YOULL PROBABLY GO OVER THE
FALLS, AND THIS COULD BLOW UP MY
ENTIRE GAME.
SO I GOT TO THINK ABOUT WHAT IM
GOING TO DO, AND ITS GOING TO
BE SOMETHING THAT HAPPENS ON THE
SPOT AT TRIBAL.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
CARL RETURNING FROM EXILE
ISLAND.
CARL WILL BE LISTENING IN AND
THEN GOING BACK TO CAMP AFTER
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO CLOSE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YOU GUYS LOST.
YOU GET BACK THE CAMP.
YOU HAVE FLEE DPLIEETHS AND ONLY
TWO DAVIDS.
NATALIA, WAS IT CLEAR IT WOULD
BE AN EASY VOTE, ITS DAVIE OR
ITS ELIZABETH.
EXACTLY.
OBVIOUSLY THE THREE GOLIATHS
NEEDED TO CHAT, TO SEE WHERE OUR
HEADS ARE AT.
WE DID.
HOW CONCERNED ARE YOU,
ELIZABETH?
IM CONCERNED, MAN.
I WAS ABOUT READY TO POOP MY
PANTS TODAY, NOT GOING THE LIE.
IM HOPING THAT THEYLL THROW ME
A BONE, BECAUSE OF MY CHARACTER
AND THE FACT THAT IM LOYAL AND
ONCE YOU GET ME ON YOUR SIDE,
IM THERE FOR THE LONG HAUL.
Jeff: DAVIE, DID YOU TRY TO
PLEAD YOUR CASE TODAY?
YEAH, ABSOLUTELY, JEFF.
LISTEN, LICKS GOT THREE KIDS,
FAMILY, SHE DIDNT COME FROM
MUCH.
SHES GOT A GOOD STORY IF SHE
MAKES IT TO THE FINAL TRIBAL.
SHE COULD BEAT EM ALL.
ALSO, SHES GOT A LOT OF FRIENDS
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
I WAS BLINDSIDED ON THE FIRST
VOTE.
Jeff: BOY, ELIZABETH,
DAVIES GAME IS VERY CLEAR,
THROW YOU UNDER THE BUS WITH
EVERY COMMENT THAT HE CAN.
YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
Jeff: NATALIA, HAS THE GAME
KICKED FULL IN OR ARE WE STILL
HOVERING AROUND IT?
NO, THE GAME HAS STARTED.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU HAVE A TRIBE OF
FIVE PEOPLE AND YOU LOSE, YOU
GOT TO START PLAYING.
AND TO BE HONEST WITH YOU, JEFF,
IM EXCITED TO PLAY THIS GAME.
IM EXCITED TO COME TO TRIBAL
AND EXPERIENCE EVERYTHING THAT I
CAN.
I MEAN, IF I GO HOME TONIGHT,
GUNS ABLAZING, IM HAPPY.
Jeff: ELIZABETH, THAT IS
THE MARK OF THE MODERN
"SURVIVOR" PLAYER, WHICH IS IF I
GO DOWN, I WANT TO BURN OUT
RATHER THAN FADE AWAY.
Jeff: YEAH, YOU GOT TO
START PLAYING THE WIN FROM THE
MOMENT YOU FIRST GET YOUR BUFF.
THAT INCLUDES TONIGHT.
YOU GOT TO BE WILLING TO HAVE
SOME BALLS AND MAKE BIG MOVES.
YOU CANT JUST MAKE THE SIMPLE,
EASY MOVES AND HAVE A RESUME AT
THE END OF THE GAME.
Jeff: NATALIA, THAT IS THE
BEST THING ELIZABETH COULD EVER
SAY IN THIS SITUATION AT TRIBAL
IS TO PUSH THE BIG MOVE AND SAY
ONE OF YOU GUYS SHOULD DO
SOMETHING.
ELIZABETH, NOT GOING THE LIE,
IS DESPERATE, BUT HOW THE ONE
"SURVIVOR" IS MAKING BIG MOVES.
ITS JUST DECIDING WHEN TO MAKE
THOSE WIG MOVES.
AND YOU CAN WAIT UNTIL ITS
TOO LATE AND FIGURE OUT LATER, I
SHOULD HAVE MADE A MOVE THEN.
I THINK TONIGHT WILL BE A HUGE
DETERMINING FACTOR IN WHO WILL
BE SITTING AT THAT FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
Jeff: NATALIA, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF THIS?
I DONT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
IM JUST MAKING SURE
EVERYONES ON THE SAME PAGE.
NO.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
I THINK ITS UNEASY BECAUSE
WE HAD A PLAN GOING INTO IT.
WE HAD A PLAN, AND HIM DOING
THAT IS TOTALLY NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE PLAN.
I TRUST HIM.
IM GOOD.
Jeff: NATALIA, ITS AS IF
YOURE PROCESSING IT BEHIND YOUR
EYES.
IS THAT TENSION NEAR TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT THIS COULD MEAN.
YES, IT IS.
IM NOT OKAY WITH WHAT HAPPENED
RIGHT NOW.
ITS THE SAME THING, RIGHT?
YES.
Jeff: DAVIE, NOBODY TALKED
TO YOU.
NO ONE TALKED TO ME.
I DONT KNOW IF THATS A GOOD
THING OR A BAD THING.
BUT I GUESS WERE ABOUT TO SEE.
Jeff: ELIZABETH, THIS IS
"SURVIVOR."
SURE ENOUGH IS.
Jeff: THIS IS WHAT YOU
DREAM ABOUT.
WHEN YOURE SITTING ON THE
COUCH, ITS EXCITING TO WATCH.
WHEN YOURE SITTING RIGHT HERE,
ITS NOT SO MUCH EXCITING, ITS
LIKE --.
Jeff: REASSURING GOING ON.
LETS GO.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
NATALIA, YOURE UP.
IM JUST GOING TO BE REAL
WITH YOU.
I DONT TRUST YOU AND I DONT
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
I REALLY DONT KNOW WHAT JUST
HAPPENED.
SO SORRY.
Jeff: IM GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE ELIZABETH.
DAVIE.
NATALIA.
THATS ONE VOTE ELIZABETH, ONE
VOTE DAVIE, ONE VOTE NATALIA.
NATALIA.
THATS TWO VOTES NATALIA, ONE
VOTE ELIZABETH, ONE VOTE DAVIE,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR,"
NATALIA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW I COULDNT TRUST YOU.
IM SORRY.
DONT BE SORRY.
SHUT UP.
WHERE DO I PUT THIS?
Jeff: NATALIA, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
DID YOU KNOW?
ME?
NO.
WHY ARE YOU SMILING?
OH, MY GOD.
I CANT HANDLE YOU RIGHT NOW.
ITS A GAME.
Jeff: WELL, IT DOESNT
MATTER THE NUMBER OF DAYS INTO
THE GAME OR THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
ON A TRIBE, THERES ALWAYS AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR A BIG MOVE.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
CARL, A BUFF WILL BE WAITING FOR
YOU BECOME AT CAMP.
YES, SIR.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," THERES NOWHERE TO
RUN.
I TRUST MY GUT.
ALEX MIND SIDED ME.
THIS WAS NOT SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: NOWHERE TO HIDE.
SHE HAS A MASTERS IN
UNGRACIOUSNESS.
IM READY FOR SURVIVOR
WITHOUT NATALIE.
Jeff: BECAUSE THE STORM IS
COMING.
THATS THE GOLIATH.
IM JUST UPSET BECAUSE I KNEW
THE SECOND WE GOT TO THIS TRIBE
THERE WAS A SHIFT IN ALEC.
I SHOULD HAVE WENT WITH MY GUT
AND I DID NOT GO WITH MY GUT.
I THINK I SHOULD HAVE MADE A BIG
MOVE AND CONTINUOUSLY MAKE A BIG
MOVE AND I PLAYED A STUPID GAME
TONIGHT.
IM JUST PISSED.
I WANT TO HURT HIM SO BAD.