Jeff: WELCOME TO THE SEASON
FINALE OF "SURVIVOR: DAVID VS.
GOLIATH," OUR 37th SEASON,
AND IT HAS BEEN ONE OF OUR MOST
POPULAR.
LETS SAY HELLO TO THE PLAYERS
WHO HAVE MADE IT SO FUN TO
WATCH, THE PAINFUL, EARLY
VOTEOUTS BEFORE YOU REALLY EVER
GET YOUR FOOTING.PAT, JESSICA,
BEE, NATALIA, NATALE, LYRISA
OUR JURY SO FAR, ELIZABETH,
JOHN, DAN, CARL, GABBY, AND
CHRISTIAN VOTED OUT LAST WEEK.
AND WHERE THE MONEY IS, THE
FINAL SIX, TWO DAVID, DAVIE AND
NICK, FOUR GOLIATH, KARA,
ANGELINA, ALISON, AND MIKE.
THREE OF THESE WILL TAKE IT TO
THE JURY SIDE.
THREE OF THESE WILL MAKE IT TO
THE END WITH A SHOT THE WIN.
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
A FUN FINALE NIGHT.
AND I JUST WANT TO ADDRESS THE
PARENTS.
WE KNOW ITS A SCHOOL NIGHT, SO
THANK YOU FOR LETTING YOUR KIDS
STAY UP A LITTLE LATER TONIGHT.
THANKS TO ALL THE FAMILIES FROM
OUT OF TOWN WHO HAVE THEIR KIDS
HERE TONIGHT.
I LOVE.
THIS WE MAKE THIS SHOW FOR
FAMILIES.
WE LOVE IT WHEN YOU WATCH
TOGETHER.
AND FOR ALL YOU YOUNG VIEWERS
WHO DREAM OF BEING ON THE ISLAND
ONE DAY, IT CAN HAPPEN.
IT HAPPENED WITH DAVIE.
HES BEEN WATCHING SINCE HE WAS
EIGHT.
OKAY.
LETS GET TO IT.
ITS THE FINALE: "SURVIVOR:
DAVID VS. GOLIATH."
FOR OUR 37th SEASON, 20
PLAYERS WERE DIVIDED INTO TWO
TRIBES.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: DAVID
VS. GOLIATH."
LETS GO!
COME ON.
Jeff: FOR 35 DAYS IT HAS
BEEN A BATTLE.
OH, MY GOD.
FOR YOUR SAFETY, WERE GOING
TO EVACUATE YOU FROM YOUR
ISLAND.
Jeff: WITH EVER-CHANGING
ALLIANCES.
I WANT TO PLAY MY NUMBER-ONE
ALLY.
Jeff: LEADING
OF STUNNING BLINDSIDES.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND BASED ON THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL --
I DONT KNOW.
I THINK WERE STILL GOING
100mph.
Jeff: -- THIS BATTLE SHOWS
NO SIGNS OF SLOWING DOWN.
NOW ONLY SIX REMAIN.
FOUR GOLIATHS -- KARA, MIKE,
ALISON, AND ANGELINA.
AND TWO DAVIDS -- NICK AND
DAVIE.
ITS THE FINALE OF "SURVIVOR:
DAVID VS. GOLIATH."
THE DAVIDS HAVE BEEN UNDER
THE GUN FROM THE GET-GO.
BECAUSE OF IT THEYVE GOTTEN
CRAFTY, FINDING IDOLS LEFT AN
RIGHT.
NOW THAT THE END IS IN SIGHT,
AND SINCE IDOLS WERE PLAYED AT
THE LAST TRIBAL, THAT MEANS
EVERYONE IS PANICKING, RUNNING
DOWN THE BEACH, LOOKING FOR MY
IDOLS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT EVERYONE IS
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL, BUT I WANT
THAT IDOL FOR MYSELF.
THIS IS A SCAVENGER HUNT WITH
BIG STAKES, BIG STAKES, $1
MILLION STAKES, LIKE GO LOOK,
GET OUT OF THE SHELTER, GET OFF
THE HAMMOCK, GO LOOK FOR AN
IDOL.
I AM THE ONE IN THE HOT SEAT.
MY NAME HAS BEEN OUT THERE FOR
THE LAST THREE TRIBAL COUNCILS.
I KNOW THERE HAS TO BE AN IDOL
OUT HERE.
I WANT IT.
I HAVE TO BE IN CHARGE OF MY OWN
DESTINY OUT HERE.
ANY LUCK?
NO LUCK ON THIS END.
WHAT ABOUT YALL?
NO.
YOURE SWEATING LIKE HELL.
OH, MY GOD.
CONGRATULATION, YOU HAVE FOUND A
CLUE TO A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
YOU WILL HAVE TO WORK FAST.
THE IDOL IS AT THE TOP OF THE
RUNG.
THERE IS A LADDER TO RETRIEVE
THE IDOL.
GOOD LUCK.
OH, MY GOSH.
I FOUND
THE
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, BUT THIS ONE IS
GOING TO BE A TRICKY ONE TO
FIND.
YOU KNOW, HOW BIG IS THIS
LADDER?
HOW TALL IS THIS ROCK?
HOW DO I GET THIS LADDER?
OH, MY GOSH.
MAKE SURE NO ONE IS COMING.
OKAY.
SO, OF COURSE, THIS LADDER IS
PROBABLY LIKE EIGHT FEET TALL.
I WAS THINKING, I DONT KNOW, A
STEP STOOL OR SOMETHING, BUT
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
THIS IS THE FINAL SIX.
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE, RIGHT?
SO I HIDE MY LADDER AND I WALK
BACK UP TO THE WELL, BECAUSE I
NEEDED TO SCOUT OUT THE AREA.
OH, MY GOD.
I REALIZE THAT THE CLUE HAS
FALLEN OUT OF MY BRA AT SOME
POINT.
THIS IS SUCH AN AMATEUR THING TO
DO, LOSE YOUR CLUE?
LIKE ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IM FEELING LIKE SUCH A NEWB.
I HAVE NO DO IT NOW IF I LOST
THE CLUE, BECAUSE IF SOMEONE
ELSE FINDS THE CLUE AND FINDS
THE LADDER, THEY GET IT.
IM SCREWED.
I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO MAKE MY
MAD DASH TO THIS ROCK AND FIND
MY IDOL NOW.
IM LOOKING AROUND THE WELL.
THERE IS ONE HUGE ROCK WALL.
ALL RIGHT.
IM USING THE LADDER.
IM CLIMBING THIS ROCK WALL.
AN IM GOING TO FIND THIS IDOL.
OUCH.
OH, MY GOD.
IM LIKE LITERALLY STUCK IN
HERE.
I THINK I WENT TOO FAR.
SO I CLIMBED TOO HIGH.
NOW IM STUCK.
AND IM TRYING TO GET DOWN
SAFELY.
BUT ITS SUPER STEEP.
ITS A CLIFF.
SO I HAVE TO GET BACK DOWN SO I
CAN FIND THE IDOL AND GET OUT OF
HERE.
I FEEL LIKE IM SEEING THINGS
THAT ARENT THERE BECAUSE IM
LOOKING SO HARD.
SO THERES NO IDOL UP THERE.
FINALLY I BARELY MADE IT DOWN.
I COULD HAVE DIED.
I TAKE MY LADDER.
I PUT IT BACK INTO HIDING JUST
IN THE NICK OF TIME, BECAUSE I
COME BACK TO THE WELL, AND
PEOPLE ARE THERE.
SO I HAVE TO COME UP WITH
SOMETHING, BECAUSE I CANT JUST
BE LIKE, HEY, GUY, IM HANGING
OUT BY THE WELL, BECAUSE THEYRE
GOING THE SEE RIGHT THROUGH
THAT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, NO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I FELL REALLY BAD.
YOU FELL ON YOUR BACK?
WHAT HURTS?
OH, MY GOD.
IM SO SORRY.
I START TO CRY.
I TELL THEM THAT I HAD FALLEN
FROM A TREE.
IM SO GLAD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
WHAT DID YOU HIT?
I JUST LEAN INTO ALL OF THEM.
I HAVE ALISON CHECK ME FOR
BRUISES.
OKAY.
I DONT SEE ANYTHING.
IM SORRY.
NICK IS GIVING ME A HUG.
DAVIE IS GIVING ME A HUG.
IM LIKE, CAN YOU GUYS STAY WITH
ME.
I FEEL LIGHT-HEADED.
I WAS JUST LIKE IN A DAZE.
OH.
I THINK EVERYONE BOUGHT IT.
SO AT THIS POINT I HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO COME BACK
THE FIND THIS IDOL.
ITS MY IDOL, AND I WILL NOT
STOP AT ANYTHING UNTIL I FIND
IT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, MIKE, GOT
THE TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BECOME UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING THE RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES.
YOULL THEN USE A BALL TO HOOK A
TARGET, RELEASING PUZZLE STEPS.
YOU WILL USE THOSE STEPS TO
ASSEMBLE A STAIRCASE AND RACE TO
THE TOP, WHERE YOU WILL SOLVE A
63-PIECE "SURVIVOR" PUZZLE.
OH, MY GOD.
WOW.
Jeff: FIRST TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT IN
THE FINAL FIVE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODYS ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
ADVENTURE AND A SHOT AT THE $1
MILLION WILL COME TO AN END.
IN ADDITION, PLAYING FOR REWARD.
REALLY?
HERE WE GO.
Jeff: YEAH.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WILL
ENJOY BACK AT CAMP SPAGHETTI.
MMM.
Jeff: MEAT SAUCE AND
VEGETARIAN, GARLIC BREAD AND
CAKE FOR DESSERT.
THERE IT IS.
Jeff: AT THIS POINT IN THE
GAME, ANY FOOD IS FUEL FOR YOUR
BODY, AN YOUR TANKS ARE ON
EMPTY.
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
YES.
Jeff: GO!
YOU GOT TO GET OVER THESE FIRST
OBSTACLES.
THIS IS WHAT 36 DAYS LOOKS LIKE.
DAVIE AND NICK VERY QUICK.
MIKE AND ANGELINA TAKING A
LITTLE LONGER.
THATS OKAY.
WE ARE EARLY IN THIS CHALLENGE.
NOW YOUVE GOT TO TOSS THAT BALL
AND GET IT IN THE TARGET TO
RELEASE YOUR PUZZLE PIECES.
OH, DAMMIT.
Jeff: MIKE GOING FOR IT.
MIKE JUST SHORT.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE ENOUGH ROPE TO
GET THERE.
KARA RELEASES HERS.
SHES GOOD.
DAVIE CATCHES HIS.
HES GOOD.
IT IS NOW DAVIE AND KARA
STARTING TO WORK ON THEIR PUZZLE
STAIRCASE.
DAMMIT.
Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE STILL
TRYING THE HOOK THAT TARGET.
ANGELINAS GOOD.
NICK IS GOOD.
MIKES GOT HIS.
PULL IT.
THATS HOW YOU DO IT.
IT IS NOW ALISON THE ONLY PLAYER
LEFT WHO HAS NOT HOOKED HER
TARGET.
NICK HAS HIS FIRST PIECE IN THE
STAIRCASE.
THE STAIRCASE IS ANOTHER PUZZLE
TO SOLVE.
THERE IS ONE PIECE FOR EACH
STEP, AND YOU HAVE TO GO IN
ORDER.
KARA HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
NICK WRONG, GOT TO GO BACK.
ANGELINA HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
ALISON STILL FIGHTING TO GET IN
THIS.
MIKE HAS HIS FIRST PIECE.
KARA COMING BACK WITH HER THIRD.
SHES RIGHT.
DAVIE HAS HIS FIRST.
ALISON HOOKS HER TARGET.
ALISON IS GOOD.
SHES BACK IN IT NOW.
KARA WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
IT IS KARA IN THE EARLY LEAD
FOLLOWED BY MIKE ON HER TAIL.
ALISON HAS HER FIRST PIECE.
NICK COMES BACK WITH HIS SECOND
PIECE.
ITS RIGHT.
HERE COMES MIKE.
KARAS RIGHT.
MIKE IS RIGHT.
IT IS STILL RIGHT NOW A SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN KARA AND MIKE WITH
ANGELINA RIGHT BEHIND.
HERES DAVIE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
IS HE RIGHT?
YES.
DAY 36, EVERYBODY FIGHTING TO
STAY IN THIS GAME.
KARA NOW EXTENDING HER LEAD.
HERE COMES ANGELINA NOW.
SHES ON KARAS TAIL.
NICK NOW FALLING BEHIND.
DAVIE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
MIKE WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
KARA DOWN TO HER LAST PIECE.
SHE WILL BE THE FIRST TO GET TO
HER PUZZLE.
KARAS DONE.
IT IS KARA NOW WITH THE EARLY
ADVANTAGE.
ALREADY STARTING TO SOLVE THAT
63-PIECE PUZZLE.
DAVIE HAS HIS LAST PIECE.
DAVIES GOOD.
HE CAN START WORKING ON HIS
PUZZLE.
ANGELINA COMING BACK WITH HER
LAST PIECE.
MIKE HAS HIS LAST PIECE.
HE CAN START WORKING ON HIS
PUZZLE.
ALISON STILL FIGHTING.
NICK STILL FIGHTING.
ANGELINA CAN WORK ON HER PUZZLE.
WEVE GOT FOUR PEOPLE NOW ON THE
PUZZLE.
ANGELINA, KARA, DAVIE, AND MIKE.
TWO PEOPLE STILL TRYING TO GET
UP HERE.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
IT IS A MONSTER OF A PUZZLE.
NICK IS UP WITH HIS FINAL PIECE
IN THE STAIRCASE.
NICK NOW CAN START WORKING ON
HIS PUZZLE.
IT IS JUST ALISON NOW.
SHE CONTINUES TO FIGHT FOR HER
SHOT IN THIS GAME WITH TRIBAL
COUNCIL ON THE LINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOURE SOLVING.
IT IS THE LOGO OF THIS SEASON.
YOURE WEARING IT ON YOUR BUFF.
ALISON IS UP.
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THEIR
PUZZLE.
ALISON HAS A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
UP.
NICK WITH A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
IT WOULD BE A HUGE
COME-FROM-BEHIND WIN IF ALISON
OR NICK COULD PULL THIS OUT.
KARA HAS BEEN IN THE LEAD FROM
THE BEGINNING.
SHES GOT TO THE PUZZLE FIRST
AND HAS HAD THE MOST TIME ON THE
PUZZLE.
ANGELINA RIGHT ON HER TAIL.
MIKE IS IN THIS.
NICK CONTINUES TO FIGHT PIECE BY
PIECE TO STAY IN IT.
THIS IS YOUR SPECIALTY, IT WILL
COME IN VERY HANDY RIGHT NOW.
KARAS PUZZLE REALLY COMING
TOGETHER NOW.
KARA AND ANGELINA SIDE BY SIDE
AND NECK AND NECK IN THIS
CHALLENGE NOW.
THEY ARE THE LEADERS.
NICK HAS PIECES ALL OVER THE
PLACE, BUT THAT PUZZLE IS COMING
TOGETHER.
DAVIE INVESTIGATE DOWN.
MIKE WITH MORE PROGRESS AND
ANOTHER PIECE.
ALISON SLOWING DOWN NOW.
YOU NEED TO KEEP FIGHTING RIGHT
NOW, BECAUSE YOU ARE IN IT.
YOU GOT A SHOT TO WIN IT.
THIS IS WHAT YOU DREAM OF, THAT
NECKLACE ON DAY 36 WOULD BE SO
NICE.
NICK IS IN IT NOW.
WOW.
HES MADE UP A LOT OF TIME.
ONE OF THE MOST COMPETITIVE
PUZZLES I CAN REMEMBER.
SOMEBODYS GOING TO GET ON A
ROLL HERE AND PULL THIS OUT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS VERY CLOSE.
IT IS ANGELINA, KARA, MIKE, AND
NICK FIGHTING FOR IMMOUNTY WITH
ONLY A FEW PIECES LEFT.
WHEN YOU HAVE IT, STEP BACK AND
YELL.
YOU GOT TO LET ME KNOW.
KARA STRUGGLES TO FIND ANOTHER
PIECE.
MIKE HAS ANOTHER PIECE.
ANGELINA DOWN TO FOUR PIECES
LEFT.
NICK WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
NICK DOWN TO HIS LAST FEW
PIECES.
AND ANOTHER AND ANOTHER.
JEFF, JEFF, JEFF!
Jeff: NICK WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
YEAH, BABY.
Jeff: GUARANTEED A SPOT IN
THE FINAL FIVE.
WOW.
WHAT A FINISH.
THAT WAS AS CLOSE AS YOU COULD
GET.
WOW.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
NICELY DONE.
Jeff: HUGE COME-FROM-BEHIND
VICTORY FOR NICK.
NICK, COME ON OVER.
THIS HAS BEEN MY DREAM FOR A
VERY LONG TIME.
Jeff: CONGRATULATIONS.
SMILE.
THATS GOING TO BE MY PROFILE
PIC.
Jeff: NICK SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
YOU ARE GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FIVE.
IN ADDITION YOU HAVE WON REWARD.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO JOIN YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
OH, GOSH.
WELL, YOU SAID THERE WOULD BE
VEGETARIAN STUFF IN THERE, IM
NOT GOING TO DO MUCH WITH THAT,
SO IM GOING TO PICK ANGELINA TO
TAKE CARE OF THAT HALF FOR ME.
ILL TAKE CARE OF THE MEAT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE CHOICE INCH
DOING SO, YOURE GOING TO BRING
ONE PERSON WITH YOU.
IM A VEGETARIAN, TOO.
Jeff: YOU WILL BRING THREE
PEOPLE WITH YOU, THREE PEOPLE
WILL BE LEFT BACK AT CAMP.
IM TELLING HIM, HE DOESNT
NEED TO PICK ME.
HE ALREADY PICKED ME FOR THE
FAMILY VISIT.
I DO APPRECIATE YOU SAYING,
THAT DAVIE.
WITH THAT CASE, IM GOING TO
HAVE TO CHOOSE MIKE.
IM SORRY TO
Jeff: MY JABENI CREW.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: ALISON, THIS IS
BECOMING A COMMON STORY.
ONCE AGAIN NOT CHOSEN.
YOU KNOW, IM CLAWING MY WAY
THROUGH THIS GAME, AND IM VERY
HUNGRY RIGHT NOW.
THEY ALL KNOW THAT.
IM A BAG OF BONES, BUT IM
STILL HERE, SO IM STILL
SMILING.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERES WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN.
NICK, BACK AT CAMP, YOU,
ANGELINA, AND MIKE WILL ENJOY
SPAGHETTI, MEAT AND VEGETARIAN,
GARLIC BREAD, CAKE, WINE.
ALISON, KARA, DAVIE, NOTHING FOR
YOU.
THE BIGGER PICTURE, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, WHERE ONE OF
THE FIVE OF YOU WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
IT WONT BE YOU.
CONGRATS.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
NO GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
IT WAS CRUSHING TO LOSE AND
NOT GO ON REWARD BECAUSE IM
JUST THE PERSON LEFT BEHIND
EVERY TIME.
GOD, IT IS HARD TO CONSTANTLY BE
THE ONE IN THE CROSS-FIRE.
BEAUTIFUL.
I WALK INTO THE REWARD, AND
WHERE ARE WE BUT THE WATERWELL.
I KNOW THAT THE IDOL IS IN
PROXIMITY, AND I LOST MY CLUE,
SO I CANT REALLY RECALL THE
LITTLE DETAILS.
IM NOT SURE EXACTLY WHERE IT
IS.
THE FOOD IS HONESTLY BARELY ON
MY MIND AT THIS POINT.
JUST WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
UH-HUH.
GUYS, LETS GET A CHEERS
GOING HERE.
OH, YEAH, BABY.
LIFE IS GOOD.
CHEERS, CHEERS, CHEERS.
SURE, THEYRE SITTING THERE
PLOTTING OUR DEMISE.
I MEAN, I WANT TO THINK THAT
NICK HAS MY BACK ON THAT REWARD,
BUT THAT JABENI STRONG THING IS
SCARY.
THAT IS SCARY.
IM HOPING THAT ALISON WILL
BE THE ONE TO GO, BUT IM
VULNERABLE URGE AS WELL.
I DONT HAVE AN IDOL, BUT AT
LEAST I DO HAVE NICK IN THIS
GAME, WHO I CAN NOW SAY I REALLY
TRUST.
WE KNOW WEVE GOT EACH OTHERS
BACK.
DAMN, I CAN HEAR THEM LAUGHING
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU ARE MY BROTHERS.
CAN WE HAVE CAKE FIRST?
UH-HUH.
WEVE BEEN TOGETHER SINCE
JABENI.
I WANT TO BE NEXT TO YOU TWO,
AND ITS NOT BECAUSE I THINK WE
CAN BEAT YOU, ITS BECAUSE WE
PLAYED DIFFERENT GAMES AND I
THINK WE ALL HAVE A SHOT.
WHAT WOULD GET THE THREE OF US
THERE AND WORK BACKWARD?
I THINK ALISON FIRST, IN MY
OPINION.
I FEEL SIMILARLY, SO THIS CAN
BE THE ALISON SMACKDOWN.
IF IT WAS UP TO ME, I FEEL
LIKE I WOULD TAKE OUT DAVIE.
I GENERALLY SEE DAVIE WINNING IF
HE GETS TO THE END.
I DONT THINK DAVIE WOULD GET
THAT MANY VOTES.
I JUST WANT TO GET RID OF
ALISON.
I KNOW.
OKAY.
IM FINE TO SEND ALISON HOME.
IVE BASICALLY HAD TO PUT MY
FOOT DOWN.
I WANTED ALISON GONE FOREVER.
DAVIE HAS GOT TO STAY HERE.
WERE A TIGHT TWO, AND I CANT
WITH B THE ONLY DAVID WHEN
THERES FIVE PEOPLE LEFT.
IF I DONT WIN THIS TOMORROW AND
IM THE ONLY DAVID, THERES A
GOOD CHANCE ILL BE GOING HOME.
WELL, I GAVE MY WORD, SO IM
STICKING WITH IT.
IT WILL BE ALISON UNLESS SHE
PLAYS AN IDOL.
ALISON COULD ALREADY HAVE IT.
I DONT THINK SHE DOES.
DO YOU?
OKAY, GUYS, I GOT TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING?
IT HAS TO STAY HERE.
PROMISE?
UH-HUH.
I FOUND A CLUE THIS MORNING.
THERE WAS A CLUE.
THERES A LADDER I DUG UP.
IT SAID THAT IT WAS IN THE ROCK
BEHIND THE WELL.
I GOT TO THE HIGHEST POINT AND I
WAS STUCK.
I COULD HAVE SLIPPED AND JUST
FALLEN OFF.
I LITERALLY COULD HAVE DIED THIS
MORNING LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
I DONT KNOW.
I NEED YOUR BRAINS, AND PLEASE,
THIS IS JUST US, NO ONE ELSE.
OF COURSE.
NO ONE ELSE.
NOTHING.
GIVEN THE BIG LADDER AND
LOSING THE CLUE, I RECOGNIZE I
NEED A LITTLE BIT OF HELP FROM
MY FRIENDS.
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED THE START MOVING.
SORRY TO TAKE US FROM THE FOOD.
WHAT?
COME.
IM COMING.
HOLD ON.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHERE THE
LADDER IS.
ITS LIKE A JOB.
WE BASICALLY SPRING INTO
ACTION AND DECIDE TO DIVIDE AND
CONQUER.
THE CLUE IS PROBABLY IN THE
SAND, BUT WERE GOING TO
START --
ILL FIND IT.
WHERES THE CLUE?
I THINK ITS AT THE TREETOP.
REALLY USE THE MANPOWER TO FIND
MY IDOL.
FIND THE CLUE.
YOU WOULDNT NEED A LADDER TO
GET UP THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
THESE STORMS ARE LITERALLY --
OUCH, OUCH, OUCH.
LETS FINISH THIS UP.
LETS GET THIS JOB DONE.
THEYRE IDIOTS.
YOU FOUND IT?
ITS THERE.
ITS BEHIND THIS ROCK.
I BET YOU ITS BEHIND THIS ROCK.
CAN DO IT?
WILL YOU HOLD IT FOR ME.
STABILIZE.
IS THAT IT?
YES!
OH, MY GOD.
GOOD EYE.
THIS IS A TEAM EFFORT.
I COULDNT HAVE DONE IT WITHOUT
BOTH OF YOU.
ITS UNCOMMON FOR WOMEN TO FIND
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO I MADE IT ONE OF MY PERSONAL
GOALS.
IM BASICALLY SPEECHLESS WHEN I
FIND IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THE FACT THAT I FOUND AN IDOL
WITH MY TWO CLOSE ESTIMATES OUT
HERE BONDED THEM TO ME EVEN
MORE.
AND GUYS, LIKE WE CANT TELL
ANYONE.
WE NEED TO GET RID OF THE
LADDER, AND THEYRE STOKED.
THEYRE SO RELIEVED THAT ALISON
DOESNT HAVE IT.
THIS IDOL IS EVERYTHING.
HEY, GUYS.
WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS IT?
I CERTAINLY RECOGNIZE THAT IF
I DONT FLIP THE SCRIPT TODAY,
IT VERY WELL COULD BE ME GOING
HOME.
ANGELINA AND I CERTAINLY HAVE A
HISTORY TOGETHER, AND I KNOW
THAT SHE WANTS ME OUT.
SURVIVING TODAY IS MY GREATEST
TEST TO DATE.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
IM THINKING DAVIE, BECAUSE
AS LONG AS HES IN THIS GAME,
NONE OF US CAN WIN.
ILL BE HONEST WITH YOU, I
COULD SWAY THIS EITHER WAY.
I KNOW YOU COULD.
ILL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
IVE BEEN DRIVING THE LAST
THREEISH VOTES.
I UNDERSTAND.
I DONT MEAN TO SAY THAT IN A
MOBSTER WAY.
THE POWER IS IN MY HANDS.
I WORKED VERY HARD TO BE IN THIS
POSITION RIGHT NOW, AND ITS
FINALLY TIME TO GET RID OF
ALISON.
WELL ITS LIKE I MAY BE GOING
HOME TODAY.
I KNOW THAT.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THERES NO NICETIES AT
THIS POINT.
I FEEL A LITTLE BIT LIKE A MOB
BOSS.
SHES WRONGED ME BEFORE.
IM EAGER TO GET SOME REVENGE ON
ALISON.
SHES WANTED ALISON OUT
FOREVER.
SHE WANTED TO DO IT LAST TIME.
SHES BEEN OBSESSED WITH ALISON.
NICK WANTS ALISON OUT, TOO.
AND I THINK ITS A MISTAKE.
I THINK WE SHOULD VOTE OUT
DAVIE, TAKE HIM OUT NEXT.
ON THE REWARD, ANGELINA AND NICK
WAS PRETTY FIRM, TODAY IS THE
DAY, WERE GETTING RID OF
ALISON.
I GAVE THEM BOTH MY WORD WE
WOULD GET RID OF ALISON, BUT I
CANT LET IT GO.
I DONT WANT THE KEEP DAVIE,shs
HES A BEAST.
LETS GET OUT DAVIE.
WHATS FUNNY IS DAVIE IS
FINISHING STRONG AND ALISON WAS
LAST IN THE CHALLENGE.
EXACTLY.
SO PICK UP DAVIE.
I AGREE.
MIKE HAS BEEN IN CHARGE OF ALL
THESE BLINDSIDES AND NOW HE
THINKS DAVIE WOULD BE A GOOD
NEXT TARGET.
BINGO, THATS WHAT I WANT.
DAVIE HAS HAD AN IMPRESSIVE GAME
SO FAR.
I CANT HAVE HIM STAY.
YOU THINK ALISON?
I HOPE THEYRE IN THE LYING
TO YOU BECAUSE WERE SO CLOSE.
ITS ALL ABOUT ANGELINA.
ANGELINA HAS A BIG EGO.
SHES GOLIATH.
THE MORE I MAKE IT FEEL LIKE
THIS IS HER DECISION, THE MORE
LIKELY IM GOING TO GET HER TO
DO WHAT I NEED HER TO DO.
I BIT MY TONGUE EARLIER, BUT
I FEEL LIKE ALISON IS LESS OF AN
ISSUE THAN DAVIE.
LIKE HIS STORY, HIS ACTION, HIS
RELATIONSHIP WITH NICK IS WAY
MORE THREATENING TO US AND, YOU
KNOW, THATS SCARY.
I JUST NEED ALISON OUT OF MY
WAY.
I DONT TRUST HIM.
I DONT TRUST EITHER OF THEM.
WOULD YOU AT LEAST CONSIDER
VOTING DAVIE OUT WITH ME AND
KARA?
OH, MY GOD.
THIS WHOLE TRIBAL COMES DOWN
TO WHETHER I HAVE DONE A
PERSUASIVE JOB OF CONVINCING
ANGELINA.
IM JUST SO CONFLICTED, MIKE.
IM SO CONFLICTED.
I KNOW DAVIES A THREAT, TOO.
IF HE REALLY CANT DO IT,
THEN OBVIOUSLY I DONT WANT IT
TO BE A --
ITS A MUCH BETTER MOVE TO
KEEP ALISON IN THE GAME THAN
DAVIE.
IM IN A TREACHEROUS SITUATION
WHERE ANGELINA AND NICK BOTH
WANT ALISON OUT, AND I GAVE THEM
MY WORD I WOULD VOTE ALISON OUT.
BUT NICK AND DAVIE HAVE BEEN
BROS FROM THE BEGINNING.
I WANT TO BREAK THOSE TWO UP.
I WOULD RATHER HAVE DAVIE GONE
AND NICK ALL TO MYSELF.
I HAVE TO THREAD THE NEEDLE.
ITS NOT GOING TO BE AN EASY
CAKE WALK UNTIL THE END.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH, JOHN, DAN, ALEC,
CARL, GABBY, AND CHRISTIAN VOTED
OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO LETS START WITH TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
ONE OF THE CLOSEST FINISHES IN A
LONG TIME.
FOR A WHILE EVERYBODY HAD A
SHOT.
ULTIMATELY NICK PULLS IT OUT.
NICK, WHATS THE FEELING ON DAY
36 TO PULL OUT THAT WIN?
YEAH, I WAS JUMPING UP AND
DOWN WHEN I FINALLY SOLVED ALL
63 PIECES OF THAT THING.
ITS THE BEST FEELING IVE HAD
OUT HERE FOR SURE.
Jeff: ANGELINA, AT THE
OTHER END OF THE SPECTRUM, WHEN
YOU GOT BACK THE CAMP, DID
PEOPLE FEEL THEY WERE IN
TROUBLE?
A LOT OF NAMES WERE THROWN
OUT.
NAMES WERE THROWN OUT AT OUR
TABLE.
NAMES WERE THROWN OUT BACK AT
CAMP.
Jeff: ALISON YOU WERE
SHAKING YOUR HEAD.
I FEEL LIKE TWO NAMES MAYBE
WERE THROWN OUT, MINE AND
DAVIES.
Jeff: DAVIE, YOURE
NODDING.
THAT RINGS TRUE TO YOU?
YEAH, THATS FAIR, JEFF.
LAST TRIBAL, MYSELF AND ALISON
WERE THE ONLY ONE OTHER THAN
CHRISTIAN WHO GOT VOTES, SO YOU
KIND OF KNEW THAT IT WAS GOING
TO BE ME OR HER THAT WAS GOING
TO BE ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK
TONIGHT.
Jeff: SO ALISON, WHAT DO
YOU DO?
BECAUSE EVEN HERE AT TRIBAL, YOU
AND ANGELINA HAVE GONE AT IT A
FEW TIMES.
FAIR?
FAIR.
Jeff: NOW THERE ARE ONLY
SIX PEOPLE.
IF YOURE ONE OF THE PEOPLE IN
TROUBLE, DO YOU GO TO ANGELINA
AND SAY, LISTEN, I KNOW WE
HAVENT ALWAYS GOTTEN ALONG, BUT
NOT ME, NOT TONIGHT.
I MEAN, ITS INTERESTING,
ANGELINA AND I FIRST WERE
ALLIES, AND EVEN AS ADVERSARIES,
THERE STILL WAS A CONNECTION AND
A BOND, SO AT SOME POINT, CAN WE
FALL BACK AT THAT?
WELL, THE LAST TWO TRIBALS MY
VOTE COULD HAVE BEEN FOR ALISON,
INSTEAD OF GOING FOR GABBY, I
COULD HAVE GONE FOR ALISON.
INSTEAD OF GOING FOR CHRISTIAN,
I COULD HAVE GONE FOR ALISON,
BUT WERE AT THIS POINT NOW
WHERE OUR FATES ARE TIED UP.
WEVE HAD A BROKEN ROAD.
YOU NEVER KNOW IN THIS GAME
WHERE YOULL END UP WITH PEOPLE.
Jeff: ALISON, YOU NEVER
KNOW, BUT YOU DID JUST HEAR
ANGELINA SAY, COULD HAVE VOTED
FOR YOU TWO TRIBALS AGO.
COULD HAVE VOTED FOR YOU THE
LAST TRIBAL.
NEXT SENTENCE COULD BE, MAYBE
ILL JUST DO IT TONIGHT.
AND SHE KNOWS I COULD WORK
WITH SOME PEOPLE TO GET HER OUT
TONIGHT.
SHE KNOWS THIS.
THIS IS NOT AN UNKNOWN.
THIS IS NOT NEW INFORMATION
TO ME.
Jeff: DAVIE, WHERE DO YOU
FALL IN THIS?
IF YOU ARE ONE OF THE TARGETS,
ARE YOU MAYBE THE SECOND CHOICE?
YEAH, I DO FEEL LIKE THERE IS
A PECKING ORDER, BUT IT DOESNT
MAKE ME COMFORTABLE.
Jeff: NICK, WHEN YOU GET
DOWN TO THIS NUMBER AND YOU HAVE
THE NECKLACE, WHAT KIND OF
OPPORTUNITY DOES THAT PRESENT
FOR YOU?
HAVING THE NECKLACE
ABSOLUTELY MAKES ME MORE
RELAXED.
IT OPENS ME UP TO PLAY THE GAME
MORE AGGRESSIVELY, BUT LONG
STORY SHORT, ITS A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY FOR PEOPLE TO BE ON
THE SAME PAGE AS ME TONIGHT.
Jeff: WOW, MIKE, THAT WAS A
THREAT.
YOU SHOULD BE WITH ME TONIGHT,
BECAUSE I CAN MAKE SOMETHING
HAPPEN.
WELL, I THINK NICK IS A GREAT
PARTNER WHETHER HES GOT THE
IMMUNITY NECKLACE OR NOT.
I MEAN, 95% OF THE TIME HES
BEEN HONEST WITH ME, AND I FEEL
LIKE 95% OF THE TIME IVE BEEN
HONEST WITH HIM.
Jeff: THATS PRETTY GOOD ON
"SURVIVOR."
THATS HOW I FEEL.
ITS PRETTY GOOD.
SO I WANT TO BE ON THE SAME PAGE
AS NICK.
Jeff: DAVIE, CONCERN YOU AT
ALL THAT A BLINDSIDE RIGHT NOW
COULD REALLY LEAVE A STICK, SO I
WANT TO BE KIND TO PEOPLE EVEN
IF IM ABOUT TO WRITE THEIR NAME
DOWN.
I THINK THE SMALLER THE TRIBE
GETS, THE STRONGER THE BONDS
GET, AND THE MORE YOU THINK YOU
CAN TRUST SOMEONE, AND IF YOU
ARE BLINDSIDED, THAT CAN LEAVE
NASTY TASTE IN SOMEONES MOUTH,
AND THAT COULD BE YOUR MILLION
DOLLAR MISTAKE.
Jeff: WOW.
MIKE, DAVIE JUST REALLY SUMMED
IT UP, ITS NOT THAT THE NUMBERS
GET SMALLER, ITS THAT THE BONDS
GET TIGHTER, SO A BLINDSIDE
HURTS A LITTLE MORE.
DOES THAT RUN THROUGH YOUR HEAD,
HOW YOU VOTE SOMEBODY OUT?
WELL RUSSIA YOU SAYING PEOPLE
ARE LYING?
YEAH, I DO UNDERSTAND THE
FEELING OF BETRAYAL AND IM SURE
I WILL FEEL THAT AT SOME POINT,
BUT YOU JUST HAVE TO TAKE A
LITTLE BIT MORE OF AN ANALYTICAL
PERSPECTIVE ON IT, AND THINK
ABOUT WHAT IS GOING TO HELP YOU
MOVE FURTHER.
ITS JUST THE NATURE OF THIS
GAME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
KARA, YOURE UP.
PURE GAME PLAY TONIGHT.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE DAVIE.
ALISON.
THATS TWO VOTES ALISON.
DAVIE.
WERE TIED.
TWO VOTES DAVIE, TWO VOTES
ALISON.
DAVIE.
THATS THREE VOTES DAVIE, TWO
VOTES ALISON, ONE VOTE LEFT.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
DAVIE.
YOU COULD HAVE SPELLED MY
NAME RIGHT.
I DIDNT DO IT, BRO.
IM SORRY.
I DIDNT KNOW.
OF COURSE YOU DIDNT.
Jeff: DAVIE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
NO HARD FEELINGS, GUYS, BUT I
WILL SAY THIS, THE PERSON WHO
ORCHESTRATED THIS, YOU NOW HAVE
MY VOTE FOR $1 MILLION.
ITS UP FOR SOMEONE ELSE TO MAKE
A BIGGER MOVE.
LOVE YOU GUYS.
LOVE YOU, DAVIE.
DAMN.
[HOWLING]
[LAUGHTER]
Jeff: WELL, YOUVE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL, BUT TO ECHO
DAVIES WORDS, TO GET TO THE END
AND WIN THIS GAME, STILL A LOT
OF GREAT GAME PLAY TO BE HAD.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
I HAD A HELL OF A TIME OUT
HERE PLAYING THIS GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
I DONT KNOW WHO IT WAS THAT
ORCHESTRATED THE MOVE TO GET ME
OUT, BUT IM SATISFIED WITH MY
"SURVIVOR" GAME.
I WANT TO SEE A GOOD SEASON.
I WANT TO SEE SOMEBODY PLAYING
THIS GAME HARD, HARD, HARD,
BECAUSE THATS WHAT I RESPECT.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
Jeff: DAVIE ONE OF THE MOST
WELL-LIKED PLAYERS THIS SEASON.
LETS GET HIM OUT HERE.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
LOOKING DAPPER.
WOW.
LOOK AT THAT RECEPTION.
COME ON.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: STANDING OVATION.
Jeff: LETS TALK TO DAVIE.
HAVE A SEAT.
SO FIRST OF ALL, THERE ARE TEARS
IN YOUR EYES RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DOES THAT FEEL LIKE?
YEAH, JEFF, JUST THE RESPONSE
THROUGHOUT THIS WHOLE SEASON HAS
BEEN OVERWHELMING.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
AND I WANT TO SPEAK PARTICULARLY
TO THE BLACK AUDIENCE, I WANTED
TO GET OUT HERE AND MAKE THEM
PROUD, BECAUSE THEY DONT REALLY
WATCH "SURVIVOR" AS MUCH AS THEY
SHOULD.
I WANTED TO CHANGE THAT.
Jeff: SO LETS JUST LOOK AT
YOUR STORY.
BECAUSE I SAID AT THE TOP OF THE
SHOW, THERE ARE LOTS OF KIDS
THAT ARE WATCHING RIGHT NOW, A
LOT OF THEM IN THE AUDIENCE THAT
ARE DREAMING.
YOU WERE THAT KID WHEN YOU WERE
LIGHT EIGHT, RIGHT?
UH-HUH, UH-HUH, WHEN I WAS
EIGHT.
Jeff: WHAT WAS THE DREAM
WHEN YOU WERE IT WILLLE?
WHAT DID YOU IMAGINE?
SO I FOUND OUT ABOUT
"SURVIVOR" IN CHURCH.
I REMEMBER TURNING TO MY MOM AND
SAYING, "IM GOING TO BE ON THAT
SHOW SOME DAY."
AND IN HIGH SCHOOL, IN MIDDLE
SCHOOL I WAS A BIT OF A NERD, A
BIT OF A BLERD.
I ALWAYS TOLD MYSELF TO BE
MYSELF.
I CREATED THAT TIME.
-- TAPE.
NOW IM HERE.
SO MY STORY HAS COME FULL
CIRCLE.
Jeff: THERE IS ANOTHER PART
OF THIS STORY.
WE ORIGINALLY SAID TO DAVIE, AND
ILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY, WE
SAID, ITS NOT GOING TO WORK OUT
THIS SEASON, MAYBE ANOTHER
SEASON SOME WE SAID NO.
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: WE GET TO FIJI.
WERE ABOUT 40 HOURS AWAY FROM
STARTING AND SOMETHING HAPPENED.
WE CALLED DAVIE UP AND WE SAY,
WE HAVE 40 HOURS, WE NEED YOU.
AND SO YOU ARE LITERALLY PACKING
AS WERE TALKING TO YOU, RIGHT,
ON THE PHONE?
YEP, YEP.
Jeff: SO WHAT WAS THAT
MOMENT LIKE WHEN THEY DIDNT
WANT ME AND NOW THEY LOVE ME.
I DIDNT EVEN TELL MY MOTHER
THAT YOU TOLD ME NOW.
SHES LIKE, "THEYRE GOING TO
CALL YOU.
I BET THEYRE GOING TO CALL
YOU."
IM LIKE, MOTHER, THEYRE NOT
GOING TO CALL ME.
AND THEN THEY DID.
IM JUMPING AROUND SCREAM, MY
DOG IS JUMPING WITH ME.
I I AM HERE.
Jeff: DAVIE, ITS BEEN SUCH
A PLEASURE.
REALLY.
AND DAVIE, THREW THE GAUNTLET
DOWN.
WERE DOWN TO FIVE.
SOMEBODY BETTER STEP UP.
ITS THE FINALE OF "DAVID VS
GOODNIGHT."
GOOD JOB DUDE.
THEY BLINDSIDE ME AND STAB ME
IN THE BACK, IT MAKES ME SICK.
I KNOW YOU DID.
ME, MIKE, AND ANGELINA SAT THERE
AT THE SPAGHETTI DINNER AND THAT
LIED THAT WERE A FINAL THREE,
NOBODY IS GOING TO TOUCH US,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
IM PISSED.
IM NOT PLAYING WITH PEOPLE THAT
DO THAT TO ME.
WHATS GOING ON?
I THOUGHT I HAD A CHANCE TO GO
TO THE END.
YOU DO.
MIKE REALLY, REALLY WANTED
DAVIE.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
YOU DIDNT GIVE ME ONE VOTE.
I KNOW.
I DONT TRUST HIM.
REALLY THOUGHT WE HAD A FINAL
THREE.
I STILL BELIEVE WE DO.
I HONESTLY BELIEVE WE DO.
I DONT BELIEVE IT.
HELL FLIP AND VOTE ME OUT.
YOU KNOW THEYRE GOING TO COME
FOR ME NOW.
WHY DO YOU FEEL THAT WAY?
BECAUSE IM NEXT.
YOURE NOT.
ANGELINA BASICALLY SAID THAT
MIKE DUG HIS HEELS IN AND HAD TO
HAVE DAVIE GO.
AND I KNOW THATS TRUE BECAUSE
MIKE DOES THAT EVERY SINGLE
VOTE.
HES BEEN SETTING ME UP THIS
WHOLE 38 DAYS.
NO.
IF YOU GET PARANOID --
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
EXHIBIT A.
IF I DONT WIN IMMUNITY, HE
MIGHT VOTE ME OUT NEXT.
WHEN MY BACK IS AGAINST THE
WALL, THATS WHEN I FIGHT AS
HARD AS I.
CAN HES OUT HERE TO WIN AND
HES OUT HERE THE LIE.
HES LIED TO ME TOO MANY TIMES.
IM WINNING IMMUNITY.
THATS WHAT IM GOING TO DO.
AND THEN ILL CHOOSE WHO GOES
HOME.
ITS ONE OF THOSE TWO GIRLS
NEXT.
IT HAS TO BE ALISON.
SHE WILL WIN.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON.
PUT ON YOUR BIG BOY PANTS.
NICK IS IN THE HAPPY THAT DAVIE
IS GONE.
ITS LIKE, NO HARD FEELINGS, BUT
I HAD TO GET RID OF YOUR PLAN
"B."
HES LIKE A LITTLE BOY.
HES A CHILD.
YEAH.
HES A CHILD WHO DIDNT KNOW
THAT HE SIGNED UP FOR THE GAME
OF "SURVIVOR."
NOTHING WILL CHANGE AS FAR AS
HOW THIS GAME IS GOING TO END.
I KNOW YOURE IN A WORSE
POSITION, BUT YOURE NOT NEXT ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
THE PLAN IS TO GET ALISON OUT.
YOU PROMISED.
I SWEAR TO --
NICK IS NOT HAPPY. HIS BUDDY
IT MAKES ME WORRIED NICK MIGHT
TRY TO BLOW UP MY SPOT.
SO I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD GET HIM
OUT OF HERE NOW BEFORE HE CAN
COME AFTER ME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
THE FINAL FIVE.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
NICK, GOT TO TAKE BACK THE
NECKLACE.
DO MY BEST TO GET IT BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BECOME UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO BE PERCHED ON A POLE IN
THE OCEAN.
ON MY GO YOULL USE A BUCKET TO
RETRIEVE WATER.
YOULL POUR THAT WATER DOWN A
CHUTE, RAISING A KEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE KEY, YOULL
DIVE INTO THE WATER, SWIM BACK
TO SHORE, UNLOCK A BUNDLE OF
PUZZLE PIECES AND USE THOSE
PIECES TO SOLVE A BLOCK PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
THIS IS SIGNIFICANT, BECAUSE AT
FOUR THE GAME CHANGES.
YOU ARE EITHER IN THE FINAL
THREE OR AT THE VERY LEAST HAVE
A SHOT TO MAKE FIRE TO GET IN
THE FINAL THREE.
THIS IS A BIG CHALLENGE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
JUST LIKE THAT GAME OVER.
TAKE A SPOT.
WELL GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY -- HOLD ON, ALISON.
I CANT BALANCE.
Jeff: YOU GOT TO START ON
YOUR FEET.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
ALISON ALREADY NERVOUS QUICKLY
GOES TO HER KNEES.
YOURE GOING TO GET THAT BUCKET,
DROP IT, PULL IT UP, AND GET
WATER.
THE TRICK IS THAT WATER IS GOING
TO START LEAKING OUT.
THE FASTER YOU GET IT UP AND
START POURING, THE BETTER.
ANGELINA UP FIRST WITH HER
BUCKET.
NOT MUCH IN THERE AND NOT MUCH
GOES IN THE CHUTE.
YOU WANT TO POUR THAT WATER IN
THE CHUTE.
THE MORE WATER IN THE CHUTE, THE
FASTER YOUR KEY WILL RISE.
NICKS KEY IS STARTING TO RISE.
ALISON NOW GETTING INTO IT.
NICK DOING A NICE JOB OF GETTING
THAT BUCKET UP VERY QUICKLY.
ALISON NOW STILL IN IT, EVEN
THOUGH SHES PETRIFIED.
ANGELINAS KEY STARTING TO RISE.
KARAS KEY STARTING TO RISE.
ALISONS ON THE MOVE.
CAN SHE REACH IT?
NO.
MIKE RIGHT NOW IN DEAD LAST.
THAT KEY HAS NOT PROVED AT ALL.
ALISON WITH ANOTHER FAST
RETRIEVAL OF WATER.
CAN SHE GET IT IN THAT CHUTE?
YES, ALISONS KEY IS VERY CLOSE.
ALISON IS THE FIRST TO GET HER
KEY, AND SHE WAS THE MOST
NERVOUS TO START THIS CHALLENGE.
ALISONS SWIMMING BACK NOW.
NOW EVERYBODY ELSE FEELING THE
PRESSURE.
NICK WITH ANOTHER NICE POUR.
WILL THIS BE ENOUGH?
NICK JUST OUT OF REACH.
IT IS ALISON BACK NOW UNLOCKING
HER PUZZLE PIECES.
WITH THE EARLY LEAD IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
NICK GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
GO.
WILL IT BE ENOUGH?
YES.
NICK REACHES HIS KEY.
HES IN THE WATER.
ALISON UNLOCKS HER PIECES.
SHE CAN START ON THE PUZZLE.
NICK RACING BACK.
KARA HAS HER KEY.
NICK BACK.
HE CAN UNLOCK HIS PIECES.
MIKE HAS HIS KEY.
NICK UNLOCKS HIS PUZZLE PIECES.
IT IS NOW ANGELINA WHO STILL
CANNOT REACH HER KEY.
SHE HAS TO RETRIEVE ANOTHER
BUCKET OF WATER.
ALISON AND NICK WORKING TO GET
THEIR PIECES FREE.
MIKE AND KARA NOW BACK.
THEY CAN UNLOCK THEIR PIECES.
ANGELINA, WILL THIS DO IT RIGHT
HERE?
ANGELINA HAS HER KEY.
SHES IN THE WATER.
IT IS ALISON AND NICK WITH THEIR
PIECES FREE.
YOURE BUILDING A FACE, TWO EYE,
A NOSE, AND A NICE TONGUE.
ANGELINA SWIMMING BACK VERY
SLOWLY, FIGHTING THAT TIDE.
THAT WATER IS TOUGH.
NICK WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
ALISON LOOKS FOR ANOTHER SPOT.
MIKE WITH A PIECE.
KARA PLACING PIECES.
ANGELINA BACK.
SHES GOING TO GET IN THIS NOW.
NICK VERY METHODICAL, NOT
PANICKING AT ALL, EACH PIECE
EXAMINING.
MIKE STILL WITH ONLY ONE PIECE.
ALISON TAKING SOME PIECES OFF
NOW.
WORKING A LITTLE BACKWARD,
TRYING THE FIND THE RIGHT ONE.
NICK WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
HES GOT A RHYTHM GOING NOW.
ALISON FIGHTING TO STAY IN THIS.
NICK WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
TURNING INTO A BLOWOUT RIGHT
NOW.
NICK THINKS HE HAS IT.
AND HE DOES!
NICK WINS HIS SECOND INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT IN
THE FINAL FOUR.
AND A GUARANTEED SHOT AT THE
FINAL THREE.
THAT WAS HARD, NICK.
THAT WAS.
Jeff: NICK, COME ON OVER.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: SECOND INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN IN A ROW.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR, AND AT THE VERY LEAST A
SHOT TO MAKE FIRE TO GET INTO
THREE.
THIS WAS A HUGE WIN.
SADLY, FOR THE REST OF YOU,
AFTER 37 DAYS IN THIS GAME,
ANGELINA, ALISON, MIKE, KARA,
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT, THE DREAM WILL END.
SHOULD BE A VERY INTERESTING
AFTERNOON IN WHAT HAS BEEN A
VERY FLUID GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
APPRECIATE IT.
I WON.
I GOT THE NECKLACE AGAIN.
IT IS FANTASTIC.
I WAS BLINDD SIDED AT THE LAST
TRIBAL.
NOW I HAVE ALL THE POWER AGAIN.
THATS GOING TO MAKE REVENGE
TASTE PRETTY SWEET.
GOOD JOB, NICK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
TWO IN A ROW.
YEAH, BABY.
LOVE IT.
AWESOME.
REALLY AWESOME.
SO NICK PULLS OUT ANOTHER
IMMUNITY WIN, BEATS ALISON, AND
I AM ELATED, BECAUSE I AM DEAD
SET ON GETTING HER OUT NEXT.
TONIGHT SHOULD BE EASY.
I HAVE AN IDOL IN MY POCKET, BUT
THE LAST TIME YOU CAN PLAY AN
IDOL IS AT FIVE, SO TONIGHT MY
PLAN IS TO CREATE AN EPIC TRIBAL
COUNCIL, MAKE AS MANY FIREWORKS
AS POSSIBLE AND HAVE ME BE THE
STAR OF THE SHOW.
SO I HAVE A VISION FOR
TONIGHT.
ALISON HAS TO GO, RIGHT.
SO YOU GET THOSE TWO TO VOTE FOR
ME.
I PLAY THE IDOL FOR MYSELF AND
WE FINALLY GET ALISON OUT.
MY DREAM SCENARIO IS PLAYING A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL CORRECTLY
AT A PIVOTAL POINT IN THE GAME.
I THINK IT MAKES ME LOOK MORE
LICK A BAD ASS TO THE JURY.
LETS BE HONEST, I HAVE NO
OUTPLAY CATEGORY.
THIS GIVES ME ONE THING.
IM PROBABLY NOT GOING TO GET
IMMUNITY.
ITS JUST FOR THE JURY.
THAT FEELS LIKE A LITTLE
EXTRA LIE.
I FEEL A LITTLE WEIRD ABOUT IT.
ITS A LITTLE CATTY, BUT IT
IS A LITTLE PERSONAL WITH
ALISON.
ANGELINAS "SURVIVOR"
STRATEGY, I DONT KNOW, ITS
FROM OUTER SPACE.
WE DONT NEED THE NEAT RICKS --
THEATRICS.
ITS DAY 37.
I DONT NEED TO HAVE SOME
SHOWCASE FOR ANGELINA.
LIKE PART OF ME WANTS TO DO A
FAKE IDOL AND MAKE HER FEEL
LIKE --
I THINK IT WOULD MAKE A MORE
EXCITING TRIBAL COUNCIL, THATS
FOR SURE.
IM GOING TO FAKE IDOL HER.
THIS SHOULD NOT BE A
COMPLICATED VOTE, BUT ANGELINA
WANTS ME TO DO THE JOB OF LYING
TO KARA AND ALISON.
I DONT MIND LYING A LITTLE BIT
TO ALISON BECAUSE SHES GOING
HOME, BUT I HAVE A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH KARA, I DONT
WANT TO JEOPARDIZE THAT BECAUSE
ANGELINA HAS AN IDEA FOR A BIG
FIREWORKS DISPLAY AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
ANGELINA HAS AN IDOL.
SHE HAS THIS PLAN SHE WANTS TO
USE THE IDOL IN SOME DRAMATIC
WAY.
SO SHE WANTS ME TO CONVINCE YOU
AND ALISON TO VOTE HER OUT, SO
SHE CAN PLAY THE IDOL.
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT IS HILARIOUS.
ITS GREAT THAT MIKE IS TELLING
ME ABOUT ANGELINAS, YOU KNOW,
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I THINK THE MORE PEOPLE THAT
KNOW ABOUT IT, THE WORSE IT IS
FOR HER.
THAT IS EVIL.
SHES EVIL.
I MEAN, ALISON SHOULD GOSH, BUT
THATS CRAZY.
SHES SO EXCITED.
THIS IS WHY SHE WANTED TO PLAY
THE GAME, TO BE A DIABOLICAL
VILLAIN.
I DONT KNOW.
VILLAINS VERSUS VILLAINS.
ANGELINA.
A MAD CASTAWAY.
MIKE WANTS ALISON TO GO, AND
YES, ALISON WOULD BE AN EASY
VOTE, BUT MIKE HAS A REALLY
STRONG SOCIAL GAME.
HES CLEARLY THE BIGGEST THREAT
TO WIN AGAINST ANY OF US IN THE
FINAL THREE.
MAYBE VOTING HIM OUT WOULD BE A
MILLION DOLLARS IN MY POCKET.
OH, MY GOD.
I HAVE THE TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
MIKE TOLD ME THAT ANGELINA HAS
THE IDOL.
DONT FREAK OUT.
WERE GOING TO GET CREATIVE.
WERE GOING TO FLIP SCRIPT
SOMEHOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT GETTING
MIKE OUT?
THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
SOMEHOW WE NEED TO GET NICK
INVOLVED.
IT IS MUSIC TO MY EARS THAT
KARAS READY TO VOTE OUT MIKE.
MIKE IS SOMEONE THAT I GENUINELY
DEEPLY CARE ABOUT, BUT MIKE IS
THE ONLY OPTION AT THIS POINT.
I HAVE TO PUT MIKES NAME OUT
THERE.
YOU ARE OBVIOUSLY BUILDING A
CASE FOR YOURSELF.
IM IN THE POSITION WHERE IF
THERE IS ANY MOVE THAT ISNT ME,
IM ALL EARS.
WELL, THEY STRAIGHT UP
BETRAYED ME LAST NIGHT.
SO IM DEFINITELY OPEN TO
OPTIONS.
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT GETTING
MYSELF TO THE FINAL THREE MORE
THAN ANYTHING.
WHEN I LOOK AT MIKE, HE HAS
GREAT RELATIONSHIPS WITH
EVERYONE.
THERES NOBODY OUT HERE THAT
DOESNT LIKE MIKE.
RIGHT.
Jeff: MIKE IS PLAYING A
GOOD STRATEGIC GAME.
AND IT GETS MY GEARS TURNING.
IM THINKING, WELL, IF IM
SITTING NEXT TO MIKE, WHERE ARE
THE VOTES GOING?
MIKE IS A THREAT TO WIN THIS
GAME.
AND HE COULD EVEN BEAT ME, AND I
THINK IVE PLAYED A VERY GOOD
GAME.
ITS REALLY GOT ME RACKING MY
BRAIN HERE ON WHAT I SHOULD DO.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO KARA?
I TALKED TO CARA.
SHE SAID SHE WOULD BE DOWN.
Jeff: REALLY?
SHE IS PREPARED.
I REALLY THINK LIKE ANGELINAS
NOT THE THREAT HERE.
MIKE IS.
I AGREE.
Jeff: ANGELINA AND MIKE ARE
VOTING ALISON.
AND ALISON IS GOING TO VOTE MIKE
BECAUSE SHELL DO WHATEVER SHES
GOT TO DO TO STAY SOME THE VOTE
TONIGHT COMES DOWN TO WHAT ME
AND KARA DECIDE IS BEST FOR OUR
GAME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE HAVE TO VOTE TOGETHER.
I WANT TO DO WHATS BEST FOR ME
AND YOU.
I DONT WANT HIM IN THE FINAL
THREE.
HE HAS PLAYED A GOOD GAME.
HE HAS, BUT IS IT BETTER THAN
ALISON?
WOULD HE GET MORE VOTES FOR HER?
THATS THE QUESTION.
I GOT BLINDSIDED LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS MIKE.
SO NOW I GOT MIKES LIFE RIGHT
HERE, AND IF I WANT TO PULL THE
TRIGGER, I CAN JUST LET HIM GO.
SHUT UP.
MIKE, YOU FOUND IT.
ALISON IS GOING HOME TONIGHT,
AND IM FEELING A LITTLE
NAUGHTY.
SO MAYBE BORDERLINE EVIL.
MAYBE BORDERLINE MEAN GIRL.
I DIDNT THINK I WOULD EVER
FIND ONE.
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
THIS FAKE IDOL IS ALMOST THE
PERFECT CHERRY ON TOP OF AN
ALREADY PERFECT NIGHT FOR ME.
SO GET READY FOR AN EPIC TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
Jeff: WELL, ITS A BIG
MOVE.
THE QUESTION IS, IS IT A GOOD
MOVE?
I WANT TO ASK AN EXPERT,
SOMEBODY WHO KNOWS THIS GAME
VERY WELL, ZEKE FROM MILLENNIALS
AND GAME CHANGERS.
ZEKE, YOURE VERY SAVVY.
ANGELINA IS PLOTTING A DELICATE
MOVE.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
YOU GOT TO WONDER IF ITS NOT
TOO BIG.
YOU WANT FIREWORKS, YOU WANT THE
JURY TO SEE YOURE PLAYING HARD,
BUT IF YOU PLAY TOO HARD, YOULL
GET VOTED OUT BEFORE YOU GET TO
THE END.
Jeff: THIS IS WHY YOURE SO
GOOD.
YES.
I GOT TO SAY HELLO TO YOUR
BOYFRIEND, NIKKO SANTOS.
YOUR CAREER IS ON FIRE.
EXCUSE ME FOR STEPPING IN FRONT
OF YOU, NOT ONLY YOUR TV SHOW,
"CRAZY RICH ASIAN," YOUR CAREER
AND LIFE HAS TO BE A FUN TIME.
ITS AMAZING.
BUT THE CHERRY ON TOP OF THE
SUNDAE IS THIS GUY RIGHT HERE.
Jeff: WHO, I MIGHT ADD,
THEY MET WHEN ZEKE WAS KIND
ENOUGH TO REPRESENT US AT THE
GLADD AWARDS.
WE MET AT THE AFTER-PARTY OF
THE GLADD AWARDS.
HE WON AND WE WERE LIKE, LETS
GO CELEBRATE.
Jeff: "SURVIVOR" MAKING
LOVE HAPPEN.
I LIKE IT.
WERE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
THE FINALE OF DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO LETS START WITH THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NICK, IT APPEARED YOU TOO WERE
BLINDSIDED BY THE DAVIE VOTE.
YES, I WAS BLINDSIDED.
I DIDNT KNOW EVERYBODY WAS
VOTING DAVIE.
I THAWING EVERYBODY WAS VOTING
ALISON.
Jeff: WHEN YOU GOT BACK THE
CAMP, WAS THERE A DISCUSSION?
YEAH, I WANTED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
I HAD A BIT OF A TEMPER AND I
WAS HOTHEADED.
IM NOT SURE WHICH STUNG MORE,
LOSING DAVIE OR BEING LEFT OUT
OF THE LOOP.
Jeff: ANGELINA, WERE YOU
PART OF THAT CONVERSATION?
I SAID, WEVE ALL BEEN THERE.
THIS GAME HAS A WAY OF PULLING
OUT EMOTIONS, SO I TALKED WITH
HIM AND EXPLAINED MY DECISION
AND I THINK WE LEFT ON A GOOD
FOOT AFTER THE CONVERSATION.
Jeff: ALISON, THE OTHER
THING THAT HAPPENED IS DAVIE
TURNED AROUND AND SAID, WHOEVER
MADE THAT MOVE, YOU HAVE MY
VOTE, UNLESS SOMEBODY ELSE TOPS
IT, DID YOU FEEL A NEED TO MAKE
MOVES THESE LAST FEW DAYS?
CERTAINLY.
I THINK WERE ALL PEDAL TO THE
METTLE AT THIS POINT.
Jeff: JEFF, THE GUY THAT
WANTS TO BE BLIND SIDED I HAD NO
PART IN.
THERES OTHER PEOPLE I HAVE
BLINDSIDED WHO PROBABLY DIDNT
APPRECIATE IT SO MUCH SOME A
COMMENT LIKE THAT WHEN SOMEONE
IS WALKING OUT THE DOOR CAN MAKE
YOU REASSESS WHAT DECISIONS AM I
GOING TO MAKE IN THE NEXT TWO
DAYS.
Jeff: ANGELINA, WHATS
REALLY INTERESTING ABOUT TONIGHT
IS THAT WHICHEVER FOUR OF YOU
SURVIVE, YOURE GUARANTEED SOME
SHOT AT THE FINAL THREE.
SO THIS IS A VERY BIG VOTE.
YEAH, I MEAN, IT WAS ALL OUT
BATTLE BACK AT CAMP TODAY.
MOSTLY BETWEEN ME AND ALISON.
Jeff: STILL.
YES, YOU KNOW, IT BOILS DOWN
TO ME AND ALISON AND WHO CAN WE
GET TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE US, AND
ITS KIND OF THE CULMINATION OF
BOTH OF OUR SOCIAL GAMES.
IM CURIOUS TO SEE HOW IT TURNS
OUT.
IM FEELING CONFIDENT, BUT YOU
NEVER KNOW UNTIL YOU KNOW.
Jeff: NICK, ANGELINA SAYS,
WHO CAN I RALLY.
YOU WOULD BE A LIKELY PERSON TO
RALLY BECAUSE YOURE SAFE.
ABSOLUTELY.
AND ANGELINA AND MIKE HAVE BEEN
CLOSE, AND KARA AND ALISON HAVE
BEEN CLOSE, SO JUST ABOUT ANY
WAY YOU SLICE IT, I GOT AN
IMPORTANT VOTE NO MATTER WHAT.
Jeff: SO ALISON, IT CAN
ONLY BE ONE OF THE FOUR OF YOU.
WERE YOU WORRIED?
DID YOU HEAR YOUR NAME?
OF COURSE.
I HAVE BEEN TARGET FOR SO LONG.
NOW THERE IS NOWHERE TO HIDE.
THE PEOPLE IN FRONT OF ME ARE
PLAYING REALLY CLEVER GAME, AS
WELL.
Jeff: WHO ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
I THINK MIKE IS A THREAT TO
SOME DEGREE.
HOWS THAT?
THATS INCORRECT.
ANYWAY, WHATEVER.
I MEAN, TO ME ITS LIKE I THINK
THERES SOMETHING GREAT ABOUT
LEAVING IT ALL OUT ON THE
ISLAND, AND THEN THERES ALSO
LEAVING WITH A SHRED OF DIGNITY.
THATS MY OPINION ON THIS.
Jeff: ALISON, THATS RIGHT
BACK TOWARD YOU.
YEAH, SO HES SITTING THERE
SAYING FOR ME TRYING TO PLAY AN
ALL-OUT GAME IS ME LOSING PRIDE,
AND HIS RELATIONSHIP IS ARGUABLY
ONE OF THE ONES IVE VALUED NOSE
OUT HIRE.
YEAH, WHATEVER.
Jeff: SO THIS IS ANOTHER
RELATIONSHIP, ALISON, THAT HAS
FRICTION.
YEAH.
Jeff: AND YOUR HOPE THEN
TONIGHT IS THAT YOU CAN RALLY
NICK AND KARA?
OF COURSE.
Jeff: KARA, THERE IS OFTEN
A POINT IN THIS GAME WHERE WHAT
WAS A LIABILITY BECOMES AN
OPPORTUNITY.
MAYBE I KEEP SOMEBODY WHO HAS
BEEN ARGUING.
MAYBE THATS BETTER FOR ME.
YEAH, WE TALKED SO MUCH ABOUT
THE END OF THE GAME AND WERE
HERE, WERE ON DAY 37.
WE CAN LOOK TO DAY 39.
YOU WANT THE LOOK WHO YOU MIGHT
BE SITTING AT THE FINAL THREE
WITH AND FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE A
FIGHTING CHANCE TO GET THOSE
VOTES OVER THE OTHER TWO YOURE
SITTING WITH.
Jeff: NICK, YOURE NODDING.
EXACTLY.
THE DECISION TONIGHT IS NOT WHO
DO I GET RID OF, ITS WHO DO I
KEEP IN THE GAME.
LIKE WHO DO I THINK I CAN BEAT?
WHO WILL TAKE ME TO THE END.
WHO CAN I BEAT IN FIRE?
SO ITS ABOUT THE OTHER THREE
PEOPLE THATS GOING TO BE WITH
ME HERE TOMORROW.
Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ALISON, YOURE UP.
ALISON, IN REAL LIFE YOU MAY
GET STRAIGHT As, BUT IN
"SURVIVOR" YOU GET A B PLUS.
ONLY BECAUSE I CANT SIT WITH
YOU IN THE FINAL THREE, BECAUSE
I DONT WANT TO GIVE ANGELINA
THE SATISFACTION OF PLAYING AN
IDOL CORRECTLY.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
TONIGHT IS THE LAST TIME YOU CAN
DO SO.
ILL PLAY THIS THING.
I HAVE A NOTE AND I HAVE A SHELL
WITH SOME ROPE AROUND IT.
I FEEL ALMOST 100% CERTAIN ITS
FALSE, BUT ILL HAVE YOU CHECK
IT OUT, BECAUSE WHATS THE HARM?
Jeff: ALISON, YES, THIS
IDOL IS A FAKE.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR YOU WILL
STILL COUNT.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
OH, IM SORRY.
WERE NOT DONE YET.
SO I MAY HAVE MADE THE WORST
FAKE IDOL IN IDOL HISTORY, BUT
LUCKILY I WAS ABLE TO FIND THIS
LITTLE GUY.
THATS GNARLY.
IM CONFIDENT I HAVE THE
VOTES TONIGHT TO GO TOWARD
ALISON, BUT ID LOVE A
GUARANTEED SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR, JEFF.
YOU MADE ME WORK FOR THAT ONE,
TOO.
Jeff: THIS IS A REAL HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR ANGELINA WILL
NOT COUNT.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MIKE.
ALISON.
WERE TIED, ONE VOTE MIKE, ONE
VOTE ALISON.
ALISON.
TWO VOTES ALISON, ONE VOTE MIKE.
16th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE NINTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ALISON, THATS THREE, THATS
ENOUGH.
YOU NEED ME TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME BE PART
OF YOUR DISFUN SHUNNAL FAMILY.
LOVE YOU, ALISON.
GREAT GAME.
THANK YOU.
REALLY A BLAST.
OH, JEFF, I WAS HOPING WE COULD
AVOID THIS.
Jeff: ALISON, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
GOOD LUCK.
ILL SEE YOU GUYS SOON.
Jeff: WELL, YOUVE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL FOUR.
TOMORROW YOULL COMPETE IN YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
THANKS, JEFF.
Jeff: GOOD NIGHT.
I CANT SAY IM TOTALLY
SURPRISED BY THAT.
IT ACTUALLY SUCKS A LOT TO BE ON
THE JURY.
I WAS ON THE EDGE OF LEAVING FOR
FIVE TRIBAL COUNCILS.
YOU CAN ONLY CHASE AWAY THE GRIM
REAPER FOR SO LONG.
THE GRIM REAPER, I ALWAYS MEAN
JEFF WITH HIS TORCH SNUFFER.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
HERE WE ARE FOR THE FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, NICK, GOT
TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
BOY, ANGELINA ALREADY STUDYING
IT.
YOU DONT EVEN NEED AN
EXPLANATION.
YOUVE SEEN THIS CHALLENGE.
YES.
Jeff: SHALL I TELL YOU
ANYWAY JUST FOR A REMINDER IS
THIS.
DEFINITELY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
FOR THE LAST TIME IMMUNITY IS
BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO HAVE ONE HAND TIED
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
ON MY GO, YOULL DROP A BALL
DOWN A CHUTE.
IT WILL SPIRAL TO THE BOTTOM
WHERE YOU MUST CATCH IT, DROP IT
BACK IN.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS WELL ADD
ANOTHER BALL, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT.
IF IT AT ANY POINT A BALL DROPS,
YOURE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, IS GUARANTEED A SPOT
AT THE FINAL THREE WHERE YOU
WILL GET A CHANCE TO PLEAD YOUR
CASE TO THE JURY ABOUT WHY YOU
DESERVE THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE $1 MILLION
PRIZE.
YOU ALSO HAVE POWER, BECAUSE YOU
WILL DECIDE WHO YOU BRING WITH
YOU TO THE FINAL THREE AND WHICH
TWO PLAYERS YOU LEAVE BEHIND TO
BATTLE IN A DO-OR-DIE
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE FOR THAT
THIRD AND FINAL SPOT.
THERE IS A LOT RIDING ON THIS
CHALLENGE.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR FIRST BALL.
AND DROP IT IN.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
IT IS THE FINAL CHALLENGE OF THE
SEASON, AND WE HAVE THREE
GOLIATHS AND ONE DAVID BATTLING
FOR A GUARANTEED SPOT AT THE
FINAL THREE.
THE KEY TO THIS CHALLENGE IS
THAT GATE IN THE MIDDLE.
ITS GOING TO SEND ONE BALL TO
THE RIGHT AND THEN THE NEXT BALL
TO THE LEFT.
ITS EASY WITH JUST ONE BALL.
BUT AS YOU GET ADDITIONAL BALLS
GOING.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER, RIGHT,
LET, RIGHT, LEFT.
IN A MOMENT YOURE GOING TO ADD
A SECOND BALL, SO START THINKING
ABOUT IT.
THIS CHALLENGE IS GOING TO BE
ALL ABOUT PACING, WHERE YOU
PLACE THAT SECOND BALL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE 15 SECONDS, ANY TIME IN
THAT WINDOW YOU CAN ADD YOUR
SECOND BALL.
EVERYBODYS DROPPED.
EVERYBODY NOW WITH TWO BALLS IN
MOTION.
BEAUTIFUL BACKDROP FOR
THE
MOST
IMPORTANT CHALLENGE IN THIS
GAME.
YOU HAVE LASTED 38 DAYS.
YOU WANT TO GUARANTEE YOURSELF A
SPOT AT THE FINAL THREE.
YOU WIN RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO ADD A THIRD BALL.
YOU DONT HAVE TO PANIC.
YOU HAVE 15 SECONDS TO DROP IT.
KARA DROPS HERS.
ANGELINA DROPS HERS.
NICK DROPS HIS AND MIKE DROPS
HIS.
EVERYBODY NOW WITH THREE BALLS.
AND WITH THAT YOU CAN FEEL THE
TENSION KICK IN.
EVERYBODY NOW A LOT MORE ALERT.
YOU DONT WANT TO DROP HERE.
YOU CAN GO FURTHER.
STAY IN THIS.
KEEP FIGHTING.
ANGELINA IS THE FIRST TO DROP.
ANGELINA IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE ARE DOWN TO THREE.
IT IS KARA, MIKE, AND NICK.
OH, SHOOT.
Jeff:MIKE WHITE DROPS HIS BAL
MIKE IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS KARA AND NICK NOW BATTLING
IT OUT IN THIS FINAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE FOR A GUARANTEED SPOT
AT THE FINAL THREE.
KEEP FIGHTING, KEEP DOING WHAT
YOURE DOING.
YOU GOT NOTHING ELSE GOING ON IN
YOUR LIFE RIGHT NOW BUT THIS
CHALLENGE IN FIJI FOR $1
MILLION.
IN A MOMENT YOURE GOING TO ADD
A FOURTH BALL.
YOU WILL HAVE ANOTHER 15 SECOND-
WINDOW.
ITS UP TO YOU WHERE YOU DROP IT
IN THAT WINDOW.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE 15 SECONDS TO DROP YOUR
FOURTH BALL.
KARA CANT DO IT.
KARA DROPS.
KARA IS OUT.
NICK WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
THREE.
JUST LIKE THAT IT IS OVER.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED, KARA?
YOU SAID 15 SECONDS AND I WAS
TRYING TO TIME IT OUT AND I
FORGOT I WAS MANAGING THREE
BALLS.
ITS LIKE THIS GAME, YOU LOOK
ASIDE FOR A SECOND AND THEN YOUR
CHANCE AT IMMUNITY IS GONE.
IT SUCKS THAT THIS IS THE
CHALLENGE THAT I FELT LIKE I
COULD DO AND THEN I FAILED.
I JUST FAILED MYSELF.
Jeff: NICK, THE OTHER END
OF THE SPECTRUM, WHAT DOES IT
FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW, ALL OF THE
TIME YOUVE SPENT WANTING TO GET
ON THE SHOW, YOURE OUT HERE
NOW, AND YOUVE DONE IT?
IT FEELS AMAZING, HONESTLY,
LIKE IVE WANTED TO BE OUT HERE
FOR YEARS, AND I DID NOT WANT
THIS CHALLENGE, I WANT SOMETHING
LICK A PUZZLE OR SOMETHING IM
GOOD AT, BUT I THINK IVE OFTEN
BEEN UNDERESTIMATED IN MY LIFE,
AND TODAY I THINK I
UNDERESTIMATED MYSELF.
AND I WAS ABLE TO OVERCOME, THAT
AND I REALLY CANT BELIEVE I
WON.
I CANT EVEN EXPLAIN HOW HAPPY I
AM RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: COME ON OVER.
FOR THE THIRD TIME, INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IS YOUR, AND THIS ONE
IS SPECIAL.
YOU HAVE MADE IT TO THE FINAL
THREE.
YOU WILL GET CHANCE TO PLEAD
YOUR CASE TO THE JURY ABOUT WHY
YOU DESERVE TO WIN THIS GAME, AN
YOURE GOING TO DECIDE WHICH ONE
OF THESE THREE, ANGELINA, KARA,
AND MIKE, YOU CHOOSE TO BRING
WITH YOU AS YOUR COMPETITION AND
WHICH TWO YOU FORCE TO COMPETE
IN A FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE TO
EARN THEIR SPOT.
IM SURE YOURE GOING TO BE A
VERY POPULAR GUY BACK AT CAMP
THIS AFTERNOON.
YEAH, I RECKON.
Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU GUYS TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THANKS, JEFF.
APPRECIATE IT.
WOW.
GOOD JOB, NICK.
HIGH-FIVE.
DONT LEAVE ME HANGING.
NICK WINS HIS THIRD IMMUNITY
NECKLACE IN A ROW, WHICH IS
AMAZING FOR ME, BECAUSE HES MY
ALLY, SO HIS WINNING IS MY
WINNING, TOO.
WANT TO GET PITCHED.
Jeff:
YEAH.
POPULAR MAN.
OF COURSE, EVERYONE WANTS TO
GIVE NICK THEIR FINAL PITCH IN
TERMS OF WHY HE SHOULD TAKE THEM
TO THE FINAL THREE.
ITS YOUR GAME TO LOSE.
I THINK SO.
IT IS THE PERFECT TWIST THAT
THE FINAL DAVID HOLDS THE FATE
OF THREE GOLIATHS IN HIS HANDS.
I HONESTLY DONT KNOW WHAT
THE PERCEPTION IS OF ME, BUT
THOSE CHICKS WILL BE GOING FOR
THE MONEY AND TRYING TO, YOU
KNOW, WHATEVER, SPIN WHATEVER
THEYRE SPINNING.
IM GOING TO COME IN ON A
DIFFERENT ANGLE.
MY GAME IS KIND OF PLAIN JANE.
I THINK THE JURY IS LIKE, KARA
GOT DRAGGED IN THE END.
IM GETTING ALL THESE
PITCHES, AND THEY SAY THERE IS
NO WAY THEY CAN WIN THE GAME.
OF COURSE THEYRE GOING TO TELL
ME, THAT BECAUSE THEY WANT ME TO
TAKE THEM.
ITS EASY, TAKE ME AND HAVE
ANGELINA FIRE.
PEOPLE LIKE ME, BUT I DONT
HAVE A GAME TO BACK IT UP.
YOU CANT TRUST ANYONE,
ESPECIALLY ON DAY 38.
THIS IS THE TIME TO USE MY
DECISION FOR ME AND MY GAME.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I WANT
WHOEVER GOES HOME TODAY TO VOTE
FOR ME AND GIVE ME THE $1
MILLION.
ARE YOU HERE TO MAKE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT?
YEAH.
IF YOU GUYS WANT TO KNOW?
I THINK THE MOST LIKELY WAY I
CAN LOSE TOMORROW IS IF IM
SITTING WITH YOU AND WITH YOU.
SO IF I GO AHEAD AND TAKE
ANGELINA, THEN ONE OF YOU WONT
BE THERE.
IM A CLOSER.
IM PERSUASIVE.
AND I HAVE SUCCESSFULLY
PERSUADED NICK TO TAKE ME TO THE
END WITH HIM.
CONGRATS TO YOU TWO.
CONGRATS.
MIKE AND KARA MIGHT WANT TO
SAY THAT NICK IS GOING TO TAKE
THE WEAKEST PLAYER, BUT I DO
BELIEVE I CAN WIN THIS GAME.
SO ITS THE FIRST TIME ITS
SINKING IN.
AFTER EVERYTHING IVE BEEN
THROUGH, SUPER PROUD OF MYSELF.
WANT ME TO GO FIRST, MIKE?
SURE.
MIKE AND I ARE GOING THE
FIGHT IT OUT IN FIRE.
ITS TOUGH, BUT AT LEAST THIS IS
MY SHOT TO GET INTO THE FINAL
THREE PROVING MY WAY THERE.
I AM SO FREAKING CLOSE.
THE PRESSURE IS ON.
BUT IM READY FOR IT AND IM NOT
GOING TO GO OUT TONIGHT WITHOUT
FIGHTING.
WOW.
AWESOME.
THE PLAYERS IN THIS GAME HAVE
UNDERESTIMATED ME AND MY GAME
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
IM A GOLIATH.
I DONT GIVE UP.
NO MATTER WHAT SITUATION IM
FACED WITH, IM GOING TO GET
PAST IT.
THATS QUICK, GIRL.
AT THIS POINT IM GOING TO
WORK MY ASS OFF TO MAKE FIRE.
I CAME HERE TO WIN.
WOULD IT MAKE IT TO THE FLAG
IN.
D SAY.
FOR ME THE FIRE-MAKING THING
HAS ALWAYS BEEN MY NIGHTMARE.
SOMETHING ABOUT MAKING THIS FIRE
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE AND THE
JURY IS MORE ANXIETY INDUCING
THAN ANYTHING THATS HAPPENED UP
TO THIS POINT.
YOU DONT NEED TO PACK MUCH.
YOURE NOT GOING HOME.
I FEEL NERVOUS ABOUT THIS.
AND I DONT KNOW, ITS GETTING
INTO MY HEAD.
NOW IM IN THIS ANXIETY MODE
THAT IM AFRAID OF BEING AFRAID
ABOUT IT.
I DONT THINK ANYONE THINKS IM
GOING TO WIN.
THIS I HAVE NEVER FELT MORE LIKE
A DAVID.
I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO SUMMON MY
INNER GOLIATH, CRUSH THIS DAVID
UNDERDOG FEEL AND JUST GO IN
THERE AND TRY TO OWN IT.
WHOA!
ITS IN MY HANDS.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I KNOW HOW TO MAKE A FIRE.
IM JUST GOING TO GO IN THERE
AND GIVE IT MY BEST SHOT.
IVE MADE IT TO DAY 38.
I DONT WANT TO GO OUT NOW.
I STILL WANT THAT ONE MORE DAY
AND ONE MORE SHOT TO WIN THIS
THING.
HK)
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SO, NICK, LETS START WITH YOU.
YOUR THIRD INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
WIN.
YOU HAVE ACCOMPLISHED THE GOAL.
YOU HAVE GOTTEN TO THE FINAL
THREE.
I MEAN, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
TEARS OF JOY WAS LIKE AN
EXPRESSION THAT PEOPLE SAY, BUT
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE, I
ACTUALLY CRIED TEARS OF JOY.
Jeff: NICK, PART OF WINNING
THAT FINAL CHALLENGE IS YOU HAVE
POWER.
YOU DECIDE TONIGHT WHO SITS NEXT
TO YOU IN ONE OF THE SPOTS AND
WHICH OTHER TWO PEOPLE HAVE TO
FIGHT FOR FIRE.
THATS RIGHT.
AND WITH GREAT POWER COMES GREAT
RESPONSIBILITY, SO, YOU KNOW,
THE TEARS OF JOY VERY QUICKLY
TURNED INTO, OH, MAN, IM IN A
SPOT HERE.
Jeff: KARA, ITS REALLY
INTERESTING WHEN YOU GET TO THIS
PHASE OF THE GAME, ALL OF THOSE
THINGS THAT WERE ASSETS YOU NOW
TURN INTO, YOU KNOW, I REALLY
WOULDNT GET ANY VOTES, I DIDNT
PLAY MUCH OF A GAME?
RIGHT, YOURE PROUD OF THE
GAME YOU PLAYED, BUT IM
PITCHING TO NICK LIKE, I DIDNT
REALLY DO MUCH OF ANYTHING, TAKE
ME, YOU CAN WIN OVER ME.
Jeff: ANGELINA, ITS ALMOST
LIKE NOBODY WANTS TO GIVE AWAY
ANYTHING MORE THAN THEY HAVE TO,
BECAUSE MAYBE NICK HASNT MADE
UP HIS MIND YET.
WE THINK THAT NICK HAS MADE
UP HIS MIND.
HE WAS COOL ENOUGH AT CAMP TO
LET US KNOW WHO HE INTENDS TO
SAVE, BUT, OF COURSE, ITS NOT
FINAL UNTIL HE TELLS YOU WHAT HE
INTENDS TO DO TONIGHT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NICK.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE WITH
YOU TO THE FINAL THREE?
WELL, I THINK I HAVE THE
LEAST PROBABILITY OF WINNING THE
GAME IF IM SITTING NEXT TO BOTH
MIKE AND KARA, SO FOR THAT
REASON, IT WOULD MAKE THE MOST
SENSE FOR ME TO TAKE ANGELINA TO
THE FINAL THREE.
Jeff: SO ANGELINA,
CONGRATULATION, YOUVE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL THREE.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
Jeff: HOW DOES THAT FEEL
IN.
IT FEELS SURREAL, IM SUPER
GRATEFUL TO NICK.
ITS INDESCRIBABLE.
Jeff: SO THAT LEAVES US
WITH MIKE AND KARA.
BEFORE WE GET TO IT, HOW
CONFIDENT ARE YOU, KARA?
I HONESTLY THINK THAT ITS
GOING TO BE A GREAT COMPETITION
TONIGHT.
ITS GOING TO BE A GOOD SHOW.
Jeff: MIKE, THAT GOT A
WEIRD REACTION, YOUR FACE DID
LIKE 50 DIFFERENT TWITCHES.
IM HOPING IF I LOSE I LOSE
QUICKLY.
BUT I HOPE I DO WELL.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO IT IS TIME TO GET TO IT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
KARA, YOULL BE ON ORANGE.
MIKE, YOULL BE ON PURPLE.
DONT REACH IN YET.
OKAY.
YOU EACH HAVE THE SAME AMOUNT OF
SUPPLIES.
THE GOAL IS REALLY SIMPLE.
BUILD A FIRE THAT IS HIGH ENOUGH
AND HOT ENOUGH TO BURN THROUGH
THE ROPE AND RAISE THE FLAG.
THE FIRST TO DO IT BECOMES THE
THIRD AND FINAL MEMBER OF THE
FINAL THREE.
THE ONE WHO DOESNT BECOMES THE
TENTH AND FINAL MEMBER OF THE
JURY.
THIS IS A DO-OR-DIE CHALLENGE.
ARE YOU BOTH READY MANY.
YES.
Jeff: GOOD LUCK AND BEGIN.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
38 DAYS IN THE MAKING COMES DOWN
TO THIS, NICK AND ANGELINA
ALREADY IN THE FINAL THREE.
WERE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
BOTH MIKE AND KARA QUICKLY START
SCRAPING MAGNESIUM.
THATS WHAT YOURE GOING TO TRY
TO IGNITE TO CATCH THAT PUFF.
BOTH AT THE SAME TIME START
GOING TO GET A SPARK.
KARA HAS THE FIRST FLAME.
IT GOES OUT.
THOSE FLAMES CAN GO OUT QUICKLY.
YOU GOT TO GET THEM TO CATCH.
MIKE WORKING TO GET SOMETHING
GOING.
HES HAVING TROUBLE GETTING A
SPARK NOW.
THERE IT IS.
MIKES GOT A LITTLE FLAME.
CAN HE THURSDAY CHUR IT WITHOUT
BLOWING IT OUT.
MIKE TRYING TO KEEP IT GOING
THAT.
FLAME NOW STARTING TO GET A
LITTLE MOMENTUM, BUT IT IS STILL
EARLY.
KARA STILL HAS A SHOT.
MIKE HAS A LONG WAY FROM THAT
ROPE.
NOW HES GOING TO TRY TO BUILD A
STRUCTURE THAT WILL TAKE THAT
FLAME ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP OF
THAT ROPE.
YOU DONT WANT TO GET A FIRE AND
LOSE IT.
MIKE HAS NOT MADE A LOT OF
PROBLEM, HES TRYING TO KEEP
THAT BASE GOING SO IT DOESNT GO
OUT, BUT IF HE DOESNT GET IT
GOING SOON, IT MIGHT.
THATS THE OPENING FOR KARA.
KARA AGAIN TRYING TO GET A
SPARK.
SHES GOT MORE MAGNESIUM.
SHES GOT TO IGNITE IT.
KARAS GOT A FLAME NOW.
AND IT GOES OUT.
PIECE BY PIECE MIKE CONTINUES TO
GROW HIS FIRE RIGHT NEXT TO HIM
KARA CONTINUES TO TRY TO GET
FIRE.
DO NOT GIVE UP.
THIS COULD VERY WELL BE A
MILLION DOLLAR FIRE YOU ARE
MAKING.
MIKE HAS A NICE FIRE GOING, BUT
THAT FIRE DOES HAVE TO GROW HIGH
ENOUGH TO REACH THAT ROPE.
KARA STILL FIGHTING.
SHES GOT A LITTLE FLAME.
GOES OUT AGAIN.
MIKES FLAME GROWING MORE NOW.
ITS STARTING TO BURN THROUGH
THE ROPE.
MIKE CAN SEE IT.
HES EYEING IT.
KARA CONTINUES TO TRY.
IT WONT MATTER.
MIKE DOES IT.
MIKE MAKES FIRE.
WOW.
MIKE WILL JOIN NICK AND ANGELINA
IN THE FINAL THREE.
KARA, AFTER 38 DAYS BECOMES THE
FINAL MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WHAT A TIEBREAKER.
YOU KNOW WHAT MIKE IS FEELING,
KARA, WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
OH, ITS JUST A FEELING OF
DEFEAT.
YOU KNOW, IM SPYING THROUGH THE
ADVERSITY, BUT IT SUCKS TO KNOW
THAT IT ENDS HERE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, KARA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
IT WAS GREAT PLAYING WITH YOU
GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
YOURE A CLASS ACT.
Jeff: KARA, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE, GUYS.
SEE YOU SOON.
Jeff: NICK, ANGELINA, MIKE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE MADE IT TO THE FINAL
THREE.
YOU HAVE DONE WHAT EVERYBODY WHO
STARTS THIS ADVENTURE HOPES TO
DO BUT SO FEW ACTUALLY
ACCOMPLISH.
YOU HAVE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN
GO.
TOMORROW NIGHT THE POWER SHIFTS
TO THE JURY.
TEN PEOPLE THAT YOU ULTIMATELY
VOTED OUT HAVE ALL THE POWER.
THEY WILL DECIDE WHO THEY THINK
IS MOST DESERVING OF THE TITLE
OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE $1
MILLION PRIZE THAT GOES ALONG
WITH IT.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT HERE IN
FIJI.
I ENCOURAGE YOU TO TRY TO GET AS
MUCH SLEEP AS YOU CAN SO YOU N
BE AS SHARP AS POSSIBLE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
WELL SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT FOR
YOUR FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IM PROUD FOR THE FINAL
THREE, DISAPPOINTED THAT ITS
NOT GOING TO BE ME IN THERE, BUT
IM TAKING MY SPOT AS THE TENTH
JUROR VERY SERIOUSLY.
IM PROUD OF THE GAME I PLAYED.
I CAME OUT HERE THE PLAY AS HARD
AS I POSSIBLY COULD, AND I KNOW
I DID EXACTLY THAT.
I CANT BEAVER ITS US.
DAY 39.
WERE STILL HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT?
I DIDNT.
YOU AND I HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
THE ENTIRE TIME.
THATS TRUE.
I LIKE YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
I CAN BARELY BELIEVE IM IN THE
FINAL THREE.
I HEAR IT COMING OUT OF MY MOUTH
BUT IT DOESNT FEEL REAL.
ITS A DREAM COME TRUE.
ITS STILL SINKING IN.
DAY 39.
Jeff: OH, WOW.
EVEN THOUGH I HAVE ALL THE
LOVE IN THE WORLD FOR NICK AND
MIKE, TODAY THEY ARE MY BIGGEST
COMPETITORS.
THEYVE PLAY TOUGH GAME, BUT ME
BEING A GOLIATH, I HAVE THIS
DRIVE INSIDE OF ME.
AND I FOUGHT TOOTH AND NAIL TO
MAKE IT TO THE END AS A STRONG
PLAYER.
THIS GAME TESTED ME MORE THAN
ANYONE ELSE IN THE FINAL THREE.
AND TAUGHT ME, I DONT HAVE TO
BE PERFECT.
I DONT HAVE TO BE POLISHED ALL
THE TIME.
I DONT HAVE TO BE MADE UP ALL
I CAN JUST BE ME AND THAT IM SO
CAPABLE OF ANYTHING.
BREAKFAST.
DAY 39 "SURVIVOR" BREAKFAST.
WAFFLE, EGG, CHAMPAGNE.
DAY 39 IS SO SURREAL.
ALL WE HAVE LEFT IS ONE TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT MADE ME SO PROUD OF THE GAME
IVE PLAYEDEN I FOUGHT HARD TO
GET HERE.
IM NOT GOING TO NOT BE PROUD OF
MYSELF.
TO DO IT AS AN UNDERDOG IS A
BADGE OF HONOR, AS WELL.
IM PROUD TO BE THE LAST DAVID
IN THE GAME.
SO AWESOME.
I LOVE YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
BUBBLY.
DAY 39.
FINAL THREE.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN A DAVID.
I WAS PROBABLY ONE OF THE ONLY
KIDS IN LAW SCHOOL THAT GREW UP
IN A TRAILER, BUT IT MADE ME WHO
I AM.
IT MADE ME LEARN HOW TO MAKE
MYSELF BE SOMEBODY.
THATS THE THING ABOUT
"SURVIVOR."
I HAD TO BUILD RELATIONSHIPS AT
THE RIGHT TIME.
HIDE THE GO FIND ADVANTAGE, WIN
IMMUNITY.
I HAVE HAD TO DO EVERYTHING OUT
MERE OTHER THAN A BACK PHILLIP.
TONIGHT ONE OF THE BIGGEST
NIGHTS OF MY LIFE, BECAUSE I
HAVE CHANCE TO WIN $1 MILLION
TONIGHT.
WHEN DOES THAT EVER HAPPEN TO
SOME COUNTRY BOY FROM
SOUTHEASTERN KENTUCKY, YOU KNOW?
DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH IS AN
EPIC STORY, AND AS A STORYTELLER
WHO LOVES THIS GAME, I WANTED TO
BE HERE FOR EVERY BIT OF IT, AND
I WAS, AND IM STILL IN IT.
FOR ME, LIFE IS ABOUT PUSHING
MYSELF, SO I WANTED TO COME OUT
HERE AND SEE HOW I FARED, AND
NOT ONLY DID I STOMACH IT, BUT I
LIKED IT.
I FIFTH FIFTH FELT ALIVE.
AT THIS AGE, THATS WHAT YOU
WANT, YOU WANT THE FEEL LIKE
YOURE LEAVING IT ALL OUT ON THE
ISLAND.
I FEEL LIKE I DID.
I FEEL LIKE I LEFT IT OUT ON THE
ISLAND AND IM GOING THE TAKE
THAT LESSON AND LIVE THE REST OF
MY LIFE THAT WAY.
OTHER PEOPLE PLAYED BETTER
PHYSICAL GAMES.
I DIDNT COMPETE IN THAT WAY,
BUT I DO THINK MY SOCIAL GAME
WAS KIND OF INSPIRED.
YOU KNOW, I WASNT THE ONE AT
THE WHEELS, BECAUSE THE PERSON
AT THE WHEEL ALWAYS GOT THEIR
HEAD CHOPPED OFF THE NEXT DAY,
BUT I WAS BEHIND THE DRIVER
SAYING, YOU MIGHT WANT TO TURN
LEFT, YOU MIGHT WANT TO TURN
RIGHT, AND THE CAR WENT TO WAY I
WANTED IT TO GO.
I CAN TAKE CREDIT FOR THAT.
TONIGHT I HAVE TO MAKE SURE
EVERYONE ON THE JURY SEES THAT,
BECAUSE THE STORY IS NOT OVER.
AND I HAVE GOT TO WIN.
I CAME HERE TO PLAY A GAME.
I AM COMPETITIVE.
IM NOT HERE TO MAKE IT TO THE
END.
IM HERE TO WIN THE GAME.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH, JOHN, DAN, ALEC,
CARL, GABBY, CHRISTIAN, DAVIE,
ALISON, AND KARA, WHO LOST IN
THE FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO YOUR FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SO WE STARTED THIS SEASON WITH
TWO GROUPS, DAVIDS AND GOLIATHS.
FITTINGLY WE HAVE MEMBERS OF
EACH GROUP STILL IN THE GAME.
AT VARIOUS TIMES THROUGHOUT THE
SEASON, YOU HAVE ALL DESCRIBED
THIS GAME PLAY AS FLUID, THAT
ALLIANCES AND THE STYLE OF PLAY
WOULD SHIFT FROM DAY TO DAY.
AND WE SAW THAT FLUIDITY WHEN IT
CAME TO INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
THERE WERE TEN INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES THIS SEASON.
EIGHT OF THEM WERE WON BY
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
THATS 80% OF THE CHALLENGES WON
BY A DIFFERENT PERSON.
WE STARTED THE SEASON WITH THE
PREMISE THAT EVEN WHEN YOU HAVE
DAVIDS AND GOLIATHS ITS NOT
ABOUT WHO HAS THE ADVANTAGE, THE
QUESTION IS ALWAYS, WHAT IS THE
ADVANTAGE.
AND HERE WE ARE WITH A FINAL
THREE, EVERY ONE OF YOU POLICE
DEPARTMENT A DIFFERENT TYPE OF
GAME, AND AT VARIOUS POINTS IN
THE GAME, YOU FIGURED OUT WHAT
THE ADVANTAGE WAS IN A GIVEN
SITUATION AND YOU CAPITALIZED ON
THAT.
AND TONIGHT, IN THAT CONTEXT,
THE JURY WILL NOW DECIDE WHICH
ONE OF THE THREE OF YOU THEY
THINK PLAYED THE BEST OVERALL
GAME AND IS MOST DESERVING OF
THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND
THE MILLION DOLLAR PRIZE.
ILL GIVE YOU GUYS A MOMENT AND
WELL GET STARTED.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ITS TIME TO GET TO FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WE WILL START WITH THE OUTWIT
PORTION OF THE GAME.
THIS IS THE SOCIAL PART OF THE
GAME, ALLIANCES YOU HAD, HOW YOU
DEALT WITH BLINDSIDE, THE
EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE.
WHO WANTS TO GET US STARTED?
THAT WOULD BE ME, JEFF.
FIRST OF ALL, I WANTED TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU THREE WERE ABLE TO DO WHAT
WE WERE NOT.
EACH OF YOU HAVE A LOT TO BE
PROUD OF.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT ALMOST
ALL OF US ARE UNDECIDED.
SO I REALLY WANT YALL TO CUT
THE CRAP, ALL RIGHT, AND YOU
DONT HAVE TO BE POLISHED, JUST
BE REAL AND ATHEN TICK, BECAUSE
IF YOURE GOING A POLITICAL
ANSWER, I AINT GOING TO BE
SATISFIED.
SO DOVETAILING OFF THIS
BEAUTIFUL STATEMENT, I WOULD
LOVE IT IF YOU WOULD ALL TAKE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO HIGHLIGHT A MOVE
THAT YOU MADE IN THE GAME THAT
DEMONSTRATED HOW YOU OUTWITTED
IN SURVIVOR, AND YOU GUYS CAN GO
IN WHATEVER ORDER YOU WANT.
THE OUTWITHTO ME HAD TWO MAIN
FACTORS, INFORMATION AND TIMING.
THE INFORMATION IN MY MIND IS
THE SOCIAL DYNAMIC, THE
RELATIONSHIPS YOU CAN BUILD.
SO I WOULD HAVE ONE-ON-ONE
ALLIANCES WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE,
AND TO MAKE IT FUN, WE WOULD
EVEN NAME THEM.
CHRISTIAN, WE WERE THE
MASON-DIXON.
THAT WAS A WAY FOR ME TO BUILD A
PERSONAL CONNECTION WITH PEOPLE,
AND PEOPLE WOULD TELL ME WHAT
WAS GOING ON, THATS HOW I KNOW
WHAT EVERY VOTE IS GOING TO BE.
THATS WHEN THE TIMING COMES IN.
SO A MOVE TO HIGHLIGHT THAT IS
WHEN JOHN WENT HOME.
THAT WAS A BIG MONEY MOVE.
I MEAN, DAVIE PLAYED HIS IDOL,
AN IDOL WAS PLAYED ON ANGELINA,
AND WE SPLIT A MINORITY VOTE,
FIRST TIME IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY, TWO BIG FACTORS.
INFORMATION, TIMING.
YOURE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
SUCKS FOR ME, BUT GOOD MOVE.
WELL PLAYED.
THANK YOU.
BUT ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
THINGS IN A WRESTLING MATCH IS
THE FINISH.
PEOPLE REMEMBER THE BIG FINISH.
I FELT LIKE THE PEAK OF YOUR
SOCIAL GAME WAS RIGHT AT THAT
VOTE OUT.
CAN YOU GIVER ME ANY EXAMPLES OF
HOW YOU OUTWITTED PEOPLE DEEPER
INTO THE GAME?
WELL, YOURE RIGHT, THE VOTE
AGAINST YOU WAS PROBABLY MY
BIGGEST MOVE, BUT AFTER THAT
MOVE, I THINK THE GOLIATHS FELT
LIKE THEY COULDNT TRUST ME, AND
THEN CARL AND DAVIE, YALL GOT
BLIND SIERDED AND I DIDNT KNOW
ABOUT IT.
I WAS UPSET WHEN YOU TWO WENT
HOME.
I WAS --
WERE YOU WERE UPSET BECAUSE
YOU WERE BLINDSIDED OR WERE YOU
UPSET WHEN THEY WENT HOME?
BOTH.
I WAS OPEN FOR BUSINESS.
IM READY FOR EVERYBODY.
SO I RECONNECT WITH MY JABENI
FOLKS AND WE START MAKING MOVES
TOGETHER.
IT WAS SUPER IMPRESSIVE, BUT
I WANT TO SEGUE TO MAKE AND HEAR
ABOUT SOME OF YOUR GAME, YOUR
OUTWIT STUFF.
CAN I RESPOND?
OR DO YOU WANT TO GO AND ILL GO
AFTER?
NO, GO AHEAD.
I THINK THAT I WAS IN A
SIMILAR POSITION AS NICK.
I WAS IN A DOGHOUSE, BECAUSE OF
THE FALLOUT WITH YOU, ELIZABETH,
AND I FIFTH AMENDMENT LIKE MY
GOLIATH ALLIANCE DIDNT TRUST
ME, THE DAVIDS DIDNT REALLY
TRUST ME, I WAS CALLED AN
INSURANCE POLICY BACK AT CAMP.
MY REPUTATION WAS IN THE DUMPS.
IT MAY STILL WELL BE.
I HOPE NOT.
BUT TO YOUR COMMENT, JOHN,
AROUND WRESTLING AND FINISHING
STRONG, I WAS ABLE TO KIND OF
PICK MYSELF UP OFF THE FLOOR AND
I STARTED MAKING INROADS WITH
CARL.
I STARTED RECONNECTING WITH
CHRISTIAN AND SO I THINK THAT MY
SOCIAL GAME WAS ONE THAT WAS
EXTREMELY ADAPTABLE.
I WAS ABLE TO KEEP YOU WITH RACE
FOR THE LAST 11 DAYS.
WELL, I DO HAVE TO POINT OUT
THAT THE WHOLE POINT OF A
SELFLESS ACT IS TO BE SELFLESS.
FAIR ENOUGH.
AND NOT BRING IT UP.
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU GOT RICE
FOR THE TRIBE.
I SHOULDNT HAVE SAID THAT.
THERE WERE MOMENTS WHERE I
WASNT BEING AUTHENTIC, WHERE I
WAS PUTTING ON A CHARADE, BUT
AGAIN, I PROMISE WELL MOVE ON.
I WANT TO SAY IM ABLE TO GET
MYSELF FROM THE WEAKEST POSITION
IN THE GAME TO ONE OF THE
STRONGEST.
AND YOURE SITTING THERE IN
THE FINAL THREE.
I STILL MADE IT HERE.
BUT I WANT MIKE TO GO.
MY PERSPECTIVE WAS I WANTED
PEOPLE WHO WERE MAKING FINAL-TWO
DEALS WITH ME.
I FELT LIKE I HAD A FINAL TWO
DEAL WITH KARA, I HAD A
FINAL-TWO DEAL WITH ALISON.
I HAD A FINAL-TWO DEAL WITH
THESE TWO AND A FINAL-TWO DEAL
WITH CHRISTIAN.
I WOULD APPROACH DAVIE AND CARL,
BUT I JUST FELT ON THE PERIPHERY
OF WHATEVER YOU WERE PLANNING.
AND GABBY SIMILARLY, I FELT LIKE
WHENEVER I APPROACHED YOU, LIKE
YOU WERE NEVER REALLY GOING TO
WORK WITH ME.
SO I DIDNT SEE NECESSARILY YOU
AS A THREAT, I JUST FELT LIKE I
WOULD RATHER HAVE THREATS THAT
WANTED TO WORK WITH ME THAN
PEOPLE WHO DIDNT.
YOURE RIGHT, THAT I DIDNT
TRUST YOU, BECAUSE WHAT YOU
SAID, YOU HAD FINAL TWO DEALS
WITH EVERYBODY AND I THOUGHT IT
WAS EXTREMELY TRANSPARENT, BUT
GOOD ON YOU FOR GETTING RID OF
SOMEBODY WHO DIDNT TRUST YOU.
WANTED TO GET TO THE END.
I FELT LIKE THAT WAS MY BEST
SHOT AT FULFILLING MY JOB HERE.
ONE OF THE THINGS I HAVE HARD
TIME WITH IS YOURE SO HUMOROUS,
SO WITTY AND SARCASTIC, BUT AT
TIMES YOUR SARCASM CROSSED TO
BITING.
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS?
I DO REGRET WHAT I SAID TO
YOU AT
YOUR DIGNITY OR WHATEVER, IT WAS
A LOW BLOW, AND HONESTLY, WHEN
YOU WERE GUNNING FOR ME, I WAS
HURT.
THATS ALL I CAN SAY.
THE TRUTH IS, THERE IS A PART OF
ME THAT FEELS LIKE IVE BEEN
CREATING A CHARACTER OUT HERE.
IN MY REAL LIFE, IM SOMEBODY
WHO HAS LIKE DOZENS IF NOT
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE WHO WORK FOR
ME.
IM VERY INTENSE.
I AM REALLY COMPETITIVE.
AND I CAME IN WANTING TO PLAY
SUPER HARD, BUT GETTING TO THE
GOLIATH CAMP WAS A VERY HUMBLING
EXPERIENCE, BECAUSE I FELT LIKE
THE INPROVERTED WRITER KID THAT
I HAVE NOT FELT SINCE I WAS LIKE
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL WHERE LIKE
EVERYONE IS AROUND THE SAME AGE,
THEYRE ALL "BAY WATCH"
ATTRACTIVE, BIG EGO
PERSONALITIES, SO I STARTED
PLAYING A GAME WHICH WAS LIKE
IM JUST HAPPY TO BE HERE.
IM JUST HERE FOR THE
EXPERIENCE.
LIKE I CANT FIND MYSELF.
WHEN I GOT DOWN TO NINE PEOPLE,
I KNEW I HAD MY MOMENTS AND I
COULD START INFLUENCING THE
GAME.
GREAT ANSWER.
AND ALISON, IF YOU DONT
MIND, I THINK WE KNEW HE WAS
GOOD AND HE WAS PLAYING THE GAME
GOOD, AND I KNOW HE CAN SIT HERE
AND WIN YOUR VOTE TONIGHT
BECAUSE HE WAS PLAYING THE GAME
HARD.
THE REASON I KNEW HE WAS DOING
IT BECAUSE I WAS DOING A BIT OF
THE SAME THING.
IM AWE SHUCKS KENTUCKY BOY AND
EVERYBODY THOUGHT I COULDNT
COME OUT HERE AND PLAY A GOOD
GAME.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN ME AND
MILK IS I HAD TO TURN MY GAME
ON.
I COULDNT JUST RIDE TO THE END
WITH WHATEVER GOODNIGHTS WANTED
ME AS THEIR LITTLE SIDE SHOW OR
WHATEVER.
I HAD TO TAKE MY FATE AND PUT IT
IN MY OWN HANDS.
OKAY.
ARE WE GOOD WITH SOCIAL?
NO?
Jeff: WOW.
OKAY.
LETS KEEP GOING.
I HAVE A COMMENT TO ANGELINA
THAT I HAD BEEN WANTING TO SAY.
I FEEL LIKE NOW THE RIGHT TIME
TO SAY IT.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU PROPS FOR
BEING THE LAST WOMAN LEFT, AND I
WANT TO BRING ATTENTION TO THE
FACT THAT WOMEN ARE TREATED
DIFFERENTLY IN THIS GAME.
THANK YOU.
IF YOURE ASSERTIVE, YOURE
SEEN AS BOSTON YEAR, IF YOURE
EMOTIONAL, YOURE SEEN AS
HYSTERICAL.
SO I KNOW YOURE UP AGAINST NOT
ONLY THE DIFFICULTY OF THE GAME,
BUT ISSUES THAT FACE US OUTSIDE
OF THE GAME.
I APPRECIATE THAT, GABBY.
I THINK TO GABBYS POINT, AS A
WOMAN AND AS A WOMAN OF COLOR, I
SOMETIMES OVERCOMPENSATE, IVE
BEEN TOLD I SOUND INTERVIEWEE OR
INCENDIARY -- INCENDIARY SEAR.
ONE ON ONE I CAN BE MORE ME, BUT
IN A SPACE LIKE THIS ITS HARDER
TO DO THAT.
I WANT THE WRAP UP OUTWIT.
I WANT TO TOUCH ON EACH OF YOUR
SOCIAL GAMES.
NICK, COMING FROM DAVID, BEING
IN THE MINORITY, AND CULTIVATING
HAS TO RELATIONSHIPS AND THESE
FINAL TWO AND FINAL THREE DEALS,
I THINK IT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
ANGELINA, IT WAS INTERESTING TO
SEE YOUR EVOLUTION IN THE GAME.
I THINK IT WAS ONE OF THE BEST
MOVES TO MESS UP ON THE
ELIZABETH AND COME BACK FROM IT
AS AN UNDERDOG STORY, AND MIKE,
YOU PLAYED THE SOCIAL GAME THAT
I CAME HERE TO PLAY.
IT WAS VERY IMPRESSIVE TO WATCH.
I KNOW YOU ARE AN ACTOR, BUT I
KNOW YOURE PLAYING YOURSELF AS
MUCH AS YOU CAN IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR," SO I WANT THE
CONGRATULATE YOU ON THAT.
THANK YOU, CARA.
THANKS, KARA.
Jeff: TIME NOW TO MOVE ON
TO THE OUTPLAY PORTION OF THE
GAME.
THIS IS THE CONDITIONS PUT ON
YOU.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE IN THE JUNGLE.
YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH IDOLS OR
ADVANTAGES AND TWISTS OR
SWITCHES.
HOW DID YOU PLAY THAT PART OF
THE GAME?
MIKE, THE OUTPLAY PORTION
PART OF IT IS ABOUT CAMPFIRE.
THE ONLY TIME WE SAW YOU AT CAMP
OTHER THAN TALKING WAS EATING
RICE OR DRINKING COFFEE.
IM PRETTY SURE HERE THE FIRST
TIME THEY SEEN YOU MAKE FIRE WAS
LAST NIGHT.
BRAVO, IT WAS IMPRESSIVE, BUT
WHERE WERE YOU WHENEVER WE WERE
MAKING FIRE, BUILDING SHELTER.
ARE YOU SAYING I WAS LAZY?
ARE YOU CALLING ME THE L WORD?
WHEN I WATCHED YOU MAKE THAT
SHELTER.
THERES NO WAY I COULD HAVE CUT
THOSE BAMBOOS AND DID WHAT YOU
DID.
THATS NOT MY STRENGTH, DUDE.
AT THE SAME TIME, IM PROUD OF
HOW I DID IN THE CHALLENGES.
I AM THE OLDER GUY, AND I
PARTICIPATED IN EVERY CHALLENGE
LIKE ALL OF THEM.
LIKE MORE THAN ANYBODY.
AND I WAS NEVER THE MONKEY ON
ANYONES BACK.
I WAS ACTUALLY LIKE STOKED ON
HOW I DID IN ALL THE CHALLENGES.
I WAS HAPPY.
MIKE, THANK YOU FOR GIVING US
YOUR ANSWER, I WOULD LIKE TO
GIVE ANGELINA AND NICK A CHANCE
TO TELL US, HOW ARE YOU A DAVID
AND HOW ARE YOU A GOLIATH?
YOU WANT THEM TO REVERSE?
YES.
Jeff: ANGELINA?
I FELT A LOT OF THE DAVID
JOURNEY.
I CAME OUT HERE WITH ZERO
SURVIVAL SKILLS.
I DIDNT KNOW HOW THE MAKE FIRE.
I WAS SUPER FEARFUL OF ALL OF
THE CHALLENGES.
AND SO I HAD TO MUSTER UP A LOT
OF COURAGE AND TAKE THOSE
CHANCES.
EVEN WITH THE ID.L. STUFF, I DUG
DEEP.
I WAS LIKE, I REALLY WANT TO
FIND THIS IDOL, AND I ENDED UP
FINDING THIS TEN-FOOT LADDER,
PUT IT AGAINST A ROCK WALL.
I LITERALLY CLIMBED TO THE TOP
OF THE WATERFALL.
I WAS STUCK UP THERE.
LIKE I DONT EVEN KNOW HOW HIGH.
SO I WENT SO HARD IN THE PAINT
FOR THE IDOL --
IS THAT WHAT THOSE TEARS WERE
REALLY FOR?
YES.
I DID RIP MY PANTS CLIMBING THE
ROCK WALL.
WOW.
IM LIKE, OH, MY GOD, ANGELINAS
ON A LADDER.
I GOT THE LADDER AND KEPT
CLIMBING.
100 FEET ON THE WALL.
I DONT KNOW.
IT WAS HIGH.
LONG STORY SHORT, I WAS SO FAR
OUT OF MY COMFORT ZONE.
I LEANED INTO IT.
GOOD FOR YOU, BECAUSE
PHYSICALLY WOMEN FIND IDOLS WAY
LESS OFTEN THAN MEN.
15% OF THEM HAVE BEEN FOUND
BY WOMEN.
IT WAS EXTREMELY HARD IDOL TO
FIND.
I HAVE ONE FOLLOW-UP
QUESTION.
ANGELINA, COULD YOU TALK ABOUT
MAKING A FAKE IDOL, BECAUSE IT
FELT LIKE A PLOY TO JUST WEARS
ME.
ABSOLUTELY NOT TO EMBARRASS
YOU.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
MY INTENT WAS --
ARE YOU SHAKING YOUR HEAD?
YEAH, YOU WANTED TO EMBARRASS
HER.
NEW YORK I DID NOT.
GO AHEAD.
MY INTENT WAS I DID NOT WANT YOU
TO GO AFTER MIKE.
THE OTHER THING IS LIKE YOU AND
I HAVE BEEN BATTLING FOR A
WHILE, AND I FELT LIKE IT WOULD
BE LIKE AN EPIC END TO THE
BATTLE, SO THERE WAS A LITTLE
BIT OF NEAT RICKS TO HAVE FUN
WITH THE GAME AND PLAY
AGGRESSIVELY, BUT THE MAIN POINT
WAS TO KEEP MIKE SAFE.
OKAY.
AND I DO WANT TO GET TO NICK,
TOO.
HOW AM AGOLIATH?
FIRST, SIMPLY PUT, A GOODNIGHT,
THEY JUST ARE.
LIKE DAN, YOURE 63".
YOU JUST ARE.
JOHN, YOU CAN PROBABLY BREAK
THAT BOLDER IN HALF.
YOU JUST.
CAN LOOKING AT IT LIKE, THAT I
DO HAVE SOME GOLIATH QUALITIES
IN HOW IT RELATES TO OUTPLAY.
IM GOOD AT PUZZLES.
I DONT SIT AROUND DOING PUZZLES
ALL DAY.
THAT LED TO TWO IMMUNITY WINS.
IM THE ONLY PERSON THAT WON
MORE THAN ONE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
IM NATURAL PEOPLE PERSON.
THAT LED TO KNOWING WHERE THE
IDOLS RUSSIA WHERE THE
ADVANTAGES ARE.
I FOUND THE SECRET ADVANTAGE
BECAUSE DAVIE AND I FOUND THE
CLUE TOGETHER.
ME, CARL, AND DAVIE, WE ALL
THREE KNEW EACH OTHERS
ADVANTAGES.
THATS A TESTAMENT TO MY NATURAL
ABILITY TO CONNECT WITH
SOMEBODY.
AND WANT TO PLAY WITH ME AND TOO
HAVE FUN WITH ME.
AND THEN, OF COURSE, THE
INTELLIGENCE HELPED IN THE
CHALLENGES.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LETS MOVE ON TO THE FINAL FAST.
OUTLAST.
THIS IS WHERE IT SHIFTS BACK TO
YOU.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO DESCRIBE
TO THEM YOUR JOURNEY.
WHAT DID YOU HAVE TO GO THROUGH?
WHAT DID YOU HAVE TO OVERCOME TO
OUTLAST EVERYBODY TO GET HERE?
THIS IS YOUR PERSONAL STORY OF
WHAT THIS 39-DAY JOURNEY WAS
LIKE FOR YOU.
ANGELINA?
GET US STARTED.
SO LOOKING BACK ON DAY ONE ON
THE BARGE, I STARTED TO REALIZE
WHY I WAS A GOODNIGHT.
A LOT OF MY LIFE EVERYTHING THAT
IVE SET MY MIND TO I HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO DO.
AS A MILITARY WIFE, I THINK
WERE SOME OF THE STRONGEST
PEOPLE OUT THERE.
WE GO THROUGH A LOT IN OUR
PERSONAL HIERVETION I WAS LIKE,
IF I CAN GO THROUGH DEPLOYMENTS
MAYBE THAT WILL TRANSFER TO THE
GAME.
IT WAS OUT HERE THAT FOR THE
FIRST TIME I REALLY FELT LIKE I
HIT A ROCK BOTTOM.
I REALLY FELT LIKE BEATEN DOWN
AND VULNERABLE AND OUT OF
CONTROL IN SOME WAYS, KIND OF,
YOU KNOW, DAMAGED GOODS AS
PEOPLE SAID.
BUT I WAS ABLE TO RISE AND PICK
MYSELF UP FROM THAT SITUATION
AND BUILD RELATIONSHIPS AND FIND
A PATH FORWARD.
AND GET BACK INTO A POSITION OF
STRENGTH.
SO I FEEL LIKE I AM THE MOST
BATTLE-TESTED PLAYER SITTING IN
FRONT OF YOU.
THE STORY OF DAVID AND GOLIATH
IS ABOUT TRIUMPH.
I FEEL LIKE MY STORY OUT HERE
WAS ABOUT TRIUMPH.
Jeff: NICK?
OKAY.
SO I WENT THROUGH TONGS OF UPS
AND DOWNS IN THIS GAME, WHETHER
IT BE GETTING SWAPPED TO A TRIBE
WITH THREE GOLIATHS OR TWO
DAVID, WORKING MY BUTT OFF TO
FINALLY GET THE DAVID ALLIANCE
AN ADVANTAGE, AND THEN NEXT
THING I KNOW IM THE ONLY DAVID
LEFT.
IM NOT JUST FACING GOLIATHS.
I FEEL LIKE IM UP AGAINST THE
WHOLE PHILISTINE ARMY WHEN ITS
FOUR GOLIATHS AND ONE DAVID.
ITS WHAT IVE ALWAYS KNOWN.
FIGHTING MY WAY OUT OF THESE
STRUGGLES, HOW IVE DONE MY
WHOLE LIFE.
I MEAN, MY MOM PASSED AWAY FROM
A DRUG OVERDOSE, SO THATS WHY I
DO WHAT I DO FOR A LIVING.
I HELP PEOPLE WHO STRUGGLE WITH
DRUG ADDICTION INSTEAD OF THEM
GOING TO PRISON, I TRY TO GET
THEM TO GO TO REHAB.
YOU KNOW, BASICALLY JUST LET
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND LIKE, IF THERE
IS A BREATH LEFT IN YOUR BODY,
LIFE IS WORTH LIVING.
AND IF YOURE IN THIS GAME, IF
YOU HAVE ANY SPOT LEFT IN YOU,
IF YOU HAVE A LEFT IN YOUR BODY,
THIS GAME IS WORTH PLAYING.
YOURE NEVER OUT OF IT.
I WAS A DAVID THE ENTIRE GAME,
AND I HAD TO FIND WHATEVER
SLINGSHOT I COULD, WHETHER IT BE
THE SOCIAL GAME, THE STRATEGY
GAME, THE IMMUNITY WIN, AN
ADVANTAGE, AN IDOL, NEW
RELATIONSHIP, OLD RELATIONSHIP,
WHATEVER IT TOOK, I HAD TO FIND
MY SLINGSHOT AND I HAD TO FIND
AS MANY STONES AS I COULD FIND,
BECAUSE I THINK I WAS THE
UNDERDOG MOST OF THIS GAME.
NO.
Jeff: MIKE.
AS FAR AS MY GAME, I DONT
KNOW.
I NEVER REALLY FELT TOO NERVOUS.
I WANTED TO PLAY A GOOD GAME.
IT WASNT LIKE I JUST WANTED TO
GET TO THE END AS LIKE A GOAT OR
AS LIKE SOMEBODY WHO WASNT
PLAYING.
I WANTED TO PLAY.
AND I FEEL LIKE I DID PLAY.
FOR ME, MY PERSONAL STRUGGLE WAS
LIKE, WHAT AM I -- WHAT DO I
STAND FOR.
WHAT AM I PLAYING FOR?
WHAT DO I STAND FOR?
AND TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
COMING ON HERE MEANS TO ME TO
TRY TO FEEL LIKE THERE WAS
SOMETHING WORTHY IN MY BATTLE TO
WIN.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THEY SAY, EVERY
RAINBOW HAS A POT OF GOLD AT THE
END, AND ITS LIKE, FOR ME, IT
WAS NEVER ABOUT THE POT OF GOLD.
ITS ABOUT THE RAINBOW.
AND IT SO SPEAKS TO WHAT I
VALUE, WHICH IS TAKING A RISK,
EMBARRASSING YOURSELF, HAVING AN
ADVENTURE.
IM NOT ACTING LIKE IM A SAINT.
IM NOT SAINT, BUT LIKE IT WAS
MORE ABOUT THE STRUGGLE FOR ME
TO FEEL LIKE THIS WAS A WORTHY
ENDEAVOR FOR ME TO WIN THIS
GAME.
I JUST WANT TO TELL ALL THREE
OF YALL CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
EVERY ADVENTURE HAS TO COME TO
AN END.
THERES BEEN A LOT OF
INFORMATION DISCUSSED TONIGHT.
IM GOING TO GIVE YOU GUYS A
MOMENT THE TAKE IT ALL IN.
THEN WE WILL VOTE FOR A WINNER
OF "SURVIVOR: DAVID VS.
GOLIATH."
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
THE ONLY THING LEFT TO DO IS
VOTE, SO LETS GET A VOTE.
YOURE GOING TO VOTE.
WHATS YOUR NAME?
MY NAME IS SIMONE.
Jeff: HOW OLD ARE YOU?
I AM 13.
Jeff: WEVE BEEN DOING THIS
THE LAST FEW TIME, AND BETH
YOUNG WOMEN WERE RIGHT, SO
HERES YOUR JOB, TAKE THE PAR.
MENT AND THE PEN.
YOU HAVE TO WRITE DOWN, DONT
SHOW ME, WHO YOU EITHER WANT TO
WIN OR WHO YOU THINK IS GOING TO
WIN, AND THEN WELL SEE HOW YOU
DO.
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU GUY, WELL
HAVE THE VOTES.
WELL CROWN A WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR: DAVID VS. GOLIATH."
KEEP IT A SECRET.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
JURY, FOR THE LAST TIME, IT IS
TIME TO VOTE AND BRING THIS
SEASON TO AN END.
ILL REMIND YOU, YOURE VOTING
FOR A WINNER.
LETS DO IT.
ELIZABETH, YOURE UP.
YOU VOTED ME OUT, BRO.
YOURE NOT GETTING MY VOTE JUST
FOR THAT.
ALL THE DECISIONS YOU MADE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU OUTWIT OUTPLAYED AND
OUTLASTED.
I THINK YOU PLAYED A
TRANSFORMATIVE GAME, AND I HAVE
ENORMOUS RESPECT FOR YOUR
STRATEGIC PLAY.
THAT IS A CRITICAL DECIDING
FACTOR.
I HOPE THAT THIS CHANGES HOW THE
GAME IS PLAYED.
Jeff: ILL GO GET THE
VOTES.
JURY, NICK, ANGELINA, MIKE,
THANK YOU FOR ANOTHER GREAT
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
I WILL SEE YOU BACK IN LOS
ANGELES FOR THE READING OF THE
VOTES.
THIS IS SURREAL.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
HAVE A SEAT.
SO FUN THEME, DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH, FUN SEASON, BUT I GOT
TO SAY, IT WAS SUCH A JOY TO
WATCH YOU GUYS PLAY AND TO SEE
YOU OPEN YOURSELVES UP AND LET
US LEARN ABOUT YOUR STORIES.
ONE OF THE BEST TIMES IVE HAD
IN A LONG TIME ON "SURVIVOR," SO
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
BUT IT COMES DOWN TO THIS: ITS
A GAME FOR $1 MILLION.
OUR FINAL THREE, NICK, ANGELINA,
AND MIKE, YOU DID WHAT 17 OTHER
PEOPLE COULDNT DO.
YOU GOT HERE AND NOW THEY HAVE
MADE THEIR DECISION.
THE JURY HAS DECIDEED WHO THEY
THINK IS MOST WORTHY OF THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
$1 MILLION THAT GOES ALONG WITH
IT.
ONLY THING LEFT TO DO THIS
SEASON IS READ THE VOTES.
IM GOING TO READ THE VOTES.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST VOTE NICK.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
MIKE.
WERE TIED.
ONE VOTE NICK, ONE VOTE
MIKE.
TWO VOTES MIKE.
ONE VOTE NICK.
MIKE.
THREE VOTES MIKE, ONE VOTE NICK.
NICK.
THATS THREE VOTES MIKE, TWO
VOTES NICK.
NICK.
WERE TIED AGAIN.
ITS THE THREE VOTES MIKE, THREE
VOTES NICK.
NICK.
FOUR VOTES NICK, THREE VOTES
MIKE.
NICK.
FIVE VOTES MIKE, THREE VOTES --
FIVE VOTES NICK, THREE VOTES
MIKE.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR: DAVID
VS. GOLIATH," NICK.
THERE YOU GO.
THE WINNER OF OUR 37th
SEASON.
GO GIVE THE FAMILY A HUG.
WELL EARNED.
39 DAYS.
LETS SEE HOW SIMONE DID.
HOW DID OUR YOUNG VIEWER DO?
WHO DID YOU PUT UP, SIMONE?
SHOW US THAT VOTE.
SHE GOT IT RIGHT.
AND HERE ARE THE VOTES FROM THE
JURY.
TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT VOLTED FOR
WHO SO WE CAN SEE HOW THIS CAME
OUT.
ITS VERY HARD TO PLAY THIS GAME
AND VOTE PEOPLE OUT AND THEN GET
THEM TO COME BACK AND VOTE FOR
YOU.
THATS WHY IT IS SO TOUGH TO WIN
AND SO DELICIOUS WHEN YOU DO.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS THE "SURVIVOR" FINALE.
WE HAVE THE LIVE REUNION SHOW
COMING UP RIGHT AFTER THIS.
CELEBRATION RIGHT THERE.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org