Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
THERE WERE FOUR DAVIDS AND FOUR
GOLIATHS LEFT IN THE GAME.
FACING TRIBAL COUNCIL, NICK AND
GABBY REALIZED CRIST CRAN WAS
TOO BIG OF A THREAT.
I DONT TRUST CHRISTIAN FULLY
ANYMORE.
YOU PROBABLY NEVER WILL.
Jeff: BUT DAVIE WARNED
CHRISTIAN.
IM FLOORED.
ACCORDING TO DAVIE, GABBY IS
GUNNING FOR ME.
Jeff: AT TROOUK, CHRISTIAN
PLAYED HIS IDOL.
IM PLAYING THIS FOR MYSELF
TONIGHT.
Jeff: OKAY.
WHICH SENT HIS CLOSEST ALLY TO
THE JURY.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
LEAVING THE DAVIDS IN TOTAL
DISARRAY, AND THE GAME UP FOR
GRABS.
SEVEN ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
GOING INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL, I
HAD BEEN INFORMED BY DAVIE THAT
I SHOULD PLAY MY IDOL TONIGHT.
I PLAYED MY IDOL.
I SURVIVED.
BUT I STILL GOT FIVE VOITS VOTS.
IT INDICATES THAT IM A TARGET
TO SOME PEOPLE, INCLUDING NICK.
I SUSPECTED NICKS MOTIVES FOR
QUITE A BIT NOW, BECAUSE HES
NOT REALLY BEING HONEST WITH ME.
SERIOUSLY.
IM SORRY.
IM KIND OF BUMMED BECAUSE
THE BEST-CASE SCENARIO WAS IF
CHRISTIAN GOES HOME WITH AN IDOL
IN HIS POCKET, BUT HE PLAYED IT.
THE GOOD THING IS USUALLY THAT
MEANS ANOTHER IDOL IS PUT BACK
INTO THE GAME, AND I WANT TO BE
THE PERSON TO FIND IT.
SO TO DO THAT, IVE MADE, LIKE,
A FAKE IMMUNITY IDOL, AND
HOPEFULLY SOMEBODY CAN FIND THAT
IDOL, AND THEN THE SEARCH IS
OFF, AND ILL BE THE ONLY ONE
LEFT LOOKING.
AND THATS THE PARCHMENT OF MY
REAL IDOL, AND I MADE IT OUT OF
STUFF IVE BEEN COLLECTING
THROUGH THE WEEKS.
AND I TAKE IT UPON MYSELF TO
HIDE IT UNDER THE RAFT.
SO LATER ON, IM AT THE RAFT
WITH ANG LEAN AMIKE, AND
CHRISTIAN, ALL FOUR OF US THERE,
AND IM THINKING, YOU KNOW WHAT?
ILL FIND IT RIGHT HERE IN FRONT
OF EVERYBODY.
I STARTED KICKING AROUND A
STICK, LIKE, IN THE DIRT.
AND THEN I PULLED IT OUT AND IM
LIKE--
SHUT UP "P" WAIT, STOP!
DID YOU FIND IT?
SHHH!
HE DID.
HE FOUND THE IDOL.
DID YOU FIND THE IDOL?
OH, MY GOSH!
THATS YOURS.
OH, MY GOD, I CANT BELIEVE THEY
FELL FOR THAT.
EVERYBODY ERUPTS WITH
EXCITEMENT, AND IM JUST LETTING
EVERYBODY CONGRATULATE ME.
AND THE WHOLE TIME THIS IDOL IS
FAKE.
ITS NOT REAL.
AND IT JUST WORKS BEAUTIFUL.
LIKE, ITS TOO EASY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
ITS BASICALLY LIKE CALLING
OFF THE DOGS.
THE SEARCH IS OVER.
NOBODY IS GOING TO BE LOOKING
FOR THE IDOL, EXCEPT ME, AND
THAT MEANS I CAN FIND IT, AND
THEN I HAVE TWO IDOLS.
ME, ANG LENA, CHRISTIAN, AND
NICK WERE SITTING ON THE RAFT,
AND NICK JUST REACHES UNDER THE
RAFT AND FINDS THE IDOL JUST
NOW.
STOP IT.
NICK FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL UNDER THE RAFT, BUT IM
LIKE, I DONT KNOW, MAN.
I WAS BORN AT NIGHT, BUT I
WASNT BORN LAST NIGHT.
AND IM THINKING TO MYSELF,
HMMM, HES ALREADY GOT ONE IDOL.
WHAT IF HE JUST SIMPLY PULLED
OUT THE IDOL THAT HE HAS AND
OPENED IT UP IN FRONT OF THEM SO
NOBODY WOULD BE LOOKING FOR
IDOLS.
HES SMART ENOUGH TO DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, DAVIE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST KEEP
LOOKING FOR IDOLS.
IM, LIKE, DAVIE, YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT GOD HAS OUT HERE FOR YOU.
JUST SNOOP AROUND A LITTLE BIT
MORE.
SO IM LOOKING FOR THE IDOL,
GOING OVER BY THE WATERING HOLE.
IM LOOKING FOR ANY TYPE OF
RIBBONS.
ROLLED-UP SCROLLS.
NO LUCK.
AND IM KIND OF JUST DEPRESSED
AND MAYBE THERE REALLY ISNT
ANYTHING OUT HERE.
AND IF NICKS GOT TWO IDOLS, HE
COULD GO ALL THE WAY AND BEAT US
ALL, YOU KNOW.
HES A THREAT.
SO I NEED HELP TO TAKE OUT MY
BEST FRENEMY IN THIS GAME, MY
BOY NICK.
WELL, CHRISTIAN, CAN I TELL YOU
SOMETHING?
NICK HAS TWO IDOLS.
HOW THE-- HE FOUND THE SECOND
IDOL EXPWROO WE WOULD HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF HIM THIS NEXT
TRIBE.
DAVE SAYS, GUESS WHAT?
WE MIGHT HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF
NICK AT THIS NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
I SEE HIM GETTING READY TO
PICK ME AND YOU OFF WHEN THAT
OPPORTUNITY STRIKES.
OKAY.
AND IM THINKING, THATS
FANTASTIC BECAUSE NICK IS NOT IN
MY CORNER.
AND MOVING FORWARD, I HAVE TO
MAKE SURE THAT SOME OTHER THREAT
GOES OTHER THAN ME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE GET TO
TODAYS REWARD CHALLENGE?
YES.
YEAH.
Jeff: FOR TODAYS
CHALLENGE, YOURE GOING TO BE
ATTACHED TO A ROPE.
ON MY "GO," YOULL RACE TO
GATHER THAT ROPE.
WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE ENOUGH,
YOULL RACE OVER AND UNDER A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
YOULL THEN USE SANDBAGS AND
ATTEMPT TO KNOCK OVER A STACK OF
BLOCKS.
FIRST PERSON TO FINISH WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR.
YES.
YEAH.
Jeff: YOULL BE TAKEN BY
HELICOPTER TO THE MALA MALA
BEACH CLUBS, TRULY ONE OF THE
MOST SPECTACULAR PLACES IN FIJI
WHERE YOU WILL HAVE ACCESS TO
THEIR ENTIRE MENU-- SURF AND
TURF, SLIDERS, FRIED CHICKEN.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: SANDWICHES.
WOW.
Jeff: THE WORKS.
Jeff: YOU RETURN BACK TO
CAMP REFRESHED, REJUVENATED AND
REFUELED IN TIME FOR THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
THIS IS A BIG REWARD.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
OH, GOD, JUST THINKING ABOUT
IT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO, FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
YUP.
Jeff: GO!
FIRST JOB IS TO GATHER ENOUGH
ROPE.
OW!
Jeff: THE QUESTION IS HOW
MUCH IS ENOUGH?
ARE YOU TRYING TO GUESSTIMATE
HOW MUCH YOU NEED TO GET THROUGH
THE OBSTACLES TO THE SANDBAGS
AND WHERE THE SANDBAGS ARE GOING
TO LAND ONCE YOU THROW THEM.
SOMEBODY GETTING READY TO MAKE A
MOVE.
ITS GOING TO BE DAVIE HEADING
OUT FIRST.
HE THINKS HE HAS ENOUGH.
NOBODY ELSE LEADING YET.
DAVIE OVER AND UNDER THE
OBSTACLES.
DAVIE FIRST TO GET TO HIS
SANDBAGS.
HE TOSSES AND KNOCKS A FEW
BLOCKS OFF.
HERE COMES ALISON.
HERE COMES ANGELINA NOW GETTING
IN ON IT.
HERE COMES NICK.
WILL THEY HAVE ENOUGH ROPE?
DAVE WEANOTHER NICE TOSS.
FOUR BLOCKS HIT.
YOU HAVE TO KNOCK THE BLOCKS
COMPLETELY OFF.
DOES DAVIE HAVE ENOUGH ROPE NOW
TO GET TO HIS SANDBAGS?
HE DOESNT.
HE CAN ONLY GET TWO, AND THAT IS
GOING TO COST HIM.
DAVIE NOW WORKING WITH JUST TWO
SANDBAGS, WHICH OPENS THE DOOR
FOR EVERYBODY ELSE.
ALISON FIRING.
TOO BAD I CANT THROW!
Jeff: HERE COMES NICK AND
ANGELINA.
NICK WITH A HUGE HIT!
AND ANOTHER BIG HIT.
IT IS DAVIE AND NICK RIGHT NOW.
DAVIES STRETCHING OUT AS FAR AS
HE CAN TO GET TWO BAGS.
KARA NOW IN ON IT.
KARA WITH A NICE HIT.
NICK MISSES.
ANGELINA DOES NOT HAVE ENOUGH
ROPE.
SHES GOT TO GO BACK.
A HUGE STEP BACK FOR ANGELINA.
SHES GOT TO GO WAY BACK TO THE
START.
KARA WITH A BIG HIT.
SHES IN IT NOW.
NO!
Jeff: IF YOU DONT HAVE
ENOUGH ROPE, YOUVE GOT TO GO
BACK.
DAMN IT!
Jeff: DAVIE DOWN TO TWO
BLOCKS LEFT.
NICK WITH A HIT.
DAVIE COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
HE HAS ONE BLOCK LEFT.
NICK WITH TWO BLOCKS.
DAVIE WITH ONE.
WHO WILL GET BACK QUICK ENOUGH
FOR A SHOT?
NICK KNOCKS ONE OFF.
NICK DOWN TO HIS LAST BLOCK, AND
DAVIE DOWN TO HIS LAST BLOCK.
IT IS IT FOR THE WIN.
AND ANOTHER MISS!
NICK, GOING FOR THE WIN?
OH!
Jeff: NICK HITS IT.
IT DOESNT GO OFF.
IT IS BACK AND FORTH.
DAVIE DOES IT FOR THE WIN!
NICE!
Jeff: DAVIE WINS REWARD!
OH, BABY!
THAT WAS A NAIL-BITER.
Jeff: THAT WAS A SHOOT-OUT.
GOOD JOB, DAVIE.
Jeff: DAVIE, COME ON OVER.
CONGRATS, DAVIE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
HARD FOUGHT, MAN.
Jeff: BIG WIN ON DAY 33.
YOU ALREADY KNOW YOURE GOING TO
ENJOY FOOD, BEVERAGES.
THE QUESTION IS WHO IS GOING TO
JOIN YOU?
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO COME ALONG.
LOOK AT THOSE FACES.
YOU FEEL THAT PRESSURE?
ABSOLUTELY, JEFF.
Jeff: SO WHAT IS THE
FEELING RIGHT NOW?
THE FEELING IS I HAVE TO BASE
MY DECISION ON THE PEOPLE THAT
IVE BEEN CLOSEST WITH THE
LONGEST.
AND I HAVE TO REPAY NICK BACK
FOR HIS DEBT FOR CHOOSING ME FOR
THE FAMILY VISIT.
Jeff: NICK, COME ON OVER.
BEE BOTH CHOSE YOU, DAVIE.
Jeff: NOW, BEFORE DAVIE
MAKES HIS FINAL CHOICE OF WHOS
GOING TO JOIN HIM, DOES ANYBODY
HERE WANT TO PLEAD THEIR CASE?
DAVIE, THE HARD PART--
I WILL SAY SOMETHING, DAVIE,
I HATE TO PULL THIS CARD, BUT
WHEN I-- WHEN I GOT THE RICE FOR
THE TRIBE, YOU WON IMMUNITY.
AND I WAS SO PROUD OF YOU.
AND WEVE BEEN ABLE TO EAT
BECAUSE OF THAT.
I REALLY DIDNT WANT TO PULL
THAT OUT, BUT IF THAT MEANS
ANYTHING, THIS WOULD MEAN
EVERYTHING TO ME TODAY.
I REALLY THINK-- IVE GOT TO
LOOK OUT FOR THE PERSON THATS
BEEN LOOK OUT FOR ME EVER SINCE
WE WERE BACK ON THE VUKU TRIBE.
KARA.
IVE GOT TO GO WITH HER.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: KARA, COME ON OVER.
OH, MY GOD.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
SORRY, GUYS.
SORRY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DAVIE, YOU
CHOSE KARA AND NICK.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HAVE A FUN
AFTERNOON.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME ON THE
"SURVIVOR" HELICOPTER.
HAVE A GREAT TIME.
SORRY.
Jeff: ANGELINA, ALISON,
CHRISTIAN, MIKE, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
I DIDNT WANT TO USE ME
WINNING RICE FOR THE CRIEB AS
ANY KIND OF CURRENCY, BUT DAVIE
CHOOSES KARA OVER ME.
AND I CANT HELP BUT THINK DAVIE
IS PLAYING THE FIELD.
DAVIE IS KEEPING ALL HIS OPTIONS
OPEN RIGHT NOW, SO IT COULD BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR MISTAKE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
RICE!
WOOO!
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME IN 33 DAYS
THAT I TRULY FEEL, LIKE, ANGRY,
SO IM JUST--
YEAH.
BUT IN THIS MOMENT ITS JUST
KIND OF LIKE--
A BITTER TASTE.
WELL, ITS JUST LIKE
SURPRISED.
I COME BACK TO CAMP, AND IM
LEGITIMATELY PISSED.
YOU KNOW, I CANT BELIEVE THAT
DAVIE WOULD CHOOSE KARA OVER ME.
AND THE OTHER THING IS, LIKE--
AGAIN IM NOT-- I DO NOT WANT
ANY RECIPROCITY OR FAVOR ABOUT
THE RICE, BUT I STEPPED OUT OF A
PUZZLE CHALLENGE IN ORDER FOR US
ALL TO HAVE RICE.
SO ITS, LIKE, COME ON, DAVIE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT IS HIS OWN
DECISION.
LETS TALK ABOUT THAT OVER
SOME RICE!
HAVE SOME RICE.
IM JUST FUMING.
SO I SPRING INTO ACTION TO MAKE
THE BIGGEST POOT OF RICE THAT WE
CAN MANAGE.
I GUESS IT WAS REVENGE RICE.
YEAH!
BY CHOOSING KARA AND BY
CHOOSING NICK, THIS IS THE EXACT
EPITOME OF KEEP MY FRENEMIES
CLOSE, NICK; AND MY FRIENDS
CLOSER, KARA.
I DEFINITELY KNOW THAT THERE
WILL BE AN OPPORTUNITY AT THE
REWARD FOR JUST ME AND KARA TO
TALK.
BOOLA!
AND THATS WHEN I WOULD HAVE
MY CHANCE TO PUT MY PLAN INTO
ACTION, WHICH IS GETTING NICK
OUT OF THIS GAME.
FINALLY, US THREE GET TO
SPEND TIME TOGETHER
UNINTERRUPTED.
UH-HUH.
THIS REWARD IS LIKE "GOODFELLAS"
IF YOURE GOING TO TAKE THEM
OUT, YOURE GOING TO TREAT THEM
REALLY WELL AND THEN SLIT THEIR
THROATS IN THE END.
I OVERDID IT.
SO, YES, NOW THAT NICKS
GONE...
YES.
ARE YOU READY FOR SOME BIG
BOMBS RIGHT NOW?
YES.
NOT ONLY DOES NICK HAVE AN
IDOL, BUT HE MAY POSSIBLY HAVE
TWO IDOLS.
ANOTHER ONE?
YEAH.
HE NEEDS TO GET OUT.
EXACTLY.
EVERYBODY AT CAMP KNOWS THAT
NICK NOW HAS THE IDOL THAT WAS
FOUND UNDERNEATH THE RAFT.
BUT I AM SHOCKED WHEN DAVIE SAYS
THAT NICK HAS YET ANOTHER IDOL.
I MEAN, NICK IS A HUGE THREAT TO
EVERYONES GAME.
WHAT IM THINKING IS
TOMORROW, IF NICK DOESNT WIN,
ME, YOU, ALISON AND CHRISTIAN
CAN GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
IM SO DOWN FOR THAT BECAUSE
THATS WHAT I WAS THINKING TO
BEGIN WITH.
DONT TELL ANGELINA AND MIKE.
FOR SURE.
DAVIE WANTS TO VOTE OUT NICK AND
IM DROOLING AT THIS IDEA.
THIS SOUNDS LOOK A FEASIBLE PLAN
THAT IS ABSOLUTELY GOING TO TAKE
MY GAME TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
WHATS UP, MIKE?
IT WAS FUN?
IT WAS GREAT, MAN.
SORRY, DUDE.
NO WORRIES.
MIKE, YOURE THE BEST
WELCOMING COMMITTEE.
SO COMING BACK TO CAMP MY NUMBER
ONE CONVERSATION HAS TO BE WITH
ALISON.
TELL ME ABOUT THE FOOD.
BECAUSE IN ORDER FOR THIS
PLAN TO HAPPEN, WE ALSO NEED TO
GET ALISON ON BOARD TO GO ALONG
WITH THIS.
SO NICK HAS THE IDOL IN CASE YOU
DONT KNOW.
AND SO DAVIE WANTS TO VOTE NICK
OUT, AND HE WANTS IT TO BE ME,
YOU, DAVIE, AND CHRISTIAN.
OH, MY GOD.
TO VOTE NICK, AND THEN LEAVE
ANGELINA AND MIKE OUT OF IF.
BECAUSE IF WE RISK AT ALL
TELLING THEM, TOO, I FEEL THEY
WOULD USE IT TO TELL NICK.
THIS IS INSANE.
KARA REVEALS TO ME THAT DAVIE
NOW IS GUNNING FOR NICK.
I JUST KIND OF SMILED BECAUSE IN
THE PAST, I HAVE BEEN ON THE
BOTTOM, AND I WAS GOING TO BE
NEXT OUT.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, IM NO LONGER
PRESSED UP AGAINST THE WALL, BUT
INSTEAD, PERHAPS, MAKING A MOVE.
OH, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
SO EXCITING.
SO KARA GAVE ME SOME HUGE
INFORMATION.
DAVIE UNLOADED ON KARA AND WAS
LIKE, "I WANT NICK OUT NOW."
I WANT TO DEMONSTRATE WITH MIKE
THAT IM GENUINE WHEN I SAY I
WANT IT TO WORK AS A PAIR.
WHEN I THINK THAT BY PROVIDING
THIS INFORMATION TO HIM, I AM
PROVING THAT.
THATSWELL, THATS WHY I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU BECAUSE IM
WEIGHING IT OVER IN MY MIND.
DURING THE DAVIE WANTS NICK
OUT OF THE GAME REALLY BREAKS
THE GAME WIDE OPEN.
ITS SO FUN THEY THEYRE
GOING FUR EACH OTHER.
AND I ACTUALLY FEEL LIKE NICK IS
A BIG THREAT TO WIN BUT RIGHT
NOW IM REALLY TORN, BECAUSE
NICK AND I HAVE BEEN BONDED
SINCE WE JOIN JABENI, AND IT
MADE ME THINK REALLY HARD ABOUT
WHAT I NEED TO DO ABOUT THIS
NEXT VOTE.
AND IM EXCITED TO SEE WHAT I
DO.
I WANT TO SURPRISE MYSELF.
♪ ♪
WHEN I WOKE UP THIS MORNING,
IM STILL THINKING THERES STILL
SOME HOPE THAT MAYBE THERES AN
IDOL OUT THERE.
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF, DAVIE,
MAYBE YOU NEED TO GO WALK AROUND
AND SEARCH.
SO AS SOON AS THE SUN RISES, I
STARTED SEARCHING.
I SEARCHED EVERYWHERE-- BY THE
ROCK, BY THE TREE MAIL, BY THE
RAFT, OVER BY THE WATERING
HOLE-- HOPING THAT THERES
SOMETHING THAT WILL POP OUT AT
ME.
THEN OUT OF THE BLUE, I SEE SOME
TYPE OF BLUE CLOTH IN A STICK.
I GRAB IT.
IM LIKE, YES, BABY.
THIS IS IT.
YES!
I UNTIE IT.
I OPEN IT, AND THERE ARE THOSE
WORDS THEY LOVE TO SEE OUT HERE
IN FIJI.
IT SAYS, "CONGRATULATIONS."
I REMEMBER WHERE THE MERGE FEAST
WAS.
ITS AT THE END OF THE BEACH,
WAY FAR AWAY FROM THE CAMP.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE I NEED TO
BE AND IM READY TO GET THERE.
( THUNDER )
♪ ♪
SO I WAIT UNTIL ITS RAINING,
WHILE EVERYONE IN CAMP IS
DISTRACTED BY THE STORM THATS
COMING TONIGHT, AND I DECIDE TO
MAKE MY BREAK AND FIND OUT WHAT
THIS ADVANTAGE IS.
♪ ♪
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, AND ITS ONLY GOOD FOR
THIS NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HOWEVER, THAT CAN CHANGE IF IM
WILLING TO PLAY THE GAME THATS
IN FRONT OF ME.
I WOULD SMASH ONE OF THE FIRST
TWO URNS.
IF I CHOOSE CORRECTLY, I WOULD
EXTEND MY IDOL ANOTHER TRIBAL.
FICHOOSE THE WRONG ONE, I
WOULDNT BE ABLE TO VOTE AT THE
NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ITS NEVER EASY ON "SURVIVOR."
IF I LOSE THIS VOTE, IT COULD
END UP BEING A 3-3 TIE.
SOMEBODY COULD GO TO ROCKS.
I COULD GO HOME ANYWAY, AND WIN
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE, AND NOT
NEED THIS IDOL.
BUT IF I HAVE THIS IDOL, THEN I
CAN SAVE ME OR I CAN SAVE
CHRISTIAN.
I COULD PLAY THE IDOL FOR MIKE,
MAKING MIKE TRUST ME EVEN MORE.
WHAT IF NICK PLAYS HIS IDOL?
EVEN IF I CAN ONLY PLAY IT FOR
THIS ONE-- THAT CAN MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE A THREAT.
LIKE FLIPPING A COIN, FLIPPING A
FREAKING COIN.
WHEN MY MOTHER CAME HERE, SHE
SAID, "DAVIE, YOU HAVE TO
REMEMBER, WHEN YOURE IN A
DEBACLE, YOU HAVE TO CALL ON
GOD."
AND THATS WHAT I DECIDED TO DO.
LORD, IF ITS IN YOUR WILL FOR
ME TO PLAY THIS GAME, GIVE ME A
SIGN.
I ASKED GOD FOR A SIGN.
IM LOOKING AT THE FIRE TO SEE
IF ITS GOING TO POINT TO WHICH
URN I SHOULD BREAK.
THE WIND IS GOING THAT WAY, AND
I THINK THATS THE SIGN IM
LOOKING FOR.
I DONT THINK I WANT TO PLAY
THIS GAME.
THATS GOD TALKING TO ME, THIS
WIND BLOWING.
HES TELLING ME, YES, DUDE, YOU
MADE THE RIGHT DECISION.
BECAUSE I HAVE A PLAN THAT I
WANT TO PUT INTO ACTION TO TAKE
OUT NICK.
AND ME LOSING MY VOTE COULD MESS
UP THAT PLAN.
SO IM SAFE.
IM IN THE DRIVERS SEAT.
IM READY TO BUCKLE UP AND TAKE
OFF.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LETS GET
TO TODAYS IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, KARA.
YOU LOOK COLD IN THIS RAIN.
I STILL HAVE TO TAKE BACK THE
NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO STAND ON A NARROW PERCH
WHILE BALANCING A BALL ON A
WOODEN DISK.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS, WELL ADD
MORE BALLS, MAKING IT MORE
DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU FALL OFF THE
PERCH OR YOUR BALL DROPS, YOURE
OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A
ONE-IN-SIX SHOT AT GETTING TO
THE END.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE SEVENTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
WE ARE GETTING DOWN TO IT.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY STEP UP ON
YOUR PERCH.
GRAB YOUR BALL.
PLACE IT ON YOUR DISK.
IM GOG COUNT YOU IN.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
A LITTLE BIT OF FIJIAN RAIN
COMING DOWN, MAKING IT A LITTLE
MORE INTERESTING.
THE RULES ARE SIMPLE: IF YOUR
BALL DROPS, YOURE OUT.
IF YOU STEP OFF THE PERCH,
YOURE OUT.
YOUR DISK CANNOT TOUCH YOUR
BODY.
ITS OKAY ON YOUR FOREARM.
ITS OKAY WEDGED AGAINST YOUR
ELBOW.
ANGELINAS BALL IS STARTING TO
MOVE.
CHRISTIAN, WOW.
SUDDEN MOVE, QUICKLY GETS HIS
BALL BACK WHERE HE WANTS IT.
MIKES FEET REALLY SHAKING.
NICKS BALL TAKING A LITTLE
JOURNEY.
ALISON HAS BEEN MOVING THIS
ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
15 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND.
IF YOU SURVIVE THERE, WILL BE A
FRESH START, AND WELL ADD A
SECOND BALL THAT YOU WILL HAVE
TO BALANCE ON YOUR DISK.
HERE WE GO.
FIVE.
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
EVERYBODY IS SAFE.
NICE JOB.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY IS ON THEIR
PERCH.
AND THIS THJ IS BACK ON.
THIS CHALLENGE IS BACK ON AND
THIS WILL GET A LOT MORE
DIFFICULT NOW.
YOU HAVE TWO BALLS YOU ARE
TRYING TO BALANCE ON YOUR DISK.
MIKES BALL STARTING TO MOVE.
GOTTA GET IT BACK IN CONTROL.
ANGELINA, BOTH BALLS SEPARATING,
HANGING ON OPPOSITE SIDES OF THE
DISK.
THAT IS A DANGEROUS SPOT TO BE.
KARAS BALLS ARE NOW ON THE
MOVE.
KARA DROPS.
SHES OUT.
GENTLY TAKE A STEP BACKWARDS.
ANGELINA TRYING TO GET BACK IN
CONTROL OF HER BALLS.
ANGELINAS BALLS DROP.
SHE IS OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
DAVIES BALLS STARTING TO
SEPARATE NOW.
WHICH IS WORSE-- BALLS
SEPARATING OR BALLS CLANGING
TOGETHER?
BOTH GIVE YOU THAT UNCOMFORTABLE
FEELING IN THIS CHALLENGE.
CHRISTIAN WITH THE SLIGHTEST BIT
OF MOVEMENT.
NICK WOBBLING AGAIN.
ONCE AGAIN, GETTING IT BACK
UNDER CONTROL.
DAVIES BALLS NOW ON THE MOVE.
BOTH OF DAVIES BALLS DROP AT
THE SAME TIME.
DAVES OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO FOUR.
CHRISTIAN RIGHT ON THE EDGE.
CHRISTIAN, BALL DANGLING ON THE
EDGE OF HIS DISK.
CHRISTIAN COULD SENSE IT WAS
OVER BEFORE IT HAPPENED.
CHRISTIAN IS OUT, AND WERE DOWN
TO THREE-- ALISON, MIKE, AND
NICK.
WE ARE FOUR MINUTES INTO THIS
ROUND.
SURVIVE HERE, WE GO TO A THIRD
BALL.
YOU NEED TO HANG ON RIGHT HERE.
NICK NOW BACK IN CONTROL.
NICK DROPS.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
IT IS A SHOWDOWN BETWEEN TWO
GOLIATHS.
15 SECONDS LEFT IN THIS ROUND,
AND WE WILL ADD A THIRD BALL.
HANG IN THERE.
YOURE ALMOST THERE.
FIVE.
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
YOURE BOTH SAFE.
GRAB YOUR BECAUSE.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
Jeff: WE WILL MOVE TO THE
THIRD AND FINAL ROUND.
ALL RIGHT, WE ARE IN THE FINAL
ROUND OF THIS CHALLENGE.
FOR IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED SPOT IN
THE FINAL SIX.
ALISON TRYING TO OVERCOME
WOBBLING LEGS.
THAT HAS BEEN THE THING THAT HAS
HAUNTED HER THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
CAN SHE GET IT IN CONTROL?
IT WOULD BE ALISONS SECOND
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN.
IT WOULD BE MIKES FIRST.
NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT TO BE
SECURE ON "SURVIVOR."
MIKE STARTING TO WOBBLE A
LITTLE.
GOTTA GET IT BACK IN CONTROL.
MIKE WITH ONE BALL ON THE EDGE
OF HIS DISK.
MIKES BALLS NOW ON THE MOVE.
THE BALL HANGING ON THE EDGE OF
HIS DISK.
ALISON DROPS.
SHES OUT.
MIKE WINS HIS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YAY!
Jeff: MIKE, COME ON OVER.
YAY, MIKE!
Jeff: MIKE, INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IS YOURS, SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU WILL SEE DAY 36 AND A
GUARANTEED SPOT IN THE FINAL
SIX.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, ONE OF
YOU WILL SEE YOUR DREAM COME TO
AN END, BECOME THE SEVENTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
THANKS.
BEING ABLE TO WIN AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE TODAY IS THRILLING.
AND RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE IM A
LITTLE LESS NERVOUS SWINGING
FROM THE HIP BECAUSE I HAVE THIS
IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE I CAN DO
WHAT WILL SERVE MY GAME THE
BEST.
♪ ♪
GOING INTO TONIGHTS TRIBAL
COUNCIL, I WANTED TO GET RID OF
CHRISTIAN, BUT ALISON WAS SUPER
CLOSE TO BINNING THE CHALLENGE,
AND SHES A HUGE PHYSICAL
THREAT.
AND IM WORRIED AND NERVOUS THAT
THERES MORE GOLIATHS THAN
DAVIDS.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
AND IT FEELS LIKE THE TIME IS
RIGHT FOR ALISON.
IT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
I KNEW WE WERE GONNA TALK.
YEAH, I THINK EVERYONES
GOING TO TALK TODAY.
WHO ARE YOU THINKING?
I WOULD RATHER VOTE ALISON
TONIGHT IF I CAN.
ALISON THIS TIME.
CHRISTIAN NEXT TIME.
OKAY.
TO ME ITS HILARIOUS THAT SO
MANY PEOPLE ARE PASSIONATE ABOUT
GETTING ALISON OUT.
THEY DONT KNOW THERES A PLAN
IN PLACE TO TAKE OUT NICK.
THATS HOW YOU EXECUTE A GOOD
BLINDSIDE.
YOU CANT LET EVERYBODY IN ON
IT.
IM EXCITED TO BE PART OF A
BLINDSIDE THAT WOULD CHANGE THE
REST OF THE GAME COMPLETELY.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH, IM FINE.
I FIND OUT THAT THERES TWO
DIFFERENT SCENARIOS BEING RUN.
THERES THIS BIG PUSH TO HAVE
ALISON OUT.
AND AT THE SAME TIME, DAVIE IS
GUNNING FOR NICK.
BUT HAVING THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE, I FEEL A LITTLE BIT
MORE BOLD.
IM EXCITED, LIKE, THIS IS WHAT
YOU COME TO "SURVIVOR" FOR IS
TO, LIKE, HAVE AN IMPACT ON THE
GAME, AND IM THINKING CHRISTIAN
IS STILL THE BIGGEST THREAT TO
WIN THE GAME.
AND SO I GOTTA GET THE VOTES TO
GET CHRISTIAN HOME TONIGHT.
I JUST HAD A NERVOUS FEELING
THAT THERES A PART OF ME THAT
THINKS MAYBE ITS TONIGHT FOR
CHRISTIAN.
I THINK NICK IS THE GREATER
THREAT.
ARE WE DOING SOMETHING
STUPID?
IS IT BETTER TO TAKE OUT
CHRISTIAN?
I WANT IT TO BE NICK.
IM HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS
ABOUT THIS ALISON THING.
UH-HUH.
BEYOND MY BASIC POSITION,
WHICH IS ALISON IS EASILY
BEATABLE IN THE END, CHRISTIAN
WILL WIN.
HE WILL BEAT ALL OF US.
WE WOULD BE CRAZY NOT TO TAKE
OUT CHRISTIAN NOW.
HE DOESNT HAVE IMMUNITY.
HE HAS NO MORE IDOLS.
ITS, LIKE, THIS IS THE TIME.
YEAH.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YEAH, I WILL THINK ABOUT IT.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE AS MUCH
LEVERAGE AS IM EVER GOG HAVE IN
THE GAME.
I HAVE AN IMMUNITY NECKLACE, AND
I HAVE A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
LISTEN TO ME, BUT NO ONES
BUDGING.
SO ITS GETTING DIFFICULT FOR ME
TO MARSHAL THE TROOPS THEY NEED
TO GET CHRISTIAN OUT OF THE
GAME.
AND IT SHOULDNT BE THAT
DIFFICULT.
I DONT WANT--
OH, WOW!
WHILE I WAS TALKING WITH NIRK HE
DECIDES TO COME CLEAN THAT HE
WAS LYING ABOUT HIS EXTRA IDOL.
AND NOW THAT HES TOLD ME THE
TRUTH, I DONT WANT HIM OUT OF
THE GAME ANYMORE.
I THOUGHT I WAS BEING LIED TO.
TURNS OUT, I WASNT.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED FULL CIRCLE.
SO NICK IS NO LONGER THE VOTE
TONIGHT.
AND ALISON IS.
I HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
THATS ONLY GOOD FOR TONIGHT.
THAT MEANS THAT IM GOING TO
HAVE TO PLAY IT TONIGHT.
AND IM HOPING TO SEE THAT
EVERYONE IS SET FOR ALISON VOTES
FOR ALISON.
I STILL WANT TO WORK WITH
NICK TO TAKE OUT CHRISTIAN.
BUT NICK KEEPS TALKING TO
CHRISTIAN, SO I FEEL LIKE I JUST
GOTTA LAY OUT ALL THE CARDS
BECAUSE THATS THE ONLY WAY IM
GOING TO BE ABLE TO GET
CHRISTIAN OUT OF THE GAME.
DAVIES GUNNING FOR ME?
YES.
HE THINKS BECAUSE YOU HAVE
THE IDOL, THAT NOW IS THE TIME
TO TAKE YOU OUT.
THATS WHAT I WAS AFRAID OF.
OKAY, SO HE HAS KARA.
TALK TO KARA ON THE REWARD
CHALLENGE.
I TELL NICK THAT DAVIE AND
KARA ARE VOTING FOR HIM.
AND NICK IS NOW GUNNING FOR
DAVIE.
AND THE OTHER PEOPLE WANT
ALISON GONE.
FOR ME, I FEEL LIKE CHRISTIAN
IS THE MOST LIKELY PERSON LEFT
IN THE GAME TO WIN.
BUT THE PROBLEM IS ITS REALLY
HARD TO KEEP A GROUP TOGETHER
WHEN THEY ALL HAVE THEIR OWN
AGENDA.
ITS LIKE YOU THINK WITH ONLY
SEVEN PEOPLE THERE WOULDNT BE
THAT MANY POSSIBILITIES, BUT IT
SEEMS LIKE THERES MORE
POSSIBILITIES TONIGHT THAN
THERES EVER BEEN BEFORE.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH.
JOHN.
DAN.
ALEC.
CARL.
AND GABBY, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NICK, LETS TALK ABOUT WHERE WE
ARE IN THE GAME.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO
SEVEN PEOPLE, THERES A TENDENCY
TO PLAY A LITTLE MORE
CONSERVATIVE AND JUST TRY TO GET
THROUGH A VOTE.
DO YOU SENSE ANY SHIFT IN THE
PACE OF THE GAME?
I DONT KNOW.
I THINK WERE STILL GOING 100
MILES PER HOUR.
I MEAN, TO PLAY TO WIN TO MAKE
IT TO TOMORROW.
I DONT THINK THAT CALLS FOR
MORE CONSERVATIVE PLAY.
SOMETIMES IT CALLS FOR MORE
AGGRESSIVE PLAY.
Jeff: AND, ATOMIC, THE
ESSENTIAL DILEMMA WHEN YOU GET
THIS CLOSE TO THE END IS YOU TRY
TO VOTE PEOPLE OUT, BUT YOU ALSO
HAVE TO MAKE SURE THE PEOPLE YOU
LATEST BEHIND WILL BRING YOU TO
THE END.
YES, AND I PUT WAY MORE
WEIGHT IN WHOS LEFT AND WHO I
CAN WORK WITH?
ITS A WEIRD GAME, AND ITS
INDIVIDUAL AND YOU HAVE TO DO
YOUR SELF-INTEREST.
YOU CANT TRUST ANYONE, RIGHT?
THESE ARE ALL THE MESSAGES YOU
GOAT "SURVIVOR."
BUT YOU CANT GET TO THE END
WITHOUT LEANING ON OTHERS.
Jeff: DAVIE, THATS THE
TRICK, ISNT IT-- YOU CANT
TRUST ANYBODY BUT YOU HAVE TO
TRUST SOMEBODY.
THAT IS THE TRICK, JEFF.
I MEAN, YOURE TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT CAN I TRUST THIS DAY ONE
PERSON OR THIS OTHER PERSON THEY
MET AT THE MERGE OR THIS OTHER
PERSON THEY MET AT THE SWAP?
ITS JUST A MIND FRENZY.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, THE TOUGH
PART ABOUT LOYALTY, IS WHEN YOU
REACH THAT CROSSROADS WHEN THE
PERSON OR PEOPLE YOURE LOYAL TO
ARE ALSO YOUR BIGGEST THREATS.
YOU SUMMARIZED, I THINK, THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR" PRETTY WELL,
AND THE FACT THAT FOR MYSELF,
PERSONALLY, I HAVE TO REALLY
CONSIDER WHO IS WILLING TO WORK
WITH ME.
I MEAN, EVERY SINGLE PERSON
SITTING HERE HAS WRITTEN DOWN MY
NAME TO VOTE FOR ME AT SOME
POINT SINCE MERGE.
BUT FOR ME ITS HEAVILY WEIGHTED
ON WHO IS WILLING TO WORK WITH
ME, EVEN THAT PERSON MIGHT HAVE
BEEN AN ENEMY AS CLOSELY AS A
VOTE AGO.
TING MORE SPEAKS TO THE FLUID
NATURE OF THE GAME THAT WE HERE
ARE PLAYING IN THAT, YES, OLD
"SURVIVOR" WAS TIGHT VOTING
PACKS, AND HERE ITS A MUCH MORE
FLUID GAME OF WHAT IS NEXT FOR
THE NEXT VOTE?
Jeff: DAVIE, DO YOU AGREE
WITH THAT, IT REALLY IS TRIBAL
TO TRIBAL?
YEAH, IVE BEEN PREACHING
THAT FROM TRIBAL TO TRIBAL.
VOTING BLOCS, VOTING BLOCS.
YOU DONT KNOW WHO YOU CAN TRUST
AT THAT POINT IN THE GAME, THEN
THE NEXT POINT IN THE GAME.
THE GAME IS FLUID, AND ITS ALL
BASED ON VOTING BLOCKS.
I AGREE WITH THAT.
WING THIS GROUP, THERE IS NO
DEATH GRUDGE BETWEEN ANYBODY
HERE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK EVERYBODY
REALLY LIKES EACH OTHER AND, YOU
KNOW, YOU TRY TO VOTE PEOPLE OUT
AND THEN IT DOESNT WORK AND,
YOU KNOW, WE CAN STILL WORK
TOGETHER.
LIKE, SPEAKING TO CHRISTIANS
POINT, I VOTED HIM TWICE.
WHOEVER IM VOTING TONIGHT, IF
THEY DONT GO HOME TOMORROW,
ITS A NEW DAY.
AND I THINK THAT MAKES IT, YOU
KNOW, A FREE-FOR-ALL.
Jeff: NICK, IF ITS A
FREE-FOR-ALL DOES, THAT MEAN
STRATEGY IS OUT THE WINDOW, OR
DOES THAT MEAN THE STRATEGY IS
SO GOOD AND NOBODY IS FULLY
TELLING THE TRUTH?
I THINK THE STRATEGY IS THAT
GOOD.
YOU CAN COME IN HERE AND THINK
ITS A CLEAR SITUATION, BUT
THATS NEVER THE CASE.
SO, YEAH, I THINK THERES A HIGH
LEVEL OF GAME PLAY GOING ON, AND
ITS GO GOING ON BY EVERYTHING.
Jeff: ALISON, IS THERE A
CLEAR TYPE OF THREAT RIGHT NOW?
I THINK COMMON THREATS HAVE
BEEN IDENTIFIED.
AND ONCE YOUVE BEEN IDENTIFIED
AS A THREAT, ITS HARDER TO STAY
OFF OF PEOPLES HIT LISTS.
Jeff: ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
YOURSELF?
YES.
WHEN YOU SURVIVE A COUPLE OF
TRIBALS, IT STARTS TO IDENTIFY
YOU AS SOMETHING OF A THREAT.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, DO YOU
FEEL SIMILAR TO ALISON, THAT YOU
ARE AN ONGOING THREAT, AND,
THEREFORE, WILL ALWAYS BE IN
TROUBLE AT TRIBAL?
I-- I-- I MEAN YOU HOPE THAT
PEOPLES PERCEPTION OF YOU
CHANGE WHEN YOU REALIZE, HEY,
IM WILLING TO WORK WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN STOP VOTING
FOR ME, PLEASE.
IVE HAD ENOUGH.
UN, THE I THINK THE RECORD IS 19
VOTES IN A GIVEN SEASON.
AND I HAVE 15.
SO, YOU KNOW, THATS PLENTY.
THATS PLENTY.
NO MORE, PLEASE.
( LAUGHING ).
Jeff: MIKE, WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT THE FACT THAT WHAT YOURE
DOING TONIGHT COULD LITERALLY BE
A MILLION-DOLLAR RIGHT DECISION
OR A MILLION-DOLLAR WRONG
DECISION, DOES THAT MAKE YOU
WANT TO SAY, "I JUST HAVE TO
LOOK AT THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
THREATENING TO ME AND SEE IF I
CAN SWAY THE OTHERS TO GO MY
WAY?
WAY?"
YEAH, IT GETS SO COMPLICATED.
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE THAT I
TRUST, BUT THE WEIGHT OF HOLDING
YOUR CARDS CLOSE TO THE VEST AT
SOME POINT YOU WANT TO BE LIKE,
"THIS IS WHAT I KNOW TO BE THE
TRUTH."
AND HAVING THIS AROUND MY NECK
MADE ME FEEL A LITTLE BIT MORE
LIKE I NEED TO MAKE AN IMPACT
FOR TONIGHT.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KARA, YOURE UP.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
JEFF, IM PLAYING THIS FOR ME
TONIGHT.
Jeff: OKAY.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR DAVIE WILL
NOT COUNT.
OKAY.
HANG ON A SECOND, JEFF.
I FOUND THIS BY THE RAFT.
Jeff: NICK, YOURE PLAYING
THIS FOR YOURSELF?
WELL... ACTUALLY, THATS A
FAKE ONE I MADE.
I PLAYED A FAKE ONE TO GET A
READ ON THEM.
I WAS GOING TO, LIKE, SEE WHAT
THEY SAY.
I DONT THINK YOU NEED TO
PLAY IT, PERSONALLY, BUT...
OKAY.
I THINK I NEED TO PLAY MY REAL
IDOL.
I BETTER JUST BE SAFE.
I COULD BE WRONG, BUT... ITS
FOR ME.
Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR NICK WILL NOT
COUNT.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DAVIE.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DAVIE.
ALISON.
ONE VOTE ALISON.
CHRISTIAN.
ONE VOTE CHRISTIAN.
ALISON.
THATS TWO VOTES ALISON.
CHRISTIAN.
WERE TIED.
TWO VOTES ALISON, TWO VOTES
CHRISTIAN, ONE VOTE LEFT.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SEVENTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
CHRISTIAN.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WELL PLAYED, YOU GUYS.
LIKEWISE.
GOOD GAME, CHRISTIAN.
GREAT COMPETITOR.
GREAT GAME, CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
WELL PLAYED.
SORRY, CHRISTIAN.
BYE, CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: WELL, WITH ONLY A FEW
DAYS LEFT, AND THE GAME THIS
FLUID, FROM HEREON OUT, IT IS
GOING TO BE PEDAL TO THE METAL.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
DANG IT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
THE SEASON FINALE OF "SURVIVOR."
ONLY SIX ARE LEFT.
THEY LIED TRITE MY FACE,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I MAY BE GOING HOME TODAY.
YEAH.
SHES LIKE A CRUEL
PSYCHOPATH.
Jeff: WHO WILL CLAIM THE
TITLE OF SOLE "SURVIVOR"?
JOIN US FOR THE FINALE,
WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 19.
IT SURPRISES ME THAT PEOPLE
THOUGHT I WAS SUCH A HUGE THREAT
THAT I NEEDED TO GO AS SOON AS
THEY COULD MARSHAL THE VOTES.
18 VOTES, IF I CAN COUNT.
THATS AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
IT MAKES ME FEEL BIG.
IT MAKES ME FEEL FORMIDABLE.
LIKE A PERSON WHO HAS EARNED
RESPECT OF HIS COLLEAGUES.
SO MAYBE I SHOULD RESPECT MYSELF
MORE AS A CONSEQUENCE.