Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AFTER THE MERGE, THE
GOLIATHS HAD THE ADVANTAGE.
THE NUMBERS ARE 7-6.
WE NEED TO STAY GOLIATH STRONG.
Jeff: BUT AN ALLIANCE
FORMED ACROSS TRIBAL LINES.
WE HAVE A SOLID SIX.
THREE FORMER DAVIDS.
THREE FORMER GOLIATHS.
ID CALL IT A STRIKE FORCE.
Jeff: FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THERE WAS A UNANIMOUS
TARGET.
WE ALL WANT ELIZABETH.
Jeff: BUT ANGELINA SPOILED
"THE BLIND SIDE."
THEYRE THROWING YOUR NAME
OUT THERE.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ELIZABETH OUTED ANGELINA.
ANGELINA TOLD ME TODAY THAT
SHE WAS GOING TO BE VOTED FOR
ME.
THEYRE USING ME TO GET THE
NUMBERS BACK.
OBVIOUSLY YOU THINK WERE
GOING TO SIT HERE AND GET PICKED
OFF ONE BY ONE.
I DONT, I DONT.
Jeff: AND PUT THE SPOTLIGHT
ON ANGELINA.
I THINK SHE WAS STARTING TO
MANAGE THE JURY FOR HER FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I AGREE.
Jeff: BUT ELIZABETH
COULDNT SAVE HERSELF.
ELIZABETH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
12 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS A DOOZY.
I DID NOT EXPECT ELIZABETH TO
DRAG MY NAME THROUGH THE MUD.
SHE MANIPULATED SOMETHING THAT
WASNT.
NOW I UNDERSTAND WHY EVERYONE
WANTED HER OUT.
TELLING ELIZABETH IT WAS HER
NAME ON THE BLOCK WAS JURY
MANAGE.
, AND I GOT CAUGHT RED HANDED.
SO I NEED TO REASSURE EVERYONE
THAT THIS WAS A MISTAKE.
I WALKED TOWARD THE WATER LINE,
AND SHE FOLLOWED ME INTO THE
FOREST, AND SHE WAS BADGERING ME
FOR A NAME.
ITS SUPER FRUSTRATING BECAUSE
IT WAS A MOMENT OF WEAKNESS.
IT WASNT A MOMENT OF STRATEGY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IM SAYING?
AND FOR HER TO SAY I TOOK HER
ASIDE AND TOLD HER IT WAS HER,
THATS JUST IN THE TRUE.
OKAY.
ANGELINA TRIES THE MAKE UP
SOME STORY THAT, WAH, CRY, ITS
NOT MY FAULT, I HAD A MOMENT OF
WEAKNESS.
LIKE REALLY?
SHES MORE OF A THREAT THAN I
THOUGHT SHE WAS.
I DIDNT KNOW HER.
ANGELINA, YOU SLIMEBALL.
THAT WAS 100% A JURY
MANAGEMENT.
I AM NOT FOR ONE MINUTE
BUYING THAT LIE.
IT DOESNT MAKE SENSE BECAUSE I
SAW THEM GO TO THE WELL.
YOU WERE WORKING THE JURY.
YOU WENT AND TALKED TO HER.
THATS ALL THERE IS TO IT.
MY EYES WERE BIG AND SHE
FIGURED IT OUT.
THATS WHERE I HAVE EVEN MORE
OF A PROBLEM, IF YOURE NOT
GOING TO OWN YOUR MISTAKES AND
SAY, HEY, I TRIED MAKE A BOLD
MOVE, IT BACKFIRED, IM SORRY.
IF YOURE NOT WILLING TO DO
THAT, THEN I CANT TRUST YOU, SO
AS FAR AS IM CONCERNED, THE
FIRST OPPORTUNITY I GET, SHES
GONE.
IT WAS CRAZY.
ANGELINA BLEW UP HER OWN SPOT
EFFECTIVELY.
THAT WAS THE ONE TAKEAWAY I HAD.
BUT ANGELINA IN A WAY, NOW SHES
KIND OF BEEN DEFANGED OR
SOMETHING, BECAUSE ITS LIKE THE
JIG IS UP I GUESS.
THE SIX, WE HAVENT TALKED THAT
MUCH SINCE WEVE BROUGHT UP THE
SIX OR WHATEVER.
WE CAN TALK NOW IF THATS
OKAY.
I WAS LEGIT ABOUT ALL THAT.
AND LIKE IM TOTALLY ON THE
LEVEL ABOUT IT.
THIS SIX IS AWESOME.
YES.
IVE BEEN CALLING IT THE
STRIKE FORCE BECAUSE WE HAVE THE
ABILITY TO STRIKE ANYWHERE AND
WITH ANYONE.
THE STRIKE FORCE OF SIX CONSISTS
OF THREE FORMER DAVIDS AND THREE
FORMER GOLIATHS.
WE GOT MYSELF, GABBY, AND NICK
ON ONE SIDE.
ON THE OTHER SIDE YOU HAVE MIKE,
ALISON, AND ALEC.
OUR PRIMARY STRATEGY IS TO VOTE
OUT ONE OF THE GOLIATHS.
RIGHT NOW THEY SEEM AMENABLE TO
VOTE ANG LEE NARCOTIC BUT I
THINK THIS WILL BE A PIVOTAL
TEST OF TRUST FOR THE STRIKE
FORCE.
WERE INSEAR.
I HOPE YOURE SINCERE.
GABBY AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
MAKING ME FEEL LIKE SHES NOT
REALLY TAKING THIS ALLIANCE
SERIOUSLY OR SHE WOULDNT BE SO
ANGRY, TALKING ABOUT THE DAVIDS,
LIKE THEYRE PICKING US OFF ONE
BY ONE.
ITS LIKE, OKAY, YOU CLEARLY
DONT BELIEVE ANYTHING WEVE
BEEN TELLING YOU.
RIGHT NOW THERE IS THIS SIX, BUT
THE TRUTH IS THAT SOME OF THE
THINGS GABBY WAS SAYING LAST
NIGHT ACTUALLY MADE ME FEEL LIKE
SHES NOT FULLY ON BOARD.
MAYBE THESE DAVIDS ARE REALLY
THINKING ALONG TRIBAL LINES IN
WAYS THAT I WASNT THINKING
ABOUT.
I KNOW YOURE TIGHT WITH HER,
BUT THAT WAS MY ONLY ANXIOUS
TAKEAWAY.
ARE WE REALLY DOING THIS?
GABBY DOES GET EMOTIONAL AT
TIME, BUT WE ARE SOLID.
MIKE HAS CONCERNS ABOUT GABBY IN
THAT HE WAS A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT GAB YESS COMMITMENT TO
THE SIX.
THATS A WEIRD THING TO SAY.
AT LEAST HE TOLD ME, THOUGH.
THERE ARE SO MANY TREES.
MAYBE IT WILL BE LIKE A COCONUT
OR WHATEVER.
MAYBE THERE WILL BE SOMETHING
UNDER THOSE MURKY WATERS.
MAYBE.
AT THIS POINT THE DAVIDS ARE
DOWN NUMBERS.
SO EVEN THOUGH ANGELINA IS IN
TROUBLE, ME AND DAVIE WENT OUT
TO FIND AN IDOL.
LOOK FOR SOMETHING OUT OF
PLACE, STRING OR ANYTHING.
WHATS THIS?
DUDE.
YES!
WHAT IS THAT?
SURE ENOUGH WE SEE A BLUE
RIBBON.
SO WE UNRAVEL IT, AND ITS THIS
BEAUTIFUL SYMBOL I REMEMBER FROM
THE MERGE THAT LOOKS LIKE A COOL
80s DESIGN I COULD PUT ON A
T-SHIRT.
SO IM LIKE, OKAY, WELL, WHAT IS
IT?
IM THINKING WE GOT TO FIND A
PALM TREE STICKING OUT ON A
CLIFF.
ITS ALL STARTING TO COME
TOGETHER.
THIS IS A CLUE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE NEED TO START LOOKING AROUND
THIS ISLAND.
PALM TREE AND A CLIFF.
SO WE COME OUT OF THE TRAIL
ON THE BEACH, AND THEN MY BOY
CARL COMES AND JOINS US.
AND THEN WE SAW A FREAKIN PALM
TREE COMING OUT OF A CLIFF LIKE
THE SYMBOL ON THE FREAKIN
WHATEVER THE THING IS WE JUST
FOUND, AND BECAUSE THESE OTHER
PEOPLE ARE RIGHT THERE, WHAT I
DID WAS I LET THEM CONTINUE TO
JUST WALK WHILE I KIND OF JUST
CREATED A DIVERSION TO MAKE THEM
THINK THAT IM JUST OUT HERE
ENJOYING LIFE.
LOOK AT DAVIE?
WHAT IS HE DOING?
TAE KWON DO?
IM OVER HERE DOING MY OWN
THING.
MEANTIME, I KNOW NICK IS GUNG
HO, BAM, BAM, BAM, BAM, BAM.
I GET TO THE TREE, AND I SEE
A LITTLE RIBBON TIED AROUND THE
PARCHMENT JUST THE WAY THIS CLUE
WAS HIDDEN.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU NOW HAVE POWER IN THE GAME.
THIS ADVANTAGE ALLOWS YOU TO
STEAL THE VOTE FROM ANOTHER
PLAYER AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE PLAYER WHOSE VOTE YOU STEAL
WILL NOT VOTE.
EN STEAD YOU WILL CAST A SECOND
VOTE."
HE HAS AN ADVANTAGE.
YOU HAVE AN IDOL NULLIFIER.
OH, MY GOD, DUDE, WE ARE SET.
THIS COULD BE MY SLINGSHOT THAT
I USE TO TAKE DOWN A GOLIATH.
I MEAN, THIS COULD BE THE STONE
THAT GOES RIGHT TO ITS HEAD.
WE FOUND AN ADVANTAGE.
WE GET AN EXTRA VOTE.
OKAY.
PERFECT.
WEVE GOT AN ADVANTAGE IN THE
GAME.
ANOTHER ONE.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW I GOT A
FREAKIN IDOL, MY VERY OWN, NO
ONE ELSE KNOWS.
WEVE GOT TWO ADVANTAGES.
WE HAVE AN IDOL NULLIFIER.
CARL HAS THE IDOL NULLIFIER,
WHICH ALLOWS HIM TO SMASH ANY
IDOLS THAT ARE PLAYED, AND NOW
WE HAVE A FREAKIN STEAL-A-VOTE
IF WE NEED IT.
WERE THE ONLY THREE THAT
KNOW IT.
WERE OUT HERE STARTING FROM
THE BOTTOM.
NOW WERE HERE, BABY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS REWARD
CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOULL BE
DIVIDED INTO TWO TEAMS OF SIX.
ON MY GO, YOULL HOLD SANDBAGS
CONNECTED TO A TROUGH ABOVE YOUR
HEAD.
IF AT ANY POINT A SANDBAG DROPS,
THAT TROUGH WILL DUMP, AND YOUR
SHOT AT VICTORY WILL WASH AWAY.
THE LAST TEAM STANDING WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR?
YES!
Jeff: IT IS ONE OF THE
GREATEST PLEASURES IN LIFE,
PIZZA.
NO WAY, NO WAY!
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: A DOZEN PIZZAS, MEAT
AND VEGETARIAN, WAITING FOR THE
WINNING SIX BECOME AT CAMP.
WOW.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: MAYBE AFTER 21 DAYS
YOU GUYS HAVE ACTUALLY FORGOTTEN
WHAT PIZZA TASTES LIKE.
YES, WE HAVE.
OH, NO.
REALLY?
HAVE AT IT, GABBY.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: ONE TINY SLICE FOR 12
PEOPLE.
MAKE SURE THERES ENOUGH FOR
EVERYONE.
Jeff: DAN AND GENERAL AND
ALEC ON THE END HOPING THERES
SOMETHING LEFT.
IS THAT BACON?
YOU TAKE A BITE AND ILL TAKE
A BITE.
OH, YES.
OH, MAN.
Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
YEAH.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WELL DO A SCHOOLYARD PICK FOR
TEAMS.
WELL GET STARTED.
OH, GREAT.
Jeff: LETS DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOUVE DIVIDED EIGHT SANDBAGS
BETWEEN THE SIX OF YOU.
HOLD YOUR SAND BAGS ABOVE YOUR
HEADS.
EVERYBODY LOOKING GOOD.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
GABBY WAS A CAPTAIN.
SHE CHOSE CHRISTIAN, ALISON,
JOHN, ALEC, AND NICK.
MIKE WAS A CAPTAIN.
HE CHOSE CARL, KARA, DAVIE, DAN,
AND ANGELINA.
EACH SANDBAG WEIGHS TEN POUNDS,
YOU MUST ALWAYS BE HOLDING ONE
BAG, BUT YOU CAN PASS THE EXTRAS
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
GOOD FOR NOW?
UH-HUH.
Jeff: EVERY 15 MINUTES ONE
PLAYER WILL DROP OUT AND HAVE TO
GIVE THEIR SANDBAG TO SOMEONE
ELSE.
SO THE LONGER THIS CHALLENGE
GOES, THE MORE WEIGHT YOURE
GOING TO BE CARRYING.
WERE IN THE VERY EARLY STAGES
OF WHAT IS GOING TO BECOME VERY
DIFFICULT.
YOU WANT THOSE PIZZA, YOU WILL
DEFINITELYERN THEM TODAY.
-- YOU WILL DEFINITELY EARN
THEM TODAY.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME THE LOSE ONE MEMBER
FROM EACH TEAM.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
ME.
Jeff: GABBY IS GOING TO OPT
OUT.
ANGELINA IS GOING TO OPT OUT.
TAKE A SPOT DOWN HERE ON THE
FRONT.
I CHOSE THE DREAM TEAM.
YOU GOT THIS.
THANK YOU, GABBY.
Jeff: NOW YOU HAVE TEN MORE
POUNDS TO DISTRIBUTE AMONGST THE
FIVE OF YOU.
NOW ITS GOING TO GET DIFFICULT.
JOHN, GIVE IT TO ME, BECAUSE
I WANT THE SAVE YOUR ARM.
Jeff: NICK GOING TO TRADE
OFF WITH ALEC.
A LOT OF MOVE.
GOING ON.
THATS TH CHALLENGE, TRADE OFF.
WHEN IT GETS TOO HEAVY, PASS IT
OUT.
SHAKE IT OUT.
Jeff: YOU GOT TO KEEP IT
ABOVE YOUR HEAD.
MIKE, HOW YOU DOING?
I HAVE A HEAVY BAG.
I THINK THIS IS THE HEAVIEST BAG
OUT HERE.
[LAUGHTER]
MIKE.
WHY IS HE SO FUNNY?
Jeff: EVERYBODY FEELING IT.
ITS REALLY A QUESTION OF WHO IS
MASKING IT BETTER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO IS GOING TO BE THE NEXT
PERSON TO DROP OUT?
CHRISTIAN, YOU DROP.
I WILL DROP.
Jeff: CARL IS GOING TO
DROP.
GIVE IT AWAY, CARL.
GOOD LUCK.
YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN IS OUT.
CARL IS OUT.
CARL CAN BARELY MOVE.
THAT BACK SPASMING.
WERE NOW DOWN TO FOUR ON EACH
TEAM.
NOW 80 POUNDS FOR FOUR OF YOU.
TAKE ONE OF THESE REAL QUICK.
IM LOSING MY GRIP.
I JUST NEED A SECOND.
ILL TAKE IT.
Jeff: NOW ITS GOING TO GET
HEAVY.
PURPLE STRUGGLING NOW.
DAN PASSING BACK TO DAVIE.
DAVIE STRUGGLING TO KEEP THEM
UP.
DAVIE GIVES THEM BACK TO DAN.
I CAN TAKE ONE IF YOU WANT.
IM GOOD NOW.
YOU SURE?
YEAH.
EVERYBODY OKAY?
YES.
Jeff: THIS COULD END AT ANY
MOMENT IF SOMEBODY JUST CANT
HOLD ANYMORE AND DROPS THEIR
SANDBAGS.
THAT TROUGH WILL DUMP WATER, AND
ITS OVER.
ITS ABOUT WILLPOWER RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, BRO.
Jeff: NOBODY IS
COMFORTABLE.
EVERYBODY WANTS THIS TO BE OVER.
THEY JUST WANT THE OTHER FOUR TO
DROP FIRST.
PUT IT BACK ON MINE.
IM HONESTLY FINE.
Jeff: THAT PIZZA WILL TASTE
SO GOOD WHEN YOU KNOW YOU EARNED
IT.
DONT LET THAT FREAKIN FALL.
Jeff: DAN ONE HANDING THREE
BAGS.
IMPRESSIVE AND RISKY.
WHERE YOU GOT A BAG?
RIGHT HERE.
WHERES THE THREE AT?
WERE PLAYING SMART.
DAN DROPS, AND THIS IS IT.
HE GOT CONFIDENT WITH HIS THREE
BAGS AND COST HIS TEAM THE WIN.
ORANGE WINS REWARD.
A DOZEN PIZZAS WAITING BACK AT
CAMP.
MY ARMS ARE BURNING SO BAD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NICK, GABBY, CHRISTIAN, ALEC,
JOHN, ALISON, A DOZEN PIZZAS
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP,
AND FOR YOU ONLY.
WILL THAT GIVE YOU AN ADVANTAGE
IN THE NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
MOST LIKELY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE PIZZAS.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: MIKE, KARA, DAVIE,
CARL, ANGELINA, GOT NOTHING FOR
YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
WE GOT NOTHING FOR YOU
EITHER.
Jeff: FINALLY, WHAT SOMEONE
THINKS.
THE CHALLENGE WAS DAN BEING
WAY TO COCKY.
HE THINKS HE CAN RUN HIS MOUTH.
I CANT WAIT FOR IT TO CATCH UP
WITH HIM AND BITE HIM IN THE
ASS.
CRUSHED PEPPERS.
CONGRATS, YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU.
OH, MY GOD.
SO WE GET BACK THE CAMP, AND,
OF COURSE, THE PIZZA,
BREADSTICK, AND SODA WERE
LOVINGLY SPREAD IN THE MIDDLE OF
CAMP.
THE WINNERS CAN HELP THEMSELVES.
WE START EATING RIGHT THERE IN
FRONT OF EVERYONE.
WE CANT LOSE WHATEVER WE HAD
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
TAKE IT SOMEWHERE ELSE.
IM HAPPY TO START IN ON THE
RICE IF YOU WANT THE TAG TEAM.
SHOULD I GO AHEAD AND KILL
THE CHICKEN?
WHEN WHEN WE LOST THE REWARD,
IT BECAME CLEAR THAT IM NOT
HERE FOR REWARD AND IM HERE TO
GET TO THE END OF THE GAME.
OTHER PEOPLE GET CAUGHT UP IN
THE MOMENT OF THE PIZZA AND THEY
FORGET WHAT THE REAL DRAMA IS
HERE, WHICH IS STAYING IN THE
GAME.
HOW DO YOU OUTLAST EVERYONE
ELSE?
FOR ME THAT IS MY FOCUS.
AND SO I FELL LIKE I NEEDED TO
TAKE JUST A MOMENT TO LOOK AT
ALL MY OPTIONS.
I HAVE A GOLIATH ALLIANCE, AND I
HAVE A NEW ALLIANCE OF SIX,
WHICH INCLUDES THREE GOLIATHS
AND THREE DAVIDS.
BUT IM STARTING TO REALIZE THAT
IF I GO WITH THE SIX, THERES
THE RISK THE DAVIDS MIGHT PULL A
FAST ONE ON ME, TAKE CONTROL OF
THE GAME AND SCREW ME OVER.
I WANT THE MAKE SURE THAT THAT
DOESNT HAPPEN.
OKAY.
HERE IS THE THING, MY FEAR IS WE
VOTE OUT ANGELINA NOW, THERE IS
STILL ROOM FOR SOMETHING THAT WE
CANT CONTROL COULD HAPPEN.
BECAUSE THE PERSON LEFT ON THE
FIELD THAT IS THE MOST DANGEROUS
TO WIN THE GAME IS CHRISTIAN.
HES ONE OF THOSE GUYS IN A WEEK
WERE TO WEEKS, YOURE GOING TO
BE LIKE, WHY DID WE NOT TAKE
THIS I GO OUT WHEN WE HAD THE
CHANCE.
YEAH.
CHRISTIAN IS SOMEBODY I
WANTED TO WORK WITH, BUT I WORRY
BECAUSE I THINK HES JUST AS
SMART AS I AM AND CAN ACTUALLY
PULL SOME MOVES I DONT SEE
COMING.
LIKE CARL AND DAVIE, THEYRE NOT
GOING TO MOUNT SOMEN VUX, --
UNSURE REST, AND GABI COULDNT
GET PEOPLE TO FOLLOW HER INTO
BATTLE BUT CHRISTIAN COULD.
HES THE LAST PERSON WHO COULD
WEASEL HIS WAY TO THE END.
THATS MY TWO CORRECTS ON THAT.
MIKE WANTS TO BLOW UP THE
ALLIANCE OF SIX BY VOTING OUT
CHRISTIAN AND JUST CONTINUE TO
BE GOLIATH STRONG FOR NOW.
AND TAKE OUT A BIG THREAT.
I TOTALLY HEAR HIS POINT, BUT IF
WE DO THIS, IM LOCKED IN WITH
THE GOLIATHS, AN I DONT KNOW IF
THATS BEST FOR MY GAME.
THE ONLY PERSON WHO IS LIKE A
STRONG PLAYER OUT HERE BESIDES
US IS CHRISTIAN.
CHRISTIAN.
ANYBODY WATCHING THIS SEASON,
EITHER THEYRE ROOTING FOR
CHRISTIAN AND THEYRE LIKE, WHY
ARENT THEY TAKING OUT THAT GUY.
HES EVERYBODYS FAVORITE
GUY.
SO WE TAKE HIM OUT NEXT, NO
MORE DISCUSSION.
NO MORE RUNNING AROUND TOMORROW.
THATS THE PLAN.
THIS WAS MY PLAN.
THIS WAS MY IDEA.
I WAS TRYING TO LEAD THE CHARGE
ON CHRISTIAN LAST VOTE, AND NOW
I AM HAVING FLASHBACKS TO ALL
THOSE TIMES, EITHER ME OR
ANOTHER WOMAN HAD THROWN OUT AN
IDEA AND A FEW MINUTES LATER A
MAN THROWS OUT THE SAME IDEA AND
EVERYBODY IS LIKE, THATS A
GREAT IDEA.
LETS DO THAT.
AND YOURE LIKE, UM, I JUST SAID
THAT A FEW MINUTES AGO.
YOU GUYS KNOW I WANT THIS.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS WHAT
WERE GOING TO TELL HIM.
THE ONLY THING HES GOING THE
BELIEVE IS --
WHY DON WE STAY TIGHT-LIPPED
AND SAY NOTHING.
BECAUSE AFTER LAST NIGHTS
FIASCO, HES GOING THE BELIEVE
IT.
DONT YOU WANT TO BE THE STAR
OF ANOTHER TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ANGELINA.
ID RATHER NOTING BUT IF
THATS WHAT WEVE GOT TO DO,
THATS WHAT WEVE GOT TO DO.
BECAUSE MY NAME WAS THROWN
OUT THERE SO MUCH LAST TRIBAL, I
AM THE DECOY IN ORDER FOR US TO
BLINDSIDE CHRISTIAN, YET VERY
EASILY I COULD BECOME THE REAL
DEAL, BECAUSE SINCE WERE
TELLING THE DAVIDS TO VOTE FOR
ME, IF SOMETHING CRAZY HAPPENS,
IT COULD BE THE DEMISE OF MY
GAME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, ALISON, TAKE
BACK THE NECKLACE.
DANG IT.
Jeff: THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMOONTY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE YOURE
GOING TO BALANCE ON NARROW PERCH
WHILE HOLDING A BUOY BETWEEN TWO
HANDLES.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU FALL OFF THE
PERCH OR YOUR BUOY DROPS, YOURE
OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE NINTH
PERSON VOTED OUT, SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY GET ON YOUR PERCH AND
PICK UP YOUR BUOYS.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH, GET FOCUSED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD, AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON.
THIS COULD GO VERY FAST.
WEVE DONE THIS CHALLENGE ONE
TIME, IN "GAME CHANGERS."
BRAD CULPEPPER WON IT IN 23
MINUTES.
MY HERO.
Jeff: YOU ARE NOT YET 23
SECONDS.
KARA IN TROUBLE.
KARA IS THE FIRST ONE OUTS.
WERE DOWN TO 11.
KARA WILL TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
NOW ITS ALISON IN TROUBLE.
CHRISTIAN DROPS.
HES OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
ALISON DROPS.
SHES OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
EARLY CASUALTIES.
DAVIE NOW DROPS.
ITS NOW JOHN IN TROUBLE.
HE DROPS.
COME ON, BRO.
Jeff: GABBY IS OUT AN WERE
QUICKLY DOWN TO SIX.
CARL NOW SHAKING.
WOW.
CARL IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO FIVE.
WE HAVE ALREADY LOST SEVEN
PEOPLE.
IT IS ALEC, MIKE, ANGELINA, DAN,
AND NICK FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
SAFETY AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALEC LOSES HIS BALANCE, FALLS
OFF.
ALEC IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO FOUR.
GET BACK IN CONTROL.
MIKE WOBBLELING.
MIKE CANT RECOVER.
WERE DOWN TO THREE.
A LONG WAY AWAY FROM WHERE BRAD
CULPEPPER WAS WHEN HE WON IT.
WHAT IS DIFFERENT THIS TIME?
ANGELINA STARTING TO WOBBLE, BUT
A NICE RECOVERY.
NICK STRUGGLING.
CAN HE RECOVER IN NO, NICK
DROPS.
WE HAVE A SHOWDOWN, AND THEY ARE
SIDE BY SIDE, ANGELINA AND DAN
FOR IMMUNITY.
ANGELINA HOLDING HERS UP.
DAN HOLDING HIS DOWN.
BOTH WORK.
TWO GOLIATHS BATTLING IT OUT FOR
SAFETY AT TONIGHTS TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
TRIBAL COUNCIL LOOMING TONIGHT.
NINTH PERSON OUT OF THIS GAME
WILL JOIN THE JURY.
DAN WITH A NICE RECOVERY.
SWEAT DRIPPING, LEGS SHAKING.
ANGELINAS LEGS TWITCHING.
STAY STRONG.
BOTH PLAYERS DRIPPING SWEAT.
DRIP, DRIP, DRIP.
Jeff: WITH $1 MILLION
POTENTIALLY ON THE LINE.
DAN WOBBLING AGAIN.
ANGELINA SLIPPING OUT OF THE
HOLE.
SHES GOT TO RECOVER.
THATS IT.
ANGELINA DROPS.
DAN WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
[APPLAUSE]
DAN, COME ON OVER.
GOOD JOB, DAN.
Jeff: DAN SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
SADLY, FOR THE REST OF YOU,
AFTER 22 TOUGH DAYS, SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE NINTH PERSON VOTED
OUT AND BECOME THE SECOND MEMBER
OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
THANKS, JEFF.
I HOPE THAT TONIGHT WE
BLINDSIDE CHRISTIAN.
I THINK WE NEED THE STAY
TOGETHER AS THE DYSFUNCTIONAL
GOLIATH FAMILY WE ARE.
I JUST HOPE THE GOLIATHS CAN
KEEP THEIR EGOS IN CHECK AN WE
CAN MAKE THIS WORK.
CONGRATULATION, DAN.
CONGRATS, DAN.
THAT WAS HARD.
GOOD JOB, ANGELINA.
LASER FOCUSED.
EPIC WIN.
I WAS LOCKED IN, DUDE.
I WAS LIKE, IM NOT LETTING
ANGELINA BEAT ME.
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
APPRECIATE IT.
THE VOTE IS GOING TO BE EASY
TONIGHT.
IM GUESSING THERE IS A PLAN.
ANGELINA.
CANT HAVE THOSE KIND OF
SHENANIGANS.
TONIGHTS VOTE IS GOING TO BE
A HUGE SHOCK FOR THE DAVIDS.
THE STORY WEVE BEEN TELLING
THEM IS EVERYONE IS GOING TO
VOTE OUT ANGELINA, BUT WHAT
ACTUALLY IS HAPPENING IS THE
GOLIATHS ARE ALL ON THE SAME
PAGE TONIGHT TO VOTE OUT
CHRISTIAN, AND IT SUCKS.
HES AN HONORARY BROCHACHO, BUT
HES SMART.
HES CHARISMATIC.
HES GOOD SOCIALLY.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT HES A
THREAT.
SO TONIGHT ITS GOING TO BE A
#BROCHACHOBLINDSIDE.
HARD TO BE IN THE HOT SEAT.
EVEN IF ITS A PRESUMABLY FAKE
HOT SEAT.
I GET IT, BUT YOU NEED TO
KEEP IT SIMPLE, BECAUSE IF WE
TRY TO GET ALL CRAZY, THATS
WHEN STUFF GOES AWRY.
I KNOW IT DOESNT FEEL GOOD TO
HAVE YOUR NAME BEING THROWN OUT,
THERE BUT WE HAVE SEVEN OF US
AGAINST FIVE OF THEM.
OKAY.
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED AT THE
LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, MY NAME IS
ON PEOPLES LIPS.
IF THE DAVIDS HAVE ANY SORT OF
POWER, A.K.A. AN IDOL, THEY
COULD PROTECT CHRISTIAN, IN
WHICH CASE, THE NEXT RUNNER-UP
IS ME.
ITS JUST VERY STRESSFUL.
BUT ANGELINA, YOURE THE ONE
THAT MESSED UP.
NO, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU MESSED UP, RIGHT?
AND IF CHRISTIAN WHIPS OUT AN
IDOL, ILL PULL OUT THE IDOL AND
GIVE IT TO YOU.
ITS NOT A PROBLEM.
I DONT WANT YOU GONE.
DUDE, SHES GOT TO GO.
ANGELINA?
YEAH.
ITS JUST WE NEED TO GET A
DAVID OUT BEFORE WE TAKE HER.
MY QUESTION IS, CHRISTIAN BUSTS
OUT AN IDOL --
I DONT THINK CHRISTIAN HAS
AN IDOL.
I DONT THINK HE DOES EITHER.
DO WE STILL GIVE IT TO ANGELINA
OR DO WE NOT?
IM SAYING NEW YORK BECAUSE
WE STILL HAVE THE NUMBERS AT
THAT POINT.
YOU DOWN WITH THAT?
YOU GOOD WITH THAT?
OKAY.
I WOULD LOVE TO GET ANGELINA
OUT.
ANGELINA IS A THREAT, AN SHE
DOES NEED TO GO.
BUT IF EVERYONES GOING TO VOTE
FOR CHRISTIAN, IM GOING TO HAVE
TO GO WITH IT.
HOWEVER, I DONT WANT NICK TO
FEEL BLINDSIDED BY THIS VOTE.
NICK AND I HAVE A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP.
I DONT WANT TO LOSE HIS TRUST.
I GOT TO BE 100% HONEST WITH
YOU?
UH-HUH.
THEYRE BLINDSIDING
CHRISTIAN.
MIKE IS REALLY WORRIED ABOUT
CHRISTIAN WOULD BEAT US.
UH-HUH.
I DONT KNOW WHATS GOING ON
WITH MIKE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE ON THE SAME
PAGE.
WELL, NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN HE
WANTS CHRISTIAN OUT IMMEDIATELY.
IM LIKE, WHAT HAPPENED TO THE
ALLIANCE OF SIX.
TRUST ME, LIKE IM GOING
AGAINST MY ALLIANCE IN A WAY.
YOU COULD VERY EASILY GO IF YOU
WANTED TO.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL, THE
PLAN FOR ANGELINA IS ON.
BRO.
TELL ME WHAT YOURE THINKING.
I THINK THEYRE FULL OF...
THEYRE LYING TO YOU.
YOU NEED TO DO SOMETHING.
YOU THINK ITS THAT
DESPERATE?
YEAH.
EVERYONE IS TALKING, OH, ITS
ANGELINA, ITS ANGELINA, ITS
ANGELINA, WHICH IS COMFORTLING
BUT EXTREMELY SUSPICIOUS.
NOW NICK IS TELLING ME, THEYRE
LYING TO YOU, MAN, AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN IM WONDERING IF THE
GOLIATHS ARE THINKING, THAT
CHRISTIAN, HES WILEY, LETS GET
RID OF THEM.
LETS FIGURE OUT WHO THE
LEADER IS.
HOW DO WE DO IT WITHOUT A
GOLIATH VOTE.
JUST DONT DO NOTHING, JUST
WHATEVER YOU WERE DOING BEFORE
WE TALKED, KEEP DOING THAT.
DEFINITELY, DEFINITELY, MAN.
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
WHY WOULD THEY TURN ON ONE OF
THEIR OWN WHEN THEY COULD TAKE
OUT A BIG THREAT AND HAVE THE
DAVIDS ON THEIR KNEES.
IF THATS THE CASE, IM SCREWED.
I DONT HAVE AN IDOL.
I DONT HAVE IMMOONTY.
I GOT NOTHING.
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU,
DAVIE, WOULD YOU USE THE
ADVANTAGE TO SAVE CHRISTIAN?
HES IN TROUBLE?
YEAH.
WHY ARE THEY TALKING HIM
ALREADY?
THEYRE CONVINCED THAT HES
THIS HUGE THREAT.
LIKE I WAS HOPING TO SAVE IT
UNTIL WERE LIKE IN THE FINAL
SIX ORFINAL SEVEN OR SOMETHING,
BUT I DONT WANT THE SEE
CHRISTIAN GO.
IF THE GOLIATHS ARE GOING FOR
CHRISTIAN ALREADY, THAT MEANS
MAYBE THEIR PLAN IS TO PICK THE
DAVIDS OFF ONE BY ONE BY ONE BY
ONE.
NICK IS GOING ON ABOUT MAN WE
NEED TO USE THE STEAL-A-VOTE TO
SAVE CHRISTIAN, BUT THE ONLY
THING THAT CAN SAVE HIM FOR SURE
IS THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL THAT
I HAVE IN MY POCK WHICH NICK
DOESNT KNOW ABOUT.
SO WILL YOU USE IT?
AT LEAST LETS THINK ABOUT
IT.
I WOULD LIKE THE HELP
CHRISTIAN, BUT THERE IS
DEFINITELY A PART SAYING, DAVIE,
YOURE NOT IN TROUBLE, SAVE YOUR
IDOL.
MAYBE IF WE USE THE
STEAL-A-VOTE, WE CAN MAKE
SOMETHING HAPPEN.
IM NOT READY TO SEE
CHRISTIAN GO.
HES PART OF THE MASON-DIXON.
I HAVE SOME MOVES STILL.
I COULD USE MY ADVANTAGE, STEAL
A GOLIATHS VOTE AND CAUSE A TIE
VOTE.
ITS POSSIBLE IT COULD WORK,
BECAUSE THEY PROBABLY AINT
GOING TO DRAW A ROCK FOR
ANGELINA, BUT IF I USE THIS TO
STEAL A GOLIATHS VOTE AN THEY
ALL STICK TOGETHER AND COME OUT
ON TOP, THEN IM SCREWED BECAUSE
ITS GOING TO BE ME NEXT.
IM SO UNDER THE RADAR RIGHT
NOW.
NOBODY IS LOOKING THE VOTE ME
OUT.
SO I GOT SOME DECISIONS TO MAKE.
AND IF I SCREW UP, IT COULD BE
MY DOWNFALL IN THIS GAME.
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO ANGELINA, THE LAST TRIBAL WAS
A UNANIMOUS VOTE, BUT IT WAS
ANYTHING BUT UNITED.
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
Jeff: SO WHEN YOU GET BACK
THE CAMP, WHAT WENT DOWN WITH
YOU?
YOU KNOW, I WANTED TO MAKE
SURE THAT EVERYONE IN MY
ALLIANCE WAS CRYSTAL CLEAR ON
WHAT WENT DOWN, WHY IT WENT
DOWN, AND IM PUTTING A LOT OF
FAITH IN THE PEOPLE WHO SAID
THAT THEY HAVE FORGIVEN ME AND
ARE MOVING FORWARD, AND IM
HOPING THAT THAT IS THE TRUTH.
Jeff: NICK WAS THERE ANY
TALK AMONGST THE DAVIDS OF
SAYING, MAYBE ANGELINA, SHE TOOK
SOME HEAT LAST TRIBAL, MAYBE
SHES OUR CRACK.
OF COURSE, BUT IF THERE IS A
GOLIATH ALLIANCE, IT DONT
MATTER HOW MAD THEY ARE.
THEY MIGHT KEEP HER AROUND.
Jeff: MIKE, WHY NOT KEEP
GOLIATH SEVEN.
ITS FIVE EASY VOTES.
THERES AN ARGUMENT FOR, THAT
BUT THE DAVIDS HAVE BEEN AN
INFLUENCE THE LAST VOTE AND WILL
BE AN INFLUENCE TO THIS VOTE
TONIGHT, SO ITS A LOT MORE
COMPLICATED THAN THAT.
Jeff: DAVIE, SURPRISE YOU
TO HEAR MIKE SAY DAVIDS WERE
INVOLVED WITH THE ELIZABETH VOTE
AND THERE WILL BE DAVIDS
INVOLVED WITH TONIGHTS VOTE,
BECAUSE THAT DOESNT SOUND LIKE
GOLIATHS VERSUS DAVIDS.
ABSOLUTELY, JEFF.
ELIZABETH DID A GREAT THING.
SHE EXPOSED SOME CRACKS.
YOU HAD ALISON TALKING ABOUT
JURY MANAGEMENT.
YOU GOT ANGELINA TELLING
SECRETS.
SO, YOU KNOW, I WANT TO HOPE
THAT WHAT MIKE IS SAYING IS
TRUE.
I DONT BELIEVE IT ONE BIT,
JEFF.
THEY GOT THE NUMBERS, MAN.
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
YOU CAN TELL A PERSON TRUST ME
ALL DAY LONG, BUT I TRUST YOU
MORE AFTER I SEE THE VOTES READ
VERSUS JUST SITTING HERE
TALKING.
Jeff: JOHN, THAT REALLY IS
IT.
YOU DONT KNOW WHAT THE OTHER
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO DO.
YOU DONT KNOW IF THEYRE SAYING
THE TRUTH OR IF THEYRE PULLING
FAST ONE ON YOU.
HOW DO YOU NAVIGATE ALL OF THAT?
ULTIMATELY YOU GET WHAT YOU
GIVE.
IF YOU DONT GIVE ANYTHING, YOU
DONT REALLY HAVE CHANCE OF
RECEIVING ANYTHING HONEST FROM
ANYBODY.
THE PROBLEM IS IF YOU GET
WHAT YOU GIVE, THEY HIGH JUST
GIVE YOU THAT BACK.
IF YOU GIVE TO THE WRONG
PERSON, THEN YOURE BONED.
IT WORK BOTH WAYS.
YOU DONT GANN TRUST JUST BY
BOSTON, PEOPLE AROUND OR TELLING
PEOPLE HOW TO VOTE.
IT HAS TO BE A GIVE AND TAKE
RELATIONSHIP.
AND I FEEL LIKE I HAVE THAT
RELATIONSHIP WITH SOME PEOPLE
HERE.
THEY KNOW THAT IM READY TO WORK
WITH THEM, NOT JUST TONIGHT, BUT
FOR THE REST OF THE GAME.
Jeff: JOHN, WHEN YOU HEAR
NICK SAY, I DONT CARE WHAT
HAPPENS TONIGHT, IM LOYAL, WHAT
DOES THAT SAY ABOUT WHERE WE ARE
IN THE GAME?
WELL, I DONT PERSONALLY KNOW
EXACTLY WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT, BUT FOR ME, I AM FOR
VOTING OUT THREATS, BECAUSE WHEN
YOU RESPECT SOMEONE AS A THREAT,
THEY MIGHT NOT BE GOOD FOR YOUR
GAME AND IT MIGHT BE BETTER FOR
THEM TO GO.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, GENERAL
SAYS FOR HIM ITS GETTING RID OF
THREATS.
I GO BACK TO DAY ONE, YOURE
SELECTED AS THE PERCEIVED
WEAKEST, TURNS OUT YOU WERENT.
ARE YOU WORRIED THAT YOU MIGHT
BE THE OBVIOUS TARGET?
OF COURSE THAT IS MY WORRY.
YOU NEVER WANT TO BE TOO MUCH OF
A THREAT IN THIS GAME.
WHAT DID I DO?
I JUST CAME OUT AND ANNOUNCED
MYSELF, HELLO, MY NAME IS THREAT
IN THE FIRST TEN MINUTES.
Jeff: BIG BANG THEORY THEY
CALL YOU.
BUT YOU WANT TO MANAGE YOUR
THREAT LEVEL IN "SURVIVOR."
THATS SOMETHING I NEGLECTED IN
THIS GAME.
AS A RESULT, I COULD BE AN
ENORMOUS TARGET.
BUT I JUST HAVE TO POINT OUT
THAT IN SPITE OF DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE SOME
DAVIDS ON THE BROCHACHOS, AS
WELL.
Jeff: WHATS YOUR POINT
WITH THAT?
IM HOPING THAT THESE BONDS I
BUILT ACROSS THESE SWAPPED
TRIBES MEAN SOMETHING.
ALTHOUGH I WOULD ARGUE THAT
THATTEN CREASES HIS THREAT
ACTUALLY.
SO YOURE ARGUING, ANGELINA,
THAT IM AN ENORMOUS THREAT.
I WASNT PUTTING YOU OUT AT
THE BIGGEST.
BUT JUST SAID BIG THREAT AND
YOURE LIKE, ACTUALLY EVEN
BIGGER THREAT.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE --
THATS WHAT YOU COAT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU ELEVATE OTHERS OVER YOURSELF
IN ORDER TO MOVE THE TARGET AWAY
FROM YOU.
MAKE SURE I UNDERSTAND
PERFECTLY WHAT YOU MEAN, AND I
THINK YOUVE DONE THAT.
OF COURSE.
Jeff: ANGELINA, IS IT EVER
POSSIBLE TO HAVE A VOTE AND GO
BACK LUKE YOU WERE BEFORE THE
VOTE?
I THINK LAST VOTE WAS
PROBABLY THE LAST TIME THAT WE
WOULD GO BACK THE CAMP MELLOW
AND UNITED.
Jeff: SO THERE WILL BE A
CONSEQUENCE TO TONIGHTS VOTE?
THERE HAS TO BE, AND
DEPENDING ON WHERE THE LOOKS ARE
DRAWN, THERE WILL BE SOME HAPPY
PEOPLE AND SOME UNHAPPY PEOPLE.
AN WERE ALL GOING TO HAVE TO
SLEEP TOGETHER REGARDLESS.
NO ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
NICK, YOURE UP.
ILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
WHAT?
CAN I SAY A FEW THINGS, JEFF?
SURE.
FOR THE PEOPLE IN MY
ALLIANCE, IM SORRY I HAD TO
HIDE THIS FROM YOU GUYS, BUT I
THINK YOULL UNDERSTAND.
AND IM NERVOUS, JEFF, BUT IM
NOR NERVOUS FOR CHRISTIAN.
THIS IS FOR HIM.
Jeff: OKAY.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR CHRISTIAN
WILL NOT COUNT.
I WANT THE TAKE CARE OF MY
ALLIANCE, TOO.
OH, MY GOD, DAN, I LOVE YOU.
I WANT THE PLAY THIS FOR
ANGELINA.
Jeff: OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU SAY WHO IT WAS FOR.
YEAH.
THANK YOU, DAN.
Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR ANGELINA WILL
NOT COUNT.
WOW.
THATS MY ANGEL RIGHT THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
THIS IS DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH.
Jeff: FIRST VOTE,
CHRISTIAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
CHRISTIAN, DOES NOT COUNT.
CHRISTIAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
ANGELINA.
THANK GOD.
Jeff: DOES NOT COUNT.
ANGELINA.
DOES NOT COUNT.
NOW WHAT?
YOU GUYS ARE TOUGH, MAN.
Jeff: JOHN.
WITHIN VOTE JOHN.
NINTH PERSON VOLTED OUT AN THE
SECOND MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
JOHN, THATS TWO,S THAT ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
GOOD ONE, GUYS.
SORRY TO SEE YOU GO.
JOHN, I LOVE YOU, MAN.
THATS OFF THE TOP ROPE,
BROTHER.
GOOD GAME, GUYS.
Jeff: JOHN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
WE LOVE YOU.
I STILL WANT TOP COMPTROLLER
IF THATS OKAY.
YOURE IN, BROTHER.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: AN NOW, LIKE ANGELINA
SAID, YALL GET TO GO BACK TO
CAMP AND LIVE TOGETHER.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR:" WHEN THERES A BAD
BREAKUP.
WALK AROUND THE BEACH AND
FIGURE IT OUT.
I HAVE TO SEPARATE MYSELF
FROM HIM.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO PLAY THE
FIELD.
EVERY SINGLE PERSON IS LIKE,
SHOULD I GO OVER THERE?
COME TO THE DAVID, COME TO
THE GOOD SIDE.
BUT THERE ARE ALWAYS TRUST
ISSUES.
DAN IS GOING HOME.
THEYRE LYING TO MY FACE
AGAIN.
IN CLASSIC GOLIATH FASHION,
DAVID WITH THE SLING, TWO VOTES
FROM A DISTANCE.
THATS ALL IT TAKES THE TAKE
DOWN A GOLIATH IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
IRONICALLY, I PREDICTED TONIGHT
A BROCHACHO BLINDSIDE.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT CHRISTIAN,
AND IT ENDED UP BEING ME.
SON OF A BITCH.