Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": AT THE GOLIATH
TRIBE, NATALIE HAD NO FILTER.
I LIKE TO SAME IM ASSERTIVE.
SOME PEOPLE SAY ITS AGGRESSIVE.
OH, WELL.
Jeff: AND JEREMY HAD NO
BOUNDARIES.
GOING THROUGH DANS THINGS, I
UNWRAPPED THE SOCK AND I SAW THE
IDOL.
Jeff: AT THE DAVID TRIBE,
THERE WAS A PLAN IN PLACE.
BUT WHEN A NEW ALLIANCE
FORMED... THE DECISION WAS IN
THEIR HANDS.
THE PLAN IS TO ELIMINATE
JESS.
I SAY WE JUST GET LYRSA OUT
AND STAY STRONG.
THE MASON-DIXON ALLIANCE IS
IN A POWER POSITION.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CHRISTIAN AND NICK BLINDSIDED
JESSICA.
JESSICA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
LEAVING BI, DAVIE, AND CARL
STUNNED.
18 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
THERE WAS ABSOLUTELY TENSION
WHEN WE GOT BACK FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BECAUSE ME, BI, AND
CARL WERE BLINDSIDED.
IT IS NOT FUN.
IT WAS NOT FUN.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I GOTTA GIVE
IT TO THEM, MAN.
THAT WAS GOOD GAME PLAY.
THEY PLAYED ME.
LUCKILY, I HAVE THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL RIGHT NOW, AND
ITS SOMETHING THAT CAN SAVE ME,
BUT BEING LEFT OUT OF THE VOTE,
IM SHOCKED.
I SEE-- I SEE YOU AND NICK AS
MY NUMBER ONES.
YEAH.
AND I GET BLINDSIDED BY MY
NUMBER ONES.
THATS NOT A GOOD FEELING.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND YOU FEEL
BETRAYED, OKAY, BUT I CAN ONLY
TELL YOU THAT GABBY MADE A MOVE.
AND SO BASICALLY, THEY GRABBED
ME AND THEY GRABBED NICK AT THE
LAST MINUTE.
GABBY, SHES A SMART ONE,
MAN.
SHES MANIPULATIVE.
SHE WAS ABLE TO PERSUADE BOTH
NICK AND CHRISTIAN, TWO OF MY
TOP GUYS, TO VOTE AGAINST ME.
SO SHES THE ONE YOU GOTTA WATCH
OUT FOR, MAN.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
MACEOP,.
WHATS UP, DIXON?
DUDE!
MASON-DIXON JUST PULLED THE
BEST MOVE WE COULD POSSIBLY PULL
BECAUSE WE ARE RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE, RIGHT WHERE WE WANT TO
BE.
WEVE GOT THE GIRLS, WHO THINK
THAT WERE IN A FIVE-PERSON
ALLIANCE WITH THEM, AND THEN
WEVE GOT BI AND DAVIE AND CARL,
WHO WERE COMPLETELY BLINDSIDED
AND DONT WANT TO GO HOME.
SO THAT PUTS THE MASON-DIXON
LEAN RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
EXACTLY.
AND THE BEAUTY OF THE
SITUATION IS NOBODY SUSPECTS ME
AND CHRISTIAN WERE ACTUALLY
BEHIND THIS, SO I WANT TO MAKE
THEM THINK ITS GABBYS FAULT
THAT JESSICA IS GONE.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, IF WE LOSE
AGAIN, MASON-DIXONS GOING TO
DECIDE WHO GOES HOME AGAIN.
I DIDNT EXPECT THIS GAME TO
BE, YOU KNOW, THIS HARD.
JESS WAS KIND OF LIKE A DAUGHTER
TO ME.
SHE WAS A LITTLE SWEETHEART.
LOSING MY NUMBER-ONE ALLY, IT
REALLY, REALLY MADE ME MISS
HOME.
YOU KNOW, I LOVE MY FAMILY
DEARLY, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
POOF, THEYRE GONE, AND THEN,
YOU KNOW, YOU FEEL ALMOST ALL
ALONE.
BUT BEING A DAVID, I ALWAYS CAME
FROM THE BOTTOM AND WORK FOR
EVERYTHING THAT I HAVE.
SO I REALLY HAVE TO TURN IT UP
ONE MORE NOTCH, YOU KNOW.
PRETTIEST SUNRISE.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
YEAH.
WHO?
YOUR BUDDY DAVIE.
THAT TOTALLY CAUGHT ME BY
SURPRISE.
EVEN THOUGH I GOT SCREWED
OVER, IM, LIKE, WIDE AWOKE.
LIKE, IM, LIKE, GOING TO HAVE
FUN NOW.
I WAS REALLY, TRULY HURT BY THE
BLINDSIDE.
BUT IT WOKE ME UP.
IT WAS LIKE, OKAY, GIRL, TIME TO
PLAY.
ITS HAPPENING.
I WAS PLAYING A SIMPLE GAME.
EVIDENCE JUST GOING ALONG WITH
WHAT EVERYBODY WAS VOTING, BUT
IN FIGHTING, YOU HAVE TO BE
ADAPTABLE, AND YOU HAVE TO BE
RUTHLESS.
SO IM GOING TO FIGHT MY
DAMNEDEST.
THIS ISLAND IS LIKE A CAGE FOR
ME, AND ONCE THE DOOR SHUTS,
ANYTHING GOES.
AND IM GOING TO PUT MY GAME
FACE ON.
I LIKE YOU AND I TRUST YOU.
AND TO BE HONEST, I DONT FEEL
BETRAYED BY ANYBODY BUT GABBY.
SHE ALWAYS ACTS LIKE SHES,
LIKE, WORRIED ABOUT HERSELF.
SHES THE VULNERABLE ONE.
SHE ALWAYS CRIES A LOT.
ID TAKE HER OUT NEXT IF I
HAD THE OPPORTUNITY.
I WOULD, TOO.
I KNEW FROM THE MOMENT IT
HAPPENED, IT WAS GABBY.
I DIDNT EXPECT MUCH LOYALTY
FROM THE OTHER ONES THAT
FLIPPED, BUT FROM GABBY, I
EXPECTED A LOT.
AND SHE LEFT ME OUT OF THE LOOP.
SO ITS A LITTLE BIT PERSONAL,
BUT, ALSO-- ITS A LOT PERSONAL.
IN A PERFECT WORLD, I WOULD LOVE
TO SEE GABBY GO HOME.
A LITTLE BABY FISH, GUYS.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU CAUGHT A FISH!
THAT WILL BE ENOUGH FISH FOR
EVERYBODY?
LIFE IS SO GOOD.
WHEN YOURE WINNING, LIKE
GOLIATHS BEEN DOING, EVERYBODY
IS IN A REALLY GOOD MOOD.
SO RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE THE
GAME FOR ME IS ABOUT CONNECTING
WITH PEOPLE.
DO YOU STILL DO PRO WRESTLING?
YEAH, ALL TIME.
I HAVE NEVER WATCHED
WRESTLING IN MY LIFE.
WHAT?
DUDES IN SPARKLY TIGHTS.
YOU NEVER WATCHED A PRO WEST
LING MATCH?
YOU HAVE BEEN WASTING YOUR LIFE.
OUT HERE IM NOT A PRO WRESTLER.
IM ME.
HI, SEBASTIAN.
HEY, GIRL!
WHATS GOING ON?
SEA BASS.
NOT MUCH.
CLIMBING OUT OF THE SHELL.
IT FEELS TO ME LIKE IM GETTING
BETTER AT OLD-SCHOOL HUMAN
SKILLS, CONVERSATIONS, LAUGHING
WITH FRIENDS.
READY, SET, GO!
OH!
WOOOO!
IT SPRINTED THAT TIME.
ITS NOT JUST ABOUT SCHEMING,
FIGURING OUT WHO GETS VOTED OUT
NEXT.
IT IS ABOUT GROWING AS A PERSON
AND CONVICT PEOPLE.
WE NEED ALEC TO TIE A KNOT.
COME TIE A KNOT, ALEX.
DOES SHE NEED ME?
SHES SAYING YOUR NAME.
UNFORTUNATELY, I THINK
NATALIE IS ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK.
SHES USED TO BEING THE BOZ
BITCH, TELLING PEOPLE WHAT TO
DO.
IT DOESNT WORK LIKE THAT OUT
HERE.
BUT I TRUST NATALIE, AND I ALSO
THINK THAT NATALIE TRUSTS ME.
AND NATALIE IS SOMEONE THAT I
COULD WORK WITH IF WE COULD JUST
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO GET HER PAST
THE NEXT COUPLE OF TRIBALS AND
DOWN THE LINE.
I KIND OF WANT TO GO FISHING,
BUT IM SO SCARED OF LOSING THIS
AND GETTING VOTED OUT.
( LAUGHS )
"WELL, YOU KNOW, JEREMY DID LOSE
THE SPEAR.
AND KNOW HE HELPED A LOT
AROUND CAMP, BUT HE LOST THE
SPEAR AND WE REALLY CANT"-- I
ACTUALLY REALLY LIKE ALL THE
PEOPLE ON MY TRIBE BUT I FEEL
LIKE IM BONDING THE MOST WITH
JEREMY BECAUSE HES SO HILARIOUS
AND HE BOSSES ME AROUND.
WATCH YOUR FINGERS!
IVE GOTTEN TO KNOW JEREMY
AND I LIKE HIM A LOT.
WHEN UPPER IN SOUTH CAROLINA DID
YOU DO THIS A LOT?
I WOULD GO FISHING-FISHING.
WE WOULD WAKE UP AT THE CRACK OF
DAWN, GO FISHING.
I HAVE A GREAT FATHER, BUT,
UNFORTUNATELY, HE GOT EARLY
ALZHEIMERS.
BEING OUT HERE ON THE WATER JUST
REMINDS ME OF OUR MOST ENJOIBLG
TIME.
GROWING UP, I WAS THE EXACT SAME
WAY I AM NOW, AND HE WAS TRYING
TO MOLD ME.
I SAID, "DADDY, WHAT, DO YOU
THINK IM GONNA BE WHEN I GROW
UP."
HE SAID, "I DONT KNOW WHAT
YOURE GONNA BE BUT I KNOW YOU
AINT GOING TO WORK WITH YOUR
EXPHANDZ YOU AINT COMING BACK
TO THIS FARM."
I USED TO BUTT HEADS WITH HIM SO
MUCH BUT AS I GOT OLDER I
REALIZED EVERYTHING HE WAS
TELLING ME WAS TRUE AND HE WAS
TRYING TO MAKE ME BE THE BEST
MAN I COULD BE.
I JUST KNOW HOW PROUD HE WOULD
BE OF MY LIFE NOW.
HOW IM A LAWYER, IM PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."
IM LIVING MY DREAMS, AND HES
NOT ABLE TO SEE THE FRUITS OF
HIS SACRIFICE TO MAKE A BETTER
LIFE FOR ME.
AND THERES NO WAY FOR ME TO
SHOW HIM MY APPRECIATION BECAUSE
BY THE TIME I WAS AN ACTUALIZED
MAN, IT WAS TOO LATE.
IF HE SAW THIS, IT WOULD MAKE
HIM SO PROUD.
I THINK JEREMY, THE MORE YOU
GET TO KNOW HIM, YOU RAILS
THERES A REAL PERSON OF DEPTH
THERE WHO HAS SEEN A LOT AND
DONE A LOT.
BUT I THINK JEREMY BEING LIKE A
LITTLE SNEAK AND FINDINGIDE NOLZ
PEEKS JACKETS, IT JUST MAKES
HIM LOOK LIKE HELL DO ANYTHING
FOR THE MONEY.
SO IM KIND OF AFRAID TO GO DOWN
THE PRIMROSE PATH WITH JEREMY.
IM JUST A LITTLE AFRAID HES
GOING TO BE HIS OWN WORST ENEMY
DOWN LINE, AND I DONT WANT TO
BE TAKEN DOWN WITH JEREMY.
OKAY, SO, CLEARLY, ON SOME
LEVEL, YOU KNOW, BEING INVITED
TO SLAMTOWN MEANS YOU HAVE BEEN
SLAMMED.
YOURE OBSESSED.
I LOVE SELECTMAN TOWN.
I THINK THAT JOHN ON THE OTHER
TRIBE, MAYOR OF SLAMTOWN, IS
ENDLESSLY FASCINATING.
HE PRESUMABLY WAS BORN AND
RAISED IN A SLAMTOWN, WHICH
SOUNDS AWESOME TO ME.
BUT IN WINTVILLE, WHERE I GREW
UP, WE HAD HARD TIMES.
SO I CANT WAIT TO HEAR WHAT
SLAMTOWN IS LIKE.
IF YOURE IN THE SLAMMER AND
THE-- AND ALL THE PEOPLE THERE
ARE LIKE, "YOU HAVE TO GOVERN
THESE PEOPLE AND THEY HAVE
NEEDS."
AND ITS JOHN.
HES THE MAYOR.
WHAT ARE THE CITIZENS OF
SLAMTOWN CALLED?
THE SLAM TONIANS.
CHRISTIAN IS JUST THE
SWEETEST GUY.
EXPHEEZ FUNNY.
HE ALWAYS CRACKS JOKES.
AND FEEL LIKE WERE CUT FROM
THE SAME CLOTH.
HES MY NUMBER-ONE ALLY IN THIS
GAME.
THE NERDS HAVE IT.
WERE IN.
I DONT REALLY KNOW WHERE
YOURE AT, DAVIE, BECAUSE GABBY
TURNED ON JUSTIN.
YEAH.
MADE ME FEEL PRETTY CLUELESS.
I WILL NEVER TRUST GABBY AGAIN.
SHE LEFT ME OUT OF THE LOOP.
SO RIGHT NOW IM JUST SEEING
WHERE EVERYBODY IS AT BECAUSE IF
WE ALL SEEM TO BE ON THE SAME
PAGE, WE CAN GET HER OUT OF THE
GAME.
WE GOT BURNT BY HER IS WHAT
IM SAYING SO THE TIME COULD BE
RIGHT TO GET HER OUT.
BI IS TELLING ME HOW
DANGEROUS GABBY IS, AND IM
THINKING, YEAH, THAT SOUNDS
GREAT FOR ME BECAUSE I WANTED TO
PIN ALL THE BLAME ON GABBY AND
KEEP MASON-DIXON SAFE SO
EVERYTHING WENT TOGETHER
PERFECTLY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT REALLY
SCARED ME?
WHAT?
WAS HOW QUICK FREAKING GAKY
GOT JESSICA VOTED OUT.
THATS WHAT IM SAYING.
THAT SCARED ME TO DEATH.
SHE SCARES ME.
ME, TOO.
IF WE HAVE CHRISTIAN, WEVE
GOT THE NUMBERS.
WITHOUT CHRISTIAN, WE DONT.
I THINK WE WOULD HAVE
CHRISTIAN.
BECAUSE WITH US FOUR WE NEED
THE ONLY THING THAT WORRIES
ME IS CHRISTIAN AND GABBY ARE
CLOSE.
BUT HES PART OF MASON-DIXON.
HES MY NUMBER ONE, AND I WANT
TO MAKE SURE IM HIS NUMBER ONE.
SO IF I CAN GET GABBY OUT OUT OF
HERE, IM GOING TO DO IT.
I THINK THE BIGGER THE FISH
IS THE SMARTER IT IS, THE
SCAREDDIER IT IS.
YEAH.
ITS REALLY HARD.
FISH HAVE THE ADVANTAGE.
YEAH.
TALKING ABOUT, LIKE,
STARBUCKS.
BIG PIECES, SMALL PIECES?
ANYTHING THATS DRY, BASICALLY?
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY IS I SAW
TOO MANY SIDE CONVERSATIONS THAT
MADE ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
IM THE BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT
NOW, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT I THINK
THINGS OUT.
PEOPLE ARE TALKING STRATEGY
ALL MORNING?
REALLY.
THE THING IS, BEFORE THERES
A POSSIBLE TRIBE SWAP, AFTER THE
TRIBE--
YEAR, ITS BAD FOR THE TRIBE.
YEAH, WE COULD HAVE EVERY
SINGLE PERSON STILL HERE.
YOU KNOW FOR A FACT THEY WERE
TALKING STRATEGY?
NO.
BUT KNOW FROM MY GUT THEY WERE
TALKING STRATEGY.
REALLY?
JEREMY IS SEEING PEOPLE KIND OF
COUPLE OFF AND TALK IN GROUPS,
AND I WASNT STRATEGIZING.
AND AS FOR RIGHT NOW, WE DONT
HAVE TO STRATEGIZE BECAUSE
NOBODYS GETTING VOTED OUT.
SO THATS JUST PARANOIA TALKING.
FOR ME, AS A SUPERFAN, MAKING
THE MERGE IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING.
YOU DONT WANT TO GET SENT HOME
BEFORE THE MERGE.
BUT IM CONCERNED WITH SO MANY
SIDE CONVERSATIONS GOING ON
TODAY.
IF WE START BREEDING ALL OF THIS
DISTRUST AMONG US, ALL IT CAN DO
IS HURT US WHEN WE DO A TRIBE
SWAP.
I DONT THINK PEOPLE WERE
HAVING SIDE CONVERSATIONS.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU WERE HAVING
SIDE CONVERSATIONS.
I WAS TRYING TO NIP IT IN THE
BUD, MAINLY BECAUSE I THOUGHT IT
WAS COMING IN MY DIRECTION.
TODAY I HAD A TRIBAL MEETING TO
TELL THEM I DIDNT THINK IT WAS
APPROPRIATE.
SLOW IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT FOR
THE STRENGTH OF THE TRIBE.
PLAYING LIKE YOURE ON A TRIBE
WHERE YOU HAVE TO FIGHT FOR YOUR
LIFE, ON A TRIBE WHEN YOU HAVE
WON EACH CHALLENGE AND HAVE NOT
BEEN TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THERES NOTHING REALLY TO TALK
ABOUT UNTIL WE START LOSING, YOU
KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE WE ALL FEEL THE
SAME WAY.
I THINK JEREMY HAS A POINT,
THAT RIGHT NOW WE SHOULD STILL
SEE EACH OTHER AS TEAMMATES,
HOWEVER, HE IS ACTUALLY THE
PERSON HE SHOULD BE SPEAKING TO.
I THINK HES CONSTANTLY SPINNING
STRATEGIES AND POSSIBLE
SCENARIOS.
AND I THINK THATS GOING TO COME
BACK TO BITE HIM IN THE BUTT.
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF
JEREMYS TALK THIS MORNING?
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU THE
SAME THING.
I THINK IT BENEFITTED HIM.
THATS WHY I THINK HE DID IT.
I WAS LIKE, OH, IT MAKES SENSE
YOU SAY NO SIDE STRATEGIZING.
JEREMY IS VERY SMART.
I THINK PART OF HIS SPEECH WAS
STRATEGY IN THE SENSE IF WE
START TO SLOW DOWN THE
CONVERSATIONS, THEN WE STICK
WITH THE FAUC QUO, THE STATUS
QUO BEING NATALIE.
BUT IF THESE CONVERSATIONS KEEP
HAPPENING, THEN PEOPLE MIGHT
START TO WAKE UP TO THE FACT TO
IT MIGHT BE BETTER TO TAKE OUT
SOMEONE WHO MIGHT BE A THREAT,
LIKE JEREMY.
FLICK YOUR WRIST.
COME UP HIGHER.
YOU WANT TO STILL KEEP IT LOW
BUT YOU WANT TO COME OUT OF THE
WATER.
NOW FLICK YOUR WRIST.
I DID IT!
SEE.
I TOLD YOU.
KARA AND DAN, THEYRE
DEFINITELY IN A SHOWMANCE.
NATALIE IS THE FIRST TO GO IF WE
LOSE AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
YOURE POSITIVE HES THAT?
IM POSITIVE HE HAS IT.
HE SHOWED IT TO YOU?
I SAW IT IN HIS COAT.
TO BE CLEAR, NO MATTER HOW MUCH
IM TALKING ABOUT 10 STRONG,
WERE ONE FAMILY, I ALSO AM
PLAYING A GAME FOR $1 MILLION.
AND YOU DONT HAVE AN ALLIANCE
UNTIL YOU SHARE INFORMATION.
HE HAS AN IDOL AND HE DIDNT
TELL ME?
HOW GOOD ARE WE?
SO SHADY.
LET ME JUST SAY IT REAL QUICK
EYE KNOW THAT DAN HAS THE IDOL
BECAUSE I LOOKED AT IT IN HIS
PANTS AND I SAW THE NOTE.
IT SAID, "CONGRATULATIONS.
OF THE.
I DIDNT READ FARTHER THAN THAT
AND THEN I FELT THE IDOL.
JEREMY CLAIMS HE FOUND AN
IDOL IN DANS JACKET BUT IT
MAKES ME A LITTLE LEARY OF WHAT
JEREMY HAS UP HIS FANCY SLEEVES.
ONLY SOMEBODY RUNNING AROUND
SCHEMING IS GOING TO BE PARANOID
ENOUGH TO TELL EVERYONE, "HEY,
HEY, LETS NOT HAVE SIDE
CONVERSATIONS.
LETS STAY 10 STRONG."
WHICH IS CRAZY.
HES PLAYING THE GAME HARD.
DO I BLAME HIM?
NO DO I TRUST HIM?
NO.
♪ ♪
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
GOLIATHS GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK
JESSICA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
INTERESTING.
DIDNT SEE THAT.
Jeff: SO, DAY NINE.
THE ONLY THING--
WOOO!
YEAH!
I CANT EVEN SEE, JEFF!
( LAUGHING ).
Jeff: YOU KNOW, IM REALLY
IMPRESSED BECAUSE OUR FIRST
CHALLENGE WAS IN ONE OF THE
BIGGEST STORMS WEVE EVER HAD.
THE SECOND IMMUNITY CHALLENGE,
ONE OF THE HOTTEST DAYS I EVER
REMEMBER.
AND ONCE AGAIN, FOR AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, IN THE DUMPING RAIN,
BUT I SEE MORE SMILES THAN NOT.
IS THAT JUST SPEAKING TO THE
NATURE OF THE ADVENTURE INSIDE
EACH OF YOU?
YES.
YES!
Jeff: GABBY, YOUR EYES ARE
CLOSED, OPEN, CLOSED, OPEN.
I CAN BARELY OPEN MY EYES TO
LOOK AT YOU, JEFF!
THERES SO MUCH RAIN!
Jeff: SHALL WE GET TO IT.
YEAH!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, FIRST
THINGS FIRST, ANGELINA, TAKE
BACK THE IDOL.
THANK YOU.
BORROWING IT FOR NOW.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, ONE
PLAYER FROM EACH TRIBE WILL
MANEUVER THEIR WAY THROUGH AN
OBSTACLE.
THEN THREE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL WORK TOGETHER TO UNTANGLE
ROPES, GETTING THEMSELVES TO THE
FINISH.
YOULL THEN HOOK A SLED, PULL IT
BACK TO YOU, AND USE THE PIECE
ON BOARD.
IN ADDITION, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR?
YES.
( THUNDER )
UMBRELLAS?
Jeff: THAT WAS BIG.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE REWARD IS
GREAT.
( CHEERS )
OH, YES!
Jeff: BANKETS, PILLOWS,
HAMMOCK, CHAIRS.
ILL DO MY BEST TO COVER IT.
SOUND GOOD?
YAY!
THANK YOU!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GOLIATH,
YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA MEMBERS.
TWO PEOPLE SITTING OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
SO WHO IS SITTING?
ILL DO IT WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT, GUYS?
IM GONNA STAY IN THIS ONE.
WERE SITTING OUT.
AND NATALIE WANTS TO DO THE
PUZZLE.
Jeff: GOLIATHS, WHO IS IT
GOING TO BE?
NATALIA AND ANGELINA ARE GOING
TO SIT THIS ONE OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE SIT-OUT
BENCH.
ILL GIVE YOU A FEW MINUTES TO
STRATEGIZE AND WE WILL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT WAS ANOTHER SHOWDOWN BETWEEN
ALAND HE CAN BI.
ALEC HAS WON EVERY SHOWDOWN FOR
THE GOLIATHS AND HE HAS NOT
LOST.
THIS IS A REMATCH WITH BI, WHO
SLIPS, AND THEN JAMS HER LEG
THROUGH.
ALEC IS THROWING HIMSELF THROUGH
THIS FIRST OBSTACLE.
COME ON, ALEC!
YEAH, YOU GOT IT!
Jeff: ALEC NOW IS HUNG UP
AND HE GOES THE WRONG WAY, OPENS
THE DOOR FOR BI.
JIEWF GOT TO BE RIGHT.
ALEC STUCK NOW.
DOESNT KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IT IS NOW BI IN THE LEAD OVER
ALEC.
THEY BOTH GET THERE.
GET THROUGH THE ROPE!
GO, GO, GO!
GOTTA GET BACK TO YOUR MAT!
BI HOBBLING HER WAY BACK.
GO, GUYS!
BOTH TRIBES!
WE ARE DEAD EVEN NOW!
DAVIDS ARE 0 FOR 2 IN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES, BUT THE DAVIDS ARE
IN THIS ONE RIGHT NOW.
NOW IT IS ABOUT COMMUNICATION.
DAVIE, OVER TO ME, OVER TO
ME.
Jeff: YOUVE GOT TO WORK
TOGETHER, GATHERING THAT ROPE,
TALKING TO EACH OTHER.
OVER, MICHAEL, OVER.
OKAY.
Jeff: IT IS NICK, DAVIE,
AND LYRSA.
IT IS KARA, JEREMY, AND MIKE.
YOU GO OVER.
ITS A RHYTHM, YOU GUYS.
PERFECT!
SAME THING, GUYS!
Jeff: WERE BACK EVEN.
DAY NINE OF "SURVIVOR," TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
GET YOUR SLACK OUT!
ONE MORE!
ONE MORE.
Jeff: WE ARE STILL VERY
CLOSE!
GO!
Jeff: BOTH TRIBES HEADING
OVER.
OVER THE TOP, DAVIE, OVER THE
TOP!
MICHAELS OVER, JEREMYS
OVER.
THIEWR GOOD!
YOURE GOOD!
GO, GO!
IT IS ANYBODYS CHALLENGE TO WIN
RIGHT NOW.
WE NOW HAVE JOHN AND DAN TRYING
TO HOOK THE SLED, AND CARL AND
ELISABETH.
CARL AND ELISABETH HAVE WORKED
WITH ROPE THEIR WHOLE LIVES.
WILL IT PAY OFF NOW?
HOLD THE ROPE UP FOR ME.
Jeff: IT IS NOW TEAM WORK
WITH THE ROPE MANAGEMENT.
JUST MISSES!
CARL TOSSES IT.
CARL SHORT AGAIN.
HERE COMES ELISABETH NOW.
HERE GOES JOHN FOR THE GOLIATHS.
AND HES GOT IT.
THE GOLIATHS HAVE THEIR SLED.
NOW THEYVE GOT TO PULL IT BACK.
ELISABETH TOSSES IT.
ELISABETH HAS IT FOR THE DAVIDS.
COME ON, GUYS!
Jeff: GOLIATHS ALMOST
THERE.
YOURE GOOD!
TAKE OVER, PUZZLE SOLVERS!
COME ON, GUYS!
YEAH, YEAH!
Jeff: YOURE GOOD!
GET THE PUZZLE PIECES!
WE ARE STILL NECK AND NECK RIGHT
NOW.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO THE PUZZLE
PART OF THIS CHALLENGE.
IT IS NATALIE AND ALISON TAKING
ON CHRISTIAN AND GABBY.
WHAT WOULD BE THE TOP?
YOU ALL RIGHT.
I HURT MY KNEE.
Jeff: ITS GOING TO COME
DOWN TO THIS RIGHT HERE.
WHO WILL BE FASTEST AT SOLVING
THIS FOUR-PIECE PUZZLE?
THERES NO COLORS.
SO ITS COMPLETELY GEOMETRIC.
Jeff: YOU ARE MAKING A
PYRAMID.
THIS?
NO, ITS NOT GOING TO DO,
ITS NOT GOING TO DO.
YEAH.
Jeff: THIS PUZZLE COULD
SOLVE QUICKLY.
YOU COULD BE VERY CLOSE AND NOT
KNOW IT.
NATALIE SAT OUT THE LAST
CHALLENGE.
SHE WAS NOT GOING TO SIT OUT
THIS ONE.
COULD THIS ABE PYRAMID ON
TOP?
NO, ITS NOT.
Jeff: THE DAVIDS HAVE NOT
TASTED VICTORY IN AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE YET THIS SEASON.
THE GOLIATHS DONT EVEN KNOW
WHAT TRIBAL COUNCIL LOOKS LIKE.
I SEE IT, I SEE IT!
Jeff: THE DREAM ENDS
TONIGHT FOR SOMEBODY.
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
YOU DONT SEE ANY SIDE THAT
WILL FIT IN HERE?
I DO NOT SEE A SIDE.
OKAY, THEN WEVE GOT IT
WRONG.
YES!
Jeff: THE DAVIDS HAVE DONE
IT!
THE DAVIDS WIN IMMUNITY FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN THIS GAME!
STUNNING THE GOLIATH TRIBE THAT
CANNOT BELIEVE THEY LOST.
( CHEERS )
DAVIDS, CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
FIRST IMMUNITY WIN.
IN ADDITION, YOUR REWARD WILL BE
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP UPON.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
YES!
Jeff: BI, WELL HAVE
MEDICAL TAKE A LOOK AT THAT
KNEE.
ALL RIGHT, NATALIA, WILL THERE
BE ANY SECOND GUESSING ABOUT WHO
PLAYED, WHO SAT OUT, WHAT
POSITIONS PEOPLE WERE IN?
I BELIEVE THAT ANGELINA WOULD
HAVE BEEN STRONG IN THAT
CHALLENGE.
SHE SAW WHAT PIECES NEEDED TO GO
IN THE RIGHT SPOT IMMEDIATELY.
BUT AT SOME POINT YOU HAVE TO
SAY, "THIS ISNT MY PLACE, AND
MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE WOULD BE
BETTER AT IT IT."
THANK YOU.
Jeff: YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO
HAVE AN INTERESTING AFTERNOON
BACK AT CAMP.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
NATALIE IS THE REASON WE LOST
THIS CHALLENGE.
FOR TONIGHTS VOTE, IF I HAD IT
MY WAY, I WOULD BE WRITING A
SMILEY FACE NEXT TO NATALIES
NAME.
WE DID IT, BABY!
WAY TO GO, TEAM!
CHAIRS!
WE WON THE IMMUNITY AND REWARD
CHALLENGE!
IM SO HAPPY.
WE GOT A GOOD WIN TODAY.
( CHEERS ).
IM REALLY PROUD OF MYSELF
THAT I FINISHED THE PUZZLE
ALONGSIDE A DUDE WHO HAS A
Ph.D. IN ROBOTICS AND
MECHANICAL ENGINEERING, AND WE
FINALLY WON!
HOW DOES YOUR LEG FEEL?
ITS OKAY.
I SPRAINED MY M.C.L.
I TORE MY M.C.L. TRAINING
M.M.A., WAY BEFORE "SURVIVOR,"
AND ACTUALLY HAD TO PULL OUT OF
A REALLY BIG FIGHT AND NURSE IT
FOR TWO MONTHS.
UNFORTUNATELY TODAY AT THE
CHALLENGE, I FELT SOMETHING
UNSTABLE, AND I KNOW MY KNEE.
THAT SCARES ME.
ITS VERY WEAK RIGHT NOW, AND
THIS IS NOT AN EASY GAME
PHYSICALLY AT ALL.
I AM REALLY GREAT AT PUZZLES.
THIS ONE TODAY, I COULDNT SEE.
SO I DID MY BEST.
IT DIDNT COME TOGETHER.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT THE LOSS,
PARTICULARLY BECAUSE IT HAPPENED
ON MY PIECE OF THE CHALLENGE,
WHICH IS THE PUZZLE-SOLVING
ASPECT.
BUT ALL I CAN DO IS PLAY IT OIT
AT THIS POINT.
IM REALLY NOT SURE WHAT TO SAY
TO YOU ABOUT ASKING FOR YOUR
SUPPORT, BECAUSE I CAN HONESTLY
TELL YOU THAT I NEVER HAVE FELT
I HAD YOUR SUPPORT SINCE WEVE
BEEN ON THIS ISLAND.
IVE BEEN LIKE, WHERE IS MY
SUPPORT FROM MY BROTHER?
THIS IS THE TRUTH, NATALIE.
IM GOING TO TELL YOU MY TRUTH.
I DONT THINK YOU UNDERSTAND
YOUR PERSONALITY OR THE WAY YOU
SPEAK.
I DONT HAVE NO PROBLEM, YOU
KNOW, TELLING YOU TO YOUR FACE.
THATS HOW BLACK PEOPLE WORK.
IT IS.
WE TELL EACH OTHER TO OUR
FACE.
MY PITCH TO YOU IS TO
CONSIDER KEEPING ME ON THE TRIBE
IN SPITE OF ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
I DONT THINK YOU HAVE--
TRUTHFULLY, I DONT THINK YOU
HAVE THE SUPPORT.
IT WOULD BE AN UPHILL BATTLE
THAT I JUST DONT THINK ANYBODY
COULD--
IM NOT GOING TO JUST SIT
DOWN AND NOT TALK TO PEOPLE AND
NOT--
I THINK YOU SHOULD MAKE A
PITCH TO EACH PERSON.
THIS IS WHY I FEEL LIKE YOU
SHOULD TALK TO EVERYBODY.
I AM, YEAH.
IN THE PAST, I TRIED TO STEP
IN AND TRY TO BE A MEDIATOR, BUT
NATALIE HAS POOR SELF-AWARENESS
AND POOR COMMUNICATION SKILLS.
SO I ALREADY KNOW THESE NOT
GOING TO LEARN, EVEN THOUGH ITS
A BENEFIT TO HER.
YOU KNOW, YOU ONLY CAN DO WHAT
YOU CAN DO.
I FEEL LIKE ITS CLEAR WHAT
NEEDS TO HAPPEN, JUST FOR OUR
TRIBE.
WE NEED OUR TRIBE STRONG.
SHE SAID THATS WHAT SHE WAS
GOOD AT, SO THATS WHY I LET HER
COMPETE IN THE SENSE THAT SHES
FIGHTING FOR HER OWN LIFE,
RIGHT?
NATALIE HAS BEEN DIGGING HER OWN
GRAVE SINCE DAY ONE, AND ONE
COULD ARGUE THAT BY STEPPING UP
FOR THE PUZZLE AND FALLING
SHORT, THAT SHE JUST PUT A-- THE
FINAL NAIL IN HER COFFIN.
CAN I FLOAT AN IDEA BY YOU?
YES.
JEREMY.
HES TRYING TO STIR THE POT MORE
THAN ANYONE.
NATALIE IS AN EASY SECOND OUT.
SHES NOT A THREAT IN THIS GAME
AT ALL.
I KNOW.
THAT WOULD BE MY FIRST
CHOICE.
I KNOW ITS NOT AS SIMPLE, BUT I
THINK ITS THE SMARTEST.
JEREMY IS THE MUCH BETTER FIRST
PERSON TO GO BECAUSE HE IS
SMART, CHARMING, PLAYING REALLY
HARD, AND NOT SUPER TRUSTWORTHY,
VERSUS NATALIE, WHO IN ALL
CONSIDERATION, IS PRETTY
HARMLESS, IN MY OPINION.
I AM SO ON THE FENCE ABOUT
IT.
I AM HAPPY WITH EITHER.
BUT I STRONGLY PREFER JEREMY.
AND HES A TALKER.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME.
HES A CHARMER.
HES A MANIPULATOR.
IN MY DAY-TO-DAY LIFE.
USE THE POWER OF PERSUASION.
I USE IT IF IM PULLED OVER BY A
POLICE OFFICER FOR GOING A
LITTLE BIT TOO FAST.
FOR GETTING DISCOUNTS AT
RESTAURANTS -- WHATEVER IT MAY
BE.
I THINK WE HAVE A SHOT AT
JEREMY.
I WANT TO GO FOR JEREMY?
THATS WHAT I WANT TO DO.
BECAUSE EVERYONE IS DEAD SET ON
NATALIE, I KNOW ITS GOING TO BE
A LOT OF LEG WORK... I WANT HIM
OUT.
BUT FOR ME, THIS IS WHAT MAKES
ME A GOLIATH, IS IF I CAN WHIP
THESE VOTES TO COMPLETELY SHIFT
OVER FROM NATALIE TO JEREMY,
THEN TO ME, THATS MY SHINING
MOMENT OF THIS GAME.
AT LEAST ONE OF MANY, I HOPE.
I WANT HIM OUT.
IF IT WAS UP TO ME IT WOULD
BE NATALIE.
I THINK NATALIE, SHES LIKE A
DEMORALIZER AROUND CAMP.
SHES TERRIBLE AT THE
CHALLENGES.
THATS NEVER GOING TO CHANGE.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS A DONE DEAL.
NATALIE IS LIKE AN UNPLEASANT
DRAIN AROUND CAMP, AND JEREMY IS
THIS FORCE OF LIFE WHO I REALLY
LOVE.
YOU KNOW, ITS CRAZY THAT IN
NINE DAYS YOU CAN GET TO KNOW
SOMEBODY WELL ENOUGH TO FEEL
REALLY ATTACHED.
AND I KNOW HOW MUCH THE GAME
MEANS TO JEREMY.
AND HE IS HIS OWN WORST ENEMY,
BUT I THINK IT IS A SIMPLE
ANSWER, AND NATALIE IS THE
ANSWER.
NATALIE, RIGHT?
WHY?
WERE ALL VOTING JEREMY.
NO, I THINK THAT-- THERES NO
WAY WE CAN KEEP WINNING WITH HER
ON OUR TRIBE.
THERE COULD BE A SWAP SOON.
SHES GOING TO TALK BAD ABOUT
EVERY ONE OF US.
SHELL BE VOTED OUT FIRST.
MY ONLY WORRY IS THAT WE
TRIBE SWAP, AND THEN SHE JUST
TARNISHES EVERYBODY.
BUT NOBODYS GOING TO BELIEVE
HER.
I DONT THINK SO.
AND JEREMY IS A BETTER
TALKER, HES SMARTER.
YEAH, JEREMY IS GREAT WITH
PEOPLE.
HES A GREAT TALKER.
HES CHARMING.
BUT YOU CAN ALSO TRUST HIM EARLY
IN THE GAME.
I HAVE NO TRUST WITH HIM
ANYMORE.
IM DOING NATALIE.
THE TRIBE IS ACTING IN UNISON
FOR TONIGHTS VOTE, AND EVEN
THOUGH NATALIE IS THE CLEAR
CHOICE, IT MIGHT NOT BE
EVERYBODYS CLEAR CHOICE.
THEY CAN DEAL WITH NATALIE, SO
THEYRE THINKING LONG TERM WHO
ELSE DO THEY WANT OUT?
BUT I THINK THAT BECAUSE I DONT
LIKE HER SO MUCH, I DONT CARE.
CAN I HAVE A MINUTE WITH
THEM?
SURE, GO AHEAD.
I MEAN, PRIVATELY, WITHOUT
YOU HERE.
I JUST HAVE--
THAT WOULD MAKE ME--
I HAVE SOMETHING TO ASK
ABOUT.
THAT WOULD MAKE H MEANTIME TO
HEAR IT.
YOU HAVE BEEN WALKING AROUND
WHISPERING.
CAN I HAVE A CONVERSATION
WITHOUT YOU?
NOT IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR."
CAN I SEE YOU FOR A MINUTE,
KARA.
YOU JUST ALERTED ME.
YOU HAVE BEEN WALKING AROUND
WHISPERING FOR AN HOUR SO I
DONT FEEL LIKE YOU NEED TO BE A
PART OF MY CONVERSATION, EITHER.
OKAY.
GUESS WHAT?
IM NOT JUST GOING TO STAND
STILL AND TAKE THE PUNCH.
I WAS A SOFTBALL PLAYER.
( LAUGHS )
AND I STILL PLAY SOFTBALL.
IM ON A WOMENS SOFTBALL TEAM
SO, TRUST ME, I CAN THROW SOME
LOW BALLS.
I JUST WANT TO SEE WHAT YOU
ARE COOKING UP?
DIDNT YOU RECOMMEND I SHOULD
BE SCRAMBLING?
I DID RECOMMEND THAT.
ALL I ASK IS LET MY LAST TWO
HOURS BE COOL.
WE ALREADY KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IM NOT GOING TO STRESS OVER IT.
THE NEXT THING I COME BACK
AND YOURE HERE LIKE-- AND
YOURE THROWING MY NAME OUT
THERE.
I HAVENT THROWN YOUR NAME
OUT.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT FROM.
I SAID WANT I WANTED TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION--
I DONT KNOW WHAT YOU WERE
SAYING.
WHAT WOULD I BE SAYING OTHER
THAN ASKING THEM TO RECONSIDER.
TALKING ABOUT ME?
WHY WOULD I TALK ABOUT
YOU,IE,
JEREMY.
I DONT WANT MY NAME TO COME
UP IN NOT HOT SEAT.
THATS IN YOUR HEAD.
YOURE PARANOID.
I AM PARANOID.
DONT WORRY.
YOURE NOT IN THE HOT SEAT.
DO YOU THINK I FEEL OKAY ABOUT
LEAVING?
NO, I DONT.
ITS JUST HARD FOR ME.
NATALIE IS A PERFECT BLEND OF
WHAT I CALL INCOMPETENT AND
OVERCONFIDENT.
SO SHES NOW MORE THAN EVER THE
OBVIOUS VOTE BECAUSE SHE HAS
NOTHING TO OFFER.
BECAUSE WHAT YOU JUST DID
JUST THEN IS A CLEAR EXAMPLE OF
WHY WE GET OFF ON THE WRONG FOOT
BECAUSE I WAS GOG HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH THEM, HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU, AND YOU
MADE IT ABOUT YOU.
IM SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU WERE--
YOU WATCHED "SURVIVOR" BEFORE.
I REALIZE NOW, YOU HAVE NEVER
SEEN "SURVIVOR" BEFORE.
SO IM OPERATING ON YOU--
YOU KNOW WHAT, JEREMY?
THE CONVERSATION IS OVER.
IM NOT GOING TO CONTINUE GOING
BACK AND FORTH WITH YOU BECAUSE
YOU JUST-- ITS ALL ABOUT
JEREMY.
SO CUT IT SHORT.
BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS A TORCH.
GRAB A TORCH, DIP IT IN, AND GET
FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AND WHEN YOUR FIRES GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
ANGELINA, WAS THERE EVER A TIME
WHEN YOU WOULD WATCH "SURVIVOR,"
AND THE RAIN IS COMING DOWN AND
THE THUNDER CRACKS, AND YOU GO,
"IT PROBABLY DIDNT REALLY
THUNDER.
THEY PROBABLY ADDED THAT IN."
YEAH, IT DOESNT GET MORE
REAL THAN BEING HUDDLED IN A
SHELTER THAT YOURE NOT SURE IS
GOING TO HOLD UP, IN A STORM
WHERE YOURE NOT SURE IF A TREE
IS GOING TO FALL ON YOU.
WERE WET ALL THE TIME.
WHEN WE GET ANY SEMBLANCE OF
SUNLIGHT, ITS LOOK A SMALL
MIRACLE HAS HAPPENED.
BUT IT MAKES US TOUGHER PLAYS IN
THE END.
Jeff: MIKE, DESCRIBE THIS.
I JUST REMEMBER AT ONE POINT
IM LYING IN THE MUD, THERES A
CYCLONE GOING ON, AND I HAVE A
LITTLE BASKET AS MY PILLOW.
AND I TWIST IT A LITTLE WAYS AND
I GO, "THIS IS MORE
COMFORTABLE."
AND I GO, "WORK MY STANDARDS
HAVE GONE SO LOW THAT I COULD
ACTUALLY THINK THATS
COMFORTABLE."
Jeff: AND ITS RAINING
HARDER NOW THAN WHEN WE SAT DOWN
JUST A FEW SECONDS AGO.
JEREMY, WHAT HAVE THESE FIRST
NINE DAYS BEEN LIKE IN TERMS OF
THE TRIBE DYNAMICS?
WELL, ILL SAY THIS, NONE OF
US REALLY GOT ALONG, AND NATALIE
WAS KIND OF ON THE OUTSIDE OF
THE SOCIAL DYNAMIC, BECAUSE
SHES A LITTLE BIT HARDER TO
DEAL WITH.
Jeff: NATALIE, SURPRISED TO
HEAR JEREMY SAY YOUR NAME?
NOT AT ALL.
HES SAID IT A FEW TIMES SO HE
SEEMS TO HAVE ME AS HIS TARGET
WHICH I THINK IS UNCALLED FOR,
BUT IT IS WHAT IT IS, JEFF.
TO BE CLEAR, ME AND NATALIE
DONT NECESSARILY HAVE A
PROBLEM.
NORMALLY WHAT HAPPENS IS NATALIE
AND SOMEBODY ELSE HAS A PROBLEM,
SO I TOLD HER, "HEY, YOUR
COMMUNICATION SKILLS ARE POOR."
AND THE THING ABOUT NATALIE THAT
I DONT UNDERSTAND IS HOW DOES
SHE GET TO BE 57 YEARS OLD AND
DO NOT KNOW HOW TO TALK WITH
PEOPLE?
SHES RUDE.
SHE CUTS PEOPLE OFF.
SHE REALLY DOESNT KNOW HOW TO
ACT.
NOW, ANYONE WITH COMMON SENSE
PLAYING THIS GAME WOULD SAY,
"THANKS, BRO.
YOU GAVE ME THE HEADS UP.
LET ME GET MY (BLEEP) TOGETHER."
NOT NATALIE.
SHE DOUBLES DOWN AND I JUST LET
HER DO IT.
Jeff: NATALIE, THAT IS AN
EXAMPLE NOT OF THROWING SOMEBODY
UNDER THE BUS.
THAT WAS LIKE A FREEWAY OF
18-WHEELERS JUST ONE AFTER
ANOTHER AFTER ANOTHER.
THIS IS THE CEEND OF
MENTALITY THAT IM DEALING WITH.
THERES NO WAY THAT YOU CAN TELL
ME THAT HE COULDNT HAVE MADE
THIS STATEMENT AND BEEN MORE
APPROPRIATE AND HAD A MORE
PLEASANT SOUND TO HIS TONE AND
HIS VOICE.
THIS GUY IS RIDICULOUS.
TALKING ABOUT NOT BEING
SELF-AWARE.
YOU LOOK IT UP IN THE
DICTIONARY, YOURE GOING TO SEE
HIS FACE.
BECAUSE THIS IS HOW HE SPEAKS TO
PEOPLE.
NATALIE CAN THINK WHAT SHE
WANTS TO THINK, BUT I GUARANTEE
IF I DIED RIGHT NOW THEY LAID MY
BODY RIGHT THERE, NINE OF THESE
PEOPLE WOULD BE AT MY FUNERAL.
IF SHE DIED, I DONT THINK YOU
COULD SAY THE SAME.
THANK YOU, JEREMY.
Jeff: DAN, COULD PART OF
THIS BE JUST TWO VERY DIFFERENT
COMMUNICATION STYLES?
RIGHT, ITS ALMOST LIKE SHE
SPEAKS DOWN TO PEOPLE, AND IT
MAY NOT BE ON PURPOSE.
IT MAY BE WHAT SHE DOES ON A
REGULAR BASIS.
SHES A BOSS OR WHATEVER, BUT
WERE NOT HER EMPLOYEES.
AND IT WOULD BE LOVELY IF
SOMEBODY ELSE HAS AN OPINION
ABOUT THIS, BECAUSE IM VERY
OPEN TO CONSTRUCTIVE CRITICISM.
PART OF WHAT MAKES "SURVIVOR"
SO TOUGH IS THE CLASH OF HOW
WERE TRYING TO EXPRESS
OURSELVES.
SO FOR NATALIE, SHE MAY FEEL
THAT SHES GIST BEING HERSELF.
BUT THE WAY THAT ITS PERCEIVED
BY OTHERS MATTERS EVEN MORE.
AND I THINK FROM DAY ONE, IT
WAS-- EVERYONE IS TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT THEIR ROLE.
MAYBE NATALIE JUST WENT A LITTLE
TOO HARD AND SET THE TONE FOR
HERSELF DAY ONE.
AND TO BUILD OFF WHAT ALEC IS
SAYING, YOU DONT HAVE A LOT OF
TIME FOR SECOND CHANCES.
SO IF YOU COME OUT THE GATE AND
MAKE A MISTAKE WITH YOUR FIRST
IMPRESSION, YOU MAY HAVE ALREADY
DUG YOUR GRAVE.
IM JUST SO IMPRESSED THAT
IVE BEEN ABLE TO HOLD HALF OF
THIS TRIBAL COUNCIL ALL ABOUT
ME.
AND I EQUALLY IMPRESSED IF THERE
IS A BLINDSIDE TONIGHT AND THAT
ITS NOT ME.
OKAY.
Jeff: NATALIA, IT IS
INTERESTING, WHEN YOURE WINNING
YOU DONT DEAL WITH ANY OF THIS.
YOU LOSE TODAY AND THEN ITS
TRIBAL AND ITS, "OKAY, IF ITS
NATALIE, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN FOR
TOMORROW AND THE NEXT DAY?"
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT WHATS TO COME.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE YOURE
GOING TO BE PLAYING WITH ALONG
THE WAY AND YOU HAVE TO PICK AND
CHOOSE THE RIGHT PEOPLE WHO ARE
GOING TO GET YOU FURTHEST IN THE
GAME.
WELL, JEFF, I THINK IT MIGHT
BE SOMETHING FOR THE TRIBE TO
CONSIDER THEY AM 57 YEARS OLD,
SENIOR CITIZEN.
AM I REALLY A THREAT IN THE
GAME.
VERSUS SOMEONE ELSE --
JEREMY.
AND WHO IS A THREAT IN THE GAME.
BUT WE ARE STILL A TRIBE
GAME, SO ONE, YOU HAVE TO USE
HER IN CHALLENGES, AND, TWO, ITS
MOMENT WE HAVE A TRIBE SWAP,
SHES LEAVING US BEHIND.
SHES NEVER JELLED WITH US.
BOY, YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
I AM SPEAKING RIGHT NOW.
I COMMIT TO ALL NINE OF YOU IF
THERES A TRIBE SWAP, I AM
GOLIATH STRONG.
AND HERES THE FACT, JEFF: ARE
THERE SOME LEARNING LESSONS IN
HERE FOR ME?
ABSOLUTELY.
DAN POINTED OUT NOT NECESSARILY
CONTENT BUT THE DELIVERY OF THE
CONTENT.
AND I DONT HAVE ALL OF THE
ANSWERS.
I HAVE MANY OF THEM.
BUT SOMEONE BARKING DOWN MY
THROAT AND IN MY FACE AND ON MY
HEAD LIKE THIS ONE HAS DONE, GET
OUT OF TOWN.
Jeff: JOHN, SO, AS WE GET
READY TO VOTE WHAT, IS THE
CRITERIA?
ULTIMATELY, TONIGHTS VOTE IS
ABOUT KEEPING THE TRIBE STRONG.
AND THE WORD "STRONG" CAN MEAN A
LOT OF DIFFERENT THINGS.
AS FAR AS WERE CONCERNED, IT
MEANS HOW ARE WE GOING TO MOVE
FORWARD TO TAKE THE DAVIDS TO
SLAMDOWN AT THE NEXT CHALLENGE?
LAYO( LAUGHTER )
Jeff: IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
YOU TALK THAT BROTHER-SISTER
LOVE STUFF, AND YOU SHOWED ME NO
LOVE.
SO THAT STINGING SENSATION YOU
FEEL IN YOUR EYES RIGHT NOW,
THATS THE NATALIE NAPALM.
GET OFF OF MY ISLAND.
BY THE WAY, YOUR SKIN IS
GORGEOUS, DARLING.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL
IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, NATALIE.
JEREMY.
THREE VOTES JEREMY.
THATS FOUR VOTES JEREMY, ONE
VOTE NATALIE.
JEREMY.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR," JEREMY.
THATS SIX.
THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
JEREMY, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
Jeff: WELL, THE ONLY DOWN
SIDE TO A PERFECTLY EXECUTED
BLINDSIDE IS NOW EVERYBODY KNOWS
I COULD BE NEXT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
JUST WHEN YOUVE REACHING YOUR
BREAKING POINT--
RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE IM IN
A DESPERATE POSITION.
Jeff: ...THE GAME FLIPS
UPSIDE DOWN.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
SWITCHING TRIBES.
I HAVE TO GO ON A CHARM
OFFENSIVE, TRYING TO BRING
AROUND THE CHARM APOCALYPSE.
IM PROUD OF THE GAME I
PLAYED, YOU KNOW, AND IM PROUD
OF THE CONNECTIONS I MADE.
NATALIE, WHAT I DID FOR YOU WAS
TRY TO HELP YOU UNDERSTAND A
LITTLE BIT ABOUT HOW YOURE
BEING PERCEIVED.
AND IF YOU RECEIVED IT, GREAT.
YOU KNOW, I LEARNED MORE ABOUT
WHO I AM.
SO FOR ME ITS KIND OF A WIN.
BUT IF YOU GOTTA GO HOME, GO
HOME TO A COLD, RAINY NIGHT.