Previously on Survivor...
This is Survivor: David vs. Goliath.
Season 37 started
with a surprise.
The David tribe wins
the first reward!
In the Goliath tribe,
Dan fell in love with Kara...
What kind of girls do you like?
Blonde and pretty.
and found an idol.
Hey girls, girls!
I found an idol
with the prettiest girls here.
In the David tribe,
Nick found himself alone.
I can't stand someone who
doesn't do anything. Me too.
So we agree on that.
But mother nature intervened
and Pat had to be evacuated.
I love you Pat!
I love you!
It is a huge loss.
You have been three days,
with one less member
but this has just begun.
The battle is not over.
The game is still on.
19 left,
who will be expelled today?
I hope we can light the fire.
Do we have dry firewood?
How the hell do you expect
there to be that here?
And in which case, where would he be?
We have received a good blow.
Today was tough.
Pat was the one who always
boosted morale.
And having to say goodbye
to him yesterday
It was a very hard blow.
It's very wet.
Yes.
It starts to spark.
It's going to start raining.
Well, we'll try tomorrow.
It just doesn't stop, day after day.
I have never seen
anything like this in my life.
It's soaking wet, mate.
I'm sooooo tired of this.
Since we started
we have always been
wet, cold and bleak.
Because we wonder if
this is going to end sometime.
I'm wishing we can have fire.
Is it okay if I go
for a moment to pick bamboo?
But now?
Yes, if she calms down a bit.
Doesn't it bother you that it rains?
Christian, I can go with you.
I am not part of the
group that makes the decisions.
Neither do I.
We were three
hours before having the Council
and I had no idea,
no one came to talk to me.
Man, I knew it was me.
That's fatal.
I'm glad I didn't
go to the Council,
because the plan was to kick Nick out.
And I didn't want to lose him, in fact
I don't want him to go.
In fact, I personally like him
very much, we get along well.
And the fact that
we didn't have to vote
I mean we still have
ambiguity at the level of alliances.
Because once
the first vote occurs
things become clear,
and you see who each one is with.
The conclusion I
come to is that a girl has to go.
Of course, of course.
So, great
that we think the same.
Every new day that
I continue here is a blessing.
Because I was
only supposed to get to three.
So I'll go all out
or die trying.
From the first moment I have
had a connection with Christian.
We're like JT and Stephen
from Survivor Tocantins.
JT was the country boy
from Alabama and Stephen the genius.
I'm going to turn it over.
Put it down for a second.
One moment, I'm going
to turn it and we'll try.
Okay, go ahead.
Raise it up.
We both have
each other's backs so
It's time to make an alliance.
We need to put
a name to the alliance.
A name?
Yes.
Were you from Kentucky?
And you're from Baltimore.
Dude, we could be
the Mason-Dixon line.
The Mason-Dixon line passes
through Maryland and Kentucky.
So I thought it was a
good name: Mason-Dixon team.
The Mason-Dixon team.
Mason-Dixon team then.
That seems fine to me.
We better not crash it.
Let them not see us.
Mason-Dixon team.
We hit her but lip service.
It seems to me that this
alliance is going to last.
Listen guys!
We have a mail and a gift.
What is.
Let's see: "Tribe David,
It's been a rough
and unusually rough few days."
"Surviving the elements
is part of the adventure,
but this unforgiving weather
has prevented you
make the fire you have earned".
"This fire making kit should help you."
Great!
And as a gesture of goodwill
I offer you this canvas
as protection".
"Good luck
Jeff."
My goodness!
Yeah, yeah, bear with it... don't burn it
whole. Bear with it, bear with it a little.
It's going, it's going, it's going.
This is starting to go, guys.
Life is great now,
I have shelter, fire,
an idol in my jacket,
rice in my stomach.
I have Kara by my side
every night...
I am living a
dream life right now.
Where did you put my jacket?
In the tree over there.
I would feel better if the
idol was buried.
It's wrapped in a sock so...
Come on, don't play it.
Not worth it.
Kara is screwed that
someone is looking in my jacket.
I tell her: "Listen, girl
no one is going to expect my
idol to be in such an obvious place."
The only two people
who know that I have the idol
They are Natalia and Kara.
That two people know it
is clear that there are too many,
but one person
I totally trust is Tara.
Are we still keeping it a secret?
Oh we.
Clear.
I know, reminder.
I understand.
It's okay.
It is very difficult
be in an alliance with
Dan because it's too obvious.
I think Dan has a roll here.
But I think it's Kara's strategy.
And that will be your downfall.
Because romances,
whether real or not,
they do not work.
I still think that
Kara is playing with Dan.
He's been using his charms
ever since we got here.
I think he's blinded by
Kara's charms. Bad move, mate.
Bad play.
I'm going to tell you something, and
it's that you have to contain yourself
all that of the couple has to stop.
Yes.
I have to protect myself.
Because two people who
so obviously
They see that they are loyal
to each other, it never ends well.
Now I try to make them
see the girls
that I am here to
play, to be loyal to them and
And I really pray they see it.
I love to rage,
but I can't go on...
It is always attached to you.
Other than that, I was thinking
about this, girls.
We are the three of us.
You have Alec.
It's like my boy.
But what the hell!
My goodness!
I have John.
I'm with you, really.
Me too.
I'm being serious.
And you have Dan.
That's it!
My goodness!
We have... we have...
This is a lot of coincidence
although in your case it is something
obvious, but it still does not weigh you down.
Well, we'll worry about that.
With those numbers,
we can decide who goes first.
Some want Mike gone,
Dan told me he wanted him out.
And the rest want Natalie.
I don't want Mike to go.
Mike is not public enemy
number one or two for me.
Take this.
Don't let it fall.
And don't stick it in your foot.
I know I'm a bit bossy.
I have to improve that.
You think?
I think he's a good guy
in the sense that
you would like to work with us.
And the truth is that
he wants to kick Natalie out.
Natalie first, because that
way the tribe is more united.
Here we have three true Goliaths.
The three girls are
in charge and we know it.
And we have the boys
eating out of our hand.
And we also have Dan's idol
in reserve.
The fact that me and Kara
are the only ones to know
It means we have the power.
Watch over me!
I'm playing hard.
I will always get my hands on
other people's things
within the reasonable limit.
Mike was there,
making sure they didn't see me.
And looking through
Dan's things,
I saw inside the sock an idol.
And that was enough for me
and I left it there.
I wasn't surprised that he
found Dan's idol
so easily among his things.
Because he is playing with
his heart and with zero strategy.
Smart people don't leave it
in their stuff, they hide it.
He has the idol.
I don't think he's that smart,
nor will he know how to use it.
I had problems the first
day for going to look for the idol,
and the fact that Jeremy
trusts me so much
like to tell me with
hairs and details all its secrets
gives me new life.
I read the paper.
He was a true idol.
Do you think he told someone?
I think Kara.
Dan may think he is strong
and powerful because of the idol,
but actually
the information is the advantage.
And having that information is going
to have more power than the idol itself.
After having caught that octopus
people congratulated me a lot,
they thanked me and that was great.
So I decided
to go full throttle with that.
I think that's my
role here, to be the provider.
A lizard
Come on, you got her.
Did you take it?
Great, you're a machine.
I know I wanted to make a mark
here, and I'm on the right track.
This is Pat's shirt,
I'm going to use it to drop my baits.
My mother gave me this cross.
And I've been praying to God
that something good will happen to me,
something that can help me here.
I've been looking for food
nonstop more than anything else.
But I've always had my two eyes
in ninja mode, always searching.
This seems out of place.
What's that?
String.
But what...
Calm Calm.
It is well hooked.
There is no one near.
Please be an idol.
Come!
"Congratulations, you have found
the immunity idol."
Great, Dave!
That's it!
Just smell it, it smells like an idol.
I've never seen an
idol before but
It's real, man, it's a
real skin idol.
I love, I love this moment.
Thank my Lord.
I'm already starting to plot.
I'm ready to use
this thing when the time comes.
And there you go, good place to be.
And we're out of here.
Could you do me a favor
and help me take off my shirt?
I have it very attached.
Thanks.
That should be easier.
Before the last immunity challenge
they all
agreed to vote for Nick.
It was finished.
But then
Pat's accident happened.
And everything went to hell.
If you get rid of your
strongest players then
what options you have
to win challenges.
Well, basically we know
who we want out first.
Who are you thinking?
In Lyrsa.
Overall, I think
it is the weakest.
Is that I do not believe
that will
help us in the challenges.
You have to keep the tribe
strong for the challenges
because the others
are fucking beasts.
Well, I think we have
the majority to vote.
It is the weakest, so
if we end up going to the Council
My vote will go to her.
Lyrsa's name has come out because
Carl wants to keep the tribe strong.
And that doesn't seem right to me
because she is not
the weakest girl in the camp.
As long as we all agree.
No, if I agree.
That seems fine to me.
Really.
But when you hear
your friends name
you can't sit
still doing nothing, you have
to get you started.
Hey, listen...
you need to know about this.
He's saying your
name over there.
Carl said, "Lyrsa is the
weakest, we must stay strong."
And I said to him: "Yes, yes, yes".
I don't think I'm the weakest.
We have everything from the shelter
because I won it.
I don't think I'm the weakest.
I let you know what I hear.
Carl goes around saying
that they should kick me out
because I am the
weakest person in the tribe.
Wait... excuse me?
Am I the weakest?
Who the hell won the first challenge?
Me! So I don't think
I'm the weakest here.
I may not be as
athletic as other people,
but I don't think I
'm the weakest.
I hope we win tomorrow.
I also.
So I'm frustrated with Carl.
And I really want
to throw it in his face.
But here you can't
do that, or you screw up.
But I'm pretty pissed off.
I want to kick Carl out!
That was a mistake.
I have one!
Ahhh, bring him to
leave it there, let him leave it!
Jeremy is undressing.
Do I have any mucus in my nose?
None.
And in the teeth?
Clean.
Perfect.
And great hair.
Everyone is
having a good time all the time.
"Snot on the teeth?",
that's new.
They look like high school kids
so I pass on that.
We have to focus on the shelter.
I think we need to get
those leaves out of there.
Well, if the weather continues like
this I think they will be in luxury there.
The Goliath tribe
still has many things to do,
but it seems that they are very busy.
Strategically, my game
is based on going unnoticed,
get along with everyone
and I think I'm doing fine.
Unless they're
cheating on me, which I doubt.
Everybody hates Natalie.
You see.
I really feel sorry.
I don't think he even realizes it.
His attidude.
He has zero social skills.
Acting like this the only thing
you get is to stay alone.
Most of the tribe
would like to see Natalie go.
Specifically, I like
the idea of ​​working with her.
Because it would be the kind of
alliance that no one would suspect.
I want him to trust me
and help me go further.
I don't think you're as
close with Dan as you think.
Because I was talking to him before.
Do you want me to go?
Yes.
But do not say anything.
Good.
And there you have it.
Why would you throw out the older woman?
If they are newbies.
And if I go, I will not
leave here without doing anything.
Well, I want to know
why the older woman,
which has not even the
remotest chance of winning,
she is the first candidate
to be expelled.
Because it seems
that you have left me aside.
And what am
I supposed to do for you
when everyone tells me it's you?
How is the oldest person in
the tribe the biggest threat?
I'm almost 60, come on.
So I have to
know which side you stand on.
Because things are going to happen here.
Already.
Because I'm not the biggest threat.
I don't think there are numbers
enough to change the vote.
I like to say that I am blunt.
And some people will say that
's being aggressive, but I don't care.
I think they're arguing about something.
You guys are playing like you
're rookies and Davids.
I don't know if you should all
belong to the Goliaths.
We should treat each
other like fellow tribesmen
and not as adversaries.
I'm not going to wait for things to
happen, but I'm going to force them.
And if that makes people
uncomfortable, then too bad.
I'm not leaving here without a fight.
I'll be using some of
my weapons, so we'll see.
But before I go, I'm going to drop
some of my napalm, Natalie.
The clamp is going away.
To who.
She's crazy.
Yes.
She is making herself a target.
If we had some peace,
it would be great.
Yes.
What you're doing is
n't doing you any favors.
I'm the only one that's going
to try to give it a
real advice.
I am overwhelmed, and I know how
to deal with difficult people.
Look, here's the problem:
I'm not a psychologist.
And they don't pay me for this.
Failures in some social skills.
Because of your personality and
how you treat people.
Okay, let me stop you there.
I get along with everyone.
In this tribe?
Yes.
And why do you have that impression?
Because it is so.
The lack of social skills...
I already understood you.
That is all?
Listen, let me tell you this.
I'm black, so are you.
We have that approach,
and we always want
take care of each other
as much as possible, and
the lack of social skills...
you sometimes
you confuse idea and action.
That is not true.
Voucher.
He won't listen to anyone.
And she's been married for about 24 years.
That means
someone loves her just the way she is.
Which means that
it will continue as is.
I really don't
know which is worse.
Whether the storm or Natalie.
Seriously, if you had to decide!
If we lose the next challenge,
I'm going to go full milk
to kick Natalie out.
Go ahead guys!
Goliath, check out
the new David tribe.
Pat, the first one who
had to leave the game.
Can not be!
I didn't expect that.
Neither do I.
My mother Check it out.
Pat was not expelled.
In fact, there was no Council.
Pat was evacuated for
medical reasons
moments after the
last immunity challenge.
Well, while you digest that:
let's recap.
You have had to
endure an intense storm,
that you should know that it was a cyclone.
Well Jeff, you didn't have
to tell us.
Keep in mind, the weather
changes fast, and it may come back again,
And the game goes even faster.
It's time for our
next immunity challenge.
First things first, Goliath.
Give me back the idol.
We can lend it to you.
I see.
Very good, for today's challenge
one person from each tribe
going up a ladder
and recover a key that you will
use to free a raft.
You will row to the sea to
recover bags with puzzle pieces.
In the final part, you will keep your
balance on unstable boards
while trying to solve
a block puzzle.
The first tribe to finish
immunity wins, safe from voting.
Plus you're going to play for the reward.
Do you want to know what you play for?
Yes!
Make it a fishing team!
You hit the nail on the head, it's a
complete fishing outfit.
My goodness!
Mask, snorkel, fins
and for the first time,
a fishing rod.
Worth?
Of course!
Goliath, you have one member too many.
You have to seat
someone, who will it be?
Natalie, take a seat on the bench.
The old woman.
To the rest I give you a minute
for the strategies and we will begin.
All right, let's go there.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Now!
It will be Alec and Bi who
face each other in this first part.
You have two steps of the ladder.
You have to keep your balance
on one of the rungs while
you remove the step that you have
under you and put it in front.
You are going to make a very tall ladder.
Come on, Alec, come on!
Alec has a good
strategy to go up the steps.
Goliath, once again,
starts taking the lead
in an immunity challenge.
Perfect!
Alec is close to reaching the top.
Alec is here, he just has
to get up and take the key.
And he gets it.
Take a good jump!
Come on, Goliath!
You have to release the
raft and row.
Come on, Goliath!
I unhook it.
Bi still continues with the ladder.
The pressure increases.
The Goliaths are already in the water.
The Goliaths are still in the lead.
If that is!
Bi gets a rung stuck.
Hey, you're almost there!
Cheer up, Bi!
The Goliaths arrive on the platform.
Someone has to get close
to get the bags.
Alec, you go.
It's going to be Alec that goes.
Hey, go get the bags.
List!
The Goliaths have all
the bags and return to shore.
This is how a landslide victory begins.
The Goliaths are very close
to doubling the Davids.
Bi is on his last rung.
You got it, Bi!
You have to get that key!
He has it!
Well ahead!
Now they have to go to the water!
The Goliaths are back
with all their bags.
And it is now that the
Davids go looking for them.
The Goliaths have a huge advantage.
Now they are going to
try to solve the puzzle.
The David tribe gets on the raft.
You still have options!
Come on guys!
Medication.
The Davids finally reach the platform.
Bi gets on.
He has the first bag.
The raft moves away.
Hears!
The Davids are
walking away from the platform,
while Bi is still in it.
One more disaster for the David tribe.
Remad back!
The Goliaths have such an advantage
that you can take your
time looking at the pieces.
I have it!
David has his five bags.
Paddle hard!
The Davids finally make their way to shore.
Natalia places the first piece.
You gotta keep
one hand on the rope
and keep your balance
on the board while you do it.
The Davids just arrived.
You got enough rope,
Bi, hook it up!
Ready, go ahead!
The Goliaths have had
a huge advantage.
And yet they have only put
two pieces into the puzzle,
but they have spent a lot of
time seeing how they are going to do it.
Natalia loses it.
He has to come back for her.
And now look at this, Christian
places the first piece for the Davids.
Will the Goliaths spoil
this great advantage?
The Davids are back.
Angelina, take the rectangular
piece, that's the first one.
The one that makes base?
That's how it is.
Voucher.
Teamwork begins to shine.
People are beginning to
know how this is going. Nerd!
You had it right before!
I know, but I need
the other part.
Exact!
Take the other one and
put that one later!
It's what I'm trying to do!
The Davids now have
communication problems.
But that's not how it is.
Does anyone want to change?
I am too hot.
If someone sees that they can do it.
I can.
You can do it?
Yes.
Kara is going to replace Angelina.
This is one of the hottest days.
Add to that the adrenaline
and this can be exhausting.
Bi, I need...
Jessica drops it.
I think balance is
the hardest part of the puzzle.
Christian loses everything.
One setback after another.
The Goliaths
are slowly but surely gaining ground.
Alec, the next one is going to
be the one with the L shape.
Okay, now the four of us are going
to have to work at the same time.
The heat is relentless.
We've been here about an hour.
It's a long time to solve a puzzle.
Slow but sure
the Goliaths have
positioned themselves in the lead.
While the Davids have nothing.
Your only chance
is that the Goliaths make a mistake
and the puzzle falls out.
Force to put it?
You already have it!
The Goliaths have finished the puzzle.
The last part of this challenge:
is that the five must
return to the beginning
and cross the purple line.
For immunity
and a good
fishing equipment as a reward.
Be careful, tighten well
so as not to lose it.
Natalia, wait.
Okay Kara.
There are only two left.
Kara...
of...
has it.
Only Alec remains.
Slow slow.
And he succeeds! The Goliaths
win the immunity and the reward!
Good job, great effort.
It's okay, Gabbs.
Goliath, congratulations,
immunity is yours. Oh!
He came for her.
She earned it.
In addition, a
very complete fishing equipment.
This will be waiting
for you back at camp.
Goliath Tribe, without Tribal Council,
no one will go home.
Get your things and
come back, enjoy the night off.
David Tribe,
Tribal Council tonight.
Someone will be the second
person expelled.
Get your things and
come back, I'll see you at the Council.
At first glance, our
tribe all seem to get along.
But now suddenly we have
to see who is the
one that does not fit among all.
The question is how
crazy is that going to be.
It was pretty hot.
The sun was beating down hard.
It was brutal, even
by Survivor standards.
That challenge.
It seems that they are invincible.
They're hard.
And they are huge!
At times it also seems somewhat unfair.
Well, I don't agree with that.
In my sport,
technique beats anything.
So I don't think it's a size thing.
And I don't think we
have to have
that mentality every time
we go to a challenge,
thinking that they have
something that we lack.
There are solutions for
all problems,
and you know it by your
day to day life.
So don't let
two losses change your perspective.
This is shit.
Bi is absolutely correct.
But in reality, we need to
win challenges, so
for this first vote
I feel quite safe
in saying that Lyrsa should be kicked out.
Hello.
What's up.
So who are you going to vote for?
Lyrsa.
So who votes
for Lyrsa? To do the math.
I don't think anyone wants to
talk right now
because everyone agrees
to vote for her.
Yes.
From what I know so
far, the plan is to vote for Lyrsa.
But Bi and Jess may be screwing
me.
Because it seems that they
are giving me the typical answers.
What I want is
to talk about what is going to happen.
And that's what
doesn't make me feel safe.
Simple... and easy.
If people go to vote thinking
of making the tribe stronger,
that makes me feel restless.
Because I'm not much
better than Lyrsa at challenges.
I wanted tonight to be...
an easy vote.
But...
I don't feel safe at all
as if it did
days ago, and it scares me.
They're going to vote for me, right?
Yes.
Carl emphasized
that we need strength.
And I told him yes,
who was he thinking of.
I wonder why me.
I don't know, but that's what he said.
I'm so pissed off
that I'm thought to be
the weakest person
when it is not.
It's annoying, yes.
I do not want to go.
And I don't think I'm the weakest.
And you're not, okay?
I'm going crazy because I know
that my name has come out.
Fuck Carl,
he's going home, okay?
Or we can kick Jessica out.
Don't you think if we vote
for Jessica it makes more sense?
I'm not stupid, I know what's going on.
Jess is the one who gets
along with everyone.
She is very good friends with Bi
and also with Carl.
She is the one that keeps them together.
So we have to end that.
But I want to do what is best...
for the tribe.
I'm leaving, that's what you tell me.
No, you do not!
So who are you referring to?
Since I've been here
I haven't trusted...
From the first moment.
Here comes Lyrsa.
Do you want to be part of this?
Yes.
Go after Jessica, will you?
Kick Jessica out.
She is very close to Bi and Carl.
If we kick her out, those two
pillars will be lost.
You don't have to convince me,
if what I don't want is to leave.
How nice that you came.
We just changed
our minds, big time.
What happened?
If we throw Jessica out tonight...
the Carl and Jess duo is over.
Really?
And also Jess and Bi's.
So it would be a double win.
The hen cupped its wing.
And the word has spread.
The target is Jess.
And I'm surprised how quickly
things change.
But I'm motivated by
things going so fast,
because I have the impression
that a person as
hyper-frantic as me
It's perfect for dealing
with situations like this.
Christian, am I stupid?
Look, you have to trust
your instincts, I know that.
You want to play with me?
Play with you? Oh, in the sand?
No, in Survivor.
And what makes you think otherwise?
I also want to play
with you, that's why I ask you...
if you feel comfortable protecting me.
Of course.
More than Jess? Do you get along with her?
No, I don't connect with
her at all.
Do you have Nick on your side?
I think.
Gabby is basically asking me
vote the way she wants.
And I tell her that
I am with her until the end.
But I have to keep in mind
that from the perspective of challenges
Lyrsa is the most logical vote.
What's up, uncle?
Everything just exploded.
How?
They know I'm talking to you
about the plan to kick Jess out.
Don't fuck with me
I say we
kick Lyrsa out and stay strong.
At this point,
Nick and I are weighing
whether to kick out the person who wants
the most or make a big play.
In our first vote,
which is an
inherently dangerous proposition.
Let's choose one or the other
Mason-Dixon!
The Mason-Dixon alliance
are in the position of power.
And it is a very important decision.
It is our first Council,
and I can assure you that the vote
go the way I prefer it to go.
The position I
am in now, to make the final decision
It's exactly what I want to have.
Behind you there are
torches, take one.
Bring them to the fire and light them.
This is part of the tribal council ritual,
because the fire represents your life.
If the fire goes out,
you will be out.
Let's start, first Tip
but we are already on day 6.
So let's talk about the beginning.
Lyrsa, tell me about the early days.
You did not know anyone
present, and yet,
at the moment, you saw yourself
in the middle of a strong storm
and a host of
obstacles to overcome.
Being from the Caribbean I knew it
was going to rain when the time came.
But I didn't know that it
was going to happen so soon.
It has been brutal.
Jeff, you've been so relentless
that you reach a point where you give up.
And you just have to wait and pray
that mentally you hold on.
It's been really hard, Jeff.
Yes.
So Elisabeth, first
you have to survive the elements,
and in the middle of that,
this tribe of strangers
begins to become a family.
Yes, of course.
The crisis has made
people get along well together.
So it seems
people are still good
when you're surrounded by
such bad news.
To the point where
you say that everything will be fine.
So you are forced
to work together,
and a family begins to form.
And then comes the best
of Survivor: you have to fire someone.
Lyrsa, how fast
when we get to that
Does the game speed up?
You could cut the
tension with a knife.
And you might think I
don't see what's going on.
But I know what is happening.
I studied anthropology,
I know how to study people.
So I know I'm
on the tightrope 'cause
I've heard my
name out there already.
Apparently, I'm the
weakest, and I don't know why.
So I don't say anything.
In this game, we don't wait
for the Council to start playing.
And if you're playing
that way, rethink it.
Because this is a game
for a million dollars.
And you better be
active, because if you don't
your name is going to come out
and you are going to be very disappointed.
Gabby, that was well said.
It is what the game is,
and it starts from day 1.
Yes, I understand what
Jessica just said.
But I also think
everyone in this tribe is smart.
There is a reason we are here.
So I think
everyone has been active.
Bi, what do you think?
This is the first vote
Don't you stop reevaluating the
criteria when voting?
For me it is an easy vote
, I base it on performance
in the camp and
in the challenges.
Things will get more complicated
as we go along.
But for me,
right now, it's pretty simple.
Christian, Bi just
said in front of everyone:
"I know what I'm doing", which
is a very bold statement
to say in front of everyone,
which means that he is playing.
And yet it works
in this interesting game
where everyone can have
different individual reasons.
And yet, rarely,
there are nine different targets.
So in one way or another we
have organized ourselves to vote together.
All of you affirm with your
head that the vote is organized.
Nick, it's impossible.
Someone doesn't know what's going on
at least one person.
The way I see it,
this game is based on lies.
That makes trust
a rare thing to see,
and if you have it is a miracle.
But you also have to
weigh what is best for the tribe.
Because since you come back
here a lot,
it is more likely that
oneself will be the one to leave.
Yes, clearly that comes into play.
For example, everyone
can trust Mother Teresa,
but I don't think I would have
been able to do the challenge today.
So it's not just trust,
we're up against the Goliaths.
His women are towers, literally.
Christian, and what do you think of this?
How do you balance what
is good for you
and what is good for the tribe?
Well, if we were
to merge tomorrow, then
the strategy would have little to
do with what is best for the tribe.
But since we've only just begun,
is the first advice,
we are sure that there could
be a change of tribes soon.
So we have to weigh
quite a bit what the tribe needs.
So what is the level
of nerves from 0 to 10?
Jessica, and that based on what?
I think partly because
just being here is scary.
And also because
it is exciting at the same time.
There is no thrill without
risk, that's how I see it.
Cast?
Many times
that impression that something is
transcendental occurs at the moment
and I mean something
scarier than a Council.
It would be more like a roller coaster.
If in the depths of your being
Did you know the roller coaster is safe,
would you get that excited?
Or is it because at that moment you
are convinced that you are going to fall
and that you are going to die what
makes it very exciting?
Incredible.
Very good.
Sounds like it's the
perfect time to go vote.
Carl, you start.
You have to keep the tribe strong.
We have to win a challenge.
I really wanted to
work with you.
But I couldn't find a
way to do it.
I hope this works out.
Thanks.
I'll go for the votes.
If someone has the idol and
wants to play it,
now would be the time to do it.
Well, once read the
decision is final.
The expelled person will leave
the Council immediately.
I will read the votes.
First vote...
Lyrsa.
Jessica.
A tie.
Of the votes Lyrsa.
Of the votes Jessica.
Lyrsa.
Three vows Lyrsa,
of votes Jessica.
Lyrsa.
Four vows Lyrsa,
of votes Jessica.
Jessica.
Four votes Lyrsa.
Three votes Jessica.
Jessica.
A tie.
Four vows Lyrsa,
four votes Jessica.
One vote left.
Second person kicked out
of David vs Goliath:
Jessica.
Oh!
Oysters!
What has happened?
Jessica, the tribe has spoken.
It's time for you to go.
Good bye guys.
Each of you are here
because you have overcome
obstacles in your lives.
The question is: can you
do it as a tribe?
Take your torches, and come back.
That you rest
Below are scenes
from the next episode...
On the next episode of Survivor...
When you feel all alone...
I didn't know this was going to be so hard.
you need to find a soulmate...
The nerds together.
or you'll go crazy.
"Don't lose the harpoon!"
I know Dan has the idol.
We already know what he did.
Are you going around calling my name?
It's i-di-o-tas.
Being the first expelled is sad,
but at the same time it is
a compliment for me.
Since they saw me
as a great threat.
I came to play hard
from the start
And I guess I trusted
people I shouldn't have.
So that turned against me.
I guess it was the first
surprise ejection of the season.