Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR": EVERYBODY DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
OH, MY GOD.
I FREAKING KNEW TJEFF!
YEAH!
Jeff: THE GOLIATHS HAD THE
ADVANTAGE OF THREE NEW TRIBES.
THE DAVIDS ARE COLLECTIVELY
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
Jeff: WHILE CARL WAS THE
ODD MAN OUT.
YOURE GOING TO EXILE ISLAND.
WOW.
Jeff: AT EXILE ISLAND, CARL
FOUND AN ADVANTAGE.
THE VUKU TRIBE WAS FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THE GOLIATHS WERE IN CHARGE.
BUT ALEC CONSIDERED BETRAYING
ONE OF HIS OWN.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, ALEC MADE A
BIG MOVE.
I DONT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
Jeff: ...WHEN HE VOTED OUT
NATALIA.
NATALIA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND CARL JOWND THE VUKU TRIBE.
15 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
CARL IM KARA.
NICE TO PETE YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW WAS EXILE.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
REALLY?
YEAH, IT WAS HORRIBLE.
LEAVING THE TRIBAL COUNCIL, I
FEEL NAKED.
I FEEL EXPOSED.
I FEEL LIKE THIS WAS NOT
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
ALEC BLINDSIDED ME.
HE BACKSTABBED NATALIA, AND HE
FULL ON BLEW IT.
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE A BIG MOVE,
LIKE, DONT DO IT NOW.
LIKE I SAID, JUST DO IT, JUST
DO IT.
YEAH, WHICH IS AWESOME.
SO I DID IT.
YOU HAVE AWESOME TRUST WITH
THEM.
IM WORRIED ABOUT WHERE DOES IT
LEAVE ME?
RIGHT, YOU AND I ARE STILL
TOGETHER?
DO YOU PROMISE.
100%.
WHATS DONE IS DONE, AND I TRUST
MY GUT.
OKAY, LETS MOVE FORWARD,
KEEP WINNING--
YOU GOT IT.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW AM I
GOING TO GET IN THE GOOD GRACE
OF DAVIDS, BECAUSE ALEC IS THE
KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMORED THAT
SAVED ALL THREE OF THEM AND I
WAS THE ONE WHO WAS BLINDSIDED
UPON SO I HAVE SOME SCRAMBLING
TO DO.
( THUNDER )
♪ ♪
THE LIGHT SHINING ON THE
OCEAN THERE.
OH, YEAH.
THATS AWESOME!
EVER SINCE THE SWAP, IVE
BEEN SUPER WORRIED ABOUT MY
PLACE IN THE TRIBE, BUT FEELING
THE SUN RIGHT NOW HONESTLY FEELS
LIKE A GREAT SIGN FOR THE
FUTURE.
ITS A BREATH OF FRESH AIR.
BUT IM SCARED IT COULD BE TAKEN
AWAY FROM ME AT ANY MOMENT.
AND HERE COME THE CLOUDS.
OH, NO!
GO AWAY!
SERIOUSLY, WHAT THE HELL.
WIND AND RAIN, WIND AND RAIN.
ITS GOING TO BLOW RIGHT
OVER.
YEAH, THATS WHAT IM HOPING,
ITS JUST ONE BIG GRAY CLOUD.
( HURND )
I LOVE THE WEATHER!
IM JUST HAPPY TO BE HERE, AND
IM TALKING ABOUT LIVING.
SO WHEN YOURE LIVING, YOU HAVE
ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY TO
EXPERIENCE IT HOWEVER IT COMES.
THIS IS A BEAUTIFUL THING.
I THINK WE NEED TO GO.
ITS REALLY GOING.
GUYS, GET ONE OF THOSE TARPZ.
WE HAVE TO COVER THE FIRE.
AH!
THE ELEMENTS HAVE BEEN CRAZY.
LIKE, WE CANT EVEN MAKE A FIRE.
ALL THE WOOD IS WET.
WE CANT EAT RICE.
WE CANT DO NOTHING.
I MEAN, THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
WERE NOT PLAYING "SURVIVOR"
THIS SEASON.
( THUNDER )
AN HOUR AGO, WE WERE ENJOYING
THE SUN, AND THEN CLOUDS BLEW
OVER.
IT GOT REAL WINDY.
WE STARTED GETTING PELTED WITH
SAND AND RAIN.
EVERYTHING IS SOAKING WET, AND
EVERYONE IS FREEZING.
AND NOW THERE IS A RIVER OF
WATER THAT IS GOING THROUGH THE
BOTTOM OF OUR SHELTER.
ITS COMPLETELY FLOODED.
FROM THE BEGINNING OF THE GAME,
WEVE SAT THROUGH RAIN AND CRAZY
WEATHER.
BUT THIS IS UNDENIABLY CRAZIER
THAN ANYTHING WEVE SEEN.
THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS
SITUATION.
RIGHT!
TREE MAIL!
"GOOD MORNING, VUKU.
THE WEATHER CONTINUES TO IMPACT
THE THE GAME.
A MASSIVE STORM IS SET TO HIT
THE ISLANDS IN THE NEXT SEVERAL
HOURS.
FOR YOUR SAFETY, WERE GOING TO
EVACUATE YOU FROM YOUR ISLAND.
YOU WILL RETURN TO THE GAME AS
SOON AS WEATHER PERMITS.
JEFF."
HOLY CRAP!
TREE MAIL SAYS THAT THERES A
STRONG CYCLONE COMING OUR WAY,
AND THEYRE GOING TO HAVE TO
EVACUATE US FROM THE ISLAND.
ITS ABOUT TO DESTROY OUR CAMP!
THIS IS CRAZY, MAN!
IM READY TO GO.
GET MY BLACK ASS OUT OF HERE!
THIS IS CERTAINLY THE
CRAZIEST SEASON THAT I CAN
REMEMBER IN TERMS OF EVERY
SINGLE ELEMENT OF THIS GAME SO
FAR HAS BEEN FRAUGHT WITH SOME
KIND OF CRAZY CATASTROPHE.
BUT THIS IS REALLY SERIOUS.
CLEARLY, JEFF IS SO SCARED, IN
THIS CASE, HE WANTS US OUT OF
THE AREA ENTIRELY.
WERE ALL DAVIDS TODAY.
THATS THE GOLIATH.
♪ ♪
OH, MY GOSH!
WOW, GUYS.
HOLY CRAP.
MAN!
YEAH.
WE GET BACK FROM BEING
EVACUATED, AND OUR SHELTER IS
OBLITERATED.
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT STANDING.
AND HAD ANY OF US BEEN INSIDE OF
THAT, I MEAN, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
GAME OVER, FOR SURE.
WE COME BACK TO CAMP, AND I
THINK EVERYONES MOOD
IMMEDIATELY WAS LIKE OH, GOD.
NOW THIS.
IT LOOKED LIKE A BOMB WENT OFF.
IT WAS JUST LEAVES EVERYWHERE,
TREES HAD FALLEN OVER.
ITS PRETTY INTENSE.
WELL SPLIT A COUPLE OF
BAMBOOS, FIX THE FLOOR.
IT MIGHT BE WORTH ADDING ONE
MORE BEAM HERE, BECAUSE THEN WE
CAN LAY THESE A LITTLE BIT
BETTER ACROSS.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE LIVED A
LIFETIME OUT HERE ON THE ISLAND
OF FIJI.
TWO CYCLONES, A MEDICAL
EVACUATION, A PERSON QUITTING.
I MEAN, IT JUST SPEAKS TO THE
CRAZY NATURE OF THIS GAME.
IT IS MOVING AT A LIGHTNING FAST
SPEED, AND ITS UP TO US TO KEEP
UP.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
TIVA AND JABENI, GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE NEW VUKU
TRIBE.
NATALIA VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
OOOH.
WOW.
Jeff: CARL HAS JOINED THE
TRIBE.
WOW.
Jeff: BEEN A BUSY COUPLE OF
DAYS.
TURBULENT WEATHER AND BASED ON
YOUR REACTIONS, TURBULENT GAME
PLAY.
BUT YOU ARE ALL SAFE AND SOUND,
AND THE GAME IS BACK ON.
SHALL WE GET TO YOUR REWARD
CHALLENGE
( APPLAUSE ).
YES!
GET IT!
Jeff: FOR TODAYS
CHALLENGE, YOURE GOING TO USE
POLES TO KNOCK SANDBAGS OUT OF
AN OVERHEAD NET.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL YOUR SANDBAGS,
YOULL USE A GIANT SLINGSHOT TO
HIT TWO TARGETS.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
REWARD.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOURE PLAYING FOR.
YES.
OH, YEAH, BABY.
Jeff: AFTER 14 VERY TOUGH
"SURVIVOR" DAYS, TIME FOR
SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE
SUBSTANTIAL.
YES, JEFF.
CHICKENS!
( APPLAUSE ).
EGGS!
EVERYONE LOVES EGGS.
Jeff: FOUR EGG-LAYING HENS,
ONE ROOSTER FOR THE FIRST TRIBE
TO FINISH.
FOR THE SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH,
A DOZEN EGGS COURTESY OF THE
EGG-LAYING HENS.
( APPLAUSE )
LAST TRIBE TO FINISH, NOTHING
BUT A RETURN BACK TO CAMP WHERE
YOU WILL PROBABLY BE REBUILDING
YOUR SHELTER.
A LOT AT STAKE.
"SURVIVOR" IS BOOK ON.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS DAN AND JOHN.
IT IS MIKE AND NICK.
AND IT IS ALAND HE CAN DAVIE.
GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: TRYING TO POP THESE
SANDBAGS OUT OF THIS NET.
DAN AND JOHN DOING A NICE JOB.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT RIGHT
THERE.
ONE POP AT A TIME KNOCKING THE
SANDBAGS OUT.
DOING A GREAT JOB!
Jeff: NICK AND MIKE GETTING
A LITTLE MOMENTUM.
ANOTHER NICE HIT BY MIKE.
NICK KNOCKS ANOTHER ONE OUT.
ALEC DOING A GREAT JOB FOR VUKU.
DAVIE-- IM NOT SURE WHAT DAVIE
IS DOING.
JOHN HAS THE LAST ONE FOR TIVA!
TIVA CAN START PUTTING THEM IN
THE BASKET NOW.
TIVA IN THE EARLY LEAD.
GOTTA GET ALL YOUR BAGS IN THE
BASKET.
GO, DAN, GO, DAN!
Jeff: DAN NOW UNTYING KNOTS
TRYING TO RELEASE HIS SLINGSHOT.
NICK TRYING TO GET OUT THE LAST
ONE FOR JABENI.
HES GOT IT!
LETS GO, JABENI.
GOT TO GET ALL YOUR BAGS IN THE
BASKET.
VUKU HAS THEIR LAST BAG!
VUKU CAN START COLLECTING BAGS.
IT IS GOING TO BE LYRSA UNTYING
THE KNOT FOR JABENI.
IT IS NOW CARL UNTYING KNOTS FOR
VUKU.
DAN HAS HIS SLINGSHOT UNTIED.
LYRSA HAS MADE UP A LOT OF
GROUND.
SHES GOT THE SLINGSHOT FREE.
HERE COMES ANGELINA.
DAN WITH THE FIRST SHOT.
JUST MISSES.
ANGELINA NOW FOR JABENI.
SHE JUST MISSES.
KEEP GOING!
YOURE RIGHT ON IT!
Jeff: CARL HAS THE
SLINGSHOT FREE FOR VUKU.
ALEC COMES IN.
HE CAN START FIRING.
LOARKS LOWER!
Jeff: ALEC WITH ONE SHOT
SCORES THE FIRST FOR VUKU.
VUKU HAS ONE TARGET LEFT.
TIVA HAD THE EARLY LEAD.
BUT DAN CANNOT CONNECT.
ELISABETH FOR THE WIN RIGHT
HERE.
NO.
EVERYBODY STARTING TO GET ZONED
IN NOW.
ANGELINA, SHES GOT IT!
VUKU AND JABENI BOTH HAVE ONE
TARGET LEFT.
FOR THE WIN.
NICK, NO.
THAT WAS RIGHT THERE!
Jeff: ELISABETH FOR THE WIN
RIGHT HERE.
AND SHES GOT IT!
( CHEERS )
VUKU WINS REWARD!
Jeff: LOOKING FOR ONE MORE!
YOU GOT IT, DAN!
Jeff: IT HAS BEEN DAN, THE
ONLY PERSON TO FIRE FOR TIVA,
AND HE FINALLY GETS IT.
WERE TIED 1-1.
JOHN COMES IN.
ITS A SHOWDOWN RIGHT NOW
BETWEEN DAVID AND GOLIATH.
JOHN FOR THE WIN FOR TIVA.
OH!
Jeff: JUST MISSES.
YOU HIT RIM!
YOU HIT RIM.
THIS IS IT!
I FEEL IT!
Jeff: NICK FOR THE WIN.
AND HES GOT IT!
JABENI WINS REWARD, A DOZEN
EGGS.
LEAVING TIVA EMPTY-HANDED
HEADING BACK TO CAMP WITH
NOTHING.
SUNNY SIDE UP!
Jeff: VUKU, NICE JOB.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
YOUR CHICKENS WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU WHEN YOU GET THERE.
( APPLAUSE )
JABENI, CONGRATULATIONS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
YOUR EGGS WILL BE WAITING FOR
YOU WHEN YOU GET THERE.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: TEEF AGRAB YOUR
STUFF, HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
SOME OF THE TIVA TRIBE HAS
BEEN VERY CONFIDENT ABOUT OUR
ABILITY TO WIN, BUT IF WE HAD
BEEN THAT OVERCONFIDENT BEFORE
AN IMMUNITY CHALLENGE AND LOT
OF, MY BUTT COULD BE ON THE
LINE.
♪ ♪
WERE PUMPED.
VUKU TRIBE HAS WON THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE, AND WE WON SOME
FREAKING CHICKENS.
IM SO EXCITED.
ELISABETH IS FROM KENTUCKY.
WERE GOING TO HAVE KENTUCKY
CHICKEN TONIGHT.
EVERYBODY NEEDS A LITTLE K.B.C.
LAST NIGHT, ALECS DECISION
WAS AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
ITS NOW THREE DAVIDS AND TWO
GOLIATHS.
SO AT THIS POINT, I DONT HAVE A
CHOICE BUT TO THROW ALEC UNDER
THE BUS.
BECAUSE THOSE OTHER GUYS ARE
STRONG.
WILL YOU TAKE ME?
I NEED YOU GUYS AS MUCH AS YOU
NEED ME.
WERE GOOD.
COOL.
IM LOVING THIS.
I JUST PLAN ON TURNING ON MY
SOCIAL CHARM AS MUCH AS
POSSIBLE, AND OUT-CHARMING ALEC.
I HAD TRUST IN ALEC, BUT HOW AM
I SUPPOSED TO TRUST HIM MOVING
FORWARD?
EXACTLY, ESPECIALLY WHEN HE
DIDNT KEEP YOU IN THE LOOP WITH
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
I TRUST YOU GUYS WAY MORE
THAN I TRUST ALEC.
I WANT TO TRUST KARA, BUT I
STILL SENSE THAT SHE WOULD
RATHER WORK WITH THE GOLIATHS
THAN WITH THE DAVIDS.
I DO NOT GET THAT SENSE WHEN IM
TALKING WITH ALEC.
I MEAN, HES, LIKE, IN A
DECENT PLACE I THINK WITH ALL
THE GOLIATHS.
UNTIL THIS HAS HAPPENED.
RIGHT, YEAH.
NOW HE HAS TO GO DO MAJOR DAMAGE
CONTROL.
GOING FORWARD, ALEC IS GOING
TO NEED ME WAY MORE THAN KARA,
AND WE NEED TO BE WEIGHING
LOYALTY.
WE NEED TO BE WEIGHING NUMBERS.
WE HAVE THE POWER TO FOR SURE
GET RID OF A GOLIATH.
SO ITS OBVIOUS TO ME SHES THE
ONE WHO NEEDS TO BE HOME.
ME, TOO.
CONGRATULATIONS ON WUR WIN.
YEAH.
OUR WIN.
GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY.
OH, MY GOSH!
I COULDNT HAVE DREAMT OF A
BETTER REWARD PRIZE.
AS A VEGETARIAN, EGGS ARE ONE OF
MY MAIN SOURCES OF PROTEIN.
I EAT THEM ALMOST EVERY DAY BACK
HOME, AND I HAVENT HAD A LICK
OF PROTEIN IN TWO WEEKS.
AND SO WINNING THE EGGS WAS JUST
MY DREAM COME TRUE.
I THINK WE SHOULD BOIL THEM
ALL TODAY.
OH, GOD.
WEVE GOT TO EAT ALL THE EGGS
TODAY?
NO, IF WE KEEP THEM IN
SOMETHING THAT IS NOT THAT
EXPOSED TO THE SUN--
IN THIS KIND OF WEATHER,
TOMORROW MORNING THEYRE SHOT.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK?
MAYBE A DAY OR TWO.
LIKE I SAID, BY THIS TIME
TOMORROW.
THEYRE NOT GOING TO GO BAD.
ITS ONLY TWO EGGS EACH.
ITS NOT A BIG DEAL, RIGHT?
OH MY GOD!
ITS LIKE I REALLY DONT GET
THIS WOMAN.
I JUST DONT GET IT, HOW SOMEONE
CAN BE SO EGOTISTICAL IN A
SITUATION LIKE THIS.
SHEEMENTED TO COOK ALL THE EGGS.
AND THAT WOULD BE GREAT IF YOU
HAVE SOMEWHERE TO STORAGE THE
EGGS.
I WENT TO CULINARY SCHOOL, AND I
GRADUATED MAGNA CUM LAUDE.
SO I KNOW WHAT IM TALKING
ABOUT.
TIME TO GET SOME WOOD.
SHES HAS, LIKE, A MASTERS IN
UNGRACIOUSNESS.
ALL RIGHT, ILL BE BACK.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE IT TO THE
MERGE.
( LAUGHS )
THATS ALL.
I JUST DONT WANT TO PLAY WITH
HER.
IM SO SORRY, MIKE.
I DONT WANT TO PLAY WITH
HER, EITHER, ARE YOU KIDDING?
IVE HAD NINE MORE DAYS OF THIS
THAN YOU.
NATALIES HIJINKS GET OLD.
SHE PUTS A TARGET ON HER BACK.
WHENEVER THE TRIBE IS TRYING TO
MAKE AN IMPORTANT DECISION,
NATALIES VOICE IS THE LOUDEST
AND THE MOST INTRACTABLE.
AND IT JUST STARTS TO WEAR ON
YOUR NERVES.
AFTER 15 DAYS OF IT, I START TO
LOSE MY PATIENCE, AND IM READY
TO HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
"SURVIVOR" WITHOUT NATALIE.
♪ ♪
A KA-GENIUS?
ITS A STEP ABOVE A GENIUS.
THANK YOU, THATS A HIGH
COMPLIMENT.
YOU THINK SO, TOO?
FOR SURE.
HES THE PRESIDENT OF THE
BROCHACHOS.
I KIND OF CAME UP WITH THE WORD.
CAN I BE THE C.E.O.?
I CAN BE, LIKE, HEAD OF
AWESOME STUFF, H.A.S.
THE H.A.S. OF THE
BROCHAWCHOS.
CHRISTIAN WANTS TO BE PART OF
THE GUYS AND FEEL ACCEPTED AND
HE IS ACCEPTED.
HES ONE OF THE BROS.
HES ONE OF THE GROUP WE HAVE.
GABBY IS NOT PART OF IT, SO IT
MAKES GABBY MORE AN OUTSIDER, SO
FROM MY UNDERSTANDING, SHE WILL
BE THE FIRST TO GO FROM OUR
TRIBE BUT I WANT TO MAKE SURE
SHE DOESNT HAVE AN IDOL.
I STILL HAVE MY IMMUNITY, IDOL
BUT TRADITIONALLY ANY TIME YOU
GO TO A NEW ISLAND THERES A NEW
IDOL.
I HAVE AN ADVANTAGE NOBODY ELSE
HAS-- I KNOW WHAT TO LOOK FOR.
FOR ME, IM LOOKING FOR ANYTHING
THATS GREEN, LIKE OUR TIVA
GREEN.
BECAUSE THE FIRST IDOL I FOUND
IT WAS WRAPPED IN A PURPLE
STRING.
I HAVE BEEN SCOURING THIS
ISLAND, AND I CANNOT FIND THAT
SUCKER FOR THE LIFE OF ME.
AND NOT HAVING ONE HERE IS HARD
FOR ME TO BELIEVE, SO IM GOING
TO KEEP SEARCHING.
SO IM WALKING DOWN THE TRAIL,
AND THERE WAS JUST THIS OPEN
AREA TO THE LEFT.
IM-- THAT JUST-- THATS THE
ONLY BIG OPEN AREA.
SO IM LOOKING AROUND THERE, AND
I LOOK DOWN, AND I SEE AT THE
BASE OF A TREE A PIECE OF WOOD
WRAPPED IN GREEN.
I FOUND IT!
IM LIKE, WOW!
AGAIN?
REALLY?
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
NO IDOL BUT WE GOT US A CLUE.
THIS GIVES ME ANOTHER CANC TO
GET AN IDOL THAT NOBODY KNOWS
ABOUT.
THAT COULD BE THE GAME CHANGER,
TWO IDOLS.
I KNEW I COULD PLAY THIS GAME
WELL.
I WAS CONFIDENT THAT I COULD
PLAY IT WELL, BUT I DIDNT KNOW
THAT I COULD PLAY IT AS WELL AS
I AM.
I DIDNT FEEL LIKE A GOLIATH.
IM STARTING TO.
320-POUND DAN WILL BE REALLY
PROUD OF ME RIGHT NOW AND WHAT
IVE DONE, YOU KNOW.
NOT ONLY AT HOME IN MY LIFE BUT
IN THIS GAME.
BUT IT IS BEYOND IMPORTANT FOR
ME TO NOT BE CAUGHT LOOKING FOR
THIS IDOL IN THAT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
SO IM GOING TO HAVE TO BE REAL
SNEAKY TO BE ABLE TO GET IT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, LETS GET TO TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, TAKE BACK
THE IDOLS.
I DONT WANT TO GIVE IT BACK.
Jeff: THANK YOU!
THANK YOU!
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO RACE UP AND OVER AN
OBSTACLE.
YOULL THEN LIFT THE LADDER,
CLIMB UP, AND USE A ROPE TO
RAISE A BRIDGE.
CROSS THE BRIDGE, MAKE YOUR WAY
TO THE FINISH, WHERE YOU WILL
RETRIEVE A BALL.
FINALLY, YOULL MANEUVER THAT
BALL TO THE TOP A SNAKE MAZE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
DAY 15.
LETS DO IT.
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
YES.
Jeff: GO!
GOTTA GET UP AND OVER THIS FIRST
OBSTACLE.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: VUKU QUICKLY DOING A
GOOD JOB.
COME ON, CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: WHO IS GOING TO BE
LAST TO GET THERE?
NATALIE TAKES A FALL.
VUKU IN THE LEAD.
GO GREEN, GO, PURPLE!
NOW, WHO YOU GOING TO SEND UP?
CARL GOES FOR VUKU.
FIND THAT LADDER.
RETRIEVE THAT ROPE.
GABBY FOR TIVA.
CARL HAS THE ROPE.
GABBY HAS THE ROPE.
HERE GOES LYRSA.
ONE, TWO, THREE, PULL!
Jeff: NOW YOU GOTTA PULL
THE ROPE TO LIFT THE BRIDGE.
HOLD IT!
Jeff: HEAD ACROSS.
WATCH YOUR BRIDGE!
OKAY!
Jeff: GO!
GO!
THERETO GO!
LET IT GO!
JABENI IN DEAD LAST, STILL
TRYING TO LOWER THE BRIDGE.
GO, PURPLE!
GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: GREEN NOW IN THE
LEAD.
ORANGE RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
NOW EVERYBODYS GOT TO BE AT THE
MAT.
BRINGING UP THE REAR IT IS
PURPLE, FALLING WAY BEHIND.
NATALIE WITH ANOTHER HARD FALL.
HERE COMES GABBY.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
Jeff: VUKU NOW UNTYING
TRYING TO RELEASE THEIR BALL.
ORANGE, YOURE GOOD, UNTIE!
ALEC ON HER TAIL.
YOU GOT THIS, ALEC.
JUST TAKE YOUR TIME.
Jeff: BRINGING UP THE REAR
ITS NICK, MIKE, AND LYRSA.
GABBY HAS HER BAG.
IT IS JOHN FOR TIVA.
ALL RIGHT, JOHN!
YOU GOT IT!
Jeff: LYRSA NOW UNTYING,
TRYING TO RELEASE THEIR BALL.
JOHN WITH A BIT OF AN EDGE OVER
ALEC RIGHT NOW.
TAKE YOUR TIME, BROTHER.
Jeff: ALEC HAS THE BALL FOR
VUKU.
YOU GOT IT, NICK.
Jeff: AND NICK NOW HAS THE
BALL FOR JABENI.
EVERYBODY WORKING ON THE FINAL
PHASE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU HAVE TO MANEUVER THIS BALL
TO THE TOP.
YOU GOT TYOU GOT IT.
Jeff: IT LOOKS EASY.
ITS NOT.
TAKE YOUR TIME, ALEC.
YOURE GOOD, YOURE GOOD.
Jeff: TWO TRIBES WILL
FINISH, TWO TRIBES WILL BE SAFE.
GOOD MOVE.
NICE SAVE.
GREAT JOB, JOHN!
YOU GOT IT.
THERE YOU GO.
NICE, NICE.
Jeff: RIGHT NOW, ITS
JABENI TRYING TO CATCH UP WITH
VUKU AND TIVA IN THE LEAD.
ITS GETTING NARROW, BROTHER,
BE AWARE.
Jeff: BOTH TRYING TO
EXECUTE THE SAME MOVE.
LIKE YOURE ON A SURF BOARD.
OKAY, YOURE STILL GOOD.
Jeff: ALEC DROPS.
HE HAS TO START AGAIN.
THERE YOU GO.
Jeff: JOHN VERY MUCH IN
CONTROL OF THIS CHALLENGE RIGHT
NOW.
YOURE FINE, JOHN.
JOHN, DOWN, DOWN.
Jeff: AND JOHN DROPS RIGHT
BEHIND HIM.
NOW THE LEAD IS JABENI JUST LIKE
THAT.
THEY SWAP OUT.
ALL RIGHT, BROCHACHO, LETS
GO.
Jeff: IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
TAKE YOUR TIME, NICK.
Jeff: NICK HAS BEEN VERY
STEADY.
SLOWLY INCHING HIS WAY TO THE
TOP.
EASY.
Jeff: WHEREAS, ALEC, BEING
MUCH MORE AGGRESSIVE THIS TIME,
MAKING BIGGER MOVES.
YOURE DOING GREAT, MAN.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN NOW GOING
TO HAVE TO MOVE VERY FAST AND/OR
HOPE NICK DROPS.
THE CHALLENGE GETS TRICKIER.
THE HIGHER YOU MOVE ON THIS
MAZE, THE NARROWER IT GETS.
NICK SLOW AND STEADY, SO SLOW,
HES NOT EVEN MOVING.
NICE.
THERE YOU GO!
Jeff: ALEC NOW MAKE
SOMETHING MOVES.
YOURE GOOD.
NO NEED TO PANIC.
Jeff: ALEC GAINING ON NICK.
HES FIGURED SOMETHING OUT, HAS
A GOOD RHYTHM GOING.
THERE YOU GO BROCHAWCHO.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN WITH A NICE
MOVE, GAINING GROUND INCH BY
INCH.
ALEC, ANOTHER NICE MOVE.
ITS OKAY!
KEEP GOING, CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: WOW, CHRISTIAN IS
REALLY MAKING FAST WORK OF THIS.
NICE, CHRISTIAN.
GOOD MOVE, BROTHER MAN.
Jeff: NICK RIGHT BEHIND.
ALEC AND CHRISTIAN CLOSER AND
CLOSER.
THERE YOU GO!
Jeff: THEY HAVE CAUGHT AND
PASSED NICK.
OKAY, NICK.
Jeff: THIS IS "SURVIVOR" AT
ITS FINEST.
IT IS ALEC WITH A SMALL LEAD
OVER CHRISTIAN AND NICK RIGHT
BEHIND.
EVERYBODY IS IN IT RIGHT NOW.
ALEC FOR VUKU VERY CLOSE.
CAN THEY CLOSE THE DEAL?
CHRISTIAN VERY CLOSE.
NICK IS RIGHT THERE.
WHO IS GOING TO GET THERE FIRST?
TAKE YOUR TIME, ALEC.
YOUR PACE.
Jeff: ALEC DOES IT!
VUKU WINS IMMUNITY.
LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
BOTH GUYS CLOSER AND CLOSER.
AND HE DOES IT!
TIVA WINS IMMUNITY.
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU!
Jeff: SENDING JABENI TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
GREAT JOB.
BRO.
THANKS, GUYS, VERY MUCH FOR
YOUR SUPPORT.
Jeff: VINAKA,
CONGRATULATIONS, ANOTHER WIN.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM VUKU.
TIVA, CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
WELL DONE.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM TIVA.
VUKU, TIVA, GRAB YOUR STUFF,
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
JABENI, FIRST LOSS, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SIXTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
IM VOTING FOR NATALIE
BECAUSE I CANT STAND HER.
POSSIBLY, OUTSIDE OF THE GAME,
SHES AN ADORABLE LADY.
INSIDE OF THE GAME, SHES NOT.
BUT I FEEL A LITTLE BIT
UNCERTAIN BECAUSE IF THE
GOLIATHS DECIDE TO STAY STRONG,
IT WILL BE BETWEEN ME AND NICK.
♪ ♪
TODAY, WE LOST THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD BE ABLE TO
PULL THIS ONE OUT, AND WE WERE
VERY CLOSE.
BUT WE FELL SHORT.
IM SORRY, GUYS.
NO APOLOGIES.
YOU DID GREAT.
THANKS.
THAT WAS TRICKY.
IM SORRY.
SHOULD WE TRY TO GET SOME
FOOD?
YEAH.
NICK REALLY PLAYED A GREAT
GAME, BUT SOMEBODY HAS TO GO.
GOING INTO TRIBAL, WE STILL ARE
THREE GOLIATHS WITH TWO DAVIDS.
SO WERE DEBATING BETWEEN VOTING
FOR LYRSA AND NICK.
SO WHAT DO WE WANT TO DO?
KEEP HER OR KEEP HIM?
WE RAN THROUGH THE PROS AND
CONS OF VOTING OUT NICK OR
LYRSA.
WE DECIDED ON LYRSA, BECAUSE SHE
DOESNT BRING A LOT TO THE
TABLE.
THATS FUNNY.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS SILLY, BUT
THE ELEMENTS DO HAVE AN IMPACT
ON YOU.
I KNOW THATS SO, SO WRONG.
ITS SO COLD OUT HERE, AND IM
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE WHO RUNS
REALLY COLD.
AND HAVING A JACKET OUT HERE
REALLY COULD BE A HUGE BENEFIT
TO ME.
I WOULD PREFER IF SOMEONE ELSE
DID THE DIRTY WORK.
IS AND I THINK NATALIE IS
ACTUALLY A PERFECT PERSON TO
GIVE ME THAT JACKET.
YOU ALL KNOW WHAT IM WRITING
DOWN.
ARE WE GOING TO VOTE LYRSA
TONIGHT?
I WANT THAT JACKET, THAT
MEMBERS ONLY JACKET.
YOU GOTTA GET IT NOW, OR YOURE
OUT OF TIME.
IM NOT STEALING ANYBODYS
STUFF OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
WELL... HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
GIVING UP YOUR JACKET JA.
MY JACKET?
UH-HUH.
NO, IM TAKING MY JACKET WITH
ME.
THE JACKET IS WORTH A
MILLION.
ARE YOU TRYING TO BULLY ME OR
SOMETHING?
NO, I JUST ASKED A QUESTION.
THATS NOT BULLYING.
IT SEEMS LIKE IT.
I KNOW WERE PLAYING A GAME BUT
SOME THINGS ARE JUST CROSSING
THE LINE.
IF SOMEBODY IS IN A POSITION OF
POWER AND THEY USE THAT POWER TO
COERCE OR THREATEN SOMEBODY INTO
DOING SOMETHING THAT THEY DONT
WANT TO DO, THATS BULLYING, IN
MY OPINION, AND I DONT TOLERATE
BULLYING.
NATALIE SLIKE, TRYING TO
CONVINCE ME TO LEAVE MY JACKET.
NATALIE SAID, "IS THAT JACKET
WORTH $1 MILLION TO YOU?"
ARE YOU KIDDING.
SHE SAID THAT?
STEAL MINE!
ARE YOU (BLEEP) KIDDING ME.
I THINK NATALIE SHOULD GO,
BECAUSE THESE UNBEARABLE, BUT ON
THE JABENI TRIBE, THE CARDS ARE
DEFINITELY STACKED AGAINST ME.
I MEAN, THERE ARE THREE
GOLIATHS, THERE ARE TWO DAVIDS.
SO LYRSA AND I, WERE IN BRING
TROUBLE.
THERE IT IS.
MIKE TRUSTS ME.
HES MY FELLOW ROCK STAR, SO IM
HOPING WE JUST GET FOUR VOTES ON
NATALIE TODAY, ME AND MIKE COME
BACK TO CAMP TONIGHT AND HAVE AN
AIR JAM SESSION, AND WELL BE
SITTING PRETTY.
YOU GET THE FIRE GOING?
I DONT SELL ANY FIRE.
LOOK, I CANNOT DEAL WITH
THIS.
NICK AND I BOTH FEEL LIKE
NATALIES GOT TO GO, AND I WANT
TO FIGURE OUT HOW I CAN DO THAT
WITH THE GOLIATHS FEELING GOOD
ABOUT ME, SO IM JUST HOPING
THAT NICK CAN GET ANGELINA ON
BOARD.
IT WILL TAKE A LOT OF WORK, SO
HE NEEDS TO STEP UP AND COME
THROUGH ON OUR LITTLE ROCK STAR
ALLIANCE.
THE WAY I SEE IT IS WE CANT
JUST PLAY THIS GAME DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH.
I KNOW.
WERE GOG HAVE TO WORK WITH
GOLIATHS AND GOLIATHS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO WORK WITH DAVIDS.
ALL I WANT TO DO IS GO FAR WITH
PEOPLE I LIKE AND LIKE PLAYING
WITH.
WE WERE THINKING NATALIE.
ITS LONG OVERDUE.
LYRSA THINKS THAT IM VOTING
FOR NATALIE, AND NATALIE THINKS
THAT IM VOTING FOR LYRSA.
WHAT IS YOUR-- YOUR.
--
IM NERVOUS BECAUSE ITS A
BIG MOVE.
I AM AT THIS PIVOT POINT WHERE I
NEED TO LOOK AT WHO CAN I TRUST?
WHO DO I WANT AT THE MERGE?
WERE GOOD?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT?
CAN I GET THIS JACKET.
IM THE ONLY MEMBER WHO IS
GOING TO USE THIS JACKET
TONIGHTS VOTE IS SO
CRITICAL, GIVEN THAT NATALIA IS
OUT OF THE GAME NOW, BY TAKING
OUT NATALIE, WE ARE TAKING OUT
ANOTHER GOLIATH, WHICH PUTS US
EVEN MATCH, 7-7, WITH DAVID.
SO MY MINDS RACING.
THIS IS DEFINITELY A BIG
DECISION, AND THERES NO WIGGLE
ROOM.
THERES NO ROOM FOR ERROR.
♪ ♪
JEFF ALRIGHT LETS GET INTO IT
ANGELINA, 15 DAYS IN, YOU HAVE
THREE GOLIATHS AND TWO DAVIDS.
HOW BIG OF AN IMPACT DOES THAT
HAVE ON HOW THIS GAME IS GOING
TO PLAY OUT?
SO, TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
THAT IS THE BIGGEST FACTOR
BECAUSE WE LOOK AT THE NUMBERS,
NOT ONLY AT JABENI, BUT ACROSS
THE BOARD.
IT IS ABSOLUTELY CRITICAL THAT
WE CAN MAINTAIN THOSE NUMBERS.
AND SO, AT THIS POINT, WE DO
WANT TO STAY GOLIATH STRONG.
BUT THEY KEEP SAYING,
"GOLIATH STRONG.
NATALIA-- YOU GUYS DONT KNOW
WHATS GOING ON, ON THE OTHER
SIDE.
ACTUALLY, WE DID COMMIT TO
GOING GOLIATH STRONG.
THERE IS STILL A GOLIATH TRIBE.
THAT WAS THE PLAN WHEN WE
PARTED, AND IM GOING TO STAND
IN BELIEF TO WHAT IVE COMMITTED
TO SO--
BUT YOU WERENT THE FIRST
OPTION AT THAT FIRST TRIBAL.
IM ALWAYS IN TROUBLE HERE,
JEFF.
NO, ITS NOT THAT YOUR--
ALL OF THESE TRIBAL COUNCILS,
IM THE PERSON THAT SEEMS TO BE
STRUGGLING HERE.
Jeff: LETS TALK ABOUT
THAT.
IS THAT NEW FOR YOU?
IT CERTAINLY IS.
I AM NEVER THE CENTER OF DRAMA.
Jeff: IN YOUR PROFESSIONAL
LIFE BACK HOME, ARE YOU IN
CHARGE?
YES, BUT I AM MORE LAID BACK
THAN WHAT YOUD NORMALLY GET.
BEING ON THE TRIBE AND BEING
MORE COLLABORATIVE ITS OTHER
DAY THERE WAS A DISCUSSION ABOUT
THE EGGS.
IM SAYING LETS BOIL ALL THE
EGGS AND GET IT OVER WITH.
BUT WE DONT HAVE THE CORRECT
TEMPERATURE TO HOLD THE EGGS.
IN FOUR HOURS, THOSE EGGS ARE
GOING TO START CREATING
BACTERIA, AND I LEARNED THAT AT
SCHOOL.
I WENT TO SCHOOL FOR THIS.
WHAT IM SAYING IS IT DOESNT
TAKE FIVE PEOPLE TO DECIDE ON
BOILING EGGS.
ONE OR TWO PEOPLE, TELL US WHAT
TO DO, AND WELL DO IT.
I HAVE TO JUMP IN, FOR
NATALIE, HE REALLY PRIORITIZES
EFFICIENCY BUT SOMETIMES THE
FASTEST WAY TO GET THERE ISNT
TO GET EVERYONE ON THE TRAIN TO
GET TO THAT PLACE.
IT DOES FEEL NATALIE HAS
STRONG FEELINGS ABOUT A LOT OF
THINGS THAT HAPPEN AT CAMP.
REALLY?
YEAH, HOW THINGS ARE DONE,
HOW QUICKLY, THEYRE DONE, WHERE
THEY SHOULD GO.
YOU KNOW, THERES DISAPPROVAL
LOOMING IN THE AIR IF THINGS
ARENT DONE THE WAY YOU WANT
THEM TO BE DONE.
Jeff: SO, MIKE, SO FAR,
YOUVE HAD AN ISSUE WITH
NATALIE.
ANGELINA HAS HAD AN ISSUE WITH
NATALIE, AND YET IT SOUNDS
LIKE--
YOU HAVE AN ISSUE WITH ME?
WE HAVENT HAD AN ISSUE.
WE HAVE DIFFERENCES.
WE TALK IT THROUGH AND MOVE ON.
Jeff: MY BAD.
NO ISSUE WITH THE GLGHTZ.
EVERYBODY IS GETTING ALONG
REALLY WELL.
NICK, WHERE DO YOU FALL IN THIS?
TODAY, I TALK TO NATALIE.
SHE DONT CARE WHAT I HAVE TO
SAY.
ALL SHES WORRIED ABOUT IS
JACKETS.
HERES THE FACT, JEFF.
IM IN SALES.
AND I SAW IT AS A NEGOTIATING,
NOT A BULLYING.
IF YOU WANT TO STAY IN THE GAME
AND YOU HAVE SOMETHING VALUABLE
TO A MAIN PLAYER IN THE GAME,
WELL, I WAS LEVERAGING.
Jeff: YOURE SAYING, "IF
YOU GIVE ME YOUR JACKET, I MAY
THINK ABOUT VOTING FOR LYRSA?"
INDIRECTLY.
Jeff: INDIRECTLY.
WHAT ELSE WOULD IT BE?
IMPLYING THAT, YES?
I DIDNT SAY IT STRAIGHT OUT.
BUT THAT WAS THE NATURE OF THE
CONVERSATION, YES.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
ITS NOT UNBELIEVABLE.
IM IN SALES.
LIKE I SAID.
I SAID IT SHOULD BE BELIEVABLE.
IM IN SALES.
WERE NOT TALKING ABOUT A
PERSON.
WERE TALKING ABOUT A PERSON
WEARING A JACKET THEY NEEDED.
FOR ME, THATS VERY, VERY
MEAN, YOU KNOW.
ITS IMPERSONAL.
Jeff: MIKE--
ACTUALLY --
SORRY, I INTERRUPTED YOU
AGAIN YOU KEEP GOING.
ANGELINA, YOU WANT TO HELP ME
OUT WITH THE JACKET SITUATION?
SO NATALIE WAS TRYING TO HELP
ME OUT.
JUST FULL TRANSPARENCY.
BUT I WASNT EYE WOULD NEVER-- I
DID NOT STEAL ANYONES STUFF.
I DO THINK THAT NATALIE WAS
DOING THAT OUT OF LOVE FOR ME.
SHE KNOWS THAT IVE BEEN
FREEZING AT NIGHT, AND SO I DO
THINK IT CAME FROM A REALLY
RIGHT PLACE.
AND SO I DO JUST WANT TO DEFEND
HER ON THAT FRONT.
I THINK THAT IT CAME FROM LOVE.
Jeff: MIKE, ANGELINA HAS
BEEN A PEACEKEEPER THE ENTIRE
TRIBAL.
ANY TIME THERES AN ARGUMENT
WITH THE GOLIATHS, SHES THE ONE
WHO SAID, "EVEN THOUGH WE SOUND
LIKE WERE MAD AT YOU IM WITH
YOU."
YOU HAVE TO WALK A FINE LINE.
FOR ME, I DO THINK ITS STILL A
NUMBERS GAME.
KNOWING YOU HAD A GROUP THAT
MADE A COMMITMENT THAT MAYBE
WILL GIVE YOU SOME SAFETY IS
WORTH SOMETHING.
AT THE SAME TIME, WE ARE LOOKING
TOWARD THE NEXT STAGE OF THIS
GAME.
AND IT IS ABOUT PEOPLE THAT YOU
VIBE WITH, PEOPLE THAT YOU THINK
YOU CAN WORK WITH, PEOPLE THAT
YOU THINK YOU CAN TRUST.
ITS PART OF THE FACTORS THAT
YOURE WEIGHING AS AWE MAKE
DECISIONS MOVING FORWARD.
AND YOU SHOULD SEE THE
JACKETS.
IM SORRY.
I HAD TO GO THERE.
Jeff: NATALIE, I THINK I
JUST FIGURED YOU OUT.
YOU NEED THE LAST WORD.
YUP.
Jeff: IS THAT FAIR?
NO.
NOT ALWAYS.
Jeff: JACKETS AND EGGS.
IT HAS BEEN A LIVELY TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
LYRSA, YOURE UP.
TAKE YOUR MEMBERS ONLY JACKET
BACK TO BOSTON.
I LIKE YOUR PURPLE HAIR.
YOU CAN MAKE A PREACHER CUSS.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, NATALIE.
LYRSA.
NATALIE.
TWO VOTES NATALIE.
LYRSA.
WERE TIED, TWO VOTES LYRSA, TWO
VOTES NATALIE, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH," NATALIE.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
I JUSTMENTED TO GIVE YOU A
HUG.
IM SORRY.
NATALIE, IS THERE ANY WAY I
COULD HAVE YOUR JACKET?
NATALIE.
Jeff: NATALIE, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
NATALIE?
Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
THANK YOU.
IS IT WORTH $1 MILLION?
GUESS NOT.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
Jeff: WELL, BASED ON
TONIGHTS VOTE, IT WOULD APPEAR
YOU CHOSE TRIBAL HARMONY OVER
TRIBAL LINES.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
WHEN THE BATTLE LINES BLUR...
AS FAR AS THE GAMES GO, SHE
WOULD CUT YOU.
I JUST DONT TRUST ANGELINA.
Jeff: FRIENDS BECOME
ENEMIES.
I DONT LIKE STUPID PEOPLE.
Jeff: AND ENEMIES BECOME
FRIENDS.
ITS NOT DO I BLINDSIDE DAN.
ITS WHEN.
I DONT FEEL LIKE I DESERVED
ALL OF THE BAD RAP THEY GOT.
SOME OF THE THINGS THAT WERE
SAID ARE TRUE.
HOWEVER, I WAS LOVING THE GAME,
AND MY ONLY REGRET IS THAT I
DIDNT STAY IN THE GAME LONGER.
I DIDNT GIVE ANGELINA MY JACKET
BECAUSE I DIDNT KNOW IF SHE WAS
A PART OF THE REASON WHY IM
OUT.
SO WHY SHOULD I?
I DONT HAVE TO.
AND I CHOSE NOT TO.
SO IM WEARING IT.