Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
THE TRIBE WAS FACING TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND THE DAVID WERE
OUTNUMBERED.
WERE IN BIG TROUBLE.
Jeff: BUT NATALIES
ABRASIVE PERSONALITY WAS GETTING
OLD.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, ANGELINA
HAD A MASTER PLAN.
THIS IS A PHONY VOTE SO I CAN
TRY TO GET NATALIES JACKET
BEFORE SHE LEAVES.
Jeff: SHE TRIED TO CON
NATALIE.
NATALIE, IS THERE ANY WAY I
COULD HAVE YOUR JACKET?
Jeff: BUT ANGELINA WAS LEFT
EMPTY-HANDED.
NATALIE?
Jeff: WHEN NATALIE WAS SENT
HOME.
NATALIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
NATALIE?
Jeff: 14 ARE LEFT, WHO WILL
BE VOTED OAT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
YOURE HERE.
YOU CAN DO THE HONORS.
YAY!
I THOUGHT I WAS NEVER GOING TO
SEE THAT DAY HERE.
I SURVIVED TRIBAL COUNCIL ONCE
AGAIN.
I HAVE MORE LIFE THAN A CAT,
MAN.
LYRSA, JUST TO BE SUPER
CLEAR, THE ONLY REASON I WROTE
YOUR NAME WAS TO TRY TO GET THAT
JACKET.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
OH, MY GOT!
WHAT A PERFORMANCE.
ANGELINA WROTE MY NAME
BECAUSE SHE WANTED NATALIES
JACKET.
A JACKET?
LIKE, THATS VERY PETTY.
AND THATS REALLY MEAN AND THAT
SAYS A LOT ABOUT ANGELINAS
CHARACTER.
LYRSA?
WHAT.
CAN YOU DO ME THE BIGGEST
FAVOR?
SURE.
YOU WANT MY COAT?
NO.
FOR HER, THE JACKET IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN ME, SO, YEAH, I
DONT TRUST HER.
NATALIE IS GOING TO HATE US.
SHES GOING TO HATE ME.
SHES DEFINITELY GOING TO
HATE ME.
IM GOING TO HAVE TO CHANGE MY
ADDRESS.
WE GAVE UP THE GOLIATH
MAJORITY, BUT NATALIE GOING HOME
WAS BITTERSWEET.
SHE WAS BITTER AND FOR THE TRIBE
IT WAS SWEET BECAUSE NOW WE HAVE
A LITTLE BIT MORE PEACE AROUND
CAMP.
WHEN SHE WALKED OUT YOU WERE
LIKE, NATALIE, CAN I HAVE JUR
JACKET?"
I ASKED HER, LIKE, THREE
TIMES.
YOU JUMPED UP TO HUG HER, I
THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO REACH
AROUND AND GRAB THE JACKET OUT
OFIER BAG.
I WASNT GOING TO SHOPLIFT
FROM HER!
I WANTED NATALIE TO GET
BLINDSIDED BUT WALK AWAY HAVING
HER THINK I WAS ON HER SIDE TO
GET HER BEAUTIFUL FLEECE JACKET.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU CANT ALWAYS
GET EVERYTHING THAT YOU WISH
FOR.
ANGELINA, I FEEL LIKE SHES--
SHE IS SO FAKE.
JUST SO SHE COULD GET
NATALIES JACKET?
LAST NIGHT REALLY EXPOSED JUST
HOW COMPLETELY CRAZY SHE IS.
IT REALLY DID.
I THOUGHT IT WAS SO FUNNY WHEN
SHE DID THAT.
SHE WAS CRYING AND ACTING
SHOCKED.
SHE WAS LIKE...
REALLY?
THAT WAS JUST TOO MUCH.
SHE DESERVES AN EMMY.
IT WAS A PERFECTLY TRIBAL IN
MY BOOK.
NATALIE GOES HOME, AND ANGELINA
LOOKS LIKE A FOOL IN FRONT OF
EVERYBODY.
IF ANGELINA WILL DO THAT FOR A
JACKET, IMAGINE WHAT SHELL DO
FOR A MILLION DOLLARS.
AS FAR AS THE GAME GOES, SHE
WOULD CUT YOU--
SHES GOING TOO HARD.
ANGELINAS SEALING HER OWN FATE
WITH THIS KIND OF SHENANIGANS.
I KNOW SHES A SKETCH-BALL NOW,
I KNOW IT.
AND I THINK IT REALLY OPENED
MIKES PIPES SHE MIGHT FLIP ON A
DIME.
SHE WILL DEFINITELY FLIP ON A
TIME.
WE COULD GET OUT ANGELINA AND
IT WOULDNT BE NO SKIN OFF OUR
BACKS.
♪ ♪
GOING FISHING?
IM GOING TO TRY.
IM GOING TO SEE WHERE THE FISH
ARE, AND THEN IM GOING TO SEE
IF I CAN, YOU KNOW, CATCH FISH
WITH A SPEAR.
THATS AWESOME!
GIVE IT A SHOT.
SO SPEAR FISHING ON "SURVIVOR"
IS THREE EQUIPMENT COMPONENTS,
ONE OF WHICH IS THE MASK TO MAKE
SURE YOU CAN BOTH SEE AND
BREATHE UNDER WATER.
YOUR NOSE IS SO SQUISHED.
THE FLIPPERS.
DO I PUT MEAS OVER MY SHOES?
NO, YOU PUT THOAM YOUR NORMAL
FEET.
WHEN ARE A BIT AWKWARD TO
WALK IN AS I FOUND OUT THE HARD
WAY.
HAVE FUN.
THANK YOU.
IVE NEVER PUT ON A PAIR OF
FLIPPERS BEFORE, I BELIEVE.
JUST EVERY STEP WAS A BLOW TO MY
GENERAL SELF-WORTH.
JUST THE PERSONAL EGO AGONY.
( LAUGHTER )
ONCE YOU GET IN THE WATER, YOU
KNOW, ITS NICE.
AND, OF COURSE, THE BUSINESS END
HERE, THE SPEAR.
ESSENTIALLY, YOU TURN THIS INTO
A SPRING-LOADED MURDER MACHINE.
HOLD IT BACK, STORE A BUNCH OF
POTENTIAL ENERGY, AS WE CALL IT
IN THE PHYSICS BUSINESS, AND YOU
RELEASE IT IN THE FORM OF
KINETIC ENERGY-- I.E., STABBING.
I COULDNT CATCH ANY FISH.
CERTAINLY, I AM NOT A
FOOD-SEEKING MISSILE.
EVERYTHING LOOKS CLOSE, BUT IN
REALITY--
YEAH.
I GOTTA FIND A WAY TO SNEAK
UP ON THEM BETTER.
SO IF THEYRE COUNTING ON ME FOR
LARGE AMENDMENTS OF FOOD, WE MAY
BE STARVING TO DEATH.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
VUKU, TIVA, GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW JABENI TRIBE.
NATALIE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE GET TO
TODAYS REWARD CHALLENGE?
YEAH!
( APPLAUSE )
Reporter: FOR TODAYS
CHALLENGE, ONE PERSON WILL BE
ATTACHED TO A HEAVY BAG OF COKE
NUTS.
ON MY "GO," YOULL WORK TOGETHER
TO GET THAT BAG TO THE BEACH.
YOULL THEN LIFT THE BAG,
ALLOWING THE PERSON TO CLIMB
OVER AN OBSTACLE AND RETRIEVE
FOUR RINGS.
YOULL THEN ATTEMPT TO LAND
THOSE RINGS ON A TARGET.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
REWARD.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT YOURE
PLAYING FOR.
YEAH!
Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH...
YEAH!
( APPLAUSE ).
Jeff: COOKING UTENSILS,
HERBS AND SPIESS, 10
VEGETABLEICA BABES.
YUM!
Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH, TWOICA BOOKS.
WE GOT IT.
Jeff: LAST TRIBE TO FINISH.
NOTHING.
Jeff:ING NOTHING.
SUCKS.
Jeff: VUKU YOU ARE SITTING
SOMEBODY OUT, WHO WILL IT BE?
I WILL SIT OUT.
Jeff: TIVA YOU HAVE ONE
EXTRA PERSON.
WHO WILL IT BE?
ME.
Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, ILL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE WELL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO, FOR
REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, TIVA!
Jeff: YOUVE GOT TO CARRY
THOSE COCONUTS BACK TO SHORE.
GABBY TAKES A FALL.
IT IS VUKU QUICKLY IN THE LEAD.
TIVA RIGHT WITH THEM.
JABENI TRYING TO STAY IN IT
EARLY IN THIS CHALLENGE.
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
GOOD JOB, TIVA!
Jeff: TIVA AND VUKU
TOGETHER.
GABBY UP AND OVER.
ALEC UP AND OVER.
JABENI BRINGING UP THE REAR.
LETS GO, JABENI!
JABENI, YOURE DEAD LAST EARLY.
YOUVE GOT TO LIFT THAT BAG OF
COCONUTS TO GET ENOUGH SLACK TO
RETRIEVE FOUR RINGS.
GABBY IS ALREADY OVER.
ALEC IS OVER HEADING FOR HIS
FIRST RING.
LYRSA IS TAKING A LONG TIME ON
THE LADDER!
ALEC HAS HIS FIRST RING HEADING
BACK.
HES GOOD.
COMING BACK FOR THE SECOND.
THOSE BAGS ARE VERY HEAVY!
GABBY HAS THE FIRST.
LYRSA COME FIX THE ROPE.
Jeff: THIS IS A DISASTER
FOR JABENI, ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
TWO TRIBES KNOWING HOW TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR."
ONE LOOK LIKE THEYRE JUST
BEGINNING.
ALEC WHIPPING THROUGH THAT THIRD
RING.
NOBODY PROBLEM AT ALL.
ALEC NOW COMING BACK FOR THE
FOURTH AND FINAL RING FOR VUKU.
LYRSA TRYING TO GET BACK WITH
THAT FIRST RING FOR JABENI.
GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: HERE COMES GABBY WITH
THE SECOND RING.
GABBY IS GOOD WITH THE SECOND.
ALEC HAS THE FOURTH RING.
UNCLIP.
VUKU HAS THEIR FOUR RINGS.
NOW THEYLL TRY TO LAND THE
RINGS ON THE TARGET.
IT WILL BE ALEC NOW TOSSING THE
RINGS.
YOU GOTTA GO GET IT.
I NEED A LITTLE MORE ROPE.
I CANT HOLD IT MUCH LONGER
LIKE THIS.
Jeff: GABBY HAS THE FOURTH
RING.
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
Jeff: YOURE GOOD, TIVA!
UNCLIP!
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON!
Jeff: ALEC WITH ANOTHER
TOSS.
SHORT AGAIN.
Jeff: LYRSA HAS WANT FOURTH
RING FOR JABENI.
YOURE GOOD, JABENI!
UNCLIP, LYRSA!
IT IS DAN THROWING FOR TIVA.
YES!
Jeff: DAN LANDS THE FIRST
RING FOR TIVA.
ITS NOW TIVA IN THE THE LEAD.
HERE COMES JABENI.
A BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
ITS GOING TO BE NICK FOR
JABENI.
YEAH!
Jeff: HES GOT ONE.
VUKU HAD A BIG LEAD AND THEY
HAVE GIVEN IT AWAY.
DAVIE IN NOW FOR VUKU.
DAVIE TOSSES HIS FIRST TOSS AND
LANDS ONE.
WE ARE TIED 1-1-1.
WERE PLAYING TO FOUR.
JOHN TOSSES AND CONNECTS!
TIVA NOW WITH TWO AND TWO LEFT.
DAVIE JUST SHORT.
NICK SCORES THE SECOND RING.
FOR JABENI.
IT IS TIVA WITH TWO, JABENI WITH
TWO, YOU H VUKU WITH ONE.
DAN SCORES THE THIRD RING FOR
TIVA.
TIVA DOWN TO THEIR LAST RING.
VUKU HAD THE RING.
DAN COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
YES!
TIVA WINS REWARD!
LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
NICK SCORES THE THIRD RING FOR
JABENI.
DAVIE SCORES THE SECOND FOR
VUKU.
ITS NOW 3-2.
DAVIES GOT TO PICK IT UP NICK
FOR THE WIN.
AND HES GOT IT!
JABENI WINS REWARD!
( APPLAUSE ).
AT LEAST ITS NOT TRIBAL.
Jeff: TIVA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOUR REWARD WILL BE WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, ENJOY
THE AFTERNOON.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: JABENI, GOT OFF TO A
MISERABLE START BUT YOU PULLED
IT OUT.
COOKWARE, TWO KABOBS WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT CAMP.
NICE JOB.
ENJOY IT.
VUKU, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
WINNING IS THE GOOD THING,
BUT OTHERS ON THE OTHER TRIBE
WERE NOT HAPPY WE VOTED OFF
NATALIE.
MAYBE STAYING WITH ANGELINA
MAKES MORE SENSE.
IF WE MERGE TOGETHER, I HAVE
TAKEN OUT TWO GOLIATHS FROM MY
ORIGINAL TRIBE.
I WOULD HAVE A HUGE TARGET ON MY
BACK.
♪ ♪
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL!
MAN!
MY GOD!
CONGRATULATIONS, GUYS.
( APPLAUSE )
TIVAS TRIBE IS JUST ROCKING
AND ROLLING, MAN.
WE WON BY A LANDSLIDE YET AGAIN.
THATS WHAT WE DO AS TEEF AS.
I JUST WANT TO EAT A PEPPER.
I MISS CAROL A LOT, BUT OTHER
THAN THAT, I DONT KNOW HOW I
COULD BE BLAIG THE GAME BETTER
RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY GOD!
I FOUND TWO IDOLS.
DONT EAT THE PEPPERS.
DONT EAT PEPPERS.
AND NOT ONLY THAT, YOU KNOW,
IVE INDOCTRINATED CHRISTIAN
WITH ME AND JOHN, MORE OF THE
BROCHACHOS.
I TRUST HIM MORE TO PROTECT ME
AND COVER MY BACK THAN I DO
GABBY.
WHAT A GREAT MEAL.
THERE YOU GO!
ALL RIGHT, BROCHACHOS!
WE FEED EACH OTHER THE WAY WE
NEED TO FEED EACH OTHER.
THATS AN EXPERIENCE I NEVER HAD
BEFORE.
ITS ACTUALLY A FIRST FOR ME,
TOO.
ILL REMEMBER THIS.
BROCHACHOS ARE TIGHT.
ITS AN INTERESTING
TRANSITION HAPPENING.
ME, THIS IDEA OF BEING THIS COOL
GUY, COOL TO HANGUTE WITH AROUND
CAMP.
I-- I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE THAT
GUY, YOU KNOW.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE SOMEONE
THAT PEOPLE WANTED TO TALK TO.
ONE OF MY BIGGEST FEARS IN THIS
GAME AND OUTSIDE THIS GAME IS
BEING OSTRACIZED, YOU KNOW,
BEING LEFT OUT OF THE LOOP OF
FRIENDS, COLLEAGUES, AT A PARTY.
IM BECOMING THIS GOLIATH-LIKE
FIGURE FROM THESE DAVID ORIGINS.
THE FACT THAT I AM BECOMING THIS
PERSON PEOPLE LIKE TO TALK TO
AND HANG OUT WITH IS VALIDATION
THAT THIS WORK HAS BEEN PAYING
OFF, THIS SORT OF LIFETIME OF
SELF-IMPROVEMENT, IF YOU WILL.
THE BIGGEST THINGS THAT MAKE
DANCING COOL IS MISDIRECTION,
AND THE BEST EXAMPLE OF THAT IS
THE MOON WALK.
IF SOMEONE IS HAVING A SWEET
ROUTINE, THE WHOLE CROWD POPS
WHEN THEY DO SOMETHING
UNEXPECTED.
RIGHT.
I GUESS THATS LIKE MY POP AND
LOCK ADDS A VISUAL COMPELLING
ELEMENT TO IT, YEAH.
ITS OBVIOUS THESE GOLIATH
BOYS WOULD WRATH BRO DOWN WITH
CHRISTIAN AND LEAVE ME ON THE
OITS.
SO I NEED TO FIND A WAY TO TAKE
MY GAME INTO MY OWN HANDS.
BUT ITS SCARY!
ITS REALLY SCARY FOR ME.
I KNOW WE KEEP SAYING WE JUST
HAVE TO WIN, WE JUST HAVE TO
WIN.
BUT WHAT IF WE DONT?
WHAT IF WE DONT.
I KNOW IM ON THE BOTTOM, AND
I DONT WANT TO JUST LEAN ON
HOPE, HOPE THAT WE WILL WIN.
HOPE IS NOT A STRATEGY.
THIS GAME IS ABOUT TAKING
CHANCES.
YEAH.
WHICH FREAKING SCARY, AND I--
I NEED YOU.
I DONT KNOW WHO I HAVE ANYMORE.
YEAH.
LIKE, I TRUST CHRISTIAN 100%.
AND I FEEL CONNECTED TO YOU,
MORE SO THAN JOHN AND DAN.
I CANT WORK WITH DAN.
DAN DOESNT TALK TO ME ABOUT
STRATEGY, SO, LIKE, YOURE THE
ONLY PERSON THATS TALKED
STRATEGY TO ME.
I, LIKE, DONT WANT TO GET
EMOTIONAL BECAUSE THIS IS SO
LAME BUT--
I KNOW.
ITS REALLY SCARY BEING ON
THE BOTTOM AND, LIKE, AND, LIKE,
YOURE THE ONLY PERSON THAT
EXTENDED AN OLIVE BRANCH TO ME
AND CHRISTIAN.
AND, LIKE, I WANTED TO PLAY IT
COOL, BUT, LIKE, I JUST HAVE TO,
LIKE, PUT MYSELF OUT THERE.
I HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE.
I KNOW YOU HAVE MORE TO LOSE.
SEEING HER TEAR UP, SHE JUST
CUT TO MY CORE.
I AM AN EXTRAORDINARILY
EMPATHETIC PERSON.
THAT IS KIND OF MY GREATEST GIFT
AS A DOCTOR, SO WHEN I SEE
SOMEONE EMOTIONAL, MY FIRST
INSTINCT IS TO ALLEVIATE THEIR
SUFFERING.
SHE IS PUTTING A LOT OF TRUST IN
ME.
AND I THINK GABBY IS SOMEONE
THAT I CAN TRUST LONG TERM.
I THINK THIS GAME SHOULDNT BE
DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH.
YEAH.
I THINK IT SHOULD BE WHO DO
YOU TRUST?
SO IF IT WERE TO COME TO A
TRIBAL COUNCIL, IM TRYING TO
PLAY AS MUCH WITH JOHN AND DAN,
BUT THEN BLINDSIDING DAN.
I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
I IDENTIFY DAN AS A THREAT.
ON THE OTHER HAND, I FEEL LIKE
YOU, ME, AND CHRISTIAN ARE MUCH
MORE CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
AND, HONESTLY, LIKE HEART AND
HEAD TELL ME TO GO WITH YOU AND
CHRISTIAN.
OKAY.
EVERY DAY, THE LINE BETWEEN
DAVID AND GOLIATH ARE BLURRING
MORE AND MORE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AROUND AND YOU
THINK ABOUT WHO IS THE BIGGEST
THREAT, IT PROBABLY IS DAN.
HE HAS THIS BROCHACHO THING
GOING ALONG.
ITS A LITTLE BIT OF A BOYS
CLUB.
AND NOT ONLY THAT, HE HAS AN
IDOL IN HIS POCKET, AND THAT
SCARES ME.
SO NOW THE QUESTION IS LESS
BECOMING DO I BLINDSIDE DAN AND
MORE BECOMING WHEN?
BREATHE IN AND OIT.
GO OUT JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
OUT?
NOT QUITE AS CLOSE TO MY
SPINE.
OKAY.
FOUR WEEKS BEFORE I CAME OUT
HERE I COULDNT WALK BECAUSE MY
BACK WAS HURTING SO BAD.
I SUFFERED THROUGH THE FIRST 16
DAYS OF THIS ON THAT STUPID
BAMBOO, AND ITS TAKING A TOLL
ON ME MENTALLY NOT BEING ABLE TO
SLEEP.
EVERYBODY KEEPS TALKING ABOUT
WANTING TO GET THIS BED MORE
COMFORTABLE BY SPLITTING THE
BAMBOO WHERE THEYRE ALL LEVEL.
ITS DAY 16 AND AINT NOBODY
DONE NOTHING ABOUT IT.
WELL, GUESS WHAT?
I WANT TO DO IT NOW, AND IT
NEEDS TO BE DIDNT RIGHT WAY.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
I SEE ELISABETH AND KARA
START CHOPPING BAMBOO IN HALF.
ITS GOING TO BE DARK SOON.
THATS NOT A HALF-DAY PROJECT.
ITS A WHOLE-DAY PROJECT.
AND IM LIKE OH!
HOLD ON!
PUMP THE BRAKES!
I CANT SLEEP ON IT.
MY BACK IS KILLING ME.
IF WE WAS GOING TO START IT,
WE SHOULD START THAT EARLY IN
THE MORNING.
WE CANT START IT WHEN WE AINT
GOT BUT TWO HOURS OF DAYLIGHT
LEFT.
WE HAD A WHOLE DAY.
WERE GOING TO WAIT UNTIL DAY 39
TO FIX OUR FREAKING BED.
THERE ARE TWO THINGS IN LIFE I
DONT LIKE, LAZY PEOPLE AND
STUPID PEOPLE.
WHY ARE YOU SLOWING THE SPLIT
ONE AWAY.
I TOOK ALL THE HALF ONES OFF.
ITS A MISTAKE.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN A PERSON IF I
CARE ABOUT SOMETHING I CANT LET
GO.
SO WHEN IM IRRITATED, LIKE I AM
RIGHT NOW, EVERYBODYS ALREADY
GOING TO KNOW IT.
AAAAHHH!
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, IM GREAT.
YOU GOT AN ISSUE?
YEAH, I GOT ISSUES.
LET IT OUT.
THERETO OUT RIGHT NOW.
I JUST EYE JUST NEED TO GET
THIS OUT, OKAY?
GO AHEAD, GO AHEAD.
FOUR WEEKS BEFORE I CAME TO
"SURVIVOR," I COULD NOT GET UP
OUT OF BED TO GO TO THE FREAKING
BATHROOM BY MYSELF.
MY BACK WAS IN SUCH BAD SHAPE.
AND I AM NOT A WI WUSS, OKAY?
NO ONE IS SAYING YOURE A
WUSS.
I JUST NEED TO LISTEN FOR
JUST A SECOND, OKAY?
AND I HAVE BEEN SUFFERING ON
THIS BAMBOO SINCE I HAVE BEEN
HERE AND I HAVENT SAID ONE WORD
ABOUT IT, EXCEPT FOR THROWING
OUT IDEAS.
I AM IN CONSTANT PAIN.
AND I GOT TIRED OF BEING PATIENT
WAITING FOR SOMEBODY ELSE TO
HELP MAKE A BED MORE
COMFORTABLE.
AND ITS JUST REALLY FRUSTRATING
TO START TAKING IT APART AND PUT
IT BACK TOGETHER YOUR WAY
WITHOUT INVOLVE MEEG IN THE
PROCESS.
SO IT WASNT LIKE IT WAS A GROUP
DECISION.
A GROUP DECISION?
WERE GOING THERE?
IT WASNT A GROUP DECISION TO
TAKE IT APART.
FOR ONE, EVIDENCE LAYING ON
THE BED TRYING TO GET SOME LEAP,
AND IM WOKEN UP TO THE FREAKING
BAMBOO BEING SAWED IN HALF.
WITH THE DAVIDS I THOUGHT
THEY HAD THIS COWBOY HAT
CONVENTION BUT, APPARENTLY,
THERES SOME KIND OF RIFT THERE.
AS MUCH AS I HATE CONFLICTS
BETWEEN TWO PEOPLE IT ALSO MAKES
ME SIT BACK AND EAT MY POPCORN
KNOWING ITS NOT GOING TO BE ME.
IM SORRY I AM BEING A JERK
ABOUT IT.
I REALLY AM.
BUT ITS REALLY FRUSTRATING.
THINGS CHANGE EVERY SINGLE
SECOND IN THIS GAME SO WHERE THE
PERSON YOU WERE TIGHT WITH GOT
UNDER YOUR SKIN.
AS FAR AS ELISABETH GOES, WE
TEND TO CLASH.
SHES A KNOW-IT-ALL.
AND I DONT DO WELL WITH
KNOW-IT-ALLS AT THIS PARTICULAR
POINT, IF WE WERE TO LOSE I
WOULD TRY TO GET RID OF
ELIZABETH.
♪ ♪
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, LETS GET TO TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST-- TAKE BACK
THE IDOLS.
GABBY GIVES IT TO ME.
CARL MAKES ME COME GET IT.
I GET IT.
DONT WANT TO GIVE IT UP.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO CARRY A LARGE SAUCER TO
A WATER TOWER, FILL IT, MAKE
YOUR WAY THROUGH A SERIES OF
OBSTACLES, EMPTY WHATS LEFT
INTO A WELL, THEN RACE BACK.
ONCE YOU FILL THE WELL WITH
WATER, YOULL DROP A BAG OF
PUZZLE PIECES.
YOULL USE THE PIECES TO SOFT
PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WITH
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SEVENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
VUKU, ONE EXTRA MEMBER.
KARA SAT OUT LAST CHALLENGE.
CANNOT SIT OUT THIS ONE.
WHO IS GOING TO BE?
ME.
Jeff: ELISABETH GOING TO
SET OUT FOR VUKU.
TIVA, ALISON SAT OUT LAST TIME
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
ME.
Jeff: GABBY IS GOING TO SIT
OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WELL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
CHRISTIAN, YOU READY?
YES!
Jeff: SURVIVORS READY?
YUP.
Jeff: GO!
FIRST JOB IS TO GET OUT AND GET
THAT SAUCER SO YOU CAN START
GETTING WATER.
TIVA HAS THEIR SAUCER HEADING
BACK.
JABENI HAS THEIRS.
VUKU OFF TO A SLOW START NOW.
EVERYBODYS GOT TO BE ON A BEAM.
YOU DROP, YOU GOTTA GO BACK.
WAIT, SLOW, GUYS.
Jeff: THERE ARE THREE BEAMS
AND FOUR PEOPLE.
FIGURE IT OUT.
WE GOT TWE GOT IT.
Jeff: THATS HOW YOU DO IT!
VUKU HAS CAUGHT UP NOW.
SUDDENLY ITS VUKU IN THE LEAD
NOW.
HERE WE GO!
Jeff: AND JABENI, DEAD
LAST.
VUKU HAS WATER.
TIVA HAS WATER.
KEEP IT GOING.
Jeff: YOU WANT TO FILL THIS
SAUCER.
TIVA HEADING OUT WITH THEIR
FIRST SAUCER FULL OF WATER.
REPORTER, LETS GO.
Jeff: JABENI GOING TO HEAD
OUT NOW WITH NOT NEARLY AS MUCH
WATER AS TIVA HAS.
SHOULD WE GO BACK?
NO, NO, NO.
THEYRE GOING TO SPILL IT.
Jeff: YOURE GOING TO LOSE
SOME WATER ALONG THE WAY.
UP TO THE FILL THAT BABY.
THE MORE WATER YOU HAVE WHEN YOU
GET TO THE WELL, THE FEWER TRIPS
YOU WILL HAVE TO MAKE.
WE HAVE TO GO UP A LITTLE
BIT.
Jeff: AND A BIG TROP BY
VUKU.
THEY LOST HALF THEIR SAUCER.
BE CAREFUL!
OKAY, ROTATE.
Jeff: NOW IT GETS
COMPLICATED.
YOU HAVE THREE BEAMS.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOMEBODY ON
EVERY BEAM WHILE BALANCING A
SAUCER WITH WATER THAT YOU
DESPERATELY NEED TO FILL THAT
WELL.
THIS IS WHERE TEAM WORK IS
CRUCIAL!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
Jeff: JABENI LOSES NEARLY
EVERYTHING.
FUT UP AGAINST THAT THING AND
WE TIP UP.
SO PUT THAT THERE.
Jeff: THATS HOW DO YOU IT
RIGHT THERE, TIVA.
TIVA BACK, THEYRE GOING TO FILL
UP THEIR WELL.
WOW, TIVA DOES IT.
THEYVE DROPPED THEIR PUZZLE
PIECES.
GOOD JOB, TIVA!
Jeff: VUKUS GOT TO HELP
BACK.
GOOD LEAD, TIVA!
Jeff: TIVA DID A NICE JOB
IN TERMS OF TRANSPORTING WATER.
AND THAT IS GOING TO BE THE
DIFFERENCE EARLY IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
VUKU HAVING TO HEAD BACK.
JABENI DEFINITELY HAVING TO HEAD
BACK.
THEY BARELY HAVE ANY WATER IN
THEIR SAUCER.
IT IS CHRISTIAN AND ALISON
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE FOR TIVA.
THEY HAVE YET TO GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
LETS TRADE OUT THE ONES THAT
ARE NOT EDGE PIECES AND PUT THEM
OVER HERE.
Jeff: HERE COMES VUKU AND
HERE COMES JABENI.
IT HAS BEEN A NORMAL STORY FOR
JABENI TO BE DEAD LAST BUT THEY
HAVE PULLED CHALLENGES OUT IN
THE PAST.
CAN THEY DO IT AGAIN.
JABENI ALREADY EXHAUSTED EARLY
IN THE CHALLENGE BUT THEY ARE
NOT GIVING UP.
YEAH!
Jeff: VUKU DROPS THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES!
THEYRE GOOD.
ITS NOW JABENI STILL STRUGGLING
TO GET BACK.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, MY ARM --
LITERALLY TAKING A STOP TO
REST.
KARA HAS THE PUZZLE PIECES.
ITS GOING TO BE KARA AND ALEC
SOLVING THE PUZZ PEL.
LETS GO, VUKU!
Jeff: HERE COMES JABENI.
THEY NEED TO HAVE ENOUGH WATER
TO FILL THAT WELL AND IT DOES
NOT LOOK GOOD AND THEYVE LOST
WHAT LITTLE THEY HAVE AGAIN.
GOT ONE!
Jeff: ALISON AND CHRISTIAN
DOING A NICE JOB.
THEY ARE CLOSING IN ON IMMUNITY.
ALEC AND KARA CONTINUE TO WORK
TOGETHER WELL.
JABENI BACK WITH ANOTHER SAUCER
FULL OF WATER, TRYING TO GET IT
ALL IN.
A LOT OF IT IS SPLASHING OUT,
HOPING IT WILL DROP THE PUZZLE
PIECES.
REALLY?
ONE MORE.
Jeff: NO.
WOW.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, JABENI
HAS TO HEAD BACK.
JABENI LOOKS LIKE THEYRE ON
THE EDGE OF GIVING UP.
WERE NOT GOING TO GIVE UP.
NOPE, NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: YOURE CLOSE.
ONE MORE SAUCER WILL DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN WITH
ANOTHER PIECE.
ALISON WITH ONE MORE.
TIVA CLOSING IN ON ANOTHER
IMMUNITY WIN.
KEEPING THEM SAFE IN THE GAME.
VUKU NOT FAR BEHIND.
GUYS, GUYS!
Jeff: WE ARE CLOSE TO A
"SURVIVOR" BLOWOUT RIGHT NOW.
ALISON WITH THE NEXT-TO-LAST
PIECE.
ALISON AND CHRISTIAN GOING TO DO
IT TOGETHER.
THERE IT IS!
TIVA WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE AGAIN
FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL!
IT IS NOW A STORY OF VUKU VERSUS
JABENI.
IT WOULD BE AN IMPOSSIBLE
COMEBACK AT THIS POINT FOR
JABENI.
AND YET THEY STILL FIGHT.
THEIR HEART IS IN IT.
THEY JUST CANT GET THE
PERFORMANCE TO MATCH.
LET GO, LET GO.
IF WEVE GOT A CHANCE IN
HELL, WE GOTTA GO.
IM JUST TELLING YOU IF I GO
I MIGHT DROP IT.
IM JUST TRYING TO KEEP IT
TOGETHER, DUDE.
LETS GO, LETS GO.
WE HAVE TO.
Jeff: SOMETIMES THERE IS
JUST NOWHERE TO HIDE ON
"SURVIVOR."
YOU EITHER HAVE IT OR YOU DONT.
AND RIGHT NOW, JABENI IS NOWHERE
CLOSE TO HAVING IT.
ALEC AND KARA TAKING THEIR TIME.
NO RUSH.
JABENI STILL FIGHTING.
THAT "SURVIVOR" SPIRIT IS WHAT
GOT YOU OUT HERE, AND ITS WHAT
KEEPS YOU OUT HERE.
ONE MORE TIME.
OH GOD!
YOU OKAY?
Jeff: JABENI, JUST WHEN
THEY WERE BACK WITH THEIR LAST
SAUCER FULL OF WATER, LITERALLY
DROPPED THE SAUCER.
I MEAN, WE-- THERES NOTHING
WE CAN DO.
Jeff: ALEC WITH THE
NEXT-TO-LAST PIECE FOR VUKU.
DO THE PLEA OF US WANT TO TRY
TO LIFT IT UP.
THEYRE DONE.
THEY HAVE ONE PIECE LEFT.
Jeff: KARA WITH THE FINAL
PIECE SECURING IMMUNITY FOR
VUKU.
VUKU WINS EU78 IMMUNITY.
SAFE FROM TRIBAL COUNCIL.
JABENI KNOWS WHATS COMING.
TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR JABENI WHERE
ONE OF THE FOYER WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
DAY 17, A DAY NONE OF THEM WILL
FORGET.
TIVA, CONGRATULATIONS.
BEAUTIFULLY EXECUTE AT EVERY
STAGE.
WELL EARNED.
THANKS, JEFF.
( APPLAUSE )
BROCHACHO.
Jeff: VUKU,
CONGRATULATIONS.
TIVA AND VUKU NICE JOB.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY ANOTHER NICE NIGHT OFF.
THANKS, JEFF.
Jeff: WELL DONE.
IM SORERY.
SORRY.
Jeff: MIKE, ONE OF THE
THINGS ABOUT "SURVIVOR" IS YOU
CANT PREPARE FOR EVERY
CHALLENGE.
THAT WAS A TERRIBLE PERFORMANCE,
BUT ITS NOT INDICATIVE OF A
TERRIBLE TRIBE.
WHAT KEPT YOU GOING WHEN IT WAS
CLEAR THERE WAS NO CHANCE FOR
YOU GUYS TO WIN?
( SIGHS )
ITS ALL RIGHT.
I JUST KNOW THIS IS AN
IMPORTANT ELIMINATION.
AND I DONT WANT ANY OF US TO GO
HOME.
AND-- AND SO I THINK ALL OF US
WERE PUTTING BEST EFFORTS, EVEN
THOUGH WE WERE OUT-GUNNED, BUT
IM PROUD OF EVERY ONE OF THEM
AND I JUST FEEL BAD THEY
COULDNT DO MORE.
Jeff: IT IS ONLY DAY 17,
BUT 17 DAYS IS ALL IT WILL BE
FOR ONE OF THE FOUR OF YOU.
NICK, LYRSA, ANGELINA, MIKE,
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TREEBL.
IVE GOTTEN TO GO NICK, LEERS
AAND ANGELINA, AND I LIKE ALL OF
THEM.
I KNOW HOW MUCH THIS MEANS TO
THEM, AND I DONT LIKE THE IDEA
OF DASHING DREAMS.
SO TO HAVE ONE OF THEM GO
HOME... ISNT-- ISNT-- ISNT AS
FUN AS I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
IT WAS SO HARD.
YOU LOOK AT WHAT THE OTHER
TEAMS LOOKED LIKE,
MFERL-BOUND...
THEY GOT IT, IN, LIKE, TWO
MINUTES GEE,Y KNOW.
IM SOR SORRY ONE OF US HAS
TO LEAVE.
WE DID ALL WE COULD.
I REALLY WANTED ALL FOUR OF
US TO MAKE THE NEXT STAEJ OF THE
GAME WHICH IM HOPING IS A
MERGE, BUT I FEEL LIKE THIS IS
THE MOST MOMENTUM VOTE OF THE
GAME SO FAR.
WE HAVE SEVEN GOLIATHS, SEVEN
DAVIDS.
WERE HERE ON A TRIBE WITH TWO
GOLIATHS AND TWO DAEFDS.
ITS NOT JUST SOMEBODY GOING
HOME.
WHATEVER HAPPENS TODAY IS GOING
TO IMPACT EVERYBODYS GENTLEMAN
FOR THE REST OF THE GAME.
YEAH.
I MEAN, PERSONALLY, LIKE, I
WOULD LOVE TO JUST PARTY WITH
YOU ON THIS GAME.
SO--
YEAH.
AND I KNOW YOU WOULD BE LOYAL
TO, LIKE, US.
AND I KNOW YOU WANT IT.
YOU BRING A LOT TO THE TEAM.
I REALLY DONT KNOW WHY
ANGELINA THINKS I WOULD BE
WILLING TO WORK WITH HER AFTER
THE JACKET THING.
CRAZY.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
I MEAN, ILL STICK WITH NICK.
SO I THINK MAYBE ITS GONNA BE,
LIKE, A TIE OR SOMETHING.
COMING BACK FROM THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, EVIDENCE ACTUALLY
FEELING PRETTY OPEN MINDED TO
WORKING WITH LYRSA, GIVEN THAT
WERE BOTH LATINAS.
BUT IT FELT LIKE THERE WAS NO
ROOM FOR NEGOTIATION OR
COMPROMISE OR CONSIDERATION.
AND SO, THAT PUT THE NAIL IN HER
COFFIN.
IT WILL ABSOLUTELY BE LYRSA
TONIGHT.
ITS THURSDAY.
WE HAVE TO VOTE HER OUT.
FOR SURE.
YOU THINK NICK IS WITH US?
YEAH.
I MEAN, NO ONES GOING TO WANT
TO GO TO ROCKS.
NO ONE WANTS TO GO TO ROCKS.
AND WE GUARANTEE HIM SAFETY.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE NEED TO WORK ON
NICK TODAY.
OH, YEAH.
THEY ARE STICKING TOGETHER.
THATS WHAT THEY JUST TOLD
YOU?
YEAH.
I THINK WEVE GOT A CHANCE IF WE
CAN JUST GET TO THEM.
RIGHT NOW, MY LIFE IN THIS
GAME AND IN DAVID AS A NUMBER IS
HANGING BY A THREAD, AND MIKE IS
HOLDING IT.
WE NEED TO CONVINCE HIM TO
FINALLY VOTE ANGELINA OUT, BUT
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT,
SHES NOT GETTING MY JACKET.
I WILL MAYBE OFFER ONE OF MY
SOCKS AND JUST BECAUSE IT HAS A
HOLE IN IT.
I REALLY WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU,
MEEK.
IM JUST TELLING YOU THAT IM
REAL--
I KNOW YOU ARE.
AND I REALLY WANT TO STAY.
Y KNOW.
THE THING IS FOR ME, WHATEVER
HESITATION I HAVE HAS NOTHING TO
DO WITH YOU VERSUS ANGELINA.
IT HAS TO DO WITH THE GOLIATHS.
SO I JUST WANTED TO LET YOU
KNOW, I THINK YOU, ME, AND MEEK
ARE SUCHS GOOD TRIO TOGETHER.
SINCE DAY ONE I FELT REALLY
SOLID WITH YOU.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW.
I DONT HAVE ANY LOYALTY TO
HER.
SHES JUST NONSTOP STRATEGIC.
IT WOULD BE SO CRAZY.
I WANT TO WORK WITH YOU LONG
TERM.
UH-HUH.
I KNOW YOU AND MIKE WILL
PROBABLY STICK TOGETHER NO
MATTER WHAT, BUT I MEAN, I CANT
DO THAT WITH LYRSA.
YEAH.
FOR HER TO GO OUT NOW, SHED
BE SO PISSED.
CAN I ASK FOR HER SOCKS?
AND HER COAT?
Y REALLY WANT THAT COAT.
WELL, IM DOWN.
OH, MY GOD, ANGELINAS GOING TO
BE SO MAD AT ME.
YEAH, IT SUCKS TO SEE HER GO.
I LIKE HER, YOU KNOW, BUT WE
WERENT SUPER TEAT OR ANYTHING.
THERES NO QUESTION IN ME
MEEND.
YEAH.
I DONT HAVE ANY DESIRE TO WORK
WITH YAG AS FAR AS I CAN THROW
HER.
SHE THINKS SHES RUNNING THE
WHOLE SHOW.
AND THATS NOT TRUE AT ALL.
THE TRUTH IS ILL PROBABLY
DISCUSS IT WITH MIKE, MY FELLOW
ROCK STAR, AND WHATEVER WE THINK
SUITS US BEST IS WHAT WE WILL
DO.
.
YEAH, AND ITS GOOD FOR YOUR
GAME.
MY GAME IS MORE-- HERES THE
THING, IF THE DAEFDZ GET
TOGETHER AND START PICKING OFF
GOLIATH AFTER GOLIATH AFTER
GOLIATH, IM JUST BONING MY OWN
GAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I DO HAVE A LOT OF FAEGHT IN
MIKE.
AND TRUST HIM.
AT THIS POINT I FEEL LIKE MIKES
BEST FRIEND.
I THINK WE COULD GO DEEP IN THIS
NF THIS GAME AND HAVE FUN
PLAYING IT.
MY JOB IS TO CONVINCE MIKE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS BEST FOR
US?
THE SAFE PART OF ME SAYS
LYRSA.
UH-HUH.
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE LYRSAS
NOT, LIKE--
SHES NOT GOING TO BE A
THREAT TO ANYBODY.
AND, ALSO, I DO THINK THERE
IS SOME UP SIDE TO VOTING OUT
ANGELINA.
SO IM REALLY-- IM REALLY TORN.
ITS ALMOST LIKE A FREE SHOT
TO TAKE OUT A BIG THREAT.
IM REALLY STRUGGLING WITH
WHICH WAY TO GO.
I REALLY TRUST LYRSA IN A WAY I
JUST DONT TRUST ANGELINA.
I MEAN, THIS IS NOT A PLAYER TO
BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.
SHE IS HERE TO WIN.
SHE IS THE CEEND OF PERSON TO
TURN ON AND AND YOU NEVER KNOW.
BUT BY VOTING HER OUT, AM I
SCREWING EVERY GOLIATH LEFT IN
THE GAME.
THE TRUTH, IS I LIKE A LOT OF
THE GOLIATHS LEFT IN THE GAME.
MY GUT SAYS LYRSA ONE MINUTE AND
ANGELINA THE NEXT MINUTE.
LIKE, I FEEL A CHOKER ON MY NECK
AND, LIKE, ITS GETTING TIGHTER
AND TEETER.
YOU KNOW, THE CLOCK IS
TICKING.
IVE GOT TO MAKE A DECISION.
♪ ♪
Jeff: NICK, I WAS STRUCK AT
THE END OF THE CHALLENGE BY THE
CLEAR BOND THE FOUR OF YOU HAD.
DOES THAT SURPRISE YOU?
I AM SURPRISED.
I MEAN, I DONT KNOW IF ITS THE
STRUGGLES THAT THIS GROUP HAS
GONE THROUGH TOGETHER, BUT,
YEAH, TODAY WHEN WE LOST I
WASNT THINKING ABOUT ME.
I WAS THINKING, MAN, ONE OF US
HAS TO GO HOME.
Jeff: SO, MIKE, IS THERE
ANYTHING TO THE DAVID-DPLGHT OR
IS THAT OUT THE WINDOW AND ITS
NOW JUST PEOPLE?
THERES NO WRONG ANSWER HERE.
I THINK ALL FOUR OF US ARE
STRONG PLAYERS.
WED BE LUCKY TO HAVE AN
ALLIANCE WITH ANY OF US.
Jeff: SO WHATS THE
CRITERIA RIGHT NOW FOR TONIGHTS
VOTE?
WELL, IF THERE IS A MERGE, WE
ARE THINKING ABOUT WHO DO WE
TRUST TO HELP US NAVIGATE THAT
NEXT TREACHEROUS PART OF THE
GAME.
Jeff: LYRSA, IS THAT WHAT
IT IS FOR YOU, TRUST AND LOYALTY
FROM HEREON OUT?
YEAH, TO ME IT HAS BEEN FROM
THE GET-GO OF THE GAME, TRYING
TO MAKE BONDS WITH PEOPLE THAT
WILL STAY LOYAL TO ME.
AND THE BONDS THAT I CREATED
WITH THESE PEOPLE ARE MORE
STRONGER THAN WHAT WE HAD WITH
THE PEOPLE THAT WE PLAYED
BEFORE.
Jeff: ANGELINA, TRUST AND
LOYALTY NUMBER ONE FOR YOU RIGHT
NOW, LOOKING AHEAD?
TRUST, LOYALTY, AND STRATEGY.
Jeff: HOW SO?
ILL GET THERE.
I ADD STRATEGY BECAUSE IF THERE
IS MERGE, YOU HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT WHO DO I TRUST?
WHO TRUSTS ME?
AND WHO MAKES THE MOST SENSE TO
BE CONNECTED WITH ME IN THIS
GAME.
Jeff: NICK, IS THIS A BIT
OF A ROLL OF THE DICE THAT "I
HOPE WERE MAKING THE RIGHT
DECISION AND IF WE MERGE OUR
ASSUMPTIONS ABOUT WHAT IS
HAPPENING ARE CORRECT?"
ABSOLUTELY.
IT WOULD BE LIKE A WAR COMING
IN.
AND RIGHT NOW IM PICKING THE
BROTHERS AND SISTERS IM
FIGHTING BESIDE AND FIGHTING
WITH, NOT FEETING AGAIN.
ILL CUT TO THE CHASE, JEFF.
AS THE UNDERDOG IN THESE THREE
TRIBES WE HAD TO PREPARE FOR THE
WORST, AND THE THE WORST IS
COMING HERE AGAIN TONIGHT WITH
FOUR PLAYERS.
THAT BEING SAID, WE WOULDNT
HAVE MADE THE MOVE ON NATALIE
LAST TRIBAL IF WE DIDNT HAVE A
PLAN.
AND IM REALLY HOPING THAT THAT
IS WHAT WE STEK TO TONIGHT.
Jeff: LYRSA, IS THAT CODE
FOR ANYBODY WHOS WITH ME ON MY
PLAN, JUST MAKE SURE OUR PLAN IS
THE PLAN IN PLACE?
EVERYBODY ELSE HERE HAS A
PLAN SO IT ALL DEPENDS WHICH
PLAN YOURE WORKING ON AND
ULTIMATE TO MOVE FORWARD WITH.
SO I HOPE THAT MY PLAN, WHICH IS
BASED ON LOYALTY AND TRUTH,
MOVES FORWARD IN THE GAME.
Jeff: NICK, DO YOU HAVE A
PLAN?
I HAVE A PLAN.
SHES GOT A PLAN.
I THINK WE ALL HAVE A PLAN.
FOR ME PERSONALLY, IM HERE FOR
THIS TRIBE.
THE DAVID AND GOLIATH STUFF IS
OVER.
Jeff: YOUR PITCH IS I DONT
CARE ABOUT TRIBAL ALLIANCES?
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: TO GET RID OF ME
WOULD BE AN ABSOLUTE MISTAKE.
IT WOULD BE A MISTAKE.
YOUD BE WASTING A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP THAT YOU CAN USE
LATER IN THE GAME.
ILL GO TO BAT FOR NICK.
CAN I JUMP IN?
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH, SURE.
I THINK NICK IS SOMEONE WHO
IS A PLEASURE TO BE AROUND.
HE HELPS AROUND CAMP.
YOU CAN LOOK INTO HIS, LIKE,
PIERCING, WILSON BLUE EYES AND
YOU CAN SEE WHAT HES THINKING.
TO HAVE SOMEONE WHO BRINGS THAT
HONOR TO THE GAME IS-- IS SUPER
VALUABLE.
AND SO I JUST WANTED TO ADD THAT
TO WHAT YOU ALREADY SAID.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
Jeff: LYRSA, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF THAT, VERY FLATTERING.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I THINK ITS TRYING TO BUY HIS
VOTE AND VOTE AGAINST SOMEONE
ELSE.
I AM NERVOUS THAT IT MIGHT BE
ME.
ALL I CAN SAY IT IM BEING
HONEST WITH PEOPLE.
WHEN YOU TELL YOU IM GOING TO
BE WITH YOU TO THE END I WILL BE
WITH YOU TO THE END.
I DONT HAVE A REASON TO LIE
HERE.
THATS THE WAY I CARRY MYSELF IN
THE GAME.
Jeff: WHATS THE RISK WITH
TONIGHTS VOTE, MIKE?
WHAT IF YOU GUYS GET IT WRONG?
( SIGHS ).
WELL, IF WE GET IT WRONG, MY
HOPE IS THAT ITS NOT A FATAL
MISTAKE.
I DO BELIEVE THAT EVERYBODY
TRUSTS EACH OTHER AND MAYBE
THATS GOING TO END UP BEING ONE
PERSONS PROBLEM TONIGHT.
BUT OUR DECISION TONIGHT IS NOT
JUST GOING TO IMPACT OUR GAMES
HERE BUT EVERYBODY PLAYING THE
GAME ON THE FIELD.
Jeff: SO IT REALLY IS
EVERYBODY IS PUTTING ALL THEIR
CHIPS IN RIGHT NOW TONIGHT.
ONE PERSON IS GOING TO GO HOME,
AND THE THE OTHER THREE ARE
HOPING THAT THE 24TH ARE AS
LOYAL AS THEY SAY THEY ARE.
ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ANGELINA, YOURE UP.
THIS TIME THE VOTE IS
ACTUALLY FOR YOU.
LOVE YOU, CHICA.
ADIOS.
SEEING HOW YOU WERE TRYING TO
CHARM NICK, JUST CONVINCED ME I
HAVE TO VOTE YOU AND CARRY MY
PLAN OUT.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LYRSA.
ANGELINA.
ONE VOTE LYRSA, ONE VOTE
LYRSA.
THATS TWO VOTES LYRSA, ONE VOTE
ANGELINA, ONE VOTE LEFT.
SOAFG PERSON VOTED OUT,
LYRSA.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
LYRSA, THE TREEB HAS SPOKEN.
BYE, GUYS.
HAVE FUN!
BYE, LYRSA.
SORRY.
( SIGHS )
Jeff: IT SEEMS CLEAR THAT
TONIGHTS VOTE WAS NOT ABOUT WHO
TO GET RID OF BUT WHO TO KEEP
TOGETHER.
TIME WILL TELL IF YOU MADE THE
RIGHT DECISION.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
THE MERGE IS HERE.
THE GAME STARTS NOW.
Jeff: AND THE BEST-LAID
PLANS--
IM THE STRATEGIC MASTERMIND.
Jeff: ...OFTEN GO AWRY.
I HAVE YOUR BACK.
PEOPLE ARENT GOING TO SUSPECT
IT.
THERE IS A COUNTER-GOLIATH
INSURGENCY FORMING.
DAVID AND GOLIATH IS OVER.
WELL, THEY VOTE ME OUT AND I
DIDNT SEE IT COMING.
THEY PLAYED ME GOOD.
IM SUPER PISSED AT NICK BECAUSE
I DIDNT KNOW HE WAS A
FLIP-FLOPPER.
OF COURSE IT SUCKS TO LOSE, BUT
YOU WANT ME TO BE HONEST?
IM REALLY, REALLY UPSET THAT I
WILL HAVE TO SIT NEXT TO MISS
NATALIE EXPE REUNION AND I HAVE
TO GO WITH HER RIGHT NOW TO THE
PONDEROSA.