[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: ITS THE "SURVIVOR:
DAVID VS. GOLIATH" REUNION SHOW.
NICK HAS JUST WON "SURVIVORS"
37th SEASON.
YOU KNOW, WE COULDNT REALLY
GUESS THAT WE COULD HAVE A MORE
PERFECT SEASON FOR YOU TO END UP
AS WINNER.
THIS DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH IDEA,
YOU COME FROM A SMALL TOWN IN
KENTUCKY, HUMBLE BEGINNINGS,
THERES BEEN TRAGEDY IN YOU
FAMILY, AND YET IT SEEMED LIKE
DURING THE SHOW ALL THOSE THINGS
THAT HELPED MOLD YOU AND RAISE
YOU WERE ACTUALLY THE SKILLS
THAT HELPED YOU WIN.
DID YOU SEE THAT EVOLVING.
YES, I THINK I DID.
AND, YOU KNOW, I TRIED TO GET ON
THE SHOW FOR SO MANY YEARS, SO
WHEN WE WERE SITTING ON THE
BARGE AND THEY DROPPED THE THING
AND THEY SAID, DAVID VERSUS
GRIET, IM THINKING, THIS IS THE
SEASON I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE ON.
IT FELT LIKE FATE.
ALL THOSE THINGS THAT I GUESS
MADE THE HUMBLE BEGINNINGS YOU
CALL THEM, THEY DID HELP IN THE
GAME.
Jeff: I KNOW FROM TALKING
TO YOU, YOU HAD A PERSONAL
DEBATE, DO I LEAVE THE SMALL
TOWN AND GO TO THE BIG CITY AND
HAVE A BIG CAREER OR STAY IN THE
SMALL TOWN AND TRY TO HELP THE
PEOPLE, MY COMMUNITY.
DOES THE $1 MILLION IMPACT THAT
DECISION?
I THINK SO, AND, YOU KNOW, I
WANTED TO BE A LAWYER BECAUSE I
WANTED TO BE RICH BECAUSE OF THE
WAY I GREW UP.
BUT THEN SOMETHING CHANGED FOR
ME WHERE I FELT LIKE I HAD A
CALLING INSTEAD OF A CAREER.
SO I WENT AND FINALLY MADE IT
BACK HOME TO HELP PEOPLE.
NOW I FEEL LIKE IF MONEY IS NOT
AN OPTION, I DONT HAVE TO TRY
TROY TO WORK FOR A BIG FIRM AND
STAY AT HEM AND DO WHAT I FEEL
LIKE ITS MY CALLING TO DO.
A TRUE DAVID.
Jeff: THANKS, JEFF.
MIKE, IN SOME WAYS YOURE
KIND OF THE POLAR OPPOSITE.
I MEAN, COMING INTO THIS
GAME,... WELL, MEANING THIS, YOU
HAVE A REALLY BIG, SUCCESSFUL
CAREER, WHICH IS TOUGH TO DO IN
ANY FIELD, ESPECIALLY IN
HOLLYWOOD.
AND YOU HAVE TURNED DOWN A JOB
TO COME PLAY THIS GAME.
WHAT WAS THE DRAW OF "SURVIVOR"?
I THINK AS A WRITER YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU DONT WANT TO SPEND
YOUR WHOLE LIFE JUST OBSERVING
LIFE.
YOU WANT TO JUST LIVE IT, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
FOR ME, I DONT WANT THE SPEND
ALL MY CREATE DIFFICULT ON MY
WORK.
I WANT TO SPEND IT TOWARD
LIVING, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
EVEN IF IT MEANS EMBARRASSING
YOURSELF FROM FRONT OF MILLIONS
OF PEOPLE.
IT FEELS LIKE YOU HAVE TO TAKE A
CHANCE AND LIVE THE ADVENTURE
AND, YOU KNOW, GET OFF... GET
AWAY FROM YOUR COMPUTER.
Jeff: SO A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE THAT FEELING WHEN THEYRE
OUT ON THE ISLAND.
IM ALWAYS GOING TO BE LIKE
THIS.
IM GOING TO TAKE THIS BACK TO
MY REAL LIFE.
SO WHEN YOU COME BACK TO THE
PRESSURES OF HOLLYWOOD OR THE
ANXIETY OF A CELL PHONE, WERE
YOU ABLE, HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO
MOLD THIS INTO YOUR LIFE?
I FEEL LIKE I WILL.
I FEEL LIKE WHAT I LEARNED ON
"SURVIVOR" I WILL
DEFINITELY --LY KEEP CHASING THE
ADVENTURE AND ALSO CHASING THESE
PEOPLE HOPEFULLY.
Jeff: ANGELINA, LETS COME
DOWN TO YOU.
YEAH.
Jeff: WE HAVENT HAD
ANYBODY AS POLARIZING AS YOU IN
A WHILE.
YOU KNOW, I FELT FOR YOU
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW EVERYBODY...
THE WORLD KNOWS HOW BRUTAL
SOCIAL MEDIA CAN BE.
SO LETS TART THERE.
HOW HAVE YOU HANDLED ALL THE
CRITICISM THAT CAME YOUR WAY.
YEAH, SO, TO BE HONEST, IN
REAL LIFE IM NOT POLARIZING,
BUT ON "SURVIVOR" YOU ARE JUST
WITH YOUR ESSENTIAL GOODS.
THERE IS A PART OF ME, THERE IS
A BIG SIDE OF ME THAT IS
AGGRESSIVE AND CONFIDENT AND
OUTSPOKEN.
I REALLY LEAKED INTO THAT SIDE
OF MYSELF FOR THE GAME BECAUSE I
WANTED TO JUST PLAY WITH MY
HEART OUT.
I WANTED TO GO FULL STEAM FROM
THE BEGINNING, AND THATS WHAT I
DID.
THATS THE GAME I PLAYED.
I CAN BE PROUD OF THAT.
THAT BEING SAID, LIKE YOU
RECOGNIZED, THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT
THERE WHO DONT LIKE TO SEE
THAT.
AND I THINK THAT WERE IN A
REALLY UNIQUE POINT IN TIME
WHERE WOMEN ARE FINDING OUR
VOICE AND WE ARE SPEAKING UP,
AND I AM SO PROUD.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
IM SO... ITS BEEN AN HONOR TO
BE ON THE SHOW AN REPRESENT,
THAT BECAUSE THERE ARE MANY MORE
OF ME MANY THIS COUNTRY.
I THINK TIMES ARE CHANGING.
Jeff: LETS DIG A LITTLE
DEEPER.
I AGREE WITH YOU.
I THINK THAT IF A MAN HAD PLAYED
THE EXACT SAME GAME YOU PLAYED,
WE WOULD HAVE LABELED HIM OR
COMMENTED ON HIM VERY
DIFFERENTLY, 100%.
YOU PLAYED AN AGGRESSIVE, SMART
GAME.
YOU WENT FOR IT.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: BUT NOW LETS GO INTO
THE PART WHERE I HEARD PEOPLE,
LIKE BRINGING UP THE RICE OR THE
LADDER THAT WAS 100 FEET IN THE
AIR, THAT WAS ABOUT EIGHT.
I CLIMBED ABOUT 50.
Jeff: OKAY.
FAIR ENOUGH.
I DONT KNOW HOW YOU GET 50 FROM
AN EIGHT-FOOT RADDER.
BECAUSE I WENT TO THE TOP OF
THE WATERFALL.
Jeff: LET ME REMIND YOU OF
ONE OF MY FAVORITE MOMENTS.
LETS LOOK BACK EARLIER IN THE
SEASON.
IS THERE ANY WAY I COULD HAVE
YOUR JACKET?
NATALIE?
Jeff: NATALIE, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
NATALIE.
ITS TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
NOTHING.
Jeff: SO MY QUESTION WITH
THAT IS, GIVEN THAT YOU ARE A
STRONG WOMAN AND SHOULDNT BACK
DOWN FROM THAT, WAS THERE ANY
SELF-AWARENESS WHEN YOU WATCHED,
MAYBE I PUSHED THE RICE ISSUE A
LITTLE MUCH.
LOOK, NO ONE LAUGHED HARD AT
JACKET-GATE OR THE RICE
SITUATION THAN MYSELF.
I WAS LIKE, PLEASE STOP ASKING
ME SO MANY TIMES, LET NATALIE
GO, LET THE RICE GO.
SO YOU HAVE TO JUST HAVE A GOOD
SENSE OF HUMOR ABOUT IT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IN THE MOMENT IT
WAS LIKE, YOU FEEL THE
CREATIVITY, YOU FEEL THE
ADRENALINE, AND YOU JUST LEAN
IN.
IF I WERE TO PLAY AGAIN, I CAN
SEE SOME THINGS I COULD TWEAK
FOR SURE.
Jeff: OKAY.
BEFORE WE GO TO BREAK, TAKE ME
BACK TO THIS MOMENT.
WERE AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU PLAYED THE IDOL.
THERES NO MORE SECURITY YOU CAN
HAVE IN THE GAME.
AND THEN YOU SEE ME DO SOMETHING
UNUSUAL, REACH BACK INTO THE URN
TO PULL OUT THIS ROUND, ODD
DISK.
IT WAS ODD.
?OO WHAT WERE YOU THINKING IN
THAT MOMENT WHEN YOU KNEW
SOMETHING IS AWRY.
FIRST THING I THOUGHT OF WAS
I KNEW IT WAS MY TIME.
YEP, IM DONE.
THERES SOME LOOP, SOME CRAZY
SOMETHING GOING ON HERE.
I WAS HEARTBROKEN, MAN.
AND THEN I WENT IN FULL-ON
SHOCK.
I DONT EVEN REMEMBER YOU
SNUFFING MY TORCH.
Jeff: YOU WERE PART OF AN
HISTORIC MOMENT.
ITS SUCH AN HONOR UPON TART
OF THE HISTORY OF THE GAME.
ITS A BIG DEAL.
Jeff: YOU WERE PART OF THE
GAME IN AN HISTORIC GAME BECAUSE
THE GUY NEXT TO YOU CARL PLAYED
IT PERFECTLY.
AND THATS WHY YOU WERE ON THE
JURY, AS WELL.
UP NEXT, CHRISTIAN WAS ONE OF
THE BIGGEST UNDERDOGS AND ONE OF
THE MOST POPULAR PLAYERS OF THE
SEASON.
DID HIS FRIENDSHIP WITH GABBY
SURVIVE THE BETRAYAL?
AND NATALIE IS NOT HAPPY ABOUT
HOW SHE WAS PORTRAYED.
WERE GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
THE "SURVIVOR" REUNION SHOW
CONTINUES RIGHT AFTER THIS.
Jeff: WELCOME BACK TO
"SURVIVOR: DAVID VS. GOLIATH"
LIVE REUNION SHOW.
CHRISTIAN, SO YOU PLAY THIS GAME
AND YOU BECOME A BIG THREAT AND
ITS CLEAR THAT YOURE BECOMING
LIKABLE AND COULD WIN THE GAME.
BUT IN THE BEGINNING THAT FIRST
DAY, THERE HAD TO BE A BIG FEAR.
WHAT WAS THE BIGGEST FEAR FOR
YOU?
WELL, EARLY ON THE BIGGEST
FEAR IS I WOULD HIT THE BEACH
AND I WOULD BE OSTRACIZED.
I KNOW I WALK AND TALK A LITTLE
DIFFERENTLY THAN MOST PEOPLE.
I USE WORDS PEOPLE DONT
TYPICALLY USE, HYPOTHESIS AND
ALSO RITS UMS BEING CHIEF AMONG
THEM.
I DIDNT KNOW.
ITS FINE AT MY ENGINEERING
DEPARTMENT AT HOME.
I DIDNT KNOW HOW IT WOULD FLY
WITH THE MAYOR OF SLAMTOWN OR
CARL THE TRUCKER, BUT IT TURNS
OUT REALLY WELL.
I GAINED SOME CONFIDENCE AND
STEAM THROUGHOUT THE GAME.
Jeff: I THINK YOU WERE ONE
OF THE BEST EXAMPLES OF IN LIFE
SOMETIMES THESE THINGS THAT WE
THINK OF AS LIABILITIES CAN
BECOME ASSETS DEPENDING ON THE
SITUATION, LIKE THE FIVE-HOUR
CHALLENGE WHERE ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOUR ABILITY TO TALK FOREVER
BECAME THIS -- THAT WAS A VERY
CONSCIOUS DECISION ON YOUR PART,
RIGHT?
INDEED IT WAS.
ALSO I NOTICE WHEN I TALK I FEEL
IN PAIN, WHICH IS A NICE SKILL
TO HAVE IN A VERY SPECIFIC SET
OF CIRCUMSTANCES.
AND, TWO YOU KNOW, I HAD YOU
RIGHT THERE.
YOU KNOW, I REALIZED I COULD
TALK TO YOU.
I HAD YOU HELD CAPTIVE FOR SIX
HOURS.
PEOPLE WOULD PAY GOOD MONEY 20
TALK TO YOU FOR THAT LONG, SO
WHY NOT DO IT.
Jeff: WHATS THE BIG
TAKEAWAY?
WHATS THE ANALOGY FOR YOU
PLAYING "SURVIVOR"?
SO, YOU KNOW, "SURVIVOR" IN A
LOT OF WAYS LIKE YOUR
FIRST-EVERY DAY OF SCHOOL WHERE
YOU THINK YOU MIGHT KNOW WHAT
ITS GOING TO BE LIKE, BUT WHEN
YOU SHOW UP IN THE DOOR, THE
DOOR CLOSES BEHIND YOU, THERE
ARE KIDS RUNNING AROUND
EVERYWHERE, YOU REALIZE, I KNOW
NOTHING.
YOUR GAME PLAY GOES OUT THE
WINDOW.
YOU NOTICE THE THINGS YOU
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE GOOD AT
MAYBE ARE YOUR WEAKNESS, BUT
MAYBE THE THINGS YOU THOUGHT
WERE YOUR WEAKNESSES OR ARE YOUR
STRENGTHS.
OR YOUR FRIENDS YOU THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT HAVE, YOU MIGHT FIND
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT FRIENDS
LIKE THE BROCHACHOS.
Jeff: SO DONT LIMIT
YOURSELF.
DONT LIMIT YOURSELF.
YOU MIGHT BE SURPRISED WHAT YOU
CAN DO IF YOU DONT PUT YOURSELF
IN A BOX AND SPREAD YOUR WINGS.
Jeff: NICELY SAID.
GABBY, YOU GUYS HAD ONE OF THE
MOST-TALKED-ABOUT FRIENDSHIPS
EVER ON "SURVIVOR," AND THEN YOU
TURN AND BETRAY EACH OTHER.
DID IT SURVIVE.
YEAH, PRETTY MUCH AS SOON AS
I WAS VOTED OUT I WAS ROOTING
FOR CHRISTIAN TO WIN AND I WAS
SORRY WHEN HE WAS VOTED OUT, BUT
WE ARE FRIENDS.
Jeff: GOOD TO HERE.
NATALIE, I HEARD FROM OUR
PRODUCERS THAT YOU ARE NOT HAPPY
ABOUT HOW YOU WERE PORTRAYED.
SO BRING IT TO ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DISPLEASED ABOUT.
JEFF, JEFF, JEFF.
I WAS PORTRAYED AS LAZY,
CONFRONTATIONAL, PROBABLY THE
WORST PLAYER EVER, BOSSY.
I OWN THAT ONE.
AND I DIDNT REALLY GET TO SHOW
WHO I REALLY AM.
AND SO I THOUGHT WHY AM I BEING
PORTRAYED IN SUCH AN UGLY WAY.
I AM SUCH A FAN OF THE SHOW.
I LOVE THE SHOW, AND THEREFORE
WHEN I STARTED TO SEE IT AIR, I
COULDNT REALLY CELEBRATE BEING
ON THE SHOW.
Jeff: WELL, IM BEING
HONEST NOW, THAT HURTS MY HEART,
BECAUSE --
IT HURTS MY HEART, TOO, JEFF.
Jeff: NUMBER ONE, NATALIE,
I LIKED YOU ON THE SHOW.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE FANTASTIC AT
TRIBAL BECAUSE YOU HAVE AN
OPINION.
YOU WERE WILLING TO SAY WHAT YOU
FELT.
BUT IM GOING TO BE HONEST, THE
WAY I EXPERIENCED YOU AT TRIBAL
IS EXACTLY HOW I SAW IT ON THE
SHOW, AS WELL.
SO LETS JUST -- RISKY MOVE
HERE, BUP LETS JUST SEE.
I MAY REGRET THIS QUESTION.
DOES ANYBODY ELSE HERE FEEL WE
JUST COMPLETELY GOT IT WRONG
WITH YOU, WITH YOUR STORY?
WHAT?
Jeff: OKAY.
THEYRE LYING, JEFF.
Jeff: NATALIE, MAYBE YOURE
THE ONLY ONE.
MAYBE WE WERENT ABLE TO --
CAN I RESPOND TO THAT VERY
QUICKLY?
Jeff: YES.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL I WAS IN
THE HOT SEAT, SO WHAT YOU SAW AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS WHERE I NEEDED
TO BE, BECAUSE I WAS ALWAYS ON
THE DEFENSE.
I WAS THE PERSON THAT THEY
WANTED TO TAKE OUT NIGHT ONE.
SO MY WHOLE GAME WAS ABOUT
SURVIVING, NOT BEING VOTED OUT
FIRST, AND I WAS COMMITTED TO
THE TO BE FIRST GOLIATH TO GO
OUT.
SO WHAT YOU SAW AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL WAS ME BEING VERY
AGGRESSIVE, VERY ASSERTIVE AND
TRYING TO STAY IN THE GAME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE DIDNT SEE ALL THE
FLAVORS(
ANYBODY WHO MIGHT QUESTION THE
REALNESS, I THINK THIS SHOWS IT
IS REAL, VERY TRANSPARENT, WE
ALWAYS WANT TO BE HONEST, HERES
ANOTHER SOMETHING THAT SPEAKS TO
THAT.
HERE IS THE WEIGHT LOSS WE HAD
THIS YEAR.
JUST TO SHOW YOU HOW HARD IT IS
TO LIVE ON RICE.
KARA LOST 26 POUNDS.
DAN LOST 26 MORE POUNDS.
ALISON LOST 27 POUNDS.
AND DAVIE LOST 36 POUNDS.
AND WHATS CRAZY IS NOBODY CAME
CLOSE TO THE RECORD THAT THIS
GUY SET BACK IN OUR THIRD
SEASON, THATS BIG TOM BAKK IN
2001.
HE WOULD GO ON TO LOSE NEARLY 80
POUNDS.
AND IF YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS AFTER A PLAYER IS VOTED
OUT, CHECK OUT OUR PONDEROSA
EPISODES.
THEY LIVE ONLINE.
THEYRE REALLY COOL.
GREAT STUFF IF YOURE A
"SURVIVOR" FAN.
WELL TAKE QUICK BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WELL SEE HOW
PAT IS DOING AFTER HIS MEDICAL
EVACUATION AND WERE GOING TO
TELL YOU WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS
DOING NEXT SEASON.
Jeff: WELL, THIS SEASON THE
PLAYERS HAD TO ENDURE SOME
REALLY TOUGH CONDITION,
INCLUDING TWO SIGH CLONES THAT
RESULTED IN US HAVING TO
EVACUATE THEM AND A FREAK
OCCURRENCE ON A BOAT LED TO A
VERY SCARY MOMENT FROM PAT.
YOU MIGHT REMEMBER THIS FROM
EPISODE ONE.
PAT WAS IN A LOT OF PAIN AND
ULTIMATELY HAD TO BE MEDICALLY
EVACUATED.
PAT, YOU LOOK GOOD RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL GREAT, JEFF.
Jeff: ARE YOU BACK?
IM READY TO GO BACK IF YOURE
READY FOR ME TO MAKE THE CALL.
Jeff: IM READY FOR YOU.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE, DID
YOU FEEL WHEN IT WAS ALL SAID
AND DONE THAT YOU WERE IN GOOD
HANDSIOUS BECAUSE ITS A
QUESTION I GET ALLOTTED.
YOURE VULNERABLE.
YOURE TRUSTING US TO TAKE CARE
OF YOU MEDICALLY.
JEFF, THE MEDICAL TEAM AND
EVERYBODY ON THE BEACH THAT DAY,
ITS TRULY HEARTWARMING TO KNOW
HOW MUCH YOU GUYS CARE ABOUT THE
CONTESTANTS.
ITS A GREAT FAMILY.
Jeff: GREAT.
GOOD.
LOVING HEARING THAT.
WELL, AS ONE SEASON ENDS,
ANOTHER BEGINS.
HERES WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS DOING
NEXT.
FOR OUR 38th SEASON, A NEW
GROUP OF PLAYERS WILL TAKE ON
THE GREATEST SOCIAL EXPERIMENT
EVER CREATED.
IF I WANT TO DO SOMETHING, I
JUST DO IT.
IM NOT GOING TO STAY HERE FOR
39 DAYS AND PLAY A BORING GAME.
I RATHER GET VOTED OFF IN A
BLAZE OF GLORY.
IM READY TO GO.
IM A MORNING NEWS ANCHOR IN
MACON, GEORGIA.
IM A HUGE FAN OF THE SHOW.
IM GOING TO COME INTO THE GAME
LIKE THE COOL MAN.
I WANT TO BREAK THROUGH THE
WALL.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: THEYLL BE JOINED BY
FOUR RETURNING PLAYERS.
THIS GAME WILL TAKE
EVERYTHING FROM YOU, BUT YOU
ALSO HAVE TO GIVE EVERYTHING TO
THE GAME.
THERE ARE ARCHETYPES LIKE ME
THAT PEOPLE SAY WILL NEVER WIN.
IM GOING THE PROVE THEM WRONG.
THIRD TIMES THE CHARM, BABY.
I KNOW HOW HARD THIS IS GOING
TO BE.
I CAN BE STARVING.
IT CAN BE POURING.
BUT IM HERE FOR THE WIN.
THATS WHAT I WANT.
LY NEVER QUIT.
I AM FREAKING DETERMINED.
Jeff: AND A NEW LAYER TO
THE GAME WILL PUSH THEM FURTHER
THAN EVER BEFORE.
WHERE IS MY GAME GOING TO GO
FROM HERE?
YOURE SEW ALONE.
I KEEP TELLING MYSELF, DONT
QUIT.
ITS JUST REALLY HARD.
I DONT KNOW IF I CAN DO
THIS.
IM NEVER GOING TO GIVE UP.
Jeff: ITS "SURVIVOR: EDGE
OF EXTINCTION" PREMIERING NEXT
SPRING.
WERE TAKING IT TO A WHOLE OTHER
LEVEL.
"EDGE OF EXTINCTION" PIERCE IN
THE SPRING.
BE RIGHT BACK.
Jeff: THERE THEY ARE.
DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH.
I HATE TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO THESE
GUYS.
ITS BEEN A REALLY FUN SEASON,
AND IF THIS IS SPEAKING TO YOUR
DREAM AND YOU WANT TO BE A
CONTESTANT ON "SURVIVOR," GO TO
CBS.COM/CASTING, AND IF YOU WANT
TO BID ON PROMISE FROM THIS
SEASON, GO TO
SURVIVORAUCTIONS.COM.
PROCEEDS TO GO TO "SURVIVOR"
STAND UP TO CANCER.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
THANKS FOR YOUR CONTINUED
LOYALTY.
WE WILL SEE YOU IN THE SPRING
FOR A GREAT SEASON.
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
GOOD NIGHT.
THANK YOU.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org