Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT THE VIBA TRIBE,
THE MEN FORMED A BOND.
THEYRE PART OF THE
BROCHACOS.
Jeff: AND SO DID THE WOMEN.
HEART AND HEADS.
Jeff: AT THE VUKU TRIBE, AN
ALLIANCE FELL APART.
I TRUST MY GUT.
ALEC BLINDSIDED ME.
THIS IS NOT SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: AND TENSIONS WERE
HIGH.
WE AINT GOT BUT TWO HOURS OF
DAYLIGHT LEFT.
I DONT LIKE STUPID PEOPLE.
THE JABENI TRIBE WAS FACING
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND THE ROCK
STAR ALLIANCE HELD ALL THE
POWER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS BEST FOR
US?
MY GUT SAYS LYRSA ONE MINUTE
AND ANGELINA THE NEXT MINUTE.
WE HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
NICK AND MIKE SENT LYRSA HOME.
LYRSA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
BYE, GUYS.
Jeff: 13 ARE LEFT WHOM WILL
BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
ITS A DELIGHTFUL MORNING,
GUYS.
LIFE IS BETTER WHEN YOU DONT
HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL.
WHATS GOING ON?
SOMEBODY IS WAVING AT US.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
SO WE ARE HAVING AN EXTREMELY
LAZY MORNING WHEN WE HEAR THE
ROARING OF A LITTLE BIT OF
MOTOR.
THEYRE COMING TO VIBA BEACH.
WE SPRINT OUT TO THE BEACH
AND I IMMEDIATELY CAN DETECT THE
VUKU TRIBE PULLING UP.
NEXT THING I KNOW THERE IS
ANOTHER BOAT.
AND ITS THE JABENI TRIBE.
IM THINKING, THIS IS THE MERGE.
THE GAME STARTS NOW.
TO ME I THINK THE MERGE
SIGNIFIES THAT YOU REALLY START
PLAYING STRICTLY FOR YOURSELF.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
OH, MY GOD.
SO IM GOING TO HAVE TO TRY
TO BUILD SOME DIFFERENT
RELATIONSHIP, BECAUSE I DONT
THINK THAT I WILL BE ABLE TO
TRUST JUST SIMPLY THE DAVIDS,
ESPECIALLY ELIZABETH.
SHE GETS UNDER MY SKIN, AND AT
THIS POINT, I WOULD BE WILLING
TO GET RID OF HER, BUT AS OF
RIGHT NOW I JUST WANT TO TASTE A
BEER, YOU KNOW?
OH, MY GOD.
CONGRATULATIONS, EVERYTHING
YOU NEED FOR A PERFECT MERGE IS
RIGHT HERE.
OH, MY DWUD.
LOOK AT ALL THIS.
THIS WHOLE TIME I HAVE BEEN
CONCERNED.
IVE BEEN LOSING MY GAME.
I LOOK AT THE TABLE AND THERE
HAS TO BE 100,000 CALORIES AT
LEAST.
I SEE EVERYTHING THAT I COULD
HOPE TO PUT IN MY FACE, AND I AM
ABOUT TO GO TO TOWN ON ALL THIS
DELICIOUS FOOD.
CONGRATULATION, EVERYONE.
ARE THOSE SWEET POTATOES?
OH, MY GOD.
SO EVERYONE IS ENJOYING THE
FEAST, BUT EVERYBODY IS ALSO
HERE TO PLAY THE GAME.
I FEEL PRETTY GOOD GOING INTO
THE MERGE WITH THE IDEA THAT
WERE GOING THE THEY TRUE TO OUR
OWN TRIBAL ALLIANCE, EVEN THOUGH
I REALLY GOT THE LIKE CHRISTIAN
A LOT WHEN WE WERE ON TRIBE VIBA
TOGETHER.
THE NUMBERS ARE 7-6, SO WE START
WHITTLING AWAY ALL THE OLD
DAVIDS AND THEN DO BATTLE LIKE
GENTLEMEN AND LADIES AT THE END.
GABBY, WILL YOU DATE ME IN.
ILL DOUBLE DATE YOU.
I KNOW TYPICALLY WITH THE MERGE
THERE IS SOME KIND OF IDOL
HIDDEN SOMEWHERE.
SOMETIMES YOU CAN FIND A CLUE AT
FEAST.
I NOTICE WE ALL HAVE INDIVIDUAL
NAPKIN HOLDERS, AND I WAS SUPER
CONSCIOUS OF WHAT IF THERE IS
SOMETHING IN IT, AND I ALSO
NOTICED THE SIGN THAT CAME WITH
THE TABLE THAT SAID, EVERYTHING
YOU NEED FOR THE MERGE IS RIGHT
HERE.
WELL, DOES THAT ALSO MEAN SOME
KIND OF ADVANTAGE?
I DONT KNOW.
BUT I DIDNT SEE ANYTHING HIDDEN
AT THE TABLE.
THIS COULD BE "SURVIVOR"
PARANOIA WHERE YOU LOOK FOR A
SIGN IN EVERYTHING WHERE THERES
NOT ONE.
THATS WHAT THEY TOLD ME
ABOUT NATALIA.
OF COURSE, I NEVER MET HER.
IVE SEEN HER IN TRIBAL.
I LOOK AT ALEC.
ALEC LOOKS AT DAVID, AND HE
GOES... LIKE THAT.
IT COMES TO LIGHT THAT ALEC
ORCHESTRATED A BLINDSIDE AGAINST
NATALIA, AND MY FIRST REACTION
IS SHOCK.
IM LIKE, DUDE, YOURE ON A
TRIBE WITH THE MAJORITY, AND IT
SEEMS LIKE A CARELESS AND
EMOTIONAL MOVE.
YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED?
ALEC DID THAT.
WAS SHE GOING NUTS?
I DONT KNOW, BECAUSE I NEVER
MET HER.
I WAS AT EXILE.
WOW.
THIS MEANS I MEAD TO TREAD
LIGHTLY WITH ALEC.
HES ALREADY SHOWN HOW QUICKLY
HELL FLIP.
AND SO ITS A DANGEROUS
SITUATION, BECAUSE THERE ARE SIX
DAVIDS AND THERE ARE SEVEN
GOLIATHS, IF ONE PERSON WANTS TO
FLIP, THEY CAN COMPLETELY CHANGE
THE GAME.
ALL RIGHT, YALL.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
TRIBE NAME.
OKAY, OKAY.
SO I STARTED DOODLING WORDS.
AND I LIKE KALO KALO, WHICH
MEANT STARS.
IM DOWN FOR THE GOOD VIBES.
SHE KNOWS EVERYTHING.
IF YOU SAY SOMETHING... SHES SO
ANNOYING.
CARL IS DRUNK, AND HES
TELLING ME THAT HES ANNOYED
WITH ELIZABETH.
SHE DOESNT NECESSARILY FIT IN,
AND IM ALL ON BOARD.
I THINK SHES NUMBER-ONE OUT.
PRIORITY NUMBER ONE IS TO
TAKE OUT A DAVID.
SHE HAS TO GO.
I CANT TAKE HER MUCH LONGER.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS, SO WE
NEED TO TAKE THE DAVID TRIBE OUT
WHILE WE STILL CAN AND KEEP US
GOLIATH STRONG.
ALL RIGHT.
SO FIRST OFF, MASON.
IVE BEEN WAITING.
I WANT THE TALK AND THEN GET
BACK.
IM SO DPLD YOU SURVIVED ALL
THOSE VOTES.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I AM SO GLAD THAT MY PAL, THE
MASON TO MY DIXON, KENTUCKY NICK
IS STILL IN THE GAME.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
YOU PROMISE YOU WONT TELL
NOBODY?
I THINK DAN HAS ONE.
HE GAVE ME ACTUAL ACTIONABLE
INTELLIGENCE.
HE THINKS THAT DAN HAS AN IDOL.
THAT IS A PIECE OF WOOD.
THATS A HUGE PIECE OF
INFORMATION.
YEAH, WERE NUMBER ONE.
OKAY.
YEAH, DUDE.
HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE.
THATS AWESOME.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
I WAS LIKE, I NEED MY COMFORT
BLANKET.
I NEED MY PERSON WHO MAKES ME
FEEL BETTER.
REUNITING WITH KARA WAS AWESOME.
IT WAS SO NICE TO SEE HER.
WE JUMP RIGHT BACK IN THE SWING
OF THINGS.
I FOUND ANOTHER IDOL.
NO, YOU DIDNT?
YOURE THE ONLY PERSON IVE
TOLD.
REALLY?
I TOLD HER THAT I FOUND A
SECOND IDOL.
I PLANNED ON KEEPING THAT ONE
ALL TO MYSELF, BUT I WAS JUST SO
EXCITED TO SEE HER, I CANT HELP
IT.
AND IM THE ONLY ONE WHO
KNOWS?
DAN SHARES WITH ME ON THE
BEACH THAT HE NOW HAS FOUND
ANOTHER IMMUNITY IDOL, SO IM
FEELING GOOD.
WEVE GOT TWO FREAKING IDOLS.
THE MAJORITY ALLIANCE, WEVE GOT
THE GOLDEN TICKET.
JUST KEEP IT GOING.
JUST DONT MESS THIS UP.
LETS GET EVERYONE ELSE OUT
EXCEPT FOR US.
WE REALLY HAVE EACH OTHERS
BACKS IF ANYTHING HAPPENS, IF
ANYTHING POPS UP.
WERE THE MOST UNIFIED GROUP.
I THINK WE KEEP GETTING
DAVIDS OUT.
SO WHO IS FIRST?
ELIZABETH.
IM WITH YOU 100%.
LETS GET HER OUT OF HERE.
GOLIATH HAS A MAJORITY RIGHT.
NOWLY RIDE THAT WAVE AS LONG AS
THAT WAVE IS STABLE.
I LIKE CHRISTIAN.
YOU CANT LET HIM LURE YOU
IN.
HE HAS TO GO EARLY.
I THINK WE HAVE TO BLINDSIDE
HIM WHEN WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
I WOULD LOVE TO USE THE
NUMBERS TO TAKE OUT THE BIGGEST
DAVID THREAT.
WE HAVE OUR FIVE.
THIS IS LIKE REWARD, IMMUNITY,
REWARD, IMMUNITY.
THE OLD GOLIATH TRIBE.
IM WITH YOU GUYS FOR SURE, BUT
YOURE NOW EVE TO THINK GOING
ENTER A MERGE THAT THINGS ARE
GOING TO STAY DAVID AND GOLIATH,
SO ITS LIKE KEEP DOING YOUR
THING AND THINK YOURE GOLIATH
STRONG AND ILL JUMP ON BOARD
WITH THE DAVIDS.
ILL FORM THOSE CONNECTIONS.
BRO, I WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU.
IM CLOSE WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE.
THE THING IS I DONT KNOW WHO
IS GOING TO GO HOME, BUT WHAT I
DO KNOW IF WE CAN TRUST EACH
OTHER NOW, AND IF WE CAN LIKE
FORM THIS UNLIKELY RELATIONSHIP,
LIKE YOU AND ME, RIGHT, AND
WHOEVER ELSE, LIKE DUDE, IF I
HAVE YOUR BACK, LIKE PEOPLE
ARENT GOING TO SUSPECT IT.
SO WHAT YOURE SAYING IS THIS
SHOULD BE A LINE OF
COMMUNICATION THAT WE SHOULD
NURTURE BUT ON THE DOWN LOW.
100%, 100%.
IM TOTALLY ON BOARD WITH
THAT.
ITS THE MERGE.
I THINK WE WILL SEE ALLIANCES
BREAK.
THERE WILL BE TEARS SHED.
THERE WILL BE BLINDSIDES.
THERE WILL BE IDOLS FLUSHED.
ITS MY TIME TO SHINE RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE SERIOUS RESERVATIONS
ABOUT DAN AND KARA, BECAUSE I
WAS SLEEPING TWO PEOPLE AWAY,
AND HER AND DAN WERE WHISPERING
FOR ABOUT TWO HOURS.
THAT SEEMS LIKE A POTENTIAL
TWOSOME.
WHETHER OR NOT THERES ANYTHING
ROMANTIC OR NOT, THATS PRETTY
MUCH IRRELEVANT, THEYRE TWO
CLOSE PEOPLE.
THATS A THREAT TO ME.
I WANT SOME COFFEE.
I NEED A SOY LATTE STAT.
GETTING TO THE MERGE, MY
STRATEGY FROM THE BEGINNING IS
TO FIGURE OUT WHO I CAN WORK
WITH AMONGST THE DAVIDS AND WHO
PUNKS THE GOLIATHS I STILL FEEL
LIKE I CONNECT WITH.
ALISON, I STILL THINK SHES
COOL.
I LIKE ALEC.
THE THREE OF US COULD WORK WELL
TOGETHER.
I CAME OVER FROM JABENI WITH
NICK.
MY HOPE WAS TO BE ABLE TO WORK
WITH ALEC AND ALISON AND BRING
NICK INTO THE FOLD.
WE KNOW THAT LIKE THE GOLIATHS
ARE GOING TO FALL APART AT SOME
POINT, AND I WANT TO HAVE A
SOLID SIX SO WE CAN MAKE SURE TO
MONOPOLIZE THE GAME.
WE GET DOWN TO 11, WE NEED
LIKE SIX.
US THREE, BUT WE NEED
NUMBERS.
THAT WAY --
WHO DO YOU THINK?
I DIG NICK AND CHRISTIAN AND
GABBY.
YOUVE COME TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR," AND THE GAME IN MY
OPINION DOESNT REALLY START
UNTIL THE MERGE HAPPENS.
PREMERGE YOURE AT LIKE THE
PREGAME, THE PREPARTY.
EVERYONE THE STILL GETTING
READY, DOING THEIR HAIR.
THEN YOU COME HERE, AND ITS 13
OF US, AND THIS IS LIKE THE
PARTY.
THIS IS WHAT EVERYONE
R.S.V.P.s FOR.
NOW YOU CAN PICK UP THE GIRLS,
THIS IS IT.
SO IM TIGHT WITH ALISON.
YEAH.
I DIG CHRISTIAN.
IM SO GLAD YOU LIKE
CHRISTIAN.
CHRISTIAN HAS BEEN MY PERSON
THROUGHOUT THIS.
I WAS TELLING CHRISTIAN, I
THINK DAVID AND GOLIATH IS SO
OVER.
I WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU.
I WANT TO PLAY WITH NICK,
ALISON.
I DIG MIKE.
YES, I LIKE MIKE A LOT, TOO.
THIS GAME ISNT ABOUT, YOU
KNOW, JUST NUMBERS, YOU HAVE TO
EARN THIS TITLE.
YOU HAVE TO FORM CONNECTIONS AND
BUILD RELATIONSHIPS.
THATS HOW YOURE GOING TO GET
FURTHER AND FURTHER IN THE GAME.
RIGHT NOW I NEED TO FOCUS ON WHO
DO I NEED TO TALK TO.
WE WANT TO WORK ACROSS
TRIBAL, WHICH MAKES SENSE
OBVIOUSLY.
I HAVE.
I DIG CHRISTIAN.
ALISON AND CHRISTIAN?
YEAH.
IT FEELS LIKE IT MIGHT MAKE
SENSE TO TAKE TWO DAVIDS OUT
EARLY ON.
I WAS GOING TO SAY,
ELIZABETH, RIGHT?
KEEP THOSE LIVES THAT ARE
LEFT TOTALLY IN THE DARK.
YEAH, YEAH.
I JUST WATCHED OUT ON THE
BEACH AND GOT INVITED INTO AN
ALLIANCE OF SIX, THATS GOOD
NEWS FOR ME.
THIS GETS ME FURTHER IN THE GAME
AND SO WITH MORE ALLIES, WHEN
THE GOLIATHS ARE READY TO TURN
ON EACH OTHER, IM GOING TO GET
FURTHER IN THE GAME.
I HAVE NEVER FELT THIS
EXCITED ABOUT THIS GROUP IM
WITH.
AT A TOP SUPERFICIAL VIEW,
THERE ARE SEVEN GOLIATH, SIX
DAVID, WHICH WOULD ORDINARILY
LOOK QUITE BAD FOR THE DAVIDS,
BUT RIGHT NOW THERE IS A
COUNTER-GOLIATH INSURGENCY
THATS FORMING, SIX PEOPLE,
THREE FORMER DAVID, THREE FORMER
GOLIATH, MYSELF, GABBY AND NICK
ON ONE SIDE.
AND ALISON, MIKE AND ALEC ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
ID CALL IT A STRIKE FORCE,
BECAUSE ALEC, HE IS READY TO
MOVE.
HES... A LOT OF PEOPLE TALK
ABOUT DAVID AND GOLIATH BEING
OVER, BUT ALEC WALKS THE WALK.
HE APPARENTLY FLIPPED THE
SCRIPTED AT THAT INFAMOUS VUKU
TRIBAL COUNCIL WHEN NATALIA WENT
HOME, SO ALEC IS SPEARHEADING
THIS STRIKE FORCE OF SIX, WHICH
AS FAR AS IM CONCERNED WILL BE
PARACHUTED IN TO SOME
BATTLEFIELD SOMEWHERE TO DEPLOY
A VOTE AND TAKE OUT A TARGET
WHEN WE SEE FIT.
THEY WERE TALKING FOR TWO
HOURS.
THEYRE A THREAT.
IF WE COULD KEEP THE DAVIDS
TOGETHER, THAT WOULD DEFINITELY
BE MY FIRST CHOICE, BUT WE ARE
OUTNUMBERED RIGHT NOW.
SO WE HAVE TO BE ABLE TO PULL
ONE TO MAKE THAT INITIAL VOTE
OFF.
ALEC VOTED OUT A GOLIATH WHEN WE
WERE AT THE VUKU BEACH.
SO I KNOW FOR SURE THAT HES HAD
MY BACK ONCE, MAYBE HELL HAVE
IT AGAIN.
IF WE CAN GET ALL THE DAVIDS TO
VOTE DAN, WOULD YOU VOTE DAN,
TOO?
LIKE FOR THE FIRST ONE?
YEAH.
THATS A GOOD IDEA.
HES A STRATEGIC PLAYER AND HES
GOT KARA IN HIS BACK POCKET.
ALEC WOULD BE THE ODD BALL
OUT.
I WOULD BE WITH A BUNCH OF
DAVIDS, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
ITS HARD.
LIKE SO MANY PEOPLE RIGHT NOW.
THINK ABOUT IT AND LET ME
KNOW.
ELIZABETH WANTS TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE, AND WITH MY NEW ALLIANCE,
THE IDEA IN THE FUTURE IS, YEAH,
WERE GOING TO TURN ON THE
GOLIATHS AND START PICKING THEM
OFF, BUT I NEED TO PLAY DOUBLE
AGENT AS LONG AS I CAN.
THERE YOU ARE.
JUST THE MAN I WAS LOOKING FOR.
I DONT WANT THE RUIN THAT
RIGHT NOW AND HAVE TO SHOW MY
CARDS THIS EARLY.
ELIZABETH GAVE ME HER PITCH.
SHE SAID, OH, YEAH, SHE WAS
WORRIED ABOUT YOU TWO.
SHES LIKE, DOES IT CONCERN YOU?
I WAS LIKE, DOES IT CONCERN YOU?
SHES LIKE, YEAH.
THEN SHE GOES, YEAH, I WANT TO
VOTE OUT DAN.
I DONT KNOW WHY MY NAME KEEPS
COMING UP.
I TOLD YOU.
WHY ME AND NOT JOHN?
I AM FURIOUS WHEN I HEAR THAT
ELIZABETH IS THROWING MY NAME
OUT THERE.
I DONT REALLY UNDERSTAND IT,
BECAUSE I AINT DONE ANYTHING
ASTRONOMICAL, SO WHY MY NAME IS
BEING THROWN OUT IS BEYOND ME.
DONT FREAK OUT.
YEAH, YOURE FINE.
IF I GO HOME, I GO HOME.
DAN SITTING PRETTY.
TWO IMMUNITY IDOL, THE MAJORITY
ALLIANCE TELLING HIM WHATS
GOING ON.
HE SHOULD FEEL LIKE KING OF THE
CASTLE.
SO INTERNALLY IM THINKING LIKE,
GET YOURSELF TOGETHER, SLAP
YOURSELF INTO SCHAAP.
IT COULD BE SO MUCH WORSE.
ITS JUST WHATEVER.
SCREW IT.
YOU WANT TO PUT MY NAME OUT,
THERE ILL SHOW YOU WHAT I CAN
DO.
SHES GOT TO GO.
DAN.
DAN!
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO YOUR FIRST
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, TAKE BACK
THE STATUTES.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY NO M.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS NOW WHAT
YOU COVET.
BEAUTIFUL.
Jeff: WITH THIS AROUND YOUR
NECK, YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT.
LETS GET TO IT.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO SWING A PENDULUM
THROUGH A FRAME AND AROUND A
STATUE.
IF AT ANY POINT YOUR PENDULUM
STOPS OR YOUR STATUE FALLS,
YOURE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE EIGHTH
PERSON VOTED AT OF "SURVIVOR:
DAVID VS. GOLIATH."
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY GRAB YOUR PENDULUM.
START SWINGING.
GIVE EVERYBODY A CHANCE TO GET
MOMENTUM.
ONCE EVERYBODY HAS MOMENTUM, THE
CHALLENGE WILL START.
QUIET IS A GOOD THING.
EVERYONE HAS MOMENTUM.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
ANOTHER UNIQUE CHALLENGE ON
"SURVIVOR," SOMETHING YOURE NOT
GOING TO BE PRACTICING IN YOUR
BACKYARD, BUT NOW YOURE CALLED
ON TO DO IT.
IF YOUR TACH CHEW DROPS, YOURE
OUT.
IF YOU FALL OFF, YOURE OUT.
IF YOUR PENDULUM STOPS MOVING,
YOURE OUT.
YOU CAN HIT THAT FRAME, JUST
KEEP YOUR MOMENTUM GOING, KEEP
THAT STATUE ON ITS PERCH.
MIKE LOSES MOMENTUM.
MIKE IS OUT.
FIRST ONE OUT OF THIS CHALLENGE.
MICHAEL TAKE A SPOT ON THE
BENCH.
THATS HOW FAST IT CAN GO.
WERE DOWN TO 12.
CHRISTIAN LOSES MOMENTUM.
CHRISTIAN IS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
THERES NO WIGGLE ROOM IN THIS
GAME.
SURVIVORS DO OR DIE EVERY DAY.
RIGHT NOW THE STATUE IS THE
LEAST OF THE WORRIES.
JUST KEEPING MOMENTUM IS HARD.
CARL NOW PLAYING IT.
CARL LOSES MOMENTUM.
CARL IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO TEN.
GABBY LOSES MOMENTUM.
GABBY IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WERE DOWN TO NINE.
ELIZABETH LOOKING GOOD.
JOHN LOOKS LOOK HES BEEN DOING
THIS FOR YEARS.
EVERY DAY I DO.
Jeff: JUST LIKE THAT KARA
LOSES MOMENTUM.
KARA IS OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WE ARE NOW DOWN TO EIGHT.
TEN MINUTES INTO THIS FIRST
ROUND.
AT 15 MINUTES YOU WILL SWITCH
HANDS, GOING IN THE SAME
DIRECTION, A LIVE SWITCH.
ALEC IS NOW PLAYING IT.
ALEC CLANGING.
HES OKAY.
DAVIE WITH A HICCUP BUT NICE
RECOVERY.
THAT CLANG IS THE DINNER BELL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHEN YOU BANG THAT FRAME, YOUVE
GOT TO KEEP YOUR PENDULUM MOVING
NICK DROPS HIS STATUE.
WERE DOWN TO SEVEN.
ALISON, ALEC, DAN, DAVIE, JOHN,
ELIZABETH, AND ANGELINA ALL
STILL FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE GETTING READY TO MOVE TO
THE NEXT PHASE OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
YOURE GOING TO SWITCH HANDS.
TIME TO START MAKING YOUR MOVE.
THREE, TWO, ONE, SWITCH HANDS.
DAVIE CANT MAKE THE TRANSITION.
HES OUT.
ANGELINA DROPS.
SHES OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE ALEC
DROPS HIS STATUE.
WERE DOWN TO FOUR.
JOHN STEPS OFF.
JOHN OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
WERE DOWN TO THREE.
ALISON, DAN, AND ELIZABETH.
ELIZABETH NOW CLANGING.
DAN DROPS HIS STATUE.
DAN NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WERE DOWN TO TWO.
ALISON VERSUS ELIZABETH, ONE
GOLIATH, ONE DAVID.
ONE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
THIS IS IT, A SHOWDOWN.
YOU CANNOT LOSE FOCUS, NOT THIS
FAR INTO THE CHALLENGE.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP GOING.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP SWINGING.
ELIZABETH OUT OF NOWHERE LOSES
MOMENTUM.
ALISON WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
GOOD JOB, ALISON.
Jeff: ALISON, COME ON OVER.
IM TRYING TO HUG YOU.
Jeff: HUG ME.
I LIKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, GIRL.
I NEEDED A NEW PIECE OF
JEWELRY.
Jeff: WHAT ARE YOU FEELING
RIGHT NOW IN BECAUSE I CAN FEEL
YOUR ENTIRE BODY IS JUST
PULSING.
IM LITERALLY IN ECSTASY.
ALL IM THINKING ABOUT IS WHEN
MY PARENTS AND MY FAMILY WATCH
THIS, HOW PROUD THEYRE GOING TO
BE.
[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: ALISON SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 20
TOUGH DAYS, SOMEBODY GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
IT WONT BE YOU.
CONGRATS.
THATS RIGHT.
Jeff: ELIZABETH NOT WINNING
WAS A BIG FACTOR.
ELIZABETH WAS THROWING OUT MY
NAME.
THAT MOUNTAIN HAWKS ME WANT --
THAT MAKES ME WANT TO GET HER
OUT OF HERE.
ON TOP OF US, IT WOULD BE STUPID
NOT TO GET A DAVID OUT.
ITS NOT HARD, NOT HARD AT ALL.
TO ME ELIZABETH IS NOT
NECESSARILY A THREAT.
LIKE MAYBE A LITTLE BIT.
SHES A MEDIUM THREAT.
SHE WAS ONE TODAY.
LET ME FINISH.
SO SHES A MEDIUM THREAT.
SHE DOESNT HAVE ANY ALLIES.
SHE DOESNT HAVE ANY SOCIAL
GRACES, SO WHY NOT USE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO BLIND SIDE THE
DAVIDS WHEN THEY THINK ITS
GOING TO BE ELIZABETH.
CHRISTIAN THE OTHER NIGHT, HES
THE BIGGEST THREAT ON THE
DAVIDS.
HES THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN BEAT
US PROBABLY ON THAT SIDE.
IT BREAKS MY HEART.
I LOVE THE GUY, BUT HE COULD
BEAT US ALL.
I DONT WANT TO SIT AROUND AND
WAIT FOR THE GAME TO COME TO ME.
I WANT TO TAKE OUT THE BIGGEST
THREAT RIGHT NOW.
AND THAT IS CHRISTIAN.
HES A GOLIATH IN HIS OWN RIGHT.
AND IM HOPING TO SWAY HIM AT
TONIGHTS TRIBAL.
IN MILITARY WARFARE, YOU
NEVER WANT YOUR ENEMY TO KNOW
WHEN YOURE GOING TO HIT.
ITS ALWAYS A BAD CALL.
THEY KNOW ITS ELIZABETH.
GIVEN THAT MY HUSBAND SERVED IN
THE MARINE CORPS, THE WAY THAT
IM ANGLING THE CONVERSATION TO
THE GOLIATH TRIBE IS REALLY
BASED OFF OF MILITARY TACK TUX.
IT KIND OF GETS THEM FIRED UP,
LUKE WERE GOING INTO BATTLE.
SO ITS INTENTIONAL LANGUAGE IM
USING TO GET MY TRIBE IN THE
GAME.
SO TONIGHT IM RALLY
DEPENDING ON OTHER GOLIATHS TO
EXECUTE MY VISION, OUR VISION,
AND TAKE OUT
THE
BIGGEST DAVID
IN THIS GAME.
IN THE CONTEXT OF THIS GAME
IT MAKES SENSE.
ANGELINA HAS THIS BRIGHT IDEA
THAT ELIZABETH ISNT THE BIGGEST
THREAT, THEREFORE SHE DOESNT
NEED TO GO, WELL, ME, IM TORN,
BECAUSE CHRISTIAN IS A
BROCHOCHO.
I LOVE THAT KID TO DEATH.
THE REAL THING THAT BUGS ME IS
SHES TALKING ALL THESE MILITARY
TERMS.
SORRY, YOURE NOT IN THE
MILITARY.
THAT MEANS YOU DONT KNOW JACK
SQUAT.
ITS EASY WHEN YOUR NAME IS NOT
BEING THROWN OUT, THERE BUT IF
WERE IN AN ALLIANCE AND WERE
GOING TO TAKE CARE OF EACH
OTHER.
CHRISTIAN AINT GOING TO WIN THE
NEXT NINE IMMOONITIES, WE CAN
TAKE HIM OUT.
HOW HARD IS THAT TO UNDERSTAND?
ITS BASIC.
THE STORY WERE SELLING THEM
IS THAT WERE SO PA -- THETIC
THAT WED RATHER TURN ON
OURSELVES, ANYONE BUT ME.
ACT LUCK WE DONT HAVE POWER.
ORIGINALLY I WAS FINE WITH
VOTING OFF ELIZABETH AS SORT OF
A SACRIFICIAL LAMB KNOWING THAT
AFTER THIS VOTE I HAVE PEOPLE
THAT WANT TO WORK WITH ME.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING DOWN
THERE?
TALKING.
BUT TO BE A DAVID AND FEEL
LIKE AN UNDERDOG AND TO SEE IT
PLAY OUT IN REAL TIME WHERE THE
GOLIATHS WALK UP AND DOWN THE
BEACH AND FEEL LIKE THEY HAVE
THEIR PICK OF THE LITTER OF WHO
THEY WANT TO TAKE OUT, ITS JUST
SO -- I WOULDNT EXPECT ANYTHING
LESS OF THE GOLIATHS.
ITS HARD TO FEEL LIKE YOUR
FATE IS IN SOMEBODY ELSES HAND.
ITS SO INFURIATING TO FEEL
LIKE AN UNDERDOG THIS WHOLE GAME
AND HAVE TO SIT THERE IN THE
SHELTER AND HOPE THAT ITS NOT
YOU.
THEY JUST GET SO SET IN THEIR
WAYS.
SHES NOT EVEN CONVINCING
EITHER.
THE THING IS KNOW ABOUT YOU
STRIKE FORCE.
YOU HAVE NO WHAT IDEA RIGHT NOW.
ANGELINA, THE MASTER
MANIPULATOR, SHE WANTS TO GET
OUT CHRISTIAN.
BUT I HAVE BUILT THIS LITTLE
SMALL ARMY OF THREE DAVIDS AND
THREE GOLIATHS, AND IF I WERE TO
VOTE OUT CHRISTIAN, I LOSE TRUST
NOW WITH NOT ONLY GABBY, NICK,
AND CHRISTIAN, BUT I LOSE TRUST
WITH ALL THE DAVIDS, BECAUSE IN
THEIR EYES IM JUST STICKING
WITH THE GOLIATHS AND THEN ITS
US AGAINST THEM.
WE CANT FLIP ON GABBY AND
CHRISTIAN.
WE STILL SOLID?
YES.
RIGHT NOW VOTING OUT
CHRISTIAN IS NOT BEST FOR MY
GAME.
HEAR ME OUT, IM SOLID.
JUST... IT MAKES ME NERVOUS THE
UNPREDICTABILITY, THEN
PREDICTABLE NATURE OF ELIZABETH.
WE SHOULD HAVE GOT ELIZABETH.
THEN WE DECIDED CHRISTIAN.
I FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD GET
ELIZABETH.
WE ALL FOUR WANT ELIZABETH.
I WANT ELIZABETH.
WE NEED TO CONVINCE WHO?
ANGELINA.
WHAT IF ANGELINA SAYS NO?
THEN ITS GOING TO BE --
I THINK WE NEED TO TALK TO
ANGELINA.
ILL TALK TO ANGELINA.
RIGHT NOW ITS BETTER TO GET
RID OF THE CHAOS.
I DISAGREE, BUT ILL GO WITH
THE GROUP.
ILL DO IT, BUT I DISAGREE.
ITS LIKE EXTREMELY FRUSTRATE
TOOK OBAMA RUSHED BY COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PLAN TO, HAVE DAN BE
SUPER CONTINUE SENDING.
I DONT APPRECIATE THAT.
SHES OVER THERE WHISPERING.
ITS NOT HER DECISION.
HE MAKES ME SUPER NERVOUS NOW.
NOW I DONT EVEN FEEL SAFE IN MY
OWN HOME, IN MY OWN LAND.
AND ITS SECOND DAY, THIRD DAY
OF THE MERGE.
AND HE SHOULD HAVE RECOGNIZED
THAT THIS IS PART OF THE
INHERENT RISK IN FLIP-FLOPPING
AGAIN WHEN YOUR GROUP ALREADY
MADE A DECISION.
RIGHT.
AND I WASNT EVEN THERE TO BE
PART OF THAT DECISION.
LIKE AT LEAST THE FIRST TIME WE
WERE ALL THERE AND SAID 100%.
I WAS TOLD WHAT THE DO.
THATS WHAT WERE TRYING TO
AVOID.
HEY.
WE SHOULD NOT BE TALKING.
ILL PROBABLY GET IN TROUBLE.
THEYRE THROWING YOUR NAME OUT
THERE.
BUT IM THE ONLY PERSON, I WANT
TO BE UP FRONT WITH YOU, BECAUSE
IVE GOT NOTHING BUT AMAZINGNESS
FROM YOU, AND I HAVE TRIED.
I THOUGHT I HAD A DIFFERENT
PLAN.
THEN THEY FLIPPED AGAIN.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
YOU HAVE A BIG HEART, AND I
JUST RESPECT YOU AS A PERSON.
I JUST DIDNT WANT THIS.
I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THAT MEANS
TO ME.
I JUST FIGURED THE MORE
INFORMATION.
I WOULD RATHER SEE YOU HERE
TOMORROW THAN SOME OF THESE
PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT.
IM GOING TO GO BACK.
NO, ITS OKAY.
IM GOOD.
ANGELINA CAME TO ME, SORRY IF I
START CRYING, BUT I CAME HERE TO
WIN "SURVIVOR."
I DIDNT COME HERE TO GET VOTED
OUT.
AND IM WILLING TO DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES, AND THAT INCLUDES
BETRAYING SOMEBODY.
THATS WHAT SHE TOLD YOU?
YEAH.
SHES IN THE LYING TO ME.
IS IT TRUE?
YES.
I AINT GOING TO GET MY
FEELINGS HURT BECAUSE ITS A
GAME.
TELL THE GOLIATHS THAT
ANGELINA IS TELLING THEIR PLAN
AND WE GET ANGELINA OUT.
YOU THINK THAT HIGH WORK?
I NEW THERE WOULD BE A
DAYLIGHT RIGHT NOW.
SO LETS DO IT TONIGHT,
RIGHT?
AND IM NOT GOING TO BACK DOWN,
BECAUSE I AM HERE TO WIN.
I AM HERE TO WIN "SURVIVOR."
I DID NOT COME HERE TO LEAVE
TONIGHT.
RIGHT?
SO ITS GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING TRIBAL COUNCIL.
Jeff: WOW.
HERE WE ARE.
ALISON, THE MERGE VOTE OFTEN
SETS THE TONE FOR THE BACK HALF
OF THE SEASON.
DO YOU SENSE THAT MIGHT BE THE
CASE WITH TONIGHTS VOTE?
I THANK GOD I HAVE THIS
AROUND MY NECK, BECAUSE BEFORE I
WAS ONLY HAVING TO MANAGE FOUR
OF MY OWN RELATIONSHIPS.
NOW IM MANAGING 12
RELATIONSHIPS AND IM HAVING THE
TAKE THE EXPOANT OF THAT AND IM
MANAGING A TON OF RELATIONSHIPS.
HOW MANY COMBINATIONS OF
RELATIONSHIPS DO YOU HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT?
144 IS THE NUMBER.
Jeff: THERE ARE SO MANY
POSSIBLE CONFIGURATIONS OF
PEOPLE.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU HAVE TO
NAVIGATE ALL THE TIME?
YEAH.
THERES SO MANY CONVERSATIONS
GOING ON.
YOU ARE TRYING TO KEEP
EVERYTHING IN LINE AND WERE
GOING TO SEE WHETHER AND NOT
ITS STILL DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH.
BUT EVERYTHING IS SHIFTED AND,
YEAH.
Jeff: INTERESTING PAUSE.
ANGELINA, DO YOU BELIEVE ITS
STILL DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH?
SORRY.
THAT WAS WAY TOO LONG OF A
PAUSE.
I THINK GOLIATHS WANT TO TAKE A
MORE CONSERVATIVE APPROACH
TODAY.
THEY WANT TO STAY UNITED.
ITS ONE THAT IM STANDING
BEHIND TODAY.
I DISAGREE.
THE GOLIATHS ARE CONVINCING
THEMSELVES OF THIS MIRAGE THAT
EVERYTHING IS FINE, WHEN ITS
NOT THE REALITY.
THE REALITY IS THAT THERES
FRACTURES.
I KNOW THAT THE GOLIATHS ARE
GOING TO BE VOTING FOR ME
TONIGHT.
ANGELINA TOLD ME TODAY ON THE
WATERFALL TRAIL THAT SHE WAS
GOING TO BE VOTING FOR ME.
I THINK GOLIATHS KNOW THAT THERE
IS A FRACTURE IN YOUR GROUP.
JUST TO JUMP IN HERE SINCE
THIS IS KIND OF -- LIKE THIS IS
JUST BAD STRATEGY.
WE HAD A CONVERSATION, AND I
JUST SAID SOME THINGS THAT WE
TALKED ABOUT --
YOU PROBABLY SHOULD ELABORATE
ON THAT IF YOU DONT WANT YOUR
TRIBE TO WORRY ABOUT WHAT "THESE
THINGS" ARE.
I WAS NON-COMMITTAL BECAUSE SHE
WAS HEARING LIES AND I COULDNT
LIE AT THAT POINT.
IT WAS A ROUGH AFTERNOON.
I THINK SHE WAS ALREADY
STARTING TO MANAGE THE JURY FOR
HER FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I AGREE.
THATS WHAT IT IS.
THATS WHAT SHE CAME TO ME.
SHE WANTED MY VOTE.
NOBODY ELSE TOLD ELIZABETH.
BECAUSE THEY WANT YOU TO
FLIP.
IM ASK YOU FOR AN ANSWER.
ALL I SAID WAS ITS STILL UP
IN THE AIR, AND SHE LOOKED AT ME
AND I SAID, I CANT ANSWER THAT.
ELIZABETH CAME TO US, THE
DAVIDS, AND SAID, "I JUST HEARD
IT WAS MY NAME."
SHE WAS TRYING TO GET MY JURY
VOTE AND I FELL LIKE YALL
DESERVE BETTER THAN THAT.
WERE AT 13 PEOPLE.
IM NOT THINKING THAT FAR AHEAD.
IM FOCUSING RIGHT NOW.
IM WITH GOLIATH.
I WAS NOT BACKSTABBING ANYONE.
THEYRE TRYING TO FRACTURE US.
GUYS...
ALISON, WALK ME THROUGH THE
MANAGING THE JURY.
THE JURY DOES BEGIN TONIGHT.
THE POWER IS GOING TO SHIFT,
AND THE PERSON THAT WE WRITE
DOWN TONIGHT IS GOING TO
DETERMINE IF WERE WORTHY OF $1
MILLION.
SO YOU CAN HAVE A HUMAN MOMENT
WITH SOMEONE AND SAY, I DIDNT
WANT IT TO BE THIS WAY, BUT ITS
GOING TO BE YOU, AND THEN YOUVE
POCKETED A VOTE.
BUT GABBY, THATS HOW GOOD
PLAYERS PLAY.
IF YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH IT, IT
COULD BE A $1 MILLION VOTE AT
THE END.
I THINK ANGELINA DID PROBABLY
WANT TO HAVE A HUMAN MOMENT WITH
ELIZABETH.
WHAT HURTS ME IS HOW THEY CAN
EXPECT IF SHE HEARS HER NAME TO
NOT WANT TO PLAY.
I FEEL LIKE ELIZABETH IS
BASICALLY TRYING TO THROW US A
LIFELINE AND TRYING TO POINT OUT
WHERE THERE MAY BE A FRACTURE.
IM SORRY THAT ITS YOU,
ANGELINA, BUT YOU CANT BE
INSULTED THAT ELIZABETH WANTS TO
PLAY.
IM NOT INSULTED WITH THE
PLAY, GABBY.
SHE WANTS TO HELP HER FORMER
TRIBE, BECAUSE THE FACT OF THE
MATTER IS WERE AT THE BOTTOM.
I CANT IMAGINE WHAT THAT
FEELS LIKE, WELL, I KIND OF CAN
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT BE
RIGHT THERE WITH YOU.
BUT THEYRE TRYING TO FRACTURE
US.
THEYRE USING ME TO TRY TO GET
THE NUMBERS BACK.
OBVIOUSLY YOU THINK WERE
GOING TO SIT HERE AND GET PICKED
OFF ONE BY ONE.
OBVIOUSLY!
I DONT FAULT YOU FOR IT, BUT
I AM CHECKING IN WITH MY TRIBE.
YOUR NAME IS NOT OUT THERE,
GABBY.
YOUR NAME IS NOT OUT THERE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT WEVE
BEEN AT THE BOTTOM THIS WHOLE
TIME SO WERE USED TO IT.
OKAY, THE STRUGGLE WAS REAL.
JABENI WAS AT THE BOTTOM, TOO, I
FEEL YOU GIRL.
I SHOULD HAVE JUST LIED, JEFF,
BECAUSE NOW ALL OF THIS IS
HAPPENING, BUT WHAT PEOPLE KNOW
ABOUT ME IS I AM AN AUTHENTIC
PERSON, AND THIS GAME IS HARD
FOR SOMEONE WHO IS TRYING TO BE
A LOVING PERSON BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TO CUT PEOPLE.
Jeff: BUT ANGELINA, WHETHER
YOU MEANT IT OR NOT IS A LITTLE
IRRELEVANT.
PEOPLE HAVE A PERCEPTION, SO HOW
DO YOU DEAL WITH THAT?
AGAIN, IT WAS NOT JURY
MANAGE.
IT WAS A RAW HUMAN MOMENT WHERE
I COULDNT LIE.
I APOLOGIZE TO MY TRIBE.
I WASNT TRYING TO BE SNEAKY.
YEAH, YOU WERE TRYING TO BE
SNEAKY.
I THINK THAT ITS IMPORTANT THAT
THE GOLIATHS KNOW THAT THERE ARE
FRACTURES.
Jeff: WHAT IS YOUR HOPE FOR
TONIGHT, ELIZABETH?
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THE
DAVIDS STICK TOGETHER WITH ONE
OR TWO GOLIATHS.
GOLIATH GOT HIS HEAD CHOPPED OFF
BECAUSE HE WAS AR GAPTD AND HE
THOUGHT HE HAD IT.
I FEEL LIKE THAT SAME ATTITUDE
IS GOING ON WITH THE GOLIATHS.
ARE YOU GOING TO DEAL WITH THE
FRACTURES NOW OR LATER?
IM HOPING ONE WERE TO PEOPLE
WILL JOIN THE DAVID SIDE.
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE THE DAVID
SIDE DOES WANT TO BE STRONG.
Jeff: ANGELINA, ARE YOU
CONCERNED THAT ELIZABETHS BIG
SWING MIGHT END UP HITTING YOU.
I SURE HOPE NOT, JEFF,
BECAUSE I FEEL REALLY STRONGLY
ABOUT THE ALLIANCE THAT IM IN.
IF I HAD ANY HESITATION TODAY TO
WRITE DOWN ELIZABETHS NAME, IT
IS ALL GONE NOW.
IM EXCITED TO GO VOTE FOR
ELIZABETH AND I HOPE THAT OUR
TEAM STAYS STRONG IN THAT
DECISION TO DO SO.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
CARL, YOURE UP.
SERIOUSLY.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU OUT.
I HOPE YOU GO HOME.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ONCE THE VOTES ARE READ, THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, ANGELINA.
ELIZABETH.
THATS THREE VOTES ELIZABETH,
ONE VOTE ANGELINA.
ELIZABETH.
THATS FOUR VOTES ELIZABETH.
THATS FIVE VOTES ELIZABETH.
ONE VOTE ANGELINA.
ELIZABETH.
SIX VOTES ELIZABETH.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ELIZABETH.
SEVEN, THATS ENOUGH, YOU NEED
TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WELL, JEFF, MIGUEL WAS TO
COME IN AND HAVE AND BE MYSELF,
AND I DID.
Jeff: WELL DONE.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
GOOD LUCK YOU GUYS.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
I REALLY DO.
SEE YOU, ELIZABETH.
FUNNY WAY OF SHOWING IT.
Jeff: WELL, DESPITE A
UNANIMOUS VOTE, ITS CLEAR FROM
TONIGHTS TRIBAL COUNCIL THAT
THIS GROUP OF 12 IS ANYTHING BUT
UNITED.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN TRUST DISSOLVE
DISSOLVES.
I FEEL MANIPULATED.
ANGELINA, YOU SLIMEBAL.
Jeff: AND BONDS CRUMBLE.
GABBY IS NOT TAKING THIS
ALLIANCE SERIOUSLY.
THATS A WEIRD THING TO SAY.
Jeff: NO ONE IS SAFE.
SO WE TAKE HIM OUT NEXT?
IT COULD BE A
#BROCHACHOBLINDSIDE.
WELL, I GOT VOTED OUT.
I DID WHAT I COULD.
IT FELL ON DEAF EARS, BUT I
CERTAINLY HOPE THAT SOME CRACKS
ARE BUILT IN THE GOLIATH TRIBE,
BECAUSE I WOULD REALLY LIKE TO
SEE A DAVID WIN THIS GAME.
I STILL LOVE "SURVIVOR" MORE
THAN I EVER HAVE IN MY LIFE AND
I STILL HAD A GREAT TIME