>> Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
GABBY AND CHRISTIAN VOTED OUT A
DAVID.
CARL, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
SHOCKING NICK, DAVIE, AND
ANGELINA.
EIGHT ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
>> WELL DONE, GUYS.
>> I KNEW YOU GUYS WERE LYING TO
ME.
>> LET ME TELL YOU, I WASN'T
LYING TO YOU.
>> DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ANYBODY.
>> NO, NO.
>> NEW YORK I'M SAYING, CARL WAS
THE GODFATHER.
>> I'M GLAD HE'S GONE.
>> TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS
A SHOCK TO ME.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY VOTED OUT
CARL, AND I WAS BLIND SIDED.
I DON'T GET IT TOO.
THEY'RE SO SMART THEY'RE DUMB.
LIKE WHAT KIND OF MOVE IS THAT?
TRY TO MAKE ME UNDERSTAND WHY
CARL HAD TO GO TONIGHT.
>> OKAY, HERE'S THE THING.
>> I SAVED YOU FROM GOING VOTED
OUT THE OTHER DAY.
WE USED THREE ADVANTAGES TO GET
THE MAJORITY, AN YOU JUST GAVE
IT TO THEM.
>> WE DIDN'T GIVE THEM ANYTHING.
>> I REGRET SAVING CHRISTIAN.
WE BURNED EVERY ADVANTAGE WE HAD
TO GET DAVID LEAD, AND NOW HE
DOES THIS AND DOESN'T EVEN TELL
ME THE VOTE.
I'M PRETTY MAD.
WE'RE GOING TO BE NEXT, DUDE.
>> HOW THE HELL IS THAT
POSSIBLE?
>> GABBY, SHE...
>> I REALLY DON'T THINK GABBY IS
GOING TO FLIP.
>> SHE JUST DID, DUDE.
>> HONESTLY, EVERYONE WANTS
ALISON OUT.
SHE REALLY IS NEXT
>> IN MY MIND, THE MASON-DIXON
ALLIANCE IS DEAD.
I'M STILL GOING THE PLAY IT UP,
BUT I'M GOING TO REMEMBER, THIS
AND AS SOON AS I GET THE CHANCE,
I WON'T HESITATE "THE BLIND TO B
CHRISTIAN.
Captioning funded by CBS
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
31 DAYS IS A LONG TIME TO BE
AWAY FROM HOME.
>> YES.
>> Jeff: I'M NOT GOING TO BURY
THE LEAD.
IT'S TIME FOR SOME LOVE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: DAVIE, YOU READY TO
SEE YOUR MOM?
>> OH, YES.
>> Jeff: HAZEL, COME ON OUT.
>> MAMA.
MOM!
>> OH.
>> Jeff: HAZEL, TELL ME ABOUT
DAVIE.
>> HE'S DAVIE CROCKETT FOR ONE
THING.
HE'S AN EXPLORER.
I WOULD BE IN MY HOUSE, WHERE IS
DAVIE?
HE'LL COME BACK WITH FROGS AND
SNAKES, SCARING THE DAYLIGHTS
OUT OF ME.
BUT ABOVE ALL OF THAT, HE'S SO
LOVING.
HE'S MY MOST LOVABLE KID.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
GIVE HIM A LAST HUG.
>> OH, I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: HAZEL, YOU CAN TAKE A
SPOT RIGHT UP HERE ON THE BENCH.
>> OH, GOD.
>> Jeff: ALISON, LET'S GET
YOUR MOM OUT HERE.
WILLA, COME ON OUT.
THAT IS SOME MOM LOVE RIGHT
THERE.
ALISON, IS "SURVIVOR" PART OF
THE FAMILY EXPERIENCE OR JUST
YOURS?
>> I'M LIVING MY FAMILY'S DREAM
RIGHT NOW 100%, AND HONESTLY THE
REASON I'M OUT HERE IS BECAUSE
OF MY MOM, TO TAKE A LEAP OF
FAITH AND GO ON AN ADVENTURE
LIKE THIS IS OUTSIDE OF MY
COMFORT ZONE, AND IT'S BECAUSE
OF HER THAT I KNEW I HAD THE
STRENGTH TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: GIVE HER LAST HUG.
>> OH, MY GOD, I LOVE YOU, MOM.
>> Jeff: KARA, YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE READY FOR SOME LOVE.
LET'S GET YOUR BROTHER OUT HERE.
ERIC, COME ON OUT.
>> COME HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Jeff: KARA, THE THING ABOUT
A BROTHER-SISTER RELATIONSHIP,
ONE OF YOU IS NOT THE PARENT.
IT'S A REALLY UNIQUE DYNAMIC IN
THE FAMILY.
>> I FEEL LIKE THE LIFE THAT
WE'VE LIVED TOGETHER IS LIKE THE
LIFE... IT'S SIMILAR TO
"SURVIVOR."
YOU CAN'T DESCRIBE IT, BUT IF
YOU'VE BEEN TO IT, IT BRINGS YOU
CLOSER THAN YOU COULD IMAGINE.
WE HIT BOTTOM OUT HERE, AN I'M
SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE I WANT TO
CONSIDER MY FRIENDS, BUT I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THEIR INTENTIONS ARE,
BUT TO SEE YOU, I KNOW YOU LOVE
ME.
>> I'M HERE FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: GIVE HER LAST BIG
HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH AND I'M SO
PROUD OF YOU.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NICK.
YOU READY TO GET YOUR DAD OUT
HERE?
JIM, COME ON OUT.
>> HI.
>> Jeff: NICK, ONE THING I
NOTICED THERE IS THAT THE LITTLE
BOY CAME OUT.
I MEAN, YOU'RE A GRUN MAN, BUT
YOU SAW YOUR DAD WALKING DOWN,
AND IT JUST... YOU CHANGED.
DID YOU FEEL THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY, AND THAT'S WHAT I
FELT OUT HERE.
I FEEL LIKE I DIDN'T ALWAYS
APPRECIATE HIM, AND, YOU KNOW,
GOING TO COLLEGE, MY FRIENDS
LIKE HAD THEIR DADS' CREDIT
CARDS AND DOVE THESE CARS AND
STUFF, AND I DIDN'T HAVE THAT.
I CALLED MY BROTHER ONE DAY, AND
I SAID, YOU KNOW, I BUSH WE HAD
MORE.
HE SAID, YOU DON'T REALIZE WHAT
DAD DOES FOR US UNTIL YOU HAVE
DONATED BLOOD THE BUY MILK FOR
FIVE KIDS, YOU DON'T REALIZE
WHAT THIS MAN HAS GONE THROUGH.
I JUST HAVE SO MUCH APPRECIATION
NOW FOR WHAT HE'S DONE FOR ME
AND ALL MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS
MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> IT AIN'T A MATTER ABOUT WHAT
YOU HAVE OR WHAT YOU DON'T HAVE,
IT'S ABOUT WHAT YOU GIVE, YOU
KNOW?
IT'S ABOUT THE LOVE.
>> Jeff: THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
GIVE HIM A LAST HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GETTING TO
LIVE YOUR DREAM.
AWESOME.
GABBY, YOU READY FOR SOME LOVE?
LET'S GET YOUR MOM OUT HERE.
ENCARNITA, COME OUT.
>> YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL, GIRL.
GABRIELLE.
>> Jeff: GABBY, CAN YOU FEEL
THE YOUNG WOMAN LET GO AND THE
LITTLE GIRL COME BACK, THAT THIS
IS MOM?
>> YEAH.
SHE ALWAYS SUPPORTS ME WHEN I'M
DOING MY WORRYING THING, WHICH
IS ALL THE TIME.
>> SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN TYPE A,
LIKE HER DAD, SO SHE CALLS ME
JUST TO CALM HER DOWN.
BUT SHE'S ALWAYS MY BABY.
SHE'S ALWAYS MY LITTLE GIRL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MOM, GIVE
HER SOME LAST LOVE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: ANGELINA, YOU READY
FOR SOME LOVE?
LET'S GET YOUR MOM OUT HERE.
ANNA, COME ON OUT.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: ANGELINA, I HEARD YOU
SAY "JUST LIKE YOU TAUGHT ME,"
WHAT IS THAT INDICATIVE OF?
>> MY MOM IS LITERALLY THE
STRONGEST WOMAN I KNOW.
SHE HAS FIVE KIDS SHE PUT EVERY
OUNCE OF LOVE INTO, AND I'M SO
LUCKY THAT I GET TO BE ONE OF
THEM, BECAUSE I WOULD NOT BE THE
WOMAN WITHOUT HER.
I SACRIFICED MYSELF FOR THE
TRIBE YESTERDAY.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DID.
>> YOU GOT A LOT OF LOVE.
>> Jeff: NOW MOM IS WORKING
THE GAME.
GIVE HER A LOT OF LOVE.
>> LOVE YOU, MOM.
>> ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
HERE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND JOSH.
COME ON OUT, JOSH.
>> THAT'S THE WAY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> Jeff: SO MIKE, TELL ME
ABOUT JOSH?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN TOGETHER?
>> SIX YEARS AND LIKE WE'RE
SUPER DIFFERENT, BUT WE'RE
BONDED LIKE IN A DEEP WAY, AND I
AM SO HAPPY TO SEE HIM, AND
STOKED.
>> Jeff: MIKE, AS A WRITER,
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THIS LOVED
ONE VISIT SO FAR?
EVERY RELATIONSHIP IS UNIQUE.
WHAT'S THE TAKEAWAY?
>> FOR ME AS SOMEONE WHO HAS
BEEN PLAYING THE GAME WITH THESE
PEOPLE, IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE I
JUST WANT TO APOLOGIZE FOR
ANYTHING I'VE EVER DONE OR SAID.
IT MAKES ME REALIZE HOW NOBODY
IS ALONE AND HOW EACH PERSON HAS
A NETWORK OF PEOPLE WHO LOVE
THEM AND YOU'RE NOT JUST
IMPACTING THEM.
YOU'RE IMPACTING A WHOLE WORLD
OF PEOPLE WHO ARE DECENT, GOOD
PEOPLE AND I HOPE IT DOESN'T
DESTROY MY GAME, BUT, WHATEVER
WILL BE WILL BE.
>> Jeff: GIVE SOME LAST LOVE,
JOSH.
>> THANK YOU FOR COMING.
I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN, YOU READY
FOR SOME LOVE?
>> I THINK SO, JEFF.
I'M READY.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET YOUR
GIRLFRIEND OUT HERE.
EMILY, COME ON OUT.
>> IT'S CRAZY, YOUR HAIR.
>> THIS IS MY NEW FRIEND JEFF.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU.
JEFF, THIS IS EMILY.
EMILY, JEFF.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> I LOOK LIKE A CRAZY MAN.
I JUST PULLED OUT OF THE FOREST.
>> Jeff: THERE'S THE HUG.
THERE IT IS.
SO CHRISTIAN, FIRST THING
EVERYBODY WANTS TO KNOW ABOUT
YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SO WE'VE GOTTEN TO
KNOW YOU.
SO TELL US ABOUT THIS WOMAN,
EMILY.
>> SHE IS THE MOST
SELF-SACRIFICING, KIND, FUNNY,
SMART WOMAN I'VE EVER MET.
AN HAVING SOMEONE WHO GETS YOU
AN REALLY UNDERSTANDS HOW YOU'RE
FEELING, EVEN BEFORE YOU FEEL
IT, YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHAT IS SO
PRECIOUS.
>> Jeff: GIVE HIM A LAST HUG,
EMILY.
MAKE IT A GOOD ONE.
IT MAY BE THE LAST ONE HE GETS.
>> SEE YOU SOON.
ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN, YOU'RE
EMOTIONS SEEM TO COME OUT AS
EMILY WAS LEAVING, AS YOU WERE
SAYING GOOD-BYE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: WHY IS IT HARD FOR
YOU TO LET THAT EMOTION OUT WHEN
SHE'S STANDING RIGHT NEXT TO
YOU.
>> SEEING HER IS GREAT, BUT
LOSING HER FEELS FAR WORSE.
IT'S EASY THE TAKE YOUR LOVE ONE
FOR GRANTED.
YOU SEE THEM EVERY DAY.
AND FOR ONCE A DAY I CAN LOOK AT
HER AN REMEMBER THAT MOMENT
WHERE SHE WALKED AWAY AND USE
THAT AS A REMINDER OF
APPRECIATING WHAT YOU HAVE.
AND I THINK THAT'S WHAT A LOT OF
US WANT TO COME AWAY FROM THIS
WITH IS THAT SOME KERNEL YOU CAN
TAKE AWAY FROM THE GAME THAT
CHANGES WHO WE ARE.
I THINK THAT'S HOW I'M GOING TO
DO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR.
LET'S GET TO THE CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'LL BE
DIVIDED INTO PAIRS.
YOU'RE GOING THE RACE UNDER AN
OBSTACLE TO A SAND PIT WHERE YOU
WILL DIG UP A RING OF KEYS AND
USE THOSE KEYS TO RELEASE TWO
BALLS AND THEN ATTEMPT TO LAND
THEM ON NARROW PERCH.
THE FIRST PAIR TO FINISH WINS
MORE TIME WITH THEIR LOVED ONES
AND A BARBECUE ON A BARGE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jeff: WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> Jeff: WE'LL DRAW FOR PAIRS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD IN THE FORM OF LOVE,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> MIKE AND DAVIE, ANGELINA AND
NICK, ALISON AND KARA, AND
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY ARE FOUR
PAIRS.
YOU HAVE TO GET BACK TO SHORE.
MIKE AND DAVIE GET TO THE FIRST
OBSTACLE FIRST.
EVERYBODY CRAWLING THROUGH THAT
FIRST OBSTACLE.
MIKE AND DAVIE OUT.
THERE GOES CHRISTIAN AND GABBY.
ALISON AND KARA.
ANGELINA DEAD LAST, HOLDING NICK
UP NOW.
YOU ARE ONLY AS FAST AS YOUR
SLOWEST PERSON, AND RIGHT NOW
THAT IS ANGELINA, STILL THE ONLY
PERSON IN THIS GAME TO NOT WIN A
REWARD.
WILL THAT DROUGHT CONTINUE
TODAY.
>> COME ON!
YOU GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY NOW DIGGING
FOR THEIR KEYS.
MIKE AND DAVIE ARE FIRST TO THE
KEYS.
THEY HAVE LED THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
>> I FEEL IT, I FEEL IT.
>> Jeff: ANGELINA AND NICK
HAVE THEIR KEY.
THEY'RE BACK IN IT.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY HAVE THEIR
KEY.
>> GO, GABRIELLA.
>> Jeff: ALISON AND KARA STILL
DIGGING.
YOU HAVE FIVE KEY, YOU ONLY NEED
ONE, THE QUESTION IS WHICH ONE.
ALISON AND KARA FINALLY HAVE
THEIR KEY.
THEY'RE IN IT.
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING IN YOUR LIFE
RIGHT NOW, THAT LOVE.
NICK AND ANGELINA RELEASE THEIR
BALLS.
THEY'RE NOW IN THE LEAD.
ANGELINA AND NICK WERE IN DEAD
LAST, AN NOW THEY'RE IN THE
LEAD.
THIS IS HOW FAST THE GAME CAN
CHANGE.
DAVIE FINALLY HAS THE LOCK
UNDONE.
GO.
PICK IT UP.
ALISON AND KARA RELEASE THEIR
BAG.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GET THE BALLS
OUT OF THE BAG.
>> THEY'RE STUCK IN THERE.
>> Jeff: NICK AND ANGELINA
CAN'T DO IT.
WITNESS AGAIN THEY HAVE
SQUANDERED THE LEAD.
ALISON AND KARA HAVE THEIR BALLS
RELEASED.
THEY'RE FIRING.
MIKE AND DAVIE TOSSING BALLS.
YOU'RE TETHERED TOGETHER WHICH
MAKES IT TOUGH TO GET YOU BALL
WHEN IT GOES OFF.
ANGELINA AND NICK FINALLY HAVE
THEIR BALLS RELEASED.
THEY'RE FIRING.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY HAVE THEIR
BALLS.
EVERYBODY NOW IN IT.
EACH PERSON HAS TO LAND ONE
BALL.
KARA HAS GOT TO GO GET HER BALL
THAT.
PULLS ALISON OFF.
CHRISTIAN AND GABBY WORKING.
MIKE CLOSE.
JUST MISSES.
DAVIE JUST MISSES.
ALISON WITH A SHOT.
CAN'T GET IT TO LAND.
KARA MISSES AGAIN.
ANGELINA AND NICK WORKING.
THERE GOES DAVIE.
DAVIE SCORES FIRST FOR PURPLE.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: NICK SCORES ONE FOR
GREEN.
MIKE FOR THE WIN RIGHT HERE.
JUST MISSES.
ANGELINA CAN WIN IT.
AND SHE DOES.
FROM BEHIND, ANGELINA WINS
REWARD, EARNING LOVE ALONGSIDE
NICK AND A BARBECUE ON THE
BARGE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO WE'VE GOT FOUR, NICK AND
ANGELINA, YOU HAVE A BIG
DECISION TO MAKE.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON AN THEIR LOVED
ONE TO JOIN YOU WHOM ARE YOU
GOING TO BRING ALONG WITH YOU.
>> ME AND DAVIE MADE A PROMISE
TO EACH OTHER ALONG TIME AGO.
I ASKED HER IF SHE'S OKAY WITH
THAT AND SHE IS, SO WE'RE GOING
THE CHOOSE DAVIE.
>> Jeff: DAVIE, HAZEL, COME
JOIN US.
MOM HAS NO IDEA WHAT SHE'S IN
STORE FOR.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE CHOICE TO
MAKE, ONE MORE PLAYER AND THEIR
LOVED ONE WILL JOIN YOU, AND IN
CHOOSING, YOU WILL SEND FOUR
OTHER PEOPLE BACK TO CAMP
WITHOUT LOVE AND A LITTLE BIT OF
RICE TO LIVE ON.
>> SO THIS NEXT PERSON IS
SOMEONE WHO STOOD BY MY SIDE AND
HAS BEEN STRONG WITH ME AND I
WANT TO GIVE HIM SOME TIME,
MIKE, COME OVER HERE.
>> Jeff: MIKE, COME OVER.
JOSH, COME JOIN US.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: IT IS TIME NOW TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO THE REST OF OUR
LOVED ONES.
SAY YOUR LAST GOOD-BYES.
SORRY, LOVED ONES.
TIME FOR YOU TO HEAD BACK.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> Jeff: MIKE, ANGELINA,
DAVIE, NICK, ENJOY A ONCE IN
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME AFTERNOON.
COME ON DOWN.
>> BYE.
>> Jeff: GABBY, KARA, ALISON,
CHRISTIAN, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
>> DAVIE.
>> ALL RIGHT, MOTHER.
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
>>YOU DON'T REALIZE.
>> AN OCTOPUS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SO HOW IS THE GAME GOING?
>> IT'S GOING GOOD.
THIS RIGHT HERE COULD BE THE
FINAL FOUR.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> ARE YOU RUNNING THE GAME?
>> WORKING THE MIDDLE.
EVERYONE THINKS I'M ON THEIR
SIDE.
I DEFINITELY THINK THE FOUR OF
US, I THINK WE HIGH MAKE A DEAL
AND MAKE A FINAL FOUR.
>> THIS IS EXACTLY THE GROUP OF
FOUR THAT I WANTED HERE TODAY.
THIS IS... I MEAN, BECAUSE THERE
ARE SOME VICIOUS PEOPLE OVER
THERE.
AT THE BARBECUE WE OBVIOUSLY
SPENT THE MAJORITY OF OUR TIME
WITH OUR LOVED ONES CATCHING UP,
BUT WE ALSO TOOK THIS TIME TO
TALK SOME STRATEGY.
I WANT TO GO TO THE END WITH
PEOPLE WHO I TRULY RESPECT, AND
THAT YOU WOULD BE HAPPY SEEING
WIN IF IT'S NOT YOURSELF.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> THE LOVED ONE VISIT WORKED
OUT PERFECTLY, BECAUSE THE GROUP
OF FOUR WHO WENT IS ACTUALLY THE
GROUP I WANT TO BE IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
>> COULDN'T HAVE PICKED A BETTER
GROUP, NO WAY.
>> THIS IS MY FINAL FOUR
IDEALLY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I WOULD LOVE THAT.
>> THIS IS MY FINAL FOUR.
>> I THINK WE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO MAKE SURE THAT HAPPENS.
>> MIKE, NICK, AND ANGELINA,
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT FINAL
FOUR, BUT THEY'VE ALL SPENT MUCH
LONGER WITH EACH OTHER THAN I
HAVE, BECAUSE THEY WERE ALL ON
THE JABENI TRIBE TOGETHER.
SO I'M STARTING TO FEEL A LITTLE
BIT ON THE OUTSIDE.
I DON'T THINK THIS ALLIANCE IS
THE SMARTEST MOVE FOR ME.
>> YOU CAN TELL SHE'S A LITTLE
SHY.
I KNEW THAT EVERY COMPLIMENT I
WOULD PAY HER, SHE WOULD BE
EMBARRASSED, YOU KNOW?
SO I WAS SAYING WHAT I FELT, BUT
I ALSO WAS MEASURING HOW I SAID
IT SO SHE WOULDN'T GET
EMBARRASSED, YOU KNOW, IN FRONT
OF ALL THOSE STRANGERS.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE ONE WHO THINKS
ABOUT HER BEFORE YOU.
SO YOU THINK ABOUT HOW SHE'S
GOING TO FEEL.
>> WHEN I SAW CHRISTIAN WITH
EMILY, I NOTICED THAT HE WAS
COMFORTING HER, AND I REALIZED
THAT'S WHAT CHRISTIAN HAS BEEN
TO ME OUT HERE.
HE'S PLAYING UP THE ROLE OF
COMFORTER AND FRIEND, AND I
CAN'T LET MYSELF GET RIEWRED
INTO THAT SENSE OF SECURITY
LIKE, OH, CHRISTIAN IS LOOKING
OUT FOR ME, CHRISTIAN'S GOT MY
BACK.
I NEED TO PLAY FOR ME.
>> I AM FEELING MORE AND MORE
LIKE WE HAVE TO DO CHRISTIAN,
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
CHRISTIAN AND I HAVE MADE NEARLY
EVERY STRATEGIC MOVE TOGETHER,
BUT HE'S THE ONE PERCEIVED AS
MAKING ALL THE MOVES, SO I NEED
TO REMOVE HIM SO THAT I AM FREE
TO PLAY MY OWN GAME.
>> NOT A SOUL CAN BEAT HIM.
>> LITERALLY.
LITERALLY.
I FEEL LIKE THE GAME HAS BUSTED
WIDE OPEN AND IT'S TIME THE
PLAY.
PEOPLE HAVE SEEN ME AS
CHRISTIAN'S SIDEKICK, AND I HAVE
BEEN STRUGGLING TO FIGHT THAT
PERCEPTION.
I WANT RESPECT IN THIS GAME.
SO WHAT BETTER WAY THAN TO SLAY
MY NUMBER-ONE ALLY?
SO I'VE BEEN MULLING SOMETHING
OVER FOR THE PAST FEW DAYS
WORRYING ABOUT WHEN TO MAKE A
MOVE.
>> YES.
>> AGAINST CHRISTIAN.
WE NEED TO GET CHRISTIAN OUT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> GABBY WANTS TO BLINDSIDE
CHRISTIAN.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT WAS COMING
OUT OF HER MOUTH.
IT BLOWS MY MIND.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET
CHRISTIAN OUT OF THE GAME FOR A
WHILE.
HE'S A REALLY GOOD PLAYER.
SO I'M ALL FOR THIS PLAN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
FIRST THINGS FIRST, DAVIE, GOT
TO TAKE IT BACK.
NO HELP AT ALL.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE ON A NARROW
PERCH WHILE HOLDING A POLE
CONNECTED TO A BUCKET OF WATER.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU STEP OFF THE
PERCH OR RAISE THAT POLE TOO
HIGH OR DROP IT TOO LOW, THAT
BUCKET WILL EMPTY AND YOU'RE OUT
OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
SEVEN SHOT AT GETTING TO THE END
OF THIS GAME.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE SIXTH
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY LOOKING GOOD.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
IT REQUIRES YOU BEING IN FULL
CONTROL OF YOUR BODY.
TWO WAYS THIS CHALLENGE CAN GET
YOU.
YOU STEP OFF THE PERCH, LOSING
YOUR BALANCE, OR YOU LIFT JUST A
LITTLE TOO HIGH OR DROP JUST A
LITTLE TOO LOW, THE BUCKET OF
WATER WAITING TO DRENCH YOU,
ENDING YOUR SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
MIKE, THE SLIGHTEST TWITCH AND
MIKE IS OUT.
FIRST TO DROP.
WE ARE DOWN TO SEVEN.
MIKE NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
THAT'S HOW FAST IT CAN HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE TO THE NEXT
PHASE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU'RE GOING TO PLACE YOUR FRONT
FOOT, PLACE IT BEHIND YOUR BACK
FOOT, YOUR ARMS FURTHER OUT,
WHICH GIVES YOU LESS LEVERAGE,
MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT.
I'M GOING TO COUNT YOU IN.
GABBY, THE SLIGHTEST BIT OF A
MOVE.
GABBY DROPS, SHE IS OUT.
SECONDS AWAY FROM MOVING TO THE
NEXT ROUND.
WE ARE DOWN TO SIX.
YOU HAVE TEN SECONDS.
GOT TO GET THAT FRONT FOOT
BEHIND YOUR BACK FOOT.
SIX, FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO,
ONE.
EVERYBODY SUCCESSFULLY
NEGOTIATES THE TRANSITION.
NICE JOB.
WE WILL STAY HERE FOR TEN
MINUTES NOW.
YOUR ARM NOW FURTHER OUT, WHICH
GIVES YOU LESS LEVERAGE, MAKING
IT MORE DIFFICULT.
YOU HEAR THE BREATHING, TRYING
THE FIND THAT MEDITATION.
CHRISTIAN CONTINUES TO MAKE A
RISKY MOVE, SCRATCHING HIS HEAD.
>> Jeff: ALISON'S LEGS REALLY
TWITCH, BUT SHE'S HOLDING STEADY
IN HER PALM.
NICK, EVEN A MOVE TO THE FACE IS
RISKY.
ALISON CAN'T HANG ON ANY LONGER.
ALISON IS OUT, AND WE ARE DOWN
TO FIVE.
ANGELINA CAN'T HANG IN ANY
LONGER.
ANGELINA IS OUT.
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR.
IT IS DAVIE, KARA, CHRISTIAN,
AND NICK.
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING THE MOVE YOUR FRONT
FOOT BEHIND YOUR BACK FOOT.
THERE'S MORE PRESSURE ON YOUR
ARM, LESS LEVERAGE TOWARD YOUR
BODY.
YOU'VE GOT TEN SECONDS, NINE,
EIGHT, SEVEN, SIX, FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE.
EVERYBODY AND A HALF GAITS
ANOTHER TRANSITION.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY SAFE IN
THIS THIRD ROUND.
WE WILL GO FOR 20 MINUTES HERE.
>> NICK YOU NEED TO GO HIGHER.
THAT'S GOOD.
JUST HAIR UP.
JUST A HAIR.
>> NICK, YOU'RE DROPPING LOW.
JUST HAIR UP.
>> Jeff: A LOT OF SUPPORT FOR
NICK DOWN ON THE END.
>> AM I NICE AND CENTERED, GUYS.
>> WE DON'T WANT TO MESS YOU UP.
NICK'S WAS SUPER OBVIOUS.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON.
>> DON'T LOOK AT HIS, NICK.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN NOW
STARTING TO SHAKE A LOT.
YOU CAN SEE THAT RIGHT ARM ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
HIS POLE EDGING CLOSER, JUST
SLIDING OFF OF THE ONLY THING
HOLDING HIM IN THIS CHALLENGE.
CAN HE GET IT BACK UNDER
CONTROL.
BUT IT'S NICK WHO DROPS.
NICK IS OUT.
AN WE'RE DOWN TO THREE.
DAVIE, KARA, AND CHRISTIAN, WHO
IS BACK SOLID AGAIN.
"DAVE'S PET SHOW'S" BODY
STARTING --
DAVIE'S BODY STARTING TO MOVE
NOW.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN STEPS OFF.
CHRISTIAN IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
WE ARE DOWN TO TWO.
DAVIE AND KARA.
A DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH SHOWDOWN.
KARA HAS NOT WAVERED THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
HAS BARELY MOVED.
DAVIE STICKING SHAKING BUT STILL
UNDER CONTROL WITH HIS ARM.
DAVIE DROPS.
DAVIE IS OUT.
KARA WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
>> WOW.
WOW.
>> Jeff: KARA, COME ON OVER.
>> Jeff: GOOD JOB, KARA.
>> GOOD GIRL.
>> Jeff: KARA, INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 32
VERY TOUGH DAY, SOMEBODY VOTED
OUT.
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE SIXTH
AMERICA OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
>> I LIKE THE WAY GABBY IS
THINKING.
IT'S TIME TO TAKE OUT CHRISTIAN.
I AM CAUTIOUSLY OPTIMISTIC THAT
THIS PLAN WILL SUCCEED, HOWEVER,
WE TRIED TO GET CHRISTIAN OUT
BEFORE.
WHAT'S TO SAY HE DOESN'T PULL
SOMETHING OUT OF HIS HAT THIS
THIRD TIME AROUND, AS WELL.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, KARA.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> YOU WERE LIKE A STATUE.
>> FINALLY IT WAS TIME TO PROVE
THAT I CAN MAKE MOVES IN THIS
GAME.
AT THIS POINT IT'S GO BIG OR GO
HOME.
AND WHAT BIGGER MOVE THAN GOING
AGAINST YOUR CLOSEST ALLY, WHO
HAPPENS TO BE THE BIGGEST THREAT
IN THE GAME.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> I WAS REALLY DISAPPOINTED.
I WANTED TO DO WELL, YOU KNOW?
>> SAME.
>> AT THIS POINT WE'VE GOT TO
GET RID OF ALISON.
AS LONG AS WE HAVE EVERYONE IN
LINE.
>> CHRISTIAN BELIEVES THAT WE'RE
VOTING FOR ALISON, WHICH IS
PERFECT, BECAUSE WITH CHRISTIAN
HAVING A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE HIM OUT WHEN HE
LEAST EXPECTS IT.
SO I'M EXCITED AND I'M NERVOUS
AND I'M SAD, BECAUSE IT MEANS
BETRAYING SOMEONE THAT'S BEEN
CLOSE TO YOU FOR SO LONG, BUT I
NEED TO REMEMBER THAT CHRISTIAN
DOESN'T WANT ME TO WIN,
CHRISTIAN WANTS CHRISTIAN TO
WIN.
AND SO I HAVE TO DO IT IF I WANT
TO WIN THIS GAME.
>>OKAY.
LET'S TALK STRATEGY.
>> YEAH.
WHO ARE YOU THINKING?
>> CHRISTIAN IS THE BIGGEST
THREAT TO WIN THE GAME.
100%.
HE'S MY CLOSEST ALLY.
IT KEEPS HIM FROM GETTING ALL
THE CREDIT.
HE'S SUPER SMART.
>> OF ALL PEOPLE, GABBY COMES UP
TO ME TO SAY HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
ABOUT VOTING OUT CHRISTIAN.
I'M LIKE, I'M TOTALLY FINE WITH
IT.
I WAS TRYING TO THINK OF A WAY I
COULD GET THE NUMBERS FOR
CHRISTIAN.
I'M MISSED OFF.
I SAVED CHRISTIAN'S BUTT FROM
GOING HOME TWICE, AND WHAT DOES
HE DO?
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL, HE
TOTALLY BETRAYS ME.
>> ALISON ANKARA WOULD BE DOWN.
>> I'LL DO IT.
I CAN'T TRUST HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> AT THIS POINT CHRISTIAN IS
DEAD TO ME.
AND IT'S TIME HE GETS TASTE OF
HIS OWN MEDICINE.
>> SHE JUST COMES UP AND SAID,
CHRISTIAN.
IF IT'S CHRISTIAN, THAT'S MORE
COMPLICATED AND WE HAVE TO THINK
IF HE DOES HAVE AN IDOL.
>> I'VE SOON HIS IDOL.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> WELL, IF HE PLAYS HIS IDOL,
YOU COULD VOTE FOR GABBY.
>> NICK IS TOTALLY DOWN FOR
VOTING CHRISTIAN, BUT GABBY IS
THE BACK-UP IN CASE HE PLAYS HIS
IDOL, BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH CHRISTIAN BLINDSIDED
ME TWICE, I DON'T TAKE IT
PERSONAL.
THAT'S PART OF THE GAME.
BUT NICK IS CONVINCED THAT
CHRISTIAN HAS TO GO.
>> IT'S ABOUT TIME.
>> I'VE SHIELDED MYSELF SO FAR
BY HIDING BEHIND PEOPLE, SEEN AS
A BIG THREAT, BUT WHO IS GOING
TO BE MY SHIELD IF I GET
CHRISTIAN OUT?
SO I GOT TO KEEP CHRISTIAN IN
THIS GAME.
>> OH, MAN.
YOU REALLY GOT TO BE CAREFUL.
SHE KNOWS SHE NEEDS MOVES IN
THIS GAME TO MOVE FORWARD.
AN YOU GUYS DID THAT CARL THING
TOGETHER, RIGHT, SO SHE STILL
DOESN'T HAVE HER OWN INDIVIDUAL
MOVE.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO SHE'S LIKE, IT'S GOING TO
BE CHRISTIAN, IT'S GOING TO BE
CHRISTIAN.
>> I'M FLOORED.
ACCORDING TO DAVIE, GABBY IS
GUNNING FOR ME.
SHE FEELS LIKE SHEA DOESN'T HAVE
A CHANCE TO WIN UNLESS SHE MAKES
A MOVE AND TAKES ME OUT.
I'M STUNNED.
GABBY AND I HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
THIS ENTIRE GAME.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN SEPARATED FOR
MORE THAN AN HOUR OVER THE
COURSE OF THE WHOLE MONTH.
SO I'M HAVING HARD TIME
BELIEVING IT.
>> THE PLAN IS TO VOTE OUT
ALISON TONIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT NICK?
>> IS NICK DOWN WITH SENDING ME
HOME?
>> I REALLY THINK SO.
>> IT'S ME AND YOU.
APPARENTLY NICK WAS SO BURNED BY
THE CARL VOTE THAT HE WANTS TO
TAKE REVENGE ON ME.
I STILL HAVE MY IDOL THAT I CAN
PLAY TO ENSURE ALISON GOES HOME.
BUT THAT WOULD LEAVE ME
VULNERABLE AT THE NEXT VOTE.
SO THE BEST COURSE OF ACTION FOR
RIGHT NOW IS TO TRY TO REPAIR
THE DAMAGE WITH NICK.
FIRST OFF, IN HINDSIGHT, I DID
MAKE AN ERROR IN NOT TELLING
YOU.
THAT'S NOT -- THAT'S NOT FAIR TO
IT'S NOT FAIR TO THE
RELATIONSHIP, AN I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU FEEL MAD.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE -- I'M OWN
UP TO WHAT WAS A MISCALCULATION
ON MY PART.
YOU'RE FRUSTRATED BY THE
SITUATION.
>> I'M TRYING TO GET OVER IT.
>> CHRISTIAN IS APOLOGIZING
PROFUSELY TO ME SAYING, YOU
KNOW, HE TOOK OUR RELATIONSHIP
FOR GRANTED, BUT I DON'T TRUST
CHRISTIAN ANYMORE AND I PROBABLY
NEVER ALMOST NOW I'M GOING TO
MANIPULATE HIM.
IF HE'S CONVINCED HE'S GOT THE
MASON-DIXON BACK TOGETHER,
THAT'S GOING THE MAKE IT THAT
MUCH EASIER TO BLINDSIDE HIM.
>> HERE'S THE THING, THE MAIN
THING IS THAT ALISON THINKS SHE
HAS FOOTING, BUT SHE DOESN'T
HAVE FOOTING.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
GONE.
>> I KNOW.
>> AS LONG AS ALISON'S GONE,
THAT'S FINE.
>> NOT BEING IMMUNE HAS PUT ME
IN A TIGHT SPOT.
I KNOW I'M GETTING VOTES.
FORTUNATELY NICK STILL WANTS TO
WORK WITH ME.
>> NICK SAYS THE PLAN IS GOOD,
RIGHT?
>> GET RID OF CHRISTIAN, YES.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE I CAN MARSHAL
ENOUGH VOTES TO VOTE OUT ALISON.
I'D RATHER NOT USE MY IDOL, BUT
I'LL PLAY IT IF I FEEL I HAVE
TO, BUT HOPEFULLY I DON'T HAVE.
TO AND SO FAR I'VE BEEN RIGHT
EVERY TIME.
>> Jeff: LET'S NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELIZABETH, JOHN, DAN, ALEC, AND
CARL VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO LAST TRIBAL ANOTHER
BLINDSIDE.
ANGELINA, WHAT WAS THE FALLOUT
BACK AT CAMP?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THERE WERE SOME
PEOPLE WHO WERE SUPER PISSED.
>> Jeff: WHO WAS UPSET?
>> NICK WAS PRETTY UPSET.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS COMING
EITHER.
>> Jeff: NICK, WHAT WAS YOUR
FRUSTRATION.
>> IT WAS A BLIEKDSIDE, AND IT
WAS A BIG MOVE, BUT JUST BECAUSE
SOMETHING IS A BIG MOVE DOESN'T
MAKE IT A GOOD MOVE.
>> Jeff: WHO WERE YOU
FRUSTRATED WITH?
>> CHRISTIAN MAINLY.
I DIDN'T GET IT.
IF YOU'RE WITH ME AND YOU TRUST
ME, WHY COULDN'T YOU TELL ME?
SO EVERYBODY KNEW I WAS PISSED,
I WAS.
>> Jeff: WHEN YOU HAVE
SOMEBODY, CHRISTIAN, COME AT YOU
LIKE NICK AND SAY, HEY, I DIDN'T
LIKE IT.
DOES IT PUT A NEW FEAR IN YOU
THAT A GUY I THAWING I WAS WITH
IS NOW AGAINST ME.
>> I CERTAINLY TAKE IT VERY
SERIOUSLY, AND IT DOES AFFECT
YOUR THINKING GOING FORWARD AND
SAYING, YOU KNOW, FOR ONE YOU
HAVE TO REASSESS YOUR JUDGMENTS
AS TO HOW PEOPLE WILL REACT.
AND THAT'S ON ME.
>> Jeff:
>> WE WENT OFF TO THE SIDE AND
TALKED ABOUT IT AN REBUILT OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
IN MY HEAD, IF IT'S SOMEBODY YOU
DON'T CARE ABOUT, YOU DON'T
CARE, BUT THE PERSON YOU CARE
ABOUT, YOU SAY, HEY, WE HAVE A
PROBLEM, AND IF WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO HAVE A RELATIONSHIP,
WE NEED TO WORK IT OUT.
>> Jeff: GABBY, IT'S SO
COMPLICATED, BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
MAKE THE BIG MOVE TO SHOW YOU'RE
PLAYING THE GAME, BUT IT CAN
HURT FEELINGS, AND THOSE HURT
FEELINGS CAN THEN CHANGE THE
GAME AGAIN.
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD, BECAUSE WHEN
I CAME INTO THIS GAME, I NEEDED
A LOT OF REASSURANCE, AND THAT
CAME FROM OTHER PEOPLE A LOT OF
THE TIME, AN NOW I FIND
REASSURANCE IN MYSELF.
THAT'S WHAT MY DECISIONS GOING
FORWARD MANY THIS GAME ARE
ABOUT.
I'M GOING TO DO LESS, DO YOU
THINK THIS IS THE RIGHT MOVE, DO
YOU GIVE ME REASSURANCE, AN NOW
I'M SAYING WITH CONFIDENCE, THIS
IS HOW I'M GOING FORWARD, AND IF
IT GETS ME VOTED OUT, AT LEAST I
DID SOMETHING WITH GUMPTION.
>> Jeff: ALISON, THE LAST FEW
TRIBALS YOU HAVE SPOKEN OPENLY
THAT YOU FELT YOU WERE A FAR
GET, THAT YOU WERE A THREAT.
>> I LOOKED THE GRIM REAPER, WHO
IS YOU WITH YOUR FREAKIN' TORCH
SNUFFER IN THE EYES, LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AND I WALKED AWAY BEING
MORE OF A THREAT.
>> Jeff: YOU THINK YOU'RE MORE
OF A THREAT BECAUSE WHY IN.
>> BECAUSE I SURVIVED BEING ON
THE BOTTOM AND HELPED PULL OFF A
GREAT BLINDSIDE.
IT WAS NOT AN VJ MOVE.
IT TOOK FIVE VOTES, BUT IT WAS
MY NECK ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> Jeff: ANGELINA, DO YOU FEEL
THAT EVERYBODY IS AN EQUAL
THREAT?
IS ALISON WORRIED ABOUT NOTHING?
BECAUSE THERE ARE SEVEN OTHERS
SURROUNDING?
>> NEW YORK I DON'T THINK THAT
EVERYONE IS AN EQUAL THREAT.
MY CRITERIA IS SOMEONE WHO I
DON'T SEE ANY ENDING WITH IS A
GOOD PERSON TO GO.
>> Jeff: NICK, WHAT IS THE
CRITERIA FOR YOU?
>> WELL, PUTTING PEOPLE ON THE
JURY, AND WE'RE ALSO PUTTING WHO
WE GO TO THE END WITH, SO YOU
CAN FIND SOMEBODY WHO YOU WANT
ON THE JURY YOU DON WANT TO GO
TO THE END WORK IT LOOKS LIKE A
GOOD PERSON TO TAKE OUT.
>> Jeff: IS IT REALLY THAT
SIMPLE, MIKE?
>> A LOT OF TIMES YOU GET RID OF
A THREAT AND YOU REALIZED, OH,
THAT MIGHT NOT BE THE RIGHT
PERSON.
IT'S NEVER EASY.
IT'S NEVER SAFE.
IT'S A GAME ABOUT DECEPTION, AND
SO THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE ALL
ARE VERY CONSCIOUS OF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
GABBY, YOU'RE UP.
>> IF THIS DOESN'T WORK, THEN
I'M LOSING MY CLOSEST ALLY AND
MY BEST FRIEND IN THIS GAME, BUT
IT'S SOMETHING I NEED TO DO FOR
MY GAME.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
OKAY.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
>> A SECOND JEFF.
I'M NOT QUITE SURE YET.
I'LL PLAY IT.
THIS HAS BEEN IN MY VIEW FOR THE
PAST FOUR TRIBAL COUNCILS, AND
AS ONE MIGHT IMAGINE, IT IS
SLIGHTLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
SO I COULD BE WRONG, BUT I'M
PLAYING THIS FOR MYSELF TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR CHRISTIAN
WILL NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
>> WOW.
FIRST VOTE CHRISTIAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
CHRISTIAN.
>> HOW DID YOU GET THAT BIG
BRAIN?
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN, DOES NOT
COUNT.
CHRISTIAN, DOES NOT COUNT.
>> HE'S SO SMART.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
ALISON.
THAT'S ONE VOTE ALISON.
>> I'M SO SORRY, ALISON.
>> Jeff: GABBY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: WE'RE TIED.
ONE VOTE ALISON, ONE VOTE GABBY,
ONE VOTE LEFT.
13th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
GABBY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WOW.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> GOOD GAME, GUYS.
>> Jeff: GABBY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> BY, GABBY.
>> SORRY, CHRISTIAN, I LOVE YOU.
>> WE'LL SEE EACH OTHER SOON,
OKAY?
>> Jeff: WELL WORK ONLY SEVEN
PEOPLE LEFT AND EVERYBODY SEEING
EACH OTHER AS THREATS, THERE'S
NOWHERE TO HIDE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," EVERYONE IS ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> I WANT NEW ENGLAND OUT NEXT.
-- NICK OUT NEXT.
>> IS IT BETTER TO TAKE OUT
CHRISTIAN?
>> I WANT IT TO BE NICK.
>> I'M DROOLING AT THIS IDEA.
>> NOW IS THE TIME TO TAKE YOU
OUT.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S MORE
POSSIBILITIES THAN THERE HAS
EVER BEEN BEFORE.
>> I STARTED THIS GAME AS AN
UNDERDOG.
I STILL FEEL LIKE I WAS KIND OF
AN UNDERDOG, BUT FOR ME IT WAS A
PERSONAL TRIUMPH TO DO SOMETHING
WITH CONFIDENCE AND NOT SEEK
REASSURANCE FROM ALL OVER.
BUT IF PEOPLE SAW SOMETHING IN
ME THAT THEY WANTED TO TAKE OUT,
THEN MAYBE I'M MORE OF A GOLIATH
THAN I THOUGHT.