Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
CARL AND NICK HAD TWO
ADVANTAGES:
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: AND WHILE ALEC AND
ALISON HAD A BOND WITH THE
DAVIDS...
WE HAVE TO KEEP NICK AND
GABBY AND CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: ...IT DIDNT STOP
THEM FROM STICKING WITH THE
GOLIATHS.
SO WE TAKE HIM OUT NEXT.
THE GOLIATHS ARE ALL ON THE
SAME PAGE TONIGHT TO VOTE OUT
CHRISTIAN.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
DAVIE PLAYED HIS IDOL.
IM NERVOUS FOR CHRISTIAN.
THIS IS FOR HIM.
Jeff: WHICH FRIGHTENED
ANGELINA.
IM GOING TO TAKE CARE OF MY
ALLIANCE, TOO.
IM GOING TO PLAY THIS FOR
ANGELINA.
Jeff: BUT THE DAVIDS HAD A
DIFFERENT TARGET.
JOHN SENDING JOHN TO THE JURY.
JOHN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
11 ARE LEFT.
WHO WILL BE VOTED OUT TONIGHT?
Captioning funded by CBS
HEY, GUYS, I WANT TO SAY
SOMETHING REAL FAST.
ITS SEASON 37, GUYS.
I MEAN, I FEEL LIKE THE GAME HAS
EVOLVED ENOUGH TO WHERE WE CAN
RESPECT EACH OTHERS GAME PLAY
WITHOUT TAKING IT PERSONAL.
OH.
MY.
GOD!
DUDE, I FELT LIKE I WAS IN A
WRESTLING MATCH JUST NOW!
ALL THE WAY FROM SOUTH CAROLINA,
DAVIE RICKENBACKER SAKES DOWN
THE MAYOR.
LETS GBABY!
I GOT HIS JACKET!
I SHOULD PUT IT ON RIGHT NOW,
MAN.
IM HERE TO SAY WERE HERE TO
PLAY, LETS PLAY, GUYS.
LETS PLAY.
IM THE DEFEATER OF SLAM TOWN!
LETS GO!
YUP.
THEY MAKE THE BIG MOVE.
ALL OF US THEN ARE JUST PICKED
OFF SLOWLY BUT SURELY.
RIGHT.
MY PROBLEM IS THAT FOR TWO
VOTES, I HAVE TOLD CERTAIN
DAVIDS-- NAMELY, CHRISTIAN AND
GABBY-- THAT "OH, IM GONNA FLIP
THE SCRIPT.
IM GONNA VOTE OUT DAN.
IM GOING TO VOTE OUT ANGELINA."
RIGHT.
AND I HAVENT.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE BEEN TALK
WITH THESE DAVIDS ABOUT MAKE A
MOVE, AND I TOOK THE
CONSERVATIVE APPROACH LAST
TRIBAL, AND IT DIDNT WORK OUT
FOR ME.
BUT TO WIN THIS GAME, I WANT A
RESUME, AND I WANT TO MAKE BIG
MOVES.
AND AFTER A BOMB LIKE THAT, MY
HEAD IS GOING A MILLION MILES A
MINUTE.
I AM TRYING TO THINK, WELL,
WHERE DO MY LOYALTIES LIE?
WEVE BEEN PROMISING THEM TO GO
WITH THEM--
TO DO SOMETHING WITH THEM.
IF YOU DONT DO IT ON THE
THIRD VOTE--
WERE GONNA MISS THE BOAT.
YEAH.
FROM A NUMBERS STANDPOINT, THE
GOLIATHS STILL HAVE THE 6-5
ADVANTAGE.
BUT ALISON AND I WERE ACTUALLY
CONTEMPLATING FLIPPING, AND MIKE
KIND OF HELD US BACK A LITTLE
BIT, BUT I THINK FOR US, WEVE
BEEN GOLIATH STRONG FOR TOO
LONG.
HES JUST SITTING THERE
THINKING.
TRIBAL COUNCIL, EVERYTHING
WAS JUST TURNED UPSIDE DOWN.
IT JUST TURNED INTO A GIANT
MESS.
I PLAYED MY IDOL ON THE WRONG
PERSON, WHICH IS FRUSTRATING.
AND THEN KARA AND ALEC AND
ALISON GO OFF AND HAVE A LITTLE
POWWOW TOGETHER, AND IM SITTING
ON THE BEACH FOR, LIKE, TWO
FREAKING HOURS.
NOBODY PULLS ME ASIDE FOR A
POWWOW.
I JUST FEEL TAKEN FOR GRANTED
AND UNAPPRECIATED.
I FELT THAT KARA AND I WERE ROCK
SOLID.
BUT IT DOESNT FEEL LIKE THAT
AFTER THE VOTE.
I MEAN, IT HURTS.
ITS, LIKE, I MAKE THE
SACRIFICE FOR OUR TRIBE, AND I
GET LEFT OUT OF EVERYTHING.
I FEEL LIKE YOURE BEING
EMOTIONAL.
YEAH THATS REAL GOOD--
THATS A REAL GOOD THING TO KEEP
ME OUT OF.
DAN, WHO WAS ONCE MY ALLY, MY
GO-TO, IS COMING LOOSE AT THE
SCENES.
HE IS EMOTIONAL, AND HES
LETTING THE GAME ALMOST GET TO
HIM.
I DIDNT EVEN KNOW YOU WERE
OVER THERE!
WELL, THEN YOU SHOULD WALK
AROUND THE BEACH AND FIGURE OUT
WHO IS SPEAKING WHERE.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
YOU DONT SIT ON THE BEACH
ALONE.
I FEEL LIKE DAN IS THE ANCHOR
HOLDING ME DOWN AT A CERTAIN
STAGE OF THE GAME.
YOU HAVE TO ALWAYS BE MOVING,
ALWAYS BE TALKING, STRATEGIZING,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO
NEXT.
I HAD A FEELING THIS DAY WOULD
COME, THAT I WAS GOG HAVE TO CUT
TIES WITH HIM AT SOME POINT.
BUT THIS IS NOT EASY.
IN THE NORMAL WORLD, THIS
WOULDNT HAPPEN, BUT IN THIS
GAME, I KNOW THAT
( VOICE BREAKING )
IT SUCKS.
BUT IT HAS TO BE DONE.
I HAVE TO SEPARATE MYSELF FROM
HIM IF IM GOING TO WIN THIS
GAME.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, LETS GET TO TODAYS
REWARD CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO BE DIVIDED INTO TWO
TEAMS OF FIVE.
ON MY "GO," YOULL MAKE YOUR WAY
THROUGH AN OBSTACLE, AND
RETRIEVE A BAG OF NUMBERED
TILES.
YOULL MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE
FINISH WHERE THOSE TILES RELEASE
A KEY.
THAT KEY WILL UNLOCK A SNAKE
PUZZLE.
FIRST TEAM TO FINISH THEIR SNAKE
PUZZLE WINS REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT QIEWR PLAYING
FOR.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH!
ABSOLUTELY, JEFF.
Jeff: PREPARE YOURSELF FOR
THE BOULA BURGIR BAR.
I KNEW IT!
I NEED PROTEIN.
Jeff: CHEESEBURGERS!
BACON BURGERS!
BACON!
Jeff: COOKED TO ORDER, COLD
BEAR, SOFT DRINKS.
WERE GOING TO DO A RANDOM DRAW
FOR TWO TEAMS.
THERES ONE EXTRA PERSON,
MEANING ONE OF YOU WILL NOT BE
ON A TEAM.
ONE OF YOU WILL HAVE NO SHOOT
REWARD.
WOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WELL DRAW
FOR TEAMS.
WELL GET STARTED.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE DID A
RANDOM DRAW.
WE HAVE OUR TWO TEAMS.
WEARING PURPLE ANGELINA,
CHRISTIAN, ALISON, GABBY, AND
NICK.
WEARING ORANGE WITH A CLEAR
PHYSICAL ADVANTAGE, MIKE, DAVIE,
DAN, ALEC AND KARA.
CARL DREW THE WRONG ROCK.
CARL, NO SHOT AT REWARD.
HOW YOU FEELING?
I FEEL LIKE IM AT EXILE ALL
OVER AGAIN, JEFF.
OH!
IT SUCKS, MAN.
Jeff: HIGHS AND LOWS OF
SURVIVOR, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
OVER-UNDER.
PRETTY CLOSE RIGHT NOW OUT OF
THE GATE.
CANT DO ANYTHING TILL
EVERYBODYS THERE.
ALEC IS THERE.
DANS THERE.
NICK IS THERE FOR PURPLE.
GOTTA GET EVERYBODY THERE FIRST!
MIKE, FINALLY.
GO, ORANGE, GO, PURPLE!
IM GOOD, GO.
Jeff: NOW YOU HAVE TO LIFT
ONE PERSON TO UNTIE THOSE TILES.
I NEED HIGHER.
STAND ON MY SHOULDERS.
WE GOT YOU.
GOT IT.
Jeff: ALECS THAT.
GOING TO DROP.
GO, ORANGE!
NOW YOURE UNDER THAT NET.
GABBY TAKING A LITTLE LONGER.
SHES GOT IT.
GO, PURPLE!
CAREFUL!
WE GOT YOU!
LETS GO.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO SCRAPE UP
THOSE KNEES BUT IT WILL BE WORTH
IT FOR THE BURGER.
LETS GO, MIKE.
Jeff: ITS ORANGE THROUGH.
YOU GOTTA WAIT, MIKE.
GET BACK!
ORANGE STILL WAITING ON DAVIE.
GO, MIKE!
Jeff: PURPLE TAKING A LONG
TIME TO GET UNDER THAT NET.
EARLY LEAD TO ORANGE.
MIKE NOW GOING TO TRY TO SOLVE
THE COMBO FOR ORANGE.
YOURE GOOD, PURPLE, GO!
ITS GOING TO BE CHRISTIAN AND
MIKE!
MIKE GOING TO GIVE IT A GO FOR
ORANGE, TRYING TO SOLVE THAT
COMBINATION.
ITS NOT 27 BLANK 16.
ITS NOT 27, 36, 18.
Jeff: THIS IS ABOUT A
LITTLE BIT OF LUCK AND JUST
MOVING QUICKLY.
BOTH COMBINATIONS ARE THE SAME.
YOU HAVE A COVER IF YOU WANT TO
BLOCK IT.
OR YOU CAN LET THE OTHER TRIBE
LOOK OVER.
YES!
Jeff: MIKES GOT IT!
COVER, COVER, COVER.
18 LAST, 36 FIRST!
Jeff: ORANGE DID NOT COVER
THEIR COMBO.
ALISON MAY HAVE PICKED IT UP.
36-BLANK-18.
36-18--
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
Jeff: MIKE HAS IT RELEASED.
ORANGE CAN START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
9-11!
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: PURPLE HAS THEIR KEY!
CHRISTIAN CAN UNLOCK THE PUZZLE
PIECES.
ORANGE ALREADY WORKING.
CHRISTIANS GOT IT.
TWO PEOPLE ON THE PUZZLE.
ITS GOING TO BE CHRISTIAN AND
ALISON FOR PURPLE.
KARA AND ALEC FOR ORANGE.
YOU GOT IT.
YOURE IN IT.
Jeff: IT IS CHRISTIAN AND
ALISON NOW TRYING TO CATCH ALEC
AND KARA.
A BULA BURGER BAR.
HAMBURGERS, COLD BEER, SOFT
DRINKS.
DAY 23 ON "SURVIVOR."
THAT IS IT.
THAT IS FIVE STARS.
AS GOOD AS IT GETS.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
PURPLE HAS CAUGHT UP AND IS BACK
IN THIS.
THIS PUZZLE IS MOVING QUICKLY.
BOTH PAIRS WORK TOGETHER VERY
WELL.
GOOD GEORGE KARA, GOOD JOB.
Jeff: WERE LITERALLY EVEN
RIGHT NOW.
SAME AMOUNT OF PIECES LEFT FOR
BOTH PAIRS.
ORANGE THINKS THEY HAVE ANOTHER
PIECE.
KARA WITH ANOTHER PIECE FOR
ORANGE.
ALEC WITH A PIECE FOR ORANGE.
ORANGE STARTING TO PULL AWAY
NOW.
YOU CAN FEEL THE PANIC.
ALISON TRYING TO FORCE A PIECE.
ORANGE DOWN TO THREE PIECES
LEFT.
COME ON, GUYS, YOU GOT THIS,
YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: KEEP DIGGING, PURPLE.
KARA AND ALEC TRYING TO FINISH
THIS.
ALEC WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
IS HE WRITE RITE?
IS THIS IT?
THATS.
Jeff: THATS IT!
( CHEERS )
ORANGE PULLS IT OUT!
ALEC, CAR ADAN, MIKE, AND DAVIE
WIN REWARD AT THE BULA BURGER
BAR!
ALL RIGHT, ORANGE, NICE JOB.
DAN, ALEC, DAVIE, MIKE, KARA.
BURGERS, COLD BEER, AND SOFT
DRINKS WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
EVERYBODY GOING BACK TO CAMP.
BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP AND TAKE
YOU TO THE BULA BURGER BAR.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
CARL, YOU CAN JOIN THEM.
THIS WHOLE GAME IVE BEEN
FIGHTING WITH ALISON AND IVE
BEENMENTING TO WORK WITH HER.
AND EVEN THOUGH MY TEAM ENDED UP
LOSING, THIS IS A PRIME
OPPORTUNITY TO SEE IF SHED BE
WILLING TO MAKE A BIG MOVE AND
BE WILLING TO TURN ON THE
GOLIATHS AND COME TO THE DAVIDS.
COME WITH THE GOOD SIDE!
♪ ♪
CONGRATULATIONS.
ENJOY.
BYE, GUYS.
HEY, CONGRATULATIONS.
EAT ALL THE BURGERS FOR ME,
PLEASE.
AND ALL THE BEERS!
WE LOST THE REWARD CHALLENGE
TODAY, AND IT JUST HIT ME LIKE A
TON OF BRICKS.
THEY HAD VEGGIE BURGERS, TOO.
IM LIKE, THE VEGGIE BURGERS!
I KNOW ITS SO STUPID TO CRY
OVER VEGGIE BURGERS, BUT YOU
NEVER ANTICIPATE HOW PHYSICALLY
HARD THIS GAME IS ON YOUR
SYSTEM, AND THEN WHEN YOU ADD
ALL OF THE EMOTIONAL STUFF ON
TOP OF IT, IT KIND OF JUST FEELS
LIKE BEING, LIKE, HIT BY 1,000
WAVES AT ONCE.
AT LEAST WERE GONNA GET A
TON OF RICE.
MY QUESTION SLIKE, WHAT
ACTUALLY IS HAPPENING BETWEEN
THE GOLIATHS?
I THINK THERES, LIKE, TWO
THINGS THAT ARE GOING ON.
EVERY SINGLE PERSON IS LIKE,
"WELL, SHOULD I-- SHOULD I FLIP
THE SCRIPT?
SHOULD I GO OVER THERE?"
AND AT THE SAME TIME, EVERY
SINGLE PERSON IS SAYING, "NO, WE
HAVE THE MAJORITY."
STAY STRONG.
EXACTLY.
I BELIEVE THAT.
I HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH
ALISON SO I STILL FEEL LIKE
THERES A POTENTIAL TO WORK WITH
HER, WHICH COULD EVENTUALLY FLIP
THIS GAME AND FINALLY HELP ME
GET OUT OF BEING IN THE
MINORITY.
PLUS MY BIG MOVE WOULD HAVE
BEEN WRITING ANGELINAS NAME.
HONESTLY, I THINK ITS GOOD
THAT YOU DIDNT DO THAT, BECAUSE
THATS NOT THAT IMPRESSIVE OF A
BIG MOVE.
SOMETHING LIKE DAN WOULD
ACTUALLY BE A GAME-CHANGING
MOVE.
DAN CHANGES EVERYTHING
DYNAMICS-WISE.
I ACTUALLY CONSIDERED TAKING
OUT DAN BEFORE, SO ITS NOT A
BAD IDEA.
BUT I HAVE BEEN TORN BETWEEN
STICKING GOLIATH STRONG AND
MAKING A BIG MOVE THAT WILL BE
PUT ON MY "SURVIVOR" RESUME.
AND I HAVE BUILT A GREAT ARAB
RAEP WITH GABBY.
WE GET EACH OTHER.
AND IM SEEING ILL HAVE
SECURITY IN THE DAVID, AND ILL
NUMBER THIS BEAUTIFUL POSITION
TO PLAY THIS GAME.
IM SO FREAKING STOKED RIGHT
NOW.
CAN I GET A VEGGIE BURG WER
CHEESE AND GRILLED ONIONS?
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
THERE ARE TWO THINGS THAT CAN
HAPPEN ON A REWARD.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU GET THE FOOD...
OH, MY GOD!
I NEEDED THIS!
BUT, ALSO, ITS A GOOD TIME
TO TALK STRATEGY.
DAVIE TOOK A LITTLE WALK, AND
THE FOUR LEFT ARE ALL GOLIATHS.
SO I WAS TRYING TO RALLY THE
TROOPS AND KEEP EVERYBODY UNITED
BECAUSE WE STILL HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
BUT TRYING TO KEEP THESE
GOLIATHS TOGETHER IS LIKE
HERDING CATS.
IF WE SPLIT UP AND GO WITH THOSE
GUYS, WERE BASICALLY FORFEIT
ANYTHING CHANCE OF WINNING.
RIGHT.
WE NEED TO STAY TOGETHER LIKE
TRUE (BLEEP) GOLIATHS.
I KNOW WE ALL HATE EACH
OTHER, BUT LETS GET THROUGH
THAT.
WHY DONT WE TALK TO
CHRISTIAN AGAIN?
MIKE REALLY WANTS IT TO STAY
GOLIATH STRONG.
HE THINKS WEVE GOT THE NUMBERS.
BUT DAN IS A LIABILITY FOR MY
GAME.
SO FOR ME, I NEED TO GET HIM
OUT.
AND ITS NO LONGER DAVID VERSUS
GOLIATH.
IT FELT GOOD AND THEN IT
QUICKLY FELT BAD.
WE NEED TO BE THE FIRST THREE
TO CREATE AN ALLIANCE WITH THE
DAVIDS.
BECAUSE THAT PUTS US IN THE
STRONGEST POSITION POSSIBLE.
I WANT IT TO BE US THREE TO MAKE
THE MOVE.
YEAH, YOURE RIGHT.
LIKE, WE COULD FLIP.
I WANTED TO GET DAN OUT, SO I
NEED ALEC AND ALISON TO KNOW
THAT IM IN THIS WITH THEM, SO
TO GAIN THEIR TRUST, I WANT TO
GIVE THEM A PIECE OF
INFORMATION.
NOW, I WANT TO SHARE SOMETHING
WITH YOU THAT ONLY I KNOW.
DAN HAS ANOTHER IDOL.
OH, MY GOD.
DAN RIGHT NOW IS A THREAT IN
MANY PEOPLES EYES.
BUT HES ALSO THE LEAST
STRATEGIC OUT OF THE GOLIATHS.
ITS LIKE "SURVIVOR" 10 ONE: IF
YOU FIND AN IDOL DONT TELL
ANYONE.
ESPECIALLY DONT TELL SOME
CHARMING GIRL LIKE KARA.
ITS UNFORTUNATE FOR HIM BUT
HES GOT TO KEEP HIS MOUTH SHUT.
TAKING OUT DAN WILL BUST THIS
GAME WIDE OPEN.
BUT IM IN A GOOD POSITION, AND
THERE IS A SECURITY BLANKET IN
HAVING NUMBERS, MAJORITY RULES.
WILL IT AT THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL?
I DO NOT KNOW.
"SURVIVOR," WHEN AN IDOL GETS
PLAYED THERES ANOTHER IDOL BACK
AT CAMP.
SINCE I PLAYED AN IDOL, I THINK
THERES ANOTHER IDOL BACK AT
CAMP.
IT REALLY IS IN OUR BETTER
INTEREST TO LOOK OUT FOR EACH
OTHER.
SO US DAVIDS GOT A GAME PLAN--
TO WAKE UP AT THE CRACK OF DAWN
AND TRY TO SEE IF WE CAN FIND
SOME TYPE OF NEW ADVANTAGE OR
SOME TYPE OF NEW IDOL.
AND FINDING IDOLS IS WHAT DAVIE
RICKENBACKER DOES FOR A LIVING.
SEARCHING?
HES OVER THERE.
WE SHOULD ALL COMMIT TO THIS
PLACE FIRST.
THERES AN IDOL AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
AND I REALLY WANT TO FIND IT
THIS TIME.
I WANT TO KNOW WHERE IT IS.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE ITS OUT OF
THE HANDS OF OF THE GOLIATHS,
AND SPECIFICALLY, IN MY GRUBBY
HANDS.
I THINK ITS PRETTY MUCH
DONE.
COME AROUND BREAKFAST TIME,
EVERYONE SORT OF CALLS IT
QUITS-- GOES BACK TO CAMP, GET
THE FIRE GOING, MAYBE GET SOME
COFFEE.
BUT I WASNT DONE YET.
I TRIED TO LOOK AROUND THE BIG
LANDMARKS, AND I REALIZED, MAN,
THIS ISLAND IS PRETTY BIG.
SO I TRY A NEW STRATEGY FOR
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
I CALL IT A "BREADTH FIRST
SEARCH."
ITS SOMETHING WE DO IN ROBOTICS
AND ALGORITHMS ALL THE TIME.
THE IDEA IS YOU SEARCH AROUND A
LOT OF LITTLE PLACES A LITTLE
BIT.
I BREAK DOWN THE AREAS INTO
SECTORS.
I GOT THE WATER WELL AREA.
THATS SECTION ONE.
DOWN THE PATH NEXT TO IT, THATS
GOING TO BE SECTION TWO.
LOOK AT THE TREES ALONG THERE.
SECTION THREE IS ALONG THE WAY
BACK TO CAMP.
SO IM WORKING THROUGH MY
SECTORS AND MAKING SURE IM NOT
SPENDING TOO MUCH TIME IN ANYIVE
GIVEN ONE.
I SEE A TREE WITH LITTLE
DIFFERENT LEAVES THAN THE ONE
AROUND IT.
I THINK THIS IS THE KIND OF
THING THATS A BIT OF A
LANDMARK.
I LOOK AROUND ON THE GROUND.
I LOOK AROUND THE BACK OF THE
TREE.
NO LUCK.
THEN I SORT OF OF LOOK UP, AND I
SEE BLUE YARN.
THAT DOESNT OCCUR NATURALLY ON
THIS ISLAND.
WHAT IS THIS?
OH!
AND WOULDNT YOU KNOW IT?
ITS AN IDOL.
AT SOME POINT, IM GOING TO TELL
THE DAVIDS ABOUT THE IDOL
BECAUSE I WILL NEED THEIR HELP.
I KNOW IM A TARGET.
NOW, AND I THINK FOREVER.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, LETS GET TO TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
DAN, GOT TO TAKE BACK THE
NECKLACE.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO RACE OUT TO RETRIEVE A
BALL.
YOULL THEN BALANCE THAT BALL ON
A DISK WHILE YOU CROSS A BEAM.
ONCE YOU GET ALL THREE BALLS TO
THE FINISH, YOULL MANEUVER THEM
THROUGH A TRACK.
FIRST PERSON TO LAND ALL THREE
BALLS WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE AT THE VOTE.
GUARANTEED TO SEE DAY 26.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE TENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE THIRD
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
BIG STAKES THIS DEEP INTO THE
GAME.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
HIGH-STEP IT FIRST.
ALEC LEAPS OVER THE ENTIRE
HIGH-STEP.
THAT IS HOW YOU WIN A CHALLENGE
ON "SURVIVOR."
YOUVE GOT THREE BALLS TOTAL.
GOT TO BALANCE ONE AT A TIME ON
THE DISK WHILE BALANCING ON THE
TEETER TOTTER, THEN HEAD BACK
FOR THE NEXT ONE.
NICE JOB EARLY OUT.
DAVIE DROPS.
HES GOT TO GO BACK.
ALEC WITH A NICE BALANCE.
CARL DROPS.
DANS ACROSS.
ALEC IS ACROSS.
BOTH HEADING BACK FOR THEIR
SECOND BALLS.
HERE COMES KARA, MIKE, ANGELINA,
DAVIE.
ONCE AGAIN, ALEC LEAPS OVER THE
HIGH-STEP.
KARA HAS HER FIRST.
CHRISTIANS GOT HIS.
IT IS ALEC AND DAN IN THE LEAD.
BOTH WORKING ON THEIR SECOND
BALL.
EVERYBODY ELSE TRYING TO CATCH
THEM.
DANS BACK WITH HIS SECOND BALL.
HES GOT ONE LEFT.
ALEC RIGHT ON HIS TALL.
IT IS DAN IN THE LEAD RIGHT NOW.
HERE COMES ALEC WITH HIS SECOND
BALL.
IT IS ALEC AND DAN EARLY IN THE
CHALLENGE.
THEY ARE SPRINTING THROUGH THIS.
ALEC HEADING BACK NOW AGAIN FOR
THAT THIRD AND FINAL BALL.
CHRISTIAN DROPS.
GOTTA GO BACK.
DAN BACK FIRST WITH HIS THIRD
BALL.
HE CAN START WORKING ON THAT
TRACK.
ALEC BACK WITH HIS THIRD BALL.
HE CAN START WORKING.
IT IS DAN AND ALEC NOW TRYING TO
LAND THAT FIRST BALL.
THEY HAVE LED THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE.
GOTTA LAND ALL THREE BALLS TO
WIN.
HUGE IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
DAN LANDS HIS FIRST BALL.
ALEC LANDS HIS FIRST BALL.
KARA CAN START ON THE TRACK.
CARLS BACK.
HE CAN START ON THE TRACK.
ALEC TRYING TO LAND THAT SECOND
BALL.
HE DROPS.
GOTTA START AGAIN.
ANGELINA CAN WORK ON HER TRACK.
EVERYBODY TRYING TO CATCH ALEC
AND DAN RIGHT NOW.
CHRISTIAN WITH A BIG FALL.
THAT MIGHT HAVE CRUNCHED
SOMEWHERE HARD.
CARLS LANDING HIS FIRST BALL!
YES!
Jeff: ALISONS GOOD.
START WORKING.
DAN TRYING TO LAND HIS SECOND
BALL.
DAN DROPS.
ANGELINA WITH ONE.
ANGELINA, CARL, DAN, ALEC HAVE
ALL LANDED ONE BALL.
KARA DROPS.
ALEC MOVING VERY FAST ON THE
TRACK.
ALEC LANDS HIS SECOND BALL.
ALEC NOW IN THE LEAD WITH TWO.
EVERYBODY TRYING TO CATCH ALEC
NOW.
DAN DROPS AGAIN.
ALISON DROPS.
ALEC SLOWLY MAKING HIS WAY
ACROSS THE TRACK WITH HIS THIRD
AND FINAL BALL.
DAN TRYING TO LAND THAT SECOND
BALL.
DAN CANNOT GET HIS SECOND.
ANGELINA DROPS.
CARL DROPS.
ALEC DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO
IMMUNITY.
AND HES GOT IT!
ALEC WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL!
ALEC, COME ON OVER.
YEAH!
( APPLAUSE ).
GOOD JOB, ALEC.
WOOO!
Jeff: THIRD GOLIATH IN A
ROW TO WIN INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
A DAVID HAS YET TO WIN.
ALEC SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 25
DAYS, SADLY, ONE OF YOU GOING
HOME TONIGHT, WILL BE THE TENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT, THE THIRD
MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
IM GLAD ALEC WON.
IM GLAD ITS A GOLIATH.
OBVIOUSLY, I CANT TRUST
CHRISTIAN.
HES ONE OF THE SMARTEST PEOPLE
OUT HERE AND ONE OF THE MOST
DANGEROUS.
SO WE NEED TO CUT THE HEAD OFF
THE SNAKE, AND RIGHT NOW IT
LOOKS LIKE CHRISTIAN IS THE
HEAD.
♪ ♪
GOING DO INTO TRIBAL, ITS
HARD FOR ME TO EVEN WRAP MY HEAD
AROUND WHAT I HAVE TO DO,
BECAUSE I DO CARE ABOUT DAN AS A
PERSON.
IM PRAYING THAT IT DOESNT
BREAK DANS HEART, BUT I NEED TO
MOVE MYSELF FORWARD IN THE GAME,
SO DANS ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
THAT WAS RECORD TIME ALEC.
AND KNOWING ABOUT DANS IDOL,
WE MIGHT HAVE TO SPLIT VOTES.
SO I NEED THE DAVIDS.
WELL PLAY BALL.
WAVER YOU WANT.
YEAH?
SO HERE IS WHAT WERE
THINKING BECAUSE WE DONT KNOW
IF DAN HAS AN IDOL.
SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
SPLITTING VOTES?
ITS NO SECRET THAT DAN AND
ANGELINA ARE AT THE BOTTOM OF
THE GOLIATHS.
YEAH.
WERE READY TO PLAY.
OKAY, AWESOME.
IM SO DOWN.
KARA IS PITCHING THE DAN TO BE
THE ONE OUT.
I START TO FEEL DAVIDS ARE
TRYING TO PULL A FAST ONE OVER
ON US.
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE THEYRE ON
BOARD TOO FAST.
SO AS WE APPROACH TRIBAL
COUNCIL, IM FINALLY HAVING SOME
CLARITY.
IVE BEEN SO BUSY TRYING TO DO
SOMETHING, I DIDNT REALIZE THAT
THE RIGHT MOVE IS ACTUALLY TO
TAKE A STEP BACK AND GO WITH THE
FLOW.
STAND THERE STRONG WITH THE
GOLIATHS.
I KNOW, BECAUSE ITS-- I
KNOW.
MY MOM ALWAYS SAYS, "GO WITH
YOUR GUT INSTINCT."
OUR FIRST INSTINCT IS TO TAKE
CHRISTIAN OUT.
WE KNOW WHERE DAN FALLS.
WE KNOW WHERE KARA FALLS.
LIKE, WE HAVE A GOOD GRASP ON
THAT.
MIKE IS RIGHT.
IT WILL BE A CAKEWALK.
FROM A NUMBERS STANDPOINT, WE
STILL HAVE THE 6-5 ADVANTAGE,
AND WHEN I WEIGH OUT THE
OPTIONS, ITS COMING DOWN TO WHO
CAN I TRUST?
CAN I REALLY TRUST MY ALLIANCE
WITH THE DAVIDS?
HERE COMES KARA.
OH, PERFECT!
BUT RIGHT NOW, WE NEED TO
STAY GOLIATH STRONG AND TRY TO
TAKE OUT CHRISTIAN, WHO IS A
POTENTIAL THREAT.
IM FEELING LIKE ITS BIG
TORE GET OUT CHRISTIAN.
THATS THE BIGGER MOVE HERE.
NOT TO FLIP.
IT HAS TO BE CHRISTIAN.
MY HEAD IS IN A COMPLETE
WHIRLWIND BECAUSE THIS COULD BE
AN ABSOLUTE DISASTER.
YOUR FACE.
I HAVE TO ADJUST MY GAME
DRAMATICALLY.
I WANT TO WRITE DOWN DANS NAME,
BUT ITS GOING TO BE REALLY HARD
FOR ME TO TRY TO CONTINUE TO
SWAY VOTES TO DAN WITHOUT
PUTTING MY ENTIRE GAME IN
JEOPARDY.
YEAH, THATS WHAT WE WERE
GOING TO DO REGARDLESS.
YEAH, REGARDLESS.
OKAY.
CRAZY, MAN.
I DONT KNOW WHAT THEYRE
THINKING.
FIVE OF THEM.
ANGELINAS THERE, TOO.
THEYRE IDIOTS.
IM LOOKING AROUND, AND IM
NOTICING THE BEACH IS PRETTY
SEGREGATED.
WEVE GOT GOLIATH SITTING ON THE
RAFT.
AND WERE LIKE WHAT COULD THEY
BE TALKING ABOUT?
I DONT UNDERSTAND WHY
THEYRE OUT THERE.
YOU DONT UNDERSTAND?
LET ME BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU.
THEYRE GOLIATHS.
THEY ARE SO DUMB.
KARA SAID SHES READY BUT
THESE SCARED--
THATS WHAT EVERYONE SAYS.
I WISH I COULD DO ACROSS
TRIBAL LINES, BUT IM NERVOUS
BECAUSE ALL THE GOLIATHS ARE
LYING TO MY FACE AGAIN.
LET ME TELL YOU GUYS, YEAH, AND
THE ONLY REASON I HAVENT TOLD
YOU ALL IS BECAUSE US THREE KNEW
AND WE HAVENT HAD A CHANCE TO
DISCUSS IT TO DECIDE TO TELL
YOU.
BUT WE HAVE A SECRET ADVANTAGE.
WHERE WE CAN STEAL A VOTE.
WE CAN STEAL A VOTE.
YES!
DONT YOU LOVE SURPRISES.
DO YOU LIKE SURPRISES?
I FOUND THE IDOL.
WHERE WAS IT?
IT WAS OVER BY THE--
WHAT IS GOING ON WITH US?
GUESS WHAT?
I HAVE A (BLEEP) SECRET
ADVANTAGE AS WELL.
I HAVE AN IDOL NULLIFIER.
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS-- WE HAVE
THREE ADVANTAGES, GUYS.
THE STAKES AT THIS VOTE ARE
EXTRAORDINARILY HIGH.
YOU COULD EVEN SAY THEYRE
PIVOTAL.
THE GOLIATHS TOLD US THEY ARE ON
BOARD WITH THIS VOTE.
BUT IF I BELIEVE THEM, WE
WOULDNT NEED TO PLAY THESE
ADVANTAGES.
SO THAT IS WHAT WERE WEIGHING.
OKAY, THE ONE THATS TRICKY
TO USE IS THE IDOL NULLIFIER.
BASICALLY THE METHOD TO USE IT
IS TO LURE SOMEONE INTO PLAYING
AN IDOL.
IF WE THINK SOMEBODY HAS AN
IDOL AND WE STEAL THEIR VOTE.
SO WE HAVE AN ARSENAL.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE WE DONT
BLOW IT.
IF WE CANT TRUST THE GOLIATHS,
THEN WE HAVE TO CHANGE TACTICS.
ITS JUST A QUESTION OF HOW.
SO US DAVIDS HAVE THESE THREE
ADVANTAGES.
MY HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL THEY CAN
USE TO PROTECT ME.
NICKS VOTE STEAL, WHICH IS
PRIMARILY BENEFICIAL DURING
THESE TIGHT VOTES WHERE ONE VOTE
CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
AND CARLS IDOL NULLIFIER, WHICH
COULD CHANGE EVERYTHING IN THIS
GAME.
BUT THE QUESTION IS WHAT DO WE
PLAY AND WHEN?
AND HOW MANY FOR THIS VOTE?
OR NONE OF THEM AT ALL.
IN THIS GAME YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT
CAN GO WRONG.
AND WE CANT SCREW UP THIS VOTE.
♪ ♪
Jeff: WELL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ELISABETH AND JOHN, VOTED OUT AT
THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SO, ALISON, LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL
WAS A SHOCKER FOR A LOT OF YOU.
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: WHAT KIND OF IMPACT
HAS IT HAD ON THE GAME?
IT WAS REALLY JUST MY WAKE-UP
CALL.
FOR 20-SOMETHING DAYS I WAS IN
LA-LA LAND, AND THAT TRIBAL
COUNCIL SAID ITS TIME TO WAKE
UP.
LETS PLAY THIS GAME.
Jeff: GABBY, WAS THERE A
LITTLE SENSE OF JOY IN SOMEBODY
ELSE SUFFERING AT TRIBAL?
THAT SOUNDS SO MEAN, BUT ITS
NOT JOY, BUT MAYBE RELIEF TO
KNOW THAT THE GOLIATHS MAYBE GOT
A TASTE OF WHAT ITS LIKE TO NOT
ALWAYS BE ON TOP.
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, IS IT
INAPPROPRIATE TO SAY, "YEAH, I
KIND OF LIKE THAT YOU GUYS NOW
KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE?"
IT CAN BE SEEN AS A LITTLE
INSENSITIVE, AND YOU HAVE TO BE
COGNIZANT OF HOW QUICKLY THIS
GAME IS GOING TO SHIFT.
I MEAN, WE CANT FORGET THERE
ARE STILL SIX GOLIATHS AND FIVE
DAVID.
YOU HOPE SOMETHING HAS CHANGED,
BUT ITS DIFFICULT TO KNOW FOR
SURE.
Jeff: DAN, IF IT WAS A
WAKE-UP CALL, DOES THAT MEAN THE
WAR IS BACK ON?
IT IS NOW DAVIDS VERSUS GOLIATH
FOR SURE AGAIN?
ABSOLUTELY.
ID RATHER WORK WITH THE ENEMY I
KNOW THAN THE ENEMY I DONT
KNOW.
IF I GO WORK WITH THE DAVIDS IM
ON THE BOTTOM AND I DONT WANT
TO PLAY MY GAME THAT WAY,
EITHER.
Jeff: MIKE, ITS TRUE.
IF YOU CAN STICK TOGETHER, YOU
CAN PICK PEOPLE OFF.
IF YOU HAVE THE NUMBERS.
WHICH THE GOLIATHS DO.
YEAH, AND THATS A POWERFUL
THING TO HAVE AT THIS STAGE OF
THE GAME.
YOU KNOW, NOBODY WANTS TO BE THE
FIRST PERSON FROM A TRIBE TO
FLIP AND BE SEEN AS, LIKE, A
TRAITOR, AND TO RUIN EVERYONE IN
YOUR TRIBES GAME.
SO FOR ME, ITS DEFINITELY A
PRIORITY TO KEEP THE NUMBERS.
Jeff: ALEC, DO YOU BELIEVE
ITS STILL DAVID STRRS GOLIATH?
THIS GAME IS SO HARD.
ED DAVIDS HAVE BEEN WITH THE
DAVIDS SINCE DAY ONE.
I HAVE BEEN WITH THE GOLIATHS
SINCE DAY ONE.
NATURALLY, YOUR TRUST FALLS WITH
THOSE PEOPLE.
BUT THEN YOU WANT THE LINES TO
BLUR AND YOU WANT RELATIONSHIPS
TO FORM AND YOU WANT TO TRUST
PEOPLE BUT THERE ARE SO MANY
THINGS GOING ON.
WHEN WE TALK ABOUT BLURRED
LINES, I FEEL LIKE THERES A
MISCONCEPTION ABOUT WHAT THAT
MEANS.
WERE NOT SAYING, "HEY, LET ME
KNOW WHICH ONE OF US YOURE
PICKING OFF AND HOPE ITS NOT
ME."
WERE SAYING, "HEY, ONE OF YOU
IS AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
GOLIATHS.
LET US HELP YOU NOT BE AT THE
BOTTOM ANYMORE."
AND BE AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
DAVIDS.
THAT SOUNDS FUN, TOO.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU OWN THE BOTTOM.
AND THE BOTTOM CAN CHANGE DAY TO
DAY--
NOT WHEN YOURE IN A
MINORITY.
THINGS CHANGE DAY TO DAY ON
"SURVIVOR."
IF EVERYTHING IS STAGNANT IN
THE TRIBE YOURE OMAYBE
SWITCHING THINGS UP MIGHT MAKE
THINGS CHANGE FOR YOU.
PEOPLE REACHING OUT TO THE
GOLIATHS FIRST.
WERE DAVI DAVIDS AND WERE GOT
DOOR SLAMMED IN OUR FACES.
WHO IS MORE SINCERE HERE IN
TERMS OF WANTING TO WORK ACROSS
TRIBAL LINES BASED ON THE
INFORMATION GIVEN.
THE FACT IS WE HAD PLANS TO
WORK TOGETHER.
WE WORKED TOGETHER TO VOTE OUT
ELISABETH AND THEN WE WERE
SUPPOSED TO WORK TOGETHER TO
VOTE OUT ANGELINA.
WHEN IT WAS A GOLIATH SUPPOSE TO
GO, THEN EVERYTHING CHANGED.
Jeff: CARL, YOU AGREE WITH
THAT?
YOURE NODDING.
I MEAN, TRUST IS NOT
SOMETHING YOU CAN JUST TELL A
PERSON AND THEY RUN WITH TYOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
PEOPLE TELL ME, "TRUST ME, TRUST
ME," AND THE VOTE COMES THROUGH
AND ITS TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
AND IM LIKE HOW THE HELL DO I
TRUST YOU?
YOU DONT JUST TELL ME.
YOU HAVE TO PROVE IT.
I BELIEVE THATS GREAT EYE
LIVE THAT WAY, TOO.
WHO I DO GET GOOD VIBES FROM.
WHO CAN I TRUST?
WHAT RELATIONSHIPS DO I DEPEND
ON TO FURTHER ME IN THE GAME?
SO MANY THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
Jeff: NICK, THIS IS WHAT
YOURE REFERRING TO WHEN YOU
SAY, "BUT WE HAD A CHANCE AND
YOU GUYS WERE LYING TO US."
AND HE SAYS, "WE WANT TO PLAY
WITH THESE PEOPLE.
WE WANT TO DO THAT.
BUT THEY DONT, AND ITS BECAUSE
THE NUMBERS WERE 7-5.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO?
WE CAN BUST THE GAME WIDE OPEN,
CHANGE THE NUMBERS AND SAY,
"PLAY WITH WHO YOU WANT TO PLAY
WITH AND PLAY WHO YOU TRUST AND
FORGET ABOUT THE BUFF WE PUT ON,
ON DAY ONE."
Jeff: CHRISTIAN, YOU LISTEN
TO ALEC AND HE SAYS I DONT WANT
IT TO BE TRIBAL LINES.
I WANT US TO ALL PLAY SO I CAN
PLAY MY BEST GAME AND THE
CONVERSATION KEEPS GOING BACK TO
DAVID VERSUS GOLIATH.
GAME REMINDS OF SORT OF LIKE
AN OLD CAR THAT YOURE NOT SURE
IS GOING TO START.
YOU KNOW, WE HIT THE MERGE, AND
YOURE LIKE, OKAY, IS THE GAME
GOING TO KICK IN.
AND YOU TURN THE CAR IS & IT
DOESNT START.
THAT ALMOST BLEW OUR ENGINE.
LETS DO IT ONE MORE TIME, AND
WELL FIND OUT WHETHER OR NOT
THE CRANK ACTUALLY TURNS OVER.
WE TURN THE KEY TONIGHT.
Jeff: WOW.
SO TONIGHTS VOTE IS PIVOTAL.
TONIGHTS VOTE IS MAJOR.
EITHER ONE OF THE GOLIATHS
SWITCHED OVER AND IS GOING TO
JOIN US IN THE VOTE, OR THE
GOLIATHS ARE GOING TO TAKE A
BIGGER ADVANTAGE IN THE NUMBERS.
ITS JUST THAT SIMPLE.
Jeff: OKAY, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JEFF.
I THINK ITS THE CORRECT TIME
FOR ME TO PULL SOMETHING OUT OF
MY POCKET.
AND ITS A SECRET ADVANTAGE.
HMMM...
Jeff: GO AHEAD AND READ IT,
NICK.
"THIS ADVANTAGE ALLOWS YOU TO
STEAL A VOTE FROM ANOTHER PLAYER
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE PLAYER WHOSE VOTE YOU STEAL
WILL NOT VOTE.
INSTEAD YOU WILL CAST A SECOND
VOTE.
SO I GOT MY SECOND VOTE RIGHT
HERE.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO ITS
PRETTY CLEAR.
NICK HAS THE POWER TO STEAL A
VOTE FROM ONE PLAYER.
THAT PERSON WILL NOT VOTE.
NICK WILL GET TWO VOTES.
THE QUESTION IS BEFORE WE VOTE
WHOSE VOTE ARE YOU GOING TO
STEAL?
I THINK ILL TAKE ALISONS
VOTE.
OH, DIDNT EXPECT THAT.
Jeff: ALISON THE MOST
POWERFUL THING IN THE GAME IS
YOUR VOTE AND HE JUST TOOK IT.
I MEAN THURTS A LOT.
I WANT TO PLAY THIS GAME, AND A
BIG PART OF PLAYING THIS GAME IS
BY VOTING.
AND I WANT TO DEMONSTRATE TRUST
WITH THE PEOPLE THEY SAID, AND
NOW IM DEPRIVED OF THAT
OPPORTUNITY.
Jeff: OKAY, SO, ALISON, YOU
WILL NOT VOTE TONIGHT.
NICK, WILL YOU WILL VOTE TWICE.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
GABBY, YOURE UP.
OH, MAN!
I HAVE NO IDEA WHATS GOING TO
HAPPEN TONIGHT.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE.
I KNEW IT!
CLASSIC DAN!
OH, MAN!
SAVAGE!
THEYRE TRYING TO PULL A FAST
ONE.
ILL MAKE SURE IT AINT ME GOING
HOME.
Jeff: YOURE PLAYING THIS
FOR YOURSELF.
YES, SIR.
Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND THIS... IS THE IDOL
NULLIFIER.
THE NULLIFIER BLOCKS THE POWER
OF AN IDOL, IF PLAYED AGAINST
THE CORRECT PERSON.
THIS NULLIFIER WAS PLAYED
AGAINST DAN.
OH, MY GOD!
WOW!
WHOA!
WHAT!
Jeff: DAN, YOUR IDOL HAS NO
POWER.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST DAN WILL
STILL COUNT.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
OH, MY GOD!
FIRST VOTE, CHRISTIAN.
KEEP THE TRADITION GOING.
CHRISTIAN.
ANGELINA.
THREE VOTES CHRISTIAN, ONE VOTE
JAEG.
ANGELINA.
TWO VOTES ANGELINA.
DAN.
THATS THREE VOTES CHRISTIAN,
TWO VOTES ANGELINA, ONE VOTE
DAN.
THATS THREE VOTES CHRISTIAN,
TWO VOTES ANGELINA, TWO VOTES
DAN.
THATS THREE VOTES CHRISTIAN,
THREE VOTES DAN, TWO VOTES
ANGELINA.
DAN.
THATS FOUR VOTES DAN, THREE
VOTES CHRISTIAN, TWO VOTES
ANGELINA.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
DAN.
THATS FIVE.
THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
BING!
DAN, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
WE LOVE YOU.
BYE, DAN.
Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
Jeff: WELL, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN A LONG TIME, WERE BACK
EVEN.
FIVE DAVIDS, FIVE GOLIATHS.
BUT BASED ON THE REACTIONS AT
TONIGHTS TRIBAL, THE QUESTION
IS HAVE THE LINES FINALLY
BLURRED?
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
WHEN YOUVE BEEN BETRAYED...
YOUR NAME WAS A CONTINGENCY
PLAN.
GOLIATHS DONT KNOW HOW
VICIOUS I CAN BE.
Jeff: ...HELL HATH NO FURY.
YOURE TOO EMOTIONAL.
DO YOU NOT KNOW WHAT GAME
WERE PLAYING.
Jeff: LIKE A WOMAN SCORNED.
CARL AND GABBY ARE ON A
COLLISION COURSE.
YOU THINK WHEN YOU HAVE AN
IDOL YOURE GOLDEN, BUT I JUST
GOT KNOCKED OUT OF THE GAME.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THERE WAS
A DOGGONE IDOL NULLIFIER.
I TAKE A LOT OF PRIDE.
IM PRETTY SURE KARA FLIPPED HER
VOTE.
IT KIND OF HURTS A LITTLE BIT.
BUT IF SHE WANTS TO WORK ON THE
BOTTOM OF THE DAVIDS THATS HER
PROBLEM, NOT MINE.