Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
AT THE KAMA TRIBE, AURORA, JOE,
AND AUBRY WERE OUTCASTS.
NOBODY WANTS TO TALK TO US.
Jeff: AT THE MANU TRIBE,
WENDY WAS RUFFLING FEATHERS.
ALL CREATURES DESERVE TO
LIVE.
DO NOT TELL ME THAT WE CANT
EAT THAT CHICKEN.
Jeff: BUT WOULD GO HAD A
PLAN OF HIS OWN.
I DECIDED MAYBE ITS NOT
WENDY.
ITS CHRIS.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
CHRIS WAS VOTED OUT.
CHRIS, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
AND HAD A DECISION TO MAKE: GO
HOME OR GRAB THE TORCH AND GO TO
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
Captioning funded by CBS
I CANT BELIEVE IT!
I AM STILL PROCESSING IT.
YOU KNOW IM NOT--
YOU!
IM NOT SAD.
THEY GOT ME.
HOWS IT FEEL?
TERRIBLE.
I JUST FEEL BETRAYED.
OH!
THATS HOW IT FEELS?
BETRAYAL?
REALLY?
MAN, I GOT BLINDSIDED.
MAN, I CANT BELIEVE IT.
SERIOUSLY, YOU VOTED ME OUT, AND
HE TOTALLY BLINDSIDED KEITH, SO
THAT IS A TASTE OF YOUR OWN
MEDICINE.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOURE NOT GOING TO SHOW UP HERE
AND BE TREATED WITH OPEN ARMS.
NO THANK YOU.
NO.
THIS IS WHAT I WENT THROUGH.
READ THE SIGN, BRO.
"IF AT ANY POINT YOU WISH TO
END YOUR ADVENTURE, RAISE THE
SAIL, AND A BOAT WILL PICK YOU
UP."
YOURE NOT GOING TO COME IN
HERE TO THE FREAKING HOLIDAY
INN.
SORRY.
ITS THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
♪ ♪
IM TRYING.
IM ACTUALLY NOT AS GOOD AS
CHRIS.
WENDY LOOKS SKINNY.
YOUR WAIST LOOKS SMALL.
"SURVIVOR" DIET.
WENDYS ALWAYS UNDER THREAT
OF GOING HOME, BUT ITS NEVER
WENDY.
EVERYBODY HAS DIFFERENT STYLES
OF PLAYING THE GAME, AND THIS IS
MINE.
YOU DONT KNOW WHAT IM GOING TO
DO NEXT.
BUT, AT THE SAME TIME, I
UNDERSTAND THAT I WAS BEING
CRAZY FOR TAKING THE FLINT, SO I
PUT THE FLINT BACK AND, LIKE,
DAVID FOUND IT.
AND HE SAID, "YOU GUYS, YOU
FOUND THE FLINT."
AND EVERYBODY IS LIKE, "OH,
LOOK.
IT MYSTERIOUSLY POPPED UP."
SHE LITERALLY TOOK THE FLINT.
LIKE THATS NOT NORMAL.
IM NOT EVEN CLOSE TO BEING
DONE.
I ALREADY TOLD RICK MY MASTER
PLAN.
WHAT IS IT?
WHATS YOUR MASTER PLAN?
I DONT WANT TO TELL YOU.
YOURE GOING TO GET MAD AT ME.
GOD YOU ARE-- IVE NEVER
EITHER PLAYED WITH OR SEEN
ANYBODY PLAY THE WAY YOU DO.
LIKE A WILD CARD.
YOU WANT TO WIN, DONT YOU?
YEAH, OF COURSE I DO.
OKAY.
I... OKAY.
HEY, LOOK, I HAVENT BEEN
ELIMINATED SO FAR, SO SOMETHING
MUST BE WORK.
I FEEL LIKE IF I JUST GO WITH
THE FLOW, THINGS WILL WORK OUT.
THIS SHOULD REALLY BE WENDY.
RIGHT.
100%.
NOBODY PLAYING GAMES.
ONLY BECAUSE SHES LITERALLY,
LIKE, LIVING IN HER OWN LITTLE
EYE DONT EVEN KNOW WHATS GOING
ON UP THERE.
WHY DO YOU HAVE SUCH A
RIDICULOUSLY SMALL SHELL?
RIGHT NOW THERE ARE FIVE
PEOPLE WORKING IT, AND WENDY IS
THE OUTSIDER.
SHES NOT A NORMAL PERSON.
SHE HID OUR FLINT AND THOUGHT IT
WAS FUNNY.
WHO DOES THAT!
SHES ALWAYS GOING TO BE THIS
PERSON YOU WONT BE ABLE TO
TRUST.
WENDY IS THE VOTE.
THAT SEEMS TO MAKE THE MOST
SENSE FOR EVERYBODY.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
KAMA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW MANU TRIBE.
CHRIS, VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
OH, MY GOD!
SO WRONG!
Jeff: THAT MAY BE THE
BIGGEST REACTION IVE EVER SEEN
TO A VOTE-OUT.
RON, WHAT IS IT THAT YOURE
READING INTO SEEING CHRIS BEING
VOTED OUT?
YOU SEE HOW HARD HE WORKS IN
CHALLENGES AND YOU YOU SEE HE
WAS CARRYING ALL-- THE WHOLE
ENTIRE TRIBE.
IT & TO SEE THEY WOULD VOTE HIM
OUT, ITS ALMOST LIKE A
BETRAYAL.
Jeff: WOW, LAUREN, BIG
WORDS, "BETRAYAL," AND "CHRIS
WAS CARRYING THE ENTIRE TRIBE."
I THINK ITS INTERESTING TO
THROW OUT WORDS LIKE THAT WHEN
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT OUR CAMP
LIFE IS LIKE.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IT SPEAKS
TO THE TRUE, UNPREDICTABLE
NATURE OF THIS GAME.
BECAUSE YOURE RIGHT, YOU DONT
KNOW WHATS GOING ON.
EVERYBODY, DROP YOUR BUFFS.
OH, JEFF PROBST!
Jeff: YOURE SWITCHING FROM
TWO TRIBES TO THREE TRIBES.
EXPANSION TO THREE.
WHEN JEFF SAID, "DROP YOUR
BUFFS," I LITERALLY TURNED TO
JOE AND SAID, "IM GOING TO PEE
MY PANTS RIGHT NOW."
YOU HAVE THIS PIT IN YOUR
STOMACH.
YOU HAVE NO CONTROL OVER THAT
PART OF THE GAME.
IT IS COMPLETELY RANDOM WHO YOU
END UP WITH.
ITS TURNS YOUR GAME UPSIDE
DOWN.
Jeff: HE WE ARE.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
HERE WE GO.
GOOD LUCK YALL.
Jeff: IF YOURE BLUE GOES
GO TO BLUE.
YELLOW GOES TO YELLOW, AND GREEN
IN THE MIDDLE.
IM GREEN.
OH, MY GOD!
WERE THE WHOLE TRIBE!
WOW!
THE HAPPY FAMILY STAYING
TOGETHER, I GUESS.
Jeff: EVERYBODY FIND YOUR
SPOT--
YOURE GREEN.
OH, MY GOD, IM GREEN!
I THOUGHT I WAS BLUE.
Jeff: THIS IS CRAZY.
AT FIRST GLANCE, EVERYBODY IS
WITH THEIR OWN FORMER TRIBE
MEMBERS WITH ONE EXCEPTION,
WENDY, THE ONLY LONE WOLF NOT
WITH HER OWN ORIGINAL PACK.
NO WAY!
HOLY CRAP.
OH, MY GOD!
Jeff: I AM STUNNED.
WERE STUNNED.
WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE TO MEET
YOU GUYS.
Jeff: GAVIN, YOUVE BEEN A
FAN OF THIS GAME SINCE YOU WERE
A KID.
EVER RECALL A SWITCH LIKE THIS?
I DONT THINK SO BUT IM
HAPPY TO BE A PART OF THIS ONE.
SO IM ALL SMILES RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE
THREE NEW TRIBES, AND WE END UP
WITH, ON MANU, FOUR MEMBERS FROM
KAMA, AND ONE ORIGINAL MEMBER
FROM MANU WENDY.
YES.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING RIGHT
NOW?
BECAUSE IF "SURVIVOR" IS A GAME
OF NUMBERS, AND THESE FOUR ARE
TIGHT, YOU WOULD BE IN TROUBLE.
YEAH, I WOULD BE IN TROUBLE.
BUT ALL OF THESE PEOPLE LOOK
VERY ATHLETIC SO I DONT THINK
WERE GOING TO LOSE CHALLENGES.
Jeff: DOWN AT KAMA, FIVE
ORIGINAL KAMA, STILL WEARING
YELLOW, STILL GOING BACK TO THE
SAME CAMP.
AND IN THE MIDDLE, WITH A
BRAND-NEW TRIBE, FIVE FORMER
MANU, YOUR TRIBE NAME, LESU.
LESU.
L-E-S-U.
THAT SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
Jeff: KAMA, GRAB YOUR STUFF
AND LITERALLY HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
THANKS, JEFF.
HAVE FUN, GUYS.
Jeff: MANU, GRAB YOUR
STUFF.
WENDY, SHOW THEM AROUND CAMP.
GOOD LUCK WITH THE CHICKENS,
JOE.
WENDY IS GONNA HATE HIM IF HE
KILLS THE CHICKEN.
Jeff: LESU, A MAP TO YOUR
NEW HOME.
I COULD NOT BELIEVE WE WERE
STILL TOGETHER.
AND WENDY IS STILL ON THE TRIBE
WITH HER TIGHTEST ALLIANCE,
WHICH IS THE CHICKEN.
AND IM THINK, GOOD LUCK.
GOOD LUCK WITH WENDY.
♪ ♪
WHAT JUST HAPPENED!
INSANE!
KAMA!
COMING INTO THIS TRIBE SWAP,
I WAS SUPER NERVOUS BECAUSE I
REALLY DIDNT KNOW WHERE I STOOD
WITH THE ORIGINAL O.G. KAMA
TRIBE, BUT OUR NUMBERS GOT CUT
IN HALF SO A NEW DYNAMIC.
KAMA STRONG, ONE, TWO, THREE.
KAMA STRONG!
I THINK THE ONE DIFFERENCE
IM DOING THIS SEASON THAN PAST
SEASON IM TRYING TO BUILD MORE
STRONG, SOLID RELATIONSHIPS.
SAND EVERYWHERE, SANDY.
I FEEL REALLY GOOD WITH AURORA.
EARLY ON I FEEL LIKE WELL
CONNECTED AND I DO FEEL LIKE
SHES ON MY SIDE.
BUT THERE ARE ONLY FIVE OF US,
AND I WANT TO MAKE SURE WE HAVE
A LITTLE BIT OF A MAJORITY
GOING.
IM REALLY TRYING TO SOLIDIFY A
RELATIONSHIP WITH RON, WHO I
SEEM TO HAVE A PRETTY GOOD
RAPPORT WITH.
I FEEL GREAT WITH YOU, BRO.
I FEEL AGREEMENT WITH YOU,
TOO.
AND I THINK AURORA WOULD VOTE
WITH US.
EVERY TIME I TALK WITH HER SHES
NOTHING BUT SMILES AND
LOVEY-DOVEY AND AWESOME.
LIKE WERE IN A REALLY-- WERE
IN A GREAT SPOP SPOT.
IM JUST TRYING TO THINK OF,
LIKE, DOWN THE ROAD, WHO IS
GOING TO TRY TO TAKE ME OUT?
THE LAST THING I WOULD WANT
TO DO.
NOBODYS GOING TO VOTE YOU OUT.
THATS RIDICULOUS.
I HOPE NOT.
I HAD A GREAT CONVERSATION WITH
JOE AT THE WATERING HOLE BECAUSE
I HAD TO CONVINCE HIM I WAS WITH
HIM.
I ACTED LIKE I LOVE HIM, I ADORE
AND HE WAS LIKE, "ALL RIGHT,
RON, I GOT YOU."
BACK AT KAMA.
KAMA, KAMA.
BEST TRIBE.
SO HES WALK AROUND FEELING
REALLY CONFIDENT.
WHAT HE DOESNT KNOW 20 MINUTES
AGO I TOLD JULIA, WHY DONT YOU
GO THROUGH JOES BAG.
ILL KEEP HIM AT THE WATERING
HOLE.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE JOE
DOESNT HAVE AN IDOL.
BECAUSE IF WE LOSE A CHALLENGE,
I MAY CONSIDER VOTING HIM OUT.
HES TOO BIG OF A THREAT, AND
HES A CHALLENGE BEAST, AND WE
NEED TO GET HIM OUT AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE BECAUSE IF WE GET TO
THE MERGE, THEY COULD BE REALLY
DANGEROUS.
HEY, JULIA.
YOU FIND ANYTHING?
NO.
THERE WAS NOTHING IN THERE,
NOTHING IN HIS PANTS, NOTHING IN
HIS BAG OF SEA SHELLS.
I DONT THINK HE HAS IT.
GOOD JOB.
WERE PROBABLY NOT GOING TO LOSE
A CHALLENGE WHEN YOU LOOK AT HOW
STRONG OUR TRIBE SAND IF WE DO
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT IT, WE KNOW
THAT JOE DOESNT HAVE AN IDOL.
HES GOING TO BE AN EASY TARGET.
YOU GUYS, THE ODDS OF THAT.
THATS A SMALL PERCENT.
YOU TAKE A CONSTANT, FOUR OUT OF
13, FOUR OUT OF 11.
YOU MULTIPLY THAT FOUR TIMES.
ITS LESS THAN 1%.
I WAS LOOKING AT THOSE TRIBES, I
THINK IN CHALLENGES WE STACK UP
REALLY WELL WITH THOSE TWO
TRIBES.
I THINK WE DO.
THATS ALL WE HAVE TO DO.
THATS ALL WE NEED TO DO.
THE GOOD THING ABOUT BEING
ALL TOGETHER ON THE NEW LESU
TRIBE IS WE HAVE RELATIONSHIPS
TOGETHER.
WE TRUST EACH OTHER.
THE PROBLEM IS IF WE DONT WIN,
WERE GOING TO FRACTURE REAL
QUICK.
I WONDER WHAT WENDY IS
CONTINGENT THEM.
EVERYTHING.
OH, EVERYTHING.
WENDY WAS THE ODD DUCK OUT
AND WE COULD ALL REALLY AROUND
THAT AND NOW WERE ALL LOOKING
AT EACH OTHER.
THERES NO ODD PERSON OUT.
THERES NO DISTRACTION.
WE JUST KNOW THAT IF WE LOSE,
ONE OF US IS GOING HOME, AND
THUS FAR, WE HAVE NOT BEEN GOOD
AT WINNING.
WE SHOULD DEFINITELY GET A
FIRE GOING.
YEAH.
COMING TO A NEW CAMP SUCKS.
THERE IS NO SHELTER.
THERES VERY LITTLE RICE.
HOW CRAZY IS THIS?
THIS IS INSANE.
BEING A RETURNING PLAYER, I
KNOW "SURVIVOR" IS HARD.
EVEN THE STRONGEST PERSON CAN
BREAK UNDER THESE CIRCUMSTANCES.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I JUST THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO THROW UP FOR A SECOND.
BUT WERE GOOD.
I THINK I THOUGHT COMING OUT
HERE WOULD BE SUPER FUN, AND,
LIKE, I REALLY UNDERESTIMATED
HOW DIFFICULT IT IS TO NOT
EXPEET TO NOT SLEEP.
ITS A LOT HARDER THAN I WAS
EVER EXPECTING IT TO BE.
IM SO HUNGRY.
BUT, LIKE, I CANT EAT THE RICE
ANYMORE BECAUSE IT JUST MAKES ME
REALLY NAUSEOUS.
I KNOW, IT TASTES SO GOOD.
BUT MORE THAN, THAT I THINK
THE HARDEST PART FOR ME IS NOT
BEING ABLE TO TALK TO MY FAMILY.
I REALLY MISS MY MOM AND DAD A
LOT.
AND ITS REALLY HARD NOT TO HAVE
THAT SUPPORT SYSTEM THAT TELLS
YOU, LIKE, "ITS OKAY."
LIKE "EVERYTHINGS GOING TO BE
OKAY."
SO YOURE JUST KIND WIFE THESE,
YOU KNOW, FOUR OTHER PEOPLE THAT
YOU KIND OF TRUST, BUT THEYRE
NOT YOUR FAMILY.
THEYRE JUST PEOPLE THAT YOURE
COMPETING AGAINST.
WHY DONT WE GO DOWN TO THE
BEACH AND I CAN GIVE YOU THE
GRAND TOUR.
THATS PERFECT.
WE HAVE THE ENTIRE BEACH.
AND THE BEACHES KIND OF MEET
RIGHT THERE.
AND THERES OUR MAKESHIFT FIRE
PIT.
THATS A CLEVER IDEA.
IF YOU GUYS WANT TREE MAIL,
ITS DOWN THAT PATH.
THERE ARE A BUNCH OF SHARKS SO
THIS IS THE BEST PLACE TO FISH.
SO THEN--
THIS IS THE WELL.
NICE.
THANKS FOR SHOWING US AROUND.
ITS YOUR CAMP, TOO.
YEAH, THANK YOU.
I AM REALLY EXCITED ABOUT THE
TRIBE FLOP.
WE HAVE FOUR KAMA WITH THE LOAN
MANU.
IF WE LIEWRKZ WEVE GOT WENDY.
SHES THE EASY PICKOFF.
YOUVE GOT SPUNK, GIRL.
YOU DID.
YOUVE GOT SPUNK.
RIGHT ON.
THE I THINK IS THATS TOUGH
SIREALLY LIKE WENDY.
SHE IS VERY SWEET AND SHES A
KIND HEART.
OUR CAMP WAS NICE BUT WE
DIDNT HAVE THE VIEWS YOU HAVE
HERE.
WE HAVE THE VIEWS, BUT, LIKE,
MY TRIBE SUCKED.
REALLY?
REALLY.
IM HAPPY I GOT STUCK WITH
YOU GUYS.
I DONT CARE IF IM ON THE
BOTTOM.
THEY WERE BULLIES.
REALLY?
SERIOUS?
WHO IS THE RING LEADER.
THAT GIRL IS GIVING ME
EVERYTHING ABOUT THE MANU TRIBE.
SHES GIVING US A FULL RUNDOWN
OF EVERY SINGLE PLAYER.
YOU DONT THINK DAVE AND
KELLEY WANT TO PLAY TOGETHER?
FROM WHAT IVE SEEN, I DONT
THINK SO.
THIS GIRL IS A WEALTH OF
INFORMATION.
AND THESE AN SAVE THE.
WHERE ARE THE CHICKENS AT?
DID YOU KILL THEM YET?
WE HAVE TWO LEFT.
WE HAVE FISHING GEAR.
DO THEY LAY ANY EGGS?
THEYRE GOING TO START LAYING
SOME.
YOU THINK THEY WILL START
LAYING?
I THINK SO.
CHICKENS SEEM TO BE DOING
GOOD.
THEYRE CUTE, ARENT THEY?
HEY, CHICKENS, NO PRESSURE
BUT YOU BETTER START LAYING
EGGS, OR IM GOING TO EAT YOU.
I THINK YOU JUST CUT THE HEAD
OFF, AND THEN YOU BOIL IT, I
THINK.
AND THEN THE FEATHERS COME OUT
EASY.
ROTISSERIE CHICKEN.
I GENUINELY LIKE MY NEW
TRIBE.
I FEEL REALLY BAD DOING THIS.
I KNOW ON THEIR AGENDA WAS TO
KILL THESE CHICKENS AND,
OBVIOUSLY, I HAVE MY OWN AGENDA.
AND I FINALLY RELEASED THE
CHICKENS!
THEYRE FREE!
THEIR LIVES ARE SAVED.
THIS IS MY FASTER PLAN.
IM ECSTATIC.
I JUST HAVE TO HEAD BACK NOW, GO
TO SLEEP AND PRETEND, "WHAT?
WHAT?
WHAT CHICKENS?
IM SO HAPPY!
( THUNDER )
ITS RAINING, BRO.
OKAY, NOW ITS COMING.
ALL YOU COULD DO WAS JUST SIT
THERE IN YOUR WETNESS AND JUST
BE ANGRY, BE MAD.
BE HUNGRY, BE WHATSOEVER.
IT JUST SUCKS.
THE MIND IS THE STRONGEST THING
YOU HAVE OUT HERE, BUT ITS ALSO
THE MOST DANGEROUS THING.
IT HAS MADE ME LOOK AT THAT
MAST, RAISING THAT MAST IS A
COMPLETE LOSING SOLUTION.
LIKE, THAT MAST IS MY FOOD.
THAT MAST IS MY BURGER.
ITS A NICE BED.
ITS A HOT SHOWER.
ITS A FREAKING DRY TOWEL.
THAT MAST IS EVERYTHING.
SO RIGHT NOW MY MIND IS MY
FREAKING BEST FRIEND, BUT ALSO
MY WORST ENEMY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
HUH?
YEAH.
I NEEDED A SECOND.
IM SURE HE THINKS WERE
PLOTTING AGAINST HIM.
WHO CARES.
JUST BECAUSE YOU CRY AND YOU
WERE BLINDSIDED IN THE GAME DOES
NOT MEAN I SHOULD AUTOMATICALLY
FEEL SAD FOR YOU BECAUSE YOU DID
NOT FEEL SAD FOR ME WHEN YOU
VOTED FOR ME.
I DONT NEED HIM.
HES GOING THROUGH THE
REMORSE PROCESS.
HE IS.
I DONT WANT TO BE HERE.
BUT I AM.
ITS, LIKE, VOLUNTARY TORTURE.
IM STUCK ON AN ISLAND WITH TWO
PEOPLE THAT ARE PISSED AT ME.
IVE GOT NOTHING BUT MYSELF.
ITS REALLY HARD BEING OUT HERE.
A LOT OF MY FEARS STARTED TO
COME OUT.
IVE GOT A FEAR OF FAILURE.
OF, NEED FOR APPROVAL.
LIKE, JUST TRYING TO BE PERFECT.
THIS PERFECTIONIST.
AND, YOU KNOW, ALL THOSE FEARS
HAPPENED.
I FAILED.
LIKE, IT GOT ME VOTED OUT, THIS
IDEAL OF PLAYING A PERFECT GAME
IS COMPLETELY SHOT.
SO COMING TO TERMS WITH THAT.
MAYBE THATS A PART OF THIS
JOURNEY, TOO.
OH, MY GOD.
GOOD JOB!
THATS A WIN FOR THE DAY.
YEAH, CONGRATULATIONS.
I LIKE CHRIS TODAY BETTER
THAN CHRIS YESTERDAY, RIGHT?
YEAH.
THE REAL TEST TO ADAPTATION
IS OUT HERE.
IM OUT HERE TO GET AS FAR AS I
POSSIBLY CAN DESPITE ALL THE
OBSTACLES THAT ARE BEING THROWN
AT ME RIGHT NOW.
THANK YOU FOR LUNCH.
THIS IS AMAZING.
WERE SO HUNGRY.
TASTY.
THANK YOU FOR BEING A
FISHERMAN.
I DONT KNOW WHAT THIS ISLAND
HAS IN STORE YET.
ARE WE ON A TRIBE?
ARE WE GOING AGAINST EACH OTHER?
TIME WILL TELL.
SO IM JUST GOING TO LOOK OUT
FOR THEM AS BEST I CAN AND HOPE
THEY LOOK OUT FOR ME.
WERE KIND OF A STRANGE FAMILY
OUT HERE.
ITS A LIZARD.
DUDE, GET THAT AWAY FROM ME.
WATCH OUT, ITS COMING TO GET
YOU.
I SWEAR TO GOD, DUDE.
I WILL DROP-KICK YOU.
THAT IS LAME, FREAKING LAME.
♪ ♪
I CANT BELIEVE IT.
IN THE MORNING, CHICKENS ARE
GONE.
TO ME IT SEEMS LIKE THERES ONLY
ONE PERSON HERE TO DOESNT WANT
TO SEE THE CHICKEN, WENDY.
ITS POSSIBLE WENDY LET THE
CHICKENS GO.
SHES LIKE, "THEYRE GOING TO
KILL THEM.
IM GOING TO LET THEM GO.
CHICKENS, I JUST THINK ITS A
SOFT SPOT IN WENDYS HEART.
BUT IF I CATCH ONE, ITS NOT
GOING BACK IN THE COOP.
ITS GOING UNDER THE MACHETE.
ITS CRAZY.
SHE... SERIOUS?
THATS NOT COOL.
THATS NOT COOL, CHICKENS!
SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS WANT TO DO
TODAY?
WHAT IF WE JUST-- LETS TRY
TO CATCH IT.
NO!
WELL, WENDY, YOURE MAKING MA
THIS TOUGH.
PLEASE, GUYS.
THAT WOULD BE WORSE THAN ME
GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GIRL, YOU SET FREE BREAKFAST,
LUNCH, AND DINNER.
LIKE, IM STILL 100% ALL FOR
KILLING THE CHICKENS.
I DO NOT CARE IF WENDY CRIES
HERSELF TO SLEEP AT NIGHT.
PLEASE, GUYS, YOURE MY BEST
TRIBE.
YOURE MY TRIBEMATES.
SHE KIND OF WENT NUTS.
YOUD RATHER GET VOTED OUT THAN
SEE A CHICKEN DIE?
THATS BIZARRE.
THATS NOT SOMEONE YOU CAN
TRUST.
THATS SOMEONE YOU VOTE OUT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE
GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
YEAH!
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JULIA, I GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
AND TODAY, TWO TRIBES WILL WIN
IMMUNITY.
( APPLAUSE )
TWO TRIBES WILL BE SAFE AT THE
VOTE.
LETS GET TO IT.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO RACE OVER A SERIES OF
A-FRAMES WHILE CARRYING COILS OF
ROPE.
YOULL THEN USE THAT ROPE TO
PULL A HEAVY CRATE TO THE
FINISH.
USE THE PIECES INSIDE THE CRATE
TO SOLVE A PUZZLE.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO SOLVE THE
PUZZLE, WIN IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL, LOSERS, SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE FOURTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, DAY 11, ON
"SURVIVOR," RAIN COMING DOWN IN
FIJI.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
YOU GOTTA GET UP AND OVER THAT
A-FRAME.
ITS SIPLY, ITS SLIPPERY.
Jeff: EVERYBODY SLIDES DOWN
FOR LESU.
QUICKLY, ERIK AND GAVIN ARE UP
FOR MANU.
THEY PULL UP VICTORIA.
THEYRE PULLING UP WENDY.
JOE GETS UP NOW FOR KAMA.
THERE GOES LAUREN TRYING TO GET
UP.
I CANT!
Jeff: IT IS MANU IN THE
EARLY LEAD.
GRAB THE ROPE, PULL.
YES, YES, YOU GOT IT.
I GOT YOU.
Jeff: DAVID TRYING TO GET
UP.
KAMAS GOOD.
LESU FALLING BEHIND NOW.
MANU NOW WORKING ON THAT SECOND
WALL.
GET THE ROPE!
IT IS LAWREB FIRST UP FOR LESU.
SHE USES THE ROPE TO PULL UP
WENTWORTH.
THAT RAIN HAS MADE THE WALL VERY
SLIPPERY.
WANT TO HELP EACH SNRG.
Jeff: JOE NOW GOING TO USE
HIMSELF AS A HUMAN LADDER.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: FINALLY LESU HAS
EVERYBODY UP.
KAMA MAKING A HUMAN LADDER.
THIS IS WHAT YOU DO ON
"SURVIVOR"!
WORKING TOGETHER AS A TRIBE TO
SOLVE A PROBLEM.
I CANT REACH.
RON ON JULIAS SHOULDERS.
AND HERE COMES AUBRY.
THE ENTIRE TRIBE IS A HUMAN
LADDER.
GOOD JOB, AUBRY!
Jeff: EVERYBODY STRUGGLING
TO GET TO THE TOP.
DAVID GETS TO THE TOP FOR LESU.
THERE GOES GAVIN, NOW.
JULIE NOW GETS TO THE TOP.
THERE GOES WENTWORTH.
YOURE GOOD, MANU!
GET THE ROPE!
WOULD GO SUP, AND JOE IS UP.
EVERYBODY COMES DOWN AT ONCE.
SECOND PHASE OF THIS CHALLENGE
NOW.
YOUVE GOT TO ATTACH YOUR THREE
COILS OF ROPE.
GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: YOURE GOING TO USE
THIS NOW TO PULL THAT CRATE.
ONCE YOUR ROPES TOGETHER, YOU
CAN START PULLING.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: MANU HAS THEIR ROPE
TOGETHER.
MANU STARTING TO PULL.
THERE GOES KAMA NOW.
LESU NOW HAS THEIR ROPES
TOGETHER.
THEYRE IN ON IT.
ALL THREE TRIBES FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY ON DAY 11 IN "SURVIVOR:
EDGE OF EXTINCTION"!
ONE, TWO, THREE!
KAMAS FIRST THERE.
MANUS THERE.
YOURE GOOD!
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: BIG PULL BY LESU.
YOURE GOOD, LESU!
NOW YOU HAVE TO START UNTYING
KNOTS TO GET THAT TOP OFF.
THEN UNTIE KNOTS TO GET THE
PUZZLE PIECES FREE.
GREAT COMMUNICATION FROM
CAMBODIA.
EVERYBODY CALM AND TALKING.
MANU RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
LESU IS RIGHT BEHIND.
PUT THEM ALL IN.
Jeff: IT WILL BE JOE AND
RON ON THE PUZZLE FOR KAMA.
ERIK AND AUBRY ON THE PUZZLE FOR
MANU.
HERE COMES LESU WITH THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES.
AND ITS GOING TO BE WENTWORTH
AND DAVID ON THE PUZZLE FOR
LESU.
NOW YOU CAN START SOLVING.
GRAB THAT-- RON, GRAB THAT
PIECE.
Jeff: ITS A SLOW,
METHODICAL PROCESS AS YOU BEGIN
TO FIGURE OUT WHEN PIECES NEED
TO MOVE WHERE.
THERE ARE TWO DRAGONS.
THATS RIGHT.
ONE AT A TIME.
Jeff: THIS IS WHERE
COMMUNICATION WILL BE ESSENTIAL.
RIGHT TO LEFT.
Jeff: UP TO THE MAKE SURE
YOURE MAKING COMPLEMENTARY
MOVES.
YES, JOE.
Jeff: YOU WILL KNOW YOURE
MAKING PROGRESS AS YOU START TO
SEE THESE SYMBOLS START
TOGETHER.
SEE THE OPEN SPACE, THE ONE
ON THE LEFT?
THAT HAS TO MATCH IEWP.
NO, SWITCH THOSE.
Jeff: AUBRY GOING TO SWAP
OUT.
HERE COMES WENDY NOW FOR MANU.
ITS ERIK AND WENDY.
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
Jeff: RON AND JOE HAVE A
LOT OF MOMENTUM NOW.
THE ONE ON THE END OF THE
DRAGON IS NOT CORRECT.
Jeff: WENDY IS COMING IN
MOVING A LOT OF PIECE.
DAVID AND WENTWORTH STILL
STUDYING, TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHICH MOVES TO MAKE.
THATS RIGHT.
THE ONE IN YOUR LEFT HAND IS
WRONG.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
Jeff: MAEM THINKS THEY HAVE
IT.
AND THEY DO!
KAMA WINS IMMUNITY.
WERE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
ANOTHER ONE AT A TIME.
ONE AT A TIME.
COME OMANU!
COME ON, MANU!
Jeff: IT IS MANU AND LESU
NOW.
LETS GO, MA TUE.
YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: ERIK AND WENDY
QUICKLY MOVING PIECES DOWN.
THEY THINK THEY WERE JUST OFF A
LITTLE BIT.
YES, YES.
ARE YOU SURE ON THIS?
Jeff: WENTWORTH QUICKLY
MOVING.
DAVID MOVING PIECES.
WHO WILL GET THERE FIRST.
IS THAT RIGHT?
IS THAT RIGHT, GUYS?
JEFF!
Jeff: MANU THINKS THEY HAVE
IT.
MANU WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE FROM TRIBAL, SENDING LESU
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE THE
FOURTH PERSON WILL BE VOTED OUT
OF THIS GAME.
GOOD TRY.
GOOD WORK.
Jeff: KAMA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
KAMA REMAINS UNDEFEATED IN
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
MANU, YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY WIN.
NEW TRIBE MAKEUP, SAME TRIBE
NAME.
MAYBE THATS THE DIFFERENCE.
KAMA, MANU, GRAB WUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: LESU, FIRST CHALLENGE
AS A NEW TRIBE.
FIRST LOSS.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FOURTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
THIS TRIBE IS SO BAD.
WERE LIKE THE CLEVELAND BROWN
TRIBE.
LIKE, WE CANT GET ANYTHING
RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE IM, HONESTLY, IN A
NIGHTMARE.
THIS IS A GROUP OF FIVE PEOPLE
THAT HAS BEEN VOTING TOGETHER,
AND NOW WERE, LIKE, CUTTING OUT
ONE OF THE FAMILY.
ITS HORRIBLE.
WERE NOT VERY GOOD AT
CHALLENGES.
LESU PROVES TO BE AS GOOD AT
LOSING AS MANU.
AND NOW WE HAVE TO CANNIBALIZE
OURSELVES.
SOMEONE IS GOING HOME.
ON THE ONE HAND IT WAS REALLY
GREAT SWAPPING WITH ALL YOU
GUYS.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, NOW, HERE
WE ARE.
THIS IS WHEN IT WOULD BE NICE
TO HAVE ONE COMMON PERSON TO
VOTE OUT.
MMMM, IT WOULD BE.
IT REALLY SUCKS.
YOU BUILD THESE RELATIONSHIPS
AND YOU THINK THEYRE GOING TO
BE THE RELATIONSHIPS THAT PROPEL
YOU FORWARD IN THE GAME, AND
THEN WE END UP IN A POSITION
WHERE THE PEOPLE WE TRUST THE
MOST, WEVE GOT TO TURN ON.
LISTEN, IM NOT GOING TO
WRITE YOUR NAME DOWN NO MATTER
WHAT, LIKE...
IM NOT GOING TO WRITE YOUR
NAME DOWN NO MATTER WHAT.
THATS A PROMISE.
OKAY.
LAUREN HAS BEEN NOT EATING.
SHE HASNT EATEN IN THREE DAYS.
SHE THREW UP WHAT SHE HAD EATEN
TODAY, THIS MORNING.
I DONT KNOW IF YOU KNOW THAT.
WE LOVE LAUREN.
BUT SHES NOT EATING.
WERE NOT GOING TO BE STRONG.
WENTWORTH IS THE PERSON I
WANT OUT OF THIS GAME FOR SURE,
BUT THE TIMING JUST ISNT RIGHT.
YEAH, 100%.
WITHIN THE FIRST THREE DAYS.
I HAVE NO EVIDENCE TO BACK THIS
UP, BUT IM 100% CONVINCED THAT
WENTWORTH HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I KNOW WENTWORTHS GAME.
SHE ALWAYS STARTS LOOKING FOR
THE IDOL ON DAY ONE.
AND SO I THINK BEST-CASE
SCENARIO TONIGHT IS THAT THE
VOTE GOES TOWARDS LAUREN.
ALL IN ON LAUREN.
YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I DONT KNOW.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
BUT I WANT TO VOTE WITH YOU.
YEAH, I WANT TO VOTE WITH
YOU, TOO.
GOING INTO THIS TRIBAL, I
FEEL LIKE MY LIFE IN THIS GAME
IS THE LINE.
IM WORRIED THEY WILL THINK IM
THE WEAKEST.
EVEN THOUGH I DONT THINK I AM.
I THINK NOT EATING GIVES THIS
PERCEPTION OF, "OH, THATS A
REASON TO VOTE HER OUT."
I WAS A COLLEGIATE ATHLETE.
I PLAYED DIVISION ONE SOCCER FOR
FOUR YEARS AND IM A STRONG
PLAYER AND I DONT THINK PEOPLE
KNOW IT.
I THINK ITS MORE LIKELY THAT
WICK SWITCHES.
I THINK SO, TOO.
I THINK RICK HAS THE ABILITY
TO GO TO THE OTHER TRIBE--
AND SCHMOOZE HIS WAY IN.
I THINK I HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF STABILITY BECAUSE I HAVE THE
IDOL BUT THATS STRESSFUL, TOO,
BECAUSE I WANT TO BRING THE IDOL
TO THE MERGE.
I THINK HE WILL BE WITH US.
I THINK HE WILL BE WITH US,
TOO.
SO WHAT DO WE THINK?
IM WRITING DOWN WHAT YOU AND
LAUREN WANT TO WRITE DOWN?
YOU AND LAUREN ARE REALLY
TIGHT.
SHE NEEDS TO START EATING,
RIGHT?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
WARDOG IS IN CONTROL OF THIS
VOTE.
I THINK HE DOES WANT TO WORK
WITH ME.
MY FEAR IS HE COULD USE DAVID
AND GAVIN TO VOTE OUT LAUREN
AND HE MIGHT BE MORE
SUSCEPTIBLE TO THROW US UNDER
THE BUS AT THE MERGE.
WARDOG IS REALLY HARD TO
READ.
I THINK HES TRYING TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR" LIKE POKER, SO I
DONT KNOW IF HES TELLING THE
TRUTH.
I KNOW HES NOT JUST HAVING A
CONVERSATION WITH ME.
THERES NO WAY.
WHERES YOUR HEAD AT?
IM TORN.
THE ONLY THING I WOULD THINK
IS, LIKE, LAUREN IS NOT EVEN
EATING.
SHE HASNT EATEN FOR DAYS.
I LIKE RICK A LOT, AND SO
ITS SAD.
AND I FEEL LIKE HE CAN EASILY
TALK HIMSELF INTO ANYTHING AT
THE MERGE.
AND OUT OF-- LIKE, I DONT THINK
HE WOULD STAY TRUE TO US.
NO ONES BRAND IS MORE
LOYALTY THAN ME.
THATS MY BRAND.
SO LAURENS WEAK, IM LOYAL.
THATS JUST MY PITCH, MAN.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
AFTER BEING ABLE TO TALK TO EACH
PERSON INDIVIDUALLY, ITS
OBVIOUS THAT IM IN A CLASSIC
SWING VOTE SPOT, AND I LOVE IT.
IM BUILT FOR THIS GAME.
WHETHER IT WAS BEING IN THE
ARMY, WHETHER IT WAS PLAYING
POKER, WHETHER NOW LAW SCHOOL,
IM ALWAYS THINKING, ALWAYS
GOING THROUGH OPTIONS, NEVER
CLOSING DOORS.
AND THATS WHAT IM DOING NOW.
IM GOING TO TAKE 15-20 MINUTES
OF WARDOG TIME TO THINK.
THE TRIBE SAY TIGHT-KNIT GROUP
BUT ITS NO LONGER ABOUT THE
TRIBE NOW.
ITS ABOUT WARDOG.
AND I NEED A DANCE PARTNER.
WHO CAN GET WARDOG CLOSER TO
WINNING $1 MILLION.
I WILL MARK DAY 11, OUR LAST
DAY TOGETHER AS A HAPPY FAMILY.
GOD, THIS IS AWFUL.
SOMETIMES YOU JUST HAVE TO GO
WITH YOUR INSTINCT, GO WITH YOUR
DIFFERENT SKILL SETS, YOUR
TOOLS, BLEND THEM ALL TOGETHER
IN THE BLENDER AND SEE WHAT
COLOR COMES OUT AND THATS WHAT
IM DOING RIGHT NOW.
♪ ♪
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DEVON GIVE
ME A NEWS REPORT ABOUT WHATS
GOING ON WITH THIS TRIBE?
♪ DA-DA-DA
LESU IS EVEN LESS THAN WE EVEN
EXPECTED.
LOVE IN TRIBAL COUNCIL, BUT WILL
IT LAST?
GOOD EVENING, IM RICK DEVENS.
THIS MAY BE MY LAST REPORT."
Jeff: WHATS GOOD RIGHT NOW
ABOUT THIS TRIBE?
WE LOVE EACH OTHER.
THERES A LOT OF MUTUAL RESPECT.
AND THATS IT.
EVERYTHING ELSE IS JUST CRAP
RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: WARDOG, LITERALLY,
THATS IT-- AFFECTION FOR EACH
OTHER IS THE ONLY GOOD THING
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
AND RESPECT.
Jeff: OH, TWO THINGS.
TWO THINGS.
AND EVERYTHING ELSE IS A MESS.
YOU SEE IN CHALLENGES, WERE A
MESS.
OUR NEW CAMP IS A MESS.
Jeff: LAUREN, WHATS UP
WITH THE NEW CAMP?
THERES LIMITED AMOUNT OF
FOOD.
SUPPLIES.
AND BUILDING AN ENTIRE NEW
SHELTER WITH ONLY FIVE PEOPLE IS
EXHAUSTING.
I MEAN, IT WAS EXHAUSTING WITH
NINE PEOPLE.
SO ITS REALLY BAD.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, THERES A
LOT TO BE SAID FOR HAVING PLAYED
BEFORE, SOME ADVANTAGES COME
WITH THAT.
DOES THAT HELP AT ALL WHEN ITS
RAINING AND YOURE SLEEPING IN
THE SAND?
OR IS IT THE SAME FOR EVERYBODY?
ITS THE SAME FOR EVERYBODY.
I MEAN, I WENT THROUGH THE
RINGER IN CAMBODIA.
AND THEN WHEN IM HERE WITH THIS
TRIBE AND WERE GOING THROUGH IT
TOGETHER, IM INSTANTLY PUT BACK
THERE.
IM GOING TO GET EMOTIONAL JUST
THINKING ABOUT IT BECAUSE ITS,
LIKE-- I FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING IS
JUST PILING UP TODAY.
Jeff: HOW SO?
WERE JUST SO CLOSE.
IT SOUNDS RIDICULOUS BECAUSE
WERE ALL STRANGERS.
BUT... WEVE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
TOGETHER ALREADY, AND I JUST--
TONIGHT IS JUST REALLY HARD.
SO...
( SIGHS )
IM JUST A LITTLE SAD TONIGHT.
Jeff: DEVENS ARE YOU
SURPRISED HOW FAST YOU CAN FORM
A FAMILY WITH PEOPLE YOU MIGHT
NEVER EVEN MEET IN LIFE
OTHERWISE?
IT IS CRAZY.
WEVE BEEN OUT HERE 11 DAYS, AND
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
LIKE, EVEN IF I WAS VOTED OUT
TONIGHT, I WOULD LOVE THESE
PEOPLE.
THATS NOT TOO INSPIRE YOU TO DO
THAT.
BUT WE FEEL LIKE THE WHOLE
WORLDS AGAINST US.
WERE LOSING TO THESE TWO TRIBES
WHO ARE YELLING AND CHEERING
EACH OTHER ON, AND THE ONLY
THING WE HAVE IS EACH OTHER.
Jeff: WARDOG, WHAT IS IT
ABOUT THIS ADVENTURE THAT EVEN
ON YOUR WORST NIGHTS, YOURE
STILL SMILING?
FOR ME, I FEEL LIKE THIS IS
THE GAME OF GAMES.
AND NOW THAT IM ACTUALLY IN TI
REALIZE HOW COMPLEX THE GAME
IS-- ALL THE RELATIONSHIPS, THE
CHALLENGES, THE DUPLICITY OF
EVERYTHING THATS GOING ON.
AND THEN THERES THE ACTUAL
SURVIVAL PART WHICH TESTS ALL
YOUR SKILLS-- YOUR PHYSICAL,
YOUR MENTAL, YOUR EMOTIONAL.
I LOVE IT.
IM IN AN ADVENTURE AND ITS THE
ULTIMATE COMPETITION.
Jeff: DEVENS, ITS REALLY
INTERESTING, EVERYBODY WAS
SMILING AT SOME POINT WHILE
WARDOG WAS TALKING.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING ABOUT AS
HE WAS EXPLAINING WHY HES HERE?
IN MY REGULAR LIFE, I CAN BE
COMPLACENT, YOU KNOW.
NEWS IS SO COMPETITIVE, AND
EVERYONE WANTS TO MOVE UP TO THE
BIGGEST MARKETS.
BUT THERES ALSO, LIKE, FEAR OF
REJECTION, NOT WANTING TO TAKE
THAT RISK.
AND THEN YOU COME OUT HERE AND
ITS LIKE YOU SEND THE BIGGEST
RISK YOU COULD DO.
AND YOURE, LIKE, "I DONT WANT
TO GO HOME RIGHT NOW.
IM HERE TO PLAY."
AND YOU PROVE SOMETHING TO
YOURSELF.
AND YOU HOPE YOU CAN TAKE THAT
HOME WITH YOU.
Jeff: DAVID, YOU WERE
REALLY OPEN THE FIRST TIME YOU
PLAYED ABOUT FEARING REJECTION
FROM THE WORLD, IF YOU WERE EVEN
WORTHY TO BE ON A TRIBE.
ABSOLUTELY.
AND WHAT THEY REALIZE OR DONT
REALIZE YET IS THERE ARE THINGS
TO BE FOUND IN THIS EXPERIENCE
THAT ARE WORTH MORE THAN THE
MILLION DOLLARS THATS AT THE
END OF IT.
MY LIFE IS WAY BETTER FOR THIS
EXPERIENCE, JUDGING VUFT PLAYED
IT ONCE, THAN IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
HAD I NOT PLAYED IT AT ALL.
I THOUGHT I JUST WANTED TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR."
I WASNT UNTIL I GOT INSIDE IT
THAT I NEEDED TO PLAY IT.
Jeff: AND THAT IS WHY
EVERYONE OF YOU WANTS TO PLAY.
THE STAKES ARE SO HARD, AND
THATS WHY ITS SO HARD AND
WINNING IS SO GLORIOUS.
AND YET, LAUREN, THE GAME
DEMANDS THAT SOMEBODY GET THEIR
TORCH SNUFFED MOMENTS FROM NOW.
TONIGHT IS EXTREMELY HARD.
WE RESPECT EACH OTHER A LOT.
THIS TRIBAL IS NOT GOING TO BE
UGLY.
ITS NOT GOING TO BE HATEFUL.
ITS NOT GOING TO BE SOMETHING
THAT TEARS ANOTHER PERSON DOWN.
BUT THERE ARE GOING TO BE LINES
DRAWN BECAUSE IN A FIVE-PERSON
TRIBE, A 3-2 MAJORITY CAN TURN
TO A 2-3 MINORITY REALLY FAST.
JEFF, THE WHOLE FEELING FOR
ME IS DIFFERENT THAN THE FIRST
THREE TRIBALS.
THE FIRST THREE TRIBALS HAD A
REASON BEHIND.
THERE WAS GAMES MANSHIP.
THE TRIBAL TONIGHT, IF ITS NOT
ME, ITS ONE OF MY FOUR FAMILY
MEMBERS HERE.
IF MY TORCH IS SNUFFED, I HAVE
NO HARD FEELINGS, AND IF ITS
ONE OF THESE FOUR, I HOPE THEY
HAVE NO HARD FEELINGS AGAINST
ME.
A GAME IS A GAME.
I HAVE TO SAY THIS IS ONE OF
THE MOST EMOTIONAL INCREDIBLE
TRIBAL-- IT IS THE MOST
EMOTIONAL INCREDIBLE TRIBAL IVE
BEEN TO.
TONIGHT?
YES.
AND IVE BEEN TO A LOT OF THEM.
IT DOES FEEL SPECIAL IN A
VERY SAD WAY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
DAVID YOURE UP.
YOURE SUCH A TERRIFIC
PERSON, BUT NOT THE NOT EATING
WORRIES ME ABOUT YOU AND ABOUT
OUR CHANCES AND CHALLENGES.
IM SO SORRY.
I HATE THIS VOTE SO MUCH.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAUREN.
RICK.
ONE VOTE LAUREN, ONE VOTE RICK.
LAUREN.
THATS TWO VOTES LAUREN, ONE
VOTE RICK.
RICK.
WERE TIED-- TWO VOTES LAUREN,
TWO VOTES RICK, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION,"
RICK DEVINS.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DUDE, IM SORRY.
ITS ALL GOOD.
SEE YOU LATER, BROTHER.
Jeff: DEVENS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
I TAKE IT ALL BACK.
YOU GUYS ARE THE WORST.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
GO WIN SOMETHING.
WE LOVE YOU.
IM ROOTING FOR YOU.
♪ ♪
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR."
A DIABOLICAL PLAN.
WARDOG SAY CRAZY MAN.
Jeff: AND A RAY OF LIGHT.
ME, YOU, WENDY, GET RID OF
ERIK.
I WAS PSYCHED TO HEAR HER SAY
THAT.
Jeff: CAN PUSH YOU OVER THE
EDGE.
HURRY UP.
OH, MY GOD!
WERE ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, BUT WERE NOT OUT OF
THE GAME.
I HAD ALREADY BEEN PICTURING
MYSELF EATING A BURGER AS I LEFT
TRIBAL BUT HOLY CRAP, IM STIM
STILLIN THIS.
I GUESS IM GOING TO DO MY BEST
TO INGRATIATE MYSELF TO THESE
PEOPLE WHO HATE ME.
THERE COULD BE A LOT OF ANGER.
MAN, YOU ARE NOT IN GOOD
GRACE HERE, SWEETHEART.
THIS IS GOING TO BE WILD.