♪ ♪
Jeff: THESE 14 STRANGERS
ARE ABOUT TO BEGIN AN ADVENTURE
THAT WILL FOREVER CHANGE THEIR
LIVES.
YOU LOOK AT ME, YOU THINK
THIS IS SOME NEW YORKER.
HES A MILITARY GUY.
BUT IM CURRENTLY IN LAW SCHOOL.
AND DEFINITELY DONT WANT
ANYBODY TO KNOW IM GOING TO BE
A LAWYER BECAUSE THE WRONG FIRST
IMPRESSION COULD MAKE OR BREAK
MY ENTIRE GAME.
IM A SUPER, MEGAULTRAFAN OF
THE SHOW.
YOU DONT KNOW WHEN THIS IS
GOING TO HAPPEN, WHEN THIS IS
GOING TO FLIP, AND THIS IS GOING
TO HAPPEN, AND THATS MY LIFE.
Jeff: THEYLL COMPETE
ALONGSIDE FOUR RETURNING
PLAYERS: DAVID, AUBRY,
WENTWORTH, AND JOE.
THEIR VAST "SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE
COULD MAKE THEM A DESIRED ALLY
OR AN EASY EARLY VOTE.
I THINK THAT IM GOING TO
HAVE A TARGET ON MY BACK, BUT
IM GOING TO TRY MY HARDEST TO
NEVER SHINE BRIGHTER THAN
EVERYBODY ELSE.
Jeff: AND THERES A SECRET,
GAME-CHANGING TWIST.
AFTER BEING VOTED OUT, PLAYERS
WILL BE FACED WITH A DECISION:
GO HOME OR GO TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, WHERE THEYLL BE
PUSHED FURTHER THAN EVER BEFORE
FOR A CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THE
GAME.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
TO CLAIM THE MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR.
WELCOME TO THE 38th SEASON
OF "SURVIVOR."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HERES A SOBERING THOUGHT-- IN
LESS THAN 72 HOURS, THE FIRST
PERSON WILL BE VOTED OUT.
THATS HOW FAST THIS GAME MOVES.
AND EVERY SEASON IT GETS A
LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED, A
LITTLE MORE DIFFICULT TO WIN.
NO MATTER HOW GOOD YOU ARE, YOU
ARE ALWAYS HOVERING ON THE EDGE
OF BEING VOTED OUT.
JUST THINK OF THE HISTORY OF
GREAT "SURVIVOR" PLAYERS WHO
HAVE YET TO WIN.
IN FACT, LETS JUST INVITE FOUR
OF THEM TO JOIN YOU THIS SEASON.
( APPLAUSE )
BRING THEM IN!
WOOOO!
OH, MY GOD, THAT KELLEY
WENTWORTH?
MY TWO FAVORITES PLAYERS ARE
KELLEY WENTWORTH AND MY TOTAL
"SURVIVOR" CRUSH IS JOE.
AND SO WE SEE THIS BOAT COMING
AND THEN YOU SEE THE BLOND.
AND IM LIKE THATS FREAKING
KELLEY WENTWORTH.
AND IT GETS CLOSER AND IM LIKE,
"IS THAT JOE, TOO?"
OH, MY GOD.
DAVID.
AUBRY.
I HATE THAT YOU BROUGHT
PEOPLE I LIKE.
Jeff: COME ON UP.
THIS IS WHO YOURE GOING TO BE
PLAYING WITH: WENTWORTH, DAVI
DAVID,.
HIGH, GUYS.
MAN BUN!
Jeff: JOE.
AND AUBRY.
OH, MY GOD.
WELCOME BACK.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LETS
REVIEW THE TRACK RECORD OF THESE
FOUR RETURNING PLAYERS.
KELLEY WENTWORTH-- FIRST WOMAN
TO FIND TWO HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOLS, AND WHEN SHE FOUND
HERSELF IN A DEEP HOLE, SHE USED
ONE OF THEM FOR A RECORD-SETTING
BLINDSIDE.
DAVID WRITING-- SCARED OF PRETTY
MUCH EVERYTHING--
YOU DONT NEED TO RELIVE ALL
THAT.
Jeff: ON DAY ONE, BUT HE
DIDNT GIVE UP ON HIMSELF.
AND HE TURNED INTO A DOMINANT
STRATEGIC FORCE.
JOE HAS PLAYED MOST OF HIS
"SURVIVOR" DAYS WITH A MASSIVE
TARGET ON HIS BACK.
DESPITE THAT TARGET, JOES
TRIBES HAVE WON 16 CHALLENGES.
AND AUBRY, LITERALLY CRIED IN
THE SHELTER.
( LAUGHTER )
THE FIRST TIME SHE PLAYED, BUT
SHE OVERCAME HER INSECURITIES
AND LASTED 76 OUT OF THE
POSSIBLE 78 DAYS SHE PLAYED.
FOUR VERY DIFFERENT STYLES OF
PLAY, FOUR VERY GOOD PLAYERS.
NONE OF THEM WON.
BECAUSE "SURVIVOR" IS
UNPREDICTABLE.
AND THATS WHY ITS SO GREAT.
AND THATS WHY YOU ARE HERE.
YOU CHOSE THIS ADVENTURE.
AND WHEN "SURVIVOR" PUSHES YOU
FURTHER THAN YOU EVER IMAGINED,
THAT IS YOUR OPPORTUNITY TO
STAND UP, ADAPT, AND CONQUER.
AND THAT IS THE THEME WERE
GOING TO BE EXPLORING THIS
SEASON.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION."
( APPLAUSE )
KELLEY, DAVID, YOURE ON THE
MANU TRIBE WEARING BLUE.
SAY HELLO TO YOUR TRIBE MATES.
JOIN JUR YUR TRIBE AND PASS OUT
YOUR BUFFS.
IM LAUREN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
Jeff: JOE AND AUBRY, YOU
ARE ON THE KAMA TRIBE.
SAY HELLO TO YOUR TRIBEMATES.
ALL RIGHT, LETS KICK IT UP TO
THE NEXT LEVEL.
OOOH.
Jeff: THIS BOAT IS LOADED
WITH SUPPLIES.
SOME OFFER LONG-TERM HELP.
SOME ARE PERISHABLE.
YOU HAVE TWO MINUTES TO GET
ANYTHING OFF OF THIS BOAT INTO
YOUR BOAT.
YOUR "SURVIVOR" ADVENTURE BEGINS
NOW.
GO!
THIS IS IT, ALL THAT ENERGY
FINALLY COMING OUT.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HEY, NEED SOME HELP!
NEED SOME HELP!
Jeff: THERE GOES REEM, OUR
FIRST PERSON IS OVER.
WATCH OUT!
Jeff: NOW EVERYBODY GOING
OVER!
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: THEYRE EVERYWHERE
RIGHT NOW, ALL OVER THE PLACE,
VERY LITTLE COMMUNICATION,
EVERYBODY JUST GRABBING WHATEVER
THEY CAN AND TRY TO GET
OVERBOARD.
NOW THE JOB BECOMES TRY TO GET
WHAT YOU GOT OVERBOARD INTO YOUR
BOAT.
KEITH WORKING HARD TO GET TO
THAT BOAT.
DIG IN, KEITH!
IM NOT THE BEST SWIMMER OUT
HERE, AND IVE NEVER BEEN IN
OPEN WATER.
NATURALLY ME, WHO CANT SWIM,
WILL COST ME TO BE THE FIRST ONE
GONE, IN THIS GAME, IF YOURE ON
THE OUTS, YOURE OUT.
Jeff: DAVID AND WENTWORTH
GETTING IN THE WATER.
THE LAST TWO.
RIGHT NOW, KAMA SEEMS TO HAVE
THE EARLY ADVANTAGE WITH WHAT
THEY HAVE IN THEIR BOAT.
GOT IT.
YEAH!
WOOO!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, START
PADDLING OUT!
YEAH!
Jeff: YOUVE GOT WHAT YOU
GOT.
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION"
IS ON!
( APPLAUSE )
WEVE GOT TO GO RIGHT.
GREAT WORK!
( APPLAUSE )
GREAT.
OH, MY GOD.
STRAIGHT UP THERE.
OH, MY GOSH!
WE GOT SOME GREAT STUFF.
WELL, LETS GO LOOK AT OUR
CAMP.
CHRIS, MAN.
RICK, DUDE.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
AS EVERYONES INTRODUCING
THEMSELVES, IM SO OVERWHELMED
BY THE FACT THAT IM IN THIS
GAME.
IM STILL SO EXCITED BECAUSE IM
A HUGE FAN OF THE SHOW.
IVE WATCHED IT SINCE THE VERY
FIRST EPISODE.
IM A MORNING NEWS ANCHOR.
ARE YOU REALLY?
YEAH.
AND GET THIS-- IN THE 115th
WERE 130.
SO PRETTY GOOD.
NO ONE THINKS NEWS ANCHORS
ARE TOUGH.
IVE GOT DAD BOD OUT HERE BUT I
HAVE A LOT OF BELIEF IN MYSELF.
I WANT TO BREAK THROUGH THE
WALL-- OH, YEAH!
APPRECIATE IT.
OH, MY GOD!
ARE YOU OKAY?
IM FINE.
JUST EXTREMELY CLUMSY.
YOULL SEE THIS SEVERAL TIMES.
SO MUCH FOOD.
ITS CRAZY.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
I DONT TRUST ANYONE.
PLAYING A THIRD TIME, I KNOW
I MAY HAVE A TARGET ON MY BACK
INITIALLY, SO GETTING AN INITIAL
ALLIANCE IN THE BEGINNING IS
VERY IMPORTANT.
HOW ARE YOU?
IM GOOD, HOW ARE YOU!
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
GOOD.
I PLAYED FROM THE BOTTOM IN
"SECOND CHANCE."
THATS NOT A GOOD FEELING.
SO THIS TIME I WANT TO HAVE
GENUINE RELATIONSHIPS WHICH CAN
BE HARD FOR ME BECAUSE IM A
CLOSED OFF PERSON.
I PLAYED SOCCER IN COLLEGE.
I PLAYED SOCCER IN HOLLY, NOT
COLLEGE, BUT ITS AMAZING.
I HAVE TO BE MORE OPEN.
I HAVE TO GET TO KNOW THESE
PEOPLE ON A HUMAN LEVEL.
SO WHO KNOWS WHAT THEYRE
DOING?
WE WERE GOG ASK DAVID,
BECAUSE, IDEALLY, WE WANT TO
HAVE TWO TREES, KIND OF.
WERE WAITING ON YOUR
EXPERTISE HERE,.
OH, REALLY?
THE FIRST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR," I WAS AFRAID TO,
LIKE, VOICE AN OPINION.
CHOPPING THE WOOD, LIKE THE
SOUND OF THAT, LIKE, RATTLED ME.
I HAD TO PLUG MY EARS WITH MY
FINGERS.
AND ITS, LIKE, I WAS WORRIED
THAT MY TRIBEMATES WERE GOING TO
HAVE THAT PERCEPTION OF ME.
THIS TIME, PEOPLE ARE COMING TO
ME, THESE NEWBIES WITH LIKE,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?"
AND IM LIKE, IM TRYING TO GIVE
THEM IDEAS.
WHICH WAY WERE YOU THINKING,
GOING IN THIS DIRECTION?
SEEMS LIKE, YEAH, RIGHT.
I WANT PEOPLE TO FEEL I CAN HELP
THEM NAVIGATE, ESPECIALLY THE
VERY EARLY PART OF THIS GAME SO
THAT THEY KNOW IM A FRIEND.
YOU CAN TRUST ME, KEEP ME
AROUND.
SO YOU OPEN UP THIS LITTLE
GUY HERE.
OKAY.
AND THEN ITS JUST OVER AND
UNDER.
SO YOU GO UNDER, THEN OVER.
DO YOU DO THAT ALL THE TIME?
I HAVE MILD TURRETS.
DOES THAT MEAN IF YOU CURSE
ONE OF US OUT.
SO, LIKE THE POPULAR VERSION
OF TOWERETS IS LIKE A... THING
LIKE THAT.
I DONT HAVE THE VOCALIZED
VERSION OF IT.
I HAVE MOTOR TICKS-- I HAVE
VOCAL TIPS.
I HAVE TOURETTES WITH A TOUCH
OF O.C.D.
A TOUCH OF CO-CO-COMBO.
IF I DO AND THIS DO THIS AND
THIS ARM ONE, ITS A WHOLE BUNCH
MIXED IN.
IT HAS TO BE ALL OF THEM.
AND I FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW
THEYRE KIND OF GOOD.
BUT IF I GET REALLY EXCITED OR I
GET REALLY CONCENTRATED INTO
SOMETHING OR FITALK ABOUT THEM,
THEY ACT UP A LOT.
YEAH SO ONE OF THEM IS THAT
LITTLE BIRD NOISE.
WOW, THATS IMPRESSIVE.
IM KIND OF LIKE AN OPEN BOOK
IN A WAY.
IM NOT GOING TO BE, "HEY,EN, I
HAVE TOURETTES."
ITS SOMETHING I FEEL
COMFORTABLE ABOUT.
I TRY TO HAVE A GOOD SOCIAL GAME
BUT LETS ADMIT IT, IM AWKWARD.
IM NOT GOOD AT-- PEOPLE-- HOW
WOULD I SAY IT?
LIKE, THEY VIBE IN A WAY THEY
COULD NEVER.
BUT I HAVE TOND THAT THIS IS A
GAME, AND YOU HAVE TO PLAY BY
THE RULES OF THE GAME.
I GUESS I HAVE TO PLAY BALL!
(
CHEERS )
IVE BEEN DREAMING OF THIS
MOMENT SINCE I WAS A KID.
WHEN I WAS, LIKE EIGHT YEARS OLD
I ASK SANTA CLAUS FOR A
"SURVIVOR" BUFF.
SO IM JUST DYING TO GET IT
STARTED.
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO CHOP
THAT?
PIECE BY PIECE.
WERE COUNTING ON YOU.
COMING INTO THIS GAME, IM
REALLY TRYING TO PUT "JOEY
AMAZING" AWAY.
IM A BETTER VISUAL LEARNER.
YOURE A VISUAL LEARNER.
ITS HARD, BECAUSE NEW PLAYERS
ARE ASKING YOU, "HEY, WHAT
SHOULD I DO?"
SLAM, 45.
AND YOU DONT WANT TO POINT
YOURSELF OUT AS A THREAT, YET,
YOU HAVE SO MUCH TO OFFER THESE
NEW PLAYERS, SO WHAT DO YOU DO.
YOU GOT IT.
OH, YEAH.
YOU SMELL THAT?
IT SMELLS LIKE SUCCESS.
AAAHHHH!
FIRE!
HAVING JOE ON OUR TEAM MEANS
IM BETTER SET FOR THIS GAME.
I DONT HAVE TO MAKE FIRE.
JOE DID THAT.
I DONT HAVE TO MAKE A SHELTER.
HES JUST AMAZING.
AND I WOULD LOVE TO WORK WITH
HIM IN THIS GAME.
IM GAY AND IM STILL ON "TEAM
JOE."
WHAT NEXT?
KEEP IT ALIVE.
DONT LET IT DIE.
IM GETTING NOWHERE.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THIS HARD.
( LAUGHS )
IM DONE!
IM TRYING TO HELP OUT AROUND
CAMP AS MUCH AS I CAN, BUT I
LIVE IN NEW YORK CITY.
I HAVE NO OUTDOOR SURVIVAL
SKILLS WHATSOEVER.
OW!
OH!
I HAVE A SPLINTER!
BUT IT HURTS.
I THINK THE CLOSEST THAT I CAN
COME TO IS THAT I PEED IN BUSHES
OF CENTRAL PARK ONCE, AND THAT
WAS AN EMERGENCY.
SO THIS IS DEFINITELY GOING TO
BE A TEST FOR ME.
BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
BECAUSE I DONT WANT TO BE
THE PERSON THAT EVERYBODY LOOKS
AT AS, LIKE, THE OLDER WOMAN,
SHES A MOM.
WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
SHE DOESNT HAVE A CLUE.
YES!
( APPLAUSE )
BAMBOO INITIATION.
I THINK KAMA IS OFF TO THE BEST
START I HAVE SEEN ANY TRIBE IN
"SURVIVOR" HAVE.
WE HAVE ALL THE RATIONS.
WE HAVE FIRE ON THE FIRST DAY.
WE HAVE A POSITIVE SPIRIT.
BUT I HAVE SOMETHING ON MY MIND.
I HAVE A SECRET ADVANTAGE IN MY
POCKET.
THERE WERE 18 PEOPLE IN THAT
BOAT, AND I FOUND IT.
AND NOW IM THINKING I GOT TO
GET AWAY AND READ THIS THING.
I NEED TO GET SOME MORE WATER.
YEAH, DO IT.
I SCURRED OFF, AND IVE ONLY
GOT A FEW SPNGDZ "DIG THREE FEET
EAST OF YOUR TREE MAIL."
INITIALLY, OF COURSE, IM LIKE,
IM GOING TO GO RIGHT NOW.
IN "SURVIVOR" YOU HAVE TO LIE,
MANIPULATE, TEACH, AND AS A
TEACHER, I HAVE ALL THESE
STUDENTS THAT ARE GOING TO BE
LOOKING AT ME.
BUT THEYRE NOT STUPID.
THEY KNOW ITS A GAME.
THE RULES ALLOW YOU TO DO THESE
THINGS.
OH, MY GOD!
I GOT A MENU.
I WON THE COUPE DE GRACE OF
"SURVIVOR" ADVANTAGES.
I HAVE THE BEST THAT YOU COULD
POSSIBLY HAVE.
IT SAYS, "YOU HAVE FOUND THE
ADVANTAGE MENU THAT ALLOWS YOU
TO CHOOSE ONE OF THE FOLLOWING.
IF YOU LOSE A CHALLENGE, YOU CAN
STEAL THE REWARD FROM THE OTHER
TRIBE.
OR YOU GET AN EXTRA VOTE.
OR I COULD GET INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY.
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
IT WOULD PLAY LIKE A REGULAR
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND I WOULD
HAVE TO ANNOUNCE IT BEFORE THE
VOTE WAS READ.
COMING IN, MY GOAL WAS NOT TO BE
THE FIRST ONE VOTED OUT.
BUT THIS HAS GIVEN ME A NEW
GOAL.
IM THINKING THIS COULD PROPEL
ME NOT ONLY TO LAST FOR A WHILE
BUT TO WIN "SURVIVOR."
♪ ♪
"EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT MEANS?
I DONT KNOW, MAN.
I DONT, EITHER.
EVERYTHING HAS A REASON.
ITS SO CUTE.
ISNT IT?
LIKE A LITTLE PLACEMAT.
MAYBE IM NAIVE BUT I FEEL
LIKE IVE GOTTEN GOOD VIBES FROM
EVERYBODY SO FAR.
GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE EVERYBODYS
PUTTING IN WORK.
YEAH.
THERE ARE SOME PLAYERS THAT
REALIZE THE VALUE OF STRONG
PEOPLE.
BEING A RETURNEE, IT IS KIND OF
TERRIFYING TO PLAY WITH NEWBIES
BECAUSE IF I POP MY HEAD UP TOO
MUCH, ITS GOING TO GET LOPPED
OFF BECAUSE IM GOING TO HAVE
THAT "RETURNING PLAYER" TARGET.
I FEEL LIKE WERE IN A GOOD
SPOT, THOUGH.
I COULD HELP ON FIRE FOREVER.
SO I KNOW THAT THE BEST THING TO
DO SOMETIMES IS LAY IN THE
GRASS, AND THEN COME OUT LOOK A
COBRA WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT.
TENNESSEE.
WHAT PART OF TENNESSEE?
EAST TENNESSEE, AROUND PIGEON
FORGE.
IM NOT THE GOOD OLD SOUTHERN
BOY.
I KNOW THE SHOW, AND IM HERE
FOR ONE REASON AND ONE REASON
ONLY, AND THATS TO WIN THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR.
TELL ME SOMETHING COUNTRY YOU
DO?
I EAT FRIED PICKLES.
THAT MILLION DOLLARS IS GOING TO
COME IN HANDY.
AND FOR THE TOWN OF IRWIN, I
MIGHT BUY US A FOURTH STOP LIGHT
AND GO ON DOWN THROUGH MAIN
STREET.
I DONT KNOW YET.
WELL SEE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
HAVING JOE AND AUBRY?
I DONT KNOW.
PART OF THE EXPERIENCE IS
FIGURING EVERYTHING OUT.
AND I DONT WANT TO JUST
LIKE,INGS, HEY, JOE, HOW DO WE
DO THIS?
HEY, AUBRY, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?"
I WANT TO FIGURE IT OUT
OURSELVESS.
BEING A FIREFIGHTER, AT THE VERY
CORE ITS TAKING CARE OF PEOPLE
SO WE GET GOOD AT DEVELOPING
LIGHTNING-FAST RAPPORT, YOU
KNOW, LIKE, FOR EXAMPLE, WITH
GAVIN.
RIGHT AWAY I KIND OF GET A SENSE
THAT HES SOMEBODY THAT IS
THINKING ALONG THE SAME LINES.
SOMEONE NEW NEEDS TO WIN THIS
GAME.
WE HAVE TO KEEP JOE FOR AT
LEAST A WHILE BECAUSE HES BEST
SHIELD IN THE WORLD.
EXACTLY.
WELL JUST CROUCH BEHIND HIS
BIG, BROAD, BEAUTIFUL SHOULDERS.
WELL GET RID OF ONE OF THEM IF
WE LOSE.
IF ITS UP TO ME, ITS ABOUT GE
GETTING AUBRY OUT OF HERE FAST.
IF I COULD DO IT TOMORROW, THAT
WOULD BE GREAT.
ARE YOU GUYS DRINKING?
YES, MAAM.
IM GONNA CHECK THE CLOTHES
ON THE BEACH, TOO.
LETS GO.
CLOTHES ON THE BEACH.
I PUT EVERYTHING ON THE BEACH.
IM SUPER PLEASED WITH HOW THE
TRIBES GOING.
SO FAR, SO GOOD, MAN.
WERE ALL JUST GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER.
EVERYBODYS WORK HARD.
SWEET!
THESE ARE YOURS?
DRY.
THERES DEFINITELY AN
APPRECIATION FOR WHAT EVERYBODY
IS DOING RIGHT NOW.
SHE KEEPS, LIKE, MOVING MY...
AROUND.
I KNOW.
REEM IS SO SWEET AND JUST IS,
LIKE, SUPER HELPFUL MOM, BUT I
THINK SOME PEOPLE ARE LIKE,
"STOP MOVING MY STUFF!"
SHE JUST CANT HELP HERSELF,
MAN.
IN THE SOUTH WE WOULD SAY,
"BLESS HER HEART."
BLESS HER HEART.
I KNOW.
I FOUND MY SHIRT OUT ON THE
BEACH TODAY.
AND I WAS LIKE I HAD THAT
HANGING IN A TREE.
I KNOW.
SHE GOES, "I FUT ON THE SAND
BECAUSE IT WAS WET."
AND LIST LIKE...
YOU JUST HAVE THAT VERY
MOTHERLY VIBE.
AND I FEEL LIKE--
DONT EVER PUT ME IN THAT
CATEGORY.
I KNOW, IM SO SORRY.
ITS ALL GOOD.
I KNOW WHAT YOURE SAYING.
ITS FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, DUDE, ITS FINE?
IM A MOMMAS BOY?
ARE YOU?
YEAH.
IM HERE FOR YOU.
BUT IM GOING TO TELL YOU TO
TIGHTEN UP IF YOU GET A LITTLE
TOO SOFT.
I AM YOUNG, IM 19.
AND NOT HAVING MY MOM OUT HERE
IS KIND OF AFFECTING ME.
WHAT DO YOU DO IN FAVORITEVILLE?
I GO TO SCHOOL.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DU DUKE UNIVERSITY.
GOOD FOR YOU!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
I FEEL LIKE REEM IS THAT
MOTHERLY PERSON OUT HERE.
ONCE I FOUND OUT I WAS GOING TO
BE ON THE SHOW, I WAS LIKE,
WELL--
I WOULD LOVE TO HELP YOU
EXCEL AT SWIMMING.
DEFINITELY, I WOULD LOVE
THAT.
I THOUGHT ABOUT GOING OUT TO THE
WATER, PRACTICING SWIMMING.
AND REEM AND WENDY EVEN OFFERED
TO HELP ME WITH IT.
KEEP GOING!
KICK YOUR FEET!
ME AND MY FAMILY, WE, LIKE,
LIVE IN A TRAILER IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE COUNTRY.
AND THAT MILLION DOLLARS WILL
CHANGE OUR LIVES.
IF I DONT KNOW SOMETHING, IM
GOING TO LEARN IT.
LOOK AT KEITH!
YES, KEITH!
GOOD JOB!
THAT WAS REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
WHOS OUT THERE, WENDY AND
KEITH AND REEM?
THEY HAVE THEIR OWN
THREE-PERSON ALLIANCE.
I DONT KNOW WHAT THEYRE
DOING DOWN THERE.
PERFECT!
WE GOT THE NUMBERS.
THAT WORKED.
WE STARTED OUT AS ONE BIG
HAPPY FAMILY, AND WERE STILL A
BIG HAPPY FAMILY, BUT NATURALLY
KEITH, REEM, AND WENDY STARTED
DOING THEIR OWN THING.
AND WE SAW THAT KEITH WASNT A
GREAT SWIMMER.
AND REEM IS A BUSY BODY.
SO ITS BEEN REALLY HELPFUL FOR
THE REST OF US IN THE TRIBE
BECAUSE WERE SITTING THERE
GOING, "WOW, THOSE THREE HAVE
DIVIDED THEMSELVES AND THOSE
MIGHT BE THE THREE WE WANTED TO
VOTE OUT ANYWAY.
SO, OKAY, KEEP DIVIDING
YOURSELVES.
♪ ♪
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
THATS CRAZY.
ALL RIGHT!
ARE YOU GUYS READY FOR YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YES!
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: LETS DO IT!
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO MANEUVER THROUGH AN
OBSTACLE.
ONE PERSON MUST THEN CLIMB TO
THE TOP OF THE ROPE AND RING A
BELL.
YOULL THEN ATTEMPT TO CROSS A
THREE-TIER BALANCE BEAM.
ONCE ACROSS, START UNTYING KNOTS
TO RELEASE A BAR.
THAT BAR WILL MAKE IT MUCH
EASIER FOR THE REST OF THE TRIBE
TO CROSS THE BEAM.
ONE PERSON MUST THEN CLIMB TO
THE TOP OF THE CROWS NEST, PULL
A SLEFER TO DROP A SLIDE.
ONCE DOWN, SIX PLAYERS WILL WORK
TOGETHER TO SOLVE A GIANT SLIDE
PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
THIS IS THE IMMUNITY HIDEOL.
( APPLAUSE )
WITH THIS BACK AT CAMP, IT MEANS
YOURE NOT GOING TO TRIBAL AND
NOBODY IS GOING HOME.
WITHOUT IT, YOU ARE VULNERABLE.
ARE YOU ALSO PLAYING FOR REWARD,
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
ILL GIVE YOU GUYS A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, WELL GET STARTED.
OH, YEAH!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE
GO!
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
Jeff: CHRIS HOPPING OVER
THE ROPE!
GO, GO, GO.
YOU GOT IT.
JUST LIFT THEM UP.
THATS IT, THATS IT!
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO GET
EVERYBODY TO YOUR MAT BEFORE YOU
CAN MOVE ON.
COME ON, COME ON.
LETS GO!
KAMA IS GOING TO GET THERE
FIRST.
GO, KAMA.
GO, MANU.
ITS GOING TO BE JOE AND CHRIS
GOING UP THE ROPES.
YOU GOT IT, JOE!
Jeff: THIS IS NO EASY FEAT.
THAT IS PURE STRENGTH.
YOU GOTTA RING THE BELL.
YOURE GOOD, JOE, YOURE GOOD,
CHRIS.
GO!
Jeff: EVERYBODY UP THE ROPE
LADDER.
GO, GO, GO.
ANYBODY NEED HELP?
COME HERE, COME HERE.
Jeff: WE ARE DEAD EVEN
RIGHT NOW.
JOE, YOURE GOOD!
GO, WENDY.
Jeff: ITS GOING TO BE JOE
HEADING ACROSS FIRST.
HOLD IT, HOLD IT, HOLD IT.
Jeff: AND WENDY.
LAUREN, GO, LAUREN, GO.
JOE, YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: JOE A ACROSS.
JOE NOW UNTYING KNOTS TRYING TO
RELEASE THAT BAR WHICH WILL MAKE
THAT BEAM A LOT EASIER.
IT IS BE LAUREN FOR MANU.
GAVINS OUT.
LAUREN DROPS.
THATS IT, ERIK!
ERIK NOW FOR KAMA.
ERIKS ACROSS.
ERIK CAN NOW START WORKING ON
THE KNOTS WITH JOE.
THERE GOES AUBRY.
LOOK AT THAT!
AUBRYS ACROSS!
I FREAKING LOVE YOU GUYS.
YOU GOT IT, CHRIS.
Jeff: CHRIS FALLS.
YIS KRIS GOT TO GET BACK.
SO FAR, NOBODY FROM MANU IS
ACROSS.
THERE GOES DAVID.
GO QUICK, GO QUICK, GO QUICK!
COME OCOME ON, COME ON.
Jeff: DAVID, WILL HE BE THE
TO CROSS?
HE IS!
START WORKING ON THE KNOTS.
Jeff: GAVIN DROPS, BIG
FALL!
KAMA HAS THEIR BAR FREE.
LETS GO.
Jeff: EVERYBODY CROSS.
THATS.
YOU GOT IT, NICE.
Jeff: KAMA WITH THE EARLY
LEAD IN THIS FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
JUST KEEP GOING, DAVID, KEEP
GOING.
Jeff: THERE GOES LAUREN FOR
MANU.
LAUREN CROSSES NOW FOR MANU.
ONE PERSON HEADS ACROSS.
ITS GOING TO BE ERIK.
YOU GOT IT.
THATS IT, ERIK!
LETS GO, ERIK!
Jeff: ERIK NOW QUICKLY TO
THE TOP OF THE CROWS NEST.
PULL THE LEVER, RELEASE THE
SLIDE.
ERIK DROPS THE SLIDE.
GO!
ITS GOING TO BE JULIE
CROSSING NOW.
ONE AT A TIME.
GGIRL.
Jeff: IT IS LAUREN AND
DAVID STILL WORKING ON THOSE
KNOTS AS CHRIS GIVES IT ANOTHER
GO.
COME ON, COME ON!
YEAH!
Jeff: CHRIS IS ACROSS.
HE CAN START HELPING.
DEVYNS IS GOING IT A GO AND
DEVYNS IS ACROSS AND MANU HAS A
LITTLE MOMENT UPUM.
THERE GOES WENTWORTH.
WENTWORTH WITH A HUGE FALL.
OKAY, YOU OKAY?
SHE GASHED HER HEAD.
Jeff: WENTWORTH TOOK A HUGE
HIT ON THAT BEAM.
WENTWORTH, YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
ARE YOU OKAY, DUDE?
GOOD SLIDE G!
GOT IT!
Jeff: MANU HAS THEIR BAR
FREE.
GET READY!
GET READY.
RUN, RUN, RUN!
Jeff: MANU RUNNING ACROSS.
MANU WITH A LOT OF TIME TO MAKE
UP NOW.
LAUREN SCAMPERS ACROSS FOR MANU.
YOU GOT IT, LAUREN.
LAUREN QUICKLY TO THE TOP OF THE
CROWS NEST.
YOU GOT IT, GIRL!
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
Jeff: JOES ACROSS.
SIX PEOPLE ON THE PUZZLE NOW.
GOTTA GET THE MARKED PIECE OUT.
READY?
PUSH.
Jeff: KAMA WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
MIDDLE ONE.
Jeff: JOE DIRECTING HIS
TRIBE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THIS ONE.
Jeff: THESE PIECES ARE
HEAVY.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
LETS GO, RICK!
Jeff: MANU KNOWS CHALLENGES
CAN BE WON OR LOST ON THE
PUZZLE.
GO, MANU!
THIS GUY, OVER HERE.
Jeff: DAVID NOW TRYING TO
GET AN EYE ON THIS PUZZLE.
THIS IS WHERE YOU CAN MAKE A BIG
COMEBACK IF YOU KNOW HOW TO DO
THIS PUZZLE.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: CAN MANU CLOSE THE
GAP OR WILL KAMA HOLD ON TO
THEIR LEAD?
IT NEEDS TO BE CENTERED "P."
SMALL ONES OVER?
Jeff: SUDDENLY, KAMA COMES
TO A STOP.
HOLD ON.
SLOW DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
Jeff: MANU NOW HAS A SHOT
TO GET BACK IN THIS.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
IF THIS COMES UP, THOSE GO
OVER.
YYES, YES, YES!
Jeff: KAMA THINK THEYVE
GOT SOMETHING.
MANU FIGHTING TO BE IN THIS.
EVERYBODY USING ALL THEIR
STRENGTH.
THIS COULD BE VERY CLOSE!
GAVIN, PUSH THE ONE NEXT TO
IT A LITTLE.
WERE RIGHT THERE WITH THEM!
Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE HAS
TAKEN A TOLL ON A FEW BODES.
WERE ALMOST THERE!
ITS STUCK!
Jeff: KAMA SLIDING THEIR
LAST PIECE INTO PLACE.
KAMA FOR THE WIN.
KAMA WINS IMMUNITY!
SENDING MANU TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
WOW!
YES!
Jeff: KAMA,
CONGRATULATIONS.
FIRST IMMUNITY WIN.
( APPLAUSE ).
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: HERE WE ARE, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, SOMEBODY GOING
HOME.
KAMA, IT WILL NOT BE ANYBODY
FROM YOUR TRIBE.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
OH, ALMOST FORGOT YOUR REWARD.
FLINT.
THANK YOU, SIR.
THANKS, JEFF!
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MANU, I
THINK WENTWORTHS FACE SAYS IT
ALL.
NOTHING ABOUT THIS GAME IS EASY.
FIRST PERSON WILL BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
SHOULD MAKE FOR AN INTERESTING
AFTERNOON BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
LOSING FIRST CHALLENGE IS ONE
OF THE WORST THING TO HAPPEN TO
YOU.
YOU HAVE VERY LITTLE WIGGLE
ROOM.
YOU HAVE KNOWN THESE PEOPLE FOR
THREE GAMES DAZE.
AND I KNOW ANY LITTLE THING CAN
CENT YOU OUT OF THIS GAME AND
YOU CAN BE GONE IN A SECOND.
♪ ♪
IM SORRY, YOU GUYS.
IM SO PISSED!
YOU NEVER COME OUT HERE
EXPECTING TO LOSE AT THATS
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
EVEN THOUGH I FEEL IM MORE
INTROVERTED, I NEED TO HAVE MORE
ONE-ON-ONE CONVERSATIONS.
WHATS THE SPLIT?
TELL ME WHATS GOING ON?
WHATS ON YOUR MIND.
IT SEEMS LIKE LAUREN AND
KELLEY SEEM PRETTY TIGHT.
AND IM NOT SAYING THAT THEYRE
SHADY, BUT LAUREN AND KELLEY
NEED TO BE SEPARATED.
THOSE TWO ARE LIKE A POWER
COUPLE.
AS SOON AS I WAS AT THE WELL,
REEM WAS NOT AFRAID TO PUT IT
OUT THERE.
THEY WANT TO GET KELLY AND
LAUREN.
THEY HAVE LINKED THEM UP AS THIS
DYNAMIC DUOTHAT THEY THINK HAS
CONTROL OF EVERYTHING, SO
THEYRE TRYING TO GET THE VOTES
TOGETHER TO GET ONE OF THOSE TWO
OUT.
ARE YOU SERIOUSLY NOT WORKING
WITH THEM?
NOT YET.
AND THEYRE JUST DOGGING RICK
DOWN.
HE DOESNT EVEN HAVE, LIKE, A
CHANCE TO BREATHE.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
OF THOSE TWO.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING IN
GENERAL?
SO I WASNT REALLY FEELING
THE WHOLE WELL VIBE.
AND SOMETHING CLICKED IN MY HEAD
THEY HAVE TO START PLAYING THIS
GAME FOR ME.
AND AT THE END OF THE DAY, NO
MATTER WHO GOES HOME, I JUST
CANT BE THE ONE TO GO HOME.
THEY CROWDED ME AND RICK
INSTANTLY AND THEYRE TRYING TO
PULL RICK TO THEIR SIDE.
AND THE TARGETS ON YALL.
OF COURSE, YEAH.
OBVIOUSLY WE KNOW WHAT WERE
DOOR, RIGHT?
I DEFINITELY THINK WE NEED TO
KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG IS THE
BOTTOM LINE.
LIKE, NO MATTER WHAT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE HAVE A
BETTER CHANCE OF WINNING THE
NEXT CHALLENGE WITH WENDY AND IT
SEEMS THATS MORE IMPORTANT THAN
ANYTHING.
I DONT WITH REEM.
IF SOMEONE IT JUST KIND OF
KEEP TABS ON WENDY.
LET ME PULL HER ASIDE AND SEE
WHAT SHE SAYS AND WHO SHE THROWS
OUT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WHY DONT YOU,
YEAH, YEAH.
WENTWORTH AND LAUREN, I DONT
LIKE HOW TIGHT THEY ARE.
THEYRE A COUPLE, ANDUN COUPLES
ARE THE WIG BIGGEST THREAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DONT HAVE
FAITH IN REEM.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THE
KIND OF PLAYER.
IM VOTING WITH REEM TONIGHT.
JUST OUT OF LOYALTY TO HER.
NO, I GET IT.
I FEEL LIKE THEYRE NOT
GIVING ENOUGH CREDIT TO REEM.
THEYRE REALLY JUST TAKING HER
AGE INTO ACCOUNT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IM GOING TO PUT ALL THESE RIGHT
IN THE SUN.
SHE CANT HELP HER AGE, BUT
SHE CAN PULL HER WAIT WAET,
WHICH SHE HAS BEEN DOING.
I KNOW YOURE TRYING TO SAVE
YOUR FRIEND AND THAT SHOWS
LOYALTY BUT ITS A SINKING SHIP.
SHES GOING HOME TONIGHT.
THINK ABOUT IT.
LET ME TALK TO DAVID.
YOU GUYS TALK, BUT COME BACK
TO ME.
I WILL.
IM SERIOUS.
WE WILL, WE WILL.
OKAY.
WELL, HERES WHAT IM
THINKING NOW.
OH, NO.
MY MIND HAS CHANGED A LITTLE
BIT.
OH, NO.
MAYBE WE JUST TAKE WENDY OUT.
SHES TOO STUBBORN.
WENDY, IT WAS EXTREMELY
SURPRISING TO ME NO MATTER HOW,
LIKE, DIRECT WE WERE TELLING HER
IT WAS GOING TO BE REEM, SHE
PUSHED BACK.
AND THATS AT LEAST CAUSING
ALARM IN MY HEAD.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN DOWN THE
ROAD?
I CAN WORK WITH SOMEONE LIKE
THAT?
WHAT HELPS ME AND YOU OUT?
WHERE ARE WE BEST?
THIS VOTE TONIGHT I THINK SHOULD
MAYBE BE WENDY.
THEY WANT TO VOTE HER OFF?
THEY WANT TO VOTE ME OFF?
WHEN YOU HEAR YOUR NAME OUT
THERE, ITS LIKE, "SCREW YOU,
DUDE."
JUST BECAUSE I DIDNT GO, LIKE,
POWER LIFT BEFORE I SHOWED UP,
LIKE, THEYRE IDIOTS.
I AM SO STRONG.
YOU DONT EVEN KNOW THIS OLD
LADY, BRO.
THIS OLD LADY CAN KILL IT.
I KNOW THAT THEYRE THROWING MY
NAME AROUND.
AND I DONT REALLY BLIF A...
BECAUSE--
WOULD YOU PUT THE MACHETE
DOWN?
WENTWORTH, DOESNT DNT SHE
GET HURT TODAY?
I DIDNT GET HURT TODAY.
IM NOT DONE.
SCRAPPY, DUDE.
IM NOT GOING DOWN WITHOUT A
FIGHT.
I DIDNT LEAVE EVERYTHING TO GO
DOWN LIKE THAT.
SCREW THEM, MAN.
♪ ♪
Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH,
APPROACH THE FLAME, DIP IT IN
AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
LETS TALK ABOUT FIRST
IMPRESSION.
DEVENS, WHAT DID YOU NOTICE
ABOUT THE INITIAL VIBE OF THE
TRIBE, JUST AS A GROUP?
RIGHT OFF THE BAT, ACTUALLY,
I THINK IT WAS ONE BIG TRIBE.
BUT AS THE DAY PROGRESSED, SOME
PEOPLE WERE WEAVING FROND, SOME
PEOPLE WERE WORKING ON THE
SHELTER, SO, OBVIOUSLY, PEOPLE
KIND OF FORMED MINI-GROUPS
WITHIN THE LARGEY GROUP.
Jeff: REEM, DID YOU NOTICE,
THAT PEOPLE PAIRED IN THREES OR
FOURS?
ITS LIKE PEOPLE WHO WERE
WORKING ON CERTAIN THINGS JUST
ENDED UP TALKING BECAUSE THEY
WERE WORKING TOGETHER.
ITS NOT LIKE THEY WERE --
YOU SEEM ANNOYED ALREADY.
MY NAME GOT THROWN OUT TODAY.
IM PISSED OFF, AND THERES NO
GOOD REASON BEHIND IT.
ITS NOT LIKE PEOPLE WERE
SECRETLY SPEAKING AMONG EACH
OTHER.
THEY WERE JUST DOING THEIR JOBS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHATEVER.
IM JUST IN GENERAL ANNOYED.
BUT THAT IS PART OF THIS
GAME.
YOU KNOW, MY NAME WAS THROWN OUT
THERE.
I HEARD LAURENS NAME.
I HEARD REEMS NAME.
ITS HOW THIS GAME IT PLAYED.
FIMAY-- THE REASON WHY HER
NAME WAS EVEN THROWN OUT IS
BECAUSE SHES A LEGEND, YOU
KNOW.
IT WAS AN HONOR TO HAVE HER NAME
THROWN OUT, REALLY.
ITS NOT AN HONOR WHEN YOU
CAN STILL BE VOTED OUT.
NO DISRESPECT.
SHE IS A GREAT, GREAT PLAYER.
WHY NOT MENTION DAVIDS NAME?
WHY ME SPECIFICALLY?
IM JUST WONDERING JIEK ILL NOT
DONE.
HERES THE FUNNY THING, MY NAME
WAS THROWN OUT APPARENTLY
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO KEEP THE
TRIBE STRONG.
IM GOING WITH AGE
DISCRIMINATION, TO BE QUITE
HONEST WITH YOU.
BECAUSE HOW WOULD YOU KNOW IF I
WASNT STRONG OR NOT STRONG?
I MEAN, DO WE NEED TO HAVE, LIKE
A WRESTLING COMPETITION HERE?
IS THAT SOMETHING WE CAN DO
IN TRIBAL, JEFF?
IM JUST SAYING.
Jeff: REEM, IS THIS NORMAL
FOR YOU?
WHAT?
Jeff: ARE YOU A LITTLE
CONFRONTATIONAL JUST BY NATURE
BACK HOME?
NOT CONFRONTATIONAL, BUT IF I
THINK SOMEONES WRONG, ILL
DEFINITELY BE LIKE, "I DONT
UNDERSTAND WHY YOU THINK YOURE
RIGHT."
HELP ME UNDERSTAND.
THATS WHAT I WAS WONDERING.
IF ANYTHING, REEM, IF
SOMEONES BEING A LITTLE TOO
MUCH, SOMETIMES IT RUBS
DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES THE
WRONG WAY.
WHO WAS I BEING TOO MUCH TO?
TO ME, YOURE A LITTLE TOO
MUCH.
WHY?
WITH WHAT?
YOURE DOING STUFF AND MOVING
THINGS AROUND AND PEOPLE CANT
FIND THEIR THIDGES AND REMIND
PEOPLE TO, LIKE, DRINK THEIR
WATER AND PUT THEIR SHOES ON.
I KNOW THERES GOOD IN ALL OF
THAT.
OH, MY GOD.
SOMETIMES PEOPLE DONT WANT
TO HEAR A MOTHERLY FIGURE.
I DID THAT SO NOBODYS STUFF
GOT WET.
TOTALLY AGREE.
I WAS BEING CARING,
CONSIDERATE.
TELL ME MORE.
, PLEASE, ID LOVE TO LEARN.
YOURE TAKING THIS ONE
EXAMPLE AND MILKING IT.
PERSONALITIES CLASH.
WE ALL REALLY LIKE EVERYBODY BUT
ONE PERSON--
IM THE HATED PERSON ON THE
TRIBE.
SEE, YOURE PUT-- I NEVER
USED THE WORD "HATED."
IN MY OPINION, YOUR PERSONALITY
WOULD BE HARDEST FOR ME TO DEAL
WITH FOR 39 DAYS.
BUT YOUR CLOTHES WERE DRY
THOUGH, FOR THE RECORD, WERE
THEY NOT?
NO, BUT I-- OKAY, YOURE
RIGHT.
Jeff: WENDY, WHERE DO YOU
WEIGH IN ON THIS?
I DO SHARE CONFLICTING PBS
ABOUT REEM.
THE SAME REASONS THEY DISLIKE
HER, I LIKE HER.
IM REALLY CLOSE TO MY MOM, SO
WITH HER BEING HERE, IT KIND OF
HELPS ME OUT.
I DONT THINK ANYONE DISLIKES
REEM.
I AGREE.
IF WE HAD SOMETHING HANGING
IN THE TREE, THAT WAS PROBABLY
MY WAY OF DRYING IT OUT.
I CAN JUST BE HONEST WITH YOU
ALL?
IF YOU DIDNT WANT ME TO TOUCH
YOUR STUFF ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS
SAY, "HEY, PLEASE, DONT TOUCH
MY STUFF."
DONE.
I APPRECIATE YOUR HONESTY, I DO.
IM SORRY I TOUCHED THUR YOUR
THINGS.
Jeff: REEM, WHEN YOU SAY,
"ITS MY FAULT," THATS NOT WHAT
YOU REALLY MEAN?
WHEN I CAME OUT HERE, I
WASNT GOING TO TELL ANYBODY HOW
OLD I AM, THAT I WAS A MOM.
BUT I AM THEIR MOM.
THEY DONT WANT THEIR MOM OUT
HERE WITH THEM.
THATS FINE.
I WOULDNT HAVE-- A LOT OF
THINGS WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
DIFFERENTLY, YES.
Jeff: WENDY, WHAT DO YOU
THINKS GOING TO HAPPEN TONIGHT?
JUST FROM, LIKE, THE TALK
FROM THE CAMP AND EVERYTHING, I
AM SORRY TO SAY, BUT I FEEL LIKE
REEMS GOING HOME.
OH, ITS LIKE A NIGHTMARE.
Jeff: REEM, WE HAVENT HAD
A LOT OF TRIBALS WHERE ALMOST
THE ENTIRE CONVERSATION HAS
CENTERED AROUND ONE PERSON.
I DONT KNOW.
LIKE, IM NOT GOING TO LIE TO
YOU.
THIS IS, LIKE, A FREAKING
NIGHTMARE TO BE THE FIRST ONE
VOTED OFF, YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
IVE BEEN WATCHING SINCE DAY
ONE.
LIKE, THIS IS TERRIBLE.
IM SO DISAPPOINTED.
I GUESS IT WAS JUST TOO MUCH FOR
THEM.
BUT I HOPE ITS NOT TOO MUCH FOR
MY BEST FRIENDS AND MY FAMILY,
BECAUSE IM JUST SURPRISED.
AND, YOU KNOW, FAMOUS LAST
WORDS.
DONT BE THE FIRST ONE VOTED
OUT.
Jeff: SOMEBODY ALWAYS IS.
I KNOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
KELLEY, YOURE UP.
♪ ♪
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, REEM.
KELLEY.
WENDY.
LAUREN.
REEM.
THATS TWO VOTES REEM.
SHOCKER.
WENDY.
THATS TWO VOTES WENDY, TWO
VOTES REEM, ONE VOTE LAUREN, ONE
VOTE WENTWORTH.
REEM.
THATS THREE VOTES REEM.
WENDY.
WERE TIED, THREE VOTES WENDY,
THREE VOTES REEM, ONE VOTE LEFT.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION,"
REEM.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
Jeff: REEM, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
THANKS.
Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE, REEM.
THANK YOU!
I HOPE IT POURS DOWN RAIN ON
THOSE PEOPLE.
RIDICULOUS.
( THUNDER )
SO LAME.
WHAT?
"YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE."
"IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO PLAY
ANYMORE, FOLLOW THIS PATH, AND
YOUR ADVENTURE WILL END."
"IF YOU WANT A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THE GAME, TAKE THE TORCH
AND GET ON THE BOAT"?
HM.
NICE!
♪ ♪
OH, MY GOD!
THERE IS NOTHING HERE.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
HOLY CRAP!
WHAT IS IT?
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
IF YOUR FIRE IS TOO BRIGHT.
THEY HAD THEIR MOMENT TO
SHINE.
ITS OUR CHANCE.
JOE AND I ARE UNDER A
MAGNIFYING GLASS.
Jeff: A PHOENIX MUTT TURN.
TO RISE FROMLET ASHES OPINION.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO GO THROUGH
FOR THIS SECOND CHANCE?
NO OFFENSE, BUT SCREW MY TRIBE.
LIKE, YOURE MAD THEY PUT YOUR
FREAKING CLOTHES ON THE BEACH TO
DRY?
WHATEVER.
AND I DONT WANT TO CRY BECAUSE
IM STILL IN THE GAME AND IM
HAPPY TO BE IN THE GAME, BUT
ITS WET AND ITS COLD.
I JUST GOTTA STICK IT OUT.
EDGE OF FREAKING EXTINCTION.