>> WARDOG, LIKE, I JUST FELT
LIKE THERE WAS A LOT OF LIES AND
SCHEMES GOING ON FROM HIM THAT I
WASN'T--
>> KEEP BEING HONEST WITH THIS
GUY.
>> THAT I DIDN'T RESPECT.
>>
>> KEEP BEING HONEST WITH THIS
GUY.
TRIBAL COUNCIL DID NOT GO
ACCORDING TO MY PLAN.
WARDOG GETS VOTED OUT.
I FELT LIKE I HAD A GREAT
RELATIONSHIP WITH RON, BUT THIS
IS THE SECOND TIME HE'S LIED TO
ME AND GOTTEN RID OF SOMEONE I
WORK WITH.
SO I'M IN A DESPERATE SITUATION
RIGHT NOW.
>> WOULD YOU TALK TO ME FOR A
MINUTE?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY, MAN.
>> AFTER WE VOTE OUT WARDOG,
EVERYONE IS HAPPY WITH ME EXCEPT
FOR DEVONS BECAUSE I'VE LIED TO
HIM EVERY TRIBAL.
SO I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING TO
BRING HIM BACK CLOSER.
MY GOAL HAS BEEN TO MAKE
EVERYONE THINK I'M WORKING WITH
THEM, BECAUSE WHEN EVERYONE
THINKS YOU'RE ON THEIR SIDE,
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO VOTE YOU
OUT.
THE FIVE OF THEM ARE VOTING YOU
OUT NEXT.
>> YEAH.
>> THEY, THEY ARE, BUT I HAVE AN
IDOL.
I FOUND THIS SECRET ADVANTAGE ON
THE VERY FIRST DAY ON THE BOAT
THAT WE ARRIVED IN.
IT'S EXPIRED.
BUT HE DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW
THAT.
I'M JUST GOING TO GIVE TO YOU TO
SHOW YOU I'M LOYAL AND YOU CAN
TRUST ME.
>> OH, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> IT MEANT A LOT TO HIM.
AND NOW HE MAY RELAX THINKING
THAT HE'S SAFE.
THEN WE'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF HIM AND SEND HIM
HOME.
>> SO RON GIVES ME THIS LITTLE
MENU, WHICH PLAYS JUST LEAK A
REGULAR HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
NOT TOO SHABBY.
I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW WHY RON
WOULD GIVE THIS TO ME.
LIKE, TOTALLY CONFUSED.
THANKS, MAN.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> I HOPE THAT I DON'T HAVE TO
RELY ON THIS ADVANTAGE, SO I
NEED TO KEEP TRYING TO PLAY AS
HARDAISE CAN.
BUT I'M OPTIMISTIC.
I'M THE PHOENIX, AND I KEEP
RISING FROM THE ASHES.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO TODAY'S REWARD CHALLENGE.
LAST TIME WE RAN THIS CHALLENGE
WAS NEARLY A DECADE AGO.
"SURVIVOR: HEROES VERSUS
VILLAINS."
PLAYERS AND THEIR LOVED ONES.
CHALLENGE IS GOOD TO GO.
ALL WE'RE MISSING IS IS THE
LOVED ONES.
CUE THE MUSIC.
DEVENS, HERE'S YOUR WIFE, BECCA.
COME ON OUT.
>> SHE'S GORGEOUS.
>> SHE IS GORGEOUS, ISN'T SHE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
YOUR BEARD!
YOU LOOK GREAT!
>> YOU LOOK GREAT.
>> JEFF PUT THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE ON ME YESTERDAY?
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS!
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SO, BECCA, WHAT'S IT
LIKE FOR YOU BACK HOME?
>> OUR SON, JACK, HE DOESN'T
KNOW WHERE RICK IS.
HE ASKS ABOUT HIM, BUT HE'S NOT,
LIKE, FREAKING OUT.
NOBODY IS FREAKING OUT.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT TRIGGER YOU
AT ALL WHEN SHE BRINGS UP YOUR
SON AND HE DOESN'T KNOW WHERE
YOU ARE.
>> HALFWAY INTO THE GAME THAT
WAS A DEVASTATING THING TO THINK
ABOUT, BUT NOW, DOWN THE HOME
STRETCH, JACK IS GOING TO SEE
JEFF PUT THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE
ON ME.
IT'S GOING TO BE AWESOME.
IT'S GOING TO BE REALLY SPECIAL.
THEY ONLY GIVE ME STRENGTH NOW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HIM A
BIG HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: JULIE, ARE YOU READY
FOR SOME LOVE?
GET YOUR HUSBAND OUT HERE.
MARK, COME ON OUT.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M GOOD.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> Jeff: SHE ASKS IF HE'S
OKAY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: JULIE, IS A BIG PART
OF THE REASON YOU'RE OUT HERE IS
JUST A TEST FOR YOURSELF?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'VE BEEN SAYING IT SINCE DAY
ONE, I WANT TO PUSH MYSELF TO
THE LIMITS AND PROVE TO MYSELF,
LIKE, I KNOW I HAVE THIS ININNER
STRENGTH THEY DON'T ALWAYS SHOW
BACK AT HOME TO THE PEOPLE I'M
WITH.
BUT I THINK THE BIGGEST THING IS
THAT I UNDERESTIMATE MYSELF.
>> Jeff: DO YOU THINK THAT'S
CHANGING?
>> FOR SURE.
YOU DON'T EVEN REALIZE HOW MUCH
I'VE CHANGED.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO
BE A DIFFERENT PERSON WHEN I GET
BACK.
LIKE, I JUST FEEL LIKE I'M GOING
TO BE A BETTER WIFE AND MOTHER.
>> YOU'RE PRETTY GREAT.
YOU DON'T TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MARK, GIVE
HER A BIG HUG.
LAWREB, ARE YOU READY FOR SOME
LOVE?
HERE'S YOUR DAD, JOEY.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, I DON'T WANT
TO DOES WHAT YOU WHISPERED IN
YOUR DAD'S EERK BUT WHAT'S THE
ESSENCE OF THE COMMUNICATION
COMOOUKS?
IS THAT YOU NEED HIM TO KNOW
YOU'RE OKAY OR YOU NEED HIM TO
MAKE YOU OKAY?
>> I THINK IT'S A LITTLE OF
BOTH.
MY DAD IS MY ROCK.
I MEAN, HE'S BEEN THROUGH
EVERYTHING WITH ME.
AND IT'S JUST BEEN THE HARDEST
THING EVER NOT HAVING HIM HERE.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, IF I DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING, HOW LONG WOULD YOU
STAND THERE HUGGING YOUR DAD
LIKE THAT?
>> FOREVER.
>> Jeff: FOREVER.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE HER ONE LAST
HUG.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I LOVE YOU, BABY.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> LET'S HAVE FUN.
>> Jeff: RON, LET'S GET YOUR
HUSBAND OUT HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
LLOYD, COME ON OUT!
LET'S SEE WHO MARRIED YOU.
>> OH, MAN!
>> I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
>> I MISSED YOU, TOO.
HOW'S MOM AND DAD?
>> THEY'RE GOOD.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
>> Jeff: RON, DESCRIBE THE
COMFORT, WHEN YOU CAN FALL INTO
THE ARMS OF YOUR PARTNER,
KNOWING IT'S SAFE?
>> I MEAN, HE'S MY PROTECTOR.
IT'S BECAUSE OF HIM THAT I CAN
DO STUFF LIKE THIS BECAUSE HE
MAKES ME FEEL SO SAFE.
IT'S JUST AN AMAZING FEELING TO
HAVE SOMEONE IN YOUR LIFE, NO
MATTER WHAT YOU WANT TO DO THEY
SAY, GFOR IT."
THEY'RE CHEERING FOR YOU 100%.
>> Jeff: THAT'S HUGE.
>> YOU HAVE FACIAL HAIR?
>> YOU LIKE IT.
THESE ARE MY FRIENDS.
THESE ARE MY NEW FRIENDS.
>> HE'S EVEN BETTER LOOKING THAN
YOU SAID HE WAS.
THIS IS GREAT.
>> I LOVE OUR LIFE.
AND I'M NEVER GOING TO TAKE IT
FOR GRANTED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LLOYD,
GIVE HIM A BIG HUG.
>> OF COURSE.
>> YOU'RE DOING WELL, BABE.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, YOU READY
FOR SOME LOVE?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: LET'S GET YOUR DAD
OUT HERE.
ROCK, COME ON OUT!
>> I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
LET ME LOOK AT YOU.
>> DON'T I LOOK CRAZY?
>> NO.
YOU LOOK LIKE A FRECKLE.
>> YOU SMELL GOOD.
>> "YOU SMELL GOOD."
>> BUG SPRAY.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, WALK ME
THROUGH YOUR "SURVIVOR"
EXPERIENCE.
WHEN DID YOU FIRST START
WATCHING?
>> I STARTED WATCHING WHEN I WAS
LIKE SIX YEARS OLD WITH MY WHOLE
FAMILY, AND MY DAD IS JUST AS
BIG A FAN AS I AM SO I WAS JUST
DYING TO GET TO THIS MOMENT SO
WE COULD HAVE IT TOGETHER.
EVERY OTHER TIME I'VE CRIED IN
THIS GAME IS THINKING ABOUT THIS
MOMENT.
AND IT JUST MAKES ME A DIFFERENT
PERSON.
I CAN'T PRETEND THAT I'M, LIKE,
COLD ANYMORE.
>> SHE'S TOUGH.
SHE'S BEST.
>> Jeff: OH!
CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING BETTER FROM
YOUR DAD.
>> NO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HER A
LAST HUG, ROCK.
>> OH, BABY.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: AURORA, SOMEBODY HERE
FOR YOU.
LET'S GET YOUR BROTHER OUT HERE,
SHANE.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: THAT'S A HUG.
>> Jeff: TELL ME ABOUT YOUR
BROTHER, AURORA.
>> LIKE, I WOULDN'T BE THE
PERSON I AM TODAY WITHOUT HIM.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITIES I HAVE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING WITHOUT
HIM.
HE HAS BEEN MY BROTHER, MY
FATHER, MY PROTECTOR.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> EVERYTHING I DO, I THINK OF
WHAT-- MAKING SURE I MAKE HIM
PROUD, AND THAT EVERY DAY I'M
THE PERSON HE THOUGHT I COULD
BE.
>> AND BEYOND WHAT I THOUGHT YOU
COULD BE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GIVE HIM A
BIG HUG.
>> STAY STRONG.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Jeff: GAVIN, YOU READY FOR
SOME LOVE?
WOW!
GAVIN DOESN'T CRY.
>> NO ONE ELSE KNOWS, BUT I WAS
SUPPOSED TO GET MARRIED A WEEK
AFTER "SURVIVOR" STARTED, AND
CARLY MOVED UP THE WEDDING SO I
COULD COME OUT HERE, SO WE GOT
MARRIED TWO DAYS BEFORE.
>> Jeff: SO IT SEEMS ONLY
FITTING THAT SHE GETS TO SHARE
IN THIS WITH YOU.
CARLY, COME ON OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I LOOK AWFUL, DON'T I?
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY I LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOSH, TWO DAYS BEFORE.
>> Jeff: CARROLL, WHAT'S IT
LIKE FOR TO YOU HAVE A NEW
HUSBAND, AND THEN HE LEAVES?
>> IT'S SO OVERWHELMING TO HAVE
HIM LEAVE, YOU KNOW, RIGHT
AFTER.
IT WAS SO HARD.
BUT--
>> SO THIS IS OUR HONEYMOON.
( LAUGHTER )
EVER SINCE WE STARTED DATING,
SHE KNOWS I'VE BEEN A FAN OF
"SURVIVOR," AND, LIKE, THAT'S
BEEN MY DREAM.
BUT NOW THAT I'M OUT HERE ALL I
CAN THINK ABOUT IS GETTING BACK
HOME TO HER.
>> HE TALKS ABOUT YOU ALL THE
TIME.
>> EVERY DAY.
>> THIS IS MY DREAM.
THIS IS-- "SURVIVOR" IS GREAT,
BUT, LIKE, THIS IS IT.
I COULDN'T ASK FOR ANYTHING
MORE.
>> Jeff: WELL SAID.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE HER A LAST HUG.
( APPLAUSE )
>> CONGRATULATIONS, GUYS.
ON THE WEDDING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO THE CHALLENGE.
BY THE WAY, IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T
FIGURED IT OUT, YOU ARE
PARTICIPATING.
SO PAY ATTENTION.
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING TO WORK.
ON MY "GO" YOU'RE GOING TO RACE
DOWN WITH A BUCKET, SCOOP UP
WATER FROM THE OCEAN, RACE BACK,
ATTEMPT TO TOSS IT TO YOUR LOVED
ONE, WHO WILL TRY TO CATCH IT
AND PUT IT IN THEIR BUCKET.
FIRST PAIR TO FILL THEIR BUCKET
AND RAISE THEIR FLAG WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: IT'S AS CLOSE TO HOME
AS YOU CAN GET WHILE PLAYING
"SURVIVOR."
YOUR LOVED ONES BACK AT YOUR
CAMP WITH A "SURVIVOR" PICNIC,
FRIED CHICKEN AND APPLE PIE FOR
DESSERT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: FIND YOUR PARTNERS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD IN THE FORM OF LOVE,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS A RACE TO THE OCEAN.
YOU'RE LOOKING TO PUT WATER IN
THAT BUCKET AND TRANSFER IT TO
YOUR LOVED ONE'S BUCKET.
IT'S GOING TO BE AURORA AND
GAVIN BACK FIRST.
BIG TOSS, BUT NOT MUCH IN THERE.
NICE TOSS FROM GAVIN TO CARLY.
WHAT A HONEYMOON GIFT THIS WOULD
BE TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
HERE COMES LAUREN.
AND A NICE CATCH BY DAD.
VICTORIA COMES UP SHORT.
DEVENS TO HIS WIFE.
DRENCHES HIS WIFE.
NOT MUCH IN THE BUCKET.
HERE GOES JULIE TOWARD MARK.
NOT BAD.
RON WITH A NICES TO.
GAVIN TO CARROLL AGAIN.
>> THAT WAS GOOD!
>> Jeff: CARLY WITH A NICE
CATCH.
>> A LITTLE BIT STRAIGHTER.
>> Jeff: AURORA TO SHANE, HER.
>> SORRY.
>> A LITTLE BIT OF WATER.
HERE COMES LAUREN.
>> BIG TOSS.
>> YUP.
>> Jeff: LOVE ON THE LINE.
AND A NICE CATCH BY DAD, WHO IS
GETTING WET.
>> LET'S GO, BABE.
>> Jeff: RON WITH ANOTHER NICE
TOSS.
DEVENS TO HIS WIFE.
>> GOOD ONE!
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, I DON'T
KNOW IF DEVENS IS DOING THAT ON
PURPOSE OR NOT, BECCA.
>> HE IS.
VICTORIA STRUGGLING EVEN TO GET
BACK.
>> CAN'T BREATHE.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA IS
EXHAUSTED.
HOW BADLY DO YOU WANT THE LOVE.
AURORA TO SHANE, HER BROTHER.
>> DANG IT!
>> Jeff: THAT'S NOT EVEN WORTH
THE RUN.
JULIE, EITHER LAUGHING OR
CRYING.
>> HYPERVENTILATING!
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: EVERY TIME YOU RUN
DOWN TO THAT BEACH, IT IS TAKING
A TOLL.
>> SORRY!
>> HOW'S IT GOING, BABE?
>> GOOD, AERVE'S GOOD.
AND I MISS YOU.
>> I MISS YOU, TOO.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
>> Jeff: NICE TOSS FROM RON.
ONCE YOU START SEEING THAT
BUCKET START TO LOWER, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
HERE COMES GAVIN TO CARLY AGAIN.
THIS COULD END VERY FAST.
IF YOU HAVE A GOOD CONNECTION.
THEY'RE CLOSE.
THAT BUCKET'S MOVING.
>> LAST TOSS WAS GREAT.
>> Jeff: LAUREN WITH A NICE
TOSS TO HER DAD.
YOU ARE GETTING CLOSE.
THE TOSS TO LLOYD.
HOW MUCH DID HE GET?
NOT BAD.
EVERY LITTLE BIT HELPS.
THAT COULD DO IT.
RON AND LLOYD WIN REWARD!
>> WE GOT IT!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WE GOT HALFWAY.
>> YOU DON'T EVEN REALLY SMELL
BAD.
>> THANKS FOR THE COMPLIMENT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU'RE
GOING BACK TO CAMP WITH LLOYD.
"SURVIVOR" PICNIC.
NOW COMES THE TOUGH PART.
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO BRING WITH
YOU?
SIX PAIRS OF LOVED ONES.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR EYES YOU.
PICK ONE PLAYER AND THEIR LOVED
ONE TO JOIN YOU.
>> I LOVE EVERYBODY OVER THERE.
BUT I'M GOING TO PICK JULIE.
>> Jeff: OKAY, JULIE, COME ON
OVER.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GET TO PICK ONE
MORE PAIR.
BIG POLITICAL DECISION.
GAMES HAVE BEEN WON AND LOSTA
THIS POINT IN THE GAME.
>> I KNOW.
THEY REALLY BROKE MY HEART WHAT
I HEARD A LITTLE WHILE AGO AND I
THINK THEY NEED A PROPER
HONEYMOON, SO I'M GOING TO PICK
GAVIN.
>> Jeff: GAVIN AND CARLY, COME
ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
ALL RIGHT, SURVIVORS, SAY
GOODBYE TO YOUR LOVED ONES.
TIME FOR THEM TO GO.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> BYE.
>> I LOVE YOU, BABE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, LAUREN,
VICTORIA, AURORA, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY.
>> SEEING SOMEONE AS IMPORTANT
AS MY DAD AND TO HAVE IT TAKEN
AWAY, IT JUST SUCKS.
AND IT ABSOLUTELY MAKES ME THINK
TWICE ABOUT, YOU KNOW, WHAT KIND
OF RELATIONSHIP I HAVE WITH RON,
WHAT KIND OF STRATEGY HE'S
REALLY PLAYING.
IF THERE'S EVER AN AWARD WHERE
PICKING SOMEONE IS CRUCIAL IT'S
THE LOVED ONE'S VISIT.
YOU WHO PICK CAN MAKE OUR BREAK
YOUR GAME.
>> RON, FIRST OF ALL, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, RON.
>> YEAH, THANK YOU, RON.
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR
HONEYMOON.
>> THIS IS LOVELY!
>> WAIT, FIRST OF ALL, HOW WAS
THE TALENT SHOW?
>> AMAZING.
THEY ROCKED IT.
THEY DID GREAT.
>> I'M EATING EVERYTHING.
I'M EATING EVERYTHING.
>> I JUST CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK
AND EXPERIENCE THE MARRIED LIFE.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> YOU ARE SO CLOSE.
LIKE, YOU HAVE SO MUCH TO BE
PROUD OF.
>> RON CAME THROUGH IN THE
CLUTCH, AND HE PICKED ME FOR
THIS FAMILY VISIT.
I MEAN, I AM SUPER GRATEFUL TO
HIM.
>> GAVIN HAS TALKED ABOUT YOU
EVERY DAY ALL DAY.
>> OH!
>> LUCKILY, CARLY SUPPORTS MY
DREAM.
BUT DEEP DOWN, I STILL FEEL LIKE
WHO DOESN'T GO ON THEIR
HONEYMOON BECAUSE OF "SURVIVOR."
CARLY WROTE IN OUR VOW BOOKS,
"PART OF ME IS LEAVING"...
SORRY.
"A PART OF ME IS LEAVING WITH
YOU ON THE PLANE."
IT'S LIKE, "YEAH, LIKE, I-- I
HAVE SO MUCH TO PLAY FOR.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I HAVE PLAYED DOUBLE AGENT
AND DOUBLE-DOUBLE AGENT.
I HAVE LIED.
>> I BET.
>> I HAVE CHEATED.
>> IT'S A PART OF THE GAME.
>> I'VE MANIPULATED SO MANY
PEOPLE.
>> YOU'RE STILL HERE, RIGHT?
>> I'M IN CHARGE OF THIS GAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT THEY'RE SO LOYAL.
I MEAN, PART OF THE GAME IS
PICKING PEOPLE SO THAT THEY
THINK YOU TRUST THEM.
I WANTED TO GET THE MAXIMUM
IMPACT OUT OF MY PICKS.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE I HAVE JEWEL
NEMY POCKET.
AND THEN I PICKED GAVIN.
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
HONEYMOON.
THAT WOULDN'T HAVE SUEDE MY
DECISION.
I NEED GAVIN TO BE LOCKED IN,
AND NOW TO GIVE HIM THAT
EXPERIENCE WITH HIS NEW BRIDE,
IT'S A POWERFUL GIFT.
WHAT ARE THE THREE OF US DOING?
>> IF RICK DOESN'T WIN IMMUNITY
ATTORNEY GENERAL IT'S RICK.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> HIS BUTT'S GOT TO GO.
IN THE BEST IN MY LIFE TELLING
LLOYD, "I DID THIS.
I DID THAT."
AND HE KEPT SAYING TO ME, "DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
WIN THIS GAME."
SO IT'S MADE ME FOCUS EVEN MORE.
>> BYE, GUYS!
BYE!
>> WE'RE A GREAT TEAM.
HE BALANCES ME AND HE SUPPORTS
ME AND IT WORKS BEAUTIFULLY
TOGETHER.
>> HE IS TRYING TO MAKE EVERYONE
PARANOID RIGHT NOW.
>> MAYBE SOMEBODY SENT HIM A
CLUE.
>> BUT IF YOU HAD A CLUE, IF YOU
ALREADY HAD IT -- GO THROUGH IT.
GO THROUGH IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHY ARE YOU LOOKING IN MY
BAG?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE WALK AROUND
LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
IT'S ALLOWED IN THE GAME.
I JUST CAN'T LOOK--
>> I KNOW IT'S ALLOWED.
>> WHAT WAS I JUST SAYING.
>> AUGUST WARD!
>> NOT REALLY.
I'M GOOD.
>> I FEEL LIKE I WOULD FEEL
AWKWARD IF I GOT CAUGHT LOOKING
THROUGH SOMEONE'S BAG.
>> NO.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> SO I'M OUT SEARCHING FOR THE
IDOL AGAIN, AND I GO BACK TO
CAMP, AND I SEE AURORA CLOSING
THE FLAP OF MY BAG, AND SHE'S
BUSTED.
BUT SHE DIDN'T EVEN HIDE IT.
SHE DON'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT
NOTHING.
>> IT'S NOTHING AGAINST YOU,
RICK.
I'M JUST LOOKING.
>> OH, I KNOW.
YOU JUST GOT CAUGHT.
>> I KNOW, AND I'M TOTALLY FINE
WITH IT, DUDE.
>> I KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
FIND ANYTHING GOOD?
>> NO.
NOT REALLY.
>> YOU DIDN'T LOOK VERY HARD.
THANK GOD AURORA DIDN'T FIND THE
ADVANTAGE RON GAVE ME.
BUT I ALSO WANT TO MAKE IT
AWKWARD IN CAMP.
I WANT TO LET EVERYONE KNOW
AURORA'S GOING THROUGH BAGS.
CAN WE TRUST AURORA?
>> YEAH, THEY'RE LOOK THROUGH
BAGS.
WATCH YOUR BAGS.
>> OH, GOD.
>> WHATEVER.
>> MAYBE DON'T KEEP THE ONE I
GAVE YOU IN YOUR BAG.
>> I'M NOT LEAVING MY BAG
ANYMORE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
I'M TAKING IT EVERYWHERE.
NOW THAT EVERYONE THINKS I'M
SEARCHING FOR AN IDOL, I'M GOING
TO SEARCH FOR AN IDOL.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING ALL DAY.
IT'S A PAIN, MAN.
I LOOKED ALL OVER THE PLACE AND
I CAN'T FIND ANYTHING.
BUT IF THERE'S AN IDOL OUT HERE
FOR ME TO FIND, I'M GOING TO PUT
IN THE WORK.
THIS IS MY SECOND CHANCE,
BECAUSE I CAME BACK FROM "THE
EDGE."
IF I GO FOR IT, THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN'T DO.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU MUST BE KIDDING ME.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU FOUND THE CLUE TO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT WILL REQUIRE YOU TO BE
DARING.
IT RESTS IN THE TREES ABOVE YOUR
SHELTER.
GOOD LUCK."
OH!
I DON'T EVEN NEED IT TO BE A
SECRET.
I'M GOING TO GO GET IT RIGHT
NOW.
NO.
I WON'T.
OH, I WANT IT IN MY POSSESSION
SO BAD.
BUT I DON'T WANT THEM TON I HAVE
IT.
I WANT TO HAVE OPTIONS WITH THIS
BABY.
I MEAN, THIS COULD BE A
MILLION-DOLLAR FIND.
I MIGHT HAVE JUST STUMBLED
ACROSS A MILLION DOLLARS IN THAT
TREE.
I JUST HAVE TO SCOPE IT OUT.
WHERE I THINK IT IS.
HOLY CRAP!
THIS THING IS, LIKE, 15 FEET IN
THE AIR ABOVE CAMP.
AND I DON'T EVEN LIKE HEIGHTS.
SO THINGS ARE A LOT MORE
COMPLICATED THAN I THOUGHT THEY
WERE.
THAT'S REALLY HARD.
CAMP IS SO RARELY TOTALLY EMPTY.
NICE JOB, GUYS!
I'M JUST GOG FORCE MYSELF TO BE
PATIENT.
IT'S A GRIND, MAN.
"SURVIVOR" IS A GRIND, AND I'M
GRINDING.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
IT'S DARK, WITH EVERYONE
SLEEPING.
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
I'M GETTING THAT IDOL.
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DAN
D.N.A. BECAUSE IT IS 15 FEET IN
THE AIR IN THE MIDDLE OF OUR
CAMP.
I'M GOING FOR IT.
I'M GOING TO CLIMB THIS TREE
LIKE A NINJA, GET IT, AND GET
THE HELL OUT OF DODGE.
I GOTTA DO THIS FAST.
I GOTTA TRY TO BE QUIET.
I'M HALFWAY UP.
MY BELT GETS STUCK ON THIS OTHER
TREE.
COME OMAN!
COME ON!
I'M TRYING TO DO THIS VERY
QUIETLY.
AND I'M STILL MAKING NOISE.
ON THE SHELTER, YOU KNOW, THE
BAMBOO RUBBING AGAINST EACH
OTHER.
I FINALLY REACH FOR THE GAP AND
I'M FEELING, FEELING.
AND I FEEL SOMETHING SOLID.
AND I KNOW IT'S THE IDOL.
I GET IT IN MY POCKET, AND DOWN
THE TREE, MAN.
GOT AWAY WITH THE LOOT.
SCOT FREE.
NO ONE EVEN KNOWS THEY WERE
ROBBED.
STEALTH MISSION A SUCCESS.
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE IS SLEEPING,
I'M WORKING.
AND IT PAYS OFF.
THIS IS MY SALVATION IN THE
GAME.
THEY SEARCHED MY BAG TOO SOON.
( LAUGHS )
I HAVE WHAT RON GAVE ME.
NOW I HAVE THIS.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT'S COMING
FOR THEM.
I'M ON TOP OF THE MOON.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO USE YOUR ARMS TO BRACE
YOURSELF BETWEEN TWO WALLS WHILE
YOUR FLEETFEET ARE PERCHED ON
VERY NARROW FOOTHOLDS.
WHEN YOU DROP, YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE TONIGHT AT THE
VOTE.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S BEGIN THIS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
THIS IS THE CHALLENGE WHERE YOU
JUST HAVE TO OUTLAST THE OTHERS.
YOU DON'T THINK ABOUT GETTING
DOWN.
YOU JUST WAIT FOR THEM TO DROP
ONE BY ONE.
>> HOLY MOLY.
>> YOU GUYS GIVE ME THIS, I
PROMISE, EVERY ONE OF YOU, FINAL
THREE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: LAUREN WHAT, DO YOU
THINK OF THAT OFFER?
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE DEVENS CAN'T
DO MATH.
>> SHE'S NOT WRONG.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A CHALLENGE
THAT'S GOING TO REALLY TEST HOW
YOU'RE FEELING NONETHELESS GAME
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S REALLY JUST WILL POWER.
RON'S SHAKING HIS HEAD NO.
I DISAGREE.
RON SAYS NO, IT'S NOT WILL
POWER.
IT'S JUST PAIN.
>> IT'S PAIN.
DEVENS WITH NO WARNING DROPS AND
IS OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
VULNERABLE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHICH IS NEVER GOOD.
>> ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY TOLD YOU
IT'S GOING TO BE YOU TONIGHT.
>> YUP.
AND I SAY AS SOON AS I'M GOING,
AURORA, YOU'RE GOING TO BE A
HUGE TARGET.
YOU'VE WON TWO IMMUNITYS.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> I'M ALWAYS UNCOMFORTABLE, BUT
RIGHT NOW, I'M PRETTY GOOD.
YOU KNOW, HE KNOWS WE ALL LOVE
HIM, BUT WE'VE BEEN FLAT-OUT
HONEST.
HE'S GOT TO GO.
>> THANK YOU.
( LAUGHS )
>> Jeff: AND RON, RIGHT AFTER
DEVENS, DROPS.
21 MINUTES INTO THIS CHALLENGE.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DOING GOOD.
>> WELL.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DOING WELL.
I DID A LOT OF WALKING AROUND
TODAY.
>> FIND ANYTHING?
>> NO.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO GO FOR
TONIGHT?
>> MAYBE AURORA.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
>> Jeff: BEEN UP THERE 33
MINUTES.
VICTORIA STEPS OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE WITH ZERO WARNING.
>> YOU SAW MY LEG?
>> I'M DONE.
I'M DONE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
JULIE ANNOUNCES IT AND GOES TO
HER KNEES.
>> YOU OKAY, HONEY?
>> Jeff: JULIE FEELING NOT
ONLY 31 DAYS BUT 33 MINUTES OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
RON GOING TO GO OVER AND HELP.
>> I'M FINE.
>> GOOD JOB, JULIE.
>> I CAN'T WALK.
OH, MY GOD!
( LAUGHS ).
>> OH, IT'S BEEN FUN.
>> Jeff: OH, WOW "IT'S BEEN
FUN," AND AURORA STEPS OUT.
SHE CAN'T WALK.
AND WE ARE LEFT WITH LAUREN
RIGHT NEXT TO GAVIN.
BEEN UP THERE 50 MINUTES.
BOTH PLAYERS TRYING TO PUSH
THROUGH WHAT IS CLEARLY IMMENSE
PAIN.
THERE IS NO RELIEF.
EVERYTHING HURTS.
LAUREN AND GAVIN FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY.
LAUREN CAN'T HOLD ON.
LAUREN DROPS.
GAVIN WINS HIS SECOND INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
COME HERE.
>> Jeff: GAVIN, NICE JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, GAVIN.
>> GOOD JOB, GAVIN!
>> Jeff: GAVIN, SAFE TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SEE YOU
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THE GAME.
>> THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE DIDN'T
GO AS WELL.
I FELL OUT EARLY.
ON THE OTHER HAND, IT WAS
PERFECT BECAUSE DEVENS FELL OUT
FIRST AND HE'S THE ONE WE WANT
TO SEND HOME.
THE ONLY THING HE'S GOING TO
TRIBAL WITH TONIGHT IS THAT FAKE
ADVANTAGE.
HE WILL TRY TO PLAY IT, IT WON'T
WORK, AND HE'LL BE SENT TO THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GOOD JOCK, BROTHER.
>> AWESOME.
>> HOW ARE YOUR FEET?
>> KILLING ME.
>> THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WAS A
MASSIVE FAILURE AND AN
EMBARRASSMENT.
>> GOOD WORK, BROTHER MAN.
>> WE GET BACK TO CAMP, AND NO
ONE IS TALKING TO ME.
LIKE, THERE'S NOTHING TO TALK
ABOUT.
LIKE, OKAY, IT'S RICK.
EASY.
WE SHOULD ALL GET TOGETHER.
YOU GUYS WANT TO WORK TOGETHER?
NO TAKERS?
>> LEAVE IT BE.
LEAVE IT BE.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYONE WANTS TO
WORK WITH ME, EXCEPT FOR MAYBE
RON, AND HE COULD BE TOTALLY
FULL OF IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> OKAY, SO, 100%, LIKE, ON
BOARD, AURORA TONIGHT.
>> HOW IS IT GOING TO GO DOWN?
>> WELL, PEOPLE THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO BE YOU.
>> AND THAT'S, LIKE, REAL.
BECAUSE I NEVER ASKED FOR IT.
YOU'RE NOT JUST MESSING WITH ME.
>> YEP.
>> WELL, IT WOULD BE THE SECOND
TIME YOU GUYS SAVED ME.
SO I'D BE TOTALLY ON BOARD.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, BUDDY.
>> OKAY, YOU GUYS GO THIS WAY.
I'LL GO THAT WAY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> RON!
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
>> THERE'S A REASON WHY THE GAME
IS CALLED "SURVIVOR."
>> THE PLAN TONIGHT IS TO PUT
ALL THE VOTES ON DEVENS, BUT IF
DEVENS DOES HAVE A REAL IMMUNITY
IDOL, HIS ONE VOTE WOULD CHOOSE
WHO GOES HOME.
SO I TOLD DEVENS TO VOTE FOR
AURORA.
>> WE'RE CLEAR.
WE ARE ALL VOTING RICK.
SHOOS ALL WE NEED TO DO.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL-- AURORA,
SHE'S POSITIONED THOARS WIN THIS
GAME.
>> AURORA'S BURNED NOBODY.
THE THREE OF US HAVE ALL BURNED
PEOPLE IN OUR ORIGINAL TRIBE.
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
WE'RE ALL GOOD BEFORE--
>> I'M GOOD.
>> I LOVE YOU TWO.
>> AND I'M SO GLAD US THREE ARE
TOGETHER.
>> IT WILL BE A LIVELY TRIBAL
READING OF THE VOTES.
>> THERE'S RICK, AND THEN
THERE'S THE BACKUP PLAN IF RICK
HAS AN IDOL.
>> EXACTLY.
>> TONIGHT'S VOTE SHOULD BE
SIMPLE.
EVEN RICK KNOWS IT'S RICK.
THE PROBLEM IS WE DON'T KNOW IF
HE HAS SOME KIND OF IDOL OR
ADVANTAGE.
AND AT THIS POINT, WE HAVE TO
ASSUME HE DOES.
IF WE DIDN'T SPLIT THE VOTES,
THEN JUST WHOEVER RICK VOTES FOR
GOES HOME.
BUT I WANT TO BE THE ONE TO
DECIDE WHO GOES HOME.
>> IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS WE
HAVEN'T BEEN ON THE SAME SIDE
MOST OF THIS GAME.
I'D RATHER BE ON THE SAME SIDE.
>> I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
IT'S GOTTEN TO THE POINT NOW
WHERE I NEED SOMEONE THAT I CAN
TRUST.
IN MY HEAD, "THIS IS WHAT MAKES
MOST SENSE.
AND YOU TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK.
>> YEAH.
>> DEVENS FIRST.
>> OR IF DEVENS PLAYS AN IDOL,
WE COULD GET OUT RON.
>> I WANT RON OUT SO BADLY.
>> IF GAVIN KNOWS ME AND YOU ARE
ON BOARD, I THINK HE'LL BE MORE
THAN DOWN.
RON PICKING GAVIN AND JULIE FOR
THE LOVED ONES MADE IT VERY
CLEAR HE'S NOT WORKING WITH ME.
SO HE'S GOING TO GET STUCK ON
THE WRONG SIDE OF THE NUMBERS
WHICH I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH.
>> THERE'S SIX OF US VOTING
DEVENS, BUT WE'RE SAYING JUST IN
CASE DEVENS PLAYS SOMETHING,
LAUREN AND GAVIN ARE PICK RON.
>> I HAVE AN EXTRA VOTE.
THIS IS THE LAST TIME I CAN USE
IT.
BUT IF YOU 100%, I WOULD GIVE
GAVIN THE EXTRA VOTE.
IF THERE'S A TIE AND I'M THE ONE
THEY VOTE AFTER, I LOSE MY
ABILITY TO VOTE.
IF THERE'S A TIE WHERE I AM ONE
OF THE NAMES BEING WRITTEN DOWN,
I CAN'T REVOTE.
SO THE ONLY WAY TO ENSURE THAT
MY ADDITIONAL VOTE WILL COUNT IS
TO GIVE IT TO GAVIN BECAUSE WITH
GAVIN HAVING IMMUNITY, HE'S THE
ONE PERSON WHO IS GUARANTEED TO
BE ABLE TO VOTE IN A REVOTE.
WHICH ALLOWS US TO STAY IN
CONTROL.
BUT I'M PUTTING A LOT OF FAITH
IN GAVIN.
I JUST HOPE I DON'T GO DOWN IN
HISTORY AS ONE OF THE "SURVIVOR"
IDIOTS.
>> I HAD A VERY, VERY LONG TALK
WITH VICTORIA AND AURORA TODAY.
THEY WANT TO SPLIT THE VOTE
BETWEEN RICK AND RON.
IN CASE, LIKE, RICK PLAYS
SOMETHING.
>> YEAH.
>> WHICH, HONESTLY, GAVIN, IS
FINE WITH ME.
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE WE NEED RON OUT,
ANYWAY.
>> THE PLAN FOR TONIGHT IS
THERE'S GOING TO BE A MAJORITY
VOTING FOR RICK DEVENS, AND THEN
WE HAVE TO DECIDE WHO'S GOING TO
BE THE NEXT BIGGEST THREAT, JUST
IN CASE DEVENS PULLS OUT AN
IDOL.
AND THEY'RE SAYING IT'S GOT TO
BE RON, BUT RON JUST GAVE ME ONE
OF THE GREATEST DAYS OF MY LIFE
YESTERDAY, AND NOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO TURN AROUND AND BLINDSIDE
HIM.
>> OKAY, SO HERE'S WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
I'M GIVING YOU MY EXTRA VOTE.
>> AURORA HAS AN EXTRA VOTE, AND
SHE IS GIVING IT TO ME.
SINCE I HAVE IMMUNITY, THEN IF
THERE'S A TIE VOTE, I'M
GUARANTEED TO VOTE AGAIN.
I'M NOT SURE IF I WANT TO VOTE
FOR RON AND BURN BRIDGES BEFORE
I HAVE TO.
I KNOW THAT RON AND JULIE WANT
AURORA TO BE THE BACKUP PLAN,
BUT THAT COULD POSSIBLY DAMAGE
THE RELATIONSHIPS I'VE MADE WITH
LAUREN AND VICTORIA.
IT'S A TRICKY SITUATION.
I MEAN, IT'S ALMOST LIKE A
DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD.
>> FOR ME, TONIGHT'S TRIBAL IS
ABOUT FIGURING OUT IF RON IS
REALLY WITH ME.
SO THE PLAN IS TO USE WHAT RON
GAVE ME, WHICH HE SAYS IS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND VOTE
AURORA OUT.
DUN-DUN-DUN-DUH.
REDEMPTION FOR RON OR A VILLAIN
IN OUR MIDST?
TRIBAL WILL TELL.
AND AN IDOL READY TO BE PLAYED.
WHO WILL BENEFIT, AND WHO WILL
GO HOME?
STAY TUNED FOR THE DETAILS.
I'M RICK DEVENS.
AND THAT'S OUR TOP STORY AT VATA
BEACH.
♪
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SO, DEVENS, TODAY AT THE
CHALLENGE, YOU WERE OUT EARLY,
YOU SAT DOWN AND SAID, "IT'S ME
TONIGHT."
DO YOU STILL FEEL THAT WAY?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
NEVER A GOOD SIGN WHEN THERE'S A
SHELTER FULL OF PEOPLE AND ONE
OF THEM IS GOING THROUGH YOUR
BAG.
NOT A GREAT FEELING, JEFF.
>> Jeff: WHO GOT CAUGHT?
>> AURORA, RED HANDED.
>> WOW.
>> DEVENS MADE VERY CLEAR HE WAS
LOOKING FOR AN IDOL.
SO, HE LEFT HIS BAG.
I'M GOING TO GO THROUGH IT.
>> AND I CAN END THE SPECULATION
RIGHT NOW.
BUT I WON'T.
I'M ENJOYING MYSELF.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> JEFF, TO ME IT'S JUST WORDS.
AND WORDS IS NOT VIABLE IN THIS
GAME.
THAT'S WHY EVERYONE HAS MULTIPLE
OPTIONS, BACKUPS, AND BACKUPS
FOR THEIR BACKUP.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, WHAT'S YOUR
TAKE ON THIS?
>> IF ANYONE HAD AN IDOL, IT
WOULD BE DEVENS.
HE'S PLAYED TWO DIFFERENT
ADVANTAGES IN THIS GAME, AND YOU
JUST ALWAYS HAVE TO HAVE A PLAN
"B" AT THE VERY LEAST.
>> Jeff: RON, ARE THERE SO
MANY PLANS IN PLACE THAT IT'S A
LITTLE LIKE SPINNING THE
ROULETTE WHEEL?
>> NO, IT'S NOT THAT RANDOM.
NO LONGER ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT
WHO YOU VOTE FOR TODAY, THEN
WHEN YOU GO BACK TO CAMP, YOU
WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU KNOW WHO
WILL I BE WORKING WITH AND
WHAT'S NIGH NEXT VOTE?
>> Jeff: SO, ARE YOU WORRIED
TONIGHT LEGITIMATELY.
>> I DIDN'T HEAR MY NAME TODAY.
NOBODY SAID IT TO MY FACE.
MAYBE BEHIND MY BACK.
I HOPE I HAVE A HANDLE ON WHAT'S
HAPPENING?
>> Jeff: RON, WALK ME THROUGH
THE LOVED ONE CHALLENGE.
YOU WIN THE CHALLENGE.
YOU CHOOSE GAFFE AND I KNOW
JULIE TO BRING ALONG.
WHAT IT WAS IT LIKE FOR YOU
AFTER THE LOVE WAS OVER, AND YOU
HAVE OTHER PEOPLE BACK AT CAMP
THAT YOU DIDN'T CHOOSE?
>> I WAS HEARTBROKEN FOR
VICTORIA AND LAUREN BECAUSE IT
WAS THEIR DADS, AND THERE'S A
SPECIAL BOND BETWEEN A FATHER
AND A DAUGHTER.
AND TO HAVE THEM NOT GET TO HAVE
MORE TIME TO EXPERIENCE THIS
WITH THEM, IT WAS VERY HARD FOR
ME.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, THAT REWARD
IS VALUED BY EVERYBODY.
BUT ONLY SOME GET IT AND OTHERS
DON'T.
HUE BIG OF AN IMPACT DOES THAT
HAVE IN THIS GAME?
>> I THINK THE PEOPLE THAT HE
CHOSE WERE VERY TELLING.
THE PEOPLE THAT HE LEFT BEHIND
WAS VERY CONTINGENT.
IT TOTALLY HAD AN IMPACT ON THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: GAVIN, IS THERE ANY
PART OF YOU ON THE RECEIVING END
THAT THINKS THIS COULD BE A
DISADVANTAGE TO ME, AND ALL I
DID WAS GET SELECTED.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT COULD BE A
DISADVANTAGE, BUT I WAS THANKFUL
THAT RON CHOSE ME, AND HOPEFULLY
NO ONE HELD THAT AGAINST ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT PEOPLE THINK
IN THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: JULIE, I'M ALWAYS
TRYING TO FIND WHERE THE RHYTHM
IS.
AND THIS SEASON, TO ME, HAS FELT
LIKE A PIN BALL MACHINE WHERE
THE FLIPPERS ARE GOING, THE
BALL'S GOING EVERYWHERE, AND YOU
NEVER KNOW WHEN IT'S GOING TO
COME BACK DOWN OR POP BACK UP.
>> I FEEL LIKE THAT'S A REALLY
GOOD ANALOGY BECAUSE I'VE BEEN
IN MULTIPLE ALLIANCES AT THIS
POINT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'VE ALL BUILT
RELATIONSHIPS WITH EVERY SINGLE
PERSON THAT IS SITTING UP HERE.
AND THINGS COULD STILL PIN BALL
BACK AND FORTH ANY TIME IN THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, THAT IS
HOPEFUL WHEN YOU HEAR JULIE SAY,
"I'VE HAD MULTIPLE ALLIANCES."
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THAT MEANS THERE ARE
RELATIONSHIPS SCATTERED AMONGST
THE SEVEN YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND I'M TRYING TO FIND THE
CRACKS IN THERE, BUT,
APPARENTLY, EVERYONE KNOWS
SOMETHING I DON'T.
PEOPLE ARE NOT HAVING STRATEGIC
TALKS WITH ME.
MAYBE TOMORROW WILL BE
DIFFERENT.
>> Jeff: YOU CAN COMPARE THIS
TO ANYTHING YOU DO BACK HOME?
>> WELL, THIS PART OF THE GAME
BACK HOME, IF I WAS LIVE OUT IN
THE FIELD AND THEY SAID, "WE'RE
GOING TO GO TO RICK DEVENS RIGHT
NOW."
AND I SAID, "I'M RIGHT HERE."
"OKAY, THANKS, RICK.
WE'RE GOOD WITH YOU.
NOW ON TO THE REST OF PROGRAM."
>> I WAS WILLING TO TALK TO
DEVENS.
I HEARD HIM OUT.
IT WASN'T A CLOSED DOOR.
I'M SORRY IF YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
>> NO, YOU HEARD ME, YEAH.
>> I THINK DEVENS HIT THE NAIL
ON THE HEAD WHEN HE SAID THAT
PEOPLE MUST KNOW SOMETHING HE
DOESN'T.
I'M SURE OTHER PEOPLE KNOW
THINGS I DON'T AS WELL.
BUT FOR ME, MAKING IT TO THE
FINAL THREE, I PERSONALLY DON'T
WANT TO SIT NEXT TO DEVENS.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, HARD TO HEAR
THAT?
>> NO.
I MEAN, EVENTUALLY, THEY'RE
GOING TO REALIZE, OH, MY FINAL
THREE DIDN'T PAN OUT.
I WISH I HAD AN EXTRA VOTE RIGHT
NOW.
AND THAT'S AG WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN TO AT LEAST THREE OF
THESE PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: GAVIN, WHAT DEVENS
SAID IS ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
SOME OF ARE YOU WRONG.
>> I MEAN, I AGREE WITH HIM
100%, BUT YOU HAVE TO FEEL
CONFIDENT IN YOURSELF.
I'M SURE THE OTHER SIX OF US
THINK WE HAVE THE RIGHT PLAN.
IT'S A MATTER OF WHO IS TRUSTING
THEIR GUT, AND WHO HAS REALLY
BUILT THE RELATIONSHIPS TO GET
THEM TO THE NEXT STAGE OF THE
GAME.
>> Jeff: OKAY, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
JULIE, YOU'RE UP.
>> IF YOU DON'T GO HOME TONIGHT,
AT LEAST THERE'S BEEN A LINE
DRAWN IN THE SAND.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I THINK SOMEONE WENT THROUGH MY
BAG.
HERE WE GO.
I'D LIKE TO TRY TO ORDER
SOMETHING OFF THIS MENU.
I WANT TO SEE IF I CAN ORDER
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY OR NOT.
>> Jeff: THIS IS AN ADVANTAGE
MENU.
IT HAS A CHOICE OF THREE
ADVANTAGES, OF WHICH YOU CAN
PLAY ONE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS ADVANTAGE
EXPIRED ON DAY NINE AND HAS NO
POWER.
>> RON AND JULIE, YOU ARE
VILLAINS!
I WAS ALREADY GOING HOME.
YOU JUST WANT TO MAKE ME LOOK
STUPID.
SO MY KIDS THINK I'M AN IDIOT?
EXCEPT, YOU'VE PROVEN TIME AND
TIME AGAIN THAT YOU'RE UNTRUST
WORTHY AND DISLOYAL, AND JULIE
HAS PROVEN TIME AND TIME AGAIN
THAT SHE LOVES LYING TO PEOPLE'S
FACES.
>> YES!
>> I WOULD LIKE TO PLAY THIS
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL FOR MYSELF.
YOU GUYS ARE GEMS.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND HOLDS FULL POWER.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR DEVENS WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DEVENS.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DEVENS.
DEVENS, DOES NOT COUNT.
AURORA.
THAT'S ONE VOTE AURORA.
RON.
THAT'S ONE VOTE AURORA, ONE VOTE
THAT'S TWO VOTES RON, ONE VOTE
AURORA.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
>> PEACE, BRO.
>> Jeff: 13th PERSON VOTED
OUT AND THE TENTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY.
RON, YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR
TORCH.
>> THAT WAS MESSED UP, DUDE.
>> Jeff: RON, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> DEVENS, YOU'RE A GREAT
PLAYER.
>> I LOVE YOU, BRO.
>> IT WAS A LOT OF FUN.
>> BYE, RON.
>> SEE YOU, RON.
>> THAT FELT GOOD.
>> HERE WE GO.
Captioning funded by CBS
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR": WHEN ALL YOUR CARDS
ARE ON THE TABLE...
>> DEVENS IS TARGET NUMBER ONE.
>> Jeff: ...YOU'LL NEED TO
FIND HOPE.
>> SPECIAL DELIVERY!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: OR A JOKER COULD RUN
WILD.
>> I FEEL LIKE A KID OR THE
FUGITIVE.
>> I GOT DUPED.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN I'M NOT 100%
CERTAIN WHAT HAPPENED.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT DEVENS.
IF I HAD KNOWN HOW MUCH IT HURTS
TO BE VOTED OUT, I MAY HAVE
HANDLED MYSELF A LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENTLY.
I TOOK MY EYE OFF THE PRIZE.
>> I HEARD A LOT OF LOVELY
THINGS ABOUT YOU.
I REALLY HAVE.
>> I HAVE LIED
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org