Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT THE KAMA TRIBE,
THE RETURNING PLAYERS WERE ON
THE OUTS.
SOMEONE NEEDS TO WIN THIS
GAME.
I DONT WANT THE PLAY WITH
RETURNERS, BECAUSE THEYVE HAD
THEIR CHANCE.
Jeff: AT THE MANU TRIBE,
REEM AND WENDY WERE ISOLATING
THEMSELVES.
THOSE MIGHT BE THE THREE WE
WERE WANTING TO VOTE OUT ANY
WAY.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
REEM DUG HER OWN GRAVE.
MY NAME GOT THROWN OUT TODAY.
IM PISSED OFF.
BUT THAT IS PART OF THIS
GAME.
IM NOT DONE.
WHATEVER.
Jeff: AND WAS FIRST PERSON
VOTED OUT.
Jeff: REEM, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
THANKS.
Jeff: AND THE FIRST PERSON
TO FACE A NEW TWIST.
WHAT?
Jeff: GO HOME OR GRAB THE
TORCH AND GO TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
♪
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE I AM.
AND I STILL DONT KNOW WHATS
GOING ON.
BUT THEY DONT KNOW IM HERE.
LIKE I HOPE TO SHOW MY FACE
AGAIN AND BE LIKE, LOOK WHAT
JUST HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, I WOULD LOVE THAT.
BUT AGAIN, LIKE WHAT DO I HAVE
TO GO THROUGH FOR THIS SECOND
CHANCE?
THIS IS THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
YOU WILL HAVE TO WORK HARD FOR
EVERYTHING.
WHEN FEAR OR LONELINESS SETS IN,
YOU MUST FIND THE RESOLVE TO
OVERCOME.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU WISH TO END
YOUR ADVENTURE, RAISE THE SAIL
AND A BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP.
WHAT?
THERES NO TIME LINE ON THIS?
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IM STRANDED.
NOW I GOT NOTHING BETTER TO DO
BUT ANALYZE WHY I GOT VOTED OFF.
IM SO DISAPPOINTED.
LIKE WHY DIDNT I NOTICE I WAS
SEEMING NAGGY.
I JUST DIDNT WANT THEM TO BE
HURT.
INSTEAD I BLEW MY CHANCE.
I JUST DONT WANT TO EMBARRASS
MY KIDS.
THERE HAS TO BE A GOOD REASON TO
LEAVE THEM.
IM NOT A QUITTER THOUGH, MAN,
YOU KNOW?
IM NOT A QUITTER.
I DO NOT WANT TO DISAPPOINT MY
FAMILY.
THATS WHATS KEEPING ME FROM
RAISING THAT DAMN SAIL.
THIS IS FUNNY.
HOW ARE YOUR HANDS?
OH, MY GOD.
LOOKING LIKE AN OLD LADY.
BY MY PEDICURE STILL LOOKS
GREAT.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
LAST NIGHT?
SEVERAL PEOPLE TRIED TO GET YOU
TO COME OVER, RIGHT?
I UNDERSTAND REEM WAS DEAD IN
THE WATER, BUT I DIDNT WANT TO
SIDE WITH KELLEY.
KELLEY HAS PLAYED TWO TIMES
BEFORE.
WEVE SEEN HER GAME PLAY.
WE KNOW HOW SHE PLAYS.
ITS NOT HER FIRST RODEO, AND IF
YOU GUYS KEEP GOING WITH THE
NUMBERS, THEY WILL CONTROL THE
GAME.
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL, MY STRONGEST
ALLY REEM WAS VOTED OUT.
NOW I FEEL LIKE IM THE NEXT IN
LINE.
I BLAME KELLEY.
SHES THE RINGLEADER.
IT MAKES ME SO ANGRY.
KELLEY HAS PLAYED TWO TIMES
BEFORE THIS.
FOR ME, SHES HAD HER SHOT.
TWO TIMES YOU CANT DO IT, THEN
YOU CANT DO IT.
DONT TRY TO MESS UP FIRST-TIME
PLAYERS GAMES.
SHE HAS THIS PERSONALITY WHERE
SHE TRIES TO BECOME YOUR FRIEND.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE EATING THAT
UP.
NOT I.
I CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH THAT.
LOOK OVER THERE.
SHES ALREADY WORKING HER MAGIC.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS
HAVE THE POWER TO GET HER OUT.
LISTEN, I THINK YOUR CONCERNS
ARE TOTALLY LEGITIMATE.
YEAH.
BUT TO BE HONEST, I DONT
THINK THIS PART OF THE CAMP
RIGHT NOW IS A GOOD TIME FOR
THIS CONVERSATION.
DAVID, THE OTHER
SECOND-CHANCE PLAYER, I THINK
ITS RESONATING IN HIM, BUT
RIGHT NOW HES PLAYING MORE OF A
GO-WITH-THE-FLOW KIND OF GAME.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT I THINK HES WITH ME.
SO IF RICK AND DAVID ARE ON
BOARD WITH IT, THEN I JUST NEED
ONE MORE VOTE.
WE HAVE TO WATCH NOW.
100%.
WE HAVE TO BE REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY CAREFUL.
WE HAVE TO KEEP CLOSE TABS ON
WENDY NOW.
SHELL BE IDOL HUNTING.
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
WENDYS POSITION, BECAUSE IVE
BEEN THERE.
I HAVE BEEN ON THE BOTTOM.
I HAVE BEEN THE TARGET.
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW IT FEELS.
SHES TRYING TO GET SOMETHING
GOING, AND HAVING SOMEONE IN
CAMP WHO IS FREAKING OUT AND
KNOWS THEYRE ON THE BOTTOM IS
VERY DANGEROUS.
I THINK SHES TRYING TO SWAP
AND TAKE US OUT.
LIABILITY.
SHES PROBABLY GOING TO LOOK
FOR AN IDOL.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT GOING OUT
AS A GROUP?
DOESNT MATTER WHO GETS IT.
OH, AN OPEN IDOL HUNT?
YEAH.
WE CANT LET WENDY FIND THE
IDOL.
I MEAN, EVERYONE ELSE WORKED
WITH ME AT THE LAST TRIBAL, AND
IM GETTING THE SENSE THEY WANT
TO CONTINUE TO WORK WITH ME.
BUT ANY TIME YOUR NAME IS THROWN
OUT THERE, ITS LIKE WHAT, IF
BECAUSE SOMETIMES THESE THINGS
CATCH FIRE SOME AT THIS POINT
ITS WENDY ON THIS SIDE AND ME
ON THIS SIDE, AND WERE
BASICALLY GOING TO BATTLE, AND
ONE OF US IS GOING TO WIN THE
WAR.
WE NEED A SONG AND A DANCE.
YOU HAVE CHOREOGRAPHY?
FOR THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE -- COME KAMA, KAMA,
KAMA.
YOU BEND OVER IN FRONT OF ME.
[LAUGHTER]
KAMA.
MORALE I THINK IS A HUGE
REASON WHY WERE DOING WELL IN
THIS GAME RIGHT NOW, WHY WE WON
THE OTHER DAY.
YOU HAVE TO BE IN A POSITIVE
PLACE.
WE NEED TO FEEL BONDED, AND FOR
US, DANCING HAS BECOME OUR
THING.
K-A-M-A, KAMA, KAMA, KAMA.
TO THE FRONT.
ITS PUMP, PUMP, PUMP, AND KAMA.
I HATE KUM BA YAH SURVIVOR,
BUT ITS THE WORST.
I WANT TO BLEND IN WITH EVERYONE
ELSE.
I LIKE GOING TO TRIBAL FIRST
WHEN I PLAY "SURVIVOR," BECAUSE
YOU SEE IMMEDIATELY WHERE THE
LINES ARE.
YOU KNOW HOW TO WORK WITH IT.
WHEN ITS CONSUME "KUMBAYA" AND
IS, I JUST WON FIRST CHALLENGE,
YOU DONT KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON.
I HAVENT REALLY TALKED TO
ANYONE.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS FEELING ABOUT
RETURNING IN GENERAL?
IM GLAD THAT YOU GUYS ARE
HERE.
BUT LIKE MOVING FORWARD, IS
THAT SOMETHING THAT INTERESTS
YOU?
YEAH, YEAH.
EVERYONES GOING TO BE SCARED OF
JOE THE FURTHER ALONG WE GET,
BUT THAT TIME IS NOWHERE NEAR
HERE, AND THINGS CAN CHANGE
BEFORE THEM.
COOL.
IM FINDING IT FRUSTRATING
THAT THESE NEWBIES ARENT BEING
FORTHCOMING ABOUT THEIR
PERCEPTION OF RETURNING PLAYERS.
I KNOW JOE AND I ARE UNDER
MAGNIFYING GLASS.
WERE LIKE THESE ANTS THAT
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT REAL HARD,
AND IM AFRAID THE SUN IS GOING
TO COME AND ZAP US THE HELL OFF
THIS CAMP.
AUBRY IS CLEARLY TRYING TO
MAKE SURE SHES NOT FIRST ONE
OUT FROM OUR TRIBE, BECAUSE
AUBRY APPROACHED ME AND JULIA
AND SAID, SO HOW DO YOU FEEL
TACT RETURNING PLAYERS, WHICH IS
AN ON-THE-SPOT QUESTION TO ASK,
LIKE WHAT CAN I POSSIBLY SAY?
YEAH, WE WANT YOU GUYS GONE.
THEYVE HAD THEIR MOMENT TO
SHINE.
ITS OUR TIME TO HAVE OUR
CHANCE.
AUBRY SAID SOMETHING INTERESTING
TO ME THE OTHER DAY.
SHE GRABBED MY ARM AND SHE SAID,
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
LET ME TELL YOU, SHE SAID THE
EXACT SAME THING TO ME.
SHE SAID THE EXACT SAME THING TO
HER, THE EXACT SAME THING TO
GAVIN.
I HEARD, I JUST WANT TO HAVE
AN OPEN DIALOGUE, THOSE KEY
WORDS.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU THINK, YOU
REMIND ME OF MYSELF.
AUBRY IS GOING TO EVERYONE.
I THINK SHES A LITTLE PANICKED.
I HAVE YOU.
WE COULD START TO HAVE A
DIALOGUE.
I THINK SO.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE CAN HAVE A DIALOGUE,
BECAUSE I FEEL GREAT WITH YOU.
RIGHT.
SHES LIKE, I REALLY LIKE
YOU.
I THINK YOURE A GOOD PLAYER.
YOU REMIND ME OF PATRIOTS.
I THINK YOURE COOL.
SOME OF THE THINGS YOU REMIND
ME, THATS FUNNY.
YOU JUST REMIND ME OF ME A LOT.
I THINK YOU PLAY LIKE I DO.
WE SEE SIMILAR THINGS.
OKAY.
SAME WAVELENGTH.
SHES DOING HER BEST TO PULL
SOMEBODY IN WITH HER.
SHES DOING A GREAT JOB AT HER.
SHE MIGHT HAVE TO GO.
DID YOU CHECK THIS?
NO.
THERE WERE SO MANY LITTLE
CREVICES UP HERE.
GET A STICK.
IT USUALLY WONT BE LIKE THAT
FAR DOWN.
I ALMOST FEEL LIKE KELLEY THE
WE SHOULD ALL LOOK FOR AN IDOL
TOGETHER COULD BE COVER.
BECAUSE SHE ALREADY HAS IT?
LETS GO OVER HERE.
I REALLY LIKE KELLEY.
I FEEL GOOD WORKING ABOUT HER
WITH A BIG GROUP, BUT I DONT
HAVE ANYTHING WITH HER.
WE SHOULDNT SAY ANYTHING TO
WENDY THAT WERE CONCRETE DOING
IT.
BUT ITS POSSIBLE THAT IT IS
NOW, YOU KNOW?
WENDY FEELS LIKE HER BACK IS
AGAINST THE WALL BECAUSE SHE
LOST HER ONLY ALLY, WHICH WAS
REEM.
SHES WORRIED SHE COULD BE NEXT
TO GO.
SO WENDYS PITCH IS THAT WE
SHOULD GET RID OF WENTWORTH.
THE FUNNY THING IS I KNOW THAT
KELLEY WENTWORTH IS NOT GOING TO
LET ME GET TOO DEEP INTO THIS
GAME.
I KNOW SHE WANTS TO CUT ME SOON.
SHES A REALLY SMART PLAYER, AND
SHES GOING TO DO EVERYTHING SHE
CAN TO ELIMINATE THREATS.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
I JUST NEED TO KNOW IF YOU GUYS
ARE WORKING WITH ME OR WITH
THEM?
LISTEN, WE AGREE THAT
KELLEYS A HUGE THREAT.
IM JUST SAYING, LIKE IM A
NUMBER YOU CAN USE, AND WE HAVE
THE SAME END GAME.
WHAT WOULD OUR NUMBERS BE?
YOU, YOU, ME, KEITH AND WAR
DOG.
I WAS LOYAL TO REEM EVEN IF IT
AFFECTED MY GAME.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT IN THIS
GAME, THIS IS NOT ON DEAF EARS.
ORCHESTRATING A BLIND SIDE IS
VERY DELICATE.
YOU HAVE TO BE SO CAREFUL ABOUT
WHO YOU LET KNOW ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, KEITH SEEMS TO BE TIGHT
WITH WENDY, BUT TRYING THE PULL
IN WAR DOG, THAT MAKES ME VERY
NERVOUS, BECAUSE HE DOESNT LIKE
TO TALK TRACT UNTIL ITS
ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, WENDYS
LOYALTY AND TRUST COULD BE WORTH
MORE THAN MONEY IN THIS GAME.
SHE WOULDNT BE A BAD PERSON
OH, NO.
SHES SO LOYAL.
I THINK THATS A GREAT THING TO
HAVE IN OUR POCKET.
I DONT WANT TO SHUT THIS DOWN
AT ALL.
BUT SERIOUSLY, DUDE, I TRUSTED
YOU IN THIS GAME MORE THAN I
TRUST ANYBODY ELSE.
IM WITH YOU.
LIKE I TALK MORE GAME WITH YOU
THAN ANYBODY BY FAR.
OKAY.
COOL.
I FEEL MUCH MORE COMFORTABLE
WITH YOU.
YEAH.
IM IN.
OKAY.
GOOD, MAN, GREAT.
LOVE IT.
MY STRATEGY COMING INTO THIS
GAME IS GET WITH BIG GUYS AND
KIND OF SLIP THROUGH, AND I
THINK DAVID MIGHT BE MY GUY.
WERE TWO PEAS IN A POD.
I THINK WE SEE THE WORLD THE
SAME WAY.
WE SEE THE GAME THE SAME WAY.
IM GOING TO USE MY SENSE OF
HUMOR AND TRY TO GET IN TIGHT
WITH HIM.
I WOULD BE FINE GOING ALL THE
WAY TO THE END WITH YOU.
I SHOULDNT EVEN BE TELLING YOU,
THIS BUT YOU COULD LIKE STRING
ME ALONG AND CUT MY THROAT AT
FOUR OR FIVE, WHATEVER.
IM JUST TELLING YOU --
LETS SHAKE ON THAT ILL CUT
YOUR THROAT AT FOUR.
[LAUGHTER]
IS THAT COOL?
RICKS HYSTERICAL.
I LOVE THE GUY.
HES SO MUCH FUN TO BE AROUND.
RICK IS HONESTLY THE PERSON I
TRUST MOST IN THIS GAME.
ALSO HES VERY SMART AND
STRATEGIC, AND THAT COULD BE
REALLY GREAT FOR MY GAME.
SO IM GOING TO TRY TO KEEP RICK
AROUND FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
THERE IS AN IDOL HERE.
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
I THINK WE CAN BE MORE
AGGRESSIVE LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
WE NEED THE FIND IT.
ADVANTAGES AND IDOLS ARE IN
EVERYONES MIND.
IM THE THE BIGGEST FAN HERE.
IVE BEEN WANTING TO DO THIS FOR
SO DANG LONG.
AS A FAN WATCHING THROUGH THE
TV, IM THINKING HOW IN THE HECK
DO THESE PEOPLE FIND THIS STUFF.
AND ITS THE SAME FOR ME NOW.
ITS JUST SHOOTING IN THE DARK.
YOU TRULY HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
ITS AT.
GEOGRAPHICALLY THE SPACE IS
HUGE.
WE HAVE NO IDEA HOW THE IDOLS
ARE HIDDEN OR IF THERES CLUES
OR MARKINGS.
AND THE JUNGLE IS SO THICK THAT
YOU REALLY HAVE TO SEARCH FOR AN
EXTENDED PERIOD OF TIME.
AND TIME AWAY FROM THE TRIBE IS
SUSPICIOUS.
DO YOU EVEN THINK THERE ARE
IDOLS OUT HERE?
OF COURSE THERE ARE.
RECENTLY I SEE SOME MEN
DISAPPEARING, AND THEYRE GONE
FOR A LONG TIME.
WHETHER THEYRE GOING OFF ALONE
OR THEYRE GOING OFF IN PAIRS,
ITS QUITE OBVIOUS THERES A LOT
OF IDOL SEARCHING GOING ON.
IM SURE THEYRE LOOKING FOR
IDOLS.
EVERYBODY SHOULD BE LOOKING FOR
WHY ARENT I LOOKING FOR IDOLS?
WHY DO THE MEN ALWAYS FIND THE
IDOLS?
OKAY.
WE NEED TO BE BABYSITTING MORE.
NO, WE NEED TO BE LOOKING.
I WISH I KNEW WHAT WAS GOING ON
WITH IDOLS AND ADVANTAGES.
IM SURE PEOPLE HAVE STARTED
LOOKING, BUT I HAVE NO IDEA HOW
YOU WOULD EVEN BEGIN TO START
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, ITS A BIG PLACE, AND
EVERYTHING IS UNIQUE IN ITS OWN
WAY, BUT ALSO EXACTLY THE SAME.
THEYRE ALL TREES THAT LOOK A
LITTLE FUNKY.
WHERE DO YOU BEGIN.
THIS IS WHAT I WAS SAYING
WITH MEN VERSUS WOMEN.
WERE SITTING HERE CHITCHATTING.
WE COULD BE LOOKING FOR AN IDOL
RIGHT NOW.
ITS INTERESTING TO ME THAT
THE WOMEN AND MEN DO FALL INTO
THESE PRECONCEIVED ROLES.
I DONT KNOW IF ITS ABOUT
LIVING THIS PRIMITIVE LIFESTYLE
WHERE THE MEN WERE THE GATHERERS
AND HUNTERS -- NO, THE WOMEN
WERE THE GATHERERS.
I DONT KNOW.
I THINK ITS MY OWN PERSONAL
ISSUE THAT I HAVE TO START TO
FIGURE OUT.
IM NOT A SNEAKY PERSON.
AND IT FEELS SNEAKY TO ME TO
KIND OF SLITHER OFF SEARCHING
FOR IDOLS.
THERES A LOT OF PEOPLE
LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
THE ODDS OF YOU FINDING IT ARE
SLIM, BUT EVER SINCE I WAS A
KID, FINDING AN IDOL WAS KIND OF
ON MY "SURVIVOR" BUCKET LIST,
BECAUSE MY TWO FAVORITE FEMALE
PLAYERS WERE PARVITY AND KELLEY
WENTWORTH.
THEY WERENT JUST GIRLS THAT
RODE COATTAILS.
THEY WERE BAD ASSES, ESPECIALLY
KELLEY WENTWORTH.
KELLEY FOUND TWO IMMUNITY IDOLS
IN HER SEASON.
AN SHE USED THEM BRILLIANTLY.
ALL RIGHT, BABY.
AND SO I ALWAYS WANTED TO
FIND AN IDOL.
AND THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
YOU CAN FIND AN IDOL ANYWHERE.
I SEE A TREE THATS KIND OF
FALLEN OVER.
AND IM THINKING, IF I WAS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL, I WOULD BE HIDING
IN THERE.
I CANT BELIEVE I PULL OUT MY
BEAUTIFUL IMMUNITY IDOL PACKAGE.
"YOU HAVE FOUND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL."
I FEEL ECSTATIC.
OH, MY GOD, I FOUND AN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
FINDING IT ON THE SAME TRIBE AS
ONE OF MY ROLE MODELS MAKES IT
ASTRONOMICALLY MORE EXCITING.
I JUST HAVE TO HIDE IT, BECAUSE
I AM 100% KEEPING IT TO MYSELF.
IM VERY TIGHT WITH KELLEY, BUT
IM DEFINITELY NOT TELLING HER.
IM GLAD I HAVE IT AND SHE
DOESNT.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
KAMA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW MANU TRIBE.
REEM VOTED OUT AT FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
ABSOLUTELY.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
GOT THE TAKE BACK IF IDOL.
NO.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, BOTH
TRIBES WILL SWIM OUT TO A CAGE.
YOU HAVE TO GET UP AND OVER THE
CAGE.
YOULL THEN UNTIE A VERY LONG
AND VERY HEAVY SNAKE.
THEN YOU HAVE TO GET THE SNAKE
OUT OF THE CAGE AND BACK TO
SHORE.
YOULL PLACE IT IN THE CRADLE.
YOULL UNTIE A SERIES OF "NOT
THE NEWSES," RELEASING NUMBERED
TILES.
NOSE TILES WILL HELP YOU SOLVE
THE COMBINATION LOCK.
THAT LOCK WILL RELEASING A
RINGS.
YOULL THEN ATTEMPT TO LAND
THOSE RINGS ON A SERIES OF
TARGETS.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO SPELL
"IMMUNITY" WINS IMMUNITY.
IN ADDITION YOURE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
YES!
Jeff: WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOURE PLAYING FOR?
YES.
Jeff: TODAY YOU HAVE A
CHOICE.
YOU CAN CHOOSE BETWEEN SPICES
PLUS A FEW FIVES AND A CUTTING
BOARD, OR IF YOURE WILLING TO
DO A LITTLE WORK, A DEE --
DELUXE SURVIVOR FISHING KIT,
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO CATCH
FISH IF YOURE WILLING TO PUT IN
THE WORK AND THINK YOU CAN PULL
IT OFF.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
AUBRY, YOUVE DONE THIS
CHALLENGE BEFORE.
YES, I HAVE.
Jeff: HOW DID IT GO?
THAT IS ONE HEAVY SNAKE?
AND THE RESULT?
.
Jeff: LOST.
SEE IF YOU CAN CHANGE THAT STORY
TODAY.
KAMA, ONE EXTRA PERSON.
SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
I AM.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, JULIE,
TAKE A SPOT ON THE SIT-OUT
BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURE RIVERS READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY IN THE WATER.
GOT TO GET TO THAT CAGE AS FAST
AS YOU CAN.
KAMA MOVING THROUGH THE WATER
QUICKLY.
WENDY VERY GOOD IN THE WATER.
MANU MOVING MUCH MORE SLOWLY.
KEITH STRUGGLING IN THE WATER
LIKE HE DID IN THE MAROONING,
AND THATS FORCING TRIBE MATES
TO STAY BACK TO HELP HIM.
KAMA GETTING UP AND OVER.
MANU NOW WORKING UP AND OVER.
EVERYBODY FOR KAMA IS AT THE
CAGE.
MANU STILL WORKING TO GET KEITH
TO THE CAGE.
KEITH, COME ON.
Jeff: YOU CANNOT START
WORKING.
EVERYBODY HAS TO GET OVER.
THERE ARE FOUR SETS OF KNOTS
THAT WILL RELEASE THAT SNAKE.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE SNAKE FREE,
YOU HAVE TO GET IT UP AND OUT OF
THE CAGE.
LETS GO, GUYS.
KEITH, JUMP OVER.
Jeff: KEITH STILL TAKING A
LOT OF TIME TO GET OVER.
NOW YOU CAN START UNTYING.
KAMA HAS THEIR SNAKE FREE.
KAMA NOW TRYING TO GET UP AND
OVER THAT CAGE AND START PULLING
THAT SNAKE.
THAT SNAKE WEIGHS A LOT.
KAMA NOW WITH PLAN.
AURORA IS OVER FIRST.
KEEP GOING.
GET IT UP.
COME ON, GUYS.
Jeff: MANU HAS THEIR SNAKE
FREE.
THEY CAN START WORKING IT OUT OF
THE CAGE.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
Jeff: ERIC LITERALLY
CARRYING THAT SNAKE ON HIS BACK.
KAMA HALFWAY THERE NOW.
WE NEED ONE OF THE BIG GUYS
UP HERE.
Jeff: MANU STILL STUCK IN
THE WATER, ABSOLUTELY NO
PROGRESS MADE WITH THAT SNAKE
YET.
BACK UP!
Jeff: KAMA DOING A NICE
JOB.
THEYVE GOT MOMENTUM.
THE ENTIRE TRIBE IS WORKING
TOGETHER NOW.
HELP ME, KEITH, HELP ME,
KEITH.
Jeff: YOU CAN SEE MANU
STRUGGLING.
JOE LEAVES IT DOWN.
YOURE GOOD!
KAMA NOW HAS THEIR SNAKE FREE.
MANU NOW GETTING SOME MOMENTUM.
SUDDENLY THEY HAVE MORE SNAKE
COMING.
THERES ANOTHER BIG SECTION
COMING OUT.
MANU TRYING TO GET BACK IN THIS
NOW.
IT TAKES ALL EIGHT TRIBE MEMBERS
TO CARRY THAT SNAKE.
IT IS HEAVY.
MANU HAS THREE-QUARTERS OF THEIR
SNAKE OUT.
ONE LAST BIG PUSH WILL DO IT.
YOURE GOOD!
UP AND OVER.
YOU GOT TO GO UNDER.
VERY THE HEAVY SNAKE NOW TO DRAG
THROUGH THE SAND.
MANU HAS STRUGGLED THIS ENTIRE
CHALLENGE FROM THE GET-GO, BUT
MANU IS BACK IN THIS.
LETS GET IT ON THE TABLE.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO GET UP ON
THAT CRADLE.
EVERYTHING ABOUT THIS CHALLENGE
HAS BEEN HARD.
BUT YOU HAVE TO KEEP DIGGING.
NOW YOU CAN START UNTYING.
YOURE LOOKING FOR SIX NUMBERED
DISKS.
MANU STILL FIGHTING.
ONE, TWO, THREE...
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOURE GOOD.
ITS GOING TO BE RON SOLVING THE
COMBINATION LOCK FOR KAMA.
MANU NOW HAS THEIR SNAKE.
YOURE LOOKING FOR SIX DISKS.
GOT TO GET ALL SIX.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: THERE IT IS.
DAVID WHIPPING THROUGH THESE
NUMBERS NOW.
MEANWHILE, RON IS TRYING ONE
COMBINATION AND HES GOT IT.
THREE PEOPLE.
DAVID STILL WORKING ON THAT
COMBINATION LOCK.
PERFECT.
THERE WE GO.
DAVID TRIES ANOTHER COMBO.
HES GOT TO HOOK THESE RINGS IN
ORDER SPELLING "IMMUNITY."
JOE HAS THE FIRST LETTER FOR
KAMA.
THERE IT IS.
DAVID FINALLY INVOLVES IT.
MANU IS BACK IN THIS.
CHRIS TOSSES.
CAN HE TIE IT UP?
AND HE DOES.
WERE TIED 1-1.
CHRIS IS KEEPING MANU IN THIS.
ALL THE PRESSURE NOW ON THE RING
THROWERS.
HERE COMES ERIC.
YES, YES, YES!
Jeff: ERIC HOOKS HIS
SECOND.
CHRIS STILL FIRING FOR MANU.
NO.
HERE COMES JOE TO GET BACK IN.
THROW IT TILL YOU GET IT,
JOE.
JOE LANDS A THIRD RING FOR KAMA.
IT IS 3-1.
YES.
Jeff: CHRIS NOW A SECOND
ONE FOR MANU.
IT IS 3-2.
ITS ALL YOU, BUDDY.
Jeff: CHRIS ON AND OFF.
IM READY FOR YOU.
Jeff: HERE COMES KEITH FOR
MANU.
KEITH STRUGGLED EARLY IN THE
WATER.
HE WOULD LIKE THE MAKE IT UP
RIGHT HERE.
KEITH JUST MISSES.
GOOD JOB, KEITH.
GOOD HUSTLE.
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
Jeff: ERIC NAILS THE FOURTH
FOR KAMA.
IT IS 4-2 NOW.
KEITH TOSSES.
WAY SHORT.
THATS ALL RIGHT.
KEITH.
YES, BUDDY?
IERK HAS A FIFTH FOR KAMA.
KAMA CLOSING IN ON IT NOW.
Jeff: KEITH WOULD LIKE THE
CLOSE THE GAP.
CANT GET IT DONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
Jeff: CHRIS BACK IN.
CHRIS IS THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS
HAD ANY SUCCESS.
CHRIS HITS THE THIRD FOR MANU.
JOE HITS THE SIXTH ONE.
KAMA IS STARTING TO CLOSE IN.
CHRIS HAS GOT TO PICK UP THE
PACE.
CHRIS SNAGS THE FOURTH RING,
KEEPING MANU IN IT.
JOE HOOKS THE SEVENTH RING.
KAMA HAS ONE LEFT.
HERE COMES ERIC TO CLOSE IT OUT.
CHRIS TRYING TO STAY IN IT.
JUST MISSES.
ERIC COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE FOR
KAMA.
AND HE DOES!
KAMA WINS IMMUNITY SENDING MANU
BACK THE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
KAMA, KAMA, KAMA, KAMA.
WHEW!
Jeff: KAMA BACK-TO-BACK
CHALLENGE WINS.
[APPLAUSE]
ONCE AGAIN NOBODY GOING HOME
FROM YOUR TRIBE.
IN ADDITION, YOU HAVE A CHOICE
OF REWARD.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WELL, WERE GOING TO DO THE
FISHING GEAR.
FISHING GEAR WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL BACK AT CAMP.
NICE WORK.
ALL RIGHT, MANU, FOR THE SECOND
TIME THIS SEASON, SOMEBODY FROM
YOUR TRIBE WILL BE VOTED OUT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
LOSING OUR SECOND CHALLENGE
DEFINITELY IS DEFLATING.
IT HURTS.
BUT NOW IM THINKING MAYBE THIS
IS NOT A BITHEIR EQUATION OF
JUST WENTWORTH OR WENDY EVEN
THOUGH THEYRE GOING TO WAR WITH
EACH OTHER.
MAYBE THERES PLAN "C."
KEITH IS A LIABILITY IN
CHALLENGES.
MAYBE A NEW GAME PLAN HAS TO BE
ENACTED.
WELL, WASNT FOR A LACK
OF TRYING.
GOOD JOB.
AMAZING.
YOU GOT FOUR LETTERS ON YOUR
OWN.
NOTHING YOU COULD HAVE DONE.
THATS ALL RIGHT.
SORRY.
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO APOLOGIZE
FOR.
THE CHALLENGE WAS A DISASTER.
MY SWIMMING WAS BAD.
CHRIS HAD TO HELP ME A LOT.
AND THEN THE RINGS TOSS, I JUST
LOOK HOME.
SO IT DID NOT GO AS LANDED.
BEFORE WE LOST 24 CHALLENGE, I
WAS SURE THAT WENDY WAS GOING
HOME, BUT NOW IM THINKING THAT,
YOU KNOW, MY NAME COULD BE ON
THE CHOPPING BLOCK, SO THIS
COULD BE MY LAST DAY HERE
PLAYING SURVIVOR.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AFTER THE CHALLENGE IM THINKING
KEITH IS THE ONE TO GO NOW.
HES A LIABILITY.
AT THIS POINT WERE DOWN TO
NUMBERS.
WE CANT LOSE AGAIN.
WE NEED STRENGTH.
AND KEITH IS NOT STRONG IN
CHALLENGES.
HES KILLING US.
SO ALL THESE THINGS ADD UP.
IM THINKING TO MYSELF, HOW IS
KEITH IN THIS GAME HELPING THE
WARDOG OUT.
THE ANSWER IS HES NOT.
I DONT THINK --
THEYRE COMING UP.
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
WARDOG IS LEADING THE CHARGE TO
VOTE OUT KEITH.
ITS STUPID.
I DONT KNOW WHAT HES THINKING.
YEAH, HES FAILED MISERABLY, BUT
HES NOT A THREAT TO ANYBODY,
WHEREAS WINDY WANTS TO GET ME
OUT.
SO I AM NOT HAPPY.
I THINK ITS GOT TO BE KEITH.
HES A COMPLETE LIABILITY IN
CHALLENGES.
WENDY IS DIVING DOWN.
SHES A GOOD SWIMMER.
SHES AS TOUGH AS ANY OF THOSE
FEMALES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OKAY.
I NEW CONVINCES WARDOG TO
VOTE OUT WENTWORTH WAS GOING TO
BE DIFFICULT, AND SURE ENOUGH,
WARDOG IS VERY ADAMANT THAT
KEITH IS GOING HOME, SO NOW I
DONT THINK THAT I HAVE THE FIVE
VOTES I NEED TO GET RID OF
WENTWORTH.
ITS LIKE, DAMN.
THE THEYRE UP THERE TALKING
ABOUT POSSIBLY GETTING KEITH
OUT, BECAUSE HE WAS A NO SHOW.
UNFORTUNATELY, KEITH KIND OF
SHOT HIMSELF IN THE FOOT, WHICH
KIND OF SUCKS.
BECAUSE HES A GOOD KID.
AND I KNOW THAT THIS GAME MEANS
A LOT TO HIM.
IM SO FREAKIN SORRY, YO.
YOU DID BEYOND FREAKING AMAZING.
I PROMISE YOU I TRIED THE
SWIMMING THING.
I DONT KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
ALL I CAN TELL YOU IS THAT I
PROMISE YOU, LIKE NO MATTER AT
WHAT POINT IN THE GAME WE ARE
NEW YORK IM NEVER TURNING MY
BACK ON YOU, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
HELPED ME WAY TOO MUCH.
LITERALLY NEVER, LIKE I PROMISE
YOU, LIKE EVER, LIKE AT NO POINT
IN THE GAME.
HONESTLY, I DONT WANT KEITH
TO GO, BECAUSE KEITH HAS
SPECIFICALLY TOLD ME, IM IN
WITH YOU UNTIL THE END.
IM GOING TO STAY LOYAL TO YOU
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE.
THATS NOT THE TOP OF PLAYER YOU
VOTE OUT.
REAL QUICK, IS IT BETTER TO
KEEP KEITH AROUND?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WIN OR NOT WIN?
LETS SAY WE TAKE OUT KELLEY.
I THINK ITS SOMETHING
SERIOUS TO THINK ABOUT, BECAUSE
I DONT KNOW HOW MANY
OPPORTUNITIES IN AN UPCOMING
WITHIN WE WOULD HAVE.
EXACTLY.
WERE THINKING THE SAME
THING, MY FRIEND.
HOLY CRAP, WE MIGHT STILL BE
ABLE TO TAKE OUT WENTWORTH, AND
THE BEST PART OF THAT IS CHRIS
ACTUALLY CAME UP WITH THE IDEA.
CHRIS CAME TO ME.
WE BOTH THINK THIS IS THE PRIME
TIME FOR A BLIND SIDE.
THIS IS HUGE.
SO CHRIS CAME UP TO ME AT THE
WATER HOLE AND WAS ASKING ABOUT
IS KEITH THE RIGHT PERSON TO GET
OUT NEXT.
WHAT ABOUT KELLEY?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS GREAT.
YES!
THE ANSWER IS YES.
IF WE COULD GET HIM ON BOARD,
YOU AND I, WENDY.
WERE ON BOARD.
THATS FOUR.
WE ONLY NEED KEITH.
YES, BEST NEWS OF THE DAY.
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
I FEEL LIKE WEVE BEEN HANDED
THIS GIFT.
ITS CHRISTMAS, BECAUSE IM ALL
ABOUT BLIND SIDING WENTWORTH.
I THINK THATS A GREAT IDEA.
THIS TRIBE IS NOT BIG ENOUGH FOR
TWO RETURNING PLAYERS.
SO I WANT TO TAKE HER OUT BEFORE
SHE COMES AFTER ME.
AND AS LONG AS EVERYONE IS ON
BOARD WITH THIS PLAN, ITS
ALMOST GOING TO HAPPEN ON ITS
OWN.
OKAY.
CHRIS HAS APPROACHED US ABOUT
GETTING RID OF KELLEY.
OH, MY GOD.
IM DOWN.
IM COMPLETELY DOWN.
COMPLETELY DOWN.
IM EXCITED.
ITS HARD IN MY POSITION.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED.
THEY HAVE THE NUMBERS TO VOTE
OUT KELLEY.
I HAVE NEW LIFE.
OKAY.
WE NEED TO THINK THROUGH THIS.
YOU AND ME.
BUT THERES BEEN SOME
DISCUSSIONS ABOUT NOW WOULD BE A
REALLY GOOD TIME TO MAKE A MOVE
ON WENTWORTH BECAUSE WENTWORTH
IS ONE OF THOSE PLAYERS, SHES
ONLY GOING TO USE US UNTIL SHE
DOESNT NEED US ANYMORE.
CORRECT.
SHES GOOD ENOUGH TO KNOW
THAT.
BUT HERES THE THING.
ITS LIKE A TRIBE SWAP, WERE
TALKING ABOUT A SCENARIO IN CHE
WE NEED A COUPLE BECAUSE WELL
BE DOWN ON NUMBERS, AND I THINK
WENTWORTH MIGHT BE A BIGGER
TARGET THAN YOU AND ME.
YEAH.
SHE MIGHT BE OUR SHIELD.
THATS OUR THING.
I DONT TRUST WENTWORTH ONE BIT,
BUT I FEEL LIKE WE ALL HAVE A
SIMILAR ALIGNED GOALS RIGHT NOW.
UH-HUH.
CHRIS IS THROWING COLD WATER
ON MY IDEA.
HE WANTS TO TAKE OUT WENTWORTH,
BUT I THINK THATS VERY
SHORT-SIGHTED.
SHES A RETURNING PLAYER.
SHES A THREAT.
SHE PLAYS THE GAME HARD.
SHE FINISHED FOURTH PLACE LAST
TIME.
SHES A GAMER.
BUT THAT MEANS SHE HAS A BIGGER
TARGET ON HER BACK THAN I DO.
THATS A GREAT REASON TO KEEP
HER AROUND.
BRING A GOAT TO THE END AND TAKE
THE SPOT AWAY FROM THEM?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I MEAN, I THINK IF WE COULD
TAKE OUT WENTWORTH FIRST, WE
TAKE OUT KEITH NEXT.
WELL, WE CAN CHANGE IT.
ITS NOT TOO LATE TO GO ANOTHER
DIRECTION.
I WANT THE PLAN TO BE MY PLAN,
BUT I WANT EVERYBODY ELSE TO
FEEL LIKE ITS THEIR PLAN, TOO.
I DONT WANT THEM LOOKING AT ME
LIKE IM TRYING TO CALL THE
SHOTS.
THAT WILL JUST GET ME INTO
TROUBLE.
SO CHRIS AND MYSELF, WE GOT TO
MAKE A DECISION, BUT IF WE ARE
GOING TO TAKE OUT WENTWORTH,
THIS IS THE VOTE.
IM TRUSTING MY LIFE WITH YOU
GUYS TONIGHT.
I KNOW.
PEOPLE ARE ACTING VERY
STRANGE.
ITS MAKING ME NERVOUS.
THERE HAS BEEN A SHIFT.
AND IM LIKE, IF I WERE IN THEIR
SHOE, WHAT WOULD I DO.
THERE IS NO QUESTION, I WOULD
VOTE ME OUT.
ITS NOT LIKE THESE PEOPLE KNOW
EACH OTHERS GAME, BURR THEY DO
KNOW MINE.
I DONT KNOW WHO IS TELLING
THE TRUTH AND WHO IS NOT.
IVE BEEN IN THIS POSITION
BEFORE, AND BOTH TIMES I WAS
BLIND SIDED.
I TRUST LAUREN, BUT NOT THESE
OTHER PEOPLE.
SO MY HEART IS BEATING VERY FAST
RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL LIKE IT IS GOING TO BE
DEEÉJAAÀ VU, AND IF THEY TAKE ME O
BEFORE KEITH, IM GOING TO BE SO
PISSED OFF.
SO LAST TRIBAL, SEEMS PRETTY
CLEAR REEM WAS THE PERSON YOU
WANTED OUT, BUT WENDY, YOU GOT
VOTES, AS WELL.
YES.
Jeff: ARE YOU CONCERNED YOU
MIGHT GET VOTES AGAIN THE UN?
YEAH, I FEEL LIKE THE FIRST
VOTE ESTABLISHES WHERE YOU ARE.
SO CONSIDERING I WASNT WITH
THEM FOR THE FIRST VOTE, MAYBE
ILL GET VOTES FOR THE SECOND
ONE.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, YOU ALSO
RECEIVED A VOTE.
IS IT UNNERVING TO GET A VOTE AT
THE FIRST TRIBAL?
YEAH DID I WANT TO SEE MY
NAME, NO, BECAUSE THAT MEANS
THAT YOUR NAME IS COMING UP.
JEFF, WE ALL KNEW WHO VOTED
FOR WENTWORTH, AND IT WAS REEM,
BUT HER NAME IS STILL OUT THERE
FOR SURE.
I MEAN, SHES --
THANKS, KEVIN.
IM NOT TELLING YOU ANYTHING
YOU DONT KNOW.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, KEVIN
PIPES IN, JUST SO YOU KNOW, YOUR
NAME IS STILL OUT THERE.
BUT AS A RETURNING PLAYER, IS
THAT TO BE EXPECTED.
YEAH, IVE PLAYED BEFORE.
PEOPLE CAN USE THAT AS AN ASSET
OR A NEGATIVE.
Jeff: WHAT IS THE ASSET OF
A RETURNING PLAYER?
I THINK ONE ASSET IS THAT IM
ALWAYS GOING TO BE A SHIELD.
IM ALWAYS GOING TO BE A BIGGER
TARGET THAN MOST OF THESE
PEOPLE, ESPECIALLY IN THE EARLY
GAME WHEN PEOPLE ARE JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHO TO GET RID OF.
I ALSO THINK THAT I AM A STRONG
TRIBE MEMBER AS FAR AS LIKE
WINNING, LIKE WE NEED TO WIN.
WE NEED NUMBERS RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: LAUREN, YOURE
NODDING.
THAT RINGS TRUE TO YOU?
OH, MY GOSH, WE CANT LOSE
AGAIN, EVER AGAIN.
IT SUCKS, ITS WORST FEELING IN
THE WORLD.
I THINK IF WE CAN HAVE A STRONG
TRIBE, THAT WOULD BE THE BEST
MOVE.
Jeff: KEITH, THE TALK SEEMS
TO BE CENTERING AROUND KEEPING
THE TRIBE STRONG.
DOES THAT CONCERN YOU IN BECAUSE
NO MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT,
YOUR CHALLENGE PERFORMANCE WAS A
DISASTER.
THATS TRUE, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME, YOUR LONGEVITY IN THIS
GAME WILL NOT DEPEND ON RING
TOSS.
ONE CLEAR-CUT ROUT KEEPING THE
TRIBE STRONG, YOU COULD STILL BE
GOING TO THE MERGE WITH NUMBERS,
AND YOU HAVE SOMEONE THAT FLIPS.
IT WILL DEPEND ON THE
RELATIONSHIPS YOU WILD.
Jeff: IS IT FAIR TO KEEP
THE TRIBE STRONG AND KEITH DID
NOT GET IT CON AND HE SHOULD GO
HOME, ITS EASY?
IT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
YOURE BALANCING STAYING STRONG
AS A TRIBE, BUT ALSO STAYING
STRONG AS A VOTING UNIT, PEOPLE
YOU CAN TRUST.
THIS IS SUCH A CRUCIAL PART OF
THE GAME STRATEGICALLY.
AND TODAY IT WAS EVEN MORE
CRYSTAL CLEAR, LIKE, ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT TO FIGURE SOME THINGS
OUT.
Jeff: KEVIN, TWO BIG IDEAS
CHRIS JUST SHARED, DONT WANT TO
LOSE AGAIN, WHICH IS CHALLENGE
PERFORMANCE.
AND TRUST.
LOYALTY.
A GOOD POINT.
AND I THINK LAST TRIBAL LOYALTY,
PERFORMANCE, THEN YOU LOSE
AGAIN, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
PERFORMANCE IS LOOKING PRETTY
IMPORTANT.
MAYBE A LITTLE STRENGTH CAN GO A
LONG WAY.
IS WARDOG, IS THERE A LOT OF
TALKING AT CAMP?
ARE WE SELF-NOW?
IS THAT GAME ON, BLIND SIDES
WILL BE COMING?
I THINK THERE IS A LOT OF
TALKING GOING ON.
THERES A LOT OF DIFFERENT IDEAS
FLOATING AROUND.
AND ITS POSSIBLE SOMEBODY DOES
GET BLIND SIDED TONIGHT.
Jeff: SO WHERE IS YOUR
GAUGE ON HOW WELL YOU THINK YOU
CAN READ THESE OTHER PEOPLE?
I WILL KNOW TONIGHT IF MY
GAUGE IS STRONG OR NOT.
THOSE VOTES GET READ, ILL KNOW
WHERE I STAND ON THIS TRIBE.
Jeff: DAVID, WHATS YOUR
TAKE?
DO YOU THINK TONIGHTS VOTE WILL
BE A BLIND SIDE?
I REALLY BELIEVE TONIGHT WILL
ABSOLUTELY BE A BLIND SIDE.
I FEEL LIKE I COULD WRITE DOWN
HOW EVERYONE IS GOING TO VOTE,
AND IF IT DOESNT GO THAT WAY, I
THINK THE BLIND SIDE WILL BE ON
ME.
Jeff: KEITH, DO YOU THINK
ITS GOING TO BE A BLOIND SIDE?
I THINK EVERYBODY HAS WORKED
THE GAME TO THEIR ADVANTAGE TO
MAKE SURE THEYRE NOT THE ONES
GOING HOME, SO I THINK EVERYONE
THINKS THEYRE NOT GOING HOME,
SO, YES, I DO THINK THERE IS
GOING TO BE A BLIND SIDE.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, YOU CANT
PUT IT ANY BETTER THAN, THAT
EVERYBODY HAS TALKED TO
EVERYBODY AND IS CERTAIN THEYRE
RIGHT, WHICH MEANS IT CAN ONLY
BE ANOTHER BLIND SIDE.
YEAH, YOU HAVE THE
CONVERSATIONS YOU HAVE AND YOU
HOPE THE VOTE STICKS.
SOME PEOPLE HERE DIDNT WORK OUT
FOR THEM THIS TIME.
WHO DOESNT WANT TO CHECK
BLIND SIDE OFF THEIR LIST.
NOTCH THE TREE, DRINK FROM THE
WELL, BLIND SIDE.
I THINK YOURE FINE.
I GOT PAT ON THE SHOULDER.
Jeff: WARDOG, WHAT GAVIN
SAID IS JUST BEING HONEST.
I THINK EVERY MOVE YOU MAKE
SURE A RATIONAL DECISION.
WE WANT OUR CAKE AND WE WANT TO
EAT IT TO.
UNLESS IM DEALING WITH THE
SEVEN BEST LIARS IN THE WORLD,
WITH THE CHOICE TODAY, WE CAN
MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DAVID, YOURE UP.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KELLEY.
KEITH.
WENDY.
THATS ONE VOTE WENTWORTH, ONE
VOTE KEITH, ONE VOTE WENDY.
KEITH.
THATS TWO VOTES KEITH.
FOR REAL?
Jeff: THATS THREE VOTES
KEITH, ONE VOTE WENTWORTH, ONE
VOTE WENDY.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION,"
KEITH.
THATS FOUR, THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
WOW, WOW, WOW.
YALL THINK YOURE STILL GOING
TO WIN CHALLENGES?
Jeff: KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
GOD.
DANG, DANG, DANG.
DANG IT.
DANG.
YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE.
IF YOU WANT A CHANCE TO GET BACK
IN THE GAME, TAKE THE TORCH AND
GET IN THE BOAT.
IF YOU DO NOT WANT THE PLAY
ANYMORE, FOLLOW THIS PATH AND
YOUR ADVENTURE WILL END.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON.
OH, GOD.
COME ON, GOD.
OH, MY GOD, COME ON, GOD.
COME ON.
COME ON, GOD, COME ON.
COME ON, GOD.
COME ON, JESUS.
Captioning funded by CBS
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
SURVIVOR... WHEN THE CATS OUT
OF THE BAG...
NOBODY WANTS TO TALK US TO.
Jeff: YOULL NEED A PACK
MENTALITY.
KILL OR BE KILLED.
Jeff: OR CATCH A BREAK.
IM WORRIED BECAUSE IVE
NEVER BROKEN ANYTHING.
I DONT KNOW.
I AM LIKE SO DOWN IN THE
DUMPS.
IVE BEEN HERE FOR THREE
FREAKIN DAYS.
AND IVE EATEN MAYBE A BITE OR
TWO OF COCONUT.
I DONT KNOW, MAN.
IF NO ONE SHOWS UP, I MAZE HAVE
THE RAISE THAT FLAG.
♪