Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR":
AT THE KARMA TRIBE ALL EYES WERE
ON THE RETURNING PLAYERS.
THEYVE HAD THEIR MOMENT TO
SHINE.
ITS OUR CHANCE.
JOE AND I ARE UNDER A
MAGNIFYING GLASS.
Jeff: ANOTHER RETURNING
PLAYER WAS BEING TARGETED.
IM ALL ABOUT BLINDSIDING
WENTWORTH.
I THINK THATS A GREAT IDEA.
Jeff: AND CHRIS WANTED TO
BRING IN WAR DOG.
NOW WOULD BE A REALLY GOOD
TIME TO MAKE A MOVE ON
WENTWORTH.
Jeff: BUT WAR DOG HAD HIS
OWN AGENDA.
ITS GOT TO BE KEITH.
HOW IS KEITH IN THE GAME
HELPING THE WAR DOG OUT?
AND THE ANSWER IS, HE IS NOT.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
KEITH WAS VOTED OUT.
KEITH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
GOD!
Jeff: AND HAD A DECISION TO
MAKE.
MY GOD.
Jeff: GO HOME OR GRAB THE
TORCH AND GO TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
COME ON, GOD.
COME ON.
Captioning funded by CBS
KEITH!
THEY SENT YOU AWAY!
REEM!
AAAAH!
OH, MAN!
IM SO SORRY.
NO, DUDE.
IM SORRY.
DONT BE SORRY.
THIS IS INSANE.
THIS IS ACTUALLY INSANE.
IM SCARED OUT OF MY MIND.
ITS DARK.
ITS FREAKING DARK.
YOU LITERALLY CANNOT SEE IN
FRONT OF YOU.
KEITH, ITS ROUGH OUT HERE.
IM GOING TO TELL YOU STRAIGHT
UP.
ITS REALLY ROUGH OUT HERE.
I HAVENT EATEN IN DAYS, MAN.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YES.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO GET
SLEEP TONIGHT.
( LAUGHS ).
ITS AN EMOTIONAL ROLLER
COASTER OUT HERE.
AND KNOWING ALL OF THAT, I FEEL
NOW RESPONSIBLE FOR KEITH.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO GET SOME
FOOD.
THERE IS NO FOOD HERE.
YOU GOTTA GET IT YOURSELF.
I WAS READY TO RAISE THAT MAST,
BUT NOW, IM IN THAT "MOTHERLY"
ROLE AND I HATE TO LEAVE HIM
ALONE.
I HAVE TO STAY TO MAKE SURE HES
OKAY.
THERES SOMETHING.
ING THIS UP.
OH, THERES NEW THINGS.
OH, MY GOD!
"KEITH" AND "REEM."
THIS FREAKING GAME, BRO.
WOW!
ITS A MAP.
MAST.
WRECK.
STEPS?
IT SAYS THAT THERES THESE
STAIRS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE THEY ARE,
WHICH IS INTERESTING BECAUSE
IVE KIND OF SCOURED THIS BEACH,
I THOUGHT.
BUT I DIDNT SEE ANYTHING.
I MEAN, GRANTED, THIS ISLAND IS
HUGE.
ITS EXHAUSTING.
OH!
DO YOU SEE ANYTHING?
NO.
THERES NO STEP PATHS.
OH, MY GOD!
I DONT KNOW HOW FAR I NEED
TO GO OR IF IM JUST WANDERING
ENDLESSLY.
ITS DIFFICULT BECAUSE THIS
ISLAND IS HUGE.
BUT THEN, I SEE THE STEPS.
WERE AT THE STEPS.
ARE WE?
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
PROBLIM TIRED.
SOMETHINGS IN THERE.
ITS RICE!
THANK GOD!
YAY!
HALA-FREAKING-LULA.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS HARDLY ANY RICE.
DAMN IT!
THAT FREAKING NOTE SAYS, "YOU
HAVE TO WORK HARD FOR EVERYTH
EVERYTHING."
WE HAVE TO DO THIS EVERY DAY.
APPARENTLY, EVERY TIME WEVE GOT
TO CLIMB UP MOUNT EVEREST TO
FIND A LITTLE BIT OF RICE.
THIS SUCKS!
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
KAMA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW MANU TRIBE.
KEITH VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT, FOR TODAYS
CHALLENGE, YOURE GOING TO RACE
TO ASSEMBLE A WHEELBARROW.
YOULL PUSH IS THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES COLLECTING
SANDBAGS.
YOULL THEN DUMP THE SANDBAGS
INTO A TROUGH, TAKE THE
WHEELBARROW APART, AND USE THE
PIECES TO BUILD A SLICKSHOT.
YOULL USE THE SLINGSHOT TO FIRE
SANDBACKS AT TARGETS.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO KNOCK DOWN
ALL FOUR TARGETS WINS REWARD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE
PLAYING FOR?
YES!
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN YOU HAVE A
CHOICE.
YOU CAN CHOOSE BETWEEN:
COMFORT.
OR...
( CLUCKING ).
Jeff: YOU GOT IT.
CHICKENS.
WOW!
I LOVE CHICKENS.
Jeff: THREE HENS, ONE
ROOSTER.
BIG CHOICE.
CAM AYKAMA, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA P
SITTING TWO OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
EVERYBODY ELSE GETS A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ITS GOING TO BE FUN.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
( APPLAUSE )
Jeff: THE FIRST THING YOU
HAVE TO DO IS ASSEMBLE THE
WHEELBARROW.
THATS GOING TO TAKE TEAM WORK,
GOOD COMMUNICATION.
MANU QUICKLY WORKING TOGETHER TO
GET THE WHEEL AND THE AXLE IN.
KAMA NOW HAS THEIR WHEEL IN.
DAVID GUIDING THEM.
KEEP GOING!
LETS GO!
Jeff: ITS MANU OUT OF THE
GATE FIRST.
THE TRIB WHO HAS YET TO WIN A
CHALLENGE THIS SEASON.
THIS THING IS HEAVY.
Reporter: KAMA NOW RIGHT ON
THEIR TAIL.
IT IS ERIK, JULIE, AND JOE FOR
KAMA.
IT IS DAVID, DEVON, AND WAR DOG
FOR MANU.
GET OUT OF HERE!
BACK UP, GUYS!
GUYS!
Jeff: YOUVE GOT TO GET IN
THERE!
THERE YOU GO!
NOW YOURE GOOD!
NOW YOURE UNTYING KNOTS TRYING
TO RELEASE THAT FIRST BATCH OF
SANDBAGS.
KAMA UNTIED THEIR KNOTS A LOT
FASTER.
KAMA IS NOW IN THE LEAD.
MANU NOW HAS THEIR SANDBAGS.
THEYRE TRYING GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU GOT IT?
Jeff: ERIK, JULIE, AND JOE
DOING A NICE JOB OF MANEUVERING
THEIR WHEELBARROW.
IT IS HEAVY.
IT IS AWKWARD.
NOTHING ABOUT IT IS EASY.
KAMA NOW WHEELING INTO THAT
SECOND BATCH OF SANDBAGS.
YOURE GOOD.
DEVON, DAVID, AND WAR DOG DOING
EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO GET BAG
BACK.
YOURE GOOD!
KAMA HAS THEIR SECOND BATCH OF
SANDBAGS.
GET IN!
Jeff:YOU HAVE TO GET THEM
ALL IN THAT TRUCK.
YOU CANT HELP.
MANU HAS THEIR SECOND BATCH OF
SANDBAGS.
YOURE GOOD, KAMA!
THE CHALLENGE NOW TURNS OVER TO
THE NEXT FOUR-- AURORA, GAVIN,
JULIA, AND VICTORIA.
TURN IT THIS WAY.
Jeff: THEY HAVE TO TAKE IT
APART AND BUILD A SLINGSHOT.
MANU HAS TO TOSS BY HAND, TAKING
MORE TIME.
YOUVE GOT TO GET THEM ALL IN
THERE.
MANU CONTINUES TO STRUGGLE AT
EVERY STAGE OF EVERY CHALLENGE.
YOURE GETGOOD!
GET OUT OF THERE, GUYS.
IT IS NOW A RACE TO DISASSEMBLE
THE WHEELBARROW AND BUILD A
SLINGSHOT.
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: KAMA STRUGGLING TO
GET IT IN.
SOMETHING IS NOT LINING UP.
AND HERE COMES MANU NOW.
YOU WILL KNOW WHEN ITS IN.
IT WILL SEAT VERY NICELY.
MANUS GOES RIGHT IN.
YOURE GOOD!
IT IS NOW MANU IN THE LEAD.
KAMA STRUGGLING IT GET THIS
SLINGSHOT TO LINE UP.
NOW THEYRE GOOD.
ONCE AGAIN, CHRIS IS IN THE HERO
ROLE.
CAN HE GET IT DONE THIS TIME?
AND HE DOES.
MANU HAS THEIR FIRST.
ITS GOING TO BE GAVIN FOR KAMA
AND CHRIS FOR MANU.
THERE ARE FOUR TARGETS.
YOUVE GOT TO KNOCK DOWN ALL
FOUR.
GAVIN JUST MISSES.
CHRIS HITS THE SECOND TARGET FOR
MANU!
MANU HAS HALF THEIR TARGETS
DOWN, ONLY TWO LIFT.
GAVIN GOING TO STEP OUT.
HERE COMES JULIA TO GIVE IT A
GO.
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
JULIA KNOCKS THE FIRST TARGET
DOWN FOR KAMA.
SHES GOING TO GO AGAIN.
IT IS 2-1.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: CHRIS BACK.
AND HES GOT THE THIRD TARGET.
ONE TARGET LEFT.
ONE MORE!
Jeff: JULIE JUST MISSES ON
THE SECOND.
CHRIS COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
LOVE IT, CHRIS, LOVE IT.
CHRIS, DONT MIS.
Jeff: AND HE DOES!
MANU WINS REWARD, THEIR FIRST
CHALLENGE OF THE SEASON!
GOOD JOB, EVERYBODY.
WE NEEDED THAT WIN.
Jeff: MANU, FIRST WIN OF
THE SEASON.
ITS A BIG ONE.
WHATS IT GOING TO BE, COMFORT
OR CHICKENS?
CHICKEN.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, MANU,
CHICKENS WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, AND ENJOY YOUR BEST
VICTORY.
CAM AI GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
THANKS, JEFF.
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY.
ITS OUR FIRST WIN.
BUT SUDDENLY, MY ANKLE STARTED
THROBBING WHEN I WAS LEAVING THE
CHALLENGE, AND I LOOKED DOWN AND
IT WAS REALLY TENDER, AND IT
STARTED LOOKING SWOLLEN, AND NOW
I CANT EVEN MOVE IT.
IT KEEPS GETTING WORSE.
♪ ♪
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
I DONT CARE.
JUST DROP ME WHEREVER.
IN THE SECOND PART OF THE
CHALLENGE WE HAD TO DISASSEMBLE
THE WHEELBARROW AND I LIFTED UP
A PIN AND IT FELL ON MY ANKLE.
I WAS SO FOCUSED ON THE
CHALLENGE I THOUGHT ILL WORRY
ABOUT IT LATER.
IT HURT AND I JUST PULLED MY
FOOT OUT, AND I GOT THE WHEEL
OUT, AND WE RAN TO FINISH.
AND I DIDNT NOTICE.
IT WAS HURTING BUT NOT THIS BAD.
AS IM WALKING TO CAMP, I GUESS
I CALMED DOWN OR SOMETHING, AND
IT JUST STARTED THROBBING AND
PROGRESSIVELY GOT WORSE AND
WORSE.
AND IM JUST, LIKE, WORRIED
BECAUSE IVE NEVER BROKEN
ANYTHING.
I DONT KNOW.
LIKE, I JUST EYE JUST DONT WANT
THIS TO BE SERIOUS.
SERIOUSLY, IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING, CALL US.
WELL GRAB IT FOR YOU.
OKAY?
LETS GIVE HER SOME SPACE.
I WOULD LIKE TO LOOK AT OUR
BEAUTIFUL CHICKENS.
OH, MY GOD!
NO, HES GOING TO BE DEAD.
THE CHICKENS, WE CAN EAT THE
CHICKENS BEFORE OUR MOST
IMPORTANT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
IM SO PUMPED.
ROTISSERIE CHICKEN SOUNDS
AMAZING, DOESNT IT?
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS SIT HERE
IN PAIN AND LISTEN TO WHAT
THEYRE GOING TO DO TO THESE
CHICKENS AND ITS SO UPSETTING.
IM JUST LIKE, POOR CHICKENS.
WHAT DID THEY DO TO THE PLAYERS?
LIKE, THE PLAYERS SIGNED UP FOR
THE GAME NOT THE CHICKENS.
SO WHY SHOULD THEY BE PENALIZED.
IT TAKES A COUPLE OF HOURS TO
KILL IT, PLUCK IT.
WHO IS KILLING THE CHICKEN?
OH, GOD.
THERES NO WAY IM KILLING
ANYTHING.
IF THEYRE GOING TO LAY EGGS,
THATS AWESOME, THATS WHY WE
SHOULDNT KILL THEM ALL.
COMING INTO THIS GAME, I
ALWAYS SAID, IF MY TRIBE WERE TO
WIN CHICKENS, I WOULD RELEASE
THE CHICKENS.
BUT HOW-- HOW WOULD I BE ABLE TO
DO IT WITH THIS BUSTED ANKLE.
I THINK THEYRE GOING TO GET
AT LEAST ONE.
NOT TODAY.
DID THE CHICKENS DO?
YOU EAT CHICKEN BACK HOME,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
WERE BLEEDING HEART HYPOCRITES.
THESE CHICKENS DONT DESERVE
TO DIE.
IM WITH YOU.
CONVINCE THEM NOT TO KILL THE
CHICKENS THEN TO PROVE IT.
IM NOT I SETTING THE CHICKEN
FREE.
I WOULDNT TELL ON YOU.
BUT I THINK IT WOULD COME BACK
TO HAUNT YOU.
I NEED AN ACCOMPLICE.
--I-- I COUNT MY OUT.
COUNT ME OUT.
IT WAS PROBABLY THE MOST
SURPRISING PART OF MY GAME SO
FAR WHEN WENDY ASKED ME TO BE AN
ACCOMPLICE IN A JAIL BREAK.
SHE WANTS TO SET CHICKENS FREE.
SHES LITERALLY WILLING TO
SACRIFICE HER ENTIRE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" TO SAVE THESE
CHICKENS.
I DONT THINK IVE EVER MET
ANYONE LIKE WEND PEP SHES A
LOVABLE, EMOTIONAL NUT.
WE LOST THE REWARD CHALLENGE
TODAY, WHICH KIND OF SUCKS.
BUT WE HAVENT LOST AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE YET.
WE HAVENT HAD TO GO TO TRIBAL
YET.
AND THATS WAY MORE IMPORTANT.
YOU WERE SO GREAT.
THEY GOT LUCKY.
WHATEVER.
WERE ALL STILL HERE.
THATS ALL THAT MATTERS.
LETS REST TONIGHT AND LETS
CRUSH THEM TOMORROW.
I HAVE FOUND MYSELF IN A
GROUP OF SIX-- ME, JULIE, JULIA,
GAVIN, RON, AND ERIK.
WHICH MAKES A LOT OF SENSE
BECAUSE THERES A GENERAL
FEELING ON THE TRIBE THAT
RETURNING PLAYERS HAVE PLAYED
BEFORE.
THEYVE HAD THEIR SHOT.
THIS IS OUR FIRST CHANCE, AND WE
SHOULD GET TO PLAY BEFORE THEY
DO.
JOE AND AUBRY ARE A TARGET, AND
AURORA IS THE ONLY ONE WHO SEEMS
1,000% ON BOARD WITH THE
RETURNING PLAYERS.
SO IF WE WERE TO LOSE THE NEXT
IMMUNITY AND WE HAD TO GO TO
TRIBAL I THINK ONE OF THEMS GOT
TO GO.
HOARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
EVERYTHING?
ABOUT?
IF WE LOSE A CHALLENGE?
I FEEL LIKE IF WE LOSE, WEVE
GOT SIX OF US.
ITS A MATTER OF DECIDING WHICH
ONE OF THE THREE YOU WANT TO
VOTE OUT.
IN JOE AND AUBRY KIND OF COME
AS A PAIR.
THEY DO.
WHAT DO WE DO?
YOU AND AUBRY ARE A PAIR?
I MEAN, WE ARE KIND OF ON THE
BOTTOM OF THE BARREL.
I DONT THINK THERE IS A
BARREL.
I MEAN OVERALL LIKE, YOU
KNOW, WHAT I MEAN.
OF ALL THE PEOPLE PLAYING IN THE
GAME.
OH, MY GOD.
JOE IS OVER THERE, AND I HAD NO
IDEA!
YOU GUYS FEEL GOOD?
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY, WE CAN TELL
THAT YOU GUYS ARE ALL KIND OF
TALKING AMONGST YOURSELVES AND
TRYING TO FIGURE IT OUT, AND ME
AND HER, WERE GETTING NERVOUS.
I FEEL LIKE I JUST CANT GET A
READ ON VICTORIA AND RON BECAUSE
YOU ASK THEM KIND OF WHAT
THEYRE THINKING, AND THEY ONLY
GIVE YOU NOTHING.
SO I HAVE A FUNNY FEELING THAT I
MIGHT BE ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
SO DO YOU GUYS FEEL GOOD?
YUP.
OKAY.
I MEAN, ITS VERY CLEAR.
YEAH, I GOT SUPER WEIRD
VIBES?
SAME.
OKAY.
I THINK JOE IS LOOKING FOR
REDEMPTION, JUST LIKE I AM, AND
WE ARE SCARED COMING INTO THIS
NEW GROUP OF PLAYERS.
I GUESS THIS IS THE POINT IN
THE GAME NOW WHERE--
AT LEAST WERE SEEING WHAT
PEOPLES TRUE COLORS ARE.
I THINK RETURNEES ARE AN EASY
TARGET.
SO I FEEL LIKE I DO NEED THE
IDOL.
IM LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
IM LOOKING HIGH, LOW, IN TREES.
I DIG UP AROUND TREE MAIL,
DIGGING ON THE SIDE OF THE PATH.
LOOKING IN TREES.
I MEAN, ITS SOMETHING IVE
DREAMED ABOUT MY ENTIRE
"SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE.
I FEEL LIKE ITS IN HERE.
IVE DONE NEARLY EVERYTHING IN
"SURVIVOR," EXCEPT WIN AND GET A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND I KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO
WIN, AND IM HERE TO WIN.
BUT FIRST I NEED TO CHECK ONE
MORE THING OFF MY "SURVIVOR"
CHECKLIST.
I WANT EVERY EXPERIENCE ON
"SURVIVOR," AND THATS ONE I
HAVENT HAD.
SO I KEEP LOOKING.
THERES SOMETHING HERE.
ANYTHING I CAN SEE TO FIND THE
IDOL.
( CRYING )
CAN THE CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU HAVE FOUND THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL."
I FIND THE IDOL, AND I BREAK
DOWN IN TEARS.
I NEVER-- I NEVER THOUGHT ID
FIND ONE.
AND IVE BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH IN
"SURVIVOR," AND THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT I HAVENT GOTTEN
YET.
IM SO PROUD OF MYSELF.
ITS WORTH THE EFFORT TO WORK
THROUGH THE STRUGGLE.
AND I LOVE THIS GAME SO MUCH.
IM GOING TO MAKE IT WORK FOR
ME.
♪ ♪
( CLUCKING ).
ALL CREATURES SCERVE TO LIVE.
DO YOU EAT MEAT AT ALL?
IF YOU WERE TO KILL THE
ANIMAL, I WOULDNT.
YOU CAN EAT IT FROM THE STORE
BUT YOU WOULDNT IF SOMEBODY
ELSE DID IT.
THEYRE DEAD ALREADY, BUT
THEYRE ACTUALLY TREATED WORSE.
WE NEED TO TRY TO WIN THIS
GAME, AND TO WIN THIS GAME WE
NEED STRENGTH.
WENDY IS LOSING HER MIND.
BACK HOME SHE EATS CHICKEN AND
PORK AND MEAT AND ALL THAT.
SHES LIKE, "I KNOW IM
HYPOCRITAL."
I SAID, "ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
YOURE HIP KITTAL."
BUT WERE NOT.
IF YOU CAN SO HELP TYOU CAN BE A
VEGETARIAN.
YOURE GOING TO BE A VEGETARIAN?
YES.
ALL RIGHT.
EVEN WHEN SHES ON THE LOSING
SIDE OF AN ARGUMENT, SHES SO
STUBBORN TO THE POINT SHE SAID
SHES GOING TO BE A VEGETARIAN.
WENDY, MARK MY WORDS, THE MINUTE
I FIND OUT YOU HAVE ONE PIECE OF
MEAT IN YOUR BELLY JUST DONT
TALK TO ME AGAIN.
SHES LOST HER ROCKER.
YOU WANT TO KILL IT, FINE.
WHATEVER.
ILL KILL IT.
BUT DO NOT SIT ON YOUR HIGH
HORSE AND TELL ME THAT WE CANT
EAT THAT CHICKEN.
DOESNT SHE EAT CHICKEN BACK
HOME?
CHICKEN YOU EAT AT HOME COMES
FROM A WORSE PLACE THAN HERE
ITS RIDICULOUS.
IF THIS TRIBE LOSES AGAIN, I
WOULD WANT TO TARGET WENDY
BECAUSE WENDY DOES NOT WANT TO
KILL THE CHICKENS.
SHE HAD TO BE CARRIED INTO CAMP
BECAUSE HER ANKLE IS SO BAD, AND
ON TOP OF THAT, I SAW ONE VOTE
AT TRIBAL FOR ME, AND THAT WAS
FROM WENDY.
THERE IS ONE THING I WANTED TO
TELL YOU GUYS.
AT SOME POINT, PEOPLE-- SOMETIME
ITS BETTER TO STICK TOGETHER.
I DONT KNOW.
WEVE GOT FOUR RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT?
I MEAN, IF YOURE COMING
AFTER ME, I HAVE TO GET YOU
BEFORE YOU GET ME.
ITS KILL OR BE KILLED.
IF YOU COME AFTER ME, LIKE, I
MEAN, WATCH OUT.
♪ ♪
Jeff: OKAY, YOU GUYS READY
TO GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE?
YES!
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JULIE, GOT TO TAKE BACK THE
IDOL.
OH!
WE NOTICED.
WATCH OUT.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, THREE
TRIBE MEMBERS WILL BE IN A BOAT.
THE OTHER FOUR TRIBE MEMBERS
WILL BE TETHERED TO THE BOAT.
ON MY "GO," THOSE FOUR WILL DIVE
IN, BEGIN SWIMMING AND PUT BOAT
TO A TALL TOWER.
WOWNS REACH THE TOWER, THE TRIBE
MEMBERS IN THE BOAT, WILL CLIMB
UP, LEAP OFF, AND GRAB A KEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THREE KEYS,
YOULL USE THEM TO UNLOCK A
CHEST.
INSIDE THE CHESS, PUZZLE PIECE.
USE THE PUZZLE PIECES TO SOLVE A
CHIPS WHEEL.
FIRST TRIBE TO SPIN THEIR WHEEL,
RAISE THEIR FLAG, WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE THIRD
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
KAMA, YOU HAVE TWO EXTRA
PLAYERS.
YOURE GOING TO SIT TWO OUT.
VICTORIA, JULIA WILL SIT OUT.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BRAND-NEW "SURVIVOR" CHALLENGE.
FOUR MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE WILL
SWIM LITERALLY PULLING THEIR
OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS IN A BOAT.
YOU ARE TRYING TO GET THEM TO
THAT TOWER.
COME ON, GUYS!
LETS GO!
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
Jeff: OUT OF THE GATE, WE
ARE DEAD EVEN.
YOURE DOING GREAT!
Jeff: THAT IS WHAT YOU CALL
TEAM WORK RIGHT THERE.
WENDY, EVEN WITH A BAD ANKLE,
VERY GOOD IN THE WATER.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK RIGHT NOW.
YOUVE GOT TO GET TO THE RING.
THAT WILL LINE UP THE BOAT.
GO, GO, GO!
GO!
WAIT, WAIT!
Jeff: ITS GOING TO BE
DAVID HEADING UP.
KAMA IS THERE.
THERE GOES GAVIN.
GAVIN HAS THE KEY FOR KAMA.
HES GOT TO GET BACK.
DAVID HAS THE KEY FOR MANU.
YOURE GOOD!
GO, WENTWORTH!
GOTTA GET IN THE BOAT.
Jeff: YOURE GOOD, GO,
JULIA.
WENTWORTH NOW OUT ON THE BEAM
LOOKING FOR THAT SECOND KEY.
KELLEY HAS HERS.
JULIA HAS IT.
SHES IN THE WATER.
GO, LAUREN!
GO, GO!
Jeff: MANU IN THE LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
LAUREN HAS THE THIRD KEY.
GAUBRY!
AUBRY HEADING FOR HER THIRD AND
FINAL KEY.
START SWIMMING IN.
AUBRY WITH THE THIRD KEY FOR
KAMA.
SHES GOT TO GET BACK TO THE
BOAT.
YOURE GOOD!
GO!
KAMA TRYING TO GET BACK IN THIS.
YOURE GOOD, MANU.
GET UP!
GET UP THAT LADDER.
LETS GO, GUYS.
Jeff: KAMA TRYING TO STAY
CLOSE.
MANU STILL IN THE LEAD NOW.
THEY HAVE WON ONLY ONE CHALLENGE
THIS SEASON.
HERE COMES KAMA.
GOTTA GET EVERYBODY HERE.
YOURE GOOD.
GO, AUBRY.
IT IS DAVID ON THE KEYS FOR
MANU.
HES GOT THAT CHEST OPEN.
THERE ARE THREE SETS OF PIECES.
YOURE SOLVING THAT ONE FIRST.
KAMA NOW HAS THEIR CHEST OPEN.
THEY CAN START WORKING ON THE
WHEEL.
THE FIRST BAG ARE THE SPOKES.
YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHICH
PIECES GO TOGETHER SO THAT THEY
FIT IN PERFECTLY.
THIS IS A PUZZLE IN THE FORM OF
A SHIPS WHEEL.
MANU WON THE LAST CHALLENGE FOR
REWARD.
THEY HAVE YET TO WIN AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
NO, THIS ISNT LONG ENOUGH,
RIGHT?
YES, IT IS.
IT WORKS.
Jeff: ITS ALL ABOUT
COMMUNICATION.
PERFECT.
WHERE DOES THIS ONE GO?
Jeff: KAMA QUICKLY BACK IN
THIS.
THEY THINK THEY HAVE THE SPOKES
TOGETHER.
GOOD JOB, KAMA!
COME ON, GUYS!
Jeff: KAMA MOVING ON TO BAG
NUMBER TWO.
THEYVE GOT THEIR SPOKES PUT
TOGETHER.
ITS NOW MANU WHO IS STRUGGLING.
ITS NOT GOING TO WORK.
THIS ONE, THIS ONE!
COME ON!
YOU LOOK AT IT AND YOU TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
Jeff: THE TWO VETERANS,
DAVID AND WENTWORTH, STRUGGLING
ON THIS PUZZLE AND THEY HAVE
GIVEN UP THE LEAD.
THEY ARE ABSOLUTELY NOWHERE WITH
THE SPOKES.
THOSE DONT GO TOGETHER.
I KNOW.
THIS CANT GO HERE.
WHY IS THIS ON HERE?
Jeff: IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
KAMA HAS A BIG LEAD RIGHT NOW,
AND THEY KNOW IT.
KAMA MOVING ON TO THAT THIRD AND
FINAL SECTION.
WHERE THEY PUT THE HANDLES IN.
OKAY, OKAY.
GO, GO!
Jeff: MANU IS WRONG AGAIN!
WOW!
KAMA THINKS THEY HAVE IT.
FOR THE WIN.
WOOOO!
Jeff: KAMA WINS IMMUNITY
SENDING MANU BACK TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
SORRY.
SORRY, GUYS.
PUZZLES ARE HARD.
Jeff: KAMA, FOR THE THIRD
STRAIGHT TIME, IMMUNITY YOURS.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY ANOTHER NIGHT OFF.
ONCE AGAIN, MANU, TRIBAL
COUNCIL, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
LOSING THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE
WAS INCREDIBLY DEVASTATING, BUT
IVE ALWAYS BEEN WANTING TO
TARGET WENTWORTH, AND I THINK
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE REALLY
FOCUSED ON WENDY.
SO I HAVE A REAL OPPORTUNITY TO
TAKE OUT WENTWORTH.
I TRUST MY "SURVIVOR" INSTINCTS.
ITS TELLING ME RIGHT NOW TARGET
WENTWORTH.
♪ ♪
GOING INTO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, IM INJURED, AND I
STILL KILLED IT.
I FEEL LIKE DITHE BEST I COULD
HAVE DONE.
IM REALLY SORRY, GUYS.
NO, NO.
IM SORRY.
YOU GUYS HAVE NOTHING TO BE
SORRY ABOUT.
IM BUMMED BECAUSE I KNOW ALL
EYES ARE ON ME AT THE MOMENT AND
I FEEL LIKE TONIGHT IM GOING
HOME.
THIS IS THE LOWEST OF LOW SO
FAR.
I JUST WANT TO COOK THE
CHICKEN FOR US.
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY WITH THAT?
IM OKAY WITH IT.
YOU DONT HAVE TO CONVINCE ME
TO KILL A CHICKEN.
IF ITS UP TO ME TONIGHT,
THEYRE NOT EATING THAT CHICKEN.
READY TO DO THAT THING.
I HAVE TO FIND MY FLINT.
WHERE IS THE FLINT?
THE FLINT IS ON THE...
DONT DO IT TO ME, ALL.
DONT DO IT TO ME.
ITS SUPPOSED TO GO THERE.
DUDE, IM THE LAST ONE THAT
STARTED IT.
AND IT WAS IN THAT AREA.
YOU THINK YOU LEFT IT IN THIS
AREA?
I DID NOT TOUCH IT FROM HERE.
I WOULD WAIT TO KILL THE
CHICKEN?
YEAH.
WHERES WENDY AT?
SHE WALKED OFF.
SHE WALKED OFF?
DOWN THE BEACH.
DO YOU THINK SHE TOOK IT TO
SAVE HER CHICKEN?
NO, THAT WOULD BE INSANE.
THAT WOULD BE PSYCHOTIC.
I TOOK THEIR FLINT.
IM SURE ITS AROUND HERE.
BEING THE SMATTER I AM, I
THOUGHT THEY CANT COOK A
CHICKEN WITHOUT FIRE.
AND THEY CANT MAKE A FIRE
WITHOUT FLINT.
IS THERE ANY POSSIBILITY THAT
WEBDY TOOK IT?
SHE WAS UP TO THE CAMP WHILE
WE WERE ALL TALKING AND AS SOON
AS WE WERE DONE, SHE RUNS AWAY.
SHE DID ACTUALLY COME TO
CAMP.
WOULD YOU MIND ASKING HER,
DUDE?
SHOULD I BE THE ONE.
JUST ASK HER.
, "GIRL, DO YOU HAVE THE FLINT?"
ILL GO WITH YOU.
THE FLINT, IT DISAPPEARED,
AND THERES THIS THEORY FLOATING
AROUND THAT MAYBE WENDY TOOK IT
BECAUSE SHES BEEN AGAINST US
COOKING THE CHICKEN.
STRATEGY HERE.
APPROACHING HER.
HOW ARE YOU?
ILL LET YOU APPROACH, AND
ILL JUST KIND OF-- AT THE RIGHT
TIME ILL COME IN LIKE BAD COP.
EVERYONE IS LOSING THEIR MIND
BECAUSE OF THE FLINT.
THEYRE PROBABLY GOING TO WANT
TO VOTE OUT WENDY BECAUSE OF THE
CHICKEN DEBATE BUT I WANT TO
TAKE OUT WENTWORTH.
YOU MAY GET YOUR WISH ABOUT
THE CHICKEN.
WE ACTUALLY CANT SEEM TO FIND
THE FLINT.
YOU HAVENT SEEN IT LYING
AROUND, HAVE YOU?
CHRIS HAD IT.
YEAH, CHRIS HAD IT, AND HE
DOESNT KNOW WHERE HE PUT IT.
HE HAD IT THIS MORNING.
HOW DO YOU FEEL, TALKING SHOP
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT TONIGHT.
LETS SAY I WERE TO BE GOING
HOME TODAY.
YOU MAY NOT GO HOME.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING RIGHT
NOW?
IT WOULD BE COOL TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE.
ITS GOT TO BE KELLEY.
RIGHT.
BUT IFT REQUIRES SOME
CONVERSATIONS --
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD, AND IM
SORRY-- DONT THINK IM SULKING.
WENDY IS ABSOLUTELY THE BEST
SMOKE SCREEN.
SHE HAS DELIVERED ON A SILVER
PLATTER, VOTE ME OUT.
WELL GET THE FIRE GOING.
DID YOU FIND IT.
SHE DIDNT TAKE IT.
SHE DID NOT.
NO.
I DONT, SO.
WHERE IS IT.
DAVID, ITS STILL WENDY.
YEAH, YEAH.
I DONT WANT TO VOTE OUT WENDY.
I THINK WENDY IS SOMEONE I CAN
USE.
SHES LOYAL TO ME.
SHELL VOTE WITH ME I THINK
EVERY TIME.
YOU WANT TO KILL THE CHICKEN?
YEAH.
WHAT WE REALLY WANT IS TO
SEND KELLEY HOME.
KELLEY WENTWORTH NEEDS TO GO
HOME.
AND NOW, ITS A MATTER OF
PULLING OVER CHRIS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
TONIGHT?
I THINK THE SAFEST THING TO
DO IS WENTWORTH.
WENTWORTH?
YEAH.
DONT SAY ANYTHING TO LAUREN OR
WAR DOG.
I THINK WAR DOG WOULD BE A
NUMBER.
IM GOING TO BE HONEST WITH
YOU.
I THINK-- I REALLY BELIEVE IN MY
HEART OF HEARTS IF YOU TELL WAR
DOG WHAT WERE DOING TONIGHT,
THIS ENTIRE THING BLOWS APART.
KELLEY IS NOT GOING HOME.
HES IN MUCH TIGHTER WITH HER
THAN ANYBODY KNOWS.
WENTWORTH, SHES TOO GOOD TO
KEEP AROUND.
THE PROBLEM SIM IN PRETTY CLOSE
WITH WAR DOG, AND DAVID WANTS IT
TO BE JUST US FOUR.
BUT BACK HOME IN MY REAL LIFE,
IM SOMEONE WHO IS OPEN WITH
EVERYBODY.
SO MY BIGGEST FEAR IS THAT I
BURN BRIDGES WITH SOME OF THE
RELATIONSHIPS IVE BUILT OUT
HERE.
JUST TO PREPARE FOR TONIGHT.
YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I MEAN, WENDY.
IS IT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I MEAN, TALK TO ME.
DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER IDEA?
WE COULD BRAINSTORM NOW.
YEAH.
I THINK ITS EITHER GOING TO BE
WENDY OR WENTWORTH.
SHE PLAYS THIS GAME KIND OF LIKE
A SNAKE, DUDE.
ILL GO WITH WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO.
WENDY SHOULDNT OBVIOUS VOTE
TONIGHT.
WENDYS GOT A HURT ANKLE.
WENDY DOESNT WANT ANYTHING TO
DO WITH ANY OF THE CHICKENS.
BUT CHRIS APPROACHED ME FOR THE
SECOND TIME TO KEEP OPTIONS OVER
TO TAKE OUT WENTWORTH.
I TRUST WENTWORTH MORE THAN
CHRIS.
I DECIDE MAYBE ITS NOT WENDY OR
WENTWORTH.
MAYBE ITS CHRIS.
CHRIS, HES OUT TO GET YOU.
THIS GUYS A PROBLEM.
I WANT HIM OUT.
THIS GUY--
WHAT VOTES DO WE HAVE?
ITS BASICALLY FOUR-THREE,
RIGHT.
I JUST HAVE TO GET RICK AND
WE HAVE TO KEEP IT SHUSH.
TELL ME WHAT RICK SAYS.
WHAT DO WE DO WITH THIS GUY?
GET HIM OUT.
SO CHRIS IS COMING AFTER ME NOW,
SAYING MY NAME AND TRYING
POTENTIALLY PUT THIS PLAN
TOGETHER TO GET ME OUT.
THATS NOT GOING TO WORK FOR ME.
IF YOURE COMING FOR ME, LIKE,
YOU HAVE TO GO.
NO MORE WENDY.
VOTE CHRIS.
LOOK, HERES THE DEAL, CHRIS
SAYS LEAVE OPEN THE POSSIBILITY
THAT MAYBE WE TAKE WENTWORTH OUT
TONIGHT.
DID YOU ALREADY TALK TO HER
ABOUT THIS?
I TALKED TO HER FIRST.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU FIRST.
I DONT WANT TO BRING DAVID IN.
I DONT WANT TO BRING WENDY IN.
IF YOURE IN, WE BOTH TALK TO
LAUREN AND MAKE IT HAPPEN AND
TAKE ONE OF THE BIG THREATS OUT
OF THIS GAME.
OH, CRAP.
WAR DOG WANTS TO GET CHRIS OUT,
BECAUSE CHRIS IS GOING AFTER
KELLEY WHICH IM LIKE OH,
(BLEEP).
IM GLAD HE DOESNT KNOW IVE
BEEN GOING AFTER KELLEY.
IT WOULD BE YOU, ME, LAUREN AND
KELLEY?
YEAH, FOUR-THREE.
I DONT WANT TO ALIENATE
DAVID BECAUSE, LIKE, I DO THINK
HES A NUMBER FOR YOU AND I.
IF YOURE IN WITH THIS PLAN,
IM IN WITH YOU TALKING TO
DAVID.
IVE BEEN WAITING ALL GAME TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE.
APPARENTLY TODAY IS THE DAY FOR
BIG MOVES.
IT SUCKS BECAUSE NOW ITS ALL
COMING TO A HEAD, AND IM
GETTING PUSHED INTO A CORNER
WHERE IM GOG HAVE TO BETRAY
SOMEONE.
IM A VILLAIN NOW.
IVE BEEN TURNED INTO A VILLAIN.
SHE WASNT EVER SUPPOSED TO
KNOW HER NAME WAS COMING UP.
AND NOW SHE DOES.
SO--
HE PLAYED HIMSELF.
WE WERENT GOING TO APPROACH
WARDOG.
WE HAVE A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
OH, MY GOD, NOW IT LOOKS LIKE
WENDY ISNT EVEN AN OPTION TO
VOTE FOR ANYMORE, WHICH WAS A
SIMPLE VOTE.
NOW ITS BECOME A VOTE BETWEEN
WENTWORTH AND CHRIS.
IT SOUNDS LIKE WE HAVE OUR
WAY.
WE DO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WARDOG PAINT AID VERY PRETTY
PICTURE OF KELLEYS LOYALTY.
HERE SHE COMES.
YEAH.
NOW RICK AND I FIND
OURSELVESES IN THE MIDDLE.
WHATEVER NAME RICK AND I LAND
ON--
IVE BEEN BROUGHT UP TO
SPEED.
OH, OKAY.
...THAT IS WHO SHOULD BE
GOING HOME TONIGHT.
DAVID, I DONT TRUST ANYBODY.
ON ONE HAND ITS GOOD TO VOTE
FOR WENTWORTH, BECAUSE SHES THE
PERSON I LEAST TRUST IN THIS
GAME.
BUT FUNNY THING IS, IF I VOTE
CHRIS OUT, NO ONE IN THE GAME
WOULD KNOW THAT IM THE ONE
COMING AFTER WENTWORTH.
NO MATTER WHAT, TONIGHTS TRIBAL
COUNCIL IS GOING TO BE HUGE.
SECRETS ARE GOING TO GET
EXPOSED.
BETRAILS ARE GOING TO GET
AND I THINK NOBODY IS GOG VIEW
ANY OF THOSE BETRAILS KINDLY OR
QUIETLY.
♪ ♪
Jeff: SO , IF YOU WERE
WATCHING AT HOME HOW WOULD YOU
JUDGE THIS TRIBE?
LOSERS.
WE HAVE THREE IMMUNITIES AND ONE
WIN WE END UP WITH AN INJURED
PLAYER.
DONT FORGET ABOUT THE FLINT.
WE LOST THE FLINT IN CAMP
TODAY.
AND ARGUING OVER THE
CHICKENS.
IT WAS A DISASTER.
Jeff: LAUREN, WHAT WAS THE
ARGUMENT ABOUT THE CHICKENS?
WENDY DECIDED THAT SHE WOULD
NOT EAT A CHICKEN IF WE KILLED
IT.
I MEAN, I DIDNT FEEL LIKE IT
WAS MUCH OF AN ARGUMENT.
IT WASNT LIKE, "IM GOING TO
CAUSE CHAOS IF YOU GUYS KILL A
CHICKEN."
IT WAS BASICALLY, "I DONT FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
ILL STEP ASIDE."
Jeff: WARDOG, IS THAT YOUR
TAKE ON IT?
SHE EATS CHICKEN BACK HOME
WITH NO PROBLEM.
SHE SAID, YOURE RIGHT.
IM GOING TO BE A VEGETARIAN
NOW.
HOW IS THAT?
ITS ALMOST LIKE TALKING TO
MYSELF.
SHE HAS A LOT OF WARDOG IN HER.
WARPUP.
TECHNICALLY I HAVE BEEN
VEGETARIAN FOR EIGHT DAYS NOW,
SO IM THAT STUBBORN.
Jeff: SO, DEVENS, WHEN YOU
LOSE ONE AFTER ANOTHER AFTER
ANOTHER, THERES A POINT WHERE
IT MIGHT JUST BECOME I HAVE TO
KICK INTO GAME MODE.
I CANT WORRY ANYMORE ABOUT THE
TRIBE.
THE FIRST TWO TRIBALS WAS
BASED ON WE NEED TO GET STRONGER
AND ITS NOT WORKING.
SO YOU HAVE TO RE-EVALUATE, AND
I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE HAD THAT
RUNNING THROUGH THEIR MINDS
TODAY.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, DID YOU
FEEL A SHIFT AFTER TODAYS LOSS,
THREE THIS A ROW.
SOMETHING HAS TO CHANGE.
WERE OBVIOUSLY DOING
SOMETHING LONG AND ITS COMING
DOWN TO LOYALTY.
AS WE GET SMALLER AND SMALLER
AND THAT YOU RECALL, YOURE
GOING TO HAVE TO TRUST THE
PEOPLE YOURE WITH.
Jeff: DAVID, ITS AN
INTERESTING IDEAL IF A TRIBE
WERE TO GIVE UP ON ITSELF AND
LTS ABILITY TO WIN, THEN
SOMEBODY WHO IS SLOWING YOU DOWN
IN CHALLENGES ISNT AS BIG A
PROBLEM.
WELL, THATS, I THINK,
EXACTLY WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN
TONIGHT.
SO WHETHER OR NOT SOMEONE IS A
LIABILITY IN A CHALLENGE IS
IRRELEVANT.
I THINK THAT TONIGHT IS REALLY
ABOUT ELIMINATING THE BIGGEST
SOCIAL THREAT.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, THAT
SEEMED TO GET YOUR ATTENTION.
YEAH, I MEAN-- THERE COULD BE
MULTIPLE PLANS GOING ON.
IM NOT SURE.
UHM...
Jeff: I RARELY SEE YOU
BEING UNABLE TO ANSWER.
IM TRYING TO PROCESS WHAT
DAVID SAID.
DONT WORRY --
YEAH, DONT WORRY ABOUT IT.
HES JUST TALKING.
WARDOG, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
DAVIDS COMMENTS?
A LOT OF HIS COMMENTS KIND OF
THROW ME A LITTLE BIT OFF
BALANCE, TO BE HONEST.
IM STICKING TO MY PLAN.
AND I THINK COHESION IS THE BEST
WAY FORWARD.
Jeff: WENDY, WHEN YOU HEAR
THIS COMMENT FROM DAVID, DOES IT
MAKE GU, "OH, MAYBE THERES MORE
GAME AFOOT?"
HONESTLY, WHATEVER HAPPENS IN
TRIBAL COUNCIL, I ALWAYS FEEL
LIKE THE TRIBE IS A PYRAMID OF
DIFFERENT LAYERS AND IM RIGHT
AT THE BOTTOM.
IM JUST EXTRACTING ALL MY
INFORMATION FROM WHATS
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
Jeff: WOW.
DEVENS, THIS IS FASCINATING!
A TRIBE THAT SEEMS TO HAVE
NOTHING GOING ON BUT LOSS AFTER
LOSS AFTER LOSS RIGHT NOW SEEMS
TO BE PLAYING A VERY COMPLEX,
LAYERED GAME, ONLY EIGHT DAYS
IN.
I HOPE THIS CAN BE OUR
ADVANTAGE BECAUSE KAMA HASNT
DONE ANY OF THIS, AND WE HAVE
THREE DAYS OF PURE STRATEGY
UNDER OUR BELT RIGHT NOW SO
WERE PLAYING A MUCH MORE
DEVELOPED GAME.
I THINK JUST COMING OUT HERE,
YOU DONT REALIZE HOW GOOD THESE
PLAYERS ARE.
LIKE, THESE ARE REAL
CONVERSATIONS.
THESE ARE REAL RELATIONSHIPS.
THESE ARE REAL PEOPLE.
AND THATS SOMETHING THAT YOU
CANT FEEL BACK HOME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
LAUREN, YOURE UP.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE,
WENTWORTH.
CHRIS.
THATS TWO VOTES WENTWORTH.
WERE TIED, TWO VOTES WENTWORTH,
TWO VOTES CHRIS.
CHRIS.
THATS THREE VOTES CHRIS, TWO
VOTES WENTWORTH.
THIRD PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR,"
CHRIS.
THATS FOUR.
THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
Jeff: CHRIS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
♪ ♪
SCREW THOSE GUYS. IM GETTING
BACK IN THE BOAT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
YOU CAN FLY THE COOP--
I FINALLY DID MY PLAN OF
RELEASING THE CHICKENS!
Jeff: BUT YOU CANT ESCAPE
A TWIST.
EVERYBODY, DROP YOUR BUFFS.
NOW WE HAVE TO CANNIBALIZE
OURSELVES.
Jeff: WE ARE SWITCHING FROM
TWO TRIBES TO THREE TRIBES.
ITS A WHOLE NEW DYNAMIC NOW.
I JUST GOT LIED TO MY FACE.
TOMORROW ITS GOING TO BE
MOTIVATION AND REFOCUS.
TONIGHT ITS PAINFUL.
SOMETHING IN MY STOMACH HURTS.
I DIDNT SEE THE BLINDSIDE
COMING.
THIS IS A BLINDSIDE INSIDE OF A
BLINDSIDE BUT ITS A REDEEMING
BLINDSIDE.
IVE BEEN GIVEN A SECOND CHANCE
AND IM GOING TO MIESKT OF IT.
SCREW THOSE GUYS.
IM COMING BACK FOR YOU.