>> WHERE WERE WENDY AND KEITH?
>> DID THEY QUIT?
>> MAYBE THEY DECIDED TO GO
HOME.
>> THEY'RE STILL AT EXTINCTION.
>> AFTER MY FIRST TRIBAL THERE
WERE TWO IDIOTS, ONE WAS JOE,
THE NEXT ONE WAS ME.
WE WERE THE ONLY TWO OUT OF THE
ORIGINAL CAMBO KAMA THAT WERE IN
DARK ABOUT TONIGHT'S VOTE, SO IT
PRETTY MUCH SUCTION RIGHT NOW.
>> IF I HAVE TO WORK WITH KAMA
AND PLAY NICE, I CAN DO, THAT
BUT I HAVE NO ALLEGIANCES.
I DON'T CARE WHERE I GO AT THIS
POINT, BUT I AM ONLY GOING WITH
THE NUMBERS.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> CAN I HAVE A HUG?
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
>> BY SAVING DAVID AND RICK,
THEY TRUST ME.
THEY'RE LOYAL.
THEY OWE ME A MAJOR ONE.
>> I HAD THREE VOTES.
I THOUGHT SO.
THAT'S WHAT I FIGURED.
>> NOT ONLY DID THEY WANT TO DO
IT.
THEY WERE EVIL ABOUT IT.
LIKE, NO REMORSE WHATSOEVER.
I REALLY WANTED RICK AND DAVID
TO BE SO ANGRY WITH THE MEMBERS
OF LESU, BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
THEM FOR A SECOND TO THINK ABOUT
GOING BACK AND WORK WITH THEM,
AND THE CAVERN I HAVE BUILT WITH
LESU IS SO STRONG, THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO CROSS.
IT.
IF WE JUST STAY THE COURSE,
THREE VOTES FROM NOW, YOU KNOW
WHERE THAT PUTS YOU?
>> FAMILY VISIT.
>> HOPEFULLY.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO BE LOYAL WITH
YOU GUYS.
>> THEY MADE US GO AGAINST EACH
OTHER.
>> IT IS.
>> IT IS AURORA.
RIGHT NOW WE NEED EACH OTHER FOR
THE NEXT TWO VOTES.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE ALL DONE.
IF WE PATCH THOSE WOUNDS WITH
DEVYNS AND DAVID, IT MAY BRING
AURORA IN, WEAK SAY-- MAYBE WE
CAN GO TO ROCKS.
WE CAN GAMBLE ON ROCKS.
IF WE DON'T GO TO ROCKS, WE'RE
GOING HOME ANYWAY.
>> 20 MORE DAYS AND COUNTING.
19 LEFT TO GO.
STUPID GAME.
I LOVE IT SO MUCH.
DAMN, IT GETS HARDER.
>> JUST TRYING TO KEEP IT ALL
TOGETHER.
THAT'S ALL YOU GOTTA DO, JUST
KEEP IT-- KEEP IT TOGETHER.
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET TO TODAY'S
REWARD CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES, RETRIEVE THE BAG
OF PUZZLE PIECES, THEN RACE TO
THE FINISH.
YOU'LL THEN USE THEM TO SOLVE A
PUZZLE.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR?
CHINESE TAKE OUT, WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT CAMP.
IT'S LOOK A WEDNESDAY NIGHT BACK
HOME WATCHING "SURVIVOR."
ORDER IN.
LOSERS, NOTHING.
WE'RE GOING TO DO A RANDOM DRAW.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE OUR TWO
TEAMS.
FOR REWARD, HERE WE GO,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST PAIR, GAVIN AND WENTWORTH
AND WARDOG AND ERIK FOR BLUE.
GOT TO GET TO THAT PLATFORM.
>> COME OERIK!
>> Jeff: ERIK GETS TO THE
PLATFORM FIRST.
GAFFEN NOW THERE.
>> COME ON, WARDOG.
>> Jeff: WARDOG RIGHT BEHIND.
HERE COMES WENTWORTH.
BOTH HAVE TO BE AT THE CROWS
NEST BUFFER CAN CLIMB THAT
LADDER.
GO YELLOW.
GBLUE.
IT'S ERIK GOING UP TO UNTIE,
GAVIN GOING UP TO UNTIE FOR
YELLOW.
>> GOOD JOB, ERIK.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DOING GOOD.
>> Jeff: ERIK WITH THE FIRST
PUZZLE PLANKS FOR BLUE.
>> GOOD JOB!
>> GOOD JOB.
GO, WARDOG, GO!
GOOD JOB, BOYS!
>> Jeff: GAVIN HAS HIS PUZZLE
PLANK.
LET'S GO!
>> GO, GO, GO!
COME ON!
>> Jeff: GAFFEIP IN THE WATER.
HERE COMES WENTWORTH.
GOTTA GET THEM BACK TO SHORE.
>> COME ON, WARDOG, LET'S GO!
GOOD HUSTLE, GUYS.
>> COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: GO, BLUE!
IT IS AURORA AND DEVINS IN THE
WATER FOR BLUE.
>> GOOD JOB, DEVIN.
>> GO, YELLOW!
LAUREN IN THE WATER WITH JULIE.
THEY'VE GOT SOME TIME TO MAKE
UP.
BLUE IN THE EARLY LEAD NOW.
AURORA CROSSING THE BEAM.
IT'S GOING TO BE AURORA GOING UP
UP TO UNTIE THAT SECOND BAG OF
PUZZLE PLANKS.
>> COME OJULIE!
>> Jeff: JULIE TAKING A WHILE
TO GET UP.
EVERY SECOND YOU LOSE COULD BE
THE SECOND YOU NEED.
>> COME ON, JULIE!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
GO, YELLOW!
HUGE TIME ADVANTAGE RIGHT NOW
FOR BLUE AS AURORA HAS HER
PLANKS FREE.
YOU'RE GOOD, JUMP.
AURORA IN THE WATER, JUST MISSES
THE PLANKS.
DEVIN IS IN THE WATER.
HE HAS TO SWIM BACK TO SHORE
NOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE JULIE UNTYING
THE KNOTS.
>> COME OYELLOW!
YOU'RE DOING GREAT!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
PUZZLE MAKERS TAKE OVER.
IT'S GOING TO BE VICTORIA AND
JULIA NOW HAVE TO UNTIE EACH BAG
AND GET THEM IN THE BECAUSE OF
PUZZLE.
YELLOW HAS THEIR SECOND BATCH OF
PUZZLE PLANKS.
>> JUST PUT IT UNDER THAT--
YEAH.
>> Jeff: JULIA AND VICTORIA
WAY BIG LEAD ROOT NOW.
CAN THEY TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT?
YOU'RE GOOD, YELLOW.
PUZZLE MAKERS, TAKE OVER.
IT'S GOING TO BE DAVID AND RYAN
WORKING ON THE PUZZLE.
>> VICTORIA, THE THIRD FROM THE
TOP IS NUMBER ONE.
>> I CAN'T-- I'M NOT TALL
ENOUGH.
>> Jeff: JULIA AND VICTORIA
HAVING TO WORK TOGETHER.
THESE ARE HEAVY PIECES OF WOOD.
YOU HAVE TO USE BOTH PLAYERS TO
GET IT IN.
>> IT'S HIGHER THAN THAT.
IT'S HIGHER THAN THAT.
>> JUST PUT IT IN.
>> Jeff: DAVID AND RON TRYING
TO GET BACK IN IT.
>> JULIA, THIS ONE IS TOP.
>> Jeff: JULIA AND VIKTORRIA,
THEY ARE TAKE A LONG TIME
FIGURING THIS PUZZLE OUT.
HERE COMES DAVID AND RON WITH
THEIR LAST PLANK.
THEY HAVE DONE A NICE JOB OF
CLOSING THAT TIME GAP NOW.
JULIA AND VICTORIA STARTING TO
PICK UP THE PAILS.
THEY ARE GETTING THE HANG OF
THIS.
WE ARE VERY CLOSE RIGHT NOW.
DAVID WEDGED IN THERE, CAN'T GET
IT OUT.
>> DAVID, THE ONE ABOVE IT.
>> GET THIS, GET THIS!
>>
>> Jeff: DAVID AND RON GOING
TO SWITCH SIDES NOW.
>> THERE YOU GO, PERFECT,
PERFECT.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA AND JULIA
SLOWLY FIGURING THIS PUZZLE OUT,
PLANK BY PLANK.
>> JULIA, ARE YOU KILLING IT.
>> RON, PULL YOURS OUT!
SWITCH IT!
>> Jeff: YELLOW DOING A LOT OF
YELLING AT EACH OTHER.
THEY HAVE HIT A ROADBLOCK.
>>
>> JULIA THINKS THEY ARE ONE
BOARD AWAY WEAPON ARE THEY?
BIG REWARD ON THE LINE.
VICTORIA AND JULIA THINK THEY
HAVE IT, AND THEY DO!
AURORA, ERIK, DEVINS, WARDOG,
JULIA, AND VICTORIA, CHINESE
TAKEOUT WAITING FOR THEM BACK AT
CAMP.
>> SORRY.
>> SO WE LOST.
EVERYONE'S UPSET, BUT I'M
SITTING BACK THINKING THIS IS
AWESOME.
BECAUSE THE LAST THING I WANT IS
FOR WENTWORTH AND LAUREN TO BE
STRONG.
I WANT THEM TO BE LOST AND
LONELY BECAUSE I'M THE PUPPET
MASTER.
I'M TRYING TO BREAK THEM DOWN.
>> CHEERS.
>> GOOD REWARD, YOU GUYS!
>> THIS IS SO GOOD, YOU GUYS.
>> THIS IS BEST CHINESE FOOD
I'VE EVER HAD IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
GUYS, I KNOW I JUST MET YOU A
NEW DAYS AGO AND THIS MIGHT BE
FAST, BUT I LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> WE LOVE YOU!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I FEEL SO BAD BECAUSE I NOW
KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE TO LOSE
A REWARD.
>> YEAH.
>> WE HAVE NOT WON A DAMN THING.
>> NO.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
AWESOME?
IF A CHICKEN WALKED THROUGH THIS
CAMP RIGHT NOW AND JUST SAT
HERE.
>> OH, GOD.
IT'S LIKE, "HEY, GUYS, I HEARD
WHAT HAPPENED AT THE CHALLENGE.
EAT ME."
>>Y JUST NEEDED SOME SORT OF
FOOD, AND SOME SORT OF WIN.
I AM SO FREAKING HUNGRY.
>> WE KILLED THAT FOOD.
>> GOOD REWARD, GUYS!
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE!
>> I FEEL LIKE I AM CURSED.
LIKE, CAN'T WIN ANYTHING.
>> I JUST WANT TO APOLOGIZE FOR
VOTING FOR YOU LAST NIGHT.
>> NO, NO, NO.
HEY, AND I'M SORRY, TOO.
>> YEAH, ALL GOOD.
AT THIS POINT, I'M KIND OF ON
THE BOTTOM WITH WARDOG AND
LAUREN.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE RICK AND
DAVID STAND COMPLETELY.
BUT WE'VE GOT TO BURY THE
HATCHET.
IT'S DUMB.
THE LESER GROUP IS TOTALLY GOING
AFTER EACH OTHER AND FORGETTING
THERE IS THIS WHOLE KAMAIZATION
SWAIGZ.
IT'S WHAT KAMA WANTS TO RUN THE
GAME.
IF THE LESU FIVE COME TOGETHER
AND PULL IN...-- THE LESU FIVE
COME TOGETHER AND PULL IN
AURORA, WE HAVE SIX PEOPLE TO
TRY AND VOTE ONE OF THESE KAMA
PEOPLE OUT.
HERE'S THE DEAL-- YOU KNOW HOW
THIS GAME WORKS.
EITHER WE COME TOGETHER AND TRY
TO TAKE ONE OF THEM OUT, OR
WE'RE PROBABLY GOING TO GO ONE
BY ONE.
IT'S.
OBVIOUSLY, I'M SURE THEY TOLD
YOU GUYS LIKE YOU ARE WORKING
WITH US NOW, OR WHATEVER.
>> HERE'S MY THING, THOUGH.
ONCE DEVIN AND WARDOG, THAT'S
FIVE.
>> AURORA.
>> AURORA?
YOU REALLY THINK SHE'S KEEN ON
THAT?
I MEAN, I KNOW SHE'S ON THE
BOTTOM.
>> NUMBER ONE, OBVIOUSLY, BEING
LEFT OUT.
BECAUSE IT WOULD HAVE BEEN SO
EASY TO TELL ME BEFORE.
SO I DON'T FEEL LIKE ANY OF THEM
TRUST ME.
>> I'VE HEARD NO ONE SAY YOUR
NAME.
I MEAN, I KNOW OUR GOAL IS WE'VE
GOT TO GET TO THIS LEVEL, BUT
I'D LIKE US TO STAY LONGER THAN
THAT.
>> AURORA FEELS ON THE OUTS.
>> SHE IS.
LET'S SAY WE DO HAVE SIX.
IT WOULD BE A TIE.
>> UNLESS THEY THINK THEY HAVE,
LIKE YOU AND DEVINS OR
SOMETHING, AND THEN TRY AND
SPLIT.
>> YEAH.
THEN--
>> AND THEN WE HAVE THE NUMBERS.
>> OKAY.
ACTUALLY, I LIKE THAT PLAN.
I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT WHAT
WENTWORTH IS PROPOSING BECAUSE
THE KAMA TRIBE ARE IN CONTROL OF
THIS GAME.
I'M NOT IN CONTROL OF ANYTHING.
I'M-- I'M JUST A PIECE IN THEIR
GAME.
ESPECIALLY THE PEOPLE WHO ARE IN
CHARGE OF TLIKE RON AND ERIK.
>> I'M SORT OF LEANING TOWARDS
SPLITTING THE VOTES OVER LAUREN
AND KELLEY.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY...
>> WE NEED TO BAND TOGETHER AND
FLIP THIS GAME ON ITS HEAD.
I'VE JUST GOT TO PULL IN MY
STRONGEST ALLIANCE MEMBER, WHICH
IS DEVINS.
THAT SHOULD BE NO PROBLEM.
I'LL TALK TO RICK LATER,
OBVIOUSLY RIGHT NOW NOW.
>> I HOPE HE UNDERSTANDS THERE
ARE NO HARD FEELINGS ABOUT
ANYTHING.
>> SO, THE FIVE LESU TOGETHER.
>> I'M DYING TO GET BACK ABOUT
THE OLD LESU.
NOW THAT I KNOW I CAN TRUST YOU
GUYS, I REALLY WANT TO GET BACK
WITH YOU ALL.
>> YOU--
>> EXCEPT THEY DON'T (BLEEP)
WANT TO GET BACK WITH YOU GUYS
AT ALL?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHY WOULD I WORK WITH YOU
GUYS?
>> WELL, I MEAN--
>> YOU GUYS STABBED ME IN THE
BACK OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT TO WORK WITH KELLEY
AT ALL.
SHE TRIED TO VOTE ME OUT TWICE.
>> YOU COME HERE FOR NINTH OR
EIGHTH, THAT'S FINE.
I CAME TO WIN THE GAME.
>> WHY WOULD I WANT TO WORK WITH
THEM?
>> BECAUSE IT GETS YOU FARTHER
IN THE GAME.
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT THAT'S
TRUE.
I DON'T KNOW THAT THAT'S TRUE.
I KNOW IT GETS YOU FURGTS IN THE
GAME AND SHIKS THINGS UP.
IT WAS SO STUPID, DON'T COME OUT
HERE AND WARDOG ME AND YELL AT
ME THAT I'M NOT PLAYING THE GAME
YOU THINK I SHOULD BE PLAYING.
I'M GOING HOME.
DID YOU COME TO ME?
I DON'T LIKE BEING BARKD AT.
>> YOU'RE PLAYING WITH EMOTIONS.
>> YOU KEEP SAYING I'M PLAYING
WITH EMOTIONS.
>>
>> YOU HAVE PLAYING WITH
EMOTIONS.
>> IF I CAN'T TRUST LESU, LET'S
GET IN WITH KAMA.
THEY JUST SAVED ME AT LAST
TRIBAL.
DON'T BARK AT ME THAT I'M NOT
PLAYING THE GAME BECAUSE I'M NOT
DOING WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO.
HE NEEDS DAVID AND I TO SWING
WITH THEM BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> YOU ALWAYS REMEMBER ONE
CONVERSATION IN "SURVIVOR," YOU
WILL REMEMBER THIS ONE.
I'M A PUPET AND YOU'RE A PUPPET.
WE ARE NOT DRIVING THIS GAME.
ERIK IS DRIVING IT.
AND RON IS DRIVING IT.
WE NEED TO NAVIGATE OUR OWN
SHIPS.
>> BUT MY WAY IS BETTER FOR ME.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING NUMBERS, BRO.
I THINK YOU'RE DREAMING.
I THINK YOU'RE GETTING PLAYED.
>> THERE'S NOTHING MORE
IMPORTANT THAN BREAK UP KAMA.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY, DEVINS IS
NOT ON BOARD, 100% OPPOSED TO
IT.
>> ONE OF US IS DRUNK RIGHT NOW,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE.
I THINK I'M THE SOBER ONE.
>> I'M NOT COMING TO YOUR SIDE.
>> REMEMBER WE HAVE THE IDOL.
>> I JUST THOUGHT YOU WOULD GIVE
ME THE HALF BACK.
>> IF YOU DON'T MIND, I'D LIKE
TO HANG ON TO IT.
DEVIN IS LETTING EMOTIONS RUN TO
HIS GAME, SO THE LAST THING I
WANT TO DO IS GIVE HIM THE HALF
OF THE IDOL.
IT'S SO FRUSTRATING TO HAVE
FOUND SOMEONE I TRUST AS MUCH AS
I TRUST DEVINS AND REALIZE I
HAVE TO FIND ANOTHER PATH.
I WANTED IT TO BE WITH DEVIN BUT
THE WAY IT'S SHAPING UP RIGHT
NOW I'M NOT SURE THERE'S ANY
HOPE OF THAT.
THESE WINE BOTTLES.
>> ALL AT THE SAME TIME?
>> YEAH.
>> HONESTLY, I'M TERRIBLE WITH
RIDDLES.
I'M EVEN WORSE WITH MAPS.
I WAS READY TO TAKE A NAP.
IT'S BEEN ROCKY THUS FAR BUT
YOUR GAME IS STILL AT STAKE.
STEP BACK AND ASSESS, AN
ADVANTAGE AWAITS.
>> "STEP BACK AND ASSESS, AN
ADVANTAGE AWAITS."
>> DID YOU HEAR ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED LAST TIME?
>> UH-HUH.
>> I ALREADY HAVE MY SHOES ON
BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
THERE'S NEW ON EXTINCTION-- YOU
BEST BE RUNNING BECAUSE IT'S
LIKE BLACK FRIDAY AND YOU BETTER
GET THE TOY.
>> IF BECAUSE SOMEONE HERE'S
GOING TO GET IT.
>> I'M COMING FOR YOU, AUBRY.
I'M COMING FOR YOU.
>> CHRIS, ARE YOU NOT GOING TO
GET ME THIS TIME, PAL.
>> IT'S BEEN ROCKY THUS FAR, BUT
YOUR GAME IS STILL AT STAKE.
IS THERE A STAKE SOMEWHERE NEAR
THE ROCKS?
>> DID YOU FIND IT?
STEP BACK AND ASSESS.
>> I'VE BEEN HERE FOR THREE
FREAKING WEEKS.
I WOULD JUST LIKE TO FIND
SOMETHING.
>> "STEP BACK."
I'M NOT SURE EXACTLY WHAT IT
MEANS.
THERE ARE SOME STAIRS.
THERE ARE SOME STEPS.
AND I FEEL LIKE IT'S RIGHT UNDER
EVERYONE'S NOSE, BUT I CAN'T
SEEM TO FIND IT.
>> EVERYONE STARTS CHECKING THE
STEPS.
THEY SEE ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
I TOOK A STEP BACK, LOOK TO MY
LEFT, THERE'S A BIG HOLE IN THE
ROCK WALL.
BUT I'M LIKE, "THIS IS MINE!
"SO SNEAKY, SNEAKY, LIKE KELLEY
WENTWORTH.
NOTHING HERE.
I STICK MY HAND IN, AND TURNS
OUT, THERE IS A KEY AND A CLUE
THAT SAYS, "FOLLOW THE ROCKS TO
THE LAST IN THE SAND, WHERE YOUR
PRACTICE BEGINS."
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT THE HELL, MAN.
I GO OVER THE ROCKS, GET TO THE
SANDY BEACH, AND I SEE A POST
WITH ROPE.
IT LOOKS LIKE I FOUND THE
PRACTICE ADVANTAGE.
AND I AM STOKED.
I'VE BEEN HANGING WITH THESE
BROS, LISTEN TO THEM TALK ABOUT
HOW THEY'RE GOING TO GET BACK IN
THE GAME AND WIN.
BUT LITTLE DO THEY KNOW THAT THE
PRACTICE ADVANTAGE EVEN EXISTS.
AND I FOUND SOMETHING ELSE
TUCKED UP IN THE ROCKS-- THIS.
AN EXTRA VOTE FOR SOMEONE IN THE
GAME.
OKAY.
WOW.
THAT'S BIG.
THIS IS AMAZING!
NOW, NOT ONLY DO I GET TO
PRACTICE TO GET BACK IN THE
GAME, BUT I ALSO HAVE A DECISION
TO MAKE.
I HAVE TO DECIDE WHO I WANT TO
GIVE THIS EXTRA VOTE TO.
LOOSEN THAT.
GOTTA TIGHTEN HERE.
SO I MIGHT BE OUT OF SIGHT, OUT
OF MIND AT THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, BUT I KNOW THAT THE
GAME IS ALWAYS THERE.
AND THE ADVANTAGE COULD BE
LITERALLY THE KEY TO SOMEONE'S
GAME.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE GET TO
TODAY'S IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YEAH!
>> YES!
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
JULIE.
GOT TO TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
OH, THE FROWN.
YOU CAN WIN IT AGAIN.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO BALANCE ON YOUR TOES
WITH A BLOCK WEDGED BETWEEN YOUR
HEAD AND THE TOP OF THE FRAME.
THE LONGER THE CHALLENGE GOES,
THE MORE FATIGUED YOUR LEGS WILL
BECOME.
WHEN THEY FINALLY GIVE OUT, YOUR
BLOCK WILL DROP.
YOU'RE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BECOME THE EIGHTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
EVERYBODY PLACE YOUR BLOCKS
ABOVE YOUR HEAD.
YOU'RE GOING TO WEDGE THEM
BETWEEN YOUR HEAD AND THE TOP OF
THE FRAME, WHICH IS GOING TO
FORCE YOU TO STAND ON YOUR TOES.
THAT'S WHERE THIS CHALLENGE IS
DIFFICULT.
EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD, AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON.
AND QUICKLY, YOU WILL FEEL IT.
SOMEBODY MAY DROP VERY FAST.
IF YOU LOSE YOUR BALANCE AND
TOUCH THE FRAME, EVEN A LITTLE,
YOU'RE OUT.
WARDOG QUICKLY STRUGGLING TO
BALANCE.
THAT BLOCK FALLS.
WITHIN 15 SECONDS, WARDOG IS THE
FIRST OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
WENTWORTH ALREADY FEELING IT.
>> I'M, LIKE, SHAKING.
>> Jeff: 22 DAYS ON "SURVIVOR"
IS IMPOSSIBLE TO IMAGINE.
YOU ONLY KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
WHEN YOU ARE THE ONE WHO HAS
EXPERIENCED IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE SHAKING
SECONDS INTO THIS CHALLENGE.
WENTWORTH REALLY FIGHTING TO
KEEP THAT BALANCE.
KEEP DIGGING!
ERIK IS OUT.
HE'LL TALK A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
GAVIN DROPS OUT OF NOWHERE
PURPOSE WE'RE DOWN TO NINE.
AND WENTWORTH DROPS.
SHE'S OUT.
WE'VE ALREADY LOST FOUR OF THE
FITTEST PEOPLE IN THIS GAME.
DEVENS A SUDDEN FIVE OF THE
FITTEST NOW.
DEVENS JOINSZ THE RANKS OF THE
FITTEST SURVIVORS IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
WE ARE DOWN TO SEVEN.
JULIA WOBBLING.
JULIA, BLOCK DROPS.
SHE'S OUT.
DOWN TO SIX.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: RON DROPS.
RON IS OUT.
AND WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
>> AAH!
>> Jeff: JULIE'S OUT OF THE
CHALLENGE.
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR: DAVID,
VICTORIA, AURORA, AND LAUREN.
>> OH!
>> Jeff: DAVID, A NICE
RECOVERY.
HOLDING THAT BLOCK STEADY.
YOU'RE STILL LOOKING GOOD UP
TOP.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: VIKTORRIA, VERY CALM
RIGHT NEXT TO DAVID, HASN'T
MOVED, HASN'T OPENED HER EYES.
AURORA STILL VERY SOLID.
LAUREN VERY SOLID.
ARE WE COULD BE HERE FOR A
WHILE.
>> Jeff: 25 MINUTE IN, DAVID,
VIKTORRIA, AURORA, AND LAUREN
STILL FIGHTING FOR THAT
NECKLACE.
DAVID'S FEET MOVING ONCE AGAIN.
>> I'M A LITTLE DIZZY.
>> Jeff: FIRST BIT OF MOVEMENT
FROM LAUREN, JUST A SLIGHT
ADJUSTMENT, TRYING TO KEEP FROM
GOING NUMB, PROBABLY.
>> VERY DIZZY.
>> Jeff: AURORA WITH A BIT OF
MOVEMENT.
VICTORIA STILL ABSOLUTELY SOLID.
>> DAMN THE SKINNY GIRLS.
>> AAH!
>> Jeff: DAVID DROPS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> Jeff: THAT'S HOW EASILY IT
CAN HAPPEN.
A SLIGHT CHANGE IN THE PRESSURE
FROM YOUR HEAD TO THAT BLOCK TO
THE TOP OF THE FRAME.
AND YOU'RE OUT.
>> I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
I'M ABOUT TO BLACK OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> Jeff: MEDICAL, MEDICAL!
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> LAUREN PASSED OUT.
JUST KEEP GOING.
>> OH, MY GOOD.
>> SHE'S GOT PEOPLE AROUND HER,
VICK.
>> SHE'S OKAY.
>> LAUREN?
>> Jeff: JOE, LET ME KNOW IF
WE NEED TO STOP THIS CHALLENGE.
DON'T WORRY, SHE'S IN GOOD
HANDS.
FOR NOW WE'LL LET IT RUN.
GO DR JOE WILL LET US KNOW.
>> LAUREN, YOU CAN HEAR ME?
>> VICTORIA IT'S YOU AND I.
VICTORIA.
>> I'M OKAY, AURORA.
>> I KNOW.
YOU KNOW THAT I WAS THE ONLY
PERSON OUT OF THAT VOTE.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I NEED THIS, JUST TO FEEL
BETTER ABOUT OUR GROUP.
>> PASS ME THE ORANGE CASE OVER
THERE, PLEASE.
LAUREN, LAUREN.
>> Jeff: EVEN NOW, WHILE LAWR
SEN ON THE GROUND, AURORA IS
PLEADING WITH VICTORIA TO GIVE
THIS TO HER.
>> I WAS THE ONLY ONE LEFT OUT
OF THE VOTE, DUDE.
>> AURORA, JUST WAIT.
AURORA, IT'S NOT THE TIME.
>> YEAH, IT REALLY ISN'T.
>> NO, DUDE, SECOND-HALF
CHALLENGES ARE ALL ABOUT SKINNY,
LEAN PEOPLE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> CHECK HER PULSE.
GIVE HER A MOMENT.
>> HEY, LAUREN.
YOU JUST FAINTED.
>> DAMN IT!
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
JUST GIVE YOURSELF A MINUTE,
LAUREN.
YOU FEEL A BIT LIGHTHEADED.
>> Jeff: DR. JOE, YOU'RE OKAY
OVER THERE?
OKAY.
LAWR SEN GOOD.
SHE'S BACK.
>> YOU JUST RELAX.
>> NO ONE WAS LEFT OUT BUT ME,
VICTORIA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'M GONNA (BLEEP) LOSA.
>> YOU WANT ME TO TRUST YOU, I
NEED THIS.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, I'M JUST
CHECKING.
YOU'RE GOOD, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I'M JUST EMBARRASSED.
>> Jeff: YOU JUST-- YOU
LITERALLY JUST DROPPED PUP FELL
OFF THE CHALLENGE.
>> WELL, THAT'S EMBARRASSING.
>> Jeff: NO, I'D SAY THAT'S A
SIGN OF A WARRIOR.
I CAN TELL EVERYBODY YOU'RE
OKAY?
>> YEAH, I'M GREAT.
>> Jeff: LAWR SEN OKAY.
JUST GET BACK IN THIS.
>> I MEAN, EVEN-- YOU HEAR ERIK
SAYING, "GO, VIC."
NO ONE SAID, "GO, AURORA" AGAIN,
VIC, YOU WANT ME TO TRUST.
>> GOOD LUCK, AURORA.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THAT ONE
COUNTS.
>> Jeff: AND OUT OF NOWHERE,
VICTORIA DROPS.
AURORA DID NOT HAVE TO NEGOTIATE
FOR INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY.
AURORA WINS IMMUNITY.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BOTH WOMEN NOW TRYING TO GET
SOME FEELING BACK IN THEIR LEGS.
( APPLAUSE )
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I'M OKAY.
>> Jeff: AURORA, COME ON OVER.
( APPLAUSE )
AURORA, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTE OUT OF THIS GAME.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, AFTER 22
VERY TOUGH DAYS, SOMEBODY WILL
BECOME THE EIGHTH PERSON VOTED
OUR THE "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION."
IT WON'T BE YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CONGRATS.
>> GREAT JOB.
>> IT WAS REALLY SCARY WHEN I
PASSED OUT, BUT I WAS EVEN MORE
PISSED THAT I WAS ON THE GROUND
BECAUSE THAT MEANS I DIDN'T WIN,
AND IT LEAVES ME VERY, VERY
VULNERABLE
BUT PLAYING MY IDOL IS THE
ABSOLUTE LAST RESORT.
>> YOU GIRLS WERE INCREDIBLE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> THERE'S NOT A BETTER FEELING
THAN GOING INTO A TRIBAL,
KNOWING THAT YOU'RE 100% SAFE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN EVERYTHING
AROUND YOU HAS TOLD YOU LATELY
YOU ARE NOT SAFE.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> SO I GET BACK TO CAMP, AND
I'M HAPPY.
BUT THEN I GO IN MY BAG, AND
THERE IS A PARCHMENT.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE I DON'T HAVE
A PARCHMENT.
SO I IMMEDIATELY SNEAK AWAY.
HMMM, WHAT IS THIS?
"WHEN IT IS TIME TO VOTE, USE
THIS PARCHMENT TO CAST A SECOND
VOTE."
HOLY CRAP.
I LOVE YOU, JOE, OR AUBRY, OR
WHOEVER.
I WENT FROM FEELING LIKE NOT
ACCEPTED, TO THEN HAVING THE
POWER OF AN EXTRA VOTE TO CAST
AT ANY TIME.
IT'S AMAZING.
BUT RIGHT NOW, I'M GOING TO
STICK WITH THE NUMBERS, AND HOLD
MY TONGUE UNTIL IT'S TIME TO
MAKE A MOVE.
>> WE MADE IT, KAMA.
KAMA STRONG, ONE, TWO, THREE.
KAMA STRONG!
IF WE STAY TOGETHER, ALL OF OUR
LOVED ONES COME.
WHAT AN AMAZING JOURNEY WE
STARTED TOGETHER.
LOVED ONE TOGETHERS.
>> ERIK AND I ARE WORKING
TOGETHER TO CONTROL EVERYBODY.
AND WE'RE USING THE LOVED ONE
VISIT AS A THREAT ALMOST BY
SAYING, "DON'T WE ALL WANT TO
HAVE OUR LOVED ONES HERE?"
BY SAYING THAT IT MAKES THEM NOT
FLIP AND TRY TO HAVE ANOTHER
ALLIANCE.
IT'S GENIUS.
>> THE ONLY REASON TO NOT SPLIT
IS IF WE DON'T TRUST SEVEN
PEOPLE STANDING HERE RIGHT NOW.
AND THAT'S WHY I THINK WE SHOULD
SPLIT.
>> I THINK YOU GO-- YOU HAVE TO
GO AFTER KELLEY FIRST.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO GO AFTER THE
GIRLS, YOU HAVE TO GO AFTER
KELLEY.
>> I FIND THE GIRLS A THREAT
OVERALL, BUT LAUREN IS MUCH MORE
PHYSICAL.
>> SHE'S COMPETING VERY WELL.
>> I KNOW THIS KAMA ALLIANCE
WON'T LAST FOREVER.
THINGS ARE GOING TO GET CRAZY,
AND WHEN IT DOES, MYSELF AND RON
HAVE DAVID AND DEVENS IN OUR
POCKET TO MAKE THE BIG MOVE.
BUT IT'S NOT A WORRY FOR TODAY.
LET'S USE OUR NABS WE SO
CRAFTILY ACQUIRED, AND LET'S
SPLIT SOME VOTES, AND LET'S GET
SOME OF THOSE LESU PLAYERS OUT,
STARTING WITH KELLEY.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO CRY.
>> NO, I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE SO HAPPY TO
JUST PICK US ALL OFF, AND THEN
HAVE--
>> THEY'RE NOT LOOKING AT, LIKE,
THE BIGGER PICTURE.
>> THEY'RE NOT.
THEY JUST WANT TO HAVE A CIVIL
WAR AFTER WE'RE ALL GONE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY WANT.
>> WELL, SEE YOU ON EXTINCTION.
>> THAT'S ABOUT PROBABLY THE
SIZE OF IT.
>> THE ORIGINAL KAMA PEOPLE,
ALONG WITH RICK DEVENS, ARE ALL
THIS BIG VOTING BLOC, LIKE
THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE PROBABLY
FOR MYSELF OR LAUREN TONIGHT.
AND IT'S A SCARY THING.
LUCKILY, LAUREN AND I HAVE
IDOLS.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE AN IDOL, IT'S
JUST ABOUT, LIKE A GUT FEELING,
AND HOPING THAT YOU ARE RIGHT.
>> I KNOW THIS IS GOING TO PLAY
OUT.
IT COULD BE ME GOING ORACLEY
GOING HOME, OR LAUREN, BUT THE
SEVEN OF YOU KAMA, THE FINAL
SEVEN AIN'T GOING TO BE SEVEN.
WE HAVE TO GO OUT THERE AND TRY
TO FIND CRACKS.
YOU CAN'T SAY, "OOMS, I TRIED.
IT DIDN'T WORK."
YOU KEEP FIGHTING IN THIS GAME.
LIKE I WANT TO HAVE OPEN
COMMUNICATION WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> SOUND FAIR, RIGHT.
I LOVE TO LEAVE THE LINES OF
COMMUNICATION OPEN.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I'M FEELING LIKE SOMEBODY
IS GOING TO GET EAG OR THE
SEVEN, AND YOU, DAVID, AND
DEVENS ARE THE SOLDIERS IN THEIR
ARMY.
MY BEST STRATEGY IS TO CONVINCE
THOSE YOUNGER KAMA PEOPLE THAT
THEY NEED SOLDIERS FOR A WAR.
BECAUSE ONCE THAT WAR STARTS,
WHO IS DAVID AND DEVENS SIDING
ON?
YOU HAVE TO ASK YOURSELF: DAVID
AND DEVENS, IF THAT WAR GOES
DOWN, AND THEATRE TWO LEFT, ARE
THEY SIDING WITH YOU OR SIDING
WITH RON OR ERIK.
AND THEY GOT THOSE TWO GUYS OFF,
THEY WIN THE GAME.
WHEN IT'S TIME, IF YOU NEED A
SOLDIER, YOU HAVE WARDOG HERE.
>> GOT YOU.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> DIAL HIM UP.
>> WARDOG WAS BREAKING DOWN HIS
PERCEPTION OF THE DYNAMICS OF
KAMA.
SAYING THAT RON AND ERIK ARE
TRYING TO PULL IN DAVID AND
DEVENS, AND STRCIALLY MAKE A
MOVE ON GAVIN, VICTORIA, AND
MYSELF.
AND WARDOG MIGHT HAVE A POINT.
AND I DIDN'T REALIZE IT UNTIL HE
SAID IT.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, ERIK?
>> NOT MUCH.
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TEST
ERIK BY TRYING TO PUSH A DAVID
OR DEVENS VOTE, AND THAT WILL BE
THE TRUE TESTAMENT WHO 2 WHO'S
WORKING WITH WHO.
LET ME RUN SOMETHING PAST YOU.
DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE WISE TO
MAYBE TAKE OUT DAVID BEFORE A
LAUREN OR A KELLEY?
>> YOU MEAN, LIKE, RIGHT NOW?
>> YES.
>>UM, I THINK-- I THINK WE CAN
MAKE IT TILL EIGHT.
IN THE PAST HE WENT TO ROCKS.
IN HIS OLD SEASON.
SO I THINK HE HAS A GOOD TRACK
RECORD OF LOYALTY.
>> WARDOG WAS RIGHT-- THEY ARE
GOING TO TRY TO USE DAVID AND
DEVENS DOWN THE ROAD TO FLIP ON
US KAMA MEMBERS.
>> JUST NO ONE DO ANYTHING
STUPID.
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR FAMILY
VISIT.
>> IT MIGHT BE MY TIME TO MAKE A
BIG MOVE.
>> I FEEL LIKE ERIK, RON, AND
JAIL, AND ME, YOU AND VIC.
I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE TRYING TO
BRING IN DAVID AND DEVENS.
>> IT'S ME, YOU, AND VIC VOTE
WITH WARDOG--
>> HOLD ON.
>> AND KELLEY, WE CAN TAKE OUT
WHOEVER WE WANT.
>> WHAT IF, LIKE, WE DO THIS
VOTE, AND TAKE OUT ERIK, AND
THEN--
>> WHY NOT RON?
( WHISTLES ).
>> EARE, IC AND RON SAYING,
"WE'VE GOT TO GET TO THE FAMILY
VISIT."
IT WAS LIKE AN EPIPHANY.
I HAVE TO WIN FOR MY FAMILY, AND
THAT'S WHY I'M STEPPING MY GAME
UP AND COMING IN WITH GUNS
BLATION.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN THIS GAME
IF WE DON'T MAKE BIG MOVES LIKE
THIS.
I'M TELLING YOU, IT'S THE BEST
MOVE FOR US.
>> I'M IN.
>> SO HERE'S MY THEORY: WHAT IF
THEY'RE KEEPING DAVID AND DEVENS
TO FLIP ON KAMA.
>> IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL, THEN
WE JUST MAKE SURE WE GET OUT
DAVID SECOND.
>> VIC'S NOT DOWN WITH THE
SHENANIGANS.
>> YOU'RE NOT.
>> SHE SAID IT'S TOO SOON.
>> I JUST THINK YOU GO ONE VOTE
BEFORE YOU DO ANY OF THIS.
I DO.
>> EVERY DECISION, EVERY OPTION
CARRIES SOME RISK IN THIS GAME.
TONIGHT, WE CAN STAY KAMA
STRONG, AND IT CAN BE AN EASY
VOTE TAKING OUT KELLEY.
OR WE CAN PULL IN THE PEOPLE AT
THE BOTTOM, AND WE CAN MAKE A
BIG MOVE NOW.
AND TARGET RON OR ERIC.
THEY'VE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF THE
POWER THAT THIS ALLIANCE HAS
GOTTEN.
BUT THE BAD PART FOR THEM IS
THAT WE REALIZE IT.
AND THEY MIGHT BE AT THE WRONG
SIDE OF THE VOTE COME TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
>> Jeff: ERIC, ONE OF THE BIG
TOPICS AT THE LAST TRIBAL WAS
THE DOMINANCE OF KAMA.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT COMES
WITH THAT IS YOU HAVE TO
NAVIGATE THE RELATIONSHIPS THAT
CAN WIN OR LOSE A GAME.
>> WELL, TONIGHT, THE KAMA SEVEN
HAD A BEACH-FRONT ROUNDTABLE,
AND WE CAME UP WITH A GROUP
DECISION.
>> Jeff: BUT THAT STILL LEAVES
FIVE PEOPLE NOT IN.
HOW DO YOU NAVIGATE THOSE
RELATIONSHIPS?
>> WELL, I THINK THESE LESU
MEMBERS, THEY COME IN PACKAGES.
AND SO, YOU NAVIGATE THEM
CAREFULLY, OF COURSE.
>> I LIKE THAT TERMINOLOGY,
"PACKAGES," BECAUSE THIS PACKAGE
I'M PART OF WASN'T GIVEN ANY
KIND OF MARCHING ORDERS, SO
MAYBE THE OTHER PACKAGE IS MORE
IN WITH THE KAMA SEVEN THAN I
AM.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, WERE YOU
AWARE OF THE KAMA SEVEN HAVING
THEIR BEACH-SIDE CHAT?
>> YES, THEY DIDN'T TRY TO KEEP
IT A SECRET, AND THEY KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE I STAND.
I WAS OUT OF LESU'S FIVE AS SOON
AS I WAS VOTED OUT OF LESU'S
FIVE.
SO THE TRUST FACTOR FROM LESU IS
PRETTY MESSED UP.
>> OKAY, OKAY, DEVENS, OKAY,
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
>> I MEAN, STRAIGHT UP.
>> I HAVE NO REASON TO LIE.
I'M ALREADY AGAINST YOU GUYS, SO
I'M DOING EVERYTHING I CAN TO
GET ON THE KAMA TRAIN.
>> Jeff: DAVID, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT DEVENS IS TALK ABOUT.
>> DEVYNS AND I WERE SPARED LAST
VOTE.
THEY SAVED US.
WE ARE STAY TAIJ IN THE GAME
WHERE EVERYONE UP HERE HAS TO
DECIDE SOON WHETHER OR NOT THEY
WANT TO BE A PILOT OR A
PASSENGER.
AND A PILOT WINS AT THE END.
WITH THE NUMBERS BEING WHAT THEY
ARE, I AM A PASSENGER TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: ERIC, WHAT DOES THAT
SAY TO YOU?
>> IT'S A MESSAGE, RIGHT, IT'S A
MESSAGE TO THE KAMA SEVEN THAT
SAYS, "SOME OF YOU MAY WANT TO
CONSIDER YOUR POSITION IN THE
TRIBE."
>> BUT, HONESTLY, YOU HAVE TO
AVOID PARANOIA, AND YOU HAVE TO
STAY STRONG, AND THE LONGER YOU
CAN KEEP THAT ALLIANCE TOGETHER
WHERE PEOPLE TRUST EACH OTHER,
THE STRONGER YOU'RE GOING TO BE,
AND THE LONGER YOU LAST.
>> AND I WILL SAY MAYBE IT
DOESN'T FEEL GREAT TO FEEL LIKE
A PASSENGER, BUT I KNOW FROM
TALKING TO EVERYONE UP HERE HOW
MUCH WE ALL WANT TO SEE OUR
LOVED ONES.
SO WHY DON'T WE STAY FOCUSED
HERE, GET A COUPLE OF VOTES DOWN
THE ROAD--
>> ARE WE PLAYING FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS OR JUST PLAYING TO GET
TO THE LOVED ONES VISITS.
BY THEN, THE OTHER LESU PACKAGES
WILL BE GONE, AND MAYBE YOU
CAN'T MAKE A MOVE THEN.
>> IT'S CRAZY FOR ME TO BE
SAYING I'M AGREEING WITH WARDOG
ON A PARTICULAR POINT HERE.
GETTING TO THE LOVED ONES VISIT
SAY BENCHMARK AND IT'S IMPORTANT
TO EVERYBODY AND YOU CRAVE IT.
BUT IF YOU AREN'T CAREFUL YOU'LL
FIND YOURSELF ON DAY 39 WAY
BLANK RESUME.
THERE ARE LOTS OF BLANK SHEETS
OF PAPER SITTING UP HERE RIGHT
NOW WITH MAYBE ONLY THEIR NAMES
AND ADDRESSES.
AND A LOT OF THOSE ADDRESSES
READ, "44, 44, EDGE OF
EXTINCTION DRIVE."
>> Jeff: JULIA, IS IT TO BE
AMOUNTED THAT AT SOME POINT,
YES, WE ARE GOING TO MAKE A
MOVE.
WE HAVE TO.
THERE ARE ONLY SO MANY SPOTS AT
THE FINAL.
>> I THINK IT'S ON EVERYONE'S
MIND.
AND WHETHER OR NOT THERE OF
THEY'RE WILLING TO MAKE A MOVE
RIGHT NOW IS WHERE THEY'RE
WAVERING.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, ARE YOU IN
LINE WITH THAT?
IS EVERYBODY THINKING THAT ON
SOME LEVEL?
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF WHEN DO I
MAKE MY MOVE?
>> JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE THINKING
ABOUT IT DOESN'T MEAN NOW WITH
12 PEOPLE STILL IN THE GAME IS
WHEN YOU MAKE YOUR MOVE.
SHOOT YOUR SHOT AS LONG AS
YOU'RE NOT SHOOTING YOURSELF IN
THE FOOT.
I WANT TO KEEP MY FEET TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: RON, WHAT DO YOU SAY
TONIGHT TO MAKE SURE PEOPLE
DON'T MAKE THE MOVE?
>> FOR ME, PERSONALLY, I
WOULDN'T WANT TO GO WITH ALL OF
THE LESU MEMBERS RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE I KNOW THEY'RE PUT ME ON
THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: AND, YET, ARE YOU
FULLY OPEN FOR BUSINESS IF
PEOPLE WANT TO JOIN YOUR
ALLIANCE.
>> YES.
WE HAVE LIMITED SPACES ONLY FOR
A LIMITED TIME ONLY.
>> THERE'S NO SPACE FOR ME,
LAUREN, AND WENTWORTH.
THAT'S PRETTY CLEAR.
>> Jeff: AURORA, WHAT'S YOUR
MOOD RIGHT NOW?
BECAUSE YOU'RE WEARING THE
IMMUNITY NECKLACE, BUT UNTIL
JUST THAT MOMENT, YOU HAD HAD
NOT THE LEAST BIT OF A SMILE.
IT WAS A SCOWL.
>> I MEAN, THERE'S A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT HOW STRONG KAMA IS AND HOW
WE REALLY HAVE TAKEN CONTROL OF
THIS GAME.
BUT IF YOU LOOK, IT'S NOT THAT
WE'VE TAKEN CONTROL OF THE GAME.
IT'S THAT EVERYONE WHO'S NOT IN
THIS KAMA STRONG HAS LITERALLY
FALL TONE PIECES.
EVERYONE HAS THE CHANCE TO TAKE
CONTROL OF THIS GAME.
IT'S JUST WHO'S GOING TO
ACTUALLY DECIDE TO DO IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO VOTE.
WENTWORTH, YOU'RE UP.
>> KELLEY, SOMETIMES YOU'RE JUST
ON THE WRONG SIDE OF THE
NUMBERS.
TONIGHT, THAT'S YOU.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
>> Jeff: FIRST VOTE,
WENTWORTH.
LAUREN.
THAT'S TWO VOTES LAUREN.
WENTWORTH.
THAT'S TWO VOTES WENTWORTH.
ERIC.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES LAUREN,
TWO VOTES WENTWORTH, TWO VOTES
ERIC.
THAT'S THREE VOTES ERIC, TWO
VOTES LAUREN, TWO VOTES
WENTWORTH.
ERIC.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES ERIC.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES ERIC.
EIGHTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, ERIC.
THAT'S SIX.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> BRAVO!
MAN!
YOU GUYS ARE GOOD!
ERIC, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> WHAT A FUN EXPERIENCE.
HOPE SEE YOU SOON.
>> BY ERIC.
.
( SIGHS )
>> COME ON!
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR":
IN A FIGHT FOR THE FUTURE--
>> HOW DO WE MOVE FORWARD?
>> WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO
GETS CUSTODY OF OUR HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> THEY'RE TRYING TO BAMBOOZLE
US.
>> Jeff: CAN COME BACK TO
HAUNT YOU WOW!
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
IT.
>> YEAH, THEY GOT ME PRETTY
GOOD.
SOMEBODY MOUNTED SOMETHING, SO
HERE I AM ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT IT'S HARD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY DAYS I
HAVE TO BE HERE, BUT I HAVE A
SENSE THIS IS GOING TO BE THE
CRUCIBLE OF INTERNAL STRUGGLE.
HEY, THIS IS BETTER THAN I
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
>> DUDE, DON'T GET EXCITED.