Jeff: PREVIOUSLY ON
"SURVIVOR," AT THE MANU TRIBE,
WENDY WAS MAKING ENEMIES.
WENDY LET THE CHICKENS GO.
SHE KIND OF WENT NUTS.
AT THE KAMA TRIBE, JOE
THOUGHT HE WAS MAKING FRIENDS.
I FEEL GREAT WITH YOU, BRO.
I FEEL GREAT WITH YOU, TOO.
I ACTED LIKE I LOVE HIM, BUT
HES A RETURNING PLAYER, AND HE
CAN BE REALLY DANGEROUS.
Jeff: AT THE LESU TRIBE,
DAVID AND DEVON SAW EYE TO EYE.
IM NOT GOING TO WRITE YOUR
NAME DOWN NO MATTER WHAT.
Jeff: AND SO DID LAUREN AND
KELLEY.
I WANT TO VOTE WITH YOU.
YEAH, I WANT TO VOTE WITH
YOU.
Jeff: LEAVING WARDOG IN THE
MIDDLE.
ITS CLASSIC.
IM IN A SWING-VOTE SPOT.
Jeff: AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WARDOG MADE UP HIS MINE.
DEVON, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
Jeff:LEAVING DEVENS WITH A DE
TO MAKE.
GRAB A TORCH AND GO TO THE EDGE
OF DISTINCTION OR GO HOME.
I WAS VOTED OUT LAST NIGHT.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING HOME AND
EATING A BURGER AND DRINKING A
BEER.
I GET THROWN ON TO THE EDGE OF
DISTINCTION WITH THREE PEOPLE
WHO ARE SO HAPPY I FAILED.
EVERYTHING ABOUT EDGE OF
DISTINCTION, STARTING WITH THAT
BIG MAP JUST SAYS, YOU DONT
WANT TO BE HERE, YOURE NOT
GOING TO ENJOY YOURSELF, ITS
GOING TO SUCK.
YOU OKAY?
BUT TO ME ITS JUST ANOTHER
TEST PUT IN FRONT OF YOU WHERE
ITS LIKE, DO YOU HAVE THE
FORTITUDE TO GO INTO SOMETHING
YOU KNOW NOTHING ABOUT AND SEE
IT THROUGH AND COME OUT ON TOP?ñ
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
KAMA, MANU GETTING YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE NEW LESU TRIBE.
DEVENS VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO TODAYS REWARD
CHALLENGE?
YES.
Jeff: FOR TODAYS
CHALLENGE, YOULL RACE THROUGH A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES COLLECTING
BOLOS ALONG THE WAY.
YOULL THEN ATTEMPT TO LAND
THOSE BOLOS ON A TARGET.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR?
OH, YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH, A LITTLE SOMETHING FROM
HOME.
OH, MY GOSH.
Jeff: PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY, PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY,
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH PLUS A JAR
OF PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY, LOAF
OF BREAD AND ICE COLD MILK.
SECOND TRIBE TO FINISH, NOT AS
MUCH, A SMALL PLATE OF P.B. AND
J.
LAST TRIBE TO FINISH, NOTHING.
KAMA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
SITTING SOMEONE OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE IN.
ILL SIT.
Jeff: EULA, TAKE A SPOT ON
THE BENCH.
MANU, ONE EXTRA PERSON.
AUBRY, TAKE A SPOT ON THE BENCH.
EVERYBODY ELSE, TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AND WELL GET GOING.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH THE
ROPE BRAMBLE.
NOTHING EASY ABOUT THIS.
LAUNCH YOURSELF THROUGH IT.
JULIE COMES OUT.
WENDY IS THROUGH.
WARDOG IS THROUGH.
WENTWORTH IS THROUGH.
MANU, YOURE GOOD.
START WORKING.
KAMA, YOURE GOOD.
LESU, YOURE GOOD.
YOU GOT TO LIFT SOMEONE UP TO
GET THE TWO BOLOS.
DAVID ALMOST DROPPED BY HIS
TRIBE.
HOLD ME.
Jeff: DAVID STRUGGLING
AGAIN.
JULIE HAS THE FIRST FOR KAMA.
VICTORIA HAS THE FIRST FOR MANU.
THIS GROUP OF FOUR ON LESU
CONTINUES TO STRUGGLE IN EVERY
CHALLENGE.
DAVID GOES DOWN HARD.
YOURE GOOD, MANU.
YOURE GOOD, KAMA.
NOW YOU GOT TO CRAWL TO GET YOUR
NEXT TWO BOLOS.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
Jeff: NOW ITS LAUREN
TRYING TO GET UP.
ABSOLUTE DISASTER FOR LESU.
THEY FINALLY HAVE LAUREN OUT.
GO, GO!
Jeff: KAMA HAS YOUR NEXT
TWO.
YOU CAN START THROWING, KAMA.
MANU HAS THEIR FOUR.
YOURE GOOD, MANU.
EVERY TRIBE MEMBER HAS TO LAND
ONE BOLO.
GOT TO THROW WAY HARDER.
Jeff: LAUREN STILL WORKING
ON THAT LAST BOLO.
SHES GOT IT.
DAMMIT, WARDOG.
Jeff: AND A BIG FALL BY
LAUREN.
GAVINS FIRST FOR MANU.
THEIR FIRST.
LESU FIGHTING TO STAY IN THIS
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY
CHALLENGE.
GO, WARDOG!
Jeff: WENTWORTH IS THROUGH.
WARDOG.
YOURE GOOD, LESU.
START THROWING.
IT IS MANU WITH ONE.
NOBODY ELSE ON THE BOARD.
LAUREN TOSSES.
SHE JUST MISSES.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: AURORA ON AND OFF.
ERIC WITH A NICE TOUCH.
AND THAT WILL WORK.
RON NOW UP FOR KAMA.
RON WITHçó A NICE TOSS.
THAT WILL HOOK.
RON HAS THE FIRST FOR KAMA.
JOE WITH ONE TOSS LANDS THE
SECOND.
YOU HAVE TO LAND FOUR.
WENDY SCORES THE THIRD FOR MANU.
IT IS NOW MANU WITH THREE AND
KAMA WITH TWO.
LESU STILL WITH NOTHING.
CAN I GO YET?
Jeff: THERE GOES DAVID NOW
TRYING TO GET INTO IT FOR LESU.
DAVID JUST MISSES.
DAVID SPRINTING BACK TO GET HIS
BOLO.
VICTORIA FOR THE WIN.
NICE AND SOFT BUT GOING TO FALL
SHORT.
AURORA SCORES THE THIRD FOR
KAMA.
IT IS NOW MANU WITH THREE AND
KAMA WITH THREE.
IT IS VICTORIA VERSUS JULIE FOR
THE WIN.
JUST SHORT.
JULIE CAN WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
AND SHE DOES!
KAMA WINS REWARD.
WERE LOOKING FOR SECOND.
WENTWORTH LAUNCHES AND STICKS
IT.
VICTORIA FOR THE WIN.
JUST MISSES.
GUYS, IM SO TIRED.
Jeff: WARDOG NOW IN.
AND HE SNAGS THE SECOND FOR
LESU.
SUDDENLY LESU IS BACK IN IT.
HERE GOES LAUREN.
JUST SHORT.
FOR THE WIN, VICTORIA.
AND SHE DOES IT!
MANU WINS REWARD, PEANUT BUTTER
AND JELLY, LEAVING LESU EMPTY
HANDED ONCE AGAIN.
KAMA, THE FIVE OF YOU HAVE LOST
ONE CHALLENGE THIS ENTIRE
SEASON.
BIG VICTORY TODAY.
HUGE REWARD OF P.B. AND J WILL
BE WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BECOME AND
ENJOY IT.
MANU, NICE VICTORY FOR YOU.
YOUR P.B. AND J. WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ENJOY THE AFTERNOON.
THANKS, JEFF.
Jeff: WOW.
YEAH.
I THINK WERE RUNNING OUT OF
ADJECTIVES TO DESCRIBE THESE
DEFEATS.
ITS ALMOST LIKE WERE CURSED OR
SOMETHING.
WE HAVE TO THINK POSITIVE, AND
WE KEEP GOING BACK AND SAYING
THAT, WE HAVE TO THINK POSITIVE.
ITS THE ONLY WAY OUT OF THIS.
Jeff: INTERESTING.
I DIDNT EVEN ASK A QUESTION.
YOU ALREADY KNOW THE STORY THAT
IS UNFOLDING.
ALL RIGHT.
LESU, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOD, LIKE HOW BAD CAN WE BE?
YOU HAVE DAVID, WHO BASICALLY
ACTS AS A FEMALE.
I MEAN, HE WEIGHS LESS THAN ME.
BASICALLY WE HAVE THREE GIRLS
AND WARDOG.
SO IM JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO, BECAUSE WE CANT WIN
ANYTHING.
ONE, TWO, THREE, KAMA!
WINNING THAT REWARD JUST
SHOWED US ONCE AGAIN THAT THE
KAMA TRIBE IS A FORCE TO BE
RECKONED WITH IN THIS GAME.
WE ARE COMPLETELY DOMINATING AND
WERE ON THIS WINNING STREAK.
LOVE YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
YOU GUYS KILLED THAT.
UH-HUH.
HOWEVER, IT IS IN THE BACK OF
MY MIND THAT JOE IS THE BIGGEST
THREAT IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW, SO
I WOULD RATHER GET HIM OUT OF
THIS GAME SOONER RATHER THAN
LATER.
HOW LUCKY ARE WE?
WERE SPOILED.
WERE ALL LOVE AND SUNSHINE
AND SPRINKLES AND RAINBOWS RIGHT
NOW ON KAMA STRONG, BUT ITS
PRETTY OBVIOUS THAT IM A BIG
TARGET AND THAT IM A CHALLENGE
BEAST, SO IT SUCKS.
ITS REALLY DIFFICULT TO TRY TO
SHAKE THAT STIGMA.
SO IM JUST TRYING TO DO
ANYTHING I CAN TO MAKE IT
COMFORTABLE FOR MY TRIBE MATES,
MAKE THEM FEEL LIKE THEY NEED ME
SO THAT IM NOT THE ONE GOING
HOME.
WHERES JOE RIGHT NOW?
AT THE BEACH.
THIS IS LIKE OUR ONE SHOT TO
GET HIM OUT PREMERGE PROBABLY.
JOES DANGEROUS.
BUT THERE THREE OF US, IF WE CAN
BLIND SIDE HIM, IT WOULD BE
HUGE.
IM IN A GOOD SITUATION
GAME-WISE.
AND SINCE DAY ONE, I KEPT
TELLING EVERYONE WE HAVE TO GET
RID OF JOE, BUT NOW I HAVE
ANOTHER CONSIDERATION.
JOE IS A WORKHORSE.
I MEAN, HE KNOWS EVERYTHING, AND
A LOT OF OUR PEOPLE ON OUR TRIBE
DO NOT.
WERE NOT CATCHING THE FISH.
AND WERE NOT GETTING ALL THE
FOOD.
WE DONT KNOW WHAT TO DO.
AND SO IM STARTING TO REALIZE,
I DONT LIKE THE THOUGHT OF CAMP
WITHOUT JOE.
I THINK ILL BE MISERABLE.
JOE IS ALLOWING US TO WIN ALL
THESE CHALLENGES SO WE DONT
HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL.
IF WE ARE WITHOUT JOE, WERE
PROBABLY GOING TO LOSE THEM.
WE CAN SURVIVE WITHOUT HIM.
WE CANT LET HIM KEEP MAKING A
CASE OF WHY HE SHOULD WIN IF
HES DONE EVERYTHING.
TRUE.
JOE CANNOT GO TOO FAR IN THIS
GAME.
THATS A NO-BRAINER.
AND IM VERY CONCERNED THAT THE
FOUR RETURNING PLAYERS ARE ALL
STILL IN THE GAME.
COME MERGE, HES GOING TO BE
SO HARD TO GET OUT OF THIS GAME.
BUT WHEN HE DOESNT SEE IT
COMING...
IF YOU DONT GET RID OF
RETURNING PLAYERS, BY THE TIME
THE MERGE HITS, THEY COULD RUN
AWAY WITH THE WHOLE THING, SO IF
WE WERE TO LOSE IMMUNITY, JOE
HAS TO GO NOW.
SO P.B. AND J. POWERS
ACTIVATE.
CHEERS.
READY?
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY, ITS
LIKE A FLAVOR CHANGE, SOME
PROTEIN.
ITS PRETTY GOOD, BUT IM SO
HUNGRY TODAY.
TODAY IS FIRST DAY IM LIKE REAL
HUNGRY.
YEAH.
I FEEL LIKE IF WE CANT FISH,
WE SHOULD EAT A CHICKEN.
IF I SEE ONE, ILL GRAB ONE.
WENDY DOESNT WANT US TO EAT THE
CHICKENS.
SO THEYRE FREE RANGE.
THEYRE PART OF THE ISLAND.
AS LONG AS THEY DONT END UP
DEAD.
I FEEL LIKE WORKING WITH
WENDY WOULD BE MORE LIKE
CARRYING AROUND AN ALARM CLOCK,
BUT YOU HAVE NO CLUE WHEN ITS
GOING TO GO OFF, BUT THERE IS AN
ISSUE OF THE RETURNERS.
THE LONGER THEYRE IN THE GAME,
THE MORE DANGEROUS IT GETS.
SO LIKE ALL THINGS IN THIS GAME,
ITS A BALANCING ACT.
LIKE THEYRE GONE AND THEYRE
OUT THERE AND IT BOTHERS ME THAT
THEYRE OUT THERE.
WERE IN THE "SURVIVOR" WAITING
ROOM RIGHT NOW ON THE MANU
TRIBE.
WE HAVENT GONE TO TRIBAL YET.
NOTHING HAS HAPPENED, AND WERE
TALKING ABOUT CHICKENS.
ITS SO FRUSTRATING.
LIKE "SURVIVOR," THERE ARE MANY
GHOSTS IN THE JUNGLE IN FIJI.
I AM DYING TO PLAY.
I CAME IN AGGRESSIVE.
I FOUND MY IDOL.
AND I KIND OF SIMMERED DOWN.
NOW WE GOT TO HEAT THE DISH BACK
UP, SO WHAT IM TRYING TO DO IS
FIGURE OUT WHO THE STRATEGISTS
ARE AND FIND MYSELF ONE THAT IS
GOING TO BE ABLE TO WAKE UP FROM
THE KAMA KOOL-AID AND DO
SOMETHING ABOUT EVERYTHING COME
THE MERGE.
WOULD YOU RATHER GO INTO THE
MERGE WITH AUBRY OR WITH WENDY?
I THINK ID RATHER GO WITH
WENDY JUST BECAUSE SHES LESS OF
A STRATEGIC THREAT.
WHAT IF I WENT TO AUBRY AND
SAID, DO YOU WANT TO DO A GIRLS
THING, SO IF SHE DOES HAVE AN
IDOL, SHE WOULD LITERALLY NEVER
PLAY HER IDOL.
IT WOULD MAKE ME BELIEVE MORE
IM NOT WITH YOU GUYS.
IT FEELS LIKE THE SAFEST WAY TO
PLACATE AND.
AND THEN SHE WOULD FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE.
I THINK IT WOULD BE A GOOD
DIVERSION.
I THINK WE TELL WENDY, SAY,
LETS JUST TELL HER --
I THINK ITS IN OUR BEST
INTEREST TO GET RID OF AUBRY
FIRST WHEN SHE DOESNT SEE IT
COMING.
AS A PERSON, I REALLY LIKE
AUBRY, BUT FOR ME, IT MIGHT
SOUND BO BAD, BUT I HAVE NO
PROBLEM SEPARATING FRIENDSHIPS
FROM THE GAME.
LIKE I DONT REALLY CARE ABOUT
HOW PEOPLE FEEL OUT HERE, BUT
NOW I HAVE TO KEEP AUBRY
THINKING THAT IM ON HER SIDE.
LIKE I HAVE NO CLUE WHAT JEFF
HAS IN STORE, AND EVERYBODY HERE
IS LIKE, I DONT KNOW UNLESS IM
MISSING SOMETHING MAJOR, PEOPLE
ARE REALLY CALM, WHICH IS GOOD.
YEAH, I THINK EVERYONE IS
CALM, BECAUSE WE HAVE OUR BUFFER
VOTE.
YEAH.
I THINK SO FOR SURE.Ñi
BUT YOU HAVE SEEN "SURVIVOR."
YOU KNOW ITS LIKE...
NOTHING IS GOING TO BE THIS
EASY.
ITS GOING TO GET WEIRD.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE WHERE YOUR
HEAD WAS AT.
WOULD IT MAKE SENSE WHILE WE
STILL HAVE WENDY, TO DO
SOMETHING WITH WENDY, ME AND
YOU, ME YOU AND WENDY.
WE COULD.
BECAUSE IF WE GET RID OF LIKE
AN ERIC IN THE NEXT VOTE AND
GAVIN AFTER THAT.
VICTORIA SAID, WE HAVE TO GO
AFTER THE BIG BOYS SOONER OR
LATER, AND I WAS PSYCHED TO HEAR
HER SAY THAT.
I THINK YOURE THE ONLY ONE I
TRUST EVEN A LITTLE BIT RIGHT
NOW.
VICK WAS JUST UNDER MY NOSE.
SHES BEEN SNEAKY THE WHOLE
TIME.
THOSE GLASSES MAY BE BIG.
MAYBE I DIDNT SEE HER EYES
OPEN.
WERE THE MISFITS THAT
COULDNT.
OBVIOUSLY THE TRIBE IS IN
NEED OF A SERIOUS PICK-ME-UP.
I WAS THINKING IF YOU AND I WANT
TO TRY TO GO FISHING.
IVE NEVER FISHED BEFORE IN
MY LIFE.
HONESTLY, IM HALF FULL OF RICE.
I HAVE NO CALORIES.
OKAY.
THATS FAIR.
THIS TRIBE IS SO ON THE EDGE OF
DISTINCTION THAT SCIENTISTS
STOPPED LOOKING FOR US.
THEY ALREADY THINK WERE DEAD.
WERE LIKE THE LAST FOUR DODO
BIRDS LIVING ON A REMOTE ISLAND,
AND I THINK IM NEXT SHOULD WE
LOSE THE NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
ILL TRY TO FIND SNAILS.
IF I KNOW MY "SURVIVOR" HISTORY
AT ALL, THERE IS ABSOLUTELY A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL ON THE NEW
LESU TRIBE.
FINDING IT IS CRITICAL.
ITS SO FRUSTRATING.
BECAUSE I NEED IT BAD.
I LOOK AROUND AT ALL MY PEERS
BACK HOME, AND THEYRE MARRIED
AND THEY HAVE KIDS.
AND ITS SOMETHING THAT KIND OF
ESCAPED ME FOR YEARS.
IM 44 YEARS OLD.
ALL I HAVE IS A TWO-BEDROOM
APARTMENT AND SOME D.V.D.s ON
A SHELF.
BUT I NEED TO SHAKE THAT.
I NEED TO SHAKE THAT IN MY LIFE
AND I NEED TO SHAKE THAT IN THIS
GAME.
IT WASNT UNTIL I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" THE FIRST TIME THAT I
THINK I REALLY STARTED TO GET UP
OFF THE COUCH AND START LIVING
MY LIFE AGAIN.
ITS TIME TO BUILD ON THAT AND
MOVE FORWARD RATHER THAN JUST
STAY IN THIS ONE SPOT.
SO I ABSOLUTELY WANT THE FIND
THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I KEEP LOOKING AND I KEEP COMING
UP SHORT.
BUT I WILL NEVER GIVE UP IN THIS
GAME.
HES THE BIGGEST PROBLEM IN
EVERY CHALLENGE.
HE CANT GO OFF BY HIMSELF.
WE CANT TRUST HIM.
I HAVE BEEN SO SICK.
LUCKILY WARDOG IS ON MY SIDE.
KELLEY IS ON MY SIDE.
AND I HAVE AN IDOL FROM THE
ORIGINAL MANU.
SO IF WE GO TO ANOTHER TRIBAL,
ITS GOING TO BE DAVID.
OKAY.
HERES WHAT IM THINKING.
I THINK THAT ME AND YOU MAKE
THE BEST COMBO POST-MERGE.
I REALLY DO.
ONE MAJOR CONCERN IS A DAVID
IDOL.
YES.
OKAY.
THE SECOND MAJOR CONCERN IS IN
THE BECOME OF MY MIND, IF ITS
ME, YOU, AND LAUREN, IM
THINKING THAT LAUREN AND YOU
MIGHT TAKE ME OUT.
AND YOURE THINKING LAUREN AND
ME MIGHT TAKE YOU OUT.
LAUREN JUST HURTS US.
I THINK ME AND YOU VOTE LAUREN
OUT NOW.
WARDOG IS A CRAZY MAN.
I THINK HE HAS A LITTLE TONY IN
HIM, BUT IF WE DO LOSE, THAT
SEEMS TO BE A TREND ON THIS
TRIBE, ITS ALWAYS IMPORTANT TO
HAVE AN A, B, AND C PLAN.
I DO HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH LAUREN AND I WANT TO WORK
WITH HER, BUT I FEEL LIKE WARDOG
HAS BEEN TRUTHFUL WITH ME SO
FAR.
HES BEEN THE ONE WHO COMES TO
ME WITH IDEAS, AND DESPERATE
TIMES CALL FOR DESPERATE
MEASURES.
SO I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT A GAME
PLAN THATS GOING TO WORK FOR ME
MOVING FORWARD.
WE TAKE HER OUT.
YOURE AN EVIL MASTERMIND.
ITS "SURVIVOR," AND ITS KILL
OR BE KILLED.
THERES SOMETHING HERE.
THIS IS THE MOST EXCITING THING
THATS HAPPENED IN THE LAST FIVE
DAYS.
WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
OH, WE HAVE NEWS.
WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
WE HAVE INFORMATION.
WE HAVE NEWS.
ALL RIGHT.
IM GOING TO COLLECT WOOD, AND I
FIND THIS BOX.
OH, MY GOD.
AND ITS GOT SOMETHING FOR EACH
OF US.
FINALLY.
HALLELUJAH.
ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION,
YOU HAVE LITERALLY NOTHING SOME
AS SOON AS CHRIS CAME AROUND THE
CORNER WITH THAT BOX,ER KNEW.
I FREAKED.
THIS IS SOMETHING NEW, SOME MORE
INFORMATION.
I WAS LIKE SOME WAY OR SOMEHOW
SOMETHING IS GOING THE HAPPEN IN
MY FAVOR.
YOURE ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
YOUR GOAL IS TO GET BACK IN THE
FOLD.
IF THE STARS ALIGN, THEYLL
POINT THE WAY.
YOUR GOAL IS TO GET BACK IN
THE FOLD.
IF THE STARS ALIGN, THEYLL
POINT THE WAY.
BACK IN THE FOLD.
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FOLD IT SO
THE STARS ALIGN?
WHERE ARE STARS?
ON THE BORDER?
I FIGURED THE MAP OUT REALLY
QUICK.
THE STARS ON THE BORDER MATCH UP
WITH EACH OTHER.
AND YOU CAN SEE THAT IT MAKES
THE ARROW POINT RIGHT TO THIS
TREE WITH NO LEAVES.
THEN ON THE OTHER SIDE, THIS
ARROW POINTS RIGHT TO THIS TREE
WITH LOTS OF DIFFERENT ROOTS.
SO IT MIGHT BE MY PROUDEST
MOMENT ON "SURVIVOR" SO FAR.
ITS POINTING TO THE TREE.
WERE GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE A
PACT WE GO ALL TOGETHER.
AM I RIGHT?
I AGREE.
YOU WANT TO HAVE RICE FIRST?
WE MIGHT AS WELL.
THATS NOT TO.
RICK FIGURED OUT THE MAP.
TO BE HONEST, I WAS NOT GOING TO
FIGURE OUT THAT MAP.
THAT WHOLE FOLDING THE THING
TOGETHER, THAT NEVER WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
THIS IS TASTY.
THIS IS GOOD.
THIS SPOON IS HALF BROKEN,
BUT ITS LIKE MY OWN LITTLE
LEFT-HANDED SPOON.
THANK YOU FOR THE RICE, REEM.
ITS GOOD TO HAVE A MOM ON
YOUR TRIBE.
EVERYBODY SAID WERE GOING TO
GO FAIR AND SQUARE.
I WAS LIKE, WHAT?
I WAS LIKE, THATS NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
WHERE IS KEITH?
WHERE IS HE?
DID HE HAVE HIS SHOES ON.
KEITH, GET BACK HERE.
KEITH?
KEITH!
GO DOWN THERE AND SEE IF HES
WALKING DOWN THERE.
IS HE GOING?
YEAH.
HES WAY DOWN THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
DID HE GO?
YES, HE WENT.
KEITH, YOU JERK.
DARN IT, THAT IS SO -- YOU
KNOW WHAT, THAT IS
DISAPPOINTING, DUDE.
SHOES ON.
WOW, KEITH, WHAT AN --
HURRY UP.
YOU GUYS HAVE THE MAP?
YES.
WERE COMING FOR YOU, KEITH.
WHAT A GUY.
THE PATH IS GOING TO SPLIT,
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY WE VOTED
HIM OUT.
KEITH!
I GOT TO FIND IT.
COME ON, GOD, COME ON, GOD, COME
ON, GOD.
IS HE THERE?
WHAT THE HELL, KEITH?
THIS IS FOR FAMILY.
ITS NOT FOR CHRIS.
ITS NOT FOR REEM.
KEITH, YOU DOG.
YOU GOT HIM.
NOT COOL.
YOU GOT IT, CHRIS?
YES.
I LOOK IN THE TREE.
I PULL OUT THREE BAMBOO RODS.
THERES STRING ATTACHED TO THESE
RODS.
AND THERES A NOTE.
PRACTICE.
IT SAYS PRACTICE ON IT.
THIS IS THE FIRST EXCITING CLUE
TO WHAT WERE GOING TO BE DOING
NEXT.
MY GUESS, ITS GOT TO BE
SOMETHING YOU PRACTICE WITH TO
GET BACK INTO THE GAME.
MY MOVE IS TO BE THAT PERSON.
RICK, WHY DID I FOLD THAT MAP
RIGHT IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY?
CHRIS, YOU WILL WAIT FOR ME,
RIGHT?
YES.
I GOT IT.
CHRIS RAN TO ONE TREE.
I RAN TO THE OTHER.
WE HAD THE ADVANTAGES IN OUR
HANDS.
YOU HAVE EARNED THE RIGHT TO
GIVE THIS EXTRA VOTE TO ANY
PLAYER HEADING NOT NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THEY WILL NOT KNOW IT IS FROM
YOU.
CHOOSE WISELY.
SO I FOUND AN ADVANTAGE THEY
CAN GIVE ONE PERSON HEADING TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AN EXTRA VOTE.
WHOEVER GETS THIS VOTE, THEY
HAVE NO IDEA THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION EXISTS.
THATS PRETTY GOOD FOR
WHOEVER GETS IT.
IT WAS A WAKE-UP CALL THAT
WERE ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION,
BUT WERE NOT OUT OF THE GAME,
SO IM PLAYING OUT HERE NOW.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAYS
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
YEAH.
Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST, I
GOT TO TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
OH.
Jeff: SORRY.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE IT UP.
ITS PART OF THE GAME.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO SWIM OUT TO A RAMP,
RACE UP, AND LEAP OFF.
YOULL THEN DIVE DOWN TO
RETRIEVE A PUZZLE PIECE.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL YOUR PIECES,
YOULL PULL YOUR PONTOON TO THE
FINISH AND USE THOSE PIECES TO
BUILD A BACK TO BUOY PYRAMID.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO FINISH WIN
IMMUNITY.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
SITOUT, KAMA, ONE EXTRA PERSON.
IM GOING TO SIT OUT.
Jeff: JULIE WILL SIT OUT
FOR KAMA.
MANU?
ME.
Jeff: VICTORIA WILL SIT OUT
FOR MANU.
EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT IS ERIC FIRST IN FOR MANU.
COME ON, KEL.
AURORA FIRST IN FOR KAMA.
COME ON, KELLEY, COME ON.
NICE AND EASY.
BREATHE.
Jeff: WENTWORTH FIRST IN
FOR LESU.
NOW YOU GOT TO DIVE DOWN AND
RELEASE THAT FIRST PUZZLE PIECE.
ERIC HAS IT FOR MANU.
GOT TO GET UP ON THAT PONTOON
WITH YOUR PIECE.
WENTWORTH NOW TRYING TO GET THAT
MASK ON.
Jeff: COME ON, KELLEY, COME
ON.
YOU GOT THIS, KELLEY!
Jeff: GO, MANU.
NOW AUBRY IN THE WATER FOR MANU.
AURORA CANNOT GET THE BUOY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A SETBACK
FOR KAMA.
JOE NOW INÑi THE WATER.
AUBRY CANT GET IT FOR MANU.
HERE GOES GAVIN.
HES GOING TO GIVE IT A GO NOW.
WENTWORTH STILL WORKING.
SHE CANT GET IT.
YOU GOT TO GET DOWN THERE.
Jeff: JOE HAS IT FOR KAMA.
THEY HAVE ONE OF THEIR TWO
PIECES.
GO, KAMA.
ITS GOING TO BE JULIE IN THE
WATER NOW FOR KAMA.
WENTWORTH STILL STRUGGLING.
GOING TO GIVE UP.
WENTWORTH GOT TO GET ON THAT
PONTOON.
WENTWORTH EXHAUSTED AND CAME UP
EMPTY HANDED.
GO, LESU!
ITS GOING TO BE LAUREN IN THE
WATER NOW FOR LESU.
GAVIN HAS THE SECOND PUZZLE
PIECE FOR MANU.
MANU HAS THEIR TWO PUZZLE
PIECES.
WENDY JUST HAS TO GET TO THE
PONTOON NOW.
BIG LEAD FOR MANU.
JULIA RELEASES THE SECOND PIECE
FOR KAMA.
KAMA NOW HAS BOTH THEIR PIECES.
SHES GOT TO GET BACK.
YOURE GOOD, MANU.
UNCLIP AND START PULLING YOUR
PONTOON.
GO!
KAMA HAS BOTH PUZZLE PIECES.
RON JUST HAS TO GET HIMSELF TO
THE PONTOON.
LESU IN DEAD LAST ONCE AGAIN.
THEY ARE EMPTY HANDED.
BOTH OF THEIR TRIBES HAVE BOTH
PUZZLE PIECES.
RON BACK TO THE PONTOON FOR
KAMA.
START PULLING.
MANU NOW CAN START WORKING ON
THEIR PYRAMID.
ITS A HUGE TIME ADVANTAGE OVER
LESU.
HERE COMES KAMA.
THIS IS THE KIND OF PUZZLE YOU
COULD SOLVE VERY FAST AS THERE
ARE ONLY FOUR PIECES.
BUT IT WILL FOOL YOU.
WE CANT DO IT THAT WAY.
Jeff: MANU AND KAMA
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY AND THE
ADVANTAGE THEY HAVE IS TWO
TRIBES WILL WIN IMMUNITY, AND
RIGHT NOW ONE TRIBE IS DOING
NOTHING.
LAUREN NOW GOING TO GIVE UP.
SHES HEADING BACK.
THIS MIGHT BE ONE OF THE BIGGEST
BLOWOUTS IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
ONCE AGAIN LESU WITH LAUREN,
WENTWORTH, WARDOG AND DAVID HAVE
BEEN THROUGH EVERY SINGLE
TRIBAL.
RIGHT NOW THAT APPEARS TO BE A
STREAK THAT WILL REMAIN INTACT
AS THEY HAVE NONE OF THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES WHILE BOTH OTHER
TRIBES ARE ALREADY SOLVING.
RIGHT THERE.
SEE THAT?
Jeff: THERES ONLY FOUR
PIECES, BUT IT CAN BE VERY
DIFFICULT.
UNTIL YOU FIGURE IT OUT, AND
THEN IT WILL SOLVE INSTANTLY.
WARDOG CANT GET IT EITHER.
WENTWORTH IN DESPAIR ONCE AGAIN.
SHE SEES THE CHALLENGE SLIPPING
AWAY.
WARDOG POPS THE FIRST PUZZLE
PIECE FOR LESU.
THERE IS LIFE FOR LESU AFTER
ALL.
DAVID, YOU CAN DO IT!
Jeff: NOW DAVID IN THE
WATER.
A CHANCE FOR DAVID TO SHINE IN
AN ENVIRONMENT HE REALLY
STRUGGLES IN, THE OCEAN.
COME ON, DAVID.
Jeff: DAVIDS GOT TO GET
DOWN AND RELEASE IT, DAVID.
LETS GO!
THE GOOD NEWS IS MANU AND KAMA
HAVE NOT SOLVED THE PUZZLE, SO
THAT DOOR IS STILL TECHNICALLY
OPEN FOR LESU.
DAVID, COME ON.
COME TO THE PONTOON, IM GOING
TO GO.
Jeff: DAVID GOING TO GIVE
UP AND SWIM BACK TO THE PONTOON.
SOMEBODY FROM THAT FOUR WILL
HAVE TO GO BACK.
LESU IS NOT A TRIBE THATS
QUICK.
THEYRE JUST A TRIBE HAVING A
VERY TOUGH TIME WINNING.
GET OUT OF THE WATER.
Jeff: LAUREN GOES BACK DOWN
YET AGAIN FOR ANOTHER TRY.
IS THIS THE ONE?
IM GOING TO GET IT.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
YOU GOT THIS.
YES!
Jeff: AND SHE DOES IT.
LAUREN FREES THAT SECOND PIECE
FOR LESU.
TELL ME WHEN YOURE READY.
Jeff: UNCLIP.
START PULLING.
HERE COMES LESU NOW.
WE GOT A CHALLENGE.
PULL, GUYS, PULL.
Jeff: MANU AND KAMA HAVE
HAD A LONG TIME TO EXPERIMENT ON
THIS PUZZLE.
BUT IT HAS RESULTED IN NOTHING.
I HATE PUZZLES.
Jeff: IF LESU COULD PULL
THIS CHALLENGE OUT, IT WOULD BE
ONE OF THE GREATEST COMEBACKS IN
THE HISTORY OF "SURVIVOR".
LETS GO, LESU!
VICTORY HERE WOULD BE A MAJOR
WIN.
THIS ONE.
NO.
OKAY.
YES.
Jeff: KAMA THINKS THEY HAVE
IT.
PULL THAT UP.
Jeff: AND THAT DO.
JOE IS RIGHT.
KAMA WINS IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN.
WERE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
FOUR ON THE BOTTOM.
QUICK, QUICK.
Jeff: MANU IS AMPED UP.
GUYS, WERE SO CLOSE, GUYS.
YEAH, YEAH.
Jeff: WHO IS GOING TO GET
THERE FIRST?
WILL IT BE MANU OR LESU?
THIS IS GOING TO GO HERE.
THIS IS GOING TO GO RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT THERE.
IS THAT IT?
THAT MIGHT BE IT.
Jeff: PUT THAT THERE.
PUT THAT THERE.
DAVID TRYING SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
LESU THINKS THEY HAVE IT.
IF THEY HAVE IT, IT WOULD BE
THEIR FIRST WIN.
AND IT IS!
LESU WINS IMMUNITY SENDING MANU
TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YES!
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, GUYS.
GUYS, GUYS.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: KAMA, A FAMILIAR
STORY.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
Jeff: SWIM OUT.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
LESU, YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY WIN.
FOR THE FIRST TIME THIS SEASON
DAVID, LAUREN, WENTWORTH,
WARDOG, I WILL NOT BE SEEING YOU
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
SWIM OUT.
ENJOY THE CELEBRATION AND THE
NIGHT OFF.
MANU, SOMEBODY GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
SWIM OUT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
RIGHT NOW WE DO HAVE A COMMON
GOAL.
WE ALL THINK AUBRY NEEDS TO GO.
BUT I STILL THINK WE ARE MAKING
A BIG MOVE, AND BIG MOVES ARE
ALWAYS RISKY.
SO IM GOING TO PICK AND CHOOSE
MY WORDS CAREFULLY TO NOT OVEROR
UNDER EXPOSE WHATS REALLY
HAPPENING.
SORRY WE COULDNT PULL IT
OUT, GUYS.
MAN.
GOING TO TRIBAL, I KNOW THE
DRILL.
IT WAS ALMOST SURREAL COMING
BACK FROM LOSING THE CHALLENGE,
BECAUSE THE FOUR ORIGINAL KAMA
CAME TOGETHER, AND IT JUST
SEEMED SO EASY.
RIGHT NOW WE NEED THIS FOUR
TO GO FURTHER.
I KNOW.
LIKE WE NEED THIS TO FURTHER
OURSELVES IN THE GAME.
WERE GOING TO FORGE THIS
FOUR.
PERFECT.
-PLAN IS TO VOTED OUT WENDY.
BUT I WAS TALKING TO VICTORIA
YESTERDAY, AND SHE SAID DO WE GO
FOR ONE OF THE BIG GUYS RIGHT
NOW?
I CAN TELL YOU WANT TO DO
SOMETHING.
DONT WANT TO MISS THE
MOMENT.
NO.
IM 1,000% DOWN WITH YOU.
THE ADVANTAGE TO DOING IT NOW
IS WE HAVE NUMBERS.
I THINK WENDY WOULD DO
ANYTHING TO SAVE HERSELF, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YEAH, I KNOW.
HAVING WENDY RIGHT NOW IS AN
OPPORTUNITY TO DO SOMETHING.
THERE ARE THREE GIRL, TWO GUYS,.
I KNOW VICK ANDRY GOOD RIGHT
NOW.
WE COULD KILL ERIC OFF
TONIGHT.
ID LIKE TO MAKE A MOVE.
YOUVE SEEN ME PLAY.
THAT HAS BEEN RUNNING THROUGH MY
MIND FOR DAYS.
ITS ALL TIMING.
WE DO THAT NOW WE COULD BE
SHOOTING OURSELVES IN THE FOOT.
WE WEIGHED THE PROS AND CONS
DO.
WE WORK WITH WENDY AND TAKE OUT
AN ERIC OR A GAVIN.
ERIC IS GOING TO BE A THREAT AT
THE MERGE.
WE MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO GET HIM
OUT PHYSICALLY.
DO WE TAKE OUR HIT WHILE WE HAVE
WENDY.
WHAT KIND OF GAME DID YOU COME
IN HOPING TO PLAY?
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE DO YOU WANT
TO PLAY WITH?
PLAY WITH?
YEAH, LIKE, I MEAN, WE COULD
GO FOR ONE OF THE BOYS.
IF THATS SOMETHING YOURE
INTERESTED IN.
LIKE IF YOU GUYS SAY, YEAH,
AND I SAY NEW YORK ITS NOT
LIKE --
WE WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT, IT WOULD BE NOW.
BECAUSE THERES THREE OF US,
RIGHT?
WE HAVE THE THINK ON IT.
WENDY CANT MAKE A DECISION.
IT IS INCREDIBLY DIFFICULT TO
GET EVEN AN OPINION OUT OF HER.
AND IF YOU CANT GIVE AN OPINION
WHEN YOURE NECK IS ON THE LINE
AND ITS FOUR ORIGINAL TRIBE
MATES AGAINST YOU, I DONT KNOW
HOW I CAN WORK WITH YOU FOR THE
REST OF THE GAME.
THE DECISION FOR ME IS A BIG
DECISION, BECAUSE IT IS FORGING
AN ALLIANCE FOR ME, BUT NOBODY
HAS SEEN ANY GAME YET.
WERE GOOD?
I DONT KNOW WHO THESE PEOPLE
ARE AS PLAYERS SOME THE IDOL IS
ALWAYS FACTOR FOR ME, AND IM
WALKING AROUND WITH MY BAG,
MAKING SURE I GOT A GOOD LITTLE
SPOT FOR MY HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
TO NESTLE BEFORE GOING TO
TRIBAL, AND THERES AN ENVELOPE.
SOMEONE HAS SENT YOU THE
ADVANTAGE IN THE FORM OF A
SECRET EXTRA VOTE.
WHEN ITS TIME TO VOTE, USE THE
PARCHMENT TO CAST THE SECOND
VOTE.
IF YOURE CLEVER, NOBODY ELSE
WILL KNOW YOU VOTED TWICE.
THE LAST TIME THIS VOTE CAN BE
USED WHEN THERE ARE SEVEN PEOPLE
LEFT IN THE GAME.
THE EXTRA VOTE EXTENDS TO A TIE
AND REVOTE.
OH, MY GOSH.
SOMEONE IN THE GAME IS LOOKING
OUT FOR ME, AND I WANT TO KNOW
WHO IT IS.
BECAUSE THATS SOMEONE WHO IS ON
MY SIDE.
THIS EXTRA VOTE CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, DO I USE IT NOW AND
KNOCK OUT ERIC?
OR DO I SAVE IT POST-MERGE AND
USE IT WHEN THE NUMBERS GET
FUNKY?
ITS ABOUT TO GET REAL.
IM NOT GOOD WITH POWER
STUFF.
IM USED TO PLAYING FROM BEHIND.
I DONT KNOW HOW TO PLAY WHEN I
HAVE CARDS IN MY HAND.
WHEN I HAVE THE ROYAL FLUSH, I
DONT KNOW WHAT THE HELL TO DO.
I HAVE ALLIANCES STARTING.
I FEEL GOOD WITH VICK, BUT I
ALMOST DONT KNOW WHAT TO DO
WHEN SOMETHING SOMEWHAT POSITIVE
HAPPENS IN THIS GAME.
LIKE I HAVE CHOICES TO MAKE WITH
BIG THINGS, AND I FEEL LIKE THAT
MEANS IM GOING TO BE VOTED OUT
TONIGHT.
BUT MAYBE THATS NOT THE
MENTALITY TO HAVE.
EVERY TIME I TRY TO DO SOMETHING
IN "SURVIVOR," SOMETHING GOES
WRONG, LIKE MAYBE I HAVE TO HAVE
A LITTLE FAITH THAT MAYBE JUST A
LITTLE BITTY THING CAN GO RIGHT.
Jeff: IF YOU DONT YET HAVE
A TORCH, GRAB ONE WE HIDE YOU,
DIP IT IN, AND GET FIRE.
PART OF THE RITUAL AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS GAME,
FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO
ARE YOU.
SO, DWAFFEN, YOU CAN OFTEN GET
SCENES OF HOW TRIBAL WILL GO
BASED ON THE MOOD OF THE TRIBE
RIGHT AFTER YOU GET BACK TO CAMP
FROM LOSING A CHALLENGE.
WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU GUYS GOT
BACK?
THE MOOD WAS PRETTY DANG
RELAXED WHENEVER WE GOT BACK.
SO IM CURIOUS TO SEE WHAT
TONIGHT HOLDS.
Jeff: AUBRY, DOES THAT MEAN
NOBODY TALKED?
EVERYBODY JUST KNEW WHAT WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN?
ABSOLUTELY NOT, JEFF.
EVERYONE IS ALWAYS TALKING INCH
THIS GAME YOU HAVE TO BE A TALK
AHEAD, OTHERWISE YOURE OUT
BEFORE YOU EVEN REALIZE.
Jeff: VICTORIA, AUBRY SAYS,
YEAH, THERE WAS TALKING.
AUBRYS ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
THERE WERE DEFINITELY
CONVERSATIONS THAT I WAS IN.
IM JUST HOPING THAT EVERYONE
DIDNT GET INTO THEIR OWN HEADS.
Jeff: SO WENDY, YOURE AN
OBVIOUS CONSIDERATION TONIGHT
FOR THE SIMPLE REASON THAT THESE
FOUR HAVE BEEN TOGETHER FROM THE
BEGINNING.
YES.
1,000%.
Jeff: AND YET YOURE STILL
SMILING.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE ARE MORE
CONFUSED THAN ANYTHING ABOUT MY
GAME PLAY.
THEYRE JUST LIKE, WHO PLAYS THE
WAY YOU DO, RIGHT?
BUT I DONTÑi KNOW, I JUST FEEL
LIKE IF I WERE TO WALK DOWN AND
GET MY TORCH SNUFFED, WHY BE SAD
ABOUT THAT?
I MADE IT HERE.
Jeff: AUBRY, ONE OF THE
MOST BRUTAL PARTS OF "SURVIVOR"
IS THE FACT THAT SOMEBODY IS
TYPICALLY ON THE BOTTOM.
BUT IF YOURE WITH A GROUP OF
FOUR AND THERES A FIFTH, DOES
IT SHIFT THAT DYNAMIC A LITTLE
BIT?
I THINK EVERYONE IS TRYING TO
SUSS OUT MORE THAN JUST THEIR
ALLIANCES, LIKE WHO DO THEY
CONNECT WITH ON A GAME LEVEL,
WHO SPEAKS THE SAME LANGUAGE IN
THE GAME.
WHEN YOU FIND A BLACK CAT TO
YOUR WITCH IN "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION," ITS A PERFECT
HALLOWEEN NIGHT.
ITS LIKE HOCUS-POCUS,
ABRACADABRA, YOU CAN FIND THAT
PERSON AT ANY POINT.
Jeff: HAVE YOU FOUND YOUR
BLACK CAT?
IM HOPING I FOUND MY BLACK
CAT OR MY BLACK CATS.
Jeff: GAVIN, THE OTHER
THING THAT STICKS OUT IN THIS
GROUP OF FIVE IS AUBRY, THE ONLY
RETURNING PLAYER IN THIS GROUP.
WHATS A POSITIVE OF HAVING
AUBRY?
I THINK SHES BROUGHT ADVICE.
THATS ONE OF THE BIG THINGS FOR
US, AND I THINK ME AND AUBRY
HAVE CONNECTED ON A PERSONAL
LEVEL.
I DONT SEE HER AS A RETURNING
PLAYER AS MUCH AS SOMEONE THAT I
CAN TRUST DOWN THE ROAD.
THATS ONE OF THE REASONS I WAS
ATTRACTED TO HER FROM THE
GET-GO.
Jeff: SO WENDY, EXPERIENCE
IS A POSITIVE THAT AUBRY BRINGS.
WHATS A NEGATIVE?
WELL, I DONT THINK AUBRY
BRINGS ANY NEGATIVES.
SHES JUST THE NICEST PERSON
EVER.
Jeff: WENDY, IS IT HARD FOR
YOU TO SEPARATE THE GAME FROM
PERSONAL?
YEAH.
ITS HARD TRANSITION BETWEEN
NORMAL LIFE TO THIS GAME THAT IS
JUST LIKE YOU HAVE TO JUST DROP
ALL YOUR MORALS DOWN.
I FOUND THE TRANSITION VERY
HARD.
I DONT THINK I HAVE MADE IT
COMPLETELY YET.
Jeff: SO GAVIN, WHERE ARE
WE IN THE GAME RIGHT NOW WITH
THIS GROUP?
I THINK US FOUR, WERE JUST
GETTING STARTED UP THE ROLLER
COASTER.
WENDY HAS ALREADY WENT DOWN A
COUPLE HILLS AND SHE SURVIVED,
BUT IM BASING MY VOTE OFF WHO I
THINK IS GOING TO BENEFIT ME THE
MOST AND WHO HAS MY BACK FOR THE
DAYS TO COME.
Jeff: ERIC, DO YOU GEE WITH
THAT?
YEAH, I KNOW IVE HAD MOMENTS
WHERE I THOUGHT, AM I GETTING
DUPED TONIGHT?
COULD THIS BE HOW MY GAME ENDS?
BUT AT SOME POINT YOU HAVE TO
TRUST THE PEOPLE THAT YOU TRUST,
AND I THINK WELL FORGE IT IN
FIRE TONIGHT.
Jeff: AUBRY, THIS MAY BE A
CASE WHERE IT IS A VERY EASY
VOTE.
NO SURPRISE, NO BLIND SIDES?
I CAN SOMETIMES BE AN
OVERTHINKER, BUT SOMETIMES
THINGS ARE MORE SIMPLE THAN THEY
SEEM.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
WENDY, YOURE UP.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, AUBRY.
WENDY.
ONE VOTE AUBRY, ONE VOTE WENDY.
AUBRY.
THATS TWO VOTES AUBRY, ONE VOTE
WENDY.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR," AUBRY.
THATS THREE, THATS ENOUGH.
YOU GUYS ARE UNBELIEVABLE
PLAYERS.
Jeff: YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
WOW.
DAMN.
Jeff: AUBRY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
THANKS, AUB.
KILL IT.
WOW.
OH, THATS AN EASY DECISION.
NO-BRAINER.
I WOKE UP AND NONE OF THIS IS A
DREAM.
I GOT BURNED REAL HARD LAST
NIGHT.
I TRULY WAS BLIND SIDED IN EPIC
FASHION WITH AN IDOL AND AN
EXTRA VOTE IN MY POCKET.
LIKE J.T.-STYLE EMBARRASSMENT.
I AM COMPLETELY IN AN UTTER
STATE OF SHOCK.
AND ITS HARD TO KNOW HOW TO
PLAY WHEN YOU DONT EVEN KNOW
WHAT THE ENDING IS.
YOU DONT HAVE INFORMATION.
YOURE WITH ANGRY PEOPLE, AND
YOU DONT KNOW IF YOURE PLAYING
A GAME OR IN A BIG WAITING ROOM,
BUT I NEVER GIVE UP.
FOR ME AS SOON AS IT HITS THE
ROCK BOTTOM, THATS MY FAVORITE
PART, BECAUSE I KNOW IT CAN ONLY
GO UP.
I THRIVE ON PULLING MYSELF UP
FROM THE BOTTOM, AND THATS WHAT
IM GOING TO DO.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
KAMA AND LESTER GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE MANU TRIBE.
AUBRY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
OH, MY GOD.
WOW.
Jeff: JOE, WHAT DO YOU READ
INTO THAT?
FIRST RETURNING PLAYER OUT OF
THE GAME?
OBVIOUSLY THE KAMA STRONG IS
NO LONGER SO STRONG.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
READY TO GET TO TODAYS REWARD
CHALLENGE?
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO LEAP OVER A SERIES OF
TABLES.
YOULL THEN PULL A WILL EVERY,
DROPPING SANDBAGS.
YOULL THEN WORK TOGETHER TO GET
THOSE SANDBAGS TO THE FINISH AND
THROW THOSE SANDBAGS AT A TARGET
UNTIL YOU DROP A FLAG.
FIRST TWO TRIBES TO DROP BOTH
THEIR FLAGS WIN REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOURE PLAYING
FOR?
YES.
PLEASE.
SHOW IT TO ME.
Jeff: FIRST TRIBE TO
FINISH, COFFEE, TEA, PASTRIES,
COOKIES TO CELEBRATE WITH BACK
AT CAMP.
OH, BOY.
WOW.
Jeff: SECOND TRIBE TO
FINISH, A LITTLE SMALLER, STILL
NICE.
ICED COFFEE AND COOKIES.
LAST PLACE, NOTHING BUT ANOTHER
DAY BACK AT CAMP WITH WHATEVER
YOU CAN SCROUNGE UP.
KAMA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON
WHOM ARE YOU GOING TO SIT OUT OF
THIS CHALLENGE?
AURORA, TAKE A SPOT ON THE
SIT-OUT BENCH.
EVERYONE ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET GOING.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GO, GO GO,.
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: OVER THE TABLES IS
THE FIRST PART OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
COME ON.
GO UNDERNEATH IF YOU.
CAN ITS EASIER.
Jeff: YOU GOT SOME SUNNIES
GETTING SKINNED UP.
I CAN HEAR IT.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
Jeff: START UNTYING THOSE
KNOTS NOW.
GO.
Jeff: VICTORIA, LAUREN, AND
JULIA UNTYING KNOTS.
GOOD JOB, JULIA.
Jeff: LAUREN IS WHIPPING
THROUGH THOSE KNOTS.
YOU GOT IT, LAUREN.
Jeff: JULIA DOING A GREAT
JOB FOR KAMA.
GOOD JOB, JULIA.
Jeff: JULIA IS THROUGH.
YOURE GOOD.
LAUREN IS GOOD.
VICTORIA IS GOOD.
WE ARE VERY TIGHT RIGHT NOW.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: TWO PEOPLE AT ONE
END, THE OTHER TWO TOSSING THE
BAGS.
COME ON, GUYS.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: YOU HAVE TO HAVE ALL
THE SANDBAGS IN YOUR BIN.
COME ON, JULIE, COME ON.
FURTHER GUYS, FURTHER.
FURTHER, FURTHER, FURTHER.
THERE YOU GO.
Jeff: THE CLOSER YOU GET TO
YOUR TRIBE MATES, THE FASTER
THEY WILL GET THEM IN THE BINS.
I GOT THESE, I GOT THESE.
LOOK OVER THERE.
A COUPLE MORE.
GO, GO, GO.
Jeff: GOT TO GET THEM ALL
IN THAT BIN.
ALMOST DONE.
WERE DONE.
Jeff: KAMA HAS ALL THEIRS.
YOURE GOOD.
YEAH!
Jeff: ITS GOING TO BE JOE
THROWING FOR KAMA.
NICE.
Jeff: ONCE AGAIN JOE OUT OF
THE GATE STARTS KNOCKING THOSE
TARGETS.
FASTER.
COME ON, WARDOG.
I GOT IT.
DONT YELL AT ME.
Jeff: LESU STILL WORKING.
MANU STILL WORKING.
COME ON, GUYS.
Jeff: AN EARLY LEAD FOR
KAMA.
YEAH, JOE.
Jeff: GET THE LAST ONE IN.
Jeff: LESU HAS THEIRS.
YOURE GOOD.
GAVE WITHIN A NICE HIT FOR MANU.
AND ANOTHER.
GO, GO.
HIGHER.
COME ON, WARDOG.
YOU GOT IT.
ITS OKAY.
Jeff: "SURVIVOR" IS TOUGH,
MAN.
NOWHERE TO HIDE.
WRONG WAY.
Jeff: IF YOU NEVER THREW A
BANAL, ITS GOING TO SHOW.
LETS GO, JOE.
YOU GOT THIS.
Jeff: JOE WITH ANOTHER HIT.
NAILING IT, JOE.
Jeff: AND ANOTHER.
AND ANOTHER.
JOE IS ON FIRE.
LETS GO, JOE!
GOOD JOB.
Jeff: GAVIN NOW STARTING TO
GET THE HANG OF IT.
GOOD JOB.
THAT ONE ON THE RIGHT.
YES, JOE.
YES.
Jeff: JOE DROPS FIRST FLAG
FOR KAMA.
GAVIN DROPS THE FIRSTING FROM
FOR MANU.
LAUREN NOW IN FOR LESU.
YES, LAUREN!
Jeff: LAUREN TRYING TO KEEP
LESU IN IT.
KEEP GOING, LAUREN.
Jeff: BUT ITS A SHOWDOWN
RIGHT NOW BETWEEN GAVE INANE
JOE.
ONE MORE, ONE MORE.
Jeff: JOE VERY CLOSE.
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: THAT DOES IT.
KAMA WINS YET AGAIN.
A BIG REWARD.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
LAUREN TRYING TO KEEP LESU IN
IT.
SOMEONE WANT TO GO?
I CAN COME IN.
ITS UP TO YOU.
Jeff: ITS GOING TO BE
WARDOG BACK IN.
HE WAS COMPLETELY INEFFECTIVE.
COME ON, TRY IT.
Jeff: GAVIN CAN DO IT WITH
THIS TOSS RIGHT HERE.
SLOW DOWN.
YOU GOT TIME.
Jeff: GAVIN DOES IT FOR
MANU.
MANU WINS REWARD SENDING LESU
BACK TO CAMP WITH ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING.
ALL RIGHT.
KAMA, THE WINNING STREAK STAYS
ALIVE.
VICTORIES IN SEVEN OUT OF EIGHT
CHALLENGES.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, AND ENJOY
YOUR REWARD.
MANU, SECOND CASE, NOT QUITE AS
MUCH, BUT IN THIS CASE, ANY
VICTORY IS SWEET.
COOKIES AND ICED COFFEE WAITING
FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, ENJOY.
LESU, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
I THINK THE KAMA TRIBE IS ON
JOES SHOULDERS.
THE DUDE WINS EVERYTHING.
IM JUST JEALOUS ANOTHER TRIBE
HAS BASICALLY HAD A TWO-WEEK
VACATION.
ITS JUST SO FRUSTRATING THAT I
WANT, THAT AND I DONT HAVE
THAT, AND THERES NOTHING I CAN
DO ABOUT IT.
OH, MY GOD.
EVERYTHING YOU WANTED AND
MORE?
OH, MY GOD.
KAMA STRONG!
IT FEELS A LITTLE BIT AT THIS
POINT LIKE IM EXPECTING THAT WE
WILL WIN THE CHALLENGES.
AND I KNOW I SHOULDNT EXPECT
THAT, BUT ITS HARD TO EVEN
IMAGINE US LOSING AT THIS POINT.
JOE, YOU WON THAT CHALLENGE FOR
US.
I JUST WORRY THAT ITS GOING
TO PUT A BIGGER TARGET ON MY
BACK, SO IM GOING TO FEED YOU
ALL TO PROTECT ME EVEN MORE.
IM APPRECIATING THIS RIGHT
NOW AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW HOW
MUCH I APPRECIATE THIS.
AT THIS POINT, IM PULLING THE
WOOL OVER JOES EYES.
HES THE BIGGEST TARGET IN THIS
GAME.
HE KNOWS HE IS.
AND I KEEP JUST PRETENDING THAT
IM GOING ALONG WITH HIM, BUT
SHORT TERM TO HAVE JOE ON OUR
TRIBE RIGHT NOW IS A HUGE
BENEFIT.
SO AUBRY, I THINK THEY SAW
THE MERGE COMING AND THEY
DECIDED TO TAKE OUT A RETURNING.
IT BROKE MY HEART A LITTLE TO
WATCH AUBRY GO.
SEEING AUBRY GO HOME, IT WAS
DEFINITELY A TELLTALE SIGN THAT
THESE NEW PLAYERS ARE SEEING US
RETURN-IES AS THREATS.
STRATEGICALLY THAT REALLY HURT
MY GAME, BECAUSE I FELL LIKE I
COULD REALLY TRUST HER.
ITS REALLY HARD WHEN YOU WANT
TO COME BACK AND PLAY THIS GAME
THAT YOU LOVE SO BADLY, BUT YOU
ALSO KNOW THAT YOURE AT A
DISADVANTAGE AS SOON AS YOU HIT
THE MAT.
YOU HAVE NOWHERE TO HIDE.
YOU HAVE NO... YOU GOT NO ONE TO
RELY ON.
YOU DONT.
BUT IT MAKES YOU APPRECIATE ALL
THE PEOPLE YOU DO RELY ON AT
HOME.
IM SO BLESSED TO HAVE SO MUCH
LOVE, AND I APPRECIATE ALL MY
PEOPLE, MY FAMILY.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE ALL THAT AND
YOU HAVE TO USE IT AS FUEL.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT WHEN
YOU THINK YOURE GOING HOME,
WHEN YOU THINK YOURE OUT ON THE
OUTS, WHEN YOU THINK YOU HAVE NO
ONE THAT WANTS TO WORK WITH YOU,
THATS THE CHALLENGE IS TO HOW
ADAPTABLE ARE YOU REALLY?
HOW MUCH CAN YOU GO BEYOND WHAT
YOU THINK YOURE CAPABLE OF?
BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE A MINDSET
WHERE YOU NO LONGER HAVE
OPTIONS, THEN THATS PROBABLY
WHERE YOURE AT.
AND I DONT WANT TO BE THERE.
I LIKE TO DO WELL IN CHALLENGES.
BUT WE HAVE TO BE SUPER CAREFUL.
ITS GOING TO BE EASIER TO PUT
TARGETS ON US.
DO YOU THINK THERES BAD
BLOOD ON THEIR SIDE THAT WERE
SO STRONG AND THEY JUST MIGHT
TRY TO TAKE US OUT?
ABSOLUTELY THEYRE GOING TO.
THE OTHER TRIBES HAVE SEEN US
BE A REALLY STRONG GROUP OF
FIVE, AND IF FIRST THING I WOULD
WANT TO DO IS TAKE OUT THAT
GROUP OF FIVE, SPLIT IT UP, TAKE
OUT SOME BIG THREATS IN THE
GAME.
SO IF I CAN MAKE EVERYONE FEEL
LIKE THEYRE A BIG THREAT, MAYBE
WE CAN ALL UNITE.
LETS BE REAL, YOURE
BEAUTIFUL AND SMART, MED
STUDENT, YOU KNOW THIS GAME
REALLY WELL AND YOUVE BEEN
KILLER IN CHALLENGES.
DONT SAY ALL, THAT JOE.
YOU KNOW THEYRE ALL THINKING
IT.
I DONT THINK ANY OF US ARE PART
OF THEIR PLAN, OR IF WE ARE,
ITS TEMPORARILY.
YEAH.
PEOPLE ARE EASILY THREATENED
BY SOMEONE WHO CAN WIN A COUPLE
CHALLENGES AND SO WE HAVE TO
STICK TOGETHER.
WELL GO FAR.
BECAUSE ILL WIN THE IMMUNITIES
AND WE GET TO DECIDE WHERE WE
WANT TO GO.
WHEN YOU START HEARING JOE
SAYING THAT YOURE A THREAT,
ITS LIKE, OH, CRAP, LIKE IF
PEOPLE SEE ME AS A THREAT, THAT
IS GOING TO MAKE MY GAME A LOT
HARDER ONCE WE DO GET TO A
MERGE, SO IM DEFINITELY
ANTICIPATING HAVING TO ADAPT AND
REARRANGE SOME THINGS TO STAY IN
THE GAME.
JOE IS AMAZING AGAIN.
OH, MY GOD, WHAT MUST IT BE
LIKE TO BE HIM?
I REALLY THINK WE SHOULD TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THIS LOW TIDE.
THERES CRABS DOWN.
THERE MAYBE CRAB LEGS FOR
DINNER.
I DONT KNOW.
IM DOWN.
I NEED SOMETHING.
WE LOST.
YET AGAIN.
AND ITS SO FRUSTRATING.
ITS NOT EVEN THAT WERE LOSING,
ITS THAT WERE LOSING, AND WE
COME BACK TO THIS CRAPPY-ASS
BEACH THAT HAS NO FOOD, A CRAPPY
SHELTER.
WERE SLEEPING IN THE MUD.
ITS 24 HOUR DAYS OF JUST HELL,
ABSOLUTE HELL.
I LITERALLY NEVER CRY AT HOME,
AND IVE CRIED LIKE FOUR DAYS IN
A ROW NOW.
IM DYING, LIKE LITERALLY
WALKING UP AND DOWN I WAS
BLACKING OUT.
REALLY?
YES.
IM SO HUNGRY, BUT THE RICE
MAKES ME SO SICK.
I CANT FUNCTION.
GIRL, YOU AND I ARE LIKE THE
ONLY PEOPLE DOING THINGS LIKE
SUPER PHYSICAL IN THE
CHALLENGES.
I NEED YOU.
I JUST NEED THAT MERGE RIGHT
NOW.
WEVE HAD ALMOST NO FOOD FOR
DAYS.
AND WERE ALL FEELING IT.
ESPECIALLY LAUREN.
HE FOUND A CRAB.
PULL THAT THING UP.
HES REALLY ON THERE.
THE IDEA OF FISHING I THINK
IS COUNTERINTUITIVE BECAUSE WE
NEED TO SAVE OUR CALORIES AND
ENERGY FOR THESE CHALLENGES.
HOW ARE THEY GETTING AWAY.
BUT AT LEAST DAVID STILL HAS
LIFE.
YOU KNOW?
LAUREN IS KIND OF LIKE GIVING
UP.
MAYBE SHES THE ONE TO GO NEXT.
I KNOW THAT WENTWORTH IS GOOD
WITH IT.
BUT TO PULL IT OFF, I NEED
DAVID.
I FEEL VERY TORN RIGHT NOW.
LAUREN IS SOMEBODY THAT IVE
BEEN CLOSE TO FROM DAY ONE.
BUT HER MIND IS NOT IN THE GAME.
RIGHT.
I CAN SEE HER JUST TWIMPING.
I NEED SOMEONE WHO WILL RIDE OR
DIE.
LETS JUST SAY WE LOST LAUREN,
ARE YOU WITH US TO THE END, RIDE
OR DIE?
I DONT THINK I HAVE A
CHOICE, BUT YES.
HOPEFULLY WE JUST WIN AND
WHATEVER.
I UNDERSTAND THAT AT SOME
POINT I MIGHT HAVE TO VOTE OUT
LAUREN.
SHES LITERALLY WASTING AWAY.
HOWEVER, WARDOG, WHO IS A
PSYCHOWHEN IT COMES TO NUMBER
CRUNCHING AND FLIPPING
ALLIANCES, HES ALMOST SCARING
ME NOW.
I DONT KNOW IF I WANT TO WORK
WITH HIM.
THE THING IS I FEEL LIKE WITH
HIM I JUST AGREE A LOT.
THATS WHAT I DO.
HE DOESNT WANT TO HEAR YOUR
OPINION.
HE REALLY WANTS TO BARK AN ORDER
AT YOU AND HAVE YOU GO ON WITH
IT.
ITS A DICTATORSHIP.
WARDOG IS PLAYING REALLY
HARD, FLIPPING BACK AND FORTH,
AND ITS REALLY ANNOYING.
HE DOES NOTHING AT CAMP HE
SPENDS MOST OF HIS DAYS
STRATEGIZING AND CRUNCHING
NUMBERS.
ALSO HE SUCKS AT THESE PHYSICAL
CHALLENGE, AND ALL OF THAT IS
PUTTING A HUGE TARGET ON HIS
BACK, WHICH IS GREAT WITH ME.
WE HAVE TO DO WHATEVER IS
BEST FOR US.
IM WITH YOU.
WHEN THE GAME STARTED, I WANTED
TO VOTE OUT WENTWORTH, BUT NOW
IM WORKING WITH THE PERSON WHO
I THOUGHT WAS MY BIGGEST
ADVERSARY OUT HERE, BUT IF
THATS GOING TO GET ME TO DAY
39, THEN THATS WHAT IM GOING
TO DO.
♪
WHATS UP?
I GOT MORE INFO.
THIS MORNING WE FOUND A BASKET
WITH FIVE NEW MAPS.
THEY LOOK THE SAME AS BEFORE,
EXCEPT THERES A BUNCH OF HOLES.
SO IM ASSUMING THAT MEANS
THERES SOMETHING ELSE TO FIND.
CAN WE LESSEN THE LEVEL OF
PARANOIA THIS TIME AND NO ONE
TAKE OFF?
NO PROMISES.
WE GET THE MAP AND EVERYONE
STARTS FOLLOWING IT.
IM A NEWBIE IN THIS EDGE OF
EXTINCTION LANGUAGE.
ALL RIGHT.
IM GOING TO GO AHEAD AND GO.
I DONT KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON.
BUT THEY SEEM TO KNOW IF YOU
FOLD IT AND SOMETHING POINTS,
YOURE GOING TO FIND AN
ADVANTAGE.
IS THIS THING EVEN OUT HERE?
THERES MAD SCRAMBLE UP TOP.
I WAS ABLE TO FIGURE OUT FIRST
MAP.
BUT THE SECOND MAP WAS MUCH
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
IM LOOKING EVERYWHERE AND THEN
FINALLY ITS LIKE, OH, MY GOSH,
ITS ON THE BEACH.
WHAT I FIGURED OUT IS ALL THE
HOLES LINE UP TO ONE HOLE.
WHEN YOU LAYER THAT ON TOP OF
THE OTHER MAP, IT PUTS IT RIGHT
NEXT TO THE MAST.
OH, COME ON.
I WAS SO SURE IT WAS THERE.
I DUG AND DUG, BUT APPARENTLY I
WAS AT THE WRONG SPOT.
I KNOW DEVENS IS GOOD WITH
MAPS.
SO IM THINKING MAYBE HES JUST
OFF A LITTLE BIT.
THEN I THINK WHEN ITS SUPER LOW
TIDE, THERE ARE ALL THESE ROCKS
SHOWING THEMSELVES, SO I START
WALKING BY THE WATER TO SEE IF
MAYBE IT WAS IN THERE.
WHAT IS THAT?
FREAKING INSANE.
THIS ENTIRE TIME I HAVE
NEEDED A BREAKTHROUGH, AND THEN
ALL OF A SUDDEN IN THE SEA WATER
I FOUND THIS.
CHRIS, HES GOT IT.
THANK YOU, JESUS.
WHEN THE TIME COME, PENALIZE
YOUR BIGGEST THREAT BY ASSIGNING
THESE MAPS TO THEM.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I PRAYED
FOR.
CHRIS HAS BEEN GETTING THE BEST
OF ME.
THIS IS GOING TO LET ME PUT A
LITTLE CURSE ON CHRIS.
APPARENTLY WERE GOING TO HAVE
SOME KIND OF COMPETITION, AND
THIS COULD HELP MYSELF GET BACK
IN THE GAME.
I NEEDED IT.
AND THANK GOD THAT I GOT IT.
IM JUST PISSED BECAUSE I SAID,
WHAT DO YOU HAVE.
BUT I DIDNT TOUCH IT FIRST.
WHAT THE HELL, REEM?
YOU GAVE IT TO SOMEONE ELSE.
YOU THINK I GAVE IT AWAY?
IM NOT THAT STUPID.
I WANTED THAT.
THE RULES ARE THE RULES.
THOSE TWO GET ON MY DAMN NERVES.
YOU JUST ACCUSED ME OF GIVING
AWAY AN ADVANTAGE.
DO I HAVE COMPLETE IDIOT WRITTEN
ON MY FOREHEAD.
I DONT EVEN KNOW WHAT TO
SAY.
YOU JUST SAID I GAVE IT TO
HIM.
DONT YOU TELL ME I GAVE
SOMETHING AWAY.
WELL, YOU POINT AT IT AND HE
PICKS IT UP AND RUNS AWAY.
YOU GOT THE BIGGEST MOUTH IN
THE WHOLE COUNTRY.
YOURE THE ONE WHO SAID I GAVE
HIM THE ADVANTAGE.
BY SAYING THAT, YOU LIT OFF A
VOLCANO, BRO.
IT IS A DISASTER HERE.
IT TRULY IS THE MOST
DYSFUNCTIONAL FAMILY IVE EVER
MET.
I DONT NEED ZERO.
THEN WHY ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT IT?
BECAUSE YOURE GETTING ON MY
[BLEEPED] NERVES, AND ITS 12
DAYS OF LISTENING TO THE BULL
[BLEEPED].
AND IM DONE WITH IT.
THE WORST PART OF IT ALL, NO
ONE KNOWS HOW LONG THIS TRAIN
WRECK CAN LAST.
THATS A SCARY SITUATION,
BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE LEGITIMATELY
LOSING IT.
REEM, THATS ALL --
[SCREAMS]
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO TODAYS IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, GOT TO TAKE
BACK THE IDOL.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO CLIMB A LADDER AND THEN
MANEUVER A BAG ATTACHED TO A
ROPE THROUGH A BAMBOO FRAME.
YOULL THEN USE THE BALL INSIDE
TO DROP THE CAGE DOOR.
SPRINT TO THE FINISH TO SOLVE A
"SURVIVOR" SLIDE PUZZLE.
KAMA, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA PERSON.
WHO YOU GOING TO SIT OUT?
AURORA SAT OUT AT THE REWARD
CHALLENGE.
RON, TAKE A SPOT IN THE SIT-OUT
BENCH.
OH, ONE EXTRA THING.
OH, NO.
OH.
Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE ONLY
THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
THE TWO LOSING TRIBES GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, WOW.
Jeff: ILL GIVE YOU A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE.
WELL GET STARTED.
WOW.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
GET UP THAT LADDER, AND THEN
START TRACING THAT BAG ALONG THE
ROPES TO GET IT OUT OF THE
BAMBOO FRAME.
TRY NOT TO LET IT --.
Jeff: YOU CANT GET AHEAD
OF THE BAG.
YOURE ONLY AS SLOW AS THAT
PERSON WORKING ON THE BAG.
IT IS KAMA IN THE LEAD, WHICH IS
BECOMING PREDICTABLE STORY IN
CHALLENGES THIS SEASON.
AND THEN MANU AND LESTER SIDE BY
SIDE.
ITS GOING TO BE KAMA OUT FIRST
WITH THEIR BAG.
AURORA IS DOWN.
HERE COMES JULIE AND JOE.
THEYVE GOT TO UNTIE IT NOW.
COME ON.
GO.
Jeff: MANU COMING DOWN.
GOT TO UNTIE THEIR KNOTS.
IT IS NOW LESU IN DEAD LAST ONCE
AGAIN.
JULIA WORKING ON THE KNOTS.
YOURE GOOD!
JOE NOW GOING TO START UNTYING
KNOTS ON THE BAG, TRYING TO
RELEASE THAT MONKEYS FIST.
UP ON THE PLATFORM.
Jeff: MANU, YOURE GOOD.
GOING TO BE GAVIN UNTYING KNOTS
FOR MANU.
LAURENS GOT IT.
ITS GOING TO BE WARDOG NOW.
COME ON, JOE.
Jeff: JOE HAS THAT MONKEY
FIST.
NOW HES LOOKING TO DROP IT IN
THAT HOOP, WHICH WILL DROP THAT
CAGE DOOR.
JOE DROPS THE CAGE FOR KAMA ON
HIS VERY FIRST TOSS.
GOOD TOSS.
Jeff: GAVIN TOSSES.
HE DROPS HIS CAGE.
GO, MANU.
TWO PEOPLE ON THE PUZZLE NOW,
GOING TO BE "JULIE & JULIA" FOR
KAMA.
YOU GOT THIS, WARDOG.
GIVE THE ROPE SOME SLACK.
Jeff: MANU IS OVER.
ITS GOING TO BE VICTORIA AND
ERIC.
HERE WE GO, WARDOG.
WARDOG, NO, NO, NO.
Jeff: YOU GOT TO STAY ON
IT.Ñi
NO!
OKAY.
SORRY.
Jeff: WARDOG HAS NOT HAD A
LOT OF SUCCESS.
WARDOGS GOT IT FOR LESU.
AWKWARD BUT ACCOMPLISHED IT.
GET OVER THAT CAGE.
IT IS DAVID AND WENTWORTH FOR
LESU.
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
JULIE GOING TO STEP OUT.
JOE AND JULIA IN NOW.
OKAY, JOE.
I GOT IT.
I THINK I GOT IT.
Jeff: THIS PUZZLE COULD
TAKE A VERY LONG TIME OR IF YOU
KNOW YOUR WAY AROUND A SLIDE
PUZZLE, YOU COULD GET THIS VERY
FAST.
DAVID THINKS HE HAS SOMETHING.
LESU HAS BEEN ON A LOSING STREAK
OF EPIC PROPORTIONS.
READY?
Jeff: CAN LESU PULL OUT A
VICTORY RIGHT NOW?
JEFFREY?
Jeff: KAMA THINKS THEY HAVE
IT AND THEY DO.
WOW.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: JOE AND JULIA SOLVE
IT FOR KAMA.
KAMA WINS IMMUNITY SENDING LESU
AND MANU TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ONCE AGAIN KAMA WINS IMMUNITY.
NOBODY GOING HOME.
NICE WORK.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, LESU, MANU, TONIGHT
BOTH TRIBES WILL COME TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL TOGETHER AND VOTE ONE
PERSON OUT OF THE GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
GOING INTO TRIBAL TONIGHT,
IM LIKE PANICKING.
THERES FOUR LESU AND FOUR MANU.
WE COULD FIND OURSELVES AT A TIE
AND GOING TO ROCKS.
I HAVE GONE TO ROCKS BEFORE, AND
AS A FAN, ITS EXHILARATING.
AS A PLAYER ITS NAUSEATING.
STRAP YOURSELF IN, EVERYBODY.
ITS GOING TO BE CHAOTIC.
THE CHALLENGE WENT HORRIBLY.
KAMA WINS AGAIN.
WITH THE ADDED TWIST THAT BOTH
TRIBES WILL BE GOING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WAIT FOR IT.
DRUM ROLL.
TOGETHER.
WHICH IS AN INTERESTING PROBLEM,
BECAUSE IF WE GO TO A 4-4 TIE,
EVERYONE VOTES AGAIN.
IF NO ONE CHANGES THEIR VOTE, WE
DRAW ROCKS.
ANYONE CAN GO HOME.
FIRST OF ALL, I THINK THE
BEST THING WE COULD DO IS STICK
TOGETHER AS A FOUR.
WE CANT POSSIBLY SPLIT.
ARE YOU ALL WILLING TO DRAW
STONES?
THATS THE THING.
WE HAVE NO ALLIANCE.
SO IF WE HIT LAUREN OR WARDOG, I
THINK THEY WOULD FLIP ON OUR
SIDE.
I THINK WE HAVE A REALLY GOOD
SHOT IN BEING ABLE TO SWAY
DAVID, BECAUSE THE LESU TRIBE,
AT LEAST FROM WHEN I WAS PART OF
THAT TRIBE, THEY WERENT LOYAL
TO EACH OTHER, AND HE DOESNT
HAVE THE NUMBERS TO SURVIVE THE
MERGE, SO IM HOPING THAT DAVID
REALIZES THAT HES ON A SINKING
SHIP.
I THINK THAT SOMEBODY WILL DO
IT.
I DONT THINK THEY WOULD ALL
GO TO ROCKS.
WHAT RETURNING PLAYER IS GOING
TO COME BACK FOR A THIRD TIME
AND BE WILLING TO GO TO ROCKS?
I THINK RIGHT NOW THE FACT
THAT THEY HAVE TWO RETURNING
PLAYERS IS AN ADVANTAGE FOR US.
YOU DONT COME OUT HERE TWO,
THREE, TIMES TO GET SENT HOME
BEFORE THE MERGE BY A ROCK.
SO IN TERMS OF THIS CRAPPY
SITUATION, I FEEL LIKE OUR SIDE
COULD POSSIBLY BE SLIGHTLY
BETTER OFF.
IF WE WILL ALL GO TO ROCKS, I
THINK ALL WE HAVE TO SAY IS, YOU
CAN BELIEVE US OR NOT, BUT WERE
WILLING TO GO TO ROCKS TONIGHT.
WE DONT THINK YOUR TRIBE IS.
ROLL THE DICE?
I THINK THATS OUR BEST BET.
EVERYTHING IS A GAMBLE
TONIGHT.
BUT IM A BIG FAN OF THIS GAME.
IVE BEEN IMAGINING MYSELF IN
THESE EXACT SITUATIONS FOR
YEARS.
YOU DONT IMAGINE YOURSELF IN
THE EASY TRIBAL COUNCIL VOTE.
YOU THINK YOWFERS IN THIS
SITUATION, GOING INTO TRIBAL
COUNCIL, PROBABLY GOING TO GO TO
ROCKS.
THATS WHAT MAKES A PERSON LIKE
ME AT HOME WANT TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
ITS THIS, TONIGHT, BUT IS IT
SCARY?
YEAH.
I COULD GO HOME TONIGHT.
NO QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK THEYRE MORE LIKELY
TO PUT VOTES ON YOU OR ME?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I WISH I KNEW.
AND YOULL GO TO ROCKS?
I GUESS.
ID BE WILLING TO DO THAT.
I DONT WANT TO GO TO THE NEXT
STAGE WITHOUT YOU.
OF COURSE.
WERE IN IT TOGETHER.
YOURE MY MAN.
NO ONE WANTS TO GO OUT WITH
ROCKS.
THATS THE BIG FEAR IN THIS
GAME, BUT I DID SIGN UP TO PLAY
"SURVIVOR."
I FEEL LIKE THATS WHAT IM
DOING TONIGHT.
SO IT FEELS GOOD, BUT IM ALSO
GOING TO BE CRAPPING BRICKS.
I HAVE 100% TRUST IN ERIC AND
VICTORIA.
AND AFTER LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
WENDY IS WITH US 100%.
ILL DRAW ROCKS FOR ONE OF THEM.
I HOPE THE GOD THEYD DO THE
SAME FOR ME.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A HUGE
MOVE EITHER WAY, BUT I THINK IT
CAN WORK.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE WERE
ALL ON THE SAME PAGE.
NO QUESTION.
THE WHOLE THING TONIGHT COULD
COME DOWN TO DRAWING ROCKS.
WE JUST ALL AGREED THAT WERE
ALL DOWN FOR THAT.
IM NOT.
IM KIND OF WILLING TO PUT MY
VOTE WHEREVER TO KEEP ME IN THE
GAME.
IF I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO BETRAY
AN ALLIANCE TO MOVE MYSELF ONE
STEP FURTHER IN THE GAME, IM
GOING TO DO IT, BECAUSE I CAN
FIND AN IN SOMEWHERE ELSE.
DONT EVER TRUST ME, MAN.
I DONT KNOW IF ANYONE HAS
FIGURED THAT OUT YET.Ñi
OKAY.
SO HERES THE THING.
IF I WERE THEM, I WOULD STAY
FOUR STRONG.
UH-HUH.
TRY AND FLIP ONE OF YOU.
CORRECT.
RIGHT.
I WANT TO TAKE OUT ONE OF THE
BIG GUY, BUT I FEEL LIKE THE
LAST PERSON THEY WOULD THINK WE
WOULD TAKE OUT WOULD BE
VICTORYA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
FOUR VOTES ON WENDY, RIGHT?
WE VOTE, ONE OF THEM MIGHT BE
LIKE DO, YOU WANT THE DRAW ROCKS
FOR WENDY.
THEY MIGHT FLIP ON WENDY RIGHT
THERE.
ONCE AGAIN, WARDOG DIDNT
THEREON WHAT ANYBODY ELSE HAD TO
SAY.
HE TRIES TO OVERPOWER PEOPLE.
HES GOT HIS PLAN, AND THATS
THAT.
BUT TO BE HONEST, WARDOG IS
RIGHT.
WENDY IS NOT AN ORIGINAL KAMA
MEMBER.
SO HOPEFULLY WE HAVE TO REVOTE
SOMEONE WILL FLIP AND HELP US
VOTE HER OUT.
I THINK I SHOULD GO OVER TO
WENDY AND SAY VOTE FOR WHATEVER
NAME WE WANT HER TO VOTE FOR.
IT GOES 4, 3, 1...
I THINK THEYRE GOING TO VOTE
FOR ME, BECAUSE THEYRE GOING TO
THINK KELLEY OR YOU HAS THE
IDOL.
I THINK SHE WOULD BE THE
LOGICAL VOTE.
WE JUST CANT CRUMBLE.
THATS THE THING.
WE CANNOT.
WE HAVE TO GO IN THERE FOUR
STRONG.
ILL GO TO ROCKINGS.
ILL GO TO ROCKS.
ME TOO.
IVE DONE IT BEFORE.
THIS PLAN MAKES ME REALLY
NERVOUS.
I DIDNT COME THIS FAR JUST TO
GO TO ROCKS, BUT WARDOG ALWAYS
HAS HIS OWN AGENDAS AND NOBODY
CAN EVEN HAVE AN INPUT.
SO IM PISSED.
IM SO CLOSE TO MAKING THE
MERGE, AND THIS COULD RUIN
EVERYTHING.
WE GOT TO MERGE TOMORROW.
IM SO HUNGRY.
OKAY.
WE NEED A TON MORE FIREWOOD FOR
THIS.
JUST TO KEEP US GOING.
I GOT LIKE 15, 20 MINUTES TO
DRY THIS WOOD OUT.
OKAY.
ILL GO DOWN TO THE BEACH.
HE DOESNT CONTRIBUTE AT ALL.
ITS CRAZY.
HES SO OBVIOUSLY LIKE
PLOTTING.
HES TOTALLY PLOTTING.
WE HAVE A GOOD PLAN TONIGHT,
HOWEVER, IM WORRIED TO DEATH
ABOUT LAUREN.
SHE ISNT WELL.
ALL SHE TALKS ABOUT IS THE
MERGE, FOOD, MERGE, FOOD, MERGE,
FOOD.
I CANT WORK WITH SOMEONE LIKE
THAT.
SO IM LIKE DO, I REALLY WANT TO
GO TO ROCKS FOR THIS GIRL?
IM NOT SO SURE.
LETS GO EXPLORE.
HOWEVER, THE MANU TRIBE MIGHT BE
TARGETING ME.
BUT IF I CAN FIND AN IDOL THAT
WILL GIVE ME TREMENDOUS POWER.
WARDOG?
I CAN IN THE BELIEVE IT.
HE LITERALLY DOES NOTHING.
ITS INSANE.
LIKE WHERE IS HE?
HES PROBABLY LOOKING FOR THE
IDOL.
WARDOG DISAPPEARED.
HES NOT HELPING AT ALL.
HES NOT CONTRIBUTING AT ALL.
HE GOES OFF INTO THE JUNGLE.
WARDOG IS CREATING A WAR.
I GUESS THATS WHAT WAR DOGS DO.
HES BEING DIVISIVE.
WE NEED TO BE UNITED.
IM GOING TO GO LOOK FOR IT.
LETS GO LOOK I GUESS, RIGHT?
WHERE WERE YOU?
DOWN BY THE BEACH.
WE COULDNT FIND YOU.
YOU WERENT LOOKING HARD
ENOUGH.
I WANT TO FIND THE IDOL
BEFORE WARDOG.
HES A SCHEMER AND MANIPULATOR.
HES ALREADY CALLING THE SHOTS.
AND WITH AN IDOL, HES JUST
GOING TO GET MORE AND MORE
POWERFUL.
IT SHOULDNT BE THIS HARD.
IT SHOULDNT.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
AND THEN I LOOK UP IN THE TREE,
AND, BING, ITS JUST SITTING
RIGHT THERE.
LETS GO ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
CAMP.
IM GOING THE STAY HERE.
IN "SURVIVOR," YOU NEVER GIVE
UP, BECAUSE THIS GAME IS ALWAYS
CHANGING.
AND NEG THAT TONIGHT IS SUCH A
CRAZY TRIBAL POTENTIALLY, HAVING
THAT SAFETY IS HUGE.
IM PERPLEXED.
TONIGHTS TRIBAL COUNCIL IS
HUGE.
KELLEY AND I HAVE IDOLS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IM GOING TO
DO.
ITS NOT WORTH GOING HOME.
I KNOW.
TONIGHT THE MANU TRIBE IS
MOST LIKELY TARGETING ME OR
WARDOG.
EVERYONE IS BANKING ON THE FACT
THAT THEYRE NOT GOING TO WANT
TO GO TO ROCKS FOR WENDY, BUT IF
THEY STAY STRONG, ROCKS WILL
DETERMINE WHO GOES HOME.
I REALLY DONT WANT THE DRAW
ROCKS.
WOULD YOU GO TO ROCKS FOR
WARDOG?
IM NOT GOING TO ROCKS FOR
WARDOG.
IF WE GO TO ROCK, ITS A 1-6
CHANCE YOU GO HOME SOME IF
THEYRE VOTING FOR WARDOG, IM
GOING TO FLIP.
BUT I CAN SEE THEM GOING AFTER
ME, SO I GOT TO DECIDE IF IM
GOING TO PLAY MY IDOL OR NOT.
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE A LOT OF
ON-THE-SLY DECISIONS.
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW WHATS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
TWO TRIKES GEAR TO VOTE OUT ONE
PERSON.
VICTORIA, ANY TIME THERES A
TWIST INVOLVING TRIBAL, IT CAN
BE UNNERVING.
DID YOU FEEL A DIFFERENT SENSE
AT MANU THIS AFTERNOON?
I WOULD SAY THE MAIN
DIFFERENCE WAS THERE WERE NO
SIDE CONVERSATIONS.
IT WAS ONE LARGE CONVERSATION
BECAUSE WE GOT EVEN TRIBES HERE.
ITS FOUR AGAINST FOUR.
IF WERE NOT ALL ON THE SAME
PAGE, WERE IMMEDIATELY SCREWED.
LETS TALKING ABOUT THE LESU
TRIBE.
LAUREN, WAS IT SIMILAR TO MANU
IN THAT YOU ALL GOT TOGETHER AND
SAID, WE HAVE TO BE UNITED.
WE DIDNT EVEN HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT STAYING UNITED.
WE KNEW WE WERE GOING THE STAY
UNITED.
WERE A VERY STRONG FOUR THAT
GENUINELY HAS BEEN THROUGH SO
MUCH.
Jeff: WARDOG, PRETTY
INTERESTING, FOUR FROM ONE
TRIBE, FOUR FROM ANOTHER, BUT
ONLY ONE GOING HOME.
ITS KIND OF CRAZY, BECAUSE
WHEN YOU FIRST SAID ONLY ONE
TRIBE GETS IMMUNITY, I FELT THAT
PAIN IN MY STOMACH, BUT WHEN YOU
FIND OUT 1 OUT OF 8, PREPARING
FOR THE GUN KNIGHT AT THE O.K.
CORRAL.
I HAVE MY WYATT EARP.
THAT MAKES ME DOC HOLIDAY.
WE HAVE OUR PLAN.
WERE GOING TO STICK WITH EACH
OTHER.
ITS GOING TO BE FUN
THE TRICKY THING IS THEY
DONT KNOW US IN A TRIBE IN THE
SAME WAY WE DONT KNOW THEM.
SO ITS HARD TO PUT A LOT OF
WEIGHT INTO ANYTHING THATS
SAID.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, THIS
REALLY IS "SURVIVOR" WARFARE.
I THINK THIS IS DEFINITELY A
BATTLE TONIGHT, BUT WE ARE FOUR
STRONG.
WE WOULD WELCOME ANYONE OVER
HERE WITH OPEN ARMS.
Jeff: GAVIN IS -- GAFERREN,
WENTWORTH IS SAYING, JOIN US
RIGHT NOW AND WELL CHANGE THE
GAME.
THATS A GREAT SPEECH.
I WOULD LIKE TO EXTEND THE SAME
THING TO YOU GUYS, BECAUSE WERE
GOING TO STICK STROKE TO OUR
GUN, AS WELL.
Jeff: WENDY, ONE OTHER
INTERESTING ASPECTS IS YOU HAVE
SOME INSIGHT.
DID THE TRIBE LOOK TO YOU AND
SAY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THATS ESSENTIALLY WHAT
HAPPENED.
I FEEL LIKE IM HAVING A
FLASHBACK ON MY FIRST PART OF
THE GAME.
SO ITS LIKE IM BASICALLY IN
THE MIDDLE.
Jeff: DAVID, THATS
INTERESTING.
WENDY DIDNT SAY, I USED TO BE
WITH THEM.
SHE SAID, I FEEL LIKE IM IN THE
MIDDLE.
YEAH, THATS REALLY GOOD TO
HEAR.
I THINK IT WAS UNFORTUNATE THAT
THE SWAP KICKED WENDY OUT OF THE
GROUP OF PEOPLE, BUT WE STILL
CONSIDER HER PART OF THE TRIBE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
Jeff: WE LOVE YOU, WENDY.
WE ALWAYS DID.
THAT WASNT THE SENSE WHEN
SHE RECEIVED WENDY.
SHE FELT ON THE OUTS.
WE WELCOMED HER WITH OPEN ARMS
SOME WERE NOT CONCERNED ABOUT
HER FEELING IN THE MIDDLE.
Jeff: SO DAVID, YOU HAD TO
DISCUSS THE IDEA OF A TRUE
DEADLOCK TIE IN WHICH YOU WOULD
FORCE A ROCK DRAW.
YEAH, AND, YOU KNOW, IM
SOMEONE WHO HAS BEEN TO ROCKS.
I GO TO ROCKS FOR MY PEOPLE.
IF IT HAS TO COME TO ROCKS
TONIGHT, THEN THATS EXACTLY
WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN.
NOBODY HERE IS AFRAID TO DO
THAT.
WE TRUST EACH OTHER.
Jeff: VICTORIA, WHEN YOU
HEAR A VETERAN SAY, OH, I WILL
GO TO ROCKS, CHECK MY HISTORY,
DOES THAT HAVE ANY WEIGHT WITH
YOU?
NOT REALLY.
I FIND IT REALLY HARD TO BELIEVE
YOU WOULD COME BACK INTO THIS
GAME AGAIN AND AGAIN TO HAVE
YOUR FATE BE PUT INTO ROCKS IF
YOU HAD ANOTHER OPTION.
SO I GET IT AND I RESPECT IT,
BUT I DONT THINK YOU PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" TWICE, THREE TIMES TO
GO HOME ON A ROCK BEFORE YOU HIT
THE MERGE.
Jeff: ERIC, YOURE NODDING,
YOU AGREE.
"SURVIVOR" IS FUN, BUT ITS
NOT THAT FUN.
I DONT KNOW IF I WOULD DO IT
THREE TIMES TO GO HOME ON A ROCK
DRAW.
Jeff:
WENDY, I WOULD LIKE TO TALK
TO YOU FOR A QUICK SECOND.
SURE, LETS GO AHEAD.
Jeff: IS THAT IT?
YOU GUYS READY TO VOTE?
YEP.
WERE READY.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
WENTWORTH, YOURE UP.
Jeff: ILL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, WENDY.
LAUREN.
WENDY.
THATS TWO VOTES WENDY.
LAUREN.
WERE TIED, TWO VOTES WENDY, TWO
VOTES LAUREN.
WENDY.
THATS THREE VOTES WENDY.
TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES WENDY, THREE VOTES
LAUREN.
WENDY.
THATS FOUR VOTES WENDY, THREE
VOTES LAUREN, ONE VOTE LEFT.
LAUREN.
WERE TIED.
HERES WHATS GOING TO HAPPEN.
WERE GOING TO REVOTE.
LAUREN AND WENDY, YOU WILL NOT
VOTE.
EVERYBODY ELSE YOU CAN ONLY VOTE
FOR LAUREN OR WENDY.ñr
I JUST WANT TO SAY ONE THING.
ONCE WE MERGE, WE JUST MET YOU.
THIS IS OUR FIRST CONVERSATION.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
OUR GROUP IS GOING TO CAVE.
THIS IS LIKE THE WORST
COCKTAIL PARTY EVER.
Jeff: OKAY.
WENTWORTH, COME GRAB THE URN.
ILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
WENDY.
TWO VOTES WENDY.
THREE VOTES WENDY.
SIXTH PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION,"
WENDY.
THATS FOUR, THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
SORRY, WENDY.
SORRY.
ITS COOL, ITS COOL.
CAN YOU CALL ME BIG WENDY?
YOURE AMAZING.
Jeff: THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YEAH.
BYE, GUYS.
I GET A HUG.
WELL MISS YOU, WENDY.
WE REALLY WELL.
[APPLAUSE]
Jeff: TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
GET OUT OF HERE.
CHEESEBURGER AND SHOWER.
ONE OF A KIND.
WOW.
IM NOT GOOD WITH THE PATH.
WHATS THIS?
IF YOU DO NOT WANT THE PLAY
ANYMORE, FOLLOW THIS PATH AND
YOUR ADVENTURE WILL END.
OH, YEAH, WHERE AM I GOING?
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," ITS THAT TIME.
EVERYBODY DROP YOUR BUFFS.
WE ARE MERGED.Ñi
ITS ANOTHER "SURVIVOR" FIRST.
COME ON IN.
WAIT, WHAT?
OH, HELL NO!
IT AINT OVER.
WHATS GOING ON?
IM SO EXCITED.
YES, TREE MAIL.
ARE YOU GUYS READY?
OH, MY GOD.
ITS TIME.
YES.
YOU FINALLY GET TO GO.
TIME FOR SOME PAYBACK.