Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
WERE GOING TO HAVE TO EARN
THIS.
Jeff: KAMA GETTING YOUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE LESU TRIBE.
STILL INTRACT.
KAMA GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW MANU TRIBE.
WENDY VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHOA.
Jeff: WOW.
WARDOG, DID YOU SEE THAT
REACTION?
THAT WAS A TRUE CELEBRATION.
IT WAS.
DEFINITELY THE TRIBAL LINES ARE
STILL INTACT.
ITS EIGHT KAMA AND FOUR OLD
MANU.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SHALL WE GET TO IT?
YES.
Jeff: EVERYBODY DROP YOUR
BUFFS.
WE ARE MERGED.
THANK YOU.
Jeff: YOUR NEW BUFFS, TAKE
ONE AND PASS THEM DOWN.
I LOVE THE COLOR.
HOW FUN IS THAT.
AS SOON AS JEFF SAYS WERE
MERGED, THATS LIKE A DREAM COME
TRUE, BUT I DONT KNOW WHATS
GOING TO GO ON, SO I AM A LITTLE
WORRIED.
THATS WHAT MAKES SURVIVOR
GREAT.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHATS LOOMING
AROUND THE CORNER.
Jeff: WELL, OVER THE YEARS
CERTAIN MOMENTS ON "SURVIVOR"
HAVE BECOME ICONIC.
SOME MOMENTS TAKE YEARS TO
BECOME ICONIC.
OTHERS BECOME ICONIC THE MOMENT
THEY HAPPEN.
THIS MIGHT BE ONE OF THEM.
OH, GOD.
Jeff: COME ON IN.
WAIT.
WHAT?
I KNEW IT!
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THERES ALWAYS A TWIST.
OH, MY GOD, THEYRE ALL
COMING.
OH, MY GOD.
WOW.
THEYRE ALL BACK.
IT AINT OVER.
Jeff: THIS SEASON EVER
VOTED.
-OUT PLAYER HAD A DECISION
TO MAKE.
THEY COULD GIVE UP, OR THEY
COULD DECIDE TO STAY AND FIGHT
FOR ANOTHER SHOT TO GET BACK IN
THIS GAME.
THIS SEASON EVERY PLAYER VOTED
OUT OPTED TO FIGHT FOR ANOTHER
SHOT.
THEY WERE TAKEN TO ANOTHER
ISLAND, THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: THE DETAILS OF WHAT
THEYVE BEEN THROUGH OUT THERE
WILL BE THEIRS TO SHARE AS
INFORMATION IS KEY, BUT I FEEL
COMPELLED TO SHARE THAT THEY
HAVE HAD TO WORK EVERY BIT AS
HARD AS YOU HAVE SINCE THEYVE
BEEN VOTED OUT.
WOW.
Jeff: HERES HOW ITS GOING
TO GO.
ONE OF THESE STICKS IS ABOUT TO
EARN THEIR WAY BACK INTO THE
GAME.
FOR YOUR EDGE OF EXTINCTION
CHALLENGE, YOURE GOING THE RACE
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES
GETTING YOU TO THE FINISH WHERE
YOU MUST MANEUVER A BALL THROUGH
THE TOP OF A VERY LONG TRACK.
FIRST TO FINISH EARNS THEIR WAY
BACK INTO THIS GAME.
BEFORE WE RUN, DURING YOUR TIME
ON DISTINCTION, YOUVE HAD THE
OPPORTUNITY TO EARN ADVANTAGES
TO HELP YOU IN THIS CHALLENGE.
SOME OF YOU WERE SUCCESSFUL.
CHRIS, YOU EARNED THE ADVANTAGE
OF BAMBOO AND STRING, ALLOWING
DO YOU PRACTICE THE MIDDLE PHASE
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
DID YOU PUT IT TO USE?
YEAH, EVERY MORNING.
Jeff: YOU ALSO EARNED A
ADVANTAGE TO DISADVANTAGE
ANOTHER PERSON.
YES, I DID.
Jeff: BY GIVING THEM 30
KNOTS IN THE FINAL STAGE OF THIS
CHALLENGE.
WHO DID YOU DECIDE TO GIVE THOSE
KNOTS TO?
IM GOING TO ASSIGN THIS TO
MR. GOLIATH OVER HERE, CHRIS.
Jeff: SO, CHRIS, YOU HAVE
BOTH AN ADVANTAGE AND A
DISADVANTAGE.
EVERYBODY ELSE, YOURE ON YOUR
OWN.
THIS IS THE MOMENT YOUVE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
LETS DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR YOUR SHOT BACK IN THE GAME,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOURE GOING THE RACE UP
THE FRAME.
ITS A LADDER WITHOUT ANY RUNGS.
THEN ITS OVER THE CARGO NET TO
UNTIE YOUR BAG.
CHRIS IS OUT QUICKLY.
DEVENS IS OUT QUICKLY.
THERES KEITH.
THERE COMES AUBRY, WENDY, AND
REEM.
YOU SPENT A LOT OF TIME ON
DISTINCTION FOR THIS MOMENT.
WHATEVER IS IN THE TANK YOU NEED
IT NOW.
CHRIS HAS HIS BAG.
DEVENS HAS HIS.
KEITH HAS HIS.
WENDY HAS HERS.
AUBRY HAS HERS.
CHRIS IN THE LEAD.
EVERYBODY NOW RACING TO UNTIE
THEIR KNOTS TO GET TO THE NEXT
STAGE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
YOU GUYS GOT IT.
KEEP WORKING.
THERE YOU GO, RICK.
Jeff: EVERYBODY IS SILL IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
REEM HAS HER BAG.
DROP AND GET IT.
CHRIS IS THROUGH FIRST.
STARTS UNTYING HIS BAMBOO.
THEN AUBRY, WENDY, AND DEVENS
RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
YOURE TRYING TO BUILD A BAMBOO
POLE LONG ENOUGH THAT YOU CAN
STICK IT THROUGH THE CAGE AND
RETRIEVE YOUR KEY.
CHRIS EARNED THE ADVANTAGE WITH
LOTS OF DAYS TO PRACTICE.
WILL IT PAY OFF HERE RIGHT NOW?
AUBRY NOW WITH HER STICK.
WILL IT BE LONG ENOUGH?
AUBRY VERY CLOSE.
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: AUBRY HAS HERS.
AUBRY IS FIRST TO GET HER KEY.
AUBRY IS GOING TO GET THROUGH
THAT CAGE DOOR FIRST.
SHES COMING FOR BLOOD,
YALL.
Jeff: AUBRY IS THROUGH,
MOVING ON TO THE FINAL PHASE OF
THIS CHALLENGE.
HER JOB NOW IS TO MANEUVER THAT
BALL TO THE TOP OF THE LONG
TRACK.
CHRIS NOW GOING THE GIVE IT A
GO.
DEVENS NOW GOING TO GIVE IT A
OH, MY GOD.
Jeff: CHRIS HAS HIS KEY.
DEVENS HAS HIS KEY.
WOW.
GOOD JOB, RICK.
WE HAVE A CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY IS FIGHTING RIGHT NOW.
CHRIS IS THROUGH.
DEVENS RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
WENDY HAS HER KEY.
REEM HAS HER KEY.
CHRIS NOW HAS 30 KNOTS AS A
PENALTY ASSIGNED TO HIM BY
KEITH.
COME ON, KEITH.
Jeff: KEITH FALLS SHORT.
GOT TO WORK ON THAT STICK.
REEM IS THROUGH.
WENDY IS IN THE FINAL PHASE OF
THE CHALLENGE.
CHRIS FEELING THE PENALTY OF
THOSE 30 KNOTS.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THERE IS A
STEEP LEARNING CURVE TO THIS
FINAL PHASE.
THIS IS GOING TO REQUIRE
PATIENCE.
PANIC IS NOT YOUR FRIEND IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
AUBRY DROPS AND HAS TO START
AGAIN.
REEM DROPS AND HAS TO START
DEVENS LOOKING GOOD.
THERE YOU GO, RICK.
Jeff: WENDY DOING A NICE
JOB.
VERY SLOW, VERY STEADY, INCH BY
INCH.
MOVING UP THIS TRACK.
WENDY WITH ALL KINDS OF
OBSTACLES TO OVERCOME, AND SHE
IS DOING IT.
IT IS WENDY AND DEVENS RIGHT NOW
IN THE LEAD.
CHRIS NOW HAS HIS BALLS FREE.
HE CAN GET IN ON THIS.
YOU GOT IT, KEITH.
Jeff: KEITH STILL WORKING
ON HIS STICK.
HES BEEN OUT THERE A LONG TIME.
GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER GO.
IS IT STRONG ENOUGH?
KEITH HAS HIS KEY.
KEITH IS GOING TO BE IN THIS
NOW.
LETS GO, KEITH!
KEITH IS THROUGH.
WEVE GOT EVERYBODY NOW IN THIS
FINAL STAGE.
WENDY IS THE ONE THE BEAT.
VERY CLOSE TO THE TOP.
NICE.
Jeff: DEVENS JUST BEHIND
HER.
GOOD JOB, RICK.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
Jeff: CHRIS IS BACK MANY
THIS.
MICE MOVE, THERE CHRIS.
Jeff: REEM STRUGGLING.
THANKS.
Jeff: AUBRY PLAYING
RECKLESS NOW.
SHE HAS TO.
KEITH HAS FIGURED THIS CHALLENGE
OUT VERY QUICKLY.
KEITH DROPS.
HES GOT TO START AGAIN.
THREE PEOPLE IN IT NOW.
IT IS WENDY ALONE IN THE LEAD.
CHRIS AND DEVENS RIGHT ON HER
TAIL.
WENDY INCHES AWAY.
CAN SHE GET IT TO DROP?
WENDY DROPS.
WENDY HAS TO START AGAIN.
CHRIS NOW IN THE LEAD.
YOU HAVE PLENTY OF TIME,
BUDDY.
Jeff: CHRIS NOW VERY CLOSE
TO THE TOP, GETTING CLOSER AND
CLOSER.
HES GOT A STEADY HAND.
IS THIS IT?
YOU GOT IT.
Jeff: NO!
CHRIS DROPS.
INCHES AWAY FROM THE TOP.
WOW.
IT IS NOW DEVENS WITH A SHOT.
INCHES AWAY.
CAN HE DROP IT?
OH, MY GOSH.
STILL HOVERING.
DEVENS DOES IT!
DEVENS EARNS HIS WAY BACK INTO
THIS GAME.
DEVENS HAS DONE IT.
THAT TIME ON DISTINCTION WAS
WITH IT.
A HUGE EFFORT BY EVERYBODY AS
THE TEARS START TO FLOW FOR
EVERYONE.
IM REALLY SORRY.
THATS OKAY, DUDE.
Jeff: DEVENS, YOU
ACCOMPLISHED THE GOAL OF
DISTINCTION, WHICH IS THEY THERE
LONG ENOUGH TO GET A SHOT AND
THEN MAKE IT PAY OFF.
YOU ARE BACK IN THIS GAME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
[APPLAUSE]
DEVENS!
Jeff: JOIN YOUR NEW MERGED
TRIBE.
OH, GOD.
CONGRATS, RICK.
IM LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS.
Jeff: DEVENS HAS A FRESH
START IN THIS GAME, BUT THATS
ALL YOU HAVE.
AND NOW DISTINCTION BEGINS
AGAIN.
OH, BOY.
Jeff: EVERY PERSON VOTED
OUT WILL HAVE THE SAME
OPPORTUNITY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU ARE MERGING THE MANU BEACH,
WHERE YOUR FEAST AWAITS.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, COME
UP WITH A NEW TRIBE NAME.
BEFORE EDGE OF EXTINCTION THE
GAME IN A LOT OF WAYS WAS
GETTING THE BEST OF ME, BUT IF I
CAN WIN MY WAY BACK INTO THE
GAME, I CAN WIN CHALLENGES.
IM A WHOLE NEW MAN THANKS TO
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
Jeff: AUBRY, THATS THE
MOMENT YOU HOPE FOR.
THATS WHAT KEPT YOU GOING.
"SURVIVOR" HAS JUST GIVEN ME
SO MUCH IN MY LIFE, AND I OWE SO
MUCH TO THIS GAME, AND IM
GRATEFUL, BUT I GOT PLAYED, AND
I GOT PLAYED HARD.
IM PROUD TO STAND WITH THESE
GUYS, AND IM JUST GRATEFUL TO
YOU, JEFF, AND EVERYONE HERE,
BECAUSE I DONT THINK I WOULD
HAVE GROWN UP WITHOUT
"SURVIVOR."
Jeff: REEM, WHY ARE YOU OUT
HERE?
DUDE, LIKE IVE BEEN WATCHING
THIS FOR 18 YEARS.
ITS MY FAVORITE SHOW.
THIS IS NO TALKING, DONT CALL
ME.
THIS IS THE KIDS, COME AND
WATCH, THIS ITS FAMILY TIME.
THIS IS THE DREAM.
AND I GET VOTED OUT, AND THEN I
END UP IN HELL, MAN.
LIKE IT SUCKED.
BUT I COULDNT RAISE THAT MAST.
IM PROUD OF MYSELF.
Jeff: KEITH, HOW DO YOU GET
THROUGH DISTINCTION?
-- EXTINCTION IN.
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION, YOU
LIVE MOMENT BY MOMENT.
YOU TAKE IT STEP BY STEP, AND
THAT PAST BECOMES EVERYTHING
THAT YOU WANT.
IT BECOMES THE FOOD THAT YOU
WANT.
IT BECOMES A BED.
IM SO PROUD THAT I DID NOT GIVE
UP.
Jeff: WENDY, WHAT ARE YOU
FEELING RIGHT NOW?
YOURE FRESHLY OUT OF THE GAME?
YEAH, I FEEL KIND OF BAD THAT
I DIDNT SPEND AS LONG AS THESE
PEOPLE ON EXTINCTION.
I WENT, HAD A NICE REST, AND I
WAS BACK IN THE GAME, BUT ALL OF
YOU KHWEIS SHOULD BE SO PROUD
THAT THE SECOND YOU TOUCHED THE
SAND ON THE BEACH, YOU GUYS ARE
WINNERS, YOU HAD AN OPPORTUNITY,
NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE.
Jeff: CHRIS, WHAT WAS THE
LOWEST POINT FOR YOU ON
EXTINCTION?
WHEN I CAME OUT HERE, I
WANTED TO PLAY THIS PERFECT
GAME, AND TO HAVE THAT SLIP
THREW MY HANDS, AND HAVING TO
EMBRACE THAT AND UNDERSTAND,
LIKE, YOU CANT BE PERFECT,
YOURE GOING TO SCREW UP.
BUT BEING OUT THERE WITH THESE
GUYS, YOU HAVE TO PUT ON A FACE.
YOU DIDNT HAVE TO FAKE
ANYTHING.
YOU COULD JUST BE YOURSELF, AND
IT WAS LIKE THERAPY FOR ME.
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
REEM, KEITH, CHRIS, AUBRY,
WENDY, YOU HAVE ANOTHER DECISION
TO MAKE.
OH, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
Jeff: WHO WANTS TO GO BACK
THE DISTINCTION ISLAND FOR
ANOTHER SHOT BACK IN THIS GAME?
LETS DO IT!
Jeff: EVERYBODY GOING BACK.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
THE BOAT.
YOUR ADVENTURE CONTINUES.
WERE BACK, WERE BACK, WERE
BACK.
WHEN YOU THINK YOUVE GONE
LOW ON "SURVIVOR," IT CAN GO SO
MUCH LOWER, THE LOWER YOU GO,
THE HIGHER THE HIGHS.
WHEN JEFF SAID THAT WE COULD
COME BACK, I WAS JUMPING UP AND
DOWN LIKE A CHILD ON CHRISTMAS
MORNING.
WERE STILL IN.
IM NOT OUT OF IT.
I AM STILL PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
OH, MY GOD.
YOU LOOK SO GOOD.
WE ARRIVED AT THE MERGE, AND
I HAVE THIS OVERWHELMING FEELING
OF EXCITEMENT AND JOY.
WE ARE GOING INTO THIS WITH ALL
OF THE KAMA MEMBERS BACK
TOGETHER SOME WE HAVE EIGHT
PEOPLE IF WE CAN STICK TOGETHER.
WERE GOING TO HAVE THE
MAJORITY.
THATS AN INCREDIBLE FEELING.
HOW WAS DISTINCTION ISLAND?
ITS PURGATORY.
THE TWIST IS RIGHT ON YOUR BUFF.
YOU GET A TORCH, THERES MAP,
AND THERES A BOAT AND A
SHIPWRECK.
OF ALL THE FACES THAT I SAW
DOING THAT CHALLENGE, DEVENS WAS
THE ONE PERSON I THOUGHT, OH,
HELL NO.
LIKE WHY ARE YOU BACK HERE NOW?
I DONT WANT HIM BACK HERE.
HOW ARE YOU WITH THE DAD BOD
IN.
DAD BOD IS BACK IN THE GAME.
IM BACK, BABY.
IM BACK IN THE GAME.
BUT THERE IS DEFINITELY A FEAR
THAT YOU WILL BE THE EASY VOTE
OUT BECAUSE YOU JUST CAME BACK
IN.
MAYBE THEY RESENT IT.
MAYBE ITS JUST EASY.
SO I NEED TO MAKE A HUMAN
CONNECTION REAL EARLY SO THEY
DONT WRITE ME OFF AS THE EASY
VOTE BACK TO EDGE OF EXTINCTION
BEFORE THEY GET TO KNOW ME.
I DONT KNOW HOW YOU FEEL IN
TERMS OF YOUR OLD TRIBE, BUT I
DIDNT KNOW --
THEY VOTED ME OFF.
SO AS MUCH AS I LOVE THEM, IM A
FREE AGENT RIGHT NOW.
THE MINUTE I START SPEAKING
TO RICK AT THE MERGE FEAST, I
KNEW THAT I REALLY LIKED HIM,
AND I FELL LIKE HE WAS A GENUINE
PERSON, JUST THE FACT THAT HE
HAD THAT BIG HERO MOMENT AND WAS
ABLE TO WIN A SPOT BACK INTO
THIS GAME, LIKE IM ROOTING FOR
HIM.
I WOULD NEVER WANT TO SEE HIM GO
BACK TO THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION
SO QUICKLY.
I MEAN, IT SOUNDS LIKE A SCARY
PLACE THAT I NEVER WANT TO GO
TO.
I NEW THAT COMING BAN WAS
GOING TO BE HARD, BUT ITS WHAT
I NEEDED.
OTHER PEOPLE, THOUGH, WE GET
BACK TO THIS ISLAND AND ITS
BUYERS REMORSE.
THEIR JOURNEY IS OUT OF THIS
GAME.
AFTER I LOST, I HONESTLY FELT
DOWN AGAIN, AND THEN IT HIT ME,
IF I GET OFF THIS ISLAND RIGHT
NOW, IVE GOTTEN MORE THAN WHAT
I EVER CAME WITH.
AND THEN THERE WAS THREE.
THEN THERE WAS THREE.
I DONT THINK ANYONE HAS HAD
AN EXPERIENCE LIKE I HAVE.
EVERYTHING THAT COULD HAVE GONE
WRONG DID GO WRONG, BUT AT THE
END OF THE DAY, I FEEL SO PROUD
OF MYSELF, AND THATS WHATS
MOST IMPORTANT FOR ME.
HOW CRAZY.
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION WILL
ONLY HEAT UP.
THE WEAK ARENT GOING TO
SURVIVE, BUT WHEN EVERYONE IS
CRUMBLING AROUND ME, I KNOW JUST
WHAT TO DO, AND I HAVE A GOAL.
IM GOING TO GET MY BUTT BACK IN
THIS GAME.
HE JUST CAME BACK.
UH-HUH.
IM WORKING WITH LAUREN.
WE HAVE TWO IDOLS.
THATS A LOT OF POWER.
WE CAN DO A LOT WITH THAT IF
DONE CORRECTLY.
WE NEED TO FIND A CRACK.
THE PROBLEM IS IM IN THIS
MINORITY GROUP.
IM GOING TO NEED EVERY TOOL
THAT I CAN GIVEN THE SITUATION
THAT IM IN.
SO I 1,000% HAVE TO HAVE A TALK
WITH JOE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
EVERYTHING?
I FEEL LIKE WERE... I FEEL
LIKE THIS IS SECOND CHANCE 2.0.
HERE I AM AGAIN WITH JOE
FREAKING INGLAM.
HERE HE IS AGAIN IN THE MAJORITY
ALINES.
I FEEL LIKE IM AT HIS MERCY.
WHY?
THIS IS AN ABSOLUTE NIGHTMARE
FOR ME.
WELL SEE HOW WELKE PITCH HIM.
THIS IS A SALES PITCH FOR ME.
I DONT KNOW HOW YOU FEEL ACT
THOSE GUYS AFTER THE AUBRY
THING.
I DONT LIKE IT.
I DONT TRUST MOST OF MY KAMAS
BECAUSE ITS LIKE THEYRE ALL
TOGETHER, BUT ME AND AUBRY WERE
LIKE... AND AURORA.
AURORA WAS ON THE OUTS.
I FEEL LIKE IM ON THE BOTTOM.
ITS A WEIRD STATE OF LIMBO.
I DEFINITELY SEE DAVID AND
DEVON GOING TO THAT SIDE.
I SEE THEM SHIFTING TO THAT
GROUP.
THAT WILL TRY TO TAKE YOU OUT.
IM NOT COMING FOR YOU, JOE.
IM NOT COMING FOR YOU.
I NEED YOU HERE, TOO.
I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE JOE
WILL COME WITH ME, BUT I AM
STILL TRYING TO DECIPHER, FIGURE
OUT THIS KAMA TRIBE.
SO I THINK THE BEST PLAN IS TO
MAKE IT AN EASY VOTE, TO TAKE
OUT RICK.
SO NOW WE HAVE ALL THE GIRLS.
WHAT IS THIS SIX GIRL, SEVEN
GUYS?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
WHATS THE IDEAL?
IM OPEN TO HEARING ALL
SUGGESTIONS.
WE WANT TO GET THROUGH A SAFE
VOTE.
AND RICKS NAME KIND OF POPPED
UP.
HE COULD BE AN EASY VOTE THAT
EVERYONE COULD GET ON BOARD
WITH.
THAT DOESNT CROSS TOO MANY
LINES.
I AM SHOCKED KELLEY AND
LAUREN WANT TO VOTE DEVENS OFF
FIRST AND SEND HIM RIGHT BACK TO
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
JUST FROM A MORAL STANDPOINT,
LIKE I DONT SEE HOW YOU COULD
POSSIBLY DO THAT TO SOMEBODY TO
SEND THEM RIGHT BACK TO WHERE
THEY CAME AFTER FACING THE ODDS.
I DONT THINK RICKS BAD
IDEA.
I DONT THINK IT PISSES ANYONE
OFF.
I THINK WE GET RID OF DEVENS,
TELL ME DEVENS OR DAVID.
ILL DO IT.
KELLEY AND LAUREN SEEM SO
BRUTAL.
MAYBE ONE OF THEM SHOULD BE SENT
HER MERRY WAY OFF TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
THATS A LOT OF PIECES THAT
WE CAN PLAY WITH.
THATS GOOD RIGHT THERE.
YOU GUYS NEED A HAND?
NOT REALLY.
WHEN I GOT BACK TO CAMP, I
OPENED MY BAG, AND THERE IS A IT
LITTLE SOMETHING THERE.
IM TRYING TO KEEP A STRAIGHT
FACE.
BECAUSE I KNOW I GOT TO GET AWAY
FROM EVERYONE AND FIND OUT WHAT
IS SITTING IN MY BAG.
AND SO I PRACTICALLY RUN DOWN
THE PATH, AND I GET DOWN THE
TRAIL, I UNWRAP IT, AND... HOLY
CRAP.
AND ITS THIS BEAUTY.
TWO PIECES WITH A NOTE.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE EARNED YOUR WAY BACK
IN.
STAYING IN MAY NOT BE AS EASY.
THIS MAY HELP."
YOU MUST GIVE ONE HALF OF THIS
IMMUNITY IDOL TO ANOTHER PLAYER.
IF YOURE BOTH STILL IN THE GAME
AFTER THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
THESE TWO PIECES WHEN USED
TOGETHER BECOME ONE IDOL WITH
FULL POWER.
SO ITS AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I CANT USE IT THIS TIME.
I KEEP HALF OF IT.
I GIVE THE OTHER HALF TO ANOTHER
PLAYER IN THE GAME.
THIS MAY BE THE ONLY BAR
DWAYNEING CHIP YOU HAVE TO STAY
IN THE GAME.
THIS IDOL HAS NO POWER UNTIL
AFTER THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HOLY CRAP.
BUT ITS TRICKY BECAUSE I CANT
USE IT THIS TIME.
SO I HAVE TO DO WHAT I HAVE TO
DO TO GET PAST THIS FIRST VOTE.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO TELL.
I HAVE AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH, BUT I HAVE TO
HALF OF IT TO SOMEONE ELSE.
OKAY.
BEFORE THE TRIBAL.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YEAH.
DAVIDS THE ONE I CAN TRUST
MOST, SO HES THE ONE I FEEL
LIKE IF I HAVE TO WORK THIS IDOL
WITH SOMEONE ELSE, IM GOING TO
SHARE IT WITH MY CLOSEST ALLY.
SO OBVIOUSLY IM PLANNING ON
GIVING YOU THE OTHER HALF.
IF EITHER OF US GETS VOTED OUT,
WERE DONE.
FOR THE FIRST VOTE, ITS NOT
AN IMMUNITY ILL DOLL.
ITS JUST A BARGAINING CHIP.
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT BE ON THE
BOTTOM.
SO IM SCARED TO DEATH GOING
INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
LETS GET TO YOUR FIRST
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, RON.
GOT TO TAKE BACK TRIBAL
IMMUNITY.
THANK YOU.
TRIBAL IMMUNITY NO MORE.
THIS IS NOW WHAT YOU COVET.
THE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
LETS GET TO IT.
FOR TODAYS CHALLENGE, YOURE
GOING TO STAND ON NARROW BEAM
WHILE BALANCING A STATUE AT
REGULAR INTERVALS.
YOULL MOVE FURTHER DOWN THE
BEAM, MAKING IT MORE DIFFICULT.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU FALL OFF THE
BEAM OR YOUR STATUE DROPS,
YOURE OUT.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SEVENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
WELL GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY LOOKS GOOD.
AND THIS CHALLENGE IS ON, AND
IMMEDIATELY A HUGE GUST OF WIND
COMES.
RON IS FIRST TO DROP.
RON IS OUT.
YOUR FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
13 PEOPLE IN THE GAME.
DEVENS EARNED HIS WAY BACK IN.
COULD HE PULL IT OFF RIGHT HERE?
LITTLE BIT OF MOVEMENT.
FROM VICTORIA NOW.
GAVIN DROPS.
GAVIN THE SECOND PERSON OUT.
WE ARE DOWN TO 11.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME NOW TO MOVE FURTHER
DOWN THE BEAM.
ITS MORE NARROW, MORE
DIFFICULT.
START MAKING YOUR MOVE.
THIS IS A LIVE TRANSITION.
SO IF YOU DROP HERE, YOU ARE
OUT.
WARDOG CANT MAKE THE
TRANSITION.
WARDOG IS OUT.
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS SUCCESSFULLY
MADE THE TRANSITION.
AND THIS CHALLENGE CONTINUES.
YOULL BE IN THIS SECTION FOR
FIVE MINUTES.
JUST LIKE THAT WITH ABSOLUTELY
NO MOVEMENT DEVENS IS OUT.
HIS STATUE DROPS.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
HERE COMES ANOTHER HUGE GUST OF
WIND.
VICTORIA ALLVE THE PLACE.
VICTORIA CANT GET THIS ONE
BACK.
MORE WIND.
AURORA DROPS.
AURORA IS OUT.
SIX HAVE ALREADY DROPPED.
SEVEN STILL FIGHTING.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY SUCCESSFULLY
TRANSITIONED TO THE NEXT PHASE
OF THIS CHALLENGE.
WELL STAY HERE FOR TEN MINUTES.
JOE VERY STEADY.
DAVID WITH A LITTLE BIT OF A
WOBBLE.
WITNESS AGAIN THAT WIND PICKING
UP, WHIPPING THROUGH THIS FIELD.
MY ARMS ARE NUMB.
THERES A BUG ON MY LEG.
IT TICKLES.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, HER ARMS
WENT NUMB.
IM SORRY.
Jeff: WENTWORTH CANNOT TAKE
IT ANYMORE.
SHE DROPS.
WENTWORTH IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO SIX.
ERIC, JULIA, DAVID, JULIE, JOE,
AND LAUREN.
WERE 20 MINUTES INTO THIS
CHALLENGE.
IT IS TIME THE MOVE INTO THE
MOST NARROW PART OF THE BEAM.
YOU HAVE TO MOVE ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO THE END AND GET TOES IN
THE RED.
START MAKING YOU MOVE.
ILL LET YOU KNOW WHEN YOU GET
THERE.
SLOW AND EASY.
NO NEED TO RACE.
ERIC CANT MAKE THE TRANSITION.
ERIC IS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO FIVE.
JULIA CANT DO IT.
JULIAS OUT.
WERE DOWN TO FOUR.
AND NOW DAVID WITH A GUST OF
WIND WOBBLES.
HES OUT.
WERE DOWN TO THREE.d
EVERYBODY IS GOOD.
THAT TRANSITION GOT A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
JULIE, JOE, AND LAUREN ALL STILL
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
BEEN UP THERE 40 MINUTES.
THIS IS NOT EASY.
JULIE HAS BEEN VERY STEADY THIS
ENTIRE CHALLENGE.
JULIE, YOURE HOT.
ILL TAKE IT.
SHES BUFF.
Jeff: JOE HAS BEEN VERY
STEADY.
LAUREN REALLY HAS THE FRONT OF
HER POLE DIPPING DOWN NOW.
JOE DROPS OUT OF NOWHERE.
HE HAD BEEN ROCK STEADY.
AND WERE DOWN TO TWO.
JULIE AND LAUREN.
HERE COMES THE WIND NOW MAKING
IT EVEN MORE DIFFICULT.
LAUREN MOVING ALL OVER.
THAT STATUE HOLDING FIRM.
THAT WIND NO JOKE.
REALLY BLOWING.
CRAP.
Jeff: ANOTHER GUST OF WIND.
Jeff: LAUREN DROPS.
JULIE WINS FIRST INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY, SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
WOW.
THAT WAS SUDDEN.
LAUREN, GREAT JOB.
GREAT JOB, LADY.
YOU GIRLS ARE STRONG.
Jeff: JULIE, COME ON OVER.
JULIE, FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
WIN.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IF YOU CAN EXPRESS WHAT IT MEANS
THE MAKE HIT THE LONG AND WIN,
WHAT IS IT?
I FEEL LIKE IVE BEEN WANTING
TO BE ON "SURVIVOR" FOR 18
YEARS, AND TO WIN THIS FIRST
IMMUNITY IS...
YEAH, JULIE.
[APPLAUSE]
I FEEL LIKE MY KIDS AND MY
HUSBAND WILL BE SO PROUD OF ME.
Jeff: JULIE SAFE TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, SOMEBODY
WILL BE THE SEVENTH PERSON VOTED
OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
CONGRATS.
THE PLAN TO GET OUT DEVENS
TONIGHT HAS BEEN DISCUSSED WITH
EVERYONE, AND EVERYONE APPEARS
TO BE ON BOARD, BUT THERES SO
MANY DIFFERENT WAYS THAT IT
COULD GO.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT I HAVE A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IM VERY EXCITED THAT I HAVE
THAT LITTLE CUSHION, BECAUSE
PLAYING "SURVIVOR" BEFORE, I
KNOW HOW CRAZY VOTING IS AFTER
THE MERGE, SO I MIGHT HAVE TO
BRING OUT THE BIG GUNS.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN SCARED TO
DEATH GOING INTO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT, BUT THE FACT THAT ILL
BE WEARING THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE, THERES NO BLINDSIDES
ON ME TONIGHT.
THATS LIKE THE MOST COMFORTABLE
FEELING I COULD HAVE.
IM DYING TO TALK TO YOU.
KELLEY AND LAUREN, WE COULD
BRING IN DAVID AND RICK AND GET
KELLEY OUT.
KELLEY IS A HUGE THREAT.
AS A RETURNING PLAYER, SHE NEEDS
TO GO.
THESE ARE THE KINDS OF THINGS I
KNEW I NEEDED TO START
ORCHESTRATEING.
IM NOT JUST GOING ALONG WITH
WHATEVER PEOPLE ARE DELG ME TO
DO.
EVERYONE ON YOUR TRIBE IS
THROWING YOU UNDER THE BUS AND
THINKS YOU SHOULD GO RIGHT BACK
THERE.
THERES IN WAY IN HELL I WOULD
SEND YOU BACK, THERE BUT YOU
HAVE TO TRUST ME.
WE KNOW YOU AND DAVID LOOK LIKE
A PAIR.
WERE NOT GOINGhTG TELL YOU
DETAILS OF NAMES OR WHO OR WHAT,
BUT YOURE NOT GOING HOME.
I FEEL TOTALLY BETRAYED BY
THOSE THREE LESU MEMBERS TO SEND
ME RIGHT BACK IS A TOTAL STAB IN
THE BACK.
BUT I GOT PEOPLE ON MY SIDE
APPARENTLY, WHICH IS AWESOME.
WELL, LET ME GIVE YOU THIS.
THIS IS THE HALF OF THE IMMUNITY
IDOL.
OKAY.
JULIE SAID ALL OF LESU IS
VOTING FOR ME.
THEY HAVE NO QUALMS ABOUT VOTING
ME RIGHT BACK OUT.
THAT IS SUCH BAD GAME PLAY ON
THEIR PART.
JULIE SAID VOTE WITH US
TONIGHT AND WELL SAVE YOU.
I DONT EVEN KNOW WHO WERE
VOTING FOR YET.
BUT THEY WILL TELL ME, AND THEN
THEY WILL TELL ME WHO TO TELL
YOU.
IT SHOULD BE WENTWORTH.
I AGREE.
THANKS FOR THIS, BY THE WAY.
IT MEANS A LOT.
WERE IN IT TOGETHER.
WE ARE, DUDE.
A WHOLE WILL THE ON THE LINE
TONIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE IF I CAN GET THROUGH
TONIGHT, THEN WE HAVE THAT
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT COULD BE A WHOLE NEW
BALLGAME.
IT MIGHT BE THE PATH FORWARD IN
THIS GAME IVE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
RIGHT BACK TO WORK, JOE.
GOT TO FINISH IT, BRO.
WE GOT WORK TO DO.
WANT TO GO RIGHT NOW?
ILL GO.
OH, OKAY.
LETS GO.
HEY, BUDDY.
HEY.
WHATS THE PLAN?
WHAT DO I DO?
YOU GO FOLLOW THOSE GUYS AND
MAKE SURE THEYRE NOT ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK TONIGHT.
OKAY.
I HOPE NOT.
WHO DO YOU WANT TO VOTE FOR?
I DONT KNOW, MAN.
THIS GAME MOVES FAST, SO A
COUPLE DIFFERENT CLICKS OF
PEOPLE GET TOGETHER AND WANT THE
MAKE A MOVE.
JOE MADE A MISTAKE.
JOE, WHO DO I VOTED FOR, WHATS
GOING ON?
HE WAS VERY VAGUE.
IT DID NOT MAKE ME FEEL GOOD.
JOE IS BRUSHING ME ASIDE.
RIGHT NOW I DONT KNOW THAT I
CAN TRUST HIM.
WHAT HE DOESNT KNOW IS MY TRUE
ALLIANCE IS ERIC.
JULIE, JULIA, GAVIN, AND
VICTORIA, WERE THE KAMA SIX.
SO IM THINKING JOE LOSING IS A
GREAT OPPORTUNITY, BECAUSE IF
YOURE PLAYING "SURVIVOR" AND
YOU HAVE CHANCE TO TAKE OUT JOE,
EVERY TIME IS THE RIGHT TIME.
AND SO IVE GOT TO CONVINCE THE
KAMA SIX ITS JOE TONIGHT.
THERE THEY ARE.
GUYS, THEYRE HERE.
THERES ONE, TWO, RIGHT HERE.
HE DOESNT HAVE AN IDOL.
HES NOT EXPECTING IT.
JUST THE SIX?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
FOCUS ON THAT ONE.
GO SLOW, GUYS.
DANG.
WE MIGHT HAVE LOST HIM FOR
NOW.
ROUND ONE GOES TO THE
CHICKENS.
RON WANTS TO DO JOE, BECAUSE
JOE LOST.
NOW IS THE TIME TO GET RID OF
JOE.
I WOULD RATHER GO THE SAFER
OPTION AND GET RID OF KELLEY,
BUT ITS DEFINITELY IMPORTANT TO
GET THE DECISION RIGHT TONIGHT.
ITS
FEELS GOOD, RIGHT?
I ALREADY TALKED TO JULIA.
OKAY.
WERE JUST REHASHING MAKING
SURE NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
RON WANTS TO VOTE JOE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
ID A GO KELLEY.
KELLEY?
KELLEY.
THERES A LOT OF DIFFERENT
OPTIONS TONIGHT.
JOE BEING ONE OF THEM.
IVE HEARD RICKS NAME THROWN
OUT THERE.
IVE HEARD KELLEY WENTWORTHS
NAME THROWN OUT THERE.
THERES THREE VERY GOOD OPTIONS
ON THE TABLE.
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHICH ONE
WILL BEST SUIT US.
LETS CHECK IN.
IM PRETTY SURE WERE ALL ON THE
EXACT SAME PAGE.
I THINK WE HAVE TO TAKE A SHOT
AT EITHER JOE OR KELLEY.
TOO SOON TO GET RID OF JOE.
LISTEN, I CAN SEE THE
ARGUMENT FOR JOE, BUT I THINK
KELLEY.
IT CAN GO A MILLION DIFFERENT
WAY, BUT AT SOME POINT THE SIX
OF US HAVE TO COME TO A
CONSENSUS.
THERE IS NOT A GENERAL
CONSENSUS AS TO WHO SHOULD BE
VOTED OUT, BECAUSE ALL OF US CAN
MAKE A DIFFERENT CASE FOR WHY
KELLEY OR JOE SHOULD BE VOTED
OUT TONIGHT, AND THEYRE ALL
GOOD CASES.
ITS GETTING TRICKY.
ITS GOING VERY TRICKY.
IT IS REALLY IMPORTANT TO MAKE
THE RIGHT DECISION, BECAUSE THE
VERY FIRST VOTE RIGHT AT THE
MERGE CAN DICTATE THE REST OF
THE GAME.
Jeff: IF YOU DONT YET HAVE
A TORCH, GRAB ONE AND GET FIRE.
WELL NOW BRING IN THE MEMBERS
OF OUR JURY.
WHATS HAPPENING?
OH, BOY.
Jeff: REEM, CHRIS, AND
AUBRY, AFTER FAILING IN THEIR
BID TO GET BACK IN THE GAME TOOK
THE OPTION TO RETURN TO EDGE OF
EXTINCTION AND AWAIT ANOTHER
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THE GAME.
ALL RIGHT.
JULIE, WHAT WAS THE FEELING WITH
KAMA WHEN YOU REALIZED WE WERE
MERGING?
WAS IT THIS COULD BE FANTASTIC
FOR US?
IT WAS THE FEELING, BUT WE
WERE ALSO REALLY EXCITED TO MEET
NEW SUPREME, PEEK SPEAK TO THEM,
AND START PLAYING THE GAME THAT
WE HAVENT BEEN ABLE TO BEFORE
TONIGHT.
Jeff: RON, YOU HAD A
REACTION TO THAT?
I LOVE KAMA.
EVERYONE KNOWS THIS.
I DIDNT WANT TO SWAP.
I LOOK DOWN AND SAW THE YELLOW
BUFF, I SAID, YEP.
THEN I LOOK DOWN AND SAW A BUNCH
MORE YELLOW.
IM LIKE, THIS IS AWESOME.
Jeff: WENTWORTH, ARE YOU
SURPRISED TO BE SURPRISED TO
HEAR RON SAY HES GLAD KAMA
STAYED TOGETHER?
IM IN THE MINORITY.
IT DOESNT MAKE ME SUPER
EXCITED, BUT OVER THE PAST FEW
DAYS A LOT OF NEW RELATIONSHIPS
ARE FORMING.
I DONT KNOW ITS SO CUT AND
DRY.
Jeff: ONE OF THE OTHER BIG
STORIES IS EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
YOU EARNED YOUR WAY BACK INTO
THE GAME.
WHAT DID YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE
TRIBE, THE DYNAMICS CHANGE ALL
THE TIME?
ALL RIGHT I DONT KNOW THE
LESU DYNAMICS SINCE I LEFT.
PLUS I HAVENT MET ANYONE ON THE
ORIGINAL KAMA.
I SPENT ALL MY TIME IN
PURGATORY.
Jeff: WAS THERE ANY TALK TO
GET RID OF DEVENS SAYING, WE
VOTED HIM OUT ONCE?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
TO SEND IMRIGHT BACK, THERE
THATS STRAIGHT-UP EVIL IN MY
OPINION.
WHY WOULD WE GET RID OF SOMEBODY
WHO IS NOT A BIG THREAT COMING
INTO THE MERGE?
I JUST THINK THERE ARE BIGGER
TARGETS OUT THERE.
Jeff: JOE, WHAT DO YOU READ
INTO THAT IN.
VICTORIA SAID THERE ARE
BIGGER TARGETS.
AS A STRONGER PLAYER, THAT
DOESNT MAKE ME FEEL GOOD.
I NOW HAVE TO HAVE MANY I LITTLE
TINGLERS GOING OFF, IF YOU WILL.
I DONT THINK I SAID PHYSICAL
THREAT, DID I?
BECAUSE THERE ARE OTHER KINDS OF
THREATS.
THERE ARE STRATEGIC THREATS IN.
DID I TAKE IT THE WRONG WAY
IF I FELT THAT WAS DIRECTED AT
ME THEN IT WAS ACCURATE?
THERE ARE OTHER THINGS THAT
ARE THREATENING TO ME, SO I WANT
THE CLEAR UP WHAT I MEANT.
Jeff: RON, WHAT ABOUT
IDOLS?
PEOPLE TALKED ABOUT IDOLS.
I THINK IM FAIRLY PERCEPTIVE
PERSON, BUT I CANT TELL THIS
ANYONE HAS ONE.
NO ONE IS MENTIONING IT.
IT SEEMS LIKE THEY DONT EXIST.
EVERY SEASON YOU FEEL THAT
WAY UNTIL ALL OF A SUDDEN FOUR
IDOLS POP UP IN THE SAME TRIBAL.
SO IF THERE ARE SOME IDOLS OUT
THERE, MAYBE THEYRE NOT SHARING
THAT INFORMATION.
Jeff: DEVON, WHAT WAS THE
FEELING AT CAMP THIS AFTERNOON?
WAS IT CASUAL?
WAS IT FRENETIC.
DID PARANOIA KICK?
WHEN IT CAME TO STRATEGY,
NOBODY WANTS TO TELL YOU WHO
THEYRE GOING AFTER.
JOE DIDNT DO ANYTHING TODAY.
HE JUST PAINTED.
ARE YOU THAT COMFORTABLE THAT
YOU DONT NEED TO TALK TO
ANYBODY, OR ARE YOU THAT SCARED
THAT YOURE NOT GOING TO TALK TO
ANYBODY.
IT WAS WEIRD.
Jeff: WHAT WAS IT, JOE?
I KNOW WHERE I STAND WITH
MEMBERS OF MY TRIBE.
I HOME THAT KAMA STRONG DOES
STAY STRONG.
IM RELYING ON THOSE PAST
RELATIONSHIPS TO GET ME THROUGH
THIS EVENING.
JEFF, WHEN YOU HAVE THE
MAJORITY, YOU DONT NEED TO
SCRAMBLE SO MUCH.
WE WERE RELAXED BECAUSE WE KNEW
WE HAD THE POWER.
WE DIDNT NEED TO SCRAMBLE.
Jeff: WOW.
WENTWORTH, THATS SO FRUSTRATING
TO HEAR, ISNT IT?
YOU KIND OF CHUCKLE, BECAUSE
ITS FUNNY THAT HE SO BLATANTLY
SAID, THAT BUT IF YOURE ME,
YOURE ALWAYS ON THE BOTTOM.
SO...
Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
TIME TO VOTE.
VICTORIA, YOURE UP.
ILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
Jeff: IF NIBIRU -- IF
ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
ILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, DEVENS.
KELLEY.
DAVID.
DEVENS.
THATS TWO VOTES DEVENS.
DAVID.
THATS TWO VOTES DAVID.
WENTWORTH.
WERE TIED.
TWO VOTES DEVENS, TWO VOTES
DAVID, TWO VOTES WENTWORTH.
DAVID.
THATS THREE VOTES DAVID.
JOE.
THATS TWO VOTES JOE.
WERE TIED.
THREE VOTES JOE, THREE VOTES
DAVID.
JOE.
THATS FOUR VOTES JOE.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JOE.
THATS FIVE.
THATS ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
GOOD PLAY, GUYS.
Jeff: JOE, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE, JOE.
SEE YA, JOE.
YOU MADE A BIG MISTAKE.
EASY DECISION.
LEFT THE DOOR WIDE OPEN.
THATS THE WORST THING THEY
COULD HAVE DONE.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN YOURE FLYING
HIGH...
THEY HAVE THE POWER.
IM THE PUPPET MASTER.
IM TRYING THE BREAK THEM DOWN.
Jeff: AND LOSE CONTROL.
ONE OF US IS DRUNK RIGHT NOW.
YOURE GETTING PLAYED.
I HAVE TO FIND ANOTHER PATH
THE DAY 39.
Jeff: PREPARE FOR A CRASH.
MEDICAL!
OH, MY GOD.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
THE ONE THING I FEARED
HAPPENING HAPPENED TONIGHT.
IM TRYING THE KEEP MY EMOTIONS
TOGETHER AND NOT BREAK, BUT
MAYBE I NEED TO BE HERE.
SORRY, MAN.
WE WERE ROOTING FOR YOU.
THATS SO LAME.
THE THEME OF THE MERGE FLAG
WAS THE PHOENIX.
YOU GOT TO DIE TO BE BORN AGAIN.
THATS EXACTLY WHAT IM GOING TO
DO THIS SEASON.