>> Jeff: WELCOME TO THE SEASON
FINALE OF "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION."
TO MARK OUR 19th YEAR AND
OUR 38th SEASON, WE HAVE A
PRETTY SIMPLE QUESTION WE WANTED
TO EXPLORE: HOW FAR WOULD
PLAYERS BE WILLING TO GO FOR A
SHOT TO GET BACK IN THE GAME,
AND WHAT MIGHT THEY LEARN ABOUT
THEMSELVES IN THE PROCESS?
TONIGHT IT WILL ALL BE REVEALED.
THIS IS THE GROUP.
THEY'VE BEEN LIVING ON THE EDGE
OF EXTINCTION.
WENDY AND KEITH LEFT THE SHOW.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S TOUGH OUT THERE.
THE REST OF THE PLAYERS ARE
STILL IN IT.
TONIGHT THEY WILL ALL BATTLE,
AND ONE OF THEM WILL GET BACK IN
THE GAME.
THAT PERSON WILL JOIN OUR FINAL
FIVE, GAVIN, JULIE, LAUREN,
VICTORIA, AND DEVENS, WHO
ALREADY WON HIS WAY BACK IN.
THREE OF THEM WILL MAKE IT TO
THE END WITH A SHOT AT THE $1
MILLION PRIZE AND THE TITLE OF
SOLE SURVIVOR.
WE ARE LIVE IN LOS ANGELES WITH
A PACKED HOUSE, BECAUSE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT IS "SURVIVOR"
NIGHT.
AND ONCE AGAIN MOST OF THIS
SEASON "SURVIVOR" THE
HIGHEST-RATED SHOW FOR YOUNG
ADULT, AND THAT'S THANKS TO YOU
GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
IT IS THE FINALE, "SURVIVOR:
EDGE OF EXTINCTION."
AFTER 35 DAYS, ONLY FIVE REMAIN.
DEVENS, VICTORIA, JULIE, GAVIN,
AND LAUREN.
BUT THERE HAS NEVER BEEN A
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR" MORE WIDE
OPEN THAN THIS ONE.
BECAUSE 11 PLAYERS STILL HAVE
THE CHANCE TO BATTLE THEIR WAY
BACK IN FROM THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
WHO WILL IT BE?
AND WHO WILL GO ON TO WIN THE $1
MILLION PRIZE AND THE TIGHT OF
SOLE SURVIVOR?
COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME.
COME ON IN.
RETURNING FROM DISTINCTION FOR
THE LAST TIME.
YOU VOTED THEM OUT, ONE OF THEM
IS COMING BACK TO EITHER HELP OR
HAUNT.
SO LET'S REVIEW.
COMBINED YOU SPENT 151 NIGHTS ON
EXTING SHUN.
STARTING WITH YOU, REEM, THE
FIRST THE SAY YES, AND YOU NEVER
RAISED THAT SAIL.
YOU EACH HAVE DEEP PERSONAL
STORIES OF YOUR TIME ON
EXTINCTION.
SOMETIMES THOSE STORIES OVERLAP
AS YOU WORKED TO SURVIVE, BUT
TODAY YOU EACH HAVE ONE GOAL,
AND IT IS THE SAME -- DEFEAT
EVERYBODY ELSE TO GET BACK IN.
YOU HAVE SEEN TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THIS GAME IS ALIVE.
YOU GET BACK IN, YOU GOT A SHOT.
HERE'S HOW YOUR CHALLENGE IS
GOING TO WORK.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE ATTACHED TO A
ROPE.
ON MY GO YOU MAKE YOU WAY THREW
A SERIES OF ROPE OBSTACLES AND
UNCLICK.
YOU THEN USE PIECE OF ROPE TO
BUILD A BRIDGE AND CROSS IT.
FINALLY YOU'LL MAKE YOU WAY TO
THE END WHERE YOU WILL MANEUVER
TWO BALLS THROUGH A TABLE MAZE.
FIRST PERSON TO LAND BOTH THEIR
BALLS GETS BACK IN THIS GAME.
YOU'LL PUT THE BUFF BACK ON AND
JOIN A VERY COMPLICATED SOCIAL
MATRIX THAT YOU MUST QUICKLY
INTEGRATE.
BIG, BIG STAKES.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR A SPOT BACK IN THE GAME,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST YOU GOT TO MANEUVER
THROUGH THIS ROPE MAZE.
LOOKS EASY.
IT'S NOT.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
CHRIS THROWING HIMSELF THROUGH
IT.
ERIC THROUGH, NOW IN THE SECOND
STAGE OF THIS ROPE CHALLENGE.
ROPE MANAGE.
BECOMES KEY HERE.
AURORA IS THROUGH.
THERE'S JULIA.
THERE GOES JOE.
CHRIS IS GOOD.
>> LOOKING GOOD, CHRIS.
LOOKING GOOD, DAVID, JOE, ERIC,
KELLEY, EVERYBODY.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY IS THROUGH
NOW EXCEPT WARDOG AND RON, THE
LAST TWO IN THAT FIRST STAGE.
AUBRY FIGHTING TO SQUEEZE
THROUGH THAT ROPE.
>> I'M STUCK.
>> Jeff: REEM STRUGGLING.
>> OH, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
DUDE.
>> Jeff: REEM'S FAVORITE WORD
COMING INTO PLAY.
>> DUDE.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY STILL IN
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: IT'S AURORA THROUGH
FIRST.
SHE CAN UNCLIP.
>> YES, AURORA!
>> Jeff: NOW YOU HAVE A LOT OF
KNOTS TO UNTIE TO GET THROUGH
THIS NEXT LEG OF THE CHALLENGE.
ERIC IS THROUGH, HE CAN UNCLIP.
WENTWORTH IS THROUGH, JOE IS
THROUGH, DAVID IS THROUGH.
ALL AT ONCE WE HAVE FIVE PEOPLE
WORKING ON THEIR KNOTS NOW.
>> YES, KELLEY!
>> DON'T STOP, DON'T STOP.
>> Jeff: CHRIS IS GOOD.
HE CAN UNCLIP.
>> GOOD JOB, CHRIS.
>> Jeff: WHO WILL GET THROUGH
THESE KNOTS THE FASTEST?
IT'S GOING TO BE ERIC THROUGH,
JOE RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
NOW YOU GOT TO BUILD A ROPE
BRIDGE.
>> GO, ERIC!
>> Jeff: HERE'S WENTWORTH.
>> YES, KEL.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES AURORA.
SHE'S IN IT.
CHRIS IS THROUGH.
YOU CAN WORK THIS ROPE BRIDGE
ANYWAY YOU WANT.
YOU CAN CRAWL ON IT.
YOU CAN GET ON YOUR BUTT.
YOU CAN LAY FLAT OUT.
YOU JUST CANNOT TOUCH THE POST
ON EITHER SIDE.
YOU CANNOT TOUCH THE GROUND.
DAVID IS FINALLY THROUGH.
THAT'S A SPRINT RIGHT THERE.
HE'S GOT SOME TIME TO MAKE UP.
THE LEAD.
AURORA IS THROUGH FIRST.
AURORA WORKING ON HER KNOT.
>> GOOD JOB, AURORA.
>> Jeff: ERIC IS OFF, JOE
RIGHT BEHIND.
YOU'RE BOTH GOOD.
JOE, ERIC AND AURORA WORKING ON
THEIR LAST SET OF KNOTS HOLDING
THEM FROM THE TABLE MAZE.
CHRIS IS GOOD.
HE CAN START WORKING ON HIS
KNOTS.
AURORA HAS HER KNOTS UNTIED.
AURORA IS ON THE TABLE MAZE.
ERIC AND JOE HAVE THEIR KNOTS
UNTIED.
THREE PEOPLE ARE ON THE MAZE
RIGHT NOW, JOE, ERIC, AND
AURORA.
CHRIS WORKING ON HIS KNOTS.
CHRIS IS GOOD.
THE TABLE MAZE THE ONLY THING
LEFT IN THIS CHALLENGE NOW.
YOU GOT TO GET TWO BALLS.
THIS IS WHAT YOU FOUGHT FOR ALL
THOSE NIGHTS ON EXTINCTION FOR
THIS SHOT RIGHT HERE.
JOE VERY CLOSE WITH HIS FIRST
BALL.
JOE IN AND OUT.
AURORA NICE AND STEADY NOW.
>> GOT IT!
>> Jeff: AURORA HAS HER FIRST
BALL.
>> GOOD JOB, AURORA.
>> Jeff: SHE'S JUST GOT ONE
MORE THE LAND TO GET BACK IN
THIS GAME.
HERE'S WENTWORTH.
AURORA IS THE ONE TO BEAT RIGHT
NOW.
HERE COMES DAVID.
THIS IS IT.
WHATEVER IS IN THE TANK YOU NEED
IT RIGHT NOW.
JOE DROPS HIS FIRST BALL.
CHRIS DROPS HIS FIRST BALL.
>> GOOD JOB, CHRIS.
GOOD JOB, JOE.
>> Jeff: IT IS NOW CHRIS, JOE,
AND AURORA WITH ONE BALL AND
ONLY ONE BALL LEFT TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
HERE COMES WARDOG.
RON'S WORKING ON HIS MAZE NOW.
JOE AND CHRIS SIDE BY SIDE ON
THE MAZE.
BOTH WITH THEIR SECOND BALLS.
CHRIS GETTING CLOSER.
JOE NOW CLOSER.
JOE AROUND ONE OF THE TOUGHEST
SPOTS IF HE CAN HANG ON.
CHRIS IN THE SAME SPOT.
IT IS CHRIS AND JOE.
CHRIS IN AND OUT.
JOE COULD WIN IT RIGHT HERE.
JOE DROPS.
CHRIS FOR THE WIN.
CHRIS DOES IT.
CHRIS HAS EARNED HIMSELF A SPOT
BACK IN THE GAME.
>> CHRIS, AWESOME JOB, MAN.
>> GREAT JOB, BRO.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, 27 NIGHTS ON
EXTINCTION EARNED YOU A SHOT AT
GETTING BACK IN AND YOU GOT IT.
COME GRAB YOUR BUFF.
JOIN THE TRIBE.
CONGRATS.
THE IDEA BEHIND EXTINCTION WAS
NOT JUST A SECOND CHANCE.
IT WAS TO FURTHER EXPLORE THE
SOCIAL EXPERIMENT WITH THE
QUESTION: WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF
YOU TOOK SOMEBODY AND YOU SENT
THEM OFF TO AN ISLAND WITH NO
IDEA HOW LONG THEY WERE GOING TO
BE THERE, NO IDEA WHAT TO
EXPECT, WHAT WOULD HAPPEN?
REEM, YOU STARTED THIS.
YOU WERE THE FIRST TO SAY YES
AND 32 NIGHTS OUT THERE, YOU
NEVER ONCE RAISED THAT SAIL AND
SURRENDERED.
WHAT WAS YOUR DARKEST MOMENT?
>> THE DAY I GOT THERE.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN SO COLD, SO
ALONE, SO MISERABLE, AND THAT
WAS PROBABLY MY DARKEST MOMENT,
BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
BUT I KNEW THAT I WANTED A
CHANCE.
WE ALL CAME OUT HERE FOR A
REASON.
I CAME OUT HERE TO PROVE
SOMETHING TO MYSELF, AND I AM
PROUD OF MYSELF.
AND I HOPE THAT MY FAMILY IS
PROUD OF ME.
>> OF COURSE THEY ARE.
>> Jeff: JOE, EVERY SO OFTEN
PLAYERS COME ALONG THAT REALLY
CONNECT, ESPECIALLY WITH KIDS.
YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE GUYS.
WHAT PART OF YOUR LIFE DOES THIS
GAME REPRESENT?
>> IT'S EVERYTHING, JEFF.
LIKE I'M PLAYING FOR ALL THOSE
KIDS FROM MY FAMILY, AND I FEEL
LIKE, MAN I JUST BLEW IT.
I HAD IT RIGHT THERE AND I BLEW
IT FOR THEM, BUT THEN I GO, NO,
YOU DIDN'T.
YOU WERE DEFINED OF HOW YOU
BOUNCE BACK FROM THOSE LOSS, HOW
YOU RISE TO THE NEXT CHALLENGE,
AND NEVER QUITTING PERIOD.
>> Jeff: DAVID, WHAT WAS
EXTINCTION ABOUT FOR YOU?
>> FIRST TIME I PLAYED
"SURVIVOR," I PRETTY MUCH
RETREATED FROM LIFE, AND PLAYING
"SURVIVOR" THE FIRST TIME IT
GAVE ME THE COURAGE TO START
LIVING MY LIFE AND THEN TO START
MEETING PEOPLE.
AND THEN I CAME TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, AND YOU LOOK OVER
THE EDGE, AND ALL YOU SEE IS
EMPTINESS, AND THEN YOU QUICKLY
REALIZE, LIKE EVERYTHING THAT'S
TO BE FOUND THERE IS MADE OF THE
STUFF YOU BRING UP HERE AND IN
HERE, AND WHAT I SAW IS A REAL
VALUE IN WHAT I HAVE THAT ISN'T
THERE, ISN'T HERE, IT'S BACK
HOME, AND IT'S THE GREATEST GIFT
"SURVIVOR" ACTUALLY EVER GAVE
ME, AND IT'S OKAY THEY DIDN'T
WIN.
>> Jeff: JULIA?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE BEEN SMILING
ALMOST THE ENTIRE TIME.
WHAT IS IT YOU'RE FEELING?
>> I AM GRATEFUL THAT I GOT TO
PLAY THIS GAME THAT I LOVE, AND
HONESTLY, THAT I GOT TO GO TO
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
I LOST MY DAD WHEN I WAS SEVEN
TO HEART DISEASE, AND IT'S BEEN
18 YEARS, AND I STILL WAS NOT
ABLE TO OVERCOME THAT GRIEF, AND
IT CAUSED ME A LOT OF BURDEN,
AND ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION, I
FINALLY WAS ABLE TO REALIZE HOW
STRONG I AM AND ACTUALLY BELIEVE
IT.
SO THANK YOU, SURVEILLANCE GODS
FOR PUTTING ME HERE IN THIS
MOMENT.
I NEEDED IT.
>> Jeff: ERIC, YOU WERE OUT
THERE FOR A LONG TIME.
>> YES.
THE FIRST DAY I WOKE UP ON THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION, I THOUGHT, I
CAN'T DO THIS FOR TWO DAYS, LET
ALONE HOWEVER LONG I'D HAVE TO
BE OUT THERE.
BUT THIS FOR ME WAS ABOUT MY
KIDS.
I'VE GOT TWO BOYS.
AND I'M THE GUY THAT'S ALWAYS
GOING, YOU CAN'T QUIT, KID.
PICK YOURSELF UP.
HOW AM I GOING TO SAY THAT IF I
CAN'T DO IT MYSELF?
SO I TALKED MYSELF OUT OF THAT
MAST MAYBE ONCE A DAY.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: AUBRY,WHERE ARE YOU
RIGHT NOW?
BECAUSE EVEN WATCHING YOU IN
THAT CHALLENGE, NOT ONLY COULD I
SEE PHYSICAL FATIGUE, BUT ALSO
MENTAL FATIGUE.
YOU WERE STRUGGLING JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING?
>> I'VE BEEN THROUGH SOME VERY
PAINFUL LOSSES.
I'VE BEEN RIGHT THERE.
I TASTED IT.
I'VE SEEN IT THE MORNING OF DAY
39 AND I STILL LOST IT.
BUT "SURVIVOR" IS A REMINDER
THAT IT'S NOT THAT YOU LOSE, BUT
THE TRUE CHARACTER OF WHO YOU
ARE IS WHAT YOU DO WITH YOUR
LOSSES.
THAT'S WHAT "SURVIVOR" IS ABOUT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: WENTWORTH, WHAT HAS
THIS "SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE BEEN
FOR YOU?
>> "SURVIVOR" FOR ME HAS ALWAYS
BEEN ABOUT GAME.
IT'S NOT BEEN ABOUT THE PEOPLE,
AND I FELT LIKE PEOPLE LOOKED AT
ME AS THEIR FAVORITE PLAYER
BECAUSE I DID PLAY THEM AND I
WAS KIND OF COMPLETELY ON THE
BOTTOM AT TIME, BUT IT'S ABOUT
WHO YOU ARE AND WHAT YOU DO WITH
YOUR LIFE.
I CAME IN HERE WANTING TO WIN.
I'VE DONE IT ALL.
I'VE BEEN TO THE FINAL FOUR.
I HAVE NOTHING LEFT TO DO BUT
WIN.
I'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE.
AND I DIDN'T KNOW IN THE PAST
THEY WAS MISSING SOMETHING.
SO I'M VERY GRATEFUL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS THE FINAL PUSH.
IT'S A BRAND-NEW GAME, NEW
COMPLICATION.
JURY, GRAB YOUR STUFF, YOU'RE
NOT RETURNING TO DISTINCTION.
[APPLAUSE]
WE'LL SEE YOU AT NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> GOOD LUCK, EVERYONE.
>> BE SUPER PROUD OF YOURSELVES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DEVENS,
CHRIS, LAUREN, GAVIN, JULIE,
VICTORIA, DAY 35, FIVE DAYS
LEFT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> WHEN JEFF CALLED MY NAME OUT,
HONESTLY, I WAS IN SHOCK.
IT WAS MY 28th DAY ON THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
THIS IS THE MOST EXCITED AND
NERVOUS I'VE BEEN OUT HERE, AND
NOW I AM GOING TO DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO WIN THIS GAME.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: AN EPIC FINISH TO THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
CHRIS IS BACK IN IT, NARROWLY
DEFEATING ONE OF "SURVIVOR'S"
MOST DOMINANT CHALLENGE
PERFORMERS, JOE.
COME ON OUT, JOE.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
JOE, YOU'RE A BIT OF A
"SURVIVOR" ENIGMA IN THAT YOUR
POPULARITY IS UNDENIABLE,
OBVIOUSLY WITH KIDS, BUT WITH
WOMEN, WITH MEN, WITH FAMILIES.
YOUR STATISTICS ARE HISTORIC.
YOUR TRIBES HAVE WON 24
CHALLENGES.
YOU'VE WON SEVEN INDIVIDUAL.
THAT'S 31 WINS.
AND YET IT IS ALL THOSE
QUALITIES OF LIKABILITY AND
STRENGTH IN CHALLENGES THAT YOUR
OWN TRIBE VOTED YOU OUT.
SO CAN A GUY LIKE YOU, CAN A
PLAYER LIKE YOU WIN THIS GAME?
>> MAN, I THINK IT IS VERY,
VERY, VERY, VERY HARD FOR A
PLAYER LIKE ME TO WIN THIS GAME,
BUT THERE'S STALE CHANCE.
IT'S VERY HARD, BUT I THINK, YOU
KNOW, YOU CAN.
BUT IT'S REALLY HARD.
>> Jeff: DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE
PROMISING TO CONTINUE TO COME
BACK UNTIL YOU WIN?
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
COME ON!
>> WELL, OF COURSE, I THINK I
JUST WANT TO HANG UP THE HAT,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO SELL THE
FARM.
YOU KNOW, I JUST NEED...
>> Jeff: GIVE ME A
REGULARS,JUST GIVE ME A REST.
>> I APPRECIATE EVERYTHING SO
MUCH, AND "SURVIVOR" HAS TAUGHT
ME SO MUCH ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
APPRECIATING LIFE THAT MUCH
MORE, BUT I HAVE A FEELING I'LL
BE BACK.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
WELL, I JUST WANT TO SAY, WERE
WERE -- BEFORE WE GO TO BREAK.
I HAVE A THEORY.
YOUR ACHILLES' HEEL, THE HAIR.
IT'S THE WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: THE BALANCE.
>> I'M LIKE SAMPSON.
>> Jeff: THE GUY WHO CUTS MY
HAIR IS HERE IF YOU WANT TO CUT
IT OFF.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, YOU REALLY
THINK THIS IS IT?
>> Jeff: I DON'T KNOW.
SHOULD WE CUT IT OR KEEP IT?
>> IF I BECOME NORMAL --.
>> Jeff: CUT IT OR KEEP IT?
>> REALLY, THIS IS IT?
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION" FINALE CONTINUES
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
KEEP THE HAIR.
KEEP IT.
YOU SHOULD KEEP IT.
YOU WANT TO CUT IT?
I'LL CUT IT.
LET'S CUT IT.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> GOOD JOB, DUDE.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> PLEASURE.
I'M SO HAPPY THAT I'M IN THIS
GAME AGAIN, BUT GETTING BACK IN
AND KICKING IT BACK IN JUST LIKE
THAT, IT'S NOT EASY.
IT WILL TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF
GETTING USED TO.
SO SORRY IF I'M A LITTLE OUT OF
IT.
>> NEW YORK REACCLIMATE.
>> I'M NOT AS MENTALLY THERE AS
I WAS IN THE BEGINNING AND I'M
NOT AS PHYSICALLY THERE AT ALL,
BUT I DO HAVE INFORMATION.
IF ANYONE WANTS TO COME TALK TO
ME, COME TALK TO ME.
I HAVE TO DOWNPLAY MY GAME.
I'M NOT PERCEIVED AS TOO BIG OF
A THREAT.
MAYBE I CAN FIND SOMEONE WHO I
CAN TRUST, AT LEAST TO GET TO
THE NEXT VOTE.
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
AND IF I'M GONE TOMORROW NIGHT
BECAUSE THEY DON'T WANT TO WORK
WITH ME, WHATEVER, I JUST WENT
BASICALLY FROM LAST PLACE TO THE
FINALE.
SO I'M GOOD WITH IT, YOU KNOW.
>> CHRIS IS GIVEN US A SOFT
QUIT, LIKE IF I GO HOME
TOMORROW, I'M COOL.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
NOBODY SITS ON EDGE OF
EXTINCTION FOR ALMOST A MONTH TO
FINALLY WIN THEIR WAY BACK IN
THE GAME TO BE LIKE, IF I GO, I
GO.
IF ANYONE IS BUYING THAT,
THEY'RE INSANE.
>> HE HAS NOT GIVEN UP.
THERE'S NO WAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW HIM AT ALL.
>> HE KNOWS A LOT.
>> CHRIS IS NOT GOOD FOR MY
GAME.
I DON'T KNOW HIM AT ALL, BUT
THERE ARE TWO PEOPLE ON THIS
TRIBE THAT DO KNOW HIM, SO FOR
THEM CHRIS BECOMES AN OPTION
THAT WASN'T HERE BEFORE.
>> I HOPE THAT YOUR HEAD'S A
LITTLE MORE IN THE GAME THAN
YOU'RE LETTING ON.
>> I WANT TO GET TO THE END.
I WANT US TO BE FINAL FOUR.
>> I'M THIS CLOSE TO THE END,
AND NOW THERE IS THIS BIG
CURVEBALL OF, HEY, IT'S MY
BUDDY, WHO I BETRAYED.
I JUST GOT TO BE CAREFUL THAT I
DON'T END UP BLOWING THIS GAME
THAT I'VE WORKED SO HARD FOR.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO WRITE YOUR
NAME DOWN, I PROMISE.
I'VE BEEN DOWN THAT ROAD.
IF YOU STAB ME IN THE BACK, I
GET IT.
>> BY THE WAY, IS YOUR IDOL REAL
OR FAKE?
>> I GOT TO KNOW?
IS IT REAL OR FAKE?
>> WE'RE GOOD.
I PROMISE, WE'RE GOOD.
IT'S REAL.
>> OKAY.
SO --
>> I'M PLAYING IT.
IF I DON'T WIN TOMORROW, I'M
DEFINITELY PLAYING IT.
>> WE'VE GOT STICK TOGETHER AT
THIS POINT.
WE'RE FINISHING WHAT WE STARTED.
>> I HOPE YOU DIDN'T SPEND 28
DAYS JUST PLANNING REVENGE.
>> CHRIS AND I HAVE A
RELATIONSHIP.
WE WERE BROKEN DOWN TOGETHER ON
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
HE'S HAD A LOT OF TIME TO THINK
ABOUT THE GAME.
I'M THE ONLY PERSON WHO REALLY
BETRAYED AND BACKSTABBED HIM IN
THIS GAME.
I'M SURE HE HASN'T FORGOTTEN
THAT.
>> I KNOW FROM A JURY STANDPOINT
THE PLAYERS THAT ARE GOING TO
HAVE RESPECT ON THE JURY ARE
ONES THAT LIKE MADE MOVES.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WENTWORTH WANTS YOU TO DO
WELL.
AND THIS IS FROM WENTWORTH, YOU
HAVE TO PLAY YOUR IDOL CORRECTLY
FOR SOMEONE OR FOR SOMEONE ELSE
TO HAVE A BIG ENOUGH MOVE.
>> I KNEW YOU KNEW.
I KNEW WHOEVER CAME BACK FROM
EXTINCTION WOULD KNOW I HAD AN
IDOL.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT MY READ IS
ON CHRIS YET.
HE'S TRYING TO GET LOCKED IN IN
SOME SORT OF ALLIANCE THAT WILL
TAKE HIM FURTHER IN THIS GAME,
WHICH IS REALLY THE ONLY THING
HE CAN DO.
IT'S NOT SO MUCH IF I CAN TRUST
HIM.
IT'S DOES HE HAVE BETTER
OPTIONS.
IT'S LIKE DATING SOMEONE.
YOU KNOW?
I SHOW UP AT A BAR WITH MY
BOYFRIEND.
I SEE RYAN REYNOLDS.
YOU SHOULDN'T TRUST ME ANYMORE.
I'M GOING TO DATE RYAN REYNOLDS
IF I HAVE THE CHANCE.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
ARE THEIR BEST OPTION IF YOU'RE
GOING TO TRUST ANYONE, YOU
SHOULD TRUST ME BECAUSE I CAN
MAKE SURE THAT NO VOTES GO ON
YOU.
BUT YOU CAN TELL THEM WHAT I
HAVE, AND IT LOSES ALL ITS
POWER, AND I'M WILLING TO WORK
WITH YOU.
RIGHT NOW I THINK THAT I AM HIS
BEST OPTION, WHICH LEADS ME TO
TRUST HIM.
WHETHER OR NOT IT'S RIGHTFULLY
PLACED TRUST WILL BE WHAT WE'LL
SEE SHORTLY.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
DEVENS, TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RACE THROUGH A SERIES
OF OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL THEN CROSS THE BALANCE
BEAM, COLLECTING A BAG ALONG THE
WAY.
YOU'LL USE THE TIELTS INSIDE TO
SOLVE A COMBINATION LOCK.
YOU'LL USE THOSE PIECES TO SOLVE
A CIRCULAR PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE, GUARANTEED A
ONE IN FIVE SHOT AT GETTING TO
THE END.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT AND
WITH EXTINCTION NO LONGER AN
OPTION, IT IS DO-OR-DIE FROM
HERE ON OUT.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: FIRST TO FINISH,
STEAK.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: CHOCOLATE CAKE FOR
DESSERT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: BIG STEAK.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> OH.
MY.
GOD.
>> Jeff: FOR IMMUNITY AND
REWARD, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
LAUNCH YOURSELF THROUGH IT.
THAT'S WHAT DEVENS DOES OUT OF
THE GATE.
HE'S THROUGH.
LAUREN IS THROUGH.
CHRIS IS THROUGH.
CHRIS IS WHIPPING THROUGH THIS
CHALLENGE.
CHRIS DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
JULIE STRUGGLING TO GET UP AND
OVER.
THESE ARE HIGH.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO GET ACROSS THE
BEAM WITH THE BAG.
DEVENS ON THE BEAM NOW WORKING
ON THAT BAG OF TILES.
CHRIS NOW WORKING ON HIS BAG.
DEVENS HAS HIS.
START WORKING ON THE COMBINATION
LOCK.
CHRIS IS GOOD.
LAUREN IS GOOD.
JULIE IS GOOD.
SHE'S ACROSS.
VICTORIA IS ACROSS.
GAVIN IS NOW ACROSS.
EVERYBODY NOW WORKING ON THEIR
COMBINATION.
OUT OF NOWHERE VICTORIA WITH HER
FIRST TRY GETS IT.
NOW IT'S VICTORIA IN THE LEAD.
VICTORIA NOW CAN START WORKING
ON THAT PUZZLE.
DEVENS HAS HIS.
HE CAN START WORKING.
JULIE HAS HERS.
LAUREN HAS HERS.
GAVIN HAS HIS.
IT IS NOW CHRIS IN DEAD LAST AND
ALL ALONE TRYING TO SOLVE THAT
COMBO.
VICTORIA WITH HER FIRST COUPLE
OF PIECES.
DEVENS HAS A PIECE.
JULIE'S GOT ONE.
LAUREN WITH A PIECE.
EVERYBODY FIGHTING IN THIS
CHALLENGE NOW.
CHRIS FINALLY OPENS HIS
COMBINATION LOCK.
CHRIS HAS GOT A LOT OF TIME TO
MAKE UP.
IT IS JULIE WITH LAUREN RIGHT IN
THERE.
VICTORIA IS RIGHT IN THERE, TOO.
DEVENS TRYING TO STAY IN IT.
CHRIS AND GAVIN NOWHERE CLOSE.
>> PUZZLES AREN'T MY THING.
>> Jeff: JULIE WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> COME ON, JULIE.
>> Jeff: JULIE IS NOT WAITING
ON ANYBODY.
SHE CAN TASTE IT, A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FIVE.
ONLY A FEW PIECES LEFT.
>> COME ON, JULIE.
>> JULIE, MY GIRL.
>> THEY WEREN'T ROOTING FOR YOU
LAST TIME WHEN THEY WERE GOING
TO SPLIT THE VOTE, WERE THEY?
>> SORRY, DEVENS.
I WANT THE WIN SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: JULIE DOWN TO HER
LAST PIECE IF SHE CAN GET IT IN
WITHOUT THAT PUZZLE FALLING
APART.
IMMUNITY IS HERS FOR THE SECOND
TIME.
THE RISK NOW IS THAT THE ENTIRE
PUZZLE COLLAPSES.
JULIE TRYING THE FORCE IT IN.
>> WATCH OUT FOR THAT MIDDLE
PIECE.
JULIE FEELING THE PANIC.
>> PUT YOUR LEFT HAND LOWER.
THERE YOU GO.
CHRIS IS LITERALLY TALKING HER
THROUGH IT.
VERY UNUSUAL SITUATION.
RIGHT THERE.
>> CHRIS, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
>> YOU GOT THIS.
>> CAN SHE GET IT TO FIT THIS
TIME?
FOR THE WIN?
>> JEFF?
LOOKS GOOD TO ME.
>> Jeff: JULIE'S GOT IT!
JULIE WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
SAFE AT THE FINAL FIVE.
>> GOOD JOB, JULIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> YOU DID GREAT.
>> Jeff: JULIE, COME ON OVER.
YOUR SECOND INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
WIN.
BACK AT CAMP YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE STEAK.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON THAT WILL
ENJOY THE SAME MEAL WITH YOU.
>> THERE'S ONE PERSON OUT HERE
WHO HAS NOT HAD THE MERGE FEAST
AND WHO HAS NOT HAD ONE REWARD
FOR 35 DAYS SHE'S EATEN COCONUT
AND RICE.
CHRIS, WILL YOU JOIN ME?
>> COME ON OVER, CHRIS?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, JULIE.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE ONE MORE
PERSON TO BRING WITH YOU.
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH LAUREN.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, COME ON OVER.
DEVENS DROPS HIS HEAD.
>> I'VE GONE TO BAT FOR JEWEL
LAY NUMBER OF TIMES.
SHE KNOWS THAT.
SHE'S NEVER GONE TO BAT FOR ME.
LAUREN AND HER HAVE HAD MORE
REWARDS THAN ANYONE OUT HERE, SO
I'M DISAPPOINTED.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, GAVIN,
DEVENS, GOT NOTHING FOR YOU.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED OUT.
>> I DIDN'T WIN THE IMMUNITY
IDOL IMAND IT SUCKS, BUT WHY THE
HECK WAS CHRIS HELPING JULIE?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE BEING
LOYAL TO ME AND WORKING
TOGETHER, AND THAT BLEW MY MIND.
I WANT TO TRUST HIM, AND I KIND
OF DO TRUST HIM, BUT I'M VERY
WARY.
>> HOLY CRAP.
>> EVERYONE JUST SIT DOWN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I WAS HOPING THAT THERE WOULD
BE A REWARD WITH THE CHALLENGE
TODAY, AND I KNEW IF I WON THAT
CHRIS WOULD BE MY NUMBER-ONE
PICK.
HERE'S THE THING, YOU WILL GET
FULL OF FOOD.
I WANTED TO BRING CHRIS IN TO
ENSURE THAT DEVENS ISN'T SITTING
IN THE FINAL THREE.
I NEED RICK TO BE OUT OF THIS
GAME.
>> THE THING I REALLY WANT THE
RELAY TO YOU IS DEVENS.
HE'S TRIED FOUR TRIBAL COUNCILS
TO GET HIM OUT.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER
CHANCE.
>> I WANT THE TRY TO AT LEAST
FEEL HIM OUT, SEE IF HIS IDOL IS
REAL OR FAKE.
PLAINTIFF'S NO WAY HE SHOWS THAT
IDOL IF IT'S REAL.
>> AT THE LAST TRIBAL COUNCIL,
DEVENS PULLED OUT AN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND I'M PRAYING THAT IT'S
FAKE.
BUT IF IT'S REAL, THEN I NEED A
PLAN "B."
>> IF HE PLAYS THE IDOL TONIGHT,
THEN THE VOTES GET PUT ON
SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> THE TWO BIGGEST THREATS FROM
THE STANDPOINT OF THE JURY ARE
RICK DEVENS AND VICTORIA.
SPLITS THE VOTES BETWEEN
VICTORIA AND DEVENS.
>> IT HAS BEEN, I DON'T EVEN
THOUGH, 20 DAYS AND COUNTING
THAT I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO GET
OUT RICARDO FRANCIS.
-- RICK DEVENS.
HOPEFULLY TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT.
I REALLY LIKE THIS BACK-UP VOTE
SCENARIO.
VICTORIA AND I ARE VERY CLOSE,
BUT IT'S F WHAT CHRIS IS SAYING
IS TRUE, I HAVE NO INTENTION OF
SITTING NEXT TO VICTORIA AT THE
END.
>> HE CAN'T BE THAT MUCH OF AN
IDIOT.
>> I DON'T KNOW, IT'S JULIE.
>> THE LAST CHALLENGE IS GOING
TO BE VERY PHYSICAL AND HE JUST
ATE.
MY SUGGESTION IS WE TAKE OUT
CHRIS TODAY.
NOW HEAR ME OUT, BECAUSE WHAT IF
THEY'RE TRULY WORKING TOGETHER?
IF THEY'RE SMART, THEY DON'T
WORK WITH US.
THEY HAVE A BETTER CHANCE OF
BEATING CHRIS IN THE END THAN
ONE OF US.
IF JULIE, LAUREN, AND CHRIS ARE
NOW WORKING TOGETHER, AND WE
TAKE OUT DEVENS TONIGHT, THAT
MEANS THAT A FINAL FIVE, THOSE
THREE HAVE DECISION MAKING
POWER, LEAVING ME AND GAVIN ON
THE OUTS, AND SO AS MUCH AS I
STILL DON'T WANT TO GO UP
AGAINST DEVENS IN A FINAL THREE
WITH HIM, AS OF RIGHT NOW, I
DON'T THINK EITHER HIM OR ME
MAKE IT TO FINAL THREE IF WE
DON'T WORK TOGETHER TONIGHT.
>> THE IDEA WAS TO SPLIT BETWEEN
YOU AND CHRIS TODAY IF YOU BOTH
LOST.
THAT'S FAIRLY OBVIOUS.
>> RIGHT.
>> MY FEAR IS THAT THEY'RE
WORKING TOGETHER, RIGHT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND HE JUST LIKE TOTALLY
STOPPED THE PUZZLE TO HELP HER.
>> I TRULY DON'T KNOW WHO CHRIS
IS TRYING TO WORK WITH.
IT MAY BE ANYONE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE HE'S TELLING US ALL
WHAT WE WANT THE HEAR A LITTLE
BIT.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE WANTS TO WORK
WITH ME OR NOT.
>> WE COULD JUST VOTE FOR CHRIS?
>> THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO
IS BETRAY CHRIS AGAIN, BUT WHAT
THEY'RE PITCHING MAKES SENSE.
BECAUSE I'M WORRIED THAT CHRIS
IS PLAYING MUCH HARDER THAN HE
APPEARS AND THAT HE IS HERE TO
GET SOME REVENGE AND TRY THE WIN
THE GAME AND TAKE ME OUT IN THE
PROCESS.
I'M TOTALLY OPEN TO EVERYTHING,
INCLUDING VOTING CHRIS OUT.
>> I'M PLAYING MY IDOL TONIGHT
TO MATTER WHAT.
BUT I JUST GOT TO BE CAREFUL
THAT I'M WORKING WITH THE RIGHT
PERSON.
SO I NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT
CHRIS IS PLAYING WITH ME AND NOT
AGAINST ME.
>> HOW WAS LUNCH?
PRODUCTIVE?
>> LUNCH WAS GOOD, MAN.
BEFORE GAME TALK, I JUST
CONTINUED TO THINK ABOUT THE
FIRST TIME YOU WENT AGAINST ME
AND VOTED ME OUT.
I FELT BETRAYED.
BUT YOU WERE LIKE THE NEXT
PERSON VOTED OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND ON THE EDGE, WE MADE
AMENDS, AND WE DID IT IN A VERY
GENUINE AND REAL WAY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THAT RELATIONSHIP IS
GOING TO GET US TO THE END.
IF IT'S NOT ME WHO GETS TO THE
END, I WILL FIGHT AND DIE FOR
RICK DEVENS TO WIN THIS GAME.
>> THAT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
>> I AM COMPLETELY LOYAL TO YOU.
WHAT ELSE DO I HAVE TO DO FOR
YOU TO KNOW THAT I PROMISE?
>> WHAT DID YOU GET IN YOUR BAG
TODAY?
I KNOW YOU GOT SOMETHING.
BECAUSE I GOT SOMETHING WHEN I
CAME BACK.
>> THIS MORNING I WAS LOOKING
THROUGH MY BAG, REACHED IN, AND
PULLED OUT AN ENVELOPE, AND
OPENED IT UP, THE SAME IDOL THAT
DAVID AND DEVENS USED EARLIER IN
THE GAME.
>> HOLY COW.
>> YOU HAVE EARNED YOUR WAY BACK
IN.
STAYING IN MAY NOT BE AS EASY.
THIS MAY HELP.
YOU MUST GIVE ONE HALF OF THIS
IMMUNITY IDOL TO ANOTHER PLAYER.
IF YOU ARE BOTH STILL IN THE
GAME AFTER THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THESE TWO PIECES WHEN
USED TOGETHER BECOME ONE IDOL
WITH FULL POWER.
>> IT'S THE EXACT SAME THING.
>> I AM GIVING HALF THE IDOL TO
YOU.
HERE'S HOW YOU KNOW YOU CAN
TRUST ME.
>> YOU NEED ME HERE OR YOU LOSE
THE IDOL.
>> EXACTLY.
>> CHRIS GAVE ME HALF OF HIS
IDOL.
AND THAT IS A GUARANTEE THAT I
CAN TRUST HIM TONIGHT, BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T WANT TO LOSE THAT
IDOL.
BUT I DON'T THINK FOR A SECOND
HE THINKS HE CAN WIN AGAINST ME.
IF HE DOESN'T GET ME OUT.
BUT IF I WORK WITH GAVIN AND
VICTORIA, AND THAT'S SOMETHING I
WON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT.
PUTTING MY GAME ON THE LINE FOR
THIS PERSONAL RELATIONSHIP MAY
COME BACK THE BITE ME.
BUT IF IT'S REAL, IT CAN REALLY
PAY OFF.
>> IF THE PLAN IS WHAT ME,
LAUREN, AND JULIE SECURED AT THE
REWARD, THEN VICK'S GOING HOME.
>> I'M JUST AFRAID THEY'RE GOING
TO SPLIT IT BETWEEN THE TWO OF
US.
YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH IT?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S ON THE
LINE.
>> WHEN I GOT VOTED OUT FIRST
TIME, I GOT BLINDSIDED.
I AM NOT GOING TO LET THAT
HAPPEN AGAIN.
FOOL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU.
FOOL ME TWICE, SHAME ON ME.
THE ONLY WAY TO ENSURE I'M 100%
SAFE IS IF I CAN GET LAUREN TO
PLAY HER IDOL FOR ME.
>> ARE YOU PLAYING ME?
>> NO.
I PROMISE.
>> YOU PROMISE?
>> 100%.
WE ARE VOTING RICK.
DO YOU THINK RICK'S IDOL IS
REAL?
>> NO.
IF HE PLAYS HIS IDOL.
I'LL PLAY MY IDOL FOR YOU.
>> YOU PROMISE?
>> 100%.
>> I DO NOT WANT TO GO HOME.
BUT I'M PUTTING A LOT OF FAITH
IN A LOT OF PEOPLE, AND THAT IS
SCARY.
IF LAUREN GOES AGAINST ME, I
MIGHT BE SCREWED.
IT'S A RISKY MOVE, BUT IT'S THE
ONLY PLAY THAT I GOT TO GET ME
TO TOMORROW.
THIS IS EVERYTHING TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, GO AHEAD AND
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
YOU ARE BACK IN THE GAME.
WE'LL NOW BRING IN THE MEMBERS
OF OUR JURY.
CHRIS, LET'S START WITH YOU.
PAST 36 HOURS HAVE BEEN BIG.
YOU GET BACK IN THE GAME.
WHAT'S THE FEELING THE SECOND
TIME?
>> IT'S LIKE A ROLLER COASTER.
AND I'M THRUST INTO THIS NEW
WORLD THAT I HAVEN'T BEEN PART
OF FOR THE LAST 28 DAYS.
LIKE I'M FIGURING OUT HOW TO
PLAY THIS GAME ALL OVER AGAIN,
AND IT'S SCARY.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, COULD YOU
FEEL THAT, THAT IT WAS LIKE HE
GOT ON TO THE FREEWAY ALL OF A
SUDDEN AND CARS ARE JUST
WHIZZING PAST?
>> YEAH, BUT DID I THINK CHRIS
KIND OF JUMPED INTO WHAT HE
CONSIDERED TO BE HIS ROLE.
HE SAID, I HAVE A LOT OF
INFORMATION, AND, YOU KNOW, I'M
HERE IF YOU WANT IT.
>> Jeff: JULIE, ANOTHER
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN.
THE OTHER BIG PART WAS REWARD.
AND YOU CHOSE CHRIS AND LAUREN.
>> I PICKED CHRIS RIGHT AWAY.
HE HASN'T EATEN IN 36 DAYS.
BUT THEN YOU SAID TO PICK
SOMEBODY ELSE, AND I DECIDED TO
GO WITH LAUREN.
>> Jeff: SO DEVENS, YOU WERE
PRETTY EMOTIONAL TODAY WHEN YOU
WEREN'T PICKED
>> I WAS DISAPPOINTED OBVIOUSLY.
YOU KNOW, NUMEROUS TIMES THIS
SEASON I HAVE STEPPED UP TO BAT
FOR JULIE.
I THOUGHT SHE MIGHT ON A HUMAN
LEVEL TAKE ME FOR THE FOOD.
IT'S, YOU KNOW... I DON'T WANT
MY FIREFIGHTER FRIENDS THE MAKE
FUN OF ME.
BEING ON THE BOTTOM FOR AS LONG
AS I HAVE AND BEING TOLD EVERY
DAY, LIKE, WELL YOU NEED TO
GOSH, YOU'RE PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER
ONE, IT BREAKS YOU DOWN AFTER A
WHILE.
>> Jeff: VICTORIA, THE OTHER
PERSON SHE CHOSE WAS CHRIS.
YOU COULD MAKE AN ARGUMENT HE'S
THE EASY VOTE.
>> YEAH, YOU COULD DEFINITELY
MAKE THAT CASE.
BUT I THINK THERE IS SOMEBODY
ELSE THAT WE ALREADY ALL AGREED
ON, SO WHY ROCK THE BOAT?
>> NOTHING NEW.
I'M PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE AND
I'M ON THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, IS THERE A
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE EASY VOTE
AND THE RIGHT VOTE?
>> IF EVERY SINGLE PLAYER UP
HERE WAS ON A LEVEL PLAYING
FIELD, THEN I'D OBVIOUSLY BE THE
PERSON TO GET OUT.
BUT THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE AT
THE TOP, AND THERE'S ALWAYS
SOMEONE AT THE BOTTOM.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU
HOW TO PLAY YOUR GAME.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
INFORMATION THE MAKE DECISIONS.
>> Jeff: SO LAUREN, IT'S A
LITTLE BIT LIKE CHRIS IS TAKING
ON THE ROLE OF MESSENGER, AND
HE'S HOPING THAT THE VOTE WILL
JUST TAKE PLACE AND NOBODY WILL
EVER LOOK BACK AND SAY, WAIT A
SECOND, WHAT ABOUT THE
MESSENGER?
>> I THINK YOU HAVE TO TAKE WHAT
HE SAYS KIND OF WITH A GRAIN OF
SALT, BECAUSE THERE IS NO WAY
THAT HE'S THINKING, I'M GOING TO
GIVE THEM ABSLULTLY EVERYTHING
AND HOPE THAT THAT'S FINE,
BECAUSE IF YOU GIVE US
EVERYTHING, WHY WOULD WE WANT
THE KEEP YOU?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
LAUREN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
THE ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT THE
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I GOT SOMETHING I WOULD LIKE THE
PLAY.
>> Jeff: YOU PLAYING THIS FOR
YOURSELF?
>> FOR MYSELF, YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR DEVENS WILL
NOT COUNT.
>> JEFF?
IT'S ALL BROKEN SINCE I'VE HAD
IT SINCE LIKE DAY THE WORK BUT I
WOULD LIKE THE PLAY THIS FOR
CHRIS.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL, AND ALTHOUGH IT'S
BROKEN, THIS IDOL IS ALSO REAL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR CHRIS WILL
NOT COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOLT DEVENS.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DEVENS.
CHRIS.
DOES NOT COUNT.
VICTORIA.
THAT'S ONE VOTE VICTORIA.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: 15TH PERSON VOTED OUT
AND THE 11th MEMBER OF OUR
JURY, VICTORIA, YOU NEED TO
BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
VICTORIA, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> I'M NOT SURE WHICH OF YOU DID
IT, DEVENS, GOOD PLAY.
GAVIN, I'LL VOTE FOR YOU, MAN.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL FIVE.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW FOR YOUR
NEXT COMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT I
GOT UP, BECAUSE WE ALL KNEW THAT
AFTER I PLAYED MY IDOL LAST
NIGHT THERE WAS A GOOD CHANCE
THERE WOULD BE ANOTHER IDOL
PLANTED SOMEWHERE AROUND CAMP.
THERE'S NO DOUBT I'M TARGET
NUMBER ONE, SO I JUST KNEW I HAD
TO FIND IT BEFORE ANYONE ELSE.
BUT FIRST, I TOOK TWO FAKE IDOLS
THAT I MADE SIX DAYS AGO,
KNOWING THAT I WAS IN TROUBLE,
AND I PUT THEM IN THE EXACT SAME
CROSS WITH THE INSTRUCTION FROM
THE REAL IDOL APPLIED AT TRIBAL,
AND I HIT THEM.
HOPEFULLY THIS WILL THROW THEM
OFF THE TRABAL OF THE REAL IDOL
AND GIVE MAE CHANCE TO FIND IT
FIRST.
>> HI, RICK.
>> HI, JULIE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> AND THEN CHRIS AND JULIE
WALKED UP, AND I'M LIKE, IT'S GO
TIME.
>> I SEARCH, I SEARCH, JULIE
STARTS FOLLOWING ME, SEARCHING
IN FRONT OF ME.
BUT THEN THERE IT IS, RIGHT IN
THE CRACK OF A BENTOVER BROKEN
TREE, THE IDOL.
OH.
THAT'S IN THE GOOD NEWS FOR
ANYBODY BUT ME.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I FOUND IT.
I FOUND THE IDOL.
AND NOW THEY HAVE NO CHANCE TO
VOTE ME OUT.
YES!
HOLY CRAP.
THIS MEANS SAFETY TONIGHT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE FINAL FOUR.
I'M ON ON THE OF THE WORLD RIGHT
NOW.
>> GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
>> CONGRATULATION.
YOU HAVE A FULL-BLOWN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
>> SO DO I.
>> WE DID IT.
>> I GAVE RICK HALF THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
IT WAS A BIG RISK, SO WHEN RICK
GIVES ME THAT PIECE OF THE IDOL
BACK, I WAS SO RELIEVED, BECAUSE
HE COULD HAVE BETRAYED ME.
>> IT'S DONE.
WE CANNOT TURN ON EACH OTHER NOW
IF WE WANTED TO.
>> I'M IN A GREAT SPOT.
MY GAME AND RICK'S GAME ARE
INTERTWINED AND WE'RE GOING TO
THE FINAL FOUR TOGETHER.
SO I PICKED THE RIGHT PERSON TO
TRUST.
>> HE HAS IT.
WE JUST UH IS A HIM FIND ONE.
>> I CAN IN THE BELIEVED I
PLAYED MY ONE FOR CHRIS LAST
NIGHT.
I AM SO STUPID.
>> WE'RE NOT GIVING UP.
>> WE NEED TO FIND ONE.
>> SO RICK FINDS AN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
BUT AT LAST NIGHT'S TRIBAL
COUNCIL, TWO IDOLS WERE PLAYED,
SO IT ONLY MAKES SENSE TO ME
THAT IF TWO IDOLS WERE PLAYED,
TWO IDOLS WOULD BE THERE TO BE
FOUND TODAY.
>> LAUREN!
LAUREN!
>> NO WAY.
NO FREAKIN' WAY.
>> LAUREN!
>> I THINK THEY JUST FOUND MY
FAKE.
>> I AM SO EXCITED.
I FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO I'M SAFE.
AND I CAN'T WAIT TO PLAY IT
TONIGHT.
IT'S THE LAST THING ON MY
"SURVIVOR" BUCKET LIST.
>> THIS GAME IS NOT OVER.
>> SO JULIE FINDS THE SECOND
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, AND IN MY
HEAD I'M THINKING, I AM SCREWED.
THE ONLY THING THAT I CAN DO NOW
IS TO TRY TO WIN IMMUNITY, BUT
AS I'M GOING BACK THE CAMP, ALL
OF A SUDDEN I COME ACROSS A
LITTLE SCROLL THAT HAS BEEN
ROLLED UP IN A TREE THAT I HAVE
LOOKED IN 50 TIMES.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
IT IS IN THE TREE ABOVE YOUR
SHELTER.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
>> SHE FOUND MY FAKE.
>> IT'S A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT'S LIKE THE SURVIVOR GODS
GRANTED ME, YOU KNOW WHAT,
LAUREN, YOU WERE AN IDIOT LAST
NIGHT.
LET'S TRY AGAIN THIS NIGHT.
>> Jeff: COME ON UP, GUYS.
FIRST LOOK AT WHAT YOU'LL BE
RUNNING TODAY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, BOY.
>> WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING.
>> AMAZING.
OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, A LITTLE
DAUNTING?
>> YEAH, MAN.
WE'RE A LONG WAY UP, AND THERE'S
A LOT GOING ON.
>> Jeff: CAN WE GET TO IT?
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'LL RACE ACROSS SIX DIFFERENT
OBSTACLES OVER THE OCEAN,
COLLECTING BAGS OF PUZZLE PIECES
AS YOU GO.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL THE PIECE,
YOU'LL USE THEM TO SOLVE A
PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH GUARANTEED A
SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR, BIGGEST
STAKES SO FAR THIS SEASON.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
SIX DIFFERENT OBSTACLES YOU HAVE
TO CROSS.
ONE AT A TIME.
GRABBING PUZZLE PIECES AS YOU
GO.
DEVENS ON THE SWING STEPS.
GAVIN GOES TO THE DISK BRIDGE.
JULIE AT THE BAMBOO CRAWL.
CHRIS GOING TO TAKE ON THE
TWO-LINE BRIDGE.
LAUREN ON THE BEAM AND LADDER.
CHRIS MAKING QUICK WORK OF FIRST
ONE.
SO IS DEVENS.
GET THAT BAG ON THE TABLE.
GET BACK OUT THERE.
GAVIN STRUGGLING ON THE DISK
BRIDGE.
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
JULIE IS BACK WITH HERS.
LAUREN GETS ACROSS.
CHRIS IS NOW ON THE BA-BOOM
CRAWL.
IT'S HARD ON THE KNEES.
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW IT FROM
WATCHING IT.
CHRIS IS BAG WITH HIS SECOND
BAG.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR FIRST BAG.
CHRIS NOW WITH HIS SECOND.
DEVENS IS ACROSS.
JULIE'S ACROSS THE SWING STEP.
DEVENS HAS HIS SECOND BAG.
JULIE HAS HER SECOND.
CHRIS NOW ON THE SWING STEP.
HERE'S GAVIN WITH HIS SECOND
BAG.
CHRIS IS BACK NOW WITH HIS THIRD
LAUREN ON THE DISK BRIDGE.
IT'S A TOUGH ONE.
GAVIN AND DEVON BOTH AT THE
BALANCE BEAM.
WHO WILL GET THAT BAG UNTIED
FIRST.
THEY'RE BOTH FIGHTING FOR IT.
GAFFEN GETS IT.
GAVIN COMING BACK NOW WITH HIS
THIRD BAG.
LAUREN FINALLY ACROSS.
SHE'S GOT HER SECOND.
DEVENS SLIDING ACROSS THAT BEAM
NOW.
LOSING SOME TIME.
JULIE'S GOT HER THIRD BAG.
CHRIS HANGING ON.
HE COMES ACROSS THE BEAM BRIDGE.
DEVENS IS ACROSS THE BALANCE
BEAM.
HE'S GOT HIS THIRD BAG.
DEVENS HEADING BACK OUT.
CHRIS BACK WITH HIS FOURTH.
HERE COMES GAVING, HANGING ON
WITH A BIG SMILE.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR" RIGHT HERE.
LAUREN ON THE SWING STEPS.
SHE'S ACROSS.
SHE'S TAKING THE DEVENS APPROACH
NOW, AND THAT'S GOING TO SLOW
CHRIS DOWN.
CHRIS CANNOT PASS JULIE.
GAVIN TRYING TO MAKE UP TIME
STEP, AND STILL SMILING ON DAY
37.
GAVIN HAS HIS FIFTH BAG.
GAVIN HAS ONE MORE BAG OUT
THERE.
CHRIS GOT ONE BAG LEFT.
LAUREN WITH HER FOURTH.
IT'S GOING TO BE GAVIN TO GET
BACK FIRST WITH ALL HIS BAGS.
GAVIN CAN START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
CHRIS HAS ALL SIX.
HE CAN START ON THE PUZZLE.
IT IS CHRIS AND GAVIN ALREADY AT
WORK UNTYING ALL OF THEIR PUZZLE
PIECES.
THEY'RE TRYING THE CAPITALIZE ON
THIS EARLY LEAD.
JULIE IS ACROSS WITH HER SIXTH
BAG.
SHE CAN START ON THE PUZZLE.
DEVENS IS ACROSS.
DEVENS CAN START WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
LAUREN HAS HER SIXTH AND FINAL
BAG.
EVERYBODY IS ON THE PUZZLE NOW.
37 DAYS BRINGS US TO THIS: CHRIS
OFF TO FAST START.
GAFFEN OFF TO A FAST START.
BOTH CHRIS AND GAVIN ARE USING
THAT TIME ADVANTAGE WELL.
DEVENS, LAUREN, AND JULIA, CAN
THEY CATCH CHRIS AND GAVIN?
GAVIN IS ON FIRE ONE PIECE AFTER
ANOTHER.
EVERYBODY FRANTICALLY WORKING ON
THIS PUZZLE.
DEVENS STAYING IN THIS.
YOU CAN HIT A ROADBLOCK IN THIS
PUZZLE.
JUST BECAUSE SOMEBODY'S IN THE
LEAD DOESN'T MEAN THEY'LL WIN
IT.
LAUREN HAS A LITTLE SOMETHING
GOING.
CHRIS IS DEAD IN THE WATER.
HE'S BEEN IN THE SAME SPOT.
GAVIN INCHING HIS WAY TOWARD THE
FINAL FOUR.
PIECE BY PIECE.
DEVENS TRYING TO CATCH GAVIN.
GOT TO KEEP MOVING.
DEVENS WITH ANOTHER PIECE.
AND ANOTHER PIECE FOR DEVENS.
IT'S NOW GAVIN AND DEVENS BOTH
MAKING A RUN AT.
THIS JULIE TRYING THE STAY IN
IT.
DEVENS WITH ANOTHER BIG PIECE.
DEVENS PUZZLE NOW COMING
TOGETHER.
IT IS GAVIN ON ONE END.
DEVENS ON THE OTHER.
DAY 37.
FIGHTING FOR A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
GAVIN FEELING THE PANIC NOW, THE
PRESSURE.
GAVIN PLACES ANOTHER PIECE.
HE'S RACING NOW TO PLACE PIECES.
WHAT A COMEBACK THIS WOULD BE
FOR JEAN-CLAUDE "BABY DOC"
DUVALIER DOWN TO HANDFUL OF
PIECES.
GAVIN STILL DIGGING TO STAY IN
IT.
DEVENS CAN STEAL IT.
VICTORY IS CLOSE.
DEVENS TWO PIECES LEFT.
>> JEFF!
>> Jeff: DEVENS THINKS HE HAS
IT.
AND HE DOES.
DEVENS WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT AT THE FINAL
FOUR.
WHAT A COMEBACK.
DEVENS, COME ON OVER.
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY AGAIN IS
YOURS.
SAFE TONIGHT.
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU.
I KNOW IT'S DISAPPOINTING.
SOMEBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
CONGRATS.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE THE
PUZZLE MAN TODAY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I WON IMMUNITY AGAIN.
THEY CAN'T GET RID OF ME.
THEY'VE BEEN TRYING SO HARD TO
GET RID OF ME, AND NOW I'M GOING
TO THE FINAL FOUR.
I'M AT A POINT NOW WHERE I SEE
THE $1 MILLION.
>> I'M GOING TO GO TO THE PORCH
AND RECOLLECT FOR A FEW.
>> AT THIS POINT CHRIS HAS AN
IDOL TONIGHT, SO HE'S NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
JULIE AND LAUREN BOTH THINK
THEY'RE SAFE, BUT THEY'RE TWO
IDOLS ARE BOTH FAKE SOME THE
ONLY PERSON HERE WHO FEELS LIKE
THEY'RE IN TROUBLE IS GAVIN.
NOW I HAVE OPTIONS.
I HAVE AN IDOL THAT I FOUND THIS
MORNING, AND I'M GOING TO TRY TO
USE IT TONIGHT TO SECURE MY
PLACE IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> WELL, YOU'RE DOUBLE SAFE.
>> DOUBLE SAFE.
AND I CAN'T USE IT PAST TONIGHT.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING
TO SAY IS LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU PLAN ON DOING WITH THAT
IDOL, BUT I WOULD BE ENDEBTED TO
YOU.
>> HONESTLY, WHAT I WANT IS
PRETTY STEEP.
BUT IF YOU WON TOMORROW, I
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE IN THE FIRE
MAKING CHALLENGE.
LIKE IF YOU REALLY PROMISE ME
THAT, GUARANTEE I'D PLAY THE
IDOL ON YOU TONIGHT.
>> DEVENS APPROACHED ME WITH
THIS IDEA SAYING, WHAT IF HE
SAVES ME TONIGHT, HE SCRATCHES
MY BACK AND THEN IN RETURN IF I
WIN THE CHALLENGE TOMORROW, I
TAKE HIM TO THE FINAL THREE.
AN I'M JUST THINKING, IF I GO TO
THE END WITH DEVENS, HE'S
PROBABLY GOING TO BEAT ME.
HE'S PLAYED A GREAT GAME.
BUT I'D BE STUPID TO SAY NO.
IF OUR TRUST IS GOING TO BE
FORGED TONIGHT.
>> YOU PROMISE IF YOU WIN, YOU
TAKE ME WITH YOU?
>> I DON'T THINK I HAVE ANOTHER
OPTION HONESTLY.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> YES.
>> IT'S DONE.
I'M PLAYING IT FOR YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> I KNOW A PROMISE IS A
PROMISE.
BUT IF I'M STILL HERE TOMORROW.
I MIGHT HAVE TO GO AGAINST MY
WORD, BECAUSE BY GOD I CAME OUT
HERE NOT TO MAKE PROMISES.
I CAME OUT HERE TO WIN THIS
GAME.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO PLAY HIS
IDOL ON CHRIS BECAUSE THAT MEANS
HE MIGHT HAVE TO FACE CHRIS IN
THE FIRE MAKING CHALLENGE.
>> I WOULD SAY CHRIS.
>> WE THREE HAVE TO STICK
TOGETHER.
>> OH YEAH,.
>> I'M SUPER EXCITED.
I HAVE AN IDOL.
THAT KEEPS ME SAFE.
AND ALONG WITH GAVIN AND LAUREN,
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS TO VOTE OUT
CHRIS.
HE MADE A LOT OF FRIENDS OVER
THERE ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
SO HE COULD EASILY WIN JURY
VOTES.
ALSO, IF HE HAS TO GO TONIGHT...
>> YOU DON'T THINK CHRIS HAS
ANYTHING HE CAN PLAY TONIGHT, DO
YOU?
>> NO, I DON'T.
I THINK WE'RE FINE.
>> I'M TOTALLY GOOD WITH VOTING
OUT CHRIS.
WE WHOLEHEARTEDLY NEED HIM GONE
TONIGHT, BUT EVEN THOUGH I HAVE
AN IMMUNITY IDOL, I'M WORRIED.
BECAUSE THIS MORNING JULIE AND
RICK FOUND IDOLS, TOO.
IT'S SO HARD FOR ME TO BELIEVE
THAT THERE WERE THREE IDOLS ON
THIS BEACH.
IT MAKES ME THINK ONE OF THEM
COULD BE FAKE.
AND IF IT'S MINE, THEN I COULD
BE GONE.
SO I NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT I
GET AS FEW VOTES AS POSSIBLE.
>> HERE'S MY THING.
I THINK HE'LL TAKE JULIE TO THE
END.
AND THAT'S A SPACE THAT I WANT.
AND I THINK THAT LIKE ME AND YOU
AND GAVIN COULD GET ON BOARD TO
TAKE OUT JULIE.
>> SO LAUREN PITCHES TO ME THAT
WE VOTE JULIE TONIGHT.
BUT I THINK IT'S A SMOKE SCREEN.
I THINK I'M THE REAL TARGET, BUT
I HAVE AN IDOL, SO I'M THINKING
IT'S GOING TO BE EITHER LAUREN
OR JULIE.
JULIE HAS PROVEN TIME AND TIME
AGAIN THAT SHE'S A SOCIAL
THREAT.
SHE HAS FRIENDS FROM KAMA ON THE
JURY.
ALSO, SHE'S WON TWO IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES.
SO SHE IS DANGEROUS.
IF ANY OF US WIN TOMORROW AND
GETS IMMUNITY, I HAVE A BETTER
SHOT AT BEATING DEVENS AT FIRE
THAN SHE DOES.
>> EXACTLY.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU WANT TO
DO?
>> WITH JULIE AND LAUREN BOTH
HAVING FAKE IDOLS, DEVENS AND I
CAN CHOOSE WHO IS GOING HOME,
BUT WE HAVE TO BE ON THE SAME
PAGE.
>> YOU AND ME, WE HAVE TO FIGURE
OUT WHO WE WANT TO SEND HOME.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S LAUREN OR JULIE.
>> I THINK LAUREN OF THOSE THREE
DEFINITELY PLAYED THE MOST
STRATEGIC GAME.
LAUREN IS GOING TO THINK SHE'S
SAFE.
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING TO THINK
THEY'RE SAFE TONIGHT.
THIS IS GOOD TO BE A FUN NIGHT.
>> CHRIS HAS GOT AN IDOL.
I'VE GOT AN IDOL.
SO WE HAVE TOTAL CONTROL OF THE
VOTE TONIGHT.
LAUREN HAS BEEN ON THE RIGHT
SIDE OF ALL THESE DIFFERENT
VOTES THAT I'VE BEEN ON THE
WRONG SIDE OF, AND THAT MAKES ME
LOOK BAD, BUT JULIE COULD ALSO
BE TROUBLE, BECAUSE THERE'S
GOING TO BE A LOT OF KAMA PEOPLE
IN THAT JURY, SO WE GOT TO MAKE
A DECISION, BUT EITHER WAY, ALL
FIVE PEOPLE GOING TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL THINK THEY'RE SAFE
TONIGHT.
IT'S GOING TO BE FUN.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S START WITH TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
DEVENS, YOUR FOURTH INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY WIN.
IS PART OF THAT DRIVE COMING
FROM THE FACT THAT YOU HAVE
TRULY FELT LIKE YOU WERE GOING
HOME IF YOU DIDN'T WIN?
>> YEAH, I REALLY THINK SO.
WHEN YOUR BACK IS UP AGAINST THE
WALL, YOU JUST HAVE EVERYTHING
TO LOSE, AND I FEEL LIKE I GET
SUPER FOCUSED IN ON WHAT I'M
DOING, AND IT'S DRIVEN ME SO
FAR.
I'M SURPRISED BY IT, BUT I'M
HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, WHEN YOU GET
BACK THE CAMP, ONCE AGAIN DEVENS
IS SAFE.
WAS THAT THE CONVERSATION?
NOW WHAT?
>> YEAH.
I NEEDED TO WIN TODAY.
NOT HAVING THAT NECKLACE RIGHT
NOW REALLY MADE ME NERVOUS, SO I
HAD TO TRUST THAT THE PEOPLE AND
THE RELATIONSHIPS THAT I'VE
FORMED SINCE BEING BACK IN THIS
GAME, THEY'RE GOING TO PAY OFF,
AND I'VE HAD TO USE WHAT LITTLE
CARDS I HAVE TO PLEAD MY CASE.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE ABOUT CHRIS'S ANSWER.
THAT SEAMED TO PIQUE YOUR
INTEREST.
>> CHRIS IS SAYING, IF DOESN'T
WIN, I CAN BEAT HIM IN FIRE
MAKING.
BUT WHAT HAPPENS IF WINS HIS
FIFTH IMMUNITY AND I'M IN THE
FIRE MAKING CHALLENGE AGAINST
CHRIS?
>> JULIE, DOES CHRIS'S LOGIC
MAKE SENSE?
IF DEVENS IS SEEN AS THE NUMBER
ONE, THEN YOU SHOULD KEEP
SOMEBODY WHO HAS A CHANCE TO
BEAT THE NUMBER ONE?
>> I AGREE WITH LAUREN, THERE
ARE A LOT OF IFS THAT HAVE TO
HAPPEN, AND IT COULD BE ME IN A
FIRE HER MAKING CHANGE.
LIKE LAUREN, I DON'T WANT TO SIT
NEXT TO CHRIS.
THERE ARE TOO MANY UNKNOWNS.
>> LAST TRIBAL I MADE A GAMBLE.
AND I SAID, IF LAUREN IS TELLING
ME THE TRUTH, THEN I'M GOOD.
SO, YEAH, THERE'S A LOT OF IFS
OUT THERE.
>> ?OO CHRIS, IS THERE TRUST
BETWEEN YOU AND LAUREN BASED ON
THE IDOL PLAY, OR IS THAT GAME
PLAY AND THAT'S DONE NOW?
>> IT WAS GAME PLAY AT THAT
TIME.
NOW WHETHER OR NOT SHE WAS
TELLING ME THE TRUTH BECAUSE SHE
WANTED TO HELP ME OR BECAUSE SHE
WANTED TO BOOST HER RESUME, I
DON'T KNOW.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, IT SOUND LIKE
CHRIS WAS FRUSTRATED WITH YOU,
AND YET YOU PLAYED YOU IDOL FOR
HIM.
>> I THINK I HAVE TRUST WITH
CHRIS, BUT A I CAN'T REALLY TELL
IF HE THINKS HE HAS TRUST WITH
ME, WHICH IS FRUSTRATING BECAUSE
TRUST SHOULD WORK BOTH WAYS.
BUT I THINK THAT THE PEOPLE THAT
I HAVE A PLAN WITH TONIGHT KNOW
WHERE MY ALLEGIANCE LIES.
>> IF THEY THINK THAT TAKING ME
OUT THEY HAVE A BETTER SHOT AT
BEATING RICK, THEN THAT'S THEIR
PLAY.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THAT LIKE,
DEVENS, TO BE THE CENTER OF
EVERYTHING FOR SEVERAL TRIBALS
IN A ROW.
>> I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE AWESOME, BUT IT'S OLD NOW.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE GET SO LASER
FOCUSED ON ME THAT THEY LET THE
REST OF THE GAME GO BY.
>> Jeff: GAVIN, WHAT'S YOUR
POINT OF VIEW?
>> I'M WILLING TO GO AGAINST THE
BEST OF THEM.
I HAVE I HAVE A PROVEN TRACK
RECORD IN IMMUNITY CHALLENGES SO
FAR, SO MAYBE NEXT ONE I CAN WIN
AND THEN WE CAN DECIDE AS A
GROUP WHO WE WANT TO PUT IN THAT
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: SO YOUR PITCH IS THAT
YOU COULD WIN THE NEXT
CHALLENGE, THEREFORE, OPENING
THE DOOR TO GET RID OF WHOEVER
YOU WANT?
>> RIGHT.
I HAVE WON TWO AND I WAS CLOSE
TO WINNING THREE TODAY.
THAT WOULD HAVE TIED ME AND
DEVENS.
HE DID GET THE UPPER HAND ON ME
TODAY, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT'S GOING TO BE THE SAME CASE
FOR TOMORROW.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JULIE, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, TONIGHT IS THE LAST NIGHT
YOU CAN PLAY IT.
>> WELL, JEFF, JUST IN CASE, I
FOUND A LITTLE SOMETHING.
I DON'T THINK IT'S ME TONIGHT,
BUT I'D LIKE THE PLAY IT FOR
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS FAKE.
>>
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: ANY VOTES CAST FOR
JULIE WILL STILL COUNT.
>> WHAT?
JEFF.
>> SO HERE'S HOPING THIS ONE IS
REAL.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
I'M GOING THE PLAY IT FOR
MYSELF.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS FAKE.
>> WOW.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> Jeff: ANY VOTES CAST FOR
LAUREN WILL STILL COUNT.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> I'LL GIVE IT A SHOT, JEFF.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
>> I WILL PLAY THIS IDOL FOR
GAVIN.
>> DUDE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS, MAN?
>> I LOVE YOU, BRO.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS REAL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR GAVIN WILL
NOT COUNT.
>> WELL, HATE THE POOP ON
EVERYONE'S PARADE, BUT I MIGHT
JUST HAVE TO PLAY THIS ONE, AS
WELL.
I'M PLAYING IT FOR MYSELF.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS ALSO
REAL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR CHRIS WILL
NOT COUNT.
ANYBODY ELSE?
[LAUGHTER]
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, CHRIS.
DOES NOT COUNT.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: CHRIS.
DOES NOT COUNT.
CHRIS.
LAUREN.
ONE VOTE LAUREN.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
16th PERSON VOLTED OUT AND
THE 12th MEMBER OF OUR JURY.
LAUREN, YOU NEED TO BRING ME
YOUR TORCH.
>> THAT WAS REALLY WELL PLAYED,
RICK.
>> Jeff: LAUREN.
THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> THANK YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
SERIOUSLY, GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, LAUREN.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE MADE IT TO THE
FINAL FOUR.
TOMORROW YOU'LL COMPETE IN YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
FOR THE FOURTH TIME.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS UP BACK
UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO NEGOTIATE A ROCKING
WALKWAY WHILE ATTEMPTING TO
BALANCE BLOCKS ON A WOBBLY
LEDGE.
FIRST PERSON TO STACK ALL THEIR
BLOCKS SPELLING "FINAL THREE"
WINS IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A SPOT
AT THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE YOU WILL GET A CHANCE TO
PLEAD YOUR CASE ABOUT WHY YOU
DESERVE THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION DOLLAR
PRIZE.
THE SINGLE BIGGEST CHALLENGE OF
THE SEASON.
LET'S DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND A SPOT AT THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL, SURVIVORS
READY?
GO!
EVERYBODY OUT QUICKLY.
THAT FIRST BLOCK IS EASY.
YOU GET IT DOWN, GET BACK.
ALTHOUGH I SAY THAT AND GAVIN
DROPS AND DEVENS DROPS.
TWO DROPS ON THE FIRST AND
EASIEST PART OF THIS CHALLENGE.
THAT SPEAKS TO THE LEARNING
CURVE.
JULIE HAS HER FIRST.
COMING BACK WITH HER SECOND.
CHRIS HAS HIS SECOND BLOCK.
DEVENS REACHING FOR HIS SECOND
BLOCK.
GOT TO GET BEHIND THE LINE.
GAVIN NOW BACK AGAIN WITH HIS
FIRST BLOCK.
JULIE WITH HER THIRD.
DEVENS PLACES HIS SECOND.
CHRIS STILL HAS TWO.
CHRIS MOVING VERY SLOWLY.
DEVENS HAS SLOWED DOWN NOW,
TRYING FIGURE THIS OUT.
EVERYBODY MOVING NICE AND SLOW
NOW, TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
THAT TIPPING POINT IS.
AND DEFER DEAF JUST FOUND IT.
GAVIN DROPS AGAIN.
EVERYBODY NOW CHASING JULIE AND
SIMULTANEOUSLY HOPING JULIE WILL
DROP.
CHRIS PLAYING HIS OWN GAME NOW.
NOT WORRIED ABOUT JULIE.
JUST SLOWLY BUILDING HIS STACK
WITH HIS THIRD.
JULIE HAS HER FOURTH.
GAVIN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
IT IS JULIE WITH FOUR.
CHRIS WITH THREE.
DEVENS STILL WOBBLY DOWN ON THE
END WITH HIS FIRST.
JULIE REACHES FOR THAT FIFTH
BLOCK.
SHE'S BEEN PERFECT THIS THIS
CHALLENGE.
CHRIS NOW WITH THREE.
GAVIN AT ONE.
DEVENS AT ONE.
JULIE IN THE LEAD WITH FOUR.
COMING BACK WITH HER FIFTH.
AND JULIE DROPS EVERYTHING.
HAS TO START OVER.
THAT'S HOW FAST IT CAN CHANGE.
IT IS NOW CHRIS IN THE LEAD WITH
THREE.
THIS IS WHY YOU KEEP FIGHTING.
ANYBODY CAN DROP.
AS GAVIN JUST DID.
HAS TO GO BACK AGAIN.
CHRIS PLACES HIS FOURTH BLOCK.
CHRIS IS REALLY SLOW NOW.
HE'S GOT A LEAD.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO LOSE IT,
WHICH OPENS THE DOOR FOR DEVENS
TO TRY TO CATCH HIM.
DEVENS DROPS, LOSES EVERYTHING.
IT'S NOW CHRIS AND GAVIN DROPS.
HE'S OUT AGAIN.
CHRIS HAS BEEN VERY CONSISTENT
FOR A LONG TIME.
JULIA MOVING A LOT FASTER THAN
CHRIS TRYING TO MAKE UP TIME.
CHRIS REMAINS SLOW AND STEADY.
CHRIS NOW ALL ALONE IN THE LEAD.
COMING BACK WITH HIS FIFTH
BLOCK.
IF HE CAN MAINTAIN THIS PACE,
AND THAT BALANCE, HE'LL BE GOING
TO THE FINAL THREE.
GAVIN TRYING TO GET BACK IN IT
WITH HIS THIRD.
JULIE NOT GIVING UP.
SHE'S QUICKLY TRYING TO GET BACK
IN THIS.
DEVENS DOWN ON THE END WITH ONE
BLOCK, AND THAT JUST DROPS.
DEVENS HAS HAD NO SUCCESS IN
THIS CHALLENGE AT ALL.
IT WILL TAKE A MISTAKE FROM
CHRIS FOR ANYBODY ELSE TO HAVE A
SHOT.
AND HIS CLOSEST COMPETITOR,
GAVIN JUST DROPPED.
DEVENS NOW PICKING UP THE PACE.
DEVENS PLACES HIS THIRD.
JULIE COMING OUT WITH HER THIRD,
HOPING FOR A DISASTER FOR CHRIS.
HE'S REACHING NOW TO PLACE THAT
SIXTH AND FINAL BLOCK.
NICE TOUCH.
NOW CHRIS JUST HAS TO GET BACK
TO THE FINISH.
BOTH FEET ACROSS THE BLUE.
GAVIN DROPS.
HE'S GOT TO START AGAIN.
JULIE BACK IN IT WITH HER FOURTH
BLOCK.
DEVENS DROPS.
DEVENS HAS TO START AGAIN.
THIS WOULD BE CHRIS'S FIRST
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN, AND
WHAT A TIME FOR IT TO COME.
DEVENS DROPS AGAIN.
PANIC SETTING IN NOW.
JULIE WITH HER FIFTH BLOCK.
JULIE'S GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION.
DOES SHE RACE AND TRY THE CATCH
CHRIS OR HOPE FOR HIM TO DROP.
CHRIS IS JUST A FEW STEPS AWAY.
GOT TO GET BOTH FEET OVER THE
BLUE.
CHRIS AT SIX, JULIE AT FIVE.
CHRIS INCHING THOSE FEET BACK.
CHRIS IS EITHER GOING TO DROP OR
GOING TO WIN.
JULIE DROPS.
CHRIS HAS ONE FOOT IN THE BLUE.
THE LEFT FOOT, THE ONLY THING
STANDING BETWEEN CHRIS AND A
SPOT IN THE FINAL THREE.
CHRIS HAS IT!
CHRIS WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEEING HIMSELF A SPOT AT
THE FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL ALL THE
WAY BACK FROM THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION WITH A SHOT TO WIN
THE GAME!
WHO WOULD HAVE EVER THOUGHT THAT
COULD HAPPEN?
CHRIS, COME ON OVER.
FIRST INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY WIN
COULDN'T COME AT A BETTER TIME.
GUARANTEED A SPOT AT THE FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
TONIGHT YOU WILL DECIDE WHICH
ONE OF THESE THREE, DEVENS,
GAVIN, OR JULIE YOU CHOOSE TO
HAVE SIT NEXT TO YOU AND WHICH
TWO YOU FORCE TO BATTLE FOR
THEIR SPOT IN A FIRE-MAKING
SHOWDOWN.
I'M SURE IT'S GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING AFTERNOON FOR YOU.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU GUYS TONIGHT AT TRIAL.
CONGRATS.
WELL DONE.
>> I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD TAKE
38 DAYS BEFORE I GOT MY FIRST
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE WIN, BUT
TONIGHT THIS IS ABSOLUTELY THE
MOST IMPORTANT DECISION I'LL
HAVE THE MAKE.
I'M NOT PLAYING THIS GAME FOR
SECOND, THIRD, OR FOURTH.
I'M PLAYING THIS GAME TO WIN.
>> THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE DIDN'T
GO ACCORDING TO PLAN THAT.
CHALLENGE WAS THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THE FINAL THREE POSSIBLY
AND GOING HOME.
>> REALLY INCREDIBLE JOB.
>> CRAZY.
THIRD VOTE OUT TO FINAL THREE.
>> CHRIS HAS THE CONTROL RIGHT
NOW.
I MEAN, HE'S DETERMINING WHO IS
SAFE TONIGHT AND WHO IS BUILDING
FIRE TONIGHT.
>> GLAD I HAVE THE NECKLACE
AROUND MY NECK.
>> LOOK WHAT WE HAVE?
>> WE HAVE TOOLS TO MAKE FIRE
WITH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO TO FIRE.
THERE'S A LOT OF RANDOMNESS THAT
GOES INTO IT.
I HAVE WORKED SO HARD TO TAKE
THE RANDOMNESS OUT OF MY GAME,
BUT I'M NOT GIVING UP.
>> THIS IS COOL.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, YOU GUYS GRAB YOUR
STUFF AND DEFINITELY PRACTICE.
>> I JUST HAVE TO CONVINCE CHRIS
TO TAKE ME TO THE FINAL THREE BY
LETTING HIM KNOW HOW LOYAL I
HAVE BEEN TO HIM.
>> I CAN TALK TO EACH ONE OF YOU
GUYS.
>> LET'S DO IT, BUDDY.
>> I'M TRYING EVERYTHING I CAN
TO GUARANTEE A SPOT.
THIS IS $1 MILLION WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
THIS IS A WHOLE CHANGE TO MY
LIFE AND MY FAMILY'S LIFE.
>> WANT ME TO PLEAD MY CASE?
>> YEAH, I DO?
>> YOU KNOW BY BEING LOYAL TO
YOU, I FEEL LIKE I EITHER
SECURED MY PLACE IN THE GAME OR
SUNK MY GAME.
I OBVIOUSLY COULD HAVE WITHHELD
THE IDOL YESTERDAY, AND YOU
WOULD BE OUT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW THERE HASN'T
BEEN ANY HESITATION ABOUT ME
BEING LOYAL TO YOU SINCE WE CAME
BACK.
SO IT WOULD BE NICE TO GET PAY
BACK THERE.
>> DID YOU PRACTICE FIRE BEFORE
COMING OUT HERE?
>> YEAH, AT THIS POINT, YOU HAVE
TO MAKE FIRE TONIGHT.
YOU PLAYED THE $1 MILLION GAME.
DEVENS AND I HAVE GONE THROUGH A
LOT THIS GAME, BUT I'M AFRAID.
I'M GOING TO GO PRACTICE FIRE.
>> IF HE GOES TO PLEAD HIS CASE
AT THE FINAL TRIBAL, REGARDLESS
OF WHO IS SITTING THERE, WE ALL
LOSE TO DEVENS.
>> WHAT'S DEVENS SAYING?
>> DEVENS IS TRYING TO PLEAD HIS
CASE.
>> FOR YOU TO JUST TAKE HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> IS THAT SOMETHING YOU'RE
ACTUALLY CONSIDERING?
>> I FEEL LIKE I WOULD BE THE
STUPIDEST "SURVIVOR" PLAYER
EVER.
>> NONE OF US STAND A CHANCE.
THE WAY I LOOK AT IT IS YOU HELP
ME GET PREPARED FOR TONIGHT AND
THEN I'M GOING TO TRY MY BEST TO
BEAT HIM.
I DON'T REALLY THINK JULIE HAS A
SHOT.
>> WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS I
DON'T KNOW WHO IS GOING THE TAKE
HIM, WHETHER IT'S YOU OR JULIE,
BUT I'M GOING TO HELP YOU MAKE
FIRE.
AND I'M GOING TO HELP JULIE MAKE
AND THE BEST PERSON IS GOING TO
TAKE HIM ON AT FIRE.
>> CHRIS IS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO TO SEND TO FIRE AND WHO IS
GOING TO BE EASIER THE BEAT.
HE'S IN THE FINAL THREE NOW.
-IMPORTANT THING IS DON'T TRY TO
START TOO QUICK.
>> DEVENS IS SOMEONE I DON'T
WANT TO GO AGAINST IN THE
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE, BUT IF I
HAVE TO GO AGAINST HIM, THEN I'M
GOING TO GO TO FIRE TONIGHT, AND
I'M GOING TO WIN.
>> THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
THEN I'M GOING TO SHOW JULIE HOW
TO DO IT.
AS WELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WHEN I SEE A FLAME LIKE
THAT --
>> YOU WANT TO FOLD IT OVER.
>> AND THEN YOU WANT TO STUFF IT
IN THERE.
>> WE NEED DEVENS KNOCKED OUT OF
THIS GAME.
IF YOU WANT A SURE BET AGAINST
DEVENS, IT MAY NOT BE ME, BUT
I'M HAPPY TO STEP UP AND TAKINGE
THE CHALLENGE.
>>
>> YES.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M
UNDERESTIMATED.
I FEEL LIKE I WILL BE PRACTICING
FIRE FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
>> EVERYTHING IS SIMILAR FIND
RIGHT NOW.
MAKE FIRE OR GO HOME.
>> THERE HAS NEVER BEEN THIS
MUCH PRESSURE.
THERE'S A LOT RIDING ON IT.
WHETHER IT'S GAVIN OR JULIE, IT
DOESN'T REALLY MAKE A DIFFERENCE
IN WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
I PUT EVERYTHING INTO THIS.
TO SET MYSELF UP FOR THIS
SCENARIO.
IF I WORK HARD ENOUGH AND FOCUS
HARD ENOUGH.
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
I'VE DONE IT IN THIS GAME.
THAT'S SOMETHING I'M TAKING TO
THE FIRE MAKING TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT I'VE GOT SO MUCH ON
THE LINE.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST DECISION I
HAVE TO MAKE.
I'M WEARING THE NECKLACE.
I HAVE TOTAL CONTROL.
JULIE AND GAVIN THINK THAT THEY
CAN BEAT RICK IN FIRE.
>> WE CAN DO IT.
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M AT A
HIGH-STAKES POKER TABLE, AND I
HAVE A HAND THAT MIGHT WIN, AND
IT ALSO MIGHT NOT, SO I MIGHT
HAVE TO BE FLAT-OUT DARING,
STICK ALL MY CHIPS IN, AND LET
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPEN.
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
IT'S FOR $1 MILLION, MAN.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO LET'S GET DOWN TO IT, FINAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
CHRIS, YOU PULLED IT OFF,
GUARANTEEING YOURSELF A SPOT IN
THE FINAL THREE.
YOU WILL GET CHANCE TO PLEAD
YOUR CASE WHY YOU DESERVE THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
$1 MILLION PRIZE.
IN A LOT OF WAYS EXTINCTION IS A
BIG PART OF THE REASON YOU'RE
WHERE YOU ARE IN THIS GAME.
>> YEAH.
A LOT OF THOSE JURY MEMBERS KNOW
MY JOURNEY, AND SINCE COMING
BACK FROM THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION
AND BEATING OUT LITERALLY SOME
OF THE BEST COMPETITORS THE GAME
HAS EVER SEEN, MY JOURNEY WAS
REALLY UPHILL.
SO I HAD TO MAKE SOME MOVES, AND
I HAD TO WIN TODAY.
>> Jeff: SO YOU GUYS HEAD BACK
TO CAMP.
THERE ARE THREE PEOPLE THAT ARE
REALLY EXCITED TO TALK TO YOU.
JULIE, WHAT WAS YOUR CASE?
>> I DIDN'T PLEAD MY CASE TODAY
BECAUSE I WOULD BE SO GRATEFUL
IF HE CHOSE ME TO BE IN THE
FINAL THREE, BUT I WOULD ALSO
LOVE TO BE ABLE TO PROVE MYSELF
AND MAKE FIRE.
SO I WENT OFF AND PRACTICED
MAKING FIRE AND HE WAS VERY
HELPFUL IN GIVING ME SUGGESTIONS
AND SOME TIPS, BUT I'M HAPPY
WITH WHATEVER HE DECIDES.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE CHOSEN.
I WANT TO EARN IT.
SO DON'T PICK ME.
>> WELL, THIS IS GREAT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I WANT TO GO AGAINST DEVENS.
I DON'T WANT TO GO AGAINST
JULIE.
>> Jeff: WOW.
THAT'S A REMARKABLE STATEMENT.
I WANT FIRE.
AND I WANT DEVENS.
>> YEAH.
GAVIN KNOWS IT'S A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY TO PUT ONE MORE
THING ON THE RESUME AND TAKE OUT
THE OBVIOUS FRONT-RUNNER FOR
THIS SEASON.
SO, YEAH, GAVIN HAS A GOOD
POINT.
>> CHRIS AND I WANT TO BE REALLY
LOYAL.
I FEEL LIKE EASY DECISION
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, THROUGHOUT THE
AFTERNOON DID YOU WAIVER AT ALL
ON YOUR DECISION, OR WERE YOU
LOCKED IN?
>> ONE THING THE EDGE THOUGHT ME
IS IT'S OKAY TO BE BY YOURSELF
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
AS I LOOKED OUT AT THE OCEAN AND
JUST WACHED THE WAVES, I KNEW
MORE AND MORE EXACTLY WHAT I
NEEDED TO DO.
I CAME INTO THIS GAME WANTING TO
HAVE NO REGRETS, AND I WOULDN'T
WANT THERE TO BE ANY OTHER WAY
FOR THIS SEASON TO END.
IT'S THE BIGGEST RISK I'M
TAKING, SO TONIGHT I AM OFFERING
UP MY IMMUNITY NECKLACE, GIVING
IT TO JULIE.
>> FOR REAL?
>> THIS IS YOUR, JULIE.
AND I WILL BE MAKING FIRE
AGAINST RICK DEVENS TONIGHT.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, IS IT PART OF
YOUR SPIRITUAL JOURNEY THAT YOU
WANT TO SEE WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF,
OR DO YOU NEED YOU BELIEVE YOU
NEED TO BEAT DEVENS IN THE FIRE
MAKING TO HAVE A CHANCE TO WIN?
>> I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN THE GUY
WHO WANTS TO TAKE THE LAST SHOT.
IF I MAKE IT, THAT WILL PROVE
THAT I DESERVE TO WIN AND BE THE
SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
JULIA, GAVIN, YOU WILL BE IN THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
WHO WILL JOIN YOU?
WILL IT BE CHRIS OR DEVENS?
THEY'RE GOING TO SHOWDOWN IN A
FIRE-MAKING, DO-OR-DIE
CHALLENGE.
BECAUSE OF THE SEVERE FIJIAN
WINDS TONIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO DO
THIS SHOWDOWN UP IN THE VOTING
CONFESSIONAL WHERE MANY
DECISIONS HAVE BEEN MADE THIS
SEASON, AND ONE OF THE BIGGEST
IS GOING TO PLAY OUT UP THERE
TONIGHT.
CHRIS, DEVENS, YOUR FIRE MAKING
STATIONS UP THERE WAITING FOR
YOU.
HEAD UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'LL KEEP YOU ALL POSTED.
>> Jeff: CHRIS, DEVENS, YOU
BOTH HAVE A FLINT, KNIFE, SAME
AMOUNT OF FIRE-MAKING SUPPLIES.
THE RULES ARE SIMPLE.
YOU HAVE TO BUILD A FIRE WITH A
FLAME HIGH ENOUGH TO BURN THE
ROPE AND RAISE THE FLAG.
MAKE SENSE?
>> YEP.
>> Jeff: BOTH READY?
>> YEAH, MAN.
>> HISTORIC.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO?
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
38 DAYS ON "SURVIVOR," AND IT
COMES DOWN TO THIS FOR BOTH
CHRIS AND DEVENS.
$1 MILLION ON THE LINE.
JULIE AND GAVIN ARE ALREADY IN
THE FINAL THREE.
ONE MORE SPOT OPEN.
CHRIS BUILDING A LITTLE BIT OF A
STRUCTURE BEFORE HE STARTS
WORKING WITH HIS FLINT.
DEVENS GETS TO HIS FLINT FIRST,
SHAVING OFF SOME MAGNESIUM.
CHRIS STARTING TO SHAVE
MAGNESIUM NOW.
DEVENS NOW GOING FOR A SPARK,
TRYING THE LIGHT THAT MAGNESIUM.
THIS IS A POTENTIAL $1 MILLION
FIRE YOU'RE TRYING TO BUILD.
DEVENS GOT A LITTLE BIT OF
SOMETHING.
BUT IT GOES OUT QUICKLY.
CHRIS NOW GOING FAR SPARK.
BOTH GUYS TRYING TO GET A SPARK
GOING NOW.
CHRIS HAS FLAME QUICKLY.
TRYING THE KEEP IT GOING.
IT GOES OUT.
DEVENS HAS A LITTLE BIT OF
FLAME.
HE'S TRYING THE KEEP IT GOING.
>> YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOMETHING
FOR IT TO TAKE TO.
DEVENS' FIRE GOES OUT.
CHRIS'S FIRE GO OUT.
BOTH GUYS SCRAPING AGAIN.
CHRIS NOW GETTING MORE MAGNESIUM
WHILE DEVENS IS TRYING TO GET A
SPARK.
DEVENS HAS LITTLE BITS OF FLAME
BUT NOTHING CATCHING YET.
CHRIS HAS A LITTLE SOMETHING.
IT COMES BACK THE LIFE.
DEVENS NOW HAS A FIRE.
HE CAN TURN IT INTO SOMETHING.
IT GOES OUT AGAIN.
CHRIS HAS A LITTLE BIT OF FLAME
NOW.
GOT TO GET SOME STICKS GOING.
>> CHRIS GOT IT.
>> DEVENS HAS HAD A LITTLE FIRE
BUT CAN'T TURN IT INTO A FLAME
THAT WILL STICK.
HE'S GOT TO GET A FIRE GOING.
CHRIS ADDING A FEW MORE STICKS.
TRYING TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
FLAME HE HAS WILL STAY BURNING
AS HE TRIES TO BUILD IT HIGHER.
DEVENS NOT PANICKING NOW.
SCRAPING MORE MAGNESIUM.
CHRIS'S FIRE CONTINUING TO GROW.
LITTLE BY LITTLE.
DEVENS STILL TRYING TO GET A
SPARK, A LITTLE BIT OF FLAME TO
GIVE HIM LIFE IN THIS CHALLENGE.
AND HE DOES.
DEVENS NOW HAS A FIRE.
HE'S GOT A FLAME GOING.
AND IT'S GOING TO STICK.
ONE THING TO HAVE A FIRE.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO GET THAT FLAME
HIGH ENOUGH TO BURN THROUGH THE
ROPE DEVENS HAS A NICE FIRE
GOING.
CAN HE CATCH CHRIS IN TIME?
>> COME ON.
COME ON!
AND CHRIS'S FIRE IS STARTING TO
HIT THE ROPE.
FIRST STARTING TO BURN.
IT'S OVER.
CHRIS HAS EARNED HIS WAY INTO
THE FINAL THREE IN AN HISTORIC
MOVE TAKING ON DEVENS.
>> GOOD JOB, BRO.
STRAIGHT UP SHOWDOWN.
>> Jeff: SO, CHRIS, THAT WAS
ONE OF THE BIGGEST MOVES THAT
HAS EVER BEEN MADE IN THE GAME.
TO PULL YOURSELF OUT OF THE
FINAL THREE TO TRY TO WORK YOUR
WAY BACK IN, YOU'VE GOT TO FEEL
ON SOME LEVEL AS THOUGH YOU HAVE
COMPLETED YOUR SURVIVOR JOURNEY,
GIVING UP THAT NECKLACE.
>> IT WAS LIKE GOING BACK ON THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
I HAD TO EARN MY SPOT TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME AND I HAD TO
EARN IT AGAINST THE BEST ONE WHO
PLAYED THIS SEASON.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, YOU FOUND A
LOT OF IDOLS.
YOU WON A LOT OF IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES, AND YET ON THE NIGHT
OF THE 38th DAY OUT HERE,
YOU FALL SHORT AND THE GAME IS
OVER.
YOU NOW JOIN THE JURY.
WHAT'S THIS EXPERIENCE BEEN FOR
YOU?
>> I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE TO
LEARN ABOUT MYSELF.
I DIDN'T COME OUT HERE TO FIND
OUT ANYTHING ABOUT MYSELF.
I JUST WANTED TO WIN $1 MILLION.
BUT IT HAS A WAY OF TEACHING YOU
THINGS ABOUT YOURSELF, WHETHER
YOU WANT TO LEARN OR NOT.
I TAKE A LOT OF CONFIDENCE AWAY.
I DIDN'T THINK I WOULD PERFORM
AS WELL AS I DID IN CHALLENGES.
I DIDN'T THINK I WOULD FIND
IDOLS.
I DIDN'T THINK I WOULD HAVE THE
GUTS TO MAKE FAKE IDOLS.
I FELT LIKE I PUT EVERYTHING I
HAD INTO THE GAME.
AND I FENDED OFF ELIMINATION
FROM TRIBAL AFTER TRIBAL.
BUT I'M GOING HOME A BETTER DAD,
A BETTER HUSBAND, AND I THINK I
FEEL LIKE I CAN DO A LOT OF
THINGS THAT I MIGHT NOT HAVE
THOUGHT BEFORE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DEVENS, QUITE A JOURNEY, GOING
TO EXTINCTION, FIGHTING YOUR WAY
BACK IN AND GETTING TO THIS
POINT IS AN AMAZING STORY.
38 DAYS IS WHERE IT ENDS.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK.
IT'S BEEN BLAST.
>> LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> Jeff: DEVENS, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> YOU BECOME THE FINAL MEMBER
OF THE JURY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: JULIE, CHRIS, GAVIN,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN
GO IN THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE MADE IT TO THE FINAL.
NOW THE POWER IN THE GAME SHIFTS
TO THE JURY.
SAME PEOPLE THAT YOU VOTED OUT
EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY
ARE NOW IN CONTROL.
TOMORROW NIGHT YOU WILL FACE
YOUR FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
YOU WILL PLEAD YOUR CASE ABOUT
WHY YOU WERE THE ONE THAT
DESERVES THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE $1 MILLION
CHECK THAT GOES WITH IT.
IT IS YOUR LAST NIGHT IN FIJI.
TRY TO GET SOME SLEEP.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> THIS JUST INTO THE NEWSROOM:
CHRIS'S FLAME BREAKS THE ROPE
AND DEVENS' HEART.
PLUS AN APPLAUSE AS HE EXITS
BRINGS TEARS TO HIS EYES.
I'M RICK DEVENS.
IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE BRINGING
YOU THE NEWS, BUT THIS IS ALL
FOR US.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU IN THE REAL
WORLD REAL SOON.
>> Jeff: WELL, HE FOUGHT HIS
WAY BACK FROM EXTINCTION.
HE FOUND IDOLS.
HE WON CHALLENGES.
HE DROVE HIS TRIBE CRAZY AND HE
NEARLY PULLED OFF THE
IMPOSSIBLE.
COME ON OUT, DEVENS.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
LOOK AT THAT.
STANDING OVAGUE.
-- OVATION.
TAKE THAT IN, BROTHER.
TAKE THAT IN.
SO HAVE A SEAT.
HAVE A SEAT, GUYS.
THAT WAS REALLY NICE.
WHAT DOES THAT FEEL LIKE?
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOTTEN LOVE THIS
ENTIRE SEASON.
>> IT FEELS -- THIS FEELS GREAT.
WATCHING THAT WAS ROUGHER.
MAN, I JUST PUT SO MUCH INTO IT.
BUT THIS IS AWESOME.
IT'S BEEN REALLY -- THE
"SURVIVOR" FAMILY, MAN, THEY
COME THROUGH, DON'T THEY?
>> Jeff: THEY DO.
AND THE SHOW REALLY -- WHEN
PEOPLE CONNECT, AND THERE IS A
RELATABLE STORY, LET'S JUST TALK
ABOUT THE TWO BIG PIVOTAL MOVES.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
YOU REMAIN LOYAL TO CHRIS AND
GIVE HIM BACK THAT IDOL, WAS
THAT TRULY BECAUSE YOU JUST FELT
YOU COULDN'T BETRAY HIM AGAIN?
>> IT WAS.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU GO TO THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION, YOU'RE FACED
WITH THE PEOPLE THAT YOU
BETRAYED, AND I FELT HONESTLY
OUT THERE LIKE I HAD WRECKED
CHRIS.
LIKE I WAS VERY WORRIED ABOUT
HIM.
HE WAS SO BIG TO ME WHEN I WENT
OUT THERE.
HE WAS KIND.
HE DIDN'T HOLD IT AGAINST ME.
>> Jeff: SO YOU WANTED TO HEAL
THAT WOUND.
>> I WANTED TO HEAL IT, AND I
COULD NOT DO THAT TO HIM AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T EXPLAIN IT TO PEOPLE,
BUT I WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO WITHHOLD THE IDOL AT TRIBAL,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, SORRY, BUDDY.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
SO WHEN YOU GET THE QUID PRO QUO
MOMENT, AND HE DOESN'T REMAIN
LOYAL, IN FACT, HE TAKES YOU ON,
IS THAT A BETRAYAL OR IS IT GAME
PLAY OR CAN IT BE BOTH?
>> IT CAN BE BOTH IN "SURVIVOR."
IT CAN BE BOTH IN "SURVIVOR."
IT CERTAINLY WASN'T QUID PRO QUO
WITH THE LOYALTY, BUT HE
GUARANTEED ME FINAL FOUR.
AND HE GOT ME FINAL FOUR, AND
THEN HE MADE A MOVE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ONE LAST QUESTION.
GIVEN THE RECEPTION HERE, IT'S
OBVIOUS THAT YOU RELATE THE
PEOPLE AND YOU'RE VERY FUNNY AND
CHARMING.
WE COULD ALWAYS COUNT ON YOU FOR
A NEWSCAST.
YOUR CAREER, YOU'RE IN MACON
GEORGIA, GREAT CITY WHERE YOU
LIVE, AND THAT'S YOUR HOME, BUT
CAREER WISE IT'S A SMALLER
MARKET.
>> YES, YES.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU OPEN OR HAVE
YOU GOTTEN ANY INTEREST, IF
SOMEBODY WANTED YOU ON A MORNING
SHOW, ARE YOU OPEN TO MOVING?
IT'S JUST A -- ARE YOU OPEN TO
THAT?
>> AS LONG AS MY BOSSES COULD
SWITCH CHANNELS REAL QUICK, I'M
OPEN TO ANYTHING.
I'M OPEN TO ANYTHING.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE OUR FINAL
THREE.
DEVENS, IT'S NOT YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A PUSH TO THE FINISH.
THE FINALE RIGHT AFTER THIS.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL, MAN?
>> SAUSAGE.
EGGS, PANCAKE MIX.
>> PANCAKES ON THE GRIDDLE.
>> I CANNOT BELIEVE I HAVE MADE
IT TO DAY 39 ON "SURVIVOR."
I CAME OUT HERE TO HAVE THE
ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME, AND I
NEEDED TO PROVE TO MYSELF AND TO
MY KIDS THAT I WAS STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE ABLE TO DO THIS.
>> LET'S DO A TOAST.
I WANTED TO BE THIS ROLE MODEL
TO THEM THAT WAS MORE THAN A
MOM, SHOW THEM THEY COULD
ACCOMPLISH SOMETHING THAT WAS ON
SUCH A BIGGER LEVEL.
>> WE'RE ON "SURVIVOR."
WE'RE IN DAY 39, THE FINAL
BREAKFAST.
>> I HAVE BEEN PLAYING THE GAME
FROM DAY ONE TO DAY 39, BUT I
HAVE BEEN PLAYING IT IN MY OWN
WAY.
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET THIS
BREAKFAST.
>> I ACTUALLY CRIED AND LEANED
ON ALMOST EVERY PERSON OUT HERE
AND GOT THEIR SUPPORT AND AT THE
SAME TIME GAVE THEM SUPPORT
BACK.
I THINK THAT'S ONE OF THE
REASONS I'VE MADE IT TO THE
FINAL THREE IS BECAUSE OF THE
RELATIONSHIPS THAT I SPENT SO
MUCH TIME BUILDING.
I KNOW THAT JURY IS GOING TO BE
BRUTAL, BUT I PLAYED A GAME
THAT'S WORTHY OF BEING GRANTED
THE TITLE OF THE SOLE SURVIVOR,
AND I'M GOING TO PROVE THAT
TONIGHT.
>> WHAT'S YOUR BIGGEST DREAM?
>> PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU IN.
>> MY DREAM IS TO BUY A SAILBOAT
AND TAKE MY FAMILY AND I WANT TO
SAIL AROUND THE WORLD.
>> GAVIN AND JULIE, THEY'RE
TRYING TO OUT, LAST BUT THEY
DON'T KNOW WHAT OUTLAST REALLY
MEANS.
I SPENT 28 DAYS ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
>> GLAD TO HAVE MET YOU, GAVIN,
EVEN THOUGH YOU TRIED TO VOTE ME
OUT.
I AM THE PLAYER I AM BECAUSE OF
THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
IT TOOK WILL AND GRIT AND
REFLECTION.
AND WHEN I GOT BACK IN THE GAME,
IN THREE DAYS, MY GAME WAS
BETTER THAN TWO OTHER PLAYERS
WHO HAD 39 DAYS TO DO THE SAME
THING.
THERE IS NOTHING I CAN HANG MY
HEAD ABOUT.
BECAUSE IN MY HEART, I KNOW THAT
I DID EVERYTHING I POSSIBLY
COULD TO MAKE IT HERE AND TO
PLEAD A TRUE AND HONEST CASE TO
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE ABOUT TO
REWARD SOMEONE WITH A
LIFE-CHANGING PRIZE.
>> TWO DAYS BEFORE I LEFT, LIKE
I MADE VOWS TO MY WIFE THAT I
WAS GOING TO PROTECT HER.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY.
IF I DON'T SEIZE EVERY
OPPORTUNITY WHENEVER I HAVE THE
CHANCE, THEN I'M GOING TO GO
BACK HOME AND THINK, WHAT IF.
>> I THINK MY BIGGEST CHALLENGE
WITH THE JURY IS I DON'T WANT
PEOPLE TO THINK I JUST WENT
ALONG WITH THE VOTES.
I WANT THEM TO KNOW THAT ME
BEING SUCH A STRONG SOCIAL
PLAYER, I HAD DIFFERENT ROUTES
TO GO, AND IT WASN'T ME JUST
JUMPING ON A TRAIN AND RIDING
ALONG WITH IT.
>> IT WAS MATTER OF ME BEING SO
SOCIALLY AWARE THAT I COULD GO
WHICHEVER PATH THAT WAS BEST
GOING TO BENEFIT ME.
IF I WOULD HAVE BEEN SET IN MY
WAYS, I WOULDN'T BE WHERE I AM
TODAY IF I HAD PLAYED ONE GAME.
I HAD TO MOVE AROUND IN ORDER TO
GET IN THIS STAGE OF THE GAME.
TONIGHT IS THE BIGGEST BAT UNTIL
39 DAYS, AND I HAVE TO BRING IT
AND I'M READY.
SOLE SURVIVOR.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SO GAVIN, CHRIS, JULIE,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE LASTED 39 DAYS.
YOU HAVE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN
GO, AND TONIGHT YOU HAVE ONE
FINAL TASK, CONVINCE THE JURY
THAT YOU ARE THE ONE MOST
DESERVING OF THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE MILLION DOLLARS
THAT GOES WITH IT.
WE'LL START WITH THIS OUTWIT
PART OF THE GAME.
EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE,
ALLIANCES, RELATIONSHIPS OUTSIDE
OF THOSE, ETHICS AND MORALS IF
THOSE PLAYED THIS SEASON.
WHO WANTS TO GET US STARTED?
>> YES, MAD RESPECT FOR ALL OF
YOU GUYS.
ALL WE WANT IS TO VOTE FOR THE
BEST PLAYER, AND I THINK IT WILL
HELP TO TAKE REAL OWNERSHIP OF
YOUR GAME.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT RELATIONSHIP
WAS THE MOST VALUABLE IN YOUR
GAME.
WE'LL START WITH YOU.
>> I HAVE TO GO WITH VICTORYA.
ME AND VICTORIA WERE WITH EACH
OTHER FOR 35 DAYS, SOMETHING
ALONG THAT LINE.
WE WORKED TOGETHER ON
EVERYTHING.
SO VICTORIA WAS MY STRONGEST
ALLY IN THIS GAME, 100%.
>> GREAT.
>> CHRIS?
>> THE STRONGEST ALLY THAT I HAD
WAS RICK.
BUT I GOT SENT TO THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
I COULD HAVE BEEN BITTER.
I COULD HAVE BEEN FRUSTRATED AND
UPSET, BUT I MADE MY WAY BACK
IN, AND AGAIN I WENT WITH RICK,
AND I SAID, HEY, WE'RE GOING TO
GET TO FINAL FOUR TOGETHER.
>> AND JULIE, YOUR STRONGEST
RELATIONSHIP IN THE GAME?
>> MY CLOSEST RELATIONSHIPS WERE
WITH RON AND ERIC.
I CONTINUED TO BUILD MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH RON.
MY HEART WAS BROKEN WHEN HE GOT
BLINDSIDED.
I HAD A SECRET RELATIONSHIP WITH
LAUREN THAT KEPT ME IN THE GAME
AND THAT WAS AN EXTREMELY STRONG
BOND THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE DIDN'T
KNOW ABOUT.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> I WANT TO ASK CHRIS ON THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION, THERE WERE
SOME SOCIAL POLITICS VERY MUCH
AT WORK.
CAN YOU TELL ME HOW YOU WERE
BEING STRATEGIC ACTED YOUR
SOCIAL RELATIONSHIPS THERE?
>> YEAH.
WE WERE OUTSIDE OF THE GAME, BUT
WE WERE STILL IN THE GAME.
SO I TRIED THE MAKE REALLY
GENUINE HONEST RELATIONSHIPS
WITH EACH PERSON.
WHEN I COOKED RICE AND COCONUT
IN THE MORNING, WHENEVER I
CAUGHT STINGRAY AND FISH AND
WE'D ALL COME TOGETHER AROUND
THE FIRE, THAT WAS PART OF MY
SOCIAL GAME PLAY THROUGH
PROVIDING.
BECAUSE I WASN'T OUT OF THE GAME
YET.
>> YOU KNOW, WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION,
AND ONLY ONE PERSON IS COMING
BACK FROM THAT.
>> I WANT TO OPEN IT UP FOR YOU
RIGHT NOW.
IN THE 28 DAYS THAT CHRIS WAS
DOING HIS SOCIAL GAME PLAY ON
EDGE OF EXTINCTION, WHAT SOCIAL
RELATIONSHIPS AND STRATEGIES
WERE YOU HAVING TO NAVIGATE?
>> YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH GETTING
SENT HOME.
MY SOCIAL GAME WAS MY STRATEGIC
GAME, BUILDING BONDS AND HAVING
PEOPLE'S TRUST AND GETTING THEM
TO TRUST ME SO THEY COULD COME
TO ME WITH INFORMATION.
THIS WHOLE GAME I HAVE BUILT
SOCIAL RELATIONSHIPS WITH
BASICALLY EVERYONE OVER HERE.
>> GAVIN, MY QUESTION IS ARE YOU
BUILDING THOSE RELATIONSHIPS AS
SOMEONE IN CHARGE OR ARE YOU
BUILDING THOSE AT A GOAT.
>> I'M BUILDING THE
RELATIONSHIPS AS SOMEONE WHO IS
IN CHARGE BECAUSE I'M STILL
HERE.
I'M NOT ANYONE'S GOAT.
I CHOSE THE ROUT I CHOSE.
NO ONE DICTATED THAT FOR ME.
>> CAN WE LET THE JURY ASK THE
QUESTIONS?
THAT WAS RUDE.
>> HEY, JULIE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING PATIENT.
>> NO PROBLEM.
I GET IT.
>> SAME QUESTION.
WHAT WERE YOU DEALING WITH AS
YOU WENT THROUGH THE GAME,
PEOPLE, MANAGING RELATIONSHIPS?
>> I WAS THE NEUROTIC NEW
YORKER.
I CAN'T HIDE THAT.
I DECIDED TO TAKE THAT
"WEAKNESS" AND USE IT AS A
SOCIAL STRATEGY, AS A STRENGTH.
IT'S NOT THAT THE EMOTIONS WERE
FAKE AND I WAS BUILDING THESE
RELATIONSHIPS, IT'S THAT I
WASN'T GOING TO HIDE THEM.
>> CAN I JUST INTERJECT, YOUR
EMOTIONS IN THIS GAME DO PLAY A
ROLE AND YOU HAVE TO FEEL THOSE
EMOTION, BUT DOES THAT AFFECT
HOW YOU NAVIGATE YOUR NEXT MOVE?
>> I CAN'T CONTROL AND TURN THEM
ON AND OFF SO QUICKLY.
BUT WHEN THEY COME OUT, IT WAS
USING THEM AS A SOCIAL STRATEGY
IN MY GAME.
>> JULIE, SO AS SOMEBODY THAT
WAS ON THE RECEIVING OF ONE OF
MANY EMOTIONAL BREAKDOWNS,
YOU'RE SAYING THAT THAT WAS USED
AS A STRENGTH IN YOUR GAME IS
LIKE, COME ON, LIKE...
>> WELL, I THINK WE MAY NOT BE
GIVING YOU ENOUGH CREDIT FOR HOW
CLEVER YOUR GAME MIGHT HAVE
BEEN.
GIVE ME ONE BIG YOU THINK YOU
DID.
>> SO USING MY EMOTIONS AS PART
OF MY STRATEGY, THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL THAT JULIA GOT VOTED
OUT, I FEEL LIKE I SWAYED THAT
VOTE.
>> DID YOU EVER THINK THERE WAS
A POSSIBILITY YOU WOULD HAVE
BEEN VOTED OUT?
NO.
>> .01.
>> LET ME EXPLAIN.
>> I WAS ON ROCK BOTTOM.
RON'S PARANOIA WAS SKY HIGH.
I HAD A VERY SPECIFIC IDEA OF
HOW I WANTED THAT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TO GO.
I HAD ALREADY THROWN OUT JULIA'S
NAME THAT DAY.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE THE VOTE
WOULD HAVE SWITCHED IF I HADN'T
SAID ANYTHING AND WARDOG HADN'T
CALLED ON ME.
>> WHAT I MEANT IS IT WAS A
CATALYST FOR CONVERSATIONS THAT
WERE GOING TO START.
ALL I NEEDED TO DO WAS GET THE
CONVERSATION GOING AND I JUMPED
ON IT FAST.
>> LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT,
YOUR MOST CLEVER MOVE WAS TO
POSSIBLY THROW OUT JULIA'S NAME
AND HOPE A WARDOG WOULD COME
SAVE THE DAY?
>> I DIDN'T CONSIDER THAT YOU
SAVED THE DAY, BUT I KNEW I
WANTED TO TRY SWITCH THINGS UP.
>> AND LET CHRIS AND GAVIN
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
>> I THINK A BIG MOVE I MADE,
EVEN THOUGH I DON'T FEEL GREAT,
WAS PEOPLE LIKE AUBRY AND JOE,
PEOPLE I KNEW WERE RESPECTED
PLAYERS, BUT THAT'S WHERE I HAD
TO SEPARATE MY HEART FROM THE
GAME PLAY.
>> THAT WAS VERY CLEAR.
I FELT LIKE A PIECE OF TAXIDERMY
QUITE FRANKLY THIS SEASON, BUT
TO BE FAIR, DWAFFEN WAS ONE OF
THE ONLY PEOPLE TO COME UP TO ME
AND EVEN PRETEND THAT HE WAS
WILLING TO WORK WITH ME.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT.
>> I WAS WILLING TO WORK WITH
YOU.
>> I WILL SAY THE PERSON I
TRUSTED OF THE THREE OF YOU WAS
GAVIN.
>> SO CHRIS, NOW, THE BIG MOVE?
>> THE ORIGINAL QUESTION IS I
SPENT 28 DAYS ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
AND I JUST WANT TO REMIND YOU
GUYS THAT LIKE JULIE DID NOT GO
TO AA TRIBAL COUNCIL UNTIL DAY
17 AT THE MERGE.
SO BASICALLY WE WERE ON THE SAME
PLAYING FIELD, YOU KNOW.
>> SO WE KNOW YOU ONLY PLAYED 12
DAYS IN THE ACTUAL GAME, BUT
THAT'S AMPLE TIME TO MAKE A BIG
MOVE.
>> SO GETTING BACK INTO THE
GAME, I KNEW THAT I HAD TO GET
THROUGH ONE TRIBAL WITH NO
IMMUNITY AROUND MY NECK, NO
IDOLS AT PLAY, BUT I GOT LAUREN
TO PROMISE ME THAT IF DEVENS'
IDOL WAS REAL THAT SHE WAS GOING
THE PLAY HER IDOL FOR ME.
>> ARE YOU CLAIMING THAT AS YOUR
MOVE?
>> YEAH, I'M CLAIMING THAT WAS A
BIG STRATEGIC MOVE.
BECAUSE WE ALL KNEW LAUREN HAD
AN IDOL.
THANK YOU, KELLEY.
MY GRATITUDE IS TO YOU.
>> VERBAL DIARRHEA.
SORRY.
>> LAUREN, HOW DID HE CONVINCE
YOU TO DO THAT?
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
IT'S REALLY SAD.
>> THE ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
RON, IT'S ACTUALLY A SALES
TECHNIQUE.
IT'S CALLED A NEGATIVE REVERSE.
YOU HAVE TO BE LESS OKAY THAN A
PROSPECT FOR THEM TO FEEL LIKE
THEY NEED THEM TO SAVE YOU.
>> HE PLAYED ME LIKE A VIOLIN.
>> CLEVER.
>> JUST CURIOUS, HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE WILLING TO SAY THAT ARE
STILL UNDECIDED?
WOW.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DAG GREAT JOB.
IT CAN FEEL LIKE THE
INQUISITION.
SO KEEP FIGHTING.
>> DON'T STOP FIGHTING.
>> Jeff: SPEAKS TO THE GAME
YOU ARE ALL PLAYING WHEN YOU
HAVE THE JURY SAYING KEEP
FIGHTING AND EVERYBODY
UNDECIDED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE INTO THE OUTPLAY PART
OF THE GAME.
THIS IS THE CONDITIONS THAT ARE
PUT ON YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BUILD SHELTER.
YOU HAVE TO COMPETE IN
CHALLENGES.
YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH IDOLS AND
ADVANTAGES OR TWISTS AND
SWITCHES.
EDGE OF EXTINCTION WAS A BIG
PART OF THE OUTPLAY THIS SEASON.
SO WHO WANTS TO GET US STARTED?
>> I'LL GET US STARTED.
GUYS, THERE WERE A LOT OF IDOLS
OUT THERE.
I FOUND THEM BECAUSE I GOT OUT
THERE AND I HUSTLED AND WORKED
HARD AND FOUND THEM.
WHY DIDN'T YOU?
>> I WAS LOOKING A LOT.
AND YOU MAY HAVE HEARD MANY
SCREAMS AS I WAS LOOKING EVERY
TIME I CAME ACROSS A BUG OR A
LIZARD OR A CRAB HIDING IN A
TREE HOLM I WAS LOOKING, AND I
WAS LOOKING SO WELL I FOUND YOUR
FAKE ONE.
SO I FOUND AN IDOL.
>> I LOOKED A LITTLE BIT ALSO,
BUT I WAS ON THE SIDE WITH THE
NUMBERS FOR EVERY VOTE BUT ONE,
SO I KNEW IT WASN'T GOING TO BE
THE END OF THE WORLD.
>> CHRIS, DO YOU THINK THAT IT'S
AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE THAT NOT
ONLY DO YOU COME IN WITH JUST
THREE DAYS LEFT IN THE
INDIVIDUAL GAME, BUT YOU HAVE
ALL THIS EXTRA INFORMATION AND
STRATEGY YOU RECEIVED FROM THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
>> ACTUALLY THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION WAS AN UNFAIR
ADVANTAGE TO ME DESPITE EVEN
HAVING INFORMATION, BECAUSE I
HAD TO PLAY THE BIGGEST POSSIBLE
GAME WITH THREE DAYS THAT I
COULD POSSIBLY PLAY.
SO I FLUSHED AN IDOL, PLAYED AN
IDOL CORRECTLY MY SECOND VOTE,
WON IMMUNITY CHALLENGE ON THE
FINAL DAY, AND BIGGEST MOVE OF
THE GAME, BY FAR, GIVE UP MY
NECKLACE TO EARN MY SPOT BACK
INTO THE GAME BY MAKING FIRE
AGAINST THE NUMBER-ONE
COMPETITOR IN THE ENTIRE SEASON.
AND THAT'S THE BEST THAT I COULD
POSSIBLY DO.
THERE WAS NO OTHER SCENARIO.
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, I THINK
IT'S AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE BECAUSE
HE DIDN'T FIND THAT SECOND IDOL.
THAT WAS GIVING TO HIM.
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN VOTED OUT IF
HE HADN'T BEEN GIVEN THAT IDOL.
>> MY QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU
THINK YOU CONVINCED HIM TO GIVE
YOU BACK HALF THE IDOL?
>> BECAUSE IN THIS GAME WE SO
EASILY FORGET ABOUT SOCIAL
CAPITAL.
IT'S 38 SEASONS OF "SURVIVOR,"
AND WE REALLY HAVE FORGOTTEN
THAT YOU CANNOT TREAT PEOPLE
LIKE CHESS PIECES.
THE GAME WE FELL IN LOVE WITH
WAS NOT JUST ABOUT DECEIT AND
BACKSTABBING AND BLINDSIDING.
YOU CANNOT THINK THAT SOMEBODY
IS WHO IS GOING TO BE LOYAL WITH
YOU TO THE END IS SOMEONE YOU
CAN SCREW AROUND.
SO YOU'RE ASKING ME WHY?
IT'S BECAUSE MY RELATIONSHIP
WITH DEVENS WAS REAL.
AND WHEN I TOLD HIM I WANTED HIM
TO GO TO FINAL FOUR, I MEND IT.
>> I RESPECT EVERYTHING YOU'RE
SAYING, BUT IF YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT CLASSIC "SURVIVOR," THEN
IT'S SURVIVING 39 DAY, IT'S NOT
GETTING VOTED OUT ON DAY EIGHT
AND COMING BACK ON DAY 35 AND
HAVING A CHANCE TO WIN THIS
GAME.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN TALK ABOUT
PLAYING CLASSIC "SURVIVOR" AND
YOU HAVING MISSED THE
OPPORTUNITY.
>> BUT THE GAME EVOLVES.
THIS IS A THEME.
IT'S THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
CHRIS PLAYED WITH THE DAYS THAT
HE HAD IN THE GAME AND TO SEE
WHAT HE WAS ABLE TO DO IN THE
LAST FEW DAYS HOPING THAT YOU
WOULD HAVE DONE JUST A
PERCENTAGE OF THAT.
LIKE 39 DARES ISN'T EVERYTHING.
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH THOSE 39
DAYS.
>> I BUILT SOCIAL BONDS TO GET
ME THROUGH THIS GAME, LIKE BEING
OVER.
THERE YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
SOMETHING BACKSTABBING YOU OR
BLINDSSIDING YOU.
I WOULD LOVE TO RECONNECT WITH
ERIC AND AUBRY AND ALL THESE
PEOPLE I DONE THESE WRONGS TO,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M AT A
DISADVANTAGE.
>> AND THERE IS A LOT OF STRESS
AND MENTAL FATIGUE THAT TAKES
PLACE IN THE GAME THAT YOU LET
GO OF WHEN YOU'RE ON THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION.
SO THERE'S A BALANCE THERE.
>> LOOK, THE JURY IS NOT ON
TRIAL.
YOU THREE ARE ON TRIAL.
I'M HEARING SOME REALLY GOOD
ANSWERS, BUT SOMETIMES THIS GAME
IS ABOUT SOME PLAYER MAKING A
PLAY BETTER THAN YOU.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S IT.
>> WELL, I THINK THERE IS
ANOTHER SIDE TO THAT.
COULD EVERYONE HERE THAT DIDN'T
GET THEIR NAME WRITTEN DOWN
RAISE THEIR HAND, EVERYBODY,
JURY INCLUDED, WHO NEVER HAD
THEIR NAME WRITTEN DOWN?
PRETTY GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL NOW MOVE INTO THE OUTLAST
PART OF THE GAME.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO SUM UP
YOUR JOURNEY.
WHAT DID IT TAKE FOR YOU TO GET
FROM DAY ONE TO DAY 39?
HOW DOES IT DIFFER FROM THE
OTHER TWO?
GAVIN, GET US STARTED.
>> TODAY CHRIS ASKED ME WHAT MY
DREAM WAS.
I SAID, WELL, IT WAS THE PLAY
"SURVIVOR," BUT ONCE I GOT OUT
HEAR HERE.
I REALIZE MY DREAM IS EVERYTHING
I HAVE BACK HOME.
MY DREAM IS TO BE THE SON TO THE
BEST PARENTS I HAVE.
TO BE A BROTHER.
TO BE THE BEST DAMN HUSBAND THAT
I CAN BE FOR THE GIRL WHO MOVED
EVERYTHING IN HER LIFE FOR ME TO
HAVE THIS OPPORTUNITY.
SO I PLAYED WITH MY HEART, BUT I
WASN'T PLAYING WITH MY HEART FOR
YOU GUYS.
I WAS PLAYING WITH MY HEART FOR
HER, LIKE EVERY DECISION I MADE,
IT WAS IN ORDER FOR ME TO MOVE
ONE DAY CLOSER TO WINNING THIS
GAME SO I COULD PROTECT HER, TO
HONOR HER, AND TO PROVIDE FOR
HER.
SO THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Jeff: CHRIS?
WELL, A LOT OF YOU GUYS KNOW MY
JOURNEY BECAUSE I WAS REAL WITH
YOU ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION,
BUT I CAME INTO THIS GAME, AND I
WANTED TO CONTROL.
I WANTED TO PLAY THIS PERFECT
GAME.
AND I GOT BLINDSIDED.
AND EDGE OF EXTINCTION TAUGHT ME
I HAD TO COME TO TERMS WITH
LETTING GO OF CONTROL.
AND THAT BALL DROPPED.
I MADE MY WAY BACK INTO THE
GAME.
AND I KNEW THE ODDS WERE STACKED
SO FAR AGAINST ME THAT I HAD
LITERALLY HAD TO DO THE BEST
POSSIBLE MOVE EVERY SINGLE TIME.
SO I'M SITTING HERE AS THE FIRST
PLAYER TO GIVE UP HIS FINAL FOUR
IMMUNITY NECKLACE TO FORCE FIRE
WITH THE NUMBER-ONE COMPETITOR
OF THE SEASON AND ONE, AND THE
FIRST PLAYER TO BE PART OF THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION WITH FAMILY
THAT WAS OUTSIDE OF THE TRIBE.
AND THAT WAS A $1 MILLION
EXPERIENCE WHETHER I WON $1
MILLION OR NOT.
I'M HAPPY WITH WHATEVER YOU
DECIDE.
I RESPECT YOUR DECISION.
>> Jeff: JULIE?
>> I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
WHETHER IT'S SITTING OVER HERE
OR OVER THERE, WE HAVE ALL HAD
AN INCREDIBLE PERSONAL JOURNEY
PLAYING THIS GAME.
MINE HAS BEEN LIFE CHANGING,
LIKE LITERALLY LIFE CHANGING.
WHEN I GOT OUT HERE ON DAY ONE,
ALL I HAD IN MY MIND WAS GETTING
TO DAY 39 AND ACTUALLY WINNING
THIS GAME, AND I NEVER LOST
SIGHT OF THAT.
AND I MAY NOT BE THE TYPE OF
PLAYER THAT MOST OF YOU ARE.
I AM NOT AN AGGRESSIVE PLAYER.
I AM NOT SOMEBODY WHO LIKES
CONFRONTATION, BUT WHY DOES THAT
MEAN THAT THAT PLAYER IS ANY
LESS WORTHY OF WINNING THIS GAME
AND ONE OF THE REASONS THAT I
SAID I WANTED TO COME OUT HERE
WAS TO PROVE TO MYSELF THAT I
WAS STRONG AND THEY WAS VALUABLE
BECAUSE I HAVE FELT
UNDERESTIMATED A LOT OF MY LIFE,
AND COMING OUT HERE, YOU GET
THIS CLARITY THAT YOU CAN'T
BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T SEE AT HOME.
IT WAS PLAYING THIS GAME THAT
HAS MADE ME SEE, I'M ALREADY WHO
I AM I CAME TO PROVE TO BE.
AND I'M SO THANKFUL THAT YOU
WERE RESPECTFUL TO ALL THREE OF
US, BECAUSE YOU ALL WERE A PART
OF WHAT MADE IT LIFE CHANGING
FOR ME.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO DO.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A MOMENT THE TAKE
IN EVERYTHING YOU HEARD TONIGHT,
AND THEN WE WILL VOTE.
YOU THREE ARE ON TRIAL!
WARDOG THROWING IT DOWN.
THE VOTE FOR A WINNER IS NEXT.
EDGE OF EXTINCTION FINALE!
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO BRING THIS 39-DAY
ADVENTURE TO A CONCLUSION.
TONIGHT YOU ARE VOTING FOR A
WINNER.
REEM, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO GET THE VOTES.
GAVIN, CHRIS, JULIE, THANK YOU
FOR ANOTHER GREAT SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR."
LY SEE YOU IN LOS ANGELES FOR
THE READING OF THE VOTES.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
HAVE A SEAT.
LET'S GET TO IT.
THIS HAS BEEN SUCH A FUN SEASON.
I'M NOT GOING TO WASTE A LOT OF
TIME.
I JUST WILL SAY IT ONCE.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING PART IN
SOMETHING REALLY EXPERIMENTAL
AND LETTING US WATCH THE STORY
AND "YOU ARE MY FRIEND" -- AND
WATCH YOU GO UP AND DOWN THAT
ROLLER COASTER.
YOU HAVE BEEN WAITING A LONG
TIME FOR.
THIS GAVIN, CHRIS, JULIE, LET'S
WAIT NO MORE.
WE'LL READ THE VOTES.
HERE WE GO.
FIRST VOTE, GAVIN.
CHRIS.
WE'RE TIED.
ONE VOTE GAVIN.
ONE VOTE CHRIS.
TWO VOTES GAVIN.
CHRIS.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
TWO VOTES GAVIN, TWO VOTES
CHRIS.
GAVIN.
THAT'S THREE VOTES GAVIN.
TWO VOTES CHRIS.
WE ARE TIED AGAIN.
THREE VOTES GAVIN, THREE VOTES
CHRIS.
GAVIN.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES GAVIN.
THREE VOTES CHRIS.
CHRIS.
TIED AGAIN.
FOUR VOTES GAVIN, FOUR VOTES
CHRIS.
FIVE VOTES CHRIS.
FOUR VOTES GAVIN.
CHRIS.
THAT'S SIX VOTES CHRIS.
FOUR VOTES GAVIN.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR: EDGE OF
EXTINCTION," CHRIS.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
THERE IT IS.
THE WINNER OF OUR 38th
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
CHRIS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT HOW THE
JURY VOTED.
THROW THOSE VOTES UP THERE.
THERE IT IS.
YOU CAN SEE WHO VOTED FOR WHO.
EVERYBODY VOTED FOR CHRIS EXCEPT
FOR WENTWORTH AND LAUREN AND
AURORA AND EVEN DEVENS VOTED FOR
GAVIN.
WE HAVE A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
THE LIVE REUNION SHOW IS NEXT.