>> TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS REALLY
HARD, AND I FELL VERY ALONE.
THERE WAS A MOMENT THERE WHERE I
DIDN'T KNOW IF I WANTED TO STAY
IN THE GAME.
BUT FOR ME QUITTING IS NOT AN
OPTION BECAUSE I DON'T WANT MY
DAUGHTERS AND GRANDDAUGHTERS TO
SEE THAT.
AND MY HUSBAND.
AND MY BEACH FAMILY.
I DON'T QUIT.
I DON'T QUIT ANYTHING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO FROM
HERE.
>> YOU CAN'T REGRET WHAT YOU
DID.
>> I DON'T REGRET WHAT I DID,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
I'M A FREE AGENT.
I PLAYED MY IDOL BECAUSE IT WAS
A CRAZY TRIBAL DIRECTED AT ME.
I WISH I STILL HAD IT, BECAUSE
I'M ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK.
THEY WANT ME GONE.
>> TAKE IT DAY BY DAY.
>> YEAH.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR ANOTHER DAY.
>> OH.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
A RAT JUST JUMPED ON MY FACE.
IT JUST JUMPED ON MY FACE.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> WELL, HE'S GONE NOW.
>> IT WAS LIKE IN MY MOUTH.
>> I'M SORRY, KARISHMA.
KARISHMA, IT'S OKAY.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> THAT WAS ONE OF THE WORST
RAINS WE'VE HAD.
I HAVE DRY SOCKS YOU CAN PUT ON
YOUR FEET OR SOMETHING.
>> JUST HOLD MY HANDS.
YOU'RE FREEZING.
LAST NIGHT WAS PROBABLY THE
WORST NIGHT OF MY LIFE.
I WAS POURED ON, FREEZING, WITH
NO ONE TO KEEP ME WARM EXCEPT
FOR MISSY, AND I'M LIKE, I'M
OVER THIS, THIS SUCKS.
BUT THAT'S THE GAME.
THAT'S LITERALLY WHAT I SIGNED
UP FOR.
I HAVEN'T COME THIS FAR TO ONLY
COME THIS FAR.
AND LET A RAINY NIGHT COMPLETELY
BREAK ME.
>> KARISHMA WAS NOT THE MOST...
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
>> SHE'S LIKE, UH...
>> HOLD MY HAND.
>> SHE GETS MAD BECAUSE I ASK
FOR A BLANKET?
KARISHMA IS LUCKY TO BE HERE.
SHE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING AROUND
CAMP.
SHE LAYS IN THE BLANKET.
SHE'S ALWAYS THE FIRST TO GO TO
BED AND THE LAST THE WAKE UP.
>> DOES EVERYONE AGREE WITH ME?
SHE DOES NOT OPEN A COCONUT.
SHE DOES NOT GO GET WATER.
YOU THINK SHE'S AN 85-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN THAT HAS A SENSE OF
ENTITLEMENT.
I DON'T NEED TO KILL MYSELF.
I'M PART OF THE ELDERLY GROUP,
LUKE YOU GUYS CAN JUST TAKE CARE
OF ME.
SHE'S CRAZY.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
WE'RE STILL HERE.
DO YOU WANT TO BE HERE?
SHOW US.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU SHOULD LIKE
HELP OUT.
>> KARISHMA, WOULD YOU OPEN A
COCONUT?
WOULD YOU MIND?
THERE'S A BUNCH ON THE TRAIL.
KARISHMA OBVIOUSLY HAS MORE
RESILIENCE THAN WE THINK BECAUSE
SHE'S STILL HERE, BUT SHE'S
SHOWN ME THAT SHE'S
INCONSISTENT, UNWORKABLE,
UNGRATEFUL, AND I HAVE NO
INTEREST IN WORKING WITH SOMEONE
LIKE THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I THINK IT'S INCREDIBLY
OBVIOUS THAT I'M IN TROUBLE.
AND I CAN ONLY BLAME MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I FIRST GOT OUT
HERE, WHEN I FIRST CAME HERE, I
THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE LIKE
JUNGLE QUEEN.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE ABLE
TO MAKE FRIENDS SO EASILY, GET
ALONG WITH EVERYBODY, BUT WHEN
I'M STRUGGLING, LIKE I AM RIGHT
NOW, I THINK OF MY FAMILY, AND
SO SOMEONE LIKE MY HUSBAND, WHO
CHOOSES TO BE WITH ME AND LOVE
ME AND ME ONLY FOR THE REST OF
HIS LIFE, I MEAN, HOW COULD I
NOT SEE CLEARER THAN EVER HOW
WONDERFUL THAT KIND OF A
RELATIONSHIP IS WHEN I CAN'T
EVEN GET SOMEBODY TO TRUST ME
AND CARE FOR ME FOR EVEN ONE
VOLT OUT HERE.
I'M BEING VIEWED AS A GOAT.
ONE OF THE QUALITIES OF A GOAT
IS PREDICTABILITY.
BUT I'M IN THE A VERY GOOD ONE,
BECAUSE I E-MAIL NOT VERY
PREDICTABLE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK WHAT I DID?
I FOUND AN IDOL.
I FOUND MY LIFELINE IN THIS
GAME.
I WAS BARELY HANGING ON BY A
THAT RED.
AND THEN TO FIND THIS, IT GIVES
ME SOMETHING TO LEAN ON TO
FINALLY GET UP OFF THE GROUND
WHERE I'VE BEEN LAYING THIS
WHOLE TIME AND FINALLY DO
SOMETHING WITH IT.
THIS GIVES MAE CHANCE TO MAKE A
NAME FOR MYSELF IN THIS GAME.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME.
>> SO WE GET OUT KARISHMA.
>> GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
>> AFTER KARISHMA YOU THINK
JANET?
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> MY PUSH IS JANET IS HARD
WORKER AND IF YOU DID WANT THE
KEEP HER, THAT WOULD BE GOOD,
BUT IF NOT, I WOULD UNDERSTAND.
KARISHMA, ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOREVER, AND
YOU GOT TWO COCONUTS.
YOU WERE KWON FOR AN -- YOU WERE
GONE FOR AN HOUR.
>> I WENT AROUND IN CIRCLES.
I REALIZE, I'VE BEEN GONE FOR A
REALLY LONG TIME.
CAN I DRINK SOMEONE'S WATER?
>> YEAH.
>> SO I PLAY UP THE FEELING SICK
THING, BECAUSE THAT'S MY FIRST
INSTINCT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
>> I NEED TO CALL THE DOCTOR.
I'M SERIOUS.
CAN I HAVE AN HOUR?
>> NO.
YOU'RE GETTING WORSE.
>> THIS IS NOT YOUR DECISION
ANYMORE.
>> GUY, IT'S MY BODY, IT IS MY
DECISION.
>> IF YOU GUYS ARE TRYING TO GET
ME LIKE THROWN OUT OF THE GAME
OR SOMETHING --
>> NOBODY WANTS YOU TO GET
MEDIVACKED OUT OF THE GAME.
>> I FEEL BETTER AFTER DRINKING
SOME WATER.
>> JUST NOW, JUST LIKE THAT?
>> I DON'T NEED THIS WHOLE
DETOUR OF THE DOCTOR BEING
CALLED ON ME.
I'M THINKING, OH, MY GOD, I
DON'T NEED THIS DRAMA, I NEED TO
GET BACK, SIT DOWN, AND THINK
ABOUT HOW I'M GOING THE PLAY MY
IDOL.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, GOT THE TAKE
BACK THE NECKLACES.
AARON AND MISSY.
THANK YOU.
ONE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO STAND ON A NARROW BEAM
WHILE SPINNING A BALL INSIDE A
CIRCULAR WOODEN TRACK.
AT REGULAR INTERVALS YOU'LL MOVE
FURTHER DOWN THE BEAM, MAKING IT
MORE DIFFICULT.
IF AIN THE POINT YOU FALL OFF
THE BEAM OR YOUR BALL DROPS,
YOU'RE OUT.
TO MAKE IT A LITTLE MORE
INTERESTING.
>> UH-OH.
>> Jeff: TODAY WE'RE GOING TO
DIVIDE YOU INTO TWO GROUPS.
ONE PERSON FROM EACH GROUP WILL
WIN IMMUNITY.
BOTH GRIEWBS WILL GO TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL SEPARATELY.
BOTH GROUPS WILL VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT.
SO TWO WINNERS, TWO PEOPLE GOING
HOME.
WE'LL DRAW TO SEE WHICH GROUP
YOU'RE ON AND WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> OKAY, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE OUR TWO GROUPS COMPETING
AGAINST EACH OTHER IN ORANGE,
IT'S MISSY, TOMMY, ELAINE,
ELIZABETH, AND KARISHMA.
AND IN PURPLE IT'S DEAN, DAN,
LAURAN, AARON, NOURA, AND
JANICE.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
TWO PEOPLE GOING TO WIN
IMMUNITY.
TWO PEOPLE GOING HOME.
EVERYBODY START SPINNING.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO GET
STARTED.
THEN I'LL CALL THIS CHALLENGE TO
BEGIN.
GIVE EVERYBODY A SHOT TO GET
THEIR MOMENTUM AND GET THAT BALL
SPINNING, AND THEN THE CHALLENGE
WILL BE ALIVE FROM THAT POINT
FORWARD.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
WE'RE JUST WAITING ON DAN.
YOU HAVE 15 SECOND, DAN TO, GET
IT GOING.
DAN'S GOOD.
EVERYBODY IS GOOD, AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL THE
PRESSURE.
HOW LONG CAN YOU GO?
THIS IS A WEIRD CHALLENGE TO DO.
SOME PEOPLE JUST NATURALLY GET
IT.
OTHERS WILL ALWAYS STRUGGLE.
KARISHMA FIRST TO DROP.
SHE'S OUT.
NO SHOT AT IMMUNITY.
MAKE IT A LITTLE MORE
INTERESTING.
THE LAST PERSON STANDING NOT
ONLY WINS IMMUNITY BUT WINS FOR
THEIR GROUP PB&J WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
AN YOU WILL GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
LAST, SO YOU WILL HAVE THE
KNOWLEDGE OF THE INFORMATION OF
THE FIRST VOTE.
YOU ARE PLAYING FOR A LOT RIGHT
NOW ON DAY 27 IN "SURVIVOR."
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE NOW GOING TO PUT THE FIRST
FOOT ON THE BALANCE BEAM.
START MOVING IT IN.
YOU HAVE THE CLEAR THE PAINT.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
GOOD.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT THE LOOK
DOWN.
ELIZABETH DROPS.
SHE'S OUT.
YOU'RE GOOD, ELAINE.
DEAN'S GOOD.
DAN IS GOOD.
EVERYBODY IS GOOD.
TOMMY DROPS.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO LEFT IN
ORANGE.
AARON DROPS.
HE'S OUT.
ORANGE IS NOW DOWN TO MISSY AND
ELAINE.
DAN DROPS.
HE'S OUT.
CAN'T PEEVE IT.
LAURAN DROPS.
WE'RE DOWN THE THREE ON PURPLE.
SHE'S NOT HAPPY.
IT IS DEAN, NOURA AND JANET
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
MISSY AND ELAINE FIGHTING FOR
IMMUNITY.
LOTS OF DIFFERENT SPEEDS AND
ROTATION.
SOME PEOPLE WHIPPING IT.
OTHERS GOING VERY SLOW.
IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER, AS
LONG AS THAT BALL JUST KEEPS
MOVING INSIDE THAT TRACK.
ALL RIGHT.
I WANT EVERYBODY TO GET READY TO
MOVE TO THAT NEXT SECTION.
JANET DROPS.
SHE'S OUT AND WE'RE DOWN TO
SHOWDOWN ON BOTH COLORS BETWEEN
MISSY AND ELAINE AND DEAN AND
NOURA.
EVERYBODY START TO MAKE YOU MOVE
INTO THAT SECOND SECTION OF THE
BEAM.
DEAN DROPS.
HE'S OUT.
NOURA WINS IMMUNITY FOR PURPLE.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> Jeff: AND NOURA DROPS
BEFORE GIVING UP HER SHOT AT
WINNING ANYTHING FOR PURPLE.
>> STUPID.
>> Jeff: NOURA JUST BLEW A
GIANT OPPORTUNITY, WHICH MEANS
PBSO AND J IS GOING TO ORANGE.
>> WE COULD HAVE WON PB&J.
NOURA MIGHT HAVE LASTED LONGER.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE STAYED,
NOURA.
>> Jeff: IT IS NOW A SHOWDOWN.
MISSY, NICE SAVE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT TO DO WITH
ANOTHER NICE SAVE.
STAY IN IT.
IT IS MISSY AND ELAINE.
LAST ONE STANDING WINS IMMUNITY.
MISSY DROPS.
ELAINE WYNNS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
FOR ORANGE.
NOURA WINS FOR PURPLE.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> Jeff: NOURA, COME ON OVER.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
YOU CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THE
GAME TONIGHT.
>> CAN I HUG YOU?
>> Jeff: OF COURSE.
CONGRATS.
ELAINE, ARE YOU IN SHOCK?
>> A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
>> Jeff: COME ON OVER, ELAINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, ELAINE!
>> Jeff: COME ON, I LOVE THE
LOVE.
>> IT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
>>.
>> Jeff: CONGRATS.
>> I'M SO PSYCHED.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE BEST
MOMENTS OF MY LIFE.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHAT IS IT ABOUT A
MOMENT LIKE THIS?
BECAUSE THIS PROVES SOMETHING TO
YOU?
WHAT IS IT?
>> WELL, I'M WITH A BUNCH OF
ATHLETES WHO BEAST MODE THROUGH
EVERYTHING, AND YOU HELP TO GET
LITTLE REDNECK GAME OVER HERE,
AND I'M GOOD AT REDNECK THINGS,
SO I ROCKED IT.
>> Jeff: WORKED OUT.
YOU'RE SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME.
>> GOOD JOB, ELAINE.
>> YEAH, GIRL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, ELIZABETH,
TOMMY, ELAINE, MISSY, KARISHMA,
BACK AT CAMP, PB&J WAIT, AND
MAYBE MORE IMPORTANTLY, YOU WILL
GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL SECOND, SO
YOU WILL KNOW THE RESULTS OF
FIRST TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB, YOU GUYS.
ENJOY.
>> GOOD JOB, NOURA.
>> Jeff: NOURA, DAN, JANET,
DEAN, YOU WILL BE GOING TO THE
OLD LAIRO CAMP WHERE YOU WILL
HAVE BASIC SUPPLIES AUBRY YOU
WILL BE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
FIRST.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD OUT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
WHEN I HEARD THERE WOULD BE TWO
GROUPS GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL,
I GOT A LITTLE SCARED, BECAUSE
BEFORE THIS SPLIT, KARISHMA WAS
PROBABLY GOING TO BE THE VOTE
TONIGHT, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, I
ABSOLUTELY COULD BE GOING HOME.
IT'S NERVE-RACKING.
BUT I WILL KEEP FIGHTING.
>> WOW.
>> HOLY MOLEY.
THIS IS SO DIFFERENT.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> NOURA, GOOD WORK.
>> SO WE COME BACK TO OUR OLD
LAIRO CAMP.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
IT BRINGS BACK BAD MEMORIES.
THIS IS THE LOWEST OF THE LOW.
I WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE, GO TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL AND GET BACK TO
VOKAI BEACH.
>> LET'S SEE THIS CAMP.
>> THE LAST TWO TRIBAL COUNCILS
I'VE HAD THE NECKLACE.
THIS TRIBE SWITCH FOR ME IS
UNSETTLING, BUT THE FACT THAT
KARISHMA IS ON ONE TRIBE AND
JANET ON THIS TRIBE, THIS COULD
BE A PERFECT STORM HAPPENING,
AND GUESS WHAT?
WE GET TWO FOR THE PRICE OF ONE.
>>
>> I'M GUESSING HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> JANET, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
JANET FOUND AN IDOL.
SHE'S DANGEROUS.
>> JANET HAS BEEN ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK FOR A WHILE, BUT
AARON IS SUCH A PHYSICAL AND
SOCIAL THREAT, AND HE DIDN'T WIN
THE NECKLACE TODAY, SO HE'S LIKE
A DEER IN THE WOODS THAT'S JUST
UNATTENDED, ALONE, NO PEOPLE BY
HIS SIDE, WE HAVE A CLEAR SHOT.
LIKE WHY WOULD WE NOT TAKE IT?
>> I GO, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
AND HE GOES, JANET, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> THE BIGGEST THREAT IS AARON.
>> YES.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
YOU ACT LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO
BE --
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN EVERYBODY
WANTS TO GET RID OF AARON.
I WAS LIKE, W OO O HOO.
>> I BELIEVE YOU.
>> IT WOULD BE UNBELIEVABLE THAT
I COULD STILL BE HERE AFTER WHAT
I'VE GONE THROUGH.
THIS COULD BE UNFREAKIN'
BELIEVABLE.
>> WE'RE BACK THE PLAYING THE
GAME.
>> AND IT WOULD BE AWESOME IF
YOU AND I COULD PUT SOME CLOSURE
TO THE WORLD.
>> I THINK WE ALREADY HAVE.
NOW LET'S PLAY THE GAME, BECAUSE
RIGHT NOW I WOULD SAY IT'S 90%,
BUT I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE SOMEONE I
WANT TO VOTE WITH AND TRUST
WITH.
I HOPE IF ANYONE BRINGS MY NAME
TO YOU, YOU'LL TELL ME.
>> DEAL.
>> OKAY.
>> I SWEAR TO YOU ON MY FAMILY.
>> TWO DAYS AGO EVERYONE ACROSS
THE BOARD WANTED JANET GONE.
NOW WE COME HERE, JANET'S SAFE.
BUT IF AARON HEADS HOME, THEN
WHO ELSE DO PEOPLE SEE AS A
PHYSICAL THREAT?
ME.
SO AT LEAST FOR ME IN THE SHORT
TERM, AARON IS WAY BETTER FOR ME
IN THIS GAME THAN JANET.
>> I WANT TO RUN THROUGH SOME
THOUGHTS.
AARON, KARISHMA, LAURAN, JANET,
AND NOURA START THE TAKE OVER,
AND THEY'RE GOING TO COME FOR
THE PHYSICAL THREATS.
I THINK PEOPLE ON THE JURY WOULD
RESPECT JANET'S POSITION.
>> JANET WILL WIN THIS GAME.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> DEAN FEELS THAT WE SHOULD
VOTE OUT JANET, BECAUSE JANET IS
ONE OF THE BIGGEST THREATS IN
THIS GAME.
SHE MADE FIRE.
SHE IS EVERYONE'S MAMA.
SHE HAS A GREAT STORY, BUT JANET
HAS COME BACK TO ME, AN WE CAN
LEGITIMATELY WORK TOGETHER IN
THE FUTURE AND BE FRIENDS.
>> WE HAD UNANIMOUS JANET.
AND NOW SHE'S WORKING HER WAY
BACK IN.
>> RIGHT.
WE COULD EASILY FLIP THE VOTE
BACK THE JANET, BUT FOR MY GAME
I'M 50/50 ON WHETHER AARON OR
JANET IS BETTER.
IT'S COMPLICATED BECAUSE BEFORE
THESE TWO TRIBES HAVE SPLIT UP,
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE KARISHMA
OR JANET, BUT NOW WHO KNOWS,
RIGHT?
I WISH I COULD SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENING ON THE OTHER SIDE.
>> I'M ASSUMING KARISHMA
CONTINUES TO REMAIN THE EASY
VOTE WHEN THEY GO TO THEIR
TRIBAL.
BUT LIKE CAN IT BE THIS EASY?
>> GUYS, WELL DONE.
>> ELAINE, YOU GOT THE KISS JEFF
TODAY.
>> ELOVED IT.
>> KISS ON THE CHEEK.
KISS ON THE DIMPLE.
>> OUR TRIBAL TONIGHT IS GOING
TO BE SUPER SIMPLE.
KARISHMA GOES.
THAT WAS THE OVERALL PLAN
ANYWAY, RIGHT?
WRONG.
COMPLETELY WRONG.
I WAS SUPER HAPPY THAT THE OTHER
GROUP WAS NOT BACK IN TRIBE WITH
US.
I NEED FREEDOM OF THE CAMP.
I NEED MY TIME WITH MY GIRLS SO
I CAN DICTATE THE VOTE.
WHAT'S BEST FOR OUR GAME IS
MISSY'S GAME AND MISSY WANTS TO
WIN THE GAME.
>> HERE'S WHAT WE DO.
WE NEED TO SEPARATE TOMMY FROM
LAUREN.
IF HE GOES HOME.
SHE'S DEPENDENT ON US.
I HAVE BEEN WANTING TO
USE KARISHMA IN A WAY TO ELEVATE
MY GAME.
HAVING TOMMY GONE OPENS UP
LAUREN.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE A GUY THAT
CAN OPEN UP THE GAME.
HE'S PERSONABLE.
EVERYBODY LOVES TOMY.
NO ONE IS GOING TO AWARD
KARISHMA $1 MILLION.
>> HERE'S THE PLAN.
WE SEND TOMMY HOME.
KEEP THE GIRLS STRONG.
HAVE A ONE-ON-ONE CONVERSATION
WITH EVERY PERSON.
>> GOT IT.
>> NO, DON'T GIVE ANYBODY NAME,
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HERE, YOU
ALREADY KNOW, WANTS TO PUT THEIR
VOTES ON YOU.
THAT'S THE GAME PLAN.
BUT LISTEN.
LISTEN.
EVERYBODY IS GOING TO PUT THEIR
VOTES ON YOU.
LISTEN, WHEN WE GET THE
TRIBAL --
>> I KNOW, BUT I WANT TO TALK TO
EVERYBODY.
>> LOOK, I'M ON AT THE BOTTOM.
MISSY, I GET WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT I NEED TO TALK TO EVERYBODY.
>> COME HERE.
GIVE ME TWO MINUTES.
>> MISSY WAS TALKING AT ME, NOT
TALKING WITH ME.
SHE'S A BULLY TO ME.
I'M NOT TAKING THAT ANYMORE, NOT
FROM A 24-YEAR-OLD GIRL WHO
THINKS SHE'S ON TOP OF THE
WORLD.
>> KARISHMA, YOU WANT TO TALK?
THE ANSWER IS NO.
I WANT TO TALK.
>> I'D RATHER WAIT UNTIL YOUR
EMOTIONS ARE CALMER.
>> I'M SUPER CALM, KARISHMA.
>> JUST WAIT.
>> HOW LONG WOULD YOU LIKE THE
WAIT?
>> I DON'T HAVE A WATCH.
I'LL WAIT UNTIL I FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY, LITTLE GIRL.
I'M GOING TO NEED YOU TO CALM
DOWN.
I'M TOO OLD FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GLAD THE HEAR THAT TOMMY'S
NAME IS COMING UP AND NOT MINE,
OF COURSE, BUT I'LL TALK TO YOU
WHEN I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
I HAVE 13 YEARS ON YOU, MISSY.
I AM NOT YOUR PUPPY THAT YOU CAN
GO THROW A BONE AND HAVE ME
FETCH IT FOR YOU.
>> YOU KNOW HOW MISSY IS.
SHE'S VERY OVERBEARING.
I DON'T REALLY LIKE THAT.
>> SHE WAS GOING A MILE A MINUTE
AT ME.
SHE TRIED TO TELL ME HOW TO GET
TOMMY OUT.
>> REALLY?
HOLY COW, MISSY WANTS TOMMY OUT.
THAT DOESN'T WORK FOR ME.
AND AT THE SAME TIME, I DON'T
LIKE HOW PEOPLE TALK TO
KARISHMA.
SHE JUST NEEDS WORDS OF
ENCOURAGE.
AND POSITIVE REINFORCEMENT.
KARISHMA HAS POWER TONIGHT, MORE
POWER THAN SHE MAY REALIZE.
>> OKAY, SO BASICALLY I SEE
MISSY, ELIZABETH, ME, I'M ON THE
BOTTOM OF THAT ALLIANCE.
WHAT I'M TELLING YOU IS THAT I'M
VOTING FOR MISSY TONIGHT.
>> IF I'M GOING OUT TONIGHT, I'M
GOING OUT SWINGING AT MY BULLY.
>> MISSY IS GOING WAY TOO HARD.
THEY CAME AT KARISHMA HOT.
I'M COMING WITH COMPASSION AND
UNDERSTANDING.
SO I NEED TO STRIKE WHILE THE
IRON IS HOT.
YOU CAN'T HESITATE IN THIS GAME.
YOU HAVE TO SEIZE EVERY MOMENT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO.
WITH THIS BABY AROUND MY NECK.
THIS HELPS A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> YOU CAN TRUST ME.
SHE SAID MISSY HAD THIS WHOLE
PLAN ABOUT HOW TO GET YOU OUT.
>> TONIGHT?
>> LISTEN, I AM NOT VOTING YOU.
>> PROMISE?
>> I SWEAR.
I AM VOTING FOR MISSY AND CAR IS
VOTING MISSY.
ELIZABETH ISN'T, THOUGH.
SO THE PROBLEM IS, WE'RE HINGING
ALL OF THIS ON KARISHMA, AND
SHE'S BEEN SO WISHY WASHI.
>> MISSY HAS BROUGHT UP MY NAME
TO KNOCK ME OUT, SO OF COURSE
WHEN YOU BRING UP MY NAME, I'M
COMING AFTER YOU.
SO KARISHMA WENT FROM THE MOST
UNPOPULAR KID IN CLASS TO NOW
THE MOST POPULAR KID IN CLASS
WHERE EVERYONE WANTS HER VOTE.
>> IS IT OKAY IF YOU TALK TO ME?
MISSY HASN'T BEEN NICE TO
KARISHMA.
I VIEW HER AS A PERSON AND NOT
AS A GOAT.
I DIDN'T HAVE THE EASIEST
CHILDHOOD BEING BULLIED, SO
KARISHMA, I HOPE SHE REALIZES
THAT I ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT HER
AND WANT TO WORK WITH HER.
BESIDES, MISSY NEVER WANTED TO
MY WITH YOU BEFORE THIS VOTE.
>> I REALIZE HOW I COME OFF A
LOT, AND I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I MESSED UP.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO LIKE WALK
AWAY LIKE I DID.
>> I GOT SUPER EXCITED, BECAUSE
I SAW THE PLAN AND I SAW THE WAY
WHERE YOU STAY SOMEHOW AND TOMMY
NOW LEAVES.
>> KARISHMA, LISTEN, I AM SO
SORRY.
LY HUG YOU, LET'S CRY TOGETHER,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
WE NEED HIM THE LEAVE.
IF WE CAN GET HIM OUT TONIGHT,
THE GIRLS HAVE THE MAJORITY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WE HAVE A HUGE MAJORITY.
>> EXACTLY.
BUT WE GET TO TRIBAL, WE'RE
GOING TO DO WHAT WE WANT TO DO.
THIS IS WHY, KARISHMA, HAS TO GO
HOME.
THESE ARE THE THINGS.
I DON'T LIKE HER, I DON'T KNOW
HER.
>> WHO ARE WE TRYING TO
CONVINCE?
>> WE'RE JUST TALKING.
>> I WENT FROM BEING DOWN IN THE
DUMPS TO NOW I'M THE ONE WHO IS
GOING TO BE MAKING THE DECISION
TONIGHT WHO GOES HOME.
MISSY WAS AT THE TOP OF MY KILL
LIST BECAUSE WE'RE CONSTANTLY
FIGHTING WITH EACH OTHER, BUT
TONIGHT'S DECISION HAS TO BE
ENTIRELY LOGICAL.
IT CANNOT BE EMOTIONAL.
AS A TRIAL LAWYER, YOU HAVE TO
BE CAREFUL WITH YOUR EMOTIONS,
AND WEIGH THE RISKINGS.
SOILY WORK WITH MISSY IF IT'S
THE BEST THING FOR MY GAME.
>> EVERYONE WANTS HIM GONE.
WE HAVE A CHANCE.
>> I HEAR YOU.
FOR THE FIRST TIME I HAVE A SHOT
AT TOMMY BECAUSE HIS CLOSEST
ALLIES ARE OVER AT THE OTHER
TRIBE.
HE'S A SITTING DUCK.
IT'S PERFECT.
BUT WITH MISSY, IT SOUNDS A
LITTLE TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
FOR ALL I KNOW, SHE'S PLAYING
ME.
IT'S A LITTLE FISHY.
IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD, THERE'S
STILL A CHANCE IT COULD BE ME.
THANKFULLY, I HAVE AN IMMUNITY
IDOL IN MY TRUSTY BRA OVER HERE.
MY GUT SAYS TO PLAY IT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE I'M HERE
TO LIVE ANOTHER DAY.
>> WHERE'S THE OTHER TRIBE?
>> MAYBE THEY WENT TO LAIRO.
WHO DO YOU THINK IS GOING?
>> I THINK JANET.
>> I FEEL VERY BLESSED TO HAVE
BEEN PART OF ALL OF THIS,
ESPECIALLY AT MY AGE.
>> JANET IS GOING HOME.
AND I'M ALL BUT CERTAIN THAT
JANET KNOWS THAT HER TIME IN
THIS GAME IS UP.
I DON'T HAVE AN IMMUNITY
NECKLACE ON TODAY.
THIS IS MY VERY FIRST TIME THAT
I'M TRULY GOING TO FIND OUT THAT
THE ALLIANCE IS WORKING WITH ME.
>> SO HOPEFULLY IT'S KARISHMA
AND JANET.
>> SHE DUG HER OWN GRAVE
EARLIER.
>> A "SURVIVOR" GOD GIFT.
EASY.
SHE'S GOT TO GO.
>> I AGREE.
>> JANET IS A BOSS.
JANET IS A VERY STRONG WOMAN,
AND SHE IS A BIG THREAT, BUT A
LOT OF PEOPLE FEEL THREATENED BY
AARON.
HE'S A BEAST.
I CANNOT BEAT AARON IN
CHALLENGES.
SO TONIGHT'S GOING TO BE A
REALLY TOUGH VOTE.
>> I WAS IN TROUBLE.
I WAS ON THIN ICE, BUT IT IS NOT
ROCKET SCIENCE.
THIS GROUP IS DONE WITH AARON.
>> WE'RE GOOD.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M FEELING SAFE,
WHICH IS A SCARY PLACE TO BE,
BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN SO MANY
PLIED -- BLINDSIDE AT TRIBAL.
>> WE SHOULD ALL GET AN OSCAR.
>> I JUST HOPING I'M NOT FOOLING
MYSELF THAT IT'S GOING TO BE
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
>> LOOK AT HIM, ROLLING UP HIS
SHIRT, SHOWING HIS MUSCLES
AGAIN.
DAN, WHAT'S THE BIGGEST IMPACT
OF THIS TWIST THAT DIVIDED YOU
INTO TWO GROUPS?
>> INITIALLY IT WAS TERRIFYING,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE AN AGENDA AND
YOU HAVE AN ALLIANCE AND YOU'RE
MOVING FORWARD IN A PARTICULAR
DIRECTION, BUT THE TEAMS SEEM TO
HAVE SCRAMBLED IN A WAY THAT
SHOULD ALLOW THE PEOPLE THAT
WERE THE TARGETS TO STILL BE THE
TARGETS.
>> Jeff: REALLY INTERESTING,
JANET.
DAN JUST SPOKE FOR THE ENTIRE
GROUP, SAYING FORTUNATELY
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO GO AS
PLANNED.
>> WELL, I'M DEFINITELY LOW MAN
ON THE TOTEM POLL, AND I THINK
THAT'S DIRECTED AT ME.
>> Jeff: DEAN, HOW ABOUT FOR
YOU?
WHAT'S THE BIGGEST IMPACT FROM
YOUR POINT OF VIEW TO THIS
TWIST?
>> WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE CERTAIN
PEOPLE THAT PERHAPS YOU TRUST
THAT WERE LEFT ON THE OTHER
SIDE, IT'S VERY, VERY
CONCERNING.
THERE IS DEFINITELY
RELATIONSHIPS WITHIN THIS GROUP
THAT ARE TIGHTER THAN
RELATIONSHIPS THAT I HAVE.
>> Jeff: AARON, WHAT DID YOU
FEEL AFTER THE CHALLENGE WAS
OVER IN TERMS OF ANXIETY VERSUS
COMFORT VERSUS UNCERTAINTY?
>> ME PERSONALLY, THIS IS MY
FIRST TIME SITTING AT A TRIBAL
COUNCIL WITHOUT A NECKLACE ON,
SO IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY TO SEE IF
MY ALLIANCES AND THE
RELATIONSHIPS THAT I FORMED ARE
GOING TO HOLD UP.
>> Jeff: INTERESTING THAT YOU
SAY OPPORTUNITY.
A LOT OF PEOPLE HIGH SAY, JEFF,
I'M TERRIFIED.
THERE'S ONLY SEX PEOPLE AND I
DIDN'T WIN, BUT YOU SEEM VERY
CALM.
>> WELL, WHEN I SAY
"OPPORTUNITY," IT'S AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR MY NAME TO BE
WRITTEN ON THAT PIECE OF PAPER.
I'M NOT CALLING IT ALL, BUT WHAT
WE HAVE IS A GROUP OF
INDIVIDUALS WHO ARE WORKING
TOGETHER AND HAVE A PLAN IN
PLACE, AND AT THIS POINT IN
TIME, WE ALL FEEL COMFORTABLE
WORKING TO ACCOMPLISH WHAT WE'RE
TRYING TO ACCOMPLISH.
>> BUT YOU KNOW, STUFF ALWAYS
HAPPENS.
THERE'S ALWAYS SURPRISES.
LIKE WE LOST JACK, BOOM, BECAUSE
I UNDERESTIMATED DEAN.
ONE VOTE CAN BE WHAT CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I THINK IT'S JANET.
>> Jeff: SO JANET, WHAT DO YOU
DO IF YOU THINK IT'S YOU AND
THERE ARE ONLY FIVE PEOPLE TO
TALK TO?
>> WELL, I TALK TO A FEW PEOPLE,
AND MAYBE SOMEBODY WILL GO, DUH,
THAT MAYBE MADE SOME SENSE,
MAYBE I SHOULD MAKE A MOVE.
>> Jeff: NOURA, DID JANET
APPROACH YOU AND SAY, WE SHOULD
TALK?
>> I TALK TO JANET ALL THE TIME.
SHE'S MY MOMMY AND MY FRIEND,
BUT THERE HAS TO BE A BOUNDARY
AT SOME POINT WHERE IT'S LIKE, I
-- AM I GOING TO RISK ME BEING
HERE AHEAD OF YOU?
THERE IS A BOUNDARY THERE?
>> Jeff: DAN, WHAT DOES IT
MEAN FOR THE GAME TO LOSE TWO
PEOPLE AT ONCE?
>> I THINK THAT WAS THE OTHER
NERVE-RACKING FACTOR OF THIS
TWIST, WHICH IS THE THING THAT
WAS THREE VOTES AWAY COULD BE,
WELL, NOW LET'S PLAY AND WE HAVE
TO START EATING THE HEAD OF THE
SNAKE.
THE FEAR STARTS TO GET STOKED.
I HAVE TRIED MY HARDEST IN THIS
GAME TO HOPE THAT TRUST LEADS TO
LOYALTY, LOYALTY LEADS TO
ALLIANCES, AND ALLIANCES LEAD TO
VOTES.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DEAN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JANET.
AARON.
ONE VOTE JANET, ONE VOTE AARON.
TWO VOTES AARON, ONE VOTE JANET.
THAT'S THREE VOTES AARON, ONE
VOTE JANET.
TENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
AARON.
THAT'S FOUR, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> I TOLD YOU IT'S AARON.
>> Jeff: AARON, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
AARON, YOU CAN GO AHEAD AND TAKE
Añ;SPOT ON THE JURY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS CAN HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
WE'LL BRING IN THE NEXT GROUP.
>> YOU KNOW, I KIND OF
ANTICIPATED THIS WOULD HAPPEN AT
SOME POINT IN TIME.
I TRIED TO DELAY IT AS MUCH AS I
COULD BY WINNING THE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
THEY HAD TO GET RID OF ME.
NOW WAS THE RIGHT TIME.
KUDOS TO THEM.
HATS OFF.
I'LL SIT MY BUTT ON THE JURY.
>> GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
OUR NEW JURY MEMBER.
AARON VOTED OUT MINUTES AGO.
ELIZABETH, YOUR FACE SAYS IT
ALL.
WHAT'S GOING THROUGH YOUR MIND
RIGHT THIS MOMENT?
>> MY HEART IS BEATING REALLY
HARD.
AARON WAS ONE OF MY NUMBER ONES.
THIS SUCKS.
YEAH, THAT'S NOT REALLY --.
>> Jeff: THAT'S AN INTERESTING
THING.
YOU WERE REALLY SNEAKY BY
SEPARATING US AND KEEPING US
APART.
GAME PLAN GOT SWITCHED WITHOUT
US KNOWING.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH, WHAT
HAPPENED AFTER THE CHALLENGE
WHEN YOU GO BACK THE CAMP,
ELAINE HAS IMMUNITY, AND NOW YOU
HAVE TO START TALKING.
>> THERE WAS DEFINITELY CHAOS
AROUND CAMP, BUT I FEEL GOOD
ABOUT THE PLAN THAT I WAS A PART
OF.
I'M HOPING THAT'S THE ONE THAT
GOES THROUGH TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: MISSY, IS THAT WHAT
YOU EXPERIENCED, AS WELL IN.
>> I EXPERIENCED A LOT FROM
KARISHMA TODAY.
WE HAD QUITE A TRIP TODAY.
AND I WASN'T A GOOD ONE.
SO, YEAH.
IT WAS PRETTY BAD.
>> Jeff: KARISHMA, WHAT IS
MISSY REFERRING TO.
>> MISSY AND I HAVE BEEN BUTTING
HEADS FOR SOME TIME, NOT A
SECRET TO ANYONE HERE.
IT'S JUST -- EMOTIONS ARE REALLY
HIGH.
I LIKE TO JUST SAY MY PIECE,
WALK AWAY, AND LET IT CALM DOWN,
BUT THERE WERE TIMES WHERE MISSY
WANTED TO ESCALATE THINGS OR
WANTED TO SAY THINGS THAT I
DIDN'T FEEL WERE NECESSARY IN
THE GAME.
>> TIME OUT.
THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR," WHEN YOU
CALL SOMEONE A THREAT, THE
THINGS YOU SAY ARE, JAMAL FINDS
IDOL, HE'S ATHLETIC, HE'S A
THREAT.
KELLEE IS SOCIAL, SHE'S A
YOU DO NOT SAY, OH, SHE'S A
BULLY, SHE NEEDS TO LEAVE THE
GAME BECAUSE SHEA XI YELLS AT ME
AND SHE'S AGGRESSIVE.
>> Jeff: YOU ARE SAYING YOU'VE
BEEN LABELED THOSE THINGS?
-100 FACT.
FOR ME, I AM NOT THAT.
THAT'S NOT ME.
>> Jeff: KARISHMA IS MISSY
CORRECT, YOU LOOK AT HER AS A
BULLY OR AGGRESSIVE, THE WORD
SHE USED?
>> THERE ARE TIMES I DO, YES.
>> JEFF, I KNOW WHO I AM, AND
WHEN I LOOK IN THE MIRROR, I'M
HAPPY EVERY MORNING.
I ACCEPT MYSELF.
DO YOU?
>> I THINK IT GOES WITHOUT
SAYING I ACCEPT WHO I AM IS
100%.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS WE
CLASH, BECAUSE WE DON'T SEE EYE
TO EYE.
>> Jeff: IS PART OF THIS
DIFFERENT PEOPLE FROM DIFFERENT
WALKS OF LIFE WHO SEE THE WORLD
DIFFERENTLY AND THEY'RE NEVER
GOING TO AGREE?
>> I THINK THAT'S WHAT IT COMES
DOWN.
TO GETTING TO KNOW KARISHMA,
SHE'S A WONDERFUL PERSON.
KNOWING MISSY, SHE'S AN
INCREDIBLE PERSON.
I THINK THEY JUST BOTH VIEW SO
DIFFERENTLY THAT THEY'RE NEVER
GOING TO BE ABLE TO COINCIDE.
>> BUT I WAS THERE WITH MISSY
AND KARISHMA TODAY, AND I
THOUGHT IT WENT FANTASTIC.
I THINK WE BRIDGED THE GAP
BETWEEN BOAT OF THEIR
PERSONALITIES.
>> AND KARISHMA, I UNDERSTAND
NOT WANTING PEOPLE TO VOTE YOU
OUT, SO YOU LIE, BUT I'VE ALWAYS
TOLD YOU I WOULD LOVE TO WORK
WITH YOU.
>> Jeff: ELAINE, DO YOU
UNDERSTAND WHAT MISSY IS SAYING?
>> JEFF, THEY GOT ME SO TWISTED,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
BUT WHO AM I TO SAY ANYTHING.
THE BEEF IS BETWEEN THE TWO OF
THEM.
THE ONLY WAY TO SQUASH IT IS TO
SEND SOMEBODY HOME HONESTLY.
>> WE'RE READY TO VOTE.
>> REAL QUICK.
I LOVE YOU.
BUT THE OTHER DAY TWO AFRICAN
AMERICANS WORE THE NECKLACE AT
THE SAME TIME AND AT OUR TRIBAL
THERE WAS NO MENTION OF IT AT
ALL.
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN VERY OFTEN.
WOMEN TYPICALLY ARE THE FIRST
VOTED OUT.
MINORITIES ARE THE SECOND.
SO TO HAVE TWO MINORITIES ON THE
SAME DAY IN A DOUBLE CHALLENGE
WEAR THE NECKLACE, THAT'S JUST
SOMETHING THAT I FEEL LIKE
REPRESENTATION MATTERS, AND I
FEEL LIKE MY FUTURE NIECES AND
NEPHEWS AND MY FUTURE OTHER
FAMILY MEMBERS NEED TO SEE THAT,
BECAUSE WE'RE HERE, TOO.
>> Jeff: MISSY, I GOT TO SAY,
I LOVE THAT YOU BROUGHT IT UP.
I'M NOT SURE IF I WOULD HAVE
HIGHLIGHTED IT.
IT ACTUALLY NEVER OCCURRED TO
ME, BUT I WOULD HAVE BEEN
RELUCTANT TO FOR FEAR OF SAYING,
WOW, LIKE IT'S SOMETHING YOU
WOULDN'T EXPECT TO HAPPEN.
SO EVEN I'M LEARNING RIGHT NOW
THAT ALL OF THESE ROADS THAT
WE'RE TRYING TO WEAVE TO GET
ALONG IN HARMONY ARE FRAUGHT
WITH THEIR OWN PITFALLS.
SO I APPRECIATE YOU SPEAKING UP.
AND NOW ONCE AGAIN WE'RE GOING
TO GO FROM SOMETHING THAT SEEMS
OUTSIDE OF THE GAME AND WE'RE
GOING TO GET RIGHT BACK INTO
NAMES ON A PARCHMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
PER YOUR WISH, IT IS TIME TO
VOTE.
ELIZABETH, YOU'RE UP.
>> WHEN YOU BRING UP MY NAME,
YOU PACK YOUR BAGS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES..
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, MISSY.
TOMMY.
ONE VOTE MISSY, ONE VOTE TOMMY.
THAT'S TWO VOTES TOMMY, ONE VOTE
MISSY.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES MISSY, TWO VOTES
TOMMY.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE FIFTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
MISSY.
>> YO, WHO DID IT?
>> YOU CAME AFTER ME.
>> I DIDN'T COME AFTER YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, DAMN.
THAT WAS DOPE, THOUGH, Y'ALL.
THAT'S NOT MINE.
>> WAS IT YOU?
THAT'S WILD.
>> MISSY, FROM HERE, DIFFERENCES
AND ALL GIRL.
>> YOU KNOW I WAS KEEPING YOU
FOR THE END.
>> EVERYBODY IS KEEPING KARISHMA
>> COME ON, MISSY, IT'S OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT, JEFF, COME ON,
MAN.
>> MISSY --
>> JEFF!
>> Jeff: THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
DANG, ELAINE, I KNEW IT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU ALL LATER.
WEDNESDAY NIGHT AT 8:00.
>> LOVE YOU, MISS.
>> BYE, MISSY.
>> Jeff: WELL, WE ARE 27 DAYS
IN TO A 39-DAY GAME, AND THE
FOOT HAS NOT COME OFF THE PEDDLE
FOR EVEN A MOMENT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN ANIMALS
ATTACK...
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> HE BIT MY FINGER.
>> Jeff: ...YOU'LL NEED TO
TRAVEL IN A PACK.
>> ATTENTION, REPORT FOR DUTY.
>> Jeff: TO REACH THE TOP OF
THE FOOD CHAIN.
>> THIS IS GOING THE CHANGE MY
GAME.
>> ON A SCALE OF DOPINESS,
GETTING BLINDSIDED, THAT'S
NEGATIVELY DOPE, AND I DIDN'T
EVEN NOTICE.
SO THAT'S A BIG ENOUGH FAULT IN
MY GAME WHERE I DESERVE TO BE
HERE, BUT IT'S FINE.
LIFE GOES ON.
IT'S IN THE A BRAIN TUMOR.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE WILDEST,
CRAZIEST, WHAT IS THAT, 27 DAYS?
I'D GO 60 MORE.