YOU CAN'T JUST DO THAT
ANYMORE.
I DON'T TRUST ANYBODY
I KNOW.
I WAS KIND OF OUT OF THE LOOP ON
THAT.
WHEN PEOPLE TRIED TO TELL YOU
ABOUT RON.
I WANT TO KNOW HOW MY NAME
CAME UP.
I VOTED WHERE I THOUGHT THE
VOTES WERE GOING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY TO
YOU?
I APOLOGIZE.
WAS I THE WEAKEST PERSON OUT
HERE?
WAS I NOT THE PERSON WHO HELPED
WITH ALL THESE THINGS?
THAT WASN'T IT.
IT WAS RONNIE.
THAT'S WHY ANYBODY WANTED HIM
OUT.
WE GOT BACK THE TRIBAL.
MY ASS IS LIKE MAYBE I SHOULD BE
NICE.
NO, IT'S OKAY, IT'S JUST A GAME.
BUT I'M LIKE, NO, THAT'S NOT WHO
I AM.
>>
THAT'S JUST HOW THINGS GO.
WE DON'T NEED THIS TO TEAR US
APART.
WE'RE STILL A TRIBE.
WE STILL HAVE TO MOVE FORWARD.
AARON WAS PRETTY MAD, BUT THAT'S
PERFECT.
WITH THE GUY GONE, THE GIRL'S
ALLIANCE IS IN CONTROL, BUT I
KNOW WE CAN STILL WORK TOGETHER,
SO HE NEEDS TO STOP CRYING.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
IF PEOPLE DIDN'T WANT TO WORK
WITH YOU, YOU WOULD BE GONE.
I HAVE ZERO TRUST IN ANYBODY
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S OUT THE DOOR.
NONE.
WE SHOULD EARN IT BACK.
SOMEBODY'S WORD MEANS NOTHING
TO ME.
YOU'RE MAD AND YOU DESERVE TO
BE MAD AND I'M SORRY.
IF YOU LEAVE, WE ALL LOSE THE
GAME ANYWAY AND YOU KNOW THAT.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
EVERYBODY IS SAYING THE RIGHT
THING, BUT I DON'T TRUST ANYBODY
AT ALL.
FOOL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU.
FOOL ME TWICE, THAT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR THEM, THEIR
DAY WILL COME.
THIS SUCKS.
I GET IT.
YEAH, THIS IS A REALLY GOOD
IDEA.
YEAH.
SO THAT WAS REALLY IT.
THE FACT THAT WE KEPT IT
GOING, THAT WAS ME.
I GOT UP AND GOT SOAKING WET.
AND THIS COULD BE THAT SENSE OF
URGENCY TO HELP OURSELVES, AND
NOT JUST SIT LAZY AND SELFISH.
AND I DIDN'T GO TO SLEEP LAST
NIGHT FOR US.
I HAD THE WALK AWAY BECAUSE
SHE'S JUST COMPLAINING.
LAUREN.
DID YOU EVER FEEL, GET UP.
PEOPLE CAN'T JUST SLEEP AROUND
ANYMORE.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE I WAS
SLEEPING, SO I FEEL INNOCENT.
I JUST EXPLAINED IT.
I THINK YOU ANSWERED IT RIGHT
THERE.
AS EACH DAY GOES BY, IT GETS
HARDER TO THE AROUND NOURA.
SHE'S ANNOYING.
SHE'S COMING AT SOMEONE AT
6:00 a.m. WHEN THEY JUST WOKE UP
ISN'T SMART.
NO ONE HAS EVER PICKED ON ME
BECAUSE IT'S NOT THAT FUN.
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
WE ALL FEEL THAT IT'S WEARING TO
BE WITH SOMEONE 24 HOURS A DAY
WHO CAN BE A GRATING
PERSONALITY.
IN "SURVIVOR" YOU NEED TO BITE
YOUR TONGUE.
AND NOURA DOESN'T.
IT'S A PRETTY LAZY TRIBE IN
MY OPINION.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO TO NOT BE
LAZY?
EVERYONE SHOULD ALWAYS BRING
WOOD AND KEEP IT BY THE FIRE.
IT SHOULD ALWAYS BE THERE.
PEOPLE CAN JUST LEVEL UP.
BOTTOM LINE, WE WOULD NOT EAT
BREAKFAST EVERY DAY, WE WOULD
NOT HAVE FIRE GOING
CONTINUOUSLY.
COLLECT COCONUTS WHEN YOU GO ON
YOUR WALKS WITH YOUR LITTLE
TALK.
THERE'S A LOT OF, LET'S JUST
CHILL, I'M FINE.
AND MOLLY DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
SHE'S THAT CADDIE GIRL IN HIGH
SCHOOL THAT'S POP ALREADY AND
PRETTY AND ALL THE GUYS LIKE BUT
YOU AS A GIRL CAN SEE THROUGH.
MOLLY IS NOT THAT STRONG AND NOT
THAT HELPFUL AROUND CAMP.
SHE'S LIKE PUT TOGETHER, KNOWS
HOW TO TALK AND CHARM.
IT'S JUST LIKE, WHOA, THAT'S HOW
SHE'S GAINING EVERYONE OVER.
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
THIS IS WHY I'M GOING CRAZY
RIGHT NOW.
I APPRECIATE YOU AND I DO GET
YOU, BUT I WANT YOU THE STAY
CALM SOMETIMESFUL.
I WAS GOING CRAZY.
THAT'S WHAT HALF THIS GAME
COMES DOWN TO, HOW MUCH CAN YOU
HANDLE YOUR NERVES.
THE "KUMBAYA" IS WEARING OFF AND
PEOPLE'S PERSONALITIES ARE
SHOWING THROUGH, YOU HAVE TO
STAY WITH THEM FOR 35 DAYS.
I CAN'T.
MAYBE WITH ME BY YOUR SIDE
YOU CAN.
THAT'S TRUE.
I PROMISE I WILL BE -I'LL DO
MY BEST TO BE MORE COOL.
YOU'RE CUTE, JASON.
NOURA AND I ARE CLEARLY ON
THE OUT, AND NOURA GETTING INTO
TROUBLE IS A GOOD THING FOR MY
GAME, BUT I'M IN THIS WEIRD
COMPLEX WITH NOURA RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE SHE'S MY FRIEND, AND I
GOT INTO TROUBLE EARLY.
PEOPLE KIND OF KICKED ME TO THE
SIDE.
THE ONLY PERSON THAT REALLY CAME
TO MY AID WAS NOURA.
I FEEL I OWE HER SOMETHING.
I REALLY DO.
THEY HAVE AN ORDER OF
OPERATION, ME OR YOU.
THAT'S WHAT IT WOULD BE.
SO THE QUESTION IS --
WHO IS MAKING THE DECISIONS?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I THINK IT'S MOLLY, JAMAL,
AND JACK.
YOU THINK SHE'S IN CONTROL?
THEY'RE IN CONTROL OF A LOT
OF DECISIONS.
YOU THINK JASON OUT BEFORE
NOURA?
I REALLY DO
I THINK NOURA IS A HUGE
LIABILITY.
YOU HAVE A "REVENGE OF THE
NERDS" STRATEGY WHERE ALL THE
PEOPLE THAT ARE NOT THE POPULAR
KIDS GO AGAINST THE THREE.
WE'RE PLAYING FROM THE
BOTTOM.
I'M A TAG-ALONG HERE.
I CAN VOLT IN ANY DIRECTION ONE
WAY OR ANOTHER.
THIS SUCKS.
THE THREE AT THE TOP, THE KING,
THE QUEEN, AND THE JACK, THE
ROYAL PARTY, THEY'RE THE POPULAR
GROUP THAT EVERYONE IS LIKE,
WE'RE NOT WORTHY, WE'RE NOT
WORTHY, WE WANT TO FIT IN WITH
YOU, AND ME AND JASON ARE THE
UNDERDOGS, THE MISFIT, THE
NERDS, IT'S LIKE HIGH SCHOOL ALL
OVER AGAIN.
MAKING FIRE IS SOMETHING
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT SINCE
DAY ONE, REALLY HOUR ONE OF
BUILDING THE CAMP, BUT IT'S NOT
EASY.
AND IT JUST DIDN'T HAPPEN.
THE FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL DIDN'T
GO THE WAY I WANTED IT TO GO,
AND NOW.
THIS I'M BEYOND FRUSTRATED.
DO YOU NEED MORE DRY, LIKE A
COCONUT HUSK?
YOU CAN GIVE IT A GO.
IF I WERE A GAMBLING PERSON, I
WOULD BET TONIGHT WE'RE GOING TO
BE WET AND COLD.
WATCH OUT, YOU GOT A GIRL
WITH A KNIFE.
THERE YOU GO.
CHELSEA IS A FIRE STARTER.
YEAH, BUDDY.
CHELSEA WITHIN LIKE TWO
MINUTES, SHE GOT THE FIRE GOING,
IT SHOCKED US.
IT SHOCKED ME FOR SURE.
DON'T SMOTHER IT.
WE WERE BOTH REALLY HAPPY SHE
STARTED THE FIRE, BUT ALSO,
GREAT JOB GETTING THAT FIRE
GOING, YOU JUST RUINED MY MALE
EGO FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
FIREWOOD, GUYS, FIREWOOD.
I'M THE ONE THAT STARTED THE
FIRE.
GREAT FEELING, ESPECIALLY AS A
SUPER FAN.
I'M IS HAPPY I DID IT.
I'M SO PROUD OF MYSELF.
I'M IN A GOOD POSITION RIGHT
NOW.
I HAVE MY FIVE GIRLS.
WE HAVE THE NUMBERS, AND THE
GUYS IN THIS TRIBE ARE COOL, BUT
THE GIRLS ARE THE ONES
DOMINATING.
WE CAN DO ANYTHING THEY CAN DO.
IN FACT, WE'RE DOING IT BETTER.
OH.
CONGRATULATION, YOU HAVE FOUND A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
YES!
MY HEART WAS JUST THUMPING.
I DREAMED OF THIS MOMENT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT HAPPENED.
I WAS PUMPED.
I DIDN'T GO INTO COLLECTING
FIREWOOD EXPECTING TO FIND THE
IDOL, BUT ANY SMART "SURVIVOR"
PLAYER, YOU'RE GOING TO GATHER
THINGS, YOU'RE LOOKING FOR AN
IDOL.
THERE WERE SO MANY PEOPLE
AROUND, I WAS SO SCARED.
I JUST HAD THE KEEP MY
COMPOSURE.
FORTUNATELY THESE GUYS DON'T
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY DON'T KNOW THERE IS A
GIRL'S ALLIANCE.
THEY DON'T KNOW HOW TO MAKE
FIRE, AND CLEARLY THEY DON'T
KNOW HOW TO FIND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON IN
THEIR HEADS, BUT THE GAME HAS
STARTED, AND THEY'RE BEHIND.
♪ OMMMM
OMMMM ♪
OKAY.
SO NOW WE'RE GOING TO GET INTO
THE PHYSICAL PART OF THE
PRACTICE.
AND IT GOES LIKE THIS.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO DO THAT 50
TIMES.
READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE...
YOGA WAS INTERESTING.
WE DID THE UP-DOWN THINGS 15
TIMES.
17, 18, 19.
IT WAS EXHAUSTING, ESPECIALLY
WITH THE AMOUNT OF FOOD WE HAD.
31, 32.
BUT NOURA, SHE SOUNDED LIKE
ALL YOGA CLASSES.
THIS IS STIMULATING YOUR
PARASYMPATHETIC NERVOUS SYSTEM.
I LOVE IT.
THIS IS A UNIQUE EXPERIENCE.
AND I'M REALIZING THAT I DON'T
WANT TO BE SITTING BEHIND A DESK
OR WEARING A SUIT.
I WANT TO HAVE A FREAKING
ADVENTURE AND HAVE A REALLY GOOD
TIME.
SO I FEEL REALLY GOOD HERE.
NAMASTE, Y'ALL.
HEY, HOW MANY TIMES DO WE GET
A BOAT?
OH, BABY, WHAT DO WE GOT?
WE GOT SOMETHING!
TOGETHER AS A TRIBE.
KELLEE MUST GET ON THE BOAT AND
HEAD TO THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
SHE WILL RETURN TO THE CAMP BY
THE END OF THE DAY.
IT'S OKAY.
WE ALL HAVE TO GET IT TOGETHER.
I'M LITERALLY JUST NUMB.
MY BODY HAS GONE INTO SHOCK.
I HAD TO GET ON THE BOAT AND GO
TO THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
I'M FREAKING OUT, BECAUSE I
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
WE'RE HERE FOR YOU.
YOU GOT THIS.
SO I'M LEAVING THE BEACH,
LEAVING MY TIME, AND THOSE TWO
STATEMENTS I JUST KEPT REPEag
OVER AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN,
ASSUME NOTHING AND THINK OUTSIDE
THE BOX.
I'M APPROACHING THE ISLAND,
AND I'M EXTREMELY NERVOUS.
I STARTED THINKING ABOUT ALL THE
DIFFERENT THINGS THAT ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS COULD BE.
I IT COULD BE A FEW EARNS THAT I
HAVE TO SMASH.
THERE COULD BE A BUNCH OF IDOLS
AND CLUES ON THE ISLAND.
MAYBE SOMETHING WILL POP OUT.
THIS IS CRAZY.
WHOA.
WHAT?
WELCOME.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON OVER.
OUT POPS BOSTON ROB AND
SANDRA.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD, OH MY GOSH.
IT WAS VERY SURREAL.
IN MY MINDS THEY'RE LEGENDS.
THEY'RE CELEBRITIES.
I WAS LIKE, SHOULD I FREAK OUT?
SHOULD I PLAY IT COOL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
KELLEE.
KELLEE, THIS IS THE "ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS."
WE'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING TO YOU.
I THOUGHT, WHAT IF COCHRAN
GREETS ME.
THIS IS WAY BETTER THAN
COCHRAN.
WE ARE NOT COMPETING, WE
CANNOT VOTE, WE CANNOT WIN THE
$1 MILLION PRIZE.
OUR JOB IS TO MENTOR YOU IN THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR" AND THEN
OFFER YOU A CHANCE TO TEST WHAT
YOU'VE LEARNED.
OKAY.
SO THEY READ IT OUT LOUD.
THERE IS A LINE THAT CATCHES MY
EYE.
WHAT DOES THIS OFFER YOUúA
CHANCE TO TEST WHAT YOU'VE
LEARNED?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WE'LL GET TO THAT IN A
MINUTE.
OKAY.
I'M BEEN TO HARVARD.
I'VE BEEN THE WHARTON.
THE REASON I'M GOOD FOR TESTS
BECAUSE I PRACTICE FOR THEM.
BUT GOING ENTER A TEST TOTALLY
BLIND IS REALLY SCARY.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I'M AN MBA AT WHARTON.
I WENT THE HARVARD FOR
UNDERGRAD.
OH, COOL, SMARTY PANTS.
I TRY NOT TO BE.
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
BROCK.
YOU HAVE ANY PETS?
NO.
NO PETS.
OKAY.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
LIKE WHAT IS HAPPENING?
WHAT IS THE POINT OF THIS?
YOU GUYS EATING ANYTHING YET
ON YOUR TRIBE?
ARE YOU IN THE MAJORITY.
YOU TALKED ABOUT FIRST VOTE
YET?
ROB IS HERE, SANDRA IS HERE,
JABBERING, JABBERING, JABBERING.
I WENT TO COLLEGE AT B.U.
I WENT TO A FEW HARVARD PARTIES.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS
HAPPENING SOME IT'S HARD TO
CONCENTRATE ON THE CONVERSATION.
SO HAVE YOU MADE COCONUT
POPCORN?
HOW DID YOU MEET BROCK
I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED ABOUT
CHIROPRACTORS, ARE THEY LEGIT?
SO I HAVE FOUR DOGS, FOUR
POMERANIANS.
I HAVE ROSIE, SHE'S 16.
LOOK, EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS
ON THE ISLAND OF THE IDOL IS A
TEST.
EVERYTHING.
SHE'S OLDER NOW, SO SHE'S
GOING HALF BLIND.
IN THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR,"
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO BE PAYING
ATTENTION.
IT'S A CRITICAL SKILL.
SO ROSY, PAPA, AND THEN I
HAVE THE TWO BABIES.
PAPA IS GOING DEAF.
PAY ATTENTION, KELLEE, THIS
IS IMPORTANT.
I MARRIED AMBER, WHO I WAS ON
SEASON EIGHT.
WITH WE HAVE FOUR KIDS TOGETHER,
AND SANDRA HAS TWO GIRLS, TOO
THEY'RE 235EU7B8GS AND 21.
PI HUSBAND HAS BEEN IN THE ARMY
27 YEARS.
HE'S STILL ACTIVE DUTY.
WITH KELLEE, I THINK SHE WAS
MORE TRYING TO GET HER BEARINGS
ABOUT WHAT "ISLAND OF THE IDOLS"
WAS.
WHEN SHE SHOULD BE FOCUSING ON
WHAT WE'RE TELLING HER, BECAUSE
SHE DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS GOING TO
BE HER LESSON.
WHEN YOU FIRST GOT HERE, WE
READ YOU THE OATH.
WE TOLD YOU THAT WE WERE GOING
TO GIVE YOU AN OPPORTUNITY TO
TEST WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED.
WHAT YOU MAY NOT HAVE REALIZED
IS THAT YOUR LESSON ACTUALLY
STARTED THE MINUTE YOU ARRIVED
ON THIS BEACH.
OH, GOD.
FORT PIERCING RELATIONSHIPS
BASED ON LISTENING AND PAYING
ATTENTION IS A CRITICAL SKILL
THAT YOU NEED TO HAVE IN THIS
GAME.
WHEN I START TELLING YOU
ABOUT MY FAMILY AND THINGS THAT
ARE IMPORTANT TO ME, THEN I NEED
YOU TO LISTEN, BECAUSE THAT'S
HOW ME AND YOU ARE GOING TO FORM
BONDS AND TRUST, AND THAT'S
WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN SITTING
HERE, WE LEARNED A LOT ABOUT
EACH OTHER.
I KNOW THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND'S
NAME IS BROCK.
YOU WENT THE HARVARD AND
WHARTON.
HOW WELL
WERE YOU PAYING ATTENTION TO US?
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M GOING THE READ THIS TO YOU.
OKAY.
YOU NOW HAVE CHANCE TO EARN
AN ADVANTAGE BY TESTING HOW WELL
YOU WERE LISTENING.
WE HAVE FIVE QUESTIONS
PERTAINING TO INFORMATION WE
JUST TOLD YOU ABOUT OURSELVES.
IF YOU GET FOUR RIGHT, YOU EARN
AN IMMUNITY IDOL GOOD AT EITHER
OF THE NEXT TWO TRIBALS THAT YOU
GO TO.
IF YOU LOSE, YOU LOSE YOUR VOTE
AT THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME THINK ABOUT IT.
HAVE YOU BEEN
LISTENING TO US?
AND I'M LIKE, NOT REALLY.
LIKE, NO I'VE BEEN FREAKING OUT
IN MY HEAD THIS ENTIRE TIME.
AND I HAVE A TERRIBLE MEMORY.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
ANSWER THE QUESTIONS.
WHAT IF I SWEETEN THE DEAL?
OKAY.
YOU ONLY HAVE TO GET THREE
OUT OF FIVE OF THE QUESTIONS.
AND THE IDOL IS GOOD FOR ONE OF
YOUR NEXT THREE TRIBAL COUNCILS.
IT'S YOUR DECISION TO MAKE.
THIS IS LIKE THE BIGGEST
MOMENT I'VE HAD YET IN THIS
GAME, SO I'M JUST LIKE
CALCULATING EVERYTHING.
I COULD HAVE AN IDOL AND THAT
WOULD BE REALLY, REALLY USEFUL,
ESPECIALLY FOR THREE TRIBALS, OR
LIKE LOSE MY VOTE.
IT'S A HUGE RISK.
YOU CAME TO WIN, RIGHT?
YOLO.
LET'S PLAY.
OKAY.
IT'S ON.
OH, MY GOD.
THERE ARE FIVE QUESTIONS.
YOU HAVE TO GET THREE RIGHT TO
WIN.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YEAH.
OKAY.
SANDRA TALKED ABOUT HER HUSBAND.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE BRANCH OF
THE MILITARY HE SERVED IN?
UH... THE ARMY.
THAT'S CORRECT.
THAT'S ONE RIGHT.
HERE'S THE SECOND QUESTION.
SANDRA CLEARLY LOVES HER
DAUGHTERS.
HOW MANY DOES SHE HAVE?
TWO.
YES.
THAT'S CORRECT.
OH, MY GOD.
WE'RE GOING FOR THREE.
OKAY.
THE ONLY THING SANDRA LOVES
AS MUCH AS HER FAMILY ARE HER
DOGS.
NAME ONE.
PAPA.
WE!
THAT'S AWESOME.
HERE'S YOUR IDOL.
OH, MY GOD!
GOOD FOR THREE TRIBAL
COUNCILS.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU DID IT.
I'M GOING TO CRY.
I KNOW THAT'S REALLY NOT A
NORMAL REACTION WHEN YOU GET AN
IDOL.
I JUST PUT SO MUCH STRESS AND
PRESSURE ON MYSELF, I DON'T
JUST -I THINK THE FEAR OF
FAILURE.
WE WANT YOU TO SUCCEED.
I NEED TO CELEBRATE THE FACT
THAT I JUST GOT AN IDOL, WHICH
IS CRAZY.
THERE'S ONE MORE THING WE
NEED YOU TO DO.
I WANT YOU TO PICK THE NEXT
PERSON FROM THE OTHER TRIBE TO
COME HERE.
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
KELLEE WENT THE HARVARD.
SHE'S SMART.
SHE WAS ANALYTICAL FROM THE
SECOND SHE WALKED INTO ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS.
SHE DEFINITELY POSSESSES THE
SKILLS THAT ARE NEEDED IN THIS
GAME TO WIN, AND HER TRIBE MATES
WILL BE MAKING A MISTAKE BY
UNDERESTIMATING HER.
KELLEE'S BACK.
WHY ARE YOU THINKING?
I KNOW EVERYONE WILL WANT TO
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
DO I HAVE AN IDOL.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE?
I HAD A MENTAL BREAKDOWN.
REALLY?
ON AN IMPULSE I BURST INTO
TEARS AND STARTED CRYING.
I WANT TO THROW THE SUSPICION
OFF MY BACK.
IT'S LIKE A MAN AND WOMAN MADE
OUT OF DRIFT WOOD AND 30, 40
FEET TALL, AND THERE ARE THREE
EARNS AND YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE AN
URN.
BUT I HAVE THIS IDOL AND I HAVE
THE RULES.
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO HIDE
THIS.
I JUST LIKE -I LIKE REALLY
PARANOID ABOUT IT.
LOOK AT MY CLOTHES, LOOK
THROUGH MY BAGS, PLEASE PAT ME
DOWN.
WILL YOU GUYS LOOK THROUGH.
I'M CRYING, BECAUSE I'M LIKE,
PLEASE BELIEVE ME.
KELLEE, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
THAT.
LITTLE DO THEY NOVI THE IDOL
IN MY HAIR.
I HAVE THREE OR FOUR PEOPLE
LITERALLY HUGGING ME AND HIT MY
HAIR.
LESS THEN A CENTIMETER AWAY FROM
THAT IDOL.
BUT I HAVE AN IDOL NO ONE KNOWS
ABOUT, SO IT'S GREAT.
THANK YOU.
IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK.
VOKAI GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
IF NEAR LAIRO TRIBE.
RONNIE VOTED OUT AT FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, GOT THE TAKE
IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHANG, YOU'RE GOING
TO SWIM OUT, RELEASE A LADER
FROM THE OCEAN FLOOR.
YOU'LL USE IT TO RETRIEVE A BAG
OF BALLS.
YOU'LL THEN RACE TO THE FINISH
AND LAND THOSE BALLS IN THREE
TARGETS.
FIRST TRIBE THE FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
SPICES.
WOW.
CLEARLY WORTH PLAYING
FOR.
YEAH.
VOKAI, YOU HAVE ONE
EXTRA PERSON.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT SOMEBODY
OUT.
I'M GOING TO SIT OUT.
LAUREN IS GOING TO
SIT OUT.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE SIT-OUT
BENCH.
EVERYONE ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE, AND WE'LL GET GOING.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR REWARD AND IMMUNITY,
SURVIVORS READY, GO!
EVERYBODY IN THE WATER AT ONCE.
YOU GOT TO GET DOWN AND RELEASE
THE LADDER, WHICH IS TETHERED TO
THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN.
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT HERE, RIGHT
HERE.
FIRST YOU GOT THE
FIND THE LADDER.
THEN YOU GOT TO GET DOWN AND
START UNTYING KNOTS.
ELIZABETH IS GOING DOWN FOR
LAIRO.
JACK AND JANET FOR VOKAI.
LAIRO HAS THEIR LADDER RELEASED.
THEY CAN START MOVING.
IS IT UNTIED?
YEAH.
VOKAI HAS THEIR
LADDER.
THEY CAN NOW START MOVING.
GOOD JOB.
IT IS A LOT OF WORK
TO MOVE A VERY THE HEAVY LADDER
THROUGH THE OCEAN.
NOW YOU HAVE TO LIFT THE LADDER
AND GET ONE PERSON UP TO
RETRIEVE THE BAG.
LET'S GO.
IT'S NOW LAIRO IN THE
LEAD AS VOKAI CAN'T GET TO THEIR
BAG.
THE WATER PUSHING THEM ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
CHELSEA GOING UP VERY QUICKLY
FOR LAIRO.
YEAH, CHELSEA!
GREAT TEAMWORK BY
LAIRO.
THEY DO NOT WANT TO GO BACK THE
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CHELSEA WITH QUICK WORK OF IT.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT ON
"SURVIVOR."
CHELSEA IN THE WATER.
GO, LAIRO, YOU'RE GOOD.
IT IS VOKAI NOW GETTING CLOSER
AND CLOSER TO THEIR BAG.
BUT THEY HAVE DEFINITELY GIVEN
UP A LOT OF TIME.
LET'S GO, VOKAI!
YOU GOT THIS.
WHERE'S THE BAG?
LAIRO NOW CAN'T FIND
THE BAG.
CHELSEA TOSSES THE BAG IN THE
WATER, AND THEY CAN'T FIND IT.
WE GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
THAT'S OPENED THE
DOOR FOR VOKAI NOW.
VINCE HAS IT.
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON.
VOKAI IS STRUGGLING
TO HOLD THE LADDER.
THEY CAN'T.
CATASTROPHE FOR VOKAI.
IT IS ONE SETBACK AFTER ANOTHER.
LAIRO NOW BACK IN THE LEAD.
VOKAI GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
GO.
YOU GOT TO GET THAT LADDER IN
THE TRACKS.
HOLLY WORKING ON THE KNOT.
THAT LADER IS GOING DOWN AGAIN.
MOLLY CAN'T GET IT DONE.
ONCE AGAIN MOLLY FALLS.
COME ON, GUYS.
VOKAI HAVING A
HORRIBLE TIME OF IT RIGHT NOW.
LAIRO EXTENDING THEIR LEAD.
LET'S GO!
YOU GOT THIS.
MOLLY GOING TO GIVE
IT ANOTHER GO.
YOU GOT THIS, MOLLY.
THIRD TIME'S THE
CHARM.
THEY'RE GOOD.
LET'S GO, VOKAI!
NOW YOU GOT TO LAND
THREE BALLS IN THREE TARGETS.
LAIRO WITH A HUGE EARLY LEAD.
MISSY LANDS THE FIRST BALL.
HERE COMES VOKAI.
VOKAI STILL HAS TO GET THEIR
LADDER IN.
MISSY HAS ONE FOR LAIRO.
YOU'RE GOOD, VOKAI.
YOU HAVE TO GET EVERYBODY
ACROSS.
GO, GO, GO!
YOU HAVE TO GO HIGH.
LAIRO STILL HAS JUST
ONE BALL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE STILL IN THIS.
YOU HAVE TO GET A
FEEL FOR THIS QUICKLY.
THERE ARE THREE TARGETS.
LAIRO HAS FIRST ONE.
THEY'RE GOING TO SWITCH OUT.
HERE COMES ELAINE NOW FOR LAIRO.
SHE'S GOT IT.
THAT'S TWO FOR LAIRO.
JAMAL WITH FIRST ONE FOR VOKAI.
IT IS TWO, LAIRO, ONE, VOKAI.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
EVERY CHALLENGE HAS AN
OPPORTUNITY THE CATCH UP, AND
THIS IS IT FOR VOKAI.
JAMAL SCORES THE SECOND FOR
VOKAI.
WE ARE TIED 2-2.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
MISSY GOING TO COME BACK IN.
SHE THINKS SHE CAN WIN IT FOR
LAIRO.
AND SHE THROWS IT COMPLETELY OFF
THE BOARD.
MISSY VERSUS JAMAL FOR THE WIN.
VOKAI JUST MISSES.
LAIRO WINS IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL SENDING VOKAI TO
VOTE OUT THEIR FIRST PERSON.
LAIRO, CONGRATULATIONS.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM LAIRO.
COOKING KIT AND SPICES WILL BE
WAITING FOR YOU BACK AT CAMP.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, ENJOY
THE NIGHT OFF.
VOKAI, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
IT'S OUR FIRST TASTE OF LOSS,
AND EVERYBODY IS ON BOARD TO
VOTE OUT NOURA OR JASON.
I DO FEEL BAD FOR THEM.
COMING INTO THIS GAME, I KNEW IT
WAS GOING TO BE REALLY HARD FOR
ME TO TAKE TEACHER TOMMY, PUT
THAT ASIDE, AND BECOME
"SURVIVOR" TOMMY, BUT YOU CAN'T
PUT YOUR NECK OUT FOR SOMEBODY.
IT'S EVERY MAN FOR THEMSELF.
IT'S A BUMMER.
IT'S NOT GOING THE HAPPEN.
IT WAS HARD.
I'M GOING TO GRAB THAT
FIREWOOD.
I JUST WANT TO SAY, GUYS, I
KNOW YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN GOING
BACK AND FORTH BETWEEN ME AND
JASON, AND I'M JUST TELLING YOU,
PLEASE KEEP ME.
YOU WANT TO HELP ME SEE WHY?
I MEAN, I JUST WANT THE LEAVE
IT IN YOUR HANDS, BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT TO GO THROUGH THIS
BACK AND FORTH?
YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR
JASON?
I'M A VERY LOYAL PERSON, BUT
YOU GUYS ARE THE WHOLE GROUP.
IS THERE A REASON YOU WANT TO
TALK STRATEGY?
I THINK I WANT TO DO WHAT YOU
WOULD LIKE ME TO DO.
I JUST WANT TO BE HERE, SO
THAT'S ALL I WANT TO
COMMUNICATE.
THIS VOTE IS PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD.
JASON AND NOURA ARE ON THE OUTS.
I THINK IT IS BEST TO SPLIT THE
VOTE TO AVOID ANYTHING CRAZY
SHOULD SOMEONE HAVE AN IDOL.
THERE IS SOME CONCERN THAT JASON
DID SOME SEARCHING EARLY IN THE
GAME, SO HE'S MORE DANGEROUS TO
KEEP AROUND.
YOU DEFINITELY DON'T HAVE AN
IDOL?
NO.
LIKE THIS WOULD BE THE VOTE I
WOULD NEED TO PLAY.
I HAVE A TIGHT ALLIANCE GOING
ON WITH MOLLY AND JACK WHERE
WE'RE TRYING TO BE THIS
UNSUSPECTING ALLIANCE WHO MOVE
THE VOTE UNDERNEATH THE RADAR.
WE'RE OFFICIALLY GOOD.
AWESOME.
JASON
COOL
I THINK WE'RE IMPRESSED AND
SURPRISED THAT WE'RE HANDLING
THIS SO WELL.
I WILL WORK HARD.
GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE.
I KNOW WE BUTTED HEADS A LITTLE
BIT.
I WON'T GET EMOTIONAL, BUT YOU
KNOW I REALLY WANT TO BE HERE.
I WANT TO VOTE NOURA OUT
IMMEDIATELY.
ALL RIGHT.
JACK AND JAMAL HAVE CONCERNS
ABOUT JASON.
I DON'T.
I DO THINK NOURA IS THE EASY
VOTE, BUT I THINK IT'S ALSO A
SMART VOTE BECAUSE NOURA HAS
PROVEN TO BE ERRATIC.
NOW WE'LL MAKE AN EASY VOTE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A NICE
AFTERNOON, AND LIFE WILL GO ON.
LET'S NOT MESS IT UP.
I RECOMMEND A MID-DAY MASS.
-NAP.
I JUST WANT TO CHAT FOR A
SECOND.
WHAT ARE WE THINKING?
HOW ARE WE FEELING?
WELL, I WAS TOLD WE'RE GOING
TO SPLIT VOTES?
DO WE WANT TO GET RID OF
NOURA FIRST?
NOURA IS EASY.
BUT I THINK THE BOYS WANT
JASON?
MOLLY IS TRYING THE FLIP
THAT.
WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT
MOLLY?
I THINK SHE'S A REALLY SMART
PLAYER.
AND I THINK SHE HAS THE MEN IN
THE PALM OF HER HAND.
SHE DOES.
AND THAT'S A LOT OF POWER.
THAT'S A LOT OF POWER.
IT WOULD BE A HUGE BLIND
SIDE.
WE KNOW JASON WOULD DO IT.
WE WOULD HAVE JASON, NOURA.
I THINK WE ALL NEED TO BE
SOLID.
HEY, MOLLY, I'M WATCHING YOU
LIKE A FREAKIN' HAWK, AND I KNOW
YOUR GAME.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOUR
GAME PLAY ME, I'M GOING TO PLAY
YOU.
THE BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT NOW IS
MOLLY, AND A BLIND MAN COULD SEE
THESE THREE ARE RUNNING THE
GAME.
WHY GET OUT THE PEOPLE LIKE
NOURA AND JASON WHEN I CAN USE
THEM AND I DON'T HAVE TO BE A
SHEEP AND BE HERDED AND BE TOLD
WHAT TO DO.
WE HAVE A KING AND WE HAVE
THE JACK.
ARE YOU PICKING UP WHAT I'M
LAYING DOWN?
OH, BABY, I GOT IT.
ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS LIKE FINE MUSIC TO MY
EARS.
LIKE I WAS LIKE, ARE YOU KIDDING
ME?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
YEAH.
REVENGE OF THE NERDS TAKEOVER
HAPPENS NOW.
THE "FREAKS AND GEEKS," THE
FREAKS AND GEEKS.
PLAY IT COOL.
I SENSE THE TRADE WINDS ARE
BLOWING.
THAT'S TO TAKE OUT MOLLY.
AM I 100% CERTAIN OF THAT?
HELL NO.
IT SOUNDS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
DON'T DANCE, DON'T DANCE.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
STOP DANCING.
THERE'S IN DANCING ALLOWED.
THIS IS LIKE "FOOTLOOSE," NO
DANCEING.
THEY REALLY WANT TO GET MOLLY
OUT?
WHO DOES?
ALL THE GIRL, KELLEE, LAUREN.
NOW?
IT'S A POSSIBILITY AS LONG AS
EVERYBODY IS ON BOARD.
NOT NOW.
THIS COULD BE THE ONLY TIME.
BUT LIKE I KIND OF HAVE JACK
IN MY BACK POCKET, JAMAL.
I DO THINK IT'S A LITTLE TOO
EARLY TO MAKE THIS MOVE, BUT
THEY'RE PETRIFIED OF MOLLY.
WE DO THIS MOVE, THE TURMOIL
WILL BE CRAZY.
JACK IS GOING TO BE UPAND
JAMAL.
THIS HAPPENS, I'M LOSING TWO
OF MY CLOSEST ALLIES IN JAMAL
AND JACK.
I AM SO TORN, BECAUSE THEY FEEL
LIKE MOLLY HAS TOO MUCH POWER IN
THE GAME.
IT'S NOT THE TIME.
I DEFINITELY WOULD NOT GO FOR
THAT IF YOU'RE NOT GOING FOR
THAT.
SO IF YOU REALLY WANT HER
OUT, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
BUT THE BOYS WILL FREAK OUT.
WE CAN GET NOURA FIRST OR JASON.
WE HAVE A REALLY TOUGH DECISION.
DO YOU GO WITH THE EASY VOTE?
OR DO WE REALLY WANT THE SHUFFLE
THE DECK AND MAKE A MOVE ON YOUR
FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL?
WE HAVE THE COOL KIDS.
THERE'S THE NERDS.
AS MY PARENTS WOULD ALWAYS SAY,
HANG OUT WITH THE RIGHT CREW.
THIS CREW OVER HERE IS THE COOL
LUNCH TABLE, AND I WANT TO BE
THERE, BECAUSE I WANT THE HANG
OUT WITH THEM, HOWEVER, IS THE
COOL KIDS' TABLE WHAT'S BEST FOR
US AND MY FUTURE.
WHICH ONE IS GOING TO GET ME THE
"SURVIVOR" $1 MILLION?
BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN THE FLAME AND GET
FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE
AND WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SAY
IT, JAMAL.
SO ARE YOU, RIGHT?
THAT'S IT.
JASON, LET'S GO BACK TO THE
BEGINNING.
THOSE FIRST COUPLE OF DAYS CAN
BE VERY TELLING.
YOU HAVE A GROUP OF STRANGERS
AND NATURALLY SOME PEOPLE WILL
JUST BOND.
WHO DID YOU NOTICE OUT OF THE
GATE SEEMED TO GET ALONG WELL?
EVERYBODY EXCEPT ME.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU MENTIONED THAT THE FIRST
DAYS ARE SO IMPORTANT, BUT
WITHIN HOURS OF THE GAME
STARTING, I WAS ON THE OUTSIDE.
AND JEFF, LET'S JUST MAKE THIS
CLEAR, THIS HAS TO DO WITH
PARANOIA.
I HAVE BEEN IN PURGATORY SINCE
DAY ONE BECAUSE THE FEAR THAT I
MIGHT BE GOING TO LOOK FOR A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS SEASON
IS BASICALLY PREYING ON PEOPLE'S
PARANOIA IN THIS GAME.
TOMMY, ON THE ONE
HAND, I'M SURE YOU HAVE SOME
EMPATHY FOR JASON, BUT ON THE
OTHER HAND, THIS COULD BE AN
EASY FIRST VOTE.
I THINK THAT'S THE HARD
PARTED ABOUT IT.
NO ONE WANTS TO FEEL ON THE
OUTS, HOWEVER, YOU DON'T WANT TO
BE THE ONE GOING HOME,
ESPECIALLY IN THE FIRST TRIBAL,
SO IT COULD BE AN EASY VOTE, AND
THEN LET'S START PLAYING THE
GAME.
KELLEE, WHAT DID YOU
SEE IN RELATION TO JASON AND A
BAD START?
THE THINK I THINK JASON MADE
A MISTAKE ON IS NOT RECOGNIZING
WHAT THE GROUP CULTURE WAS.
THE GROUP CULTURE WAS NOT TO
SPLIT UP INTO SMALL GROUPS AND
GO EXPLORE THE ISLAND.
THE GROUP CULTURE IS TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT WE WERE DOING WITH THE
SHELTER.
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, LET'S
START CALL THINGS AS IT IS.
I DON'T HAVE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
I DON'T PLAN ON PLAYING A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL TONIGHT.
THIS IS MY BAG.
YOU CAN PLEASE GO THROUGH MY
STUFF.
HE'S TRYING HARD.
YOU DON'T NEED TO DO THAT.
IT KIND OF OFFENDS ME WHEN YOU
SAY YOU HAVE WITHIN IN PURGATORY
FOR THE PAST FEW DAYS NOW,
BECAUSE NONE OF US FEEL LIKE
THAT.
WE'VE ALL BEEN LIKE, JASON IS
REALLY COOL.
LIKE WE REALLY ENJOYED GETTING
TO KNOW YOU.
NOURA, WHEN YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT THIS GAME AND
BUILDING A NEW SOCIETY WITH YOUR
TRIBE, WHERE DO YOU FIT WITH THE
GROUP MENTALITY VERSUS THE,
YEAH, GROUP IS FINE AS LONG AS
IT DOVETAILS WITH MY GAME?
I STICK OUT, BUT I ALWAYS
STICK OUT.
I DON'T LIKE TO STICK IN,
HONESTLY.
AND WHEN I DON'T FIT IN, I'LL BE
LIKE, WELL, FORGET THESE PEOPLE,
I'LL SIT OUT.
I'VE DONE THAT.
MOST OF MY LIFE I HAVE BEEN ON
THE OUTS, THAT'S GIVEN ME A LOT
OF SUCCESS IN MY LIFE, BECAUSE I
DON'T FOLLOW THE CROWD.
I DO MY OWN THING.
AS A ENTREPRENEUR, IT CAN BE
BENEFICIAL.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY, WHAT
KEEPS YOU WARM AT NIGHT, WHAT
MAKES YOU HAPPY IS FITTING INCH
I'M NOT MARRIED.
I DON'T HAVE KIDS.
I'M SINGLE.
YOU KNOW, YOU START THE LOOK
BACK AT YOUR ACTUAL LIFE AND
REALIZED, OKAY, SOME OF THE
PROBLEMS HAPPENING IN MY ACTUAL
LIFE ARE BEING MAGNIFIED IN THIS
GAME.
MOLLY, ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT "SURVIVOR" SEEMS TO
SHOW IS THAT IT IS VERY HARD TO
CHANGE YOUR CORE.
NOURA JUST GAVE A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF THAT.
WHAT'S IT LIKE WHEN YOU HAVE
THAT INSIGHT INTO SOMEBODY?
I THINK KNOWING THAT ABOUT
HER PERSONALITY, YOU GET IT, OH,
OKAY.
BUT THEN THE TRICKY PART IS
THESE FIRST FEW DAYS YOU'RE
REALLY SUSSING OUT HOW ARE WE
GOING TO PLAY THIS GAME, AND IN
THIS TRIBE THERE IS A HUGE TRIBE
CULTURE.
NOURA, DID YOU FEEL A
LITTLE FOR MOLLY TOO LITTLE TOO
LATE, YEAH, I GET IT, BUT WHILE
SHE WAS BEING ON THE OUTS, WE
WERE ALL IN.
YEAH, I BELIEVE THAT.
CAN YOU UNRING THE
BELL AND START FROM SCRATCH?
I MEAN, IN MY LIFE I'M ALWAYS
USED TO TREADING WATER.
I'M USED TO THAT.
SO WHEN PEOPLE ARE LIKE, NOURA,
TAKE A BREAK, RELAX, UNTIL I
FEEL LIKE I GET THAT BREAK, I'LL
TREAD WATER UNTIL I DROWN.
SO, DAN, HERE'S WHAT
I HAVE LEARNED SO FAR.
JASON GOT OFF TO A ROCKY
STARTED.
SOUNDS LIKE NOURA ALSO GOT OFF
THE A ROCKY START.
DOES THAT SPEAK TO HOW FAST THIS
GAME IS BEING PLAYED?
I THINK THE PEOPLE PLAYING
THIS GAME ARE A LITTLE LEVEL
SMARTER THAN WHO IS IRRITATING
ME TODAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT ALL THOSE OTHER MOVES THAT
TAKE YOU FURTHER IN THE GAME,
WHAT HAPPENS, YOU KNOW, AFTER
THEY LEAVE?
SO I DO THINK THIS IS GOING TO
BE MORE A CHESS PLAY THAN A
CHECKERS PLAY AT THE END OF THE
DAY.
JAMAL, IF THIS IS A
CAR RACE, DO YOU THINK THE PEDAL
IS ALREADY TO THE METTLE?
NO.
WE ARE DEFINITELY IN FIRST GEAR.
I THINK "SURVIVOR" IS A SLOW
BURN.
SEE, THE PROBLEM IS YOU CAME
THE TRIBAL FEELING COMFORTABLE
AND THAT YOU DIDN'T EVEN BRING
ANY BAGS TONIGHT.
UH, OH.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY I'M PLAYING
AT A DIFFERENT SPEED THAN YOU'RE
PLAYING AT RIGHT NOW WHEN ME AND
NOURA HAVE HAD THE BASICALLY
FIGHT FOR OUR LIVES?
JASON, YOU ARE PLAYING FROM
THE BOTTOM IN A PICTURE-PERFECT
WAY.
YOU'RE DOING EVERYTHING RIGHT.
BUT THE GAME YOU'RE PLAYING NOW
IS NOT THE GAME I HAVE TO PLAY
RIGHT NOW.
IT WILL BE, AND I KNOW THAT, BUT
IT'S NOT THE GAME I HAVE TO PLAY
RIGHT NOW.
LAUREN, WHAT GEAR DO
YOU THINK THE GAME IS IN?
I THINK THE GAME IS IN FOURTH
GEAR.
I BELIEVE THAT ONCE YOU STEP ON
THAT BEACH, YOU HAVE TO PLAY
THIS GAME WHOLE WHOLEHEARTEDLY.
AND IF YOU DON'T, THEN YOU MIGHT
BE GOING HOME.
KELLEE, BEFORE WE
VOTE, WRAP UP WHAT WE JUST
HEARD.
I THINK THERE ARE A LOT OF
CONTRADICTIONS IN HOW EVERYONE
IS FEELING ABOUT THE GROUP.
VERSUS THEIR OWN INDIVIDUAL GAME
VERSUS WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
TONIGHT.
AND IT'S REALLY SAD, BECAUSE
WE'RE ALL GOING THE WALK OUT OF
HERE, AND THIS GROUP IS GOING TO
BE GONE FOREVER.
WOW.
I CAN'T THINK OF A
BETTER WAY THE WRAP IT UP AND
LEAD US INTO THE VOTE.
JACK, YOU'RE UP.
MOLLY, IT'S TIME FOR YOUR
REIGN TO END, MY QUEEN.
IT'S TIME FOR THE MISFITS AND
THE NERDS AND THE OUTSIDERS TO
FINALLY FEEL LIKE THEY BELONG.
I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, JASON.
NOURA.
MOLLY.
JASON.
TWO VOTES JASON.
MOLLY.
TWO VOTES MOLLY.
THAT'S THREE VOTES MOLLY, TWO
VOTES JASON, ONE VOTE NOURA.
MOLLY.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES MOLLY, TWO
VOTES JASON, ONE VOTE NOURA.
SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT, MOLLY.
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DANG, THEY PLAYED HER.
MOLLY, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE, MOLLY.
WELL, THERE IS A
BRUTAL BUT EXHILARATING TRUTH
THAT ACCOMPANIES EVERY
BLINDSIDE -IF IT COULD HAPPEN
TO THEM, IT COULD HAPPEN TO YOU.
THIS TRIBE IS DEFINITELY NOT IN
FIRST GEAR.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES FROM OUR
NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," IN A GAME OF
MANIPULATION --
HOW DO YOU FEEL WORKING WITH
US?
I'M DOWN.
SUDDENLY NOW I'M A BRO.
YOU ALL ARE STUPID.
-THERE WILL BE
BLOOD.
OH, MY.
I CAN SEE MY BONE.
AND AN IMPOSSIBLE
MISSION.
TONIGHT YOU MUST SNEAK INTO
THE OTHER TRIBE'S CAMP.
I'M STUNNED, HURT,
AND FRANKLY DIZZY FROM THIS
BLINDSIDE.
I HAVE SEEN SO MANY BLINDSIDES
ON "SURVIVOR," AND YOU'RE ALWAYS
LIKE, HOW DID THEY NOT KNOW, AND
I TRULY DID NOT KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE WHERE I WENT WRONG
OR WHAT HAPPENED OR HOW THIS
TIDE TURNED.
I GUESS I GOT COCKY AND I'VE
BEEN HUMBLED.