>> 39 SEASONS, AND THIS GAME IS
FULL OF TWISTS ANDTURNS.
>> THERE ARE ENDLESS THINGS YOU
HAVE TO ADAPT TO.
>> "SURVIVOR" IS WHERE IT'S AT
NOW, BECAUSE IT'S ABOUT TO GET
CRAZY.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS A TWIST.
WHAT THESE GUYS DON'T KNOW IS
THAT SANDRA AND I ARE ACTUALLY
OUT HERE TO SHOW THE NEW KIDS
HOW IT'S DONE.
"SURVIVOR" SCHOOL IS IN SESSION.
>> Jeff: BOSTON ROB AND
SANDRA, TWO OF "SURVIVOR'S" MOST
DOMINANT WINNERS, ARE BACK.
>> I'M THE ONLY PERSON THAT'S
EVER WON TWICE.
AND I SHOULDN'T EVEN HAVE THE
SAY IT.
YOU SHOULD ALREADY KNOW THIS,
BUT I'M COMING BACK BECAUSE IT'S
ABOUT TIME THE QUEEN TEACHES
OTHERS SOME OF HER TRICKS.
>> Jeff: THEY'RE ALREADY
ESTABLISHING THEIR WORLD, BUT
THIS TIME THEY'RE NOT COMPETING.
THEY WON'T VOTE, AND THEY CANNOT
WIN THE $1 MILLION.
INSTEAD, THEY'LL SERVE AS
MENTORS TO A NEW GROUP OF
PLAYERS.
THEY'LL LIVE ON THE ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS.
IT'S A "SURVIVOR" BOOTCAMP RUN
BY TWO MASTERS OF THE GAME.
>> WE UNDERSTAND EVERY COMPONENT
OF THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: EVERY PLAYER WHO
VISITS WILL BE INSTRUCTED IN A
DIFFERENT FACET OF "SURVIVOR."
>> YOUR LESSON IS ABOUT THE ART
OF PERSUASION, CALCULATED RISK,
STAYING CALM UNDER PRESSURE.
>> YOU CAME TO WIN, RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
>> Jeff: AND THEN BE GIVEN AN
OPPORTUNITY TO TEST WHAT THEY'VE
LEARNED FOR AN A CHANCE TO WIN
AN ADVANTAGE.
>> ARE YOU CONFIDENT ENOUGH TO
TAKE THE RISK?
>> WHAT IS YOUR GUT TELLING YOU?
>> THIS IS OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: WHICH ONINGS -- ONES
WILL RISE TO THE MOMENT?
>> HERE'S THE IDOL.
IT'S GOOD FOR ONE OF YOUR NEXT
THREE TRIBAL COUNCILS.
>> Jeff: AND WHICH ONE WILL
FALL VICTIMS TO THE LESSONS
LEARNED.
>> YOU LOSE YOUR VOTE AT NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
YOU WILL NEVER MAKE THAT SAME
MISTAKE AGAIN.
>> Jeff: AND WHO WILL HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO OUTWIT,
OUTPLAY, AND OUTLAST ALL THE
REST TO CLAIM THE $1 MILLION
PRIZE?
39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR!
>> WE'RE HEADING TOWARD THIS
BEAUTIFUL ISLAND IN FIJI.
I COULDN'T BE MORE EXCITED.
I MEAN, THERE ARE NO WORDS TO
DESCRIBE.
EXCITED IS LIKE AN
UNDERSTATEMENT.
I CAN FEEL ALL THESE MIXED
EMOTIONS READY TO JUST BURST
OUT, BUT I GOT TO KEEP THEM
DOWN, BECAUSE AS SOON AS I GET
OFF THE BOAT, I HAVE TO BE CALM,
COOL, COLLECTED KARISHMA.
>> FINALLY.
>> OH, MY.
>> I'M SO EXCITED TO SEE MY
TRIBE MATES, BUT THEN I WAS
LIKE, WHERE IS JEFF PROBST, WHAT
IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
>> WOW.
>> ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
>> I LOOKED AT OUR TRIBE FLAG
AND I SAW "SURVIVOR: ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS."
I WAS LIKE, OH,.
NO WHEN PEOPLE TALK ABOUT IDOLS
IN GENERAL, IT'S ALREADY
PARANOIA, BUT THAT'S WHAT OUR
SEASON THEME IS REVOLVING
AROUND?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THAT MEANS.
MY MIND IS BLOWN RIGHT NOW.
>> CHECK IT OUT.
>> I THINK ON TOP OF THINGS.
>> I'M FROM INDIA.
>> I'M MOAN.
>> I PLAYED HOCKEY A LONG TIME
AGO.
I PLAYED WITH THE RANGERS AND
THE KINGS A LONG TIME AGO.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> DO YOU PLAY SPORTS IN.
>> I PLAYED BASKETBALL.
>> IN COLLEGE, RIGHT?
I CAN TELL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WE HAVE AN OLYMPIC SWIMMER?
>> I AM A THREE-TIME OLYMPIC
SWIMMER, AND I AM A COMPETITOR.
IT'S BASICALLY EMBEDDED WITHIN
MY D.N.A. BECAUSE I'VE BEEN A
COMPETITIVE SWIMMER MY WHOLE
LIFE.
>> DO YOU PLAY BASEBALL?
>> NEW YORK BUT I LOVE BASEBALL.
>> I STEPPED AWAY FROM THE SPORT
A YEAR AND A HALF AGO.
IT WAS A VERY HARD TRANSITION.
YOU'RE AT THE OLYMPICS AND
YOU'RE AT SUCH A HIGH NOTE.
YOU WONDER, WLL I EVER GET
THERE AGAIN?
THIS GAME HAS HONESTLY MADE ME
AS EXCITED AS I WAS FOR THE
OLYMPICS.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD FEEL
THAT AGAIN.
>> I PLAY VIOLIN AND PIANO.
>> I PLAY THE FLUTE.
>> NO WAY.
>> ARE WE THE SAME?
>> WE ARE HAVING A GOOD TIME,
WHICH IS SUPER COOL, BECAUSE I
LITERALLY NEEDED SOME HAPPINESS
IN MY LIFE.
I WENT INTO THE MILITARY AT 18.
I PLAYED BASKETBALL FOR THE AIR
FORCE TEAM.
AND ABOUT THREE YEARS NEW YORK I
DEVELOPED A BRAIN TUMOR.
AS IT GREW, IT GORS WORSE.
AND AT ONE POINT I COULDN'T
WALK.
I COULDN'T TALK.
I ALMOST DIED.
>> WOW.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
WE TRIED SOME MEDICATION, AND I
WAS REALLY LUCKY, BECAUSE RIGHT
NOW THE TUMOR IS COMPLETELY
GONE.
SO IT'S LIKE NEW LIFE.
>> THIS IS OUR HOME.
>> THAT'S WHY I'M HERE NOW.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING DECENT.
I WANT TO BE THE SOLE SURVIVOR.
I WANT TO BE THE S-O-U-L
SURVIVOR.
IT'S GO.
>> SOMETHING IS WEIRD.
NO SCRAMBLING.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
>> THE THEME OF THE SEASON IS
"ISLAND OF THE IDOLS," WHICH
REALLY MAKES YOUR MIND GO WILD.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> I HAVE NEVER TOUCHED A BUFF
BEFORE.
>> THIS IS UNREAL.
>> I'M THINKING, ARE THERE IDOLS
ON THIS ISLAND?
IS THERE ANOTHER ISLAND THAT HAS
TONS OF IDOLS?
SO IT'S SURPRISING.
IT'S SHOCKING.
AND IT'S COOL.
I'M LAUREN, EVERYBODY.
>> HI, LAUREN.
>> I'M SO EXCITED TO MEET ALL OF
YOU GUYS.
>> MY NAME IS JAMAL.
VERY NICE THE MEET ALL OF YOU
ALL.
>> I'M TOMMY SHEEHAN FROM LONG
ISLAND, NEW YORK.
I'M A FURTH GRADE TEACHER.
>> OH, AWESOME.
>> I TEACH THE LITTLE GUYS.
>> EVERYONE ON OUR TRIBE SEEMS
SMART AND BRIGHT AND SOCIAL.
EVERYONE IS EXCITED TO BE HERE,
WHICH I THINK IS A POSITIVE
THING.
WE'RE GOING TO GET TO WORK.
>> DOES ANYBODY HAVE ANY
PREFERENCES AS TO WHAT THEY
MIGHT WANT TO DO FIRST?
>> DOES ANYONE KNOW HOW TO BUILD
A SHELT CENTER -- SHELLER?
>> WHO HAS A CONSTRUCTION
BACKGROUND?
>> COMING INTO THE GAME, I AM
WORRIED ABOUT MY AGE BECAUSE OF
THE STIGMA OF THE OLDER PERSON,
ESPECIALLY THE OLDER WOMAN.
I HAVE STARTED FIRE WITH BAMBOO.
THERE IS NO BETTER WAY TO MAKE
AN IMPACT IN THIS GAME THAN TO
MAKE FIRE.
>> I THINK SUPER MOM CAN DO IT.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
>> I AM A LIFEGUARD.
I HAVE 130 LIFEGUARDS WORKING
FOR ME.
>> READY?
>> HOLD YOUR HAND ON THE OTHER
SIDE.
>> COME ON.
>> YES, JANET!
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> IT'S BEEN MY EXPERIENCE IN
LIFE THAT IF YOU PROVE WHO YOU
ARE, PEOPLE DON'T CARE WHAT YOUR
GENDER, WHAT YOUR AGE IS.
>> WE GOT SMOKE!
IF YOU PROVE WHO YOU ARE, THEN
YOU CAN BECOME PART OF THEM.
>> GIVE ME PALM FRONDS.
>> YES!
>> KEEP GOING.
>> GET DOWN, GET DOWN.
>> WE GOT FIRE!
>> IT WAS REALLY COOL.
TO BREAK THE MOLD ON THE OLDER
WOMAN.
>> YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
>> I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT THOSE GUYS.
I SHOWED MY TRIBE THAT I HAD A
SPECIAL SET OF SKILLS, AND I
KNEW HOW TO USE THEM.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> HE NEEDS ONE OF THOSE, WHAT'S
IT CALLED?
HE'S A BEAST ON THAT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WHY DON'T YOU CUT DOWN A
TREE.
>> I'M THE FIRST MONG PERSON TO
BE CAST ON "SURVIVOR."
WE CAME OVER AS REFUGEES AFTER
THE VIETNAM WAR.
I GREW UP LOW INCOME.
I WAS FIRST IN MY FAMILY TO GO
TO AN INSTITUTION LIKE STANFORD.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN THAT TIME
OF PERSON THAT DOES THE WORK.
>> ARE YOU FRESH OUT OF SCHOOL?
>> NEW YORK I MAY IN THE LOOK
IT, BUT I'M 27.
>> I GUESS THE GUY THAT TOTALLY
SURPRISED ME IS VINCE.
VINCE DEFINITELY KNEW WHAT HE
WAS DOING.
HE'S EXCELLENT.
>> I DO STUFF LIKE THIS AT HOME.
LIKE BEING OUT IN THE WILD, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE I LIVE ON A FARM.
>> ELAINE, SHE'S NOT ALL PRISSY
WITH THE DRESS ON AND ALL THAT
KIND OF STUFF.
SHE'S GOT THE WORK BOOTS ON AND
THE HAT AND THE WHOLE BIT.
WE HIT IT OFF RIGHT AWAY.
>> HOW ARE YOU ALL FEELING ABOUT
THE GROUP?
>> A LOT OF ENERGY, A LOT OF
ENERGY.
>> JUST NERVOUS TO GET US TO THE
MERGE AS A TEAM.
WE JUST DON'T WANT TO LOSE
CHALLENGES.
THAT'S WHEN TEAMS START TO FALL
APART.
IT ISN'T ALWAYS THE BEST
ATHLETES.
IT'S WORKING TOGETHER.
>> WHEN I PLAYED IN THE NHL, I
WAS A CAPTAIN FOR EVERY TEAM I
PLAYED ON.
IF YOU'RE ON A TEAM AND YOU WANT
TO WIN, IT ISN'T ALL YOUR
PHYSICAL STRENGTH.
WAYNE GRETZKY WASN'T THE BIGGEST
GUY BUT PROBABLY THE BEST PLAYER
TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> I LIKE YOUR EARRING.
I LIKE YOU VIBE.
>> MY WHOLE WORLD IS ALL ABOUT
DISCIPLINE AND HARD WORK.
AND ELAINE AND I AND VIN, I
THINK WE'RE ALL THINKING THE
SAME WAY.
>> TOM AND ELAINE HAVE GONZALEZ
FOR A WHILE.
>> AND VIN.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO IN.
>> IF THIS IS WHAT THEY WANT TO
DO, OKAY.
>> AT THIS POINT, WE HAVE TO BE
STRONG.
THERE'S THREE PEOPLE MIS,
ELAINE, TOM, AND VIN.
THEY JUST LEFT.
SO EVERYBODY AT CAMP SAYS,
SEVEN, THREE, WE'RE GOOD.
LET'S GET BACK THE WORK.
AND THOSE THREE IMMEDIATELY
PAINTED A TARGET ON THEIR BACKS.
>> BRING 'EM IN AND WE'LL SEE
WHAT WE GOT.
>> THAT'S NICE.
I LIKE THIS.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S NICE.
>> WOW.
>> DUDE.
>> THE VOKAI TRIBE IS DOING
AWESOME.
IT COULD NOT BE GOING MORE WELL.
WE CHECK ALL THE BOXES.
WE HAVE A SHELTER.
WE HAVE FIRE, GOOD MORALE, HIGH
SPIRITS, FUN.
WE'RE CHILLING.
>> HEY.
>> I'M THINKING TO MYSELF, THIS
SEASON IS "ISLAND OF THE IDOLS,"
SO YOU GOT TO BE AN IDIOT NOT TO
ACTUALLY LOOK FOR AN IDOL.
>> GUYS, WHERE DID JASON GO?
>> THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
>> MOLLY, YOU'RE VERY
PERCEPTIVE.
>> SOMETHING IS HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
>> JASON JUST DISAPPEARED.
IT WAS THE CLICHEST "SURVIVOR"
MISTAKE OF SEARCHING FOR AN IDOL
ON DAY ONE, SO WHEN I NOTICED
THAT JASON IS GONE, THE GOAL IS
TO SAY, WHERE'S JASON.
>> I LOOK AT MY JOB AS THOUGH I
PLAY "SURVIVOR" EVERY DAY.
I'M AN ACCOUNT MANAGER.
I RUN A TALENT MANAGEMENT
COMPANY IN HOLLYWOOD.
I THINK WORKING WITH ACTORS IS
VERY SIMILAR TO "SURVIVOR,"
BECAUSE I HAVE TO GET A BUNCH OF
VERY PASSIONATE AGGRESSIVE
PEOPLE THE MAKE THE DECISIONS
THAT I REALLY DO BELIEVE ARE THE
BEST DECISIONS FOR THEM AND FOR
ME, SO THERE WAS COMPLETE
STRATEGY IN NOTICING THAT JASON
HAD JUST WANDERED OFF.
WHY WOULD ANYONE DO THAT?
YOU CAN'T DISAPPEAR DAY ONE.
>> NO, I AGREE.
>> ALL I WANTED WAS A FIRST VOTE
TO BE CREATED THAT ISN'T ME.
AN I GOT TO TELL YOU, IT WAS
JOYOUS TO WATCH.
OH, HE'S DONE.
IT'S OVER.
SO IT IS IMPOSSIBLE NOW FOR
JASON TO DIG HIMSELF OUT OF THAT
GRAVE.
>> IT'S LIKE A GIANT CLAM.
>> WOW.
I'M 23 YEARS OLD, WHICH MAKES ME
THE YOUNGEST PERSON ON THE
TRIBE.
I THINK THAT'S GOOD.
I THINK MY PLAYFUL ATTITUDE WILL
BE WITHOUT A DOUBT MY BIGGEST
ASSET.
>> OH, MY GOSH, THEY'RE GOING TO
BE SO STOKED WHEN THIS COMES IN.
>> THE GOAL IS I WANT EVERYONE
TO WANT TO HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
WITH ME.
BUT I NEED TO FIND A PERSON, AND
PERSON NUMBER ONE IS TOMMY.
WE'RE THE TWO YOUNG DUDES.
WE'RE VERY SIMILAR, AND THAT'S
AN OBVIOUS FREAKING PAIRING.
>> MY BEST FRIEND LIVES IN
VIRGINIA.
YOU COME VISIT ME AND I'LL GO
VISIT YOU AND I'LL TEACH YOU HOW
THE SURF.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AS A FOURTH GRADE TEACHER, MY
JOB IS TO MAKE SURE EVERYONE
FEELS COMFORTABLE AROUND ME.
IN THIS GAME, I'M DOING THE SAME
THING.
>> MY FAVORITE TEACHER OF ALL
TIME WAS MY FOURTH GRADE
TEACHER.
>> REALLY?
MINE TOO.
MY FOURTH GRADE TEACHER CHANGED
MY LIFE.
>> MY STRATEGY IS TO CONNECT
WITH PEOPLE IN ONE-ON-ONE
CONVERSATIONS AND GET TO KNOW
WHO THEY ARE.
>> I'M 26.
I'VE BEEN DATING MY GIRLFRIEND
FOR THREE YEARS.
>> AWESOME.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> I'M GOING TO PROPOSE.
I BOUGHT THE RING.
>> YOU ARE?
OH.
>> IT'S GREAT.
>> AND IT'S REALLY WORKING.
EVERYONE HAS BEEN COMING UP TO
ME.
I THINK I DID A GREAT JOB OF
CONNECTING WITH PEOPLE ONE ON
ONE, AN I'M BUILDING A LOT OF
ALLIANCES.
>> WE MEAD PEOPLE WE CAN TRUST.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I REALLY LIKE JAMAL A LOT.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL ALREADY I CAN SEE THE COR
GROUP FORMED WHICH IS GREAT,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE THE
PERSON ON THE OUTS.
WE KIND OF JUST CLICKED.
WE WANT TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
WE NEED TO GET RID OF THE DRAMA.
WE NEED TO GET RID OF THE
SLIMINESS.
THIS IS A TRIBE GAME.
LET'S MAKE THIS EASY AND JASON
IS THE PERSON WHO IS RUNNING
AROUND TRYING TO DO SOMETHING
FOR HIMSELF.
IT'S A LITTLE SHADY TO EVERYONE
ELSE.
IT RUBBED PEOPLE THE WRONG WAY.
>> SO JASON.
>> IT'S ANNOYING AND UPSETTING
AND WHATEVER, BUT I'M GRATEFUL
FOR IT BECAUSE IT'S THE MOST
UNIFYING THING.
WE ALL AGREE ABOUT THIS.
>> THEY THINK YOU HAVE AN IDOL.
>> WHY DO THEY THINK THAT?
>> I REALLY DON'T.
WE'VE BEEN OUT HERE FOR LIKE AN
HOUR.
HOW WOULD I FIND AN IDOL.
>> I AM THINKING, I LIKE THE GUY
AND I WANT THE WORK WITH HIM.
HE ALSO FEELS FAMILIAR TO ME AND
HE REMINDS ME OF AN EX-BOYFRIEND
THAT I FEEL IS AN AUTHENTIC GOOD
GUY I CAN TRUST.
I FELT LIKE THAT, AND I WANT TO
WORK WITH THAT.
SO WHAT'S THE FIRST THING I DO.
I GO TO HIM AND TELL HIM.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
JUST TO LET YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
PERCEPTION IS REALITY.
>> SHE SAYS, HEY, I WANT TO GIVE
YOU A HEADS UP, THERE'S TALK AND
CHATTER THAT I LEFT CAMP FOR 30
OR 40 MINUTES.
SO I'M CONCERNED.
IS THERE ANY PERSON THAT WOULD
BE MORE OF A LIABILITY AND
DISTRUSTFUL THAN SOMEBODY THAT
WOULD GO SEARCH FOR THE HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL DAY ONE?
I AM MORTIFIED.
AM I GOING TO BE THE FIRST ONE
OUT?
THAT IS MY NIGHTMARE.
>> REMIND ME TO PUT MY DRAWERS
ON.
IF NOT I'LL GO COMMANDO.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> I'LL BE IN THE FREE WORLD.
I HAVE BEEN DIFFERENT MY WHOLE
LIFE, AND I GOT PICKED ON A LOT,
SO I USE HUMOR TO DEFLECT.
I MAKE 'EM LAUGH.
THAT WAY THEY'RE LAUGHING WITH
ME AND IN THE AT ME.
>> YOU PUT SOME CUMIN?
WHAT IS THAT?
>> CONSUME SEASON LIKE A
YELLOW-REDDISH SPICE THAT YOU
PUT IN FOOD.
YOU PUT IT ON WHATEVER YOU WANT,
A COCONUT?
>> I AIN'T NEVER HEARD THAT.
>> THE LIMO DROPPED HER OFF.
>> LIKE GREY POUPON.
>> GREY POUPON.
>> WE DON'T HAVE THAT.
>> THAT'S MUSTARD.
>> THAT'S WHAT CUMIN IS.
>> I TRY TO BE THE MOST
OBSERVANT IN THIS GAME, AND
LOOKING AROUND AT THE OTHER
PLAYERS, I LIKE THE GIRLS,
BECAUSE IT SEEMS AS THOUGH ALL
FOUR OF THE OTHER WOMEN FEEL
THAT THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE
SUBSERVIENT AND THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO DO WHAT PEOPLE EXPECT
THEM TO DO.
THEY'RE GOING TO DO WHAT MOST
BENEFITS THEM.
>> DON'T SLAM INTO THE TREE.
AND IN THIS MOMENT, WHAT
BENEFITS ALL THE GIRLS IS
FORMING A WOMEN'S ALLIANCE.
>> I'M DOWN FOR DOING A GIRL'S
THING.
>> PERFECT.
>> I'M ALL ABOUT THE GIRL POWER.
WE NEED TO HAVE EACH OTHER'S
BACKS.
>> I'M TIRED OF GIRLS GOING OUT
FIRST.
WHAT IS THAT?
WHY IS THAT?
>> KEEPING THE WOMEN STRONG IS
SUPER IMPORTANT.
>> LET'S GRAB A GUY.
>> I KNOW PEOPLE THINK ELAINE,
TOM, AND VINCE ARE TOGETHER, AND
BECAUSE OF THAT, ELAINE COULD
POSSIBLY BE IN TROUBLE.
>> THEY WAS ALREADY TALKING
TRASH, HUH?
>> EVERYBODY LOOKED UP AND
COUNTED IN THEIR HEAD, 7-3.
IT'S JUST LIKE AN EASY WAY TO
MAKE A TARGET.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WELL, WE WAS CUTTING DOWN
TREES.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
THAT GOT ME A LITTLE WORRIED.
WHEN YOU FIRST HEAR ANYBODY SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR NAME, IT
MAKE YOUR HEART RACE.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR NAME TO COME
UP IN "SURVIVOR" EVER AT ALL.
SO I NEED TO START PLAYING A
LITTLE BETTER GAME, BECAUSE I'M
NOT OKAY WITH GOING HOME.
>> WHAT DO YOU NEED ME TO DO?
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
IT'S A MASSAGE PARLOR.
>> OH, DAN IS SO GOOD.
>> YOU KNOW, IN THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR," THERE IS A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT YOU'RE LIVING WITH
FOR THE FIRST TIME, LIVING WITH
ANYONE IS HARD, AND I'M A
GERMOPHOBE WHEN IT COMES TO
OTHER PEOPLE'S GROSSNESS.
>> RIGHT HERE?
>> OH, MY GOD.
A COMBINATION OF HUMAN AND
SLIGHTLY MORE ELEVATED.
IF IT GETS TOO THE HEAVY, LET ME
KNOW.
>> ARE YOU SWEATING ON MY LEG?
>> I DO GET ANNOYED WITH DAN,
BECAUSE DAN IS A REALLY TOUCHY
PERSON.
REMAKES ME FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
I DON'T THINK HE REALIZES IT.
HIS LACK OF SPATIAL AWARENESS,
FOR ME BEING A GERMOPHOBE, BUT
ALSO A GIRL, I'M LIKE, DAN, I
DON'T WANT YOUR HEAD ON MY LEG.
LIKE THAT'S JUST TOO MUCH.
LIKE I DON'T WANT YOUR SWEATY
BODY ON ME AT ALL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT 2012 SUPER BOWL WHERE THE
GIANTS CAME BECOME AND BEAT THE
PATRIOTS.
>> I WAS TAKEN ABACK BY DAN AT
FIRST.
HE'S REALLY TOUCHY.
DAN DOES NOT KNOW PERSONAL
SPACE.
>> DAN HAS BEEN MAKING ME FEEL
UNCOMFORTABLE.
I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE ANY
PROBLEMS.
I THINK DAN IS AN EASIER PERSON
TO HAVE ON YOUR SIDE.
I'M TRYING TO BE DELICATE,
BECAUSE IT IS A GAME, AND I
DON'T WANT THE RUFFLE FEATHERS
FOR AS LONG AS I POSSIBLY CAN.
IF YOU GET YOURSELF INTO A HOLE
EARLY, IT'S HARD THE CLIMB OUT
OF IT.
DAN IS VERY TOUCHY.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S LIKE, A LOT.
>> IT'S TOO MUCH FOR ME.
>> IT'S TOO MUCH FOR MOLLY, TOO.
>> THE GIRLS ARE VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE WITH DAN'S
PHYSICALITY WITH THEM.
I HAVE LEARNED AS A WOMAN, YOU
NEED TO SAY WHAT YOU THINK.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE TOTALLY
RECOGNIZED LIKE LOVE LANGUAGE IS
YOUR WAY OF SHOWING THAT YOU
CARE, SO FOR ME, I'M LIKE, I'M
JUST LIKE... YOU KNOW?
I'M NOT TRYING TO REJECT, THAT I
JUST COME FROM SUCH A DIFFERENT
PLACE.
>> I HAVE TO BE OPEN TO I'M
NOT -- I HAVE TO BE, OH, GOD SHE
DOESN'T LIKE ME BECAUSE I CAN'T
HUGGER THE WAY JANET CAN.
I GET IT.
>> THAT'S NOT -- HOPEFULLY...
WE'RE PLAYING "SURVIVOR" WHERE
IT'S ABOUT CONNECTING, BUT DAN
BEING A TOUCHY PERSON, IT'S A
LOT.
WE KIND OF TALKED ABOUT IT AND
WE HAD A REALLY GOOD
CONVERSATION, BUT I FEEL LIKE
DAN'S LACK OF SPATIAL AWARENESS
IS GOING TO HURT HIM IN THE
GAME.
>> HOW YOU DOING, GIRL?
>> I'M DOING ALL RIGHT.
>> ARE YOU FEELING HUNGRY OR
ANYTHING?
>> NOT REALLY.
I GOT A LOT OF INSULATION.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
US BIGGER PEOPLE, WE'RE PROBABLY
GOING THE LAST.
HE'S ALREADY STARVING TO DEATH.
I SEE HIS BACKBONE.
WHEN YOU PASS OUT, WE'LL GET A
WOMAN OVER THERE TO GIVE YOU
MOUTH TO MOUTH.
>> THE BIGGEST TIP I GIVE TO
OTHER POKER PLAYERS IS SIT DOWN
AND WATCH.
WATCH WHAT OTHER PLAYERS ARE
BRINGING TO THE GAME.
I CAN SEE THAT ELAINE IS
EXTREMELY LIKABLE.
SHE'S SUPER FUN.
I LIKE ELAINE.
THAT COULD BE DANGEROUS.
SOMEONE LIKE ELAINE FROM A TOWN
FROM THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
KENTUCKY WHO HAS HAD HARDSHIP
HER WHO LIFE AND WHO WORKS IN A
FACTORY, SOUNDS LIKE A CLEAR
WINNER TO ME.
>> I LIKE YOU, FROM FIRST TIME I
SEEN YOU, I KNOW YOU'RE SOLID.
IF SHE'S GOTTEN THAT FAR WITH
THAT STORY, THEY'LL AWARD HER
THAT $1 MILLION.
LIKE MYSELF, YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
A LOT.
I'VE WITHIN IN YOUR EYE, WE
UNDERSTAND THE STRUGGLE.
SO SHE'S SOMEBODY I WANT TO GET
RID OF AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR ME TO PUT OUT
GOOD VIBES, GOOD VIBE RON, TO
MAKE ELAINE FEEL SAFE.
IF SOMEBODY IS THROWING YOUR
NAME OUT, THERE I'LL LET YOU
KNOW ON THE LOW.
AND WE'LL JUST TALK.
>> OKAY.
AS LONG AS YOU STAY REAL WITH
ME, I'LL STAY REAL WITH YOU.
I TRUST YOU 100%.
>> I LITERALLY KNEW FROM THE
MINUTE THAT I HAD THE
CONVERSATION WITH RONNIE, I KNEW
THAT ME AND HIM WAS LIKE THIS.
I KNEW IT IN MY GUT.
HE IS A WEASEL, AND HE'S
SOMEBODY WHO I FIND SHADY.
I DON'T TRUST RONNIE.
SO ME HE HAS TO GO.
>> I'M TRYING TO PLAY A SOLID
GAME AND RIDE TO THE END WITH
PEOPLE I TRUST.
>> IT'S GAME TIME, YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
GUNS DRAWN.
LET'S FIND OUT.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> I'M GETTING MY FIRST LOOK AT
THE TWO TRIBES.
>> Jeff: WELCOME.
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME OFFICIALLY WELCOME YOU TO
THE 39th SEASON OF
"SURVIVOR: ISLAND OF THE IDOLS."
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
>> IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING.
>> Jeff: ELAINE, WHAT HAVE YOU
BEEN WAITING ON?
>> WELL, WE KIND OF WAS A LITTLE
MAD BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T MEET US
ON DAY ONE.
>> Jeff: WERE YOU FEELINGS
HURT?
>> KIND OF.
BASICALLY WE THOUGHT YOU QUIT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jeff: CHELSEA, OFTEN ON
"SURVIVOR" THERE IS SOME SORT OF
INFORMATION OFF THE TOP THAT
SAYS, HERE'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE THAT THIS SEASON.
SO HOW DOES IT CHANGE THOSE
FIRST 48 HOURS THAT YOU'VE
EXPERIENCED?
>> WHEN I SAY "ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS," I WENT, WHAT IS THIS?
YOU KNOW, JUST THE WORD "IDOL,"
THAT CREATES PARANOIA, SO WE
HAVE A WHOLE THEME AROUND THAT
NOW, AND NO ONE KNOWS WHAT THAT
MEANS.
BUT WE'RE SO READY.
THERE IS SO MUCH UNISON RIGHT
NOW, AND YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO WORK HARD OVER THERE.
>> WE ALWAYS WORK HARD, THOUGH.
>> Jeff: I THINK IT'S TIME TO
GET TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
>> 'D LIKE THAT.
>> Jeff: FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE
YOU'RE GOING TO RACE UP AND DOWN
AN OBSTACLE.
YOU'LL THEN DROP A BRIDGE AND
CLIMB TO THE TOP OF THE TOWER
WHERE YOU MUST SOLVE A MASSIVE
VILLAGE PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY.
THIS IS THE IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> WHOA.
>> Jeff: THIS IS WHAT YOU
COVET.
WITH THIS IN YOUR POSSESSION,
YOU ARE SAFE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS."
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
NOT ONLY DOES THIS KEEP YOUR
CAMPFIRE GOING, THIS IS WHAT YOU
NEED TO MASTER IN CASE YOU ARE
LUCKY ENOUGH TO MAKE IT TO THE
FINAL FOUR FIRE-MAKING
CHALLENGE.
A LOT AT STAKE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE AN WE'LL GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HOAR WE GO, FOR REWARD AND
IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST CHALLENGE OUT OF THE GATE,
HIT THAT NET HARD.
BOTH TRIBES MOVING QUICKLY UP
THE NET.
GOT THE MAKE YOUR WAY DOWN THE
SLIDE.
YOU GOT TO GET EVERYBODY OVER.
THIS IS A BRUTAL FIRST
CHALLENGE.
THAT'S HOW YOU THIS IT ON
"SURVIVOR".
>> LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: HERE COMES NOURA.
JANET FACE FIRST.
YOU GOT TO GET ON YOUR MAT.
YOU'RE GOOD LOCALLY DENSE FOG.
YOU'RE GOOD, LAIRO.
YOU'RE GOOD, VOKAI.
YOU GOT TO UNTIE IT AND PILL.
DEAN JUST SHORT WITH HIS FIRST
TOSS.
>> ALL RIGHT, JANET.
>> Jeff: JANET WITH A FACE
FULL OF SAND HOOKS THE ROPE.
START PULLING.
YOU'RE GOOD.
PULL!
TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT TO LIFT
THOSE LOGS.
>> PULL!
PULL!
>> Jeff: IT IS VOKAI IN THE
EARLY LEAD.
A LOT OF TEAM WORK.
VOKAI EXTENDING THEIR LEAD.
>> GO, GO GO,.
>> Jeff: RON IS IN FOR LAIRO.
RONNIE'S GOT IT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
START PULLING.
LET'S GO.
LAIRO, PICK IT UP.
NOW VOKAI MAKING A HUMAN LADDER.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, PULL!
ONE, TWO, THREE, PULL!
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD LAIRO.
>> BOYS ON THE BOTTOM, BOYS ON
THE BOTTOM.
>> Jeff: DAN ON THE BOSTON UM.
JASON.
CAN HE REACH?
HERE COMES JACK.
JACK'S GOT IT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
JACK HAS DROPPED THE ROPE.
GOT ANOTHER LADDER FORMING WITH
TOM AND AARON AND RONNIE.
HERE COMES DEAN.
DEEP STRUGGLING TO GET IT.
HE'S GOT IT.
NOW YOU GOT TO GET EVERYBODY UP.
JAMAL HAS PEOPLE ON HIS
SHOULDERS.
GREAT TEAMWORK BY BOTH TRIBES.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT IN YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
EVERYBODY WORKING TOGETHER.
LAUREN IS UP.
ELAINE IS UP.
IT IS NOW LAIRO WITH A LOT OF
MOMENTUM.
>> JACK GOING BACK DOWN.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S A HERO MOVE RIGHT THERE.
LAIRO, YOU'RE GOOD.
THREE PEOPLE ON THE PUZZLE.
LAIRO IN THE LEAD.
JACK HAS BEEN A WORKHORSE IN
THIS CHALLENGE HELPING TOMMY.
HERE COMES JAMAL.
AND THEY'VE GOT IT.
GREAT TEAMWORK!
IT IS DEAN VINCE AND CHELSEA ON
THE PUZZLE FOR LAIRO.
IT IS MOLLY, LAUREN AND JAMAL ON
THE PUZZLE FOR VOKAI.
YOU ARE BUILDING A VILLAGE ONE
HUT AT A TIME IN ORDER.
VOKAI WITH THEIR FIRST PIECE.
LAIRO HAD A NICE EARLY LEAD, BUT
THAT IS GONE.
>> THIS ONE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I NEED.
THAT'S WHAT I NEED.
>> THAT'S THE ONE.
>> THERE.
>> Jeff: VOKAI HAS THEIR THIRD
PIECE.
LAIRO HAS THEIR FIRST PIECE.
>> LOOK AT THOSE.
>> Jeff: VOKAI LOOKING FOR
THAT ROOF TO COMPLETE THE FIRST
SECTION-OF-PUZZLE.
>> THAT'S IT.
RIGHT HERE.
LIKE THIS.
>> Jeff: VOKAI HAS FIRST
SECTION OF THEIR PUZZLE
COMPLETED.
ONE HUT BUILT.
SIX TO GO.
LAIRO STILL WORKING.
>> WE'RE STILL IN THIS.
LET'S GO!
>> THIS ONE OVER HERE.
>> YEP.
>> THREE FACING THAT WAY.
>> YEAH, BABY.
>> Jeff: HERE COMES THE SECOND
ROOF FOR VOKAI, EXTENDING THEIR
LEAD.
>> THERE YOU GO, BABY.
>> Jeff: THAT'S TWO FOR VOKAI.
>> COME ON, Y'ALL.
>> Jeff: LAIRO HAS THEIR FIRST
HUT BUILT.
>> THAT'S IT.
JAMAL EXHAUSTED.
THESE PIECES ARE VERY HEAVY.
ANOTHER PIECE FOR VOKAI.
>> THERE'S A B.
ON THIS SIDE IN
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> I THINK THE SECOND ONE IS
WRONG.
>> Jeff: DEAN, CHELSEA, AND
DAN ARE AT A STANDSTILL.
>> THESE TWO AREN'T FIT, YOU
GUYS.
>> Jeff: THERE IS ONLY ONE
PIECE LEFT FOR LAIRO WITH THIS
SECTION.
THEY HAVE THREE HUTS LEFT.
>> COULD THIS PIECE BE IN THE
WRONG SPOT.
>> Jeff: LAIRO STARTING OVER
ON THEIR SECOND HUT.
>> NOT YET, NOT YET, NOT YET.
>> Jeff: VOKAI WITH ANOTHER
HUT.
THEY'RE DOWN TO TWO LEFT.
>> SOMETHING IS OFF.
>> Jeff: LAIRO IS DEAD IN THE
WATER AS VOKAI CONTINUES TO INCH
TOWARD VICTORY.
ONE HUT AT A TIME.
>> LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE BIGGEST
BLOWOUTS INFORMATION A FIRST
CHALLENGE ON "SURVIVOR."
IT IS NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> JEFF?
VOKAI WINS IMMUNITY AND REWARD.
A HUGE OPENING VICTORY BY VOKAI,
SENDING LAIRO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
VOKAI, GREAT WORK AS A TRIPE
FROM START THE FINISH IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
NICE JOB.
FLINT.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM VOKAI.
GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
AND ENJOY THE NIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
LAIRO, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
BEFORE I SEND YOU BACK TO CAMP,
ONE MORE THING.
"ISLAND OF THE IDOLS" DOES
EXIST, AND ONE OF YOU IS ABOUT
TO BE THE FIRST PERSON TO
EXPERIENCE IT.
ALL TEN OF YOUR NAMES ARE IN
THIS BAG.
THE ONE DRAWN WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON TO GO TO "ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS."
WHO WANTS THE DRAW?
>> GO AHEAD.
>> Jeff: WHATEVER YOU PULL
OUT, THAT PERSON IS GOING TO
"ISLAND OF THE IDOLS."
>> WE'RE A TEAM, GUYS.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH, WHAT'S THE
REACTION?
>> YOU KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE
HARD BEING OUT THERE ALONE.
BUT I KNOW I CAN ABSOLUTELY
HANDLE IT.
ELIZABETH, YOU WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON GOING TO "ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS."
YOU WILL RETURN BACK TO YOUR
CAMP.
YOU WILL BE GOING THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT.
HEAD OUT.
THE BOAT IS WAITING FOR YOU.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU WHEN YOU GET
BACK.
>> YEP.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, LAIRO,
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> I AM FREAKING OUT.
I DON'T WANT TO GO, BECAUSE ME
GOING TO "ISLAND OF THE IDOLS"
PUTS TARGET ON MY BACK, AND ON
TOP OF, THAT I'M MISSING
CRITICALLY IMPORTANT
STRATEGIZING TIME WITH THE
TRIBE, AND I DON'T THINK
"SURVIVOR" GODS ARE GOING TO
MAKE IT EASY, SO IT'S SCARY, AN
I'M LIKE, WHAT'S IN STORE FOR
ME.
>> "ISLAND OF THE IDOLS."
I'M TRYING THE STAY OPTIMISTIC
HERE.
THIS BEACH IS ONE OF THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL PLACES I HAVE EVER
SEEN.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
THE WALK INTO.
>> WHERE AM I?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> THAT IS SO COOL.
I SEE THESE TWO MASSIVE STATUES.
NO WAY.
AND I'M LIKE, BOSTON ROB AND
SANDRA, TWO OF THE BEST PLAYERS
TO EVER PLAY THIS GAME.
>> WELCOME.
>> WHAT?
NO WAY!
AND THEN OUT COMES WALKING
BOSTON ROB AND SANDRA.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
BOSTON ROB
>> REALLY GOOD NOW.
I WAS SO EXCITED, SURPRISED,
JUST IN SAW, BECAUSE THEY ARE
IDOLS.
THEY ARE "SURVIVOR" IDOLS.
>> COME ON UP AND WE'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, THE OATH OF
THE IDOL, WE ARE THE SURVIVOR
IDOL.
WE'RE NOT COMPETEING.
WE DO NOT VOTE, WE CANNOT WIN
THE $1 MILLION PRIZE.
OUR JOB IS TO MENTOR YOU IN THE
GAME OF "SURVIVOR" AND THEN
OFFER YOU A CHANCE TO TEST WHAT
YOU HAVE LEARNED.
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS HERE IS
INTENDED TO MAKE YOU A BETTER
SURVIVOR PLAYER.
YOU CAN THINK OF THIS PLACE AS A
"SURVIVOR" BOOTCAMP.
SANDRA AND I HAVE A PRETTY
EXTENSIVE "SURVIVOR" RESUME.
WE'VE PLAYED OVER 200 DAYS,
SEVEN SEASONS.
>> HE'S A STUPID ASS.
>> WE'VE BOTH WON THE GAME.
>> THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR:
REDEMPTION ISLAND."
>> WE'VE ALSO LOST THE GAME.
>> DON'T DO IT, JEFF.
DON'T DO IT, JEFF.
>> WE UNDERSTAND EVERY COMPONENT
OF THIS GAME.
YOU ARE HERE TO GET AS MUCH
KNOWLEDGE AS YOU CAN FROM US AND
USE IT AS YOUR WILL.
>> I LITERALLY HAVE THE CHILLS
RIGHT NOW.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> WHOEVER COMES TO ISLAND OF
THE IDOLLING WE WILL SIT DOWN
AND TALK TO THEM, ASK THEM ABOUT
THEIR "SURVIVOR" EXPERIENCE THUS
FAR.
THEN GIVE IDEAS AND STRATEGY TO
HELP THEM FURTHER THEIR GAME.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE IN A
GOOD ALLIANCE.
>> I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT ABOUT SHELTER?
>> WE HAVE A SHELTER.
WE HAVE NO FIRE.
WE CAN'T COOK THE RICE.
WE CAN'T FISH.
>> SO YOU CAN CATCH FISH, BUT
YOU DON'T HAVE A FIRE TO BE ABLE
TO COOK IT.
SINCE YOU'RE GOING THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, YOU'RE GOING TO
COME BACK WITH FLINT.
I CAN TEACH YOU HOW TO MAKE
FIRE.
>> YEAH.
>> WOULD YOU LIKE THAT?
>> I WOULD LOVE THAT.
>> IT TAKES BASICALLY THREE
ELEMENTS TO MAKE FIRE.
YOU NEED FUEL, WHICH IS WOOD,
YOU NEED A SPARK, WHICH WILL BE
YOUR FLINT, AND YOU NEED AIR,
RIGHT?
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD A FIRE
SEPARATE, BUT THEN WE'RE GOING
THE TRANSFER IT, BECAUSE IT'S
ALREADY THAT WHAT YOU HAVE.
THE BEST TEACHERS I HAVE HAD
THROUGHOUT THE COURSE OF MY LIFE
WERE ONES THAT SHOWED ME HOW TO
DO THINGS BY DOING THEM
THEMSELVES.
THIS IS FLINT.
THAT'S MAGNESIUM.
YOU SHAVE THE MAGNESIUM OFF.
THAT'S THE REASON WE'RE OUT HERE
ON THE ISLAND.
IF WE'RE GOING THE TALK THE
TALK, WE HAVE TO WALK THE WALK.
>> YOU SEE HOW HE'S GRABBING THE
FLINT IN BETWEEN THE THUMB AND
THE FINGER NICE AND TIGHT.
>> BRING YOUR HEAD IN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
AND IT'S THAT EASY.
WANT THE TRY?
>> I DO.
I WOULD LOVE THE TRY.
>> OKAY, COME ON.
>> EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS ON
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS IS A
LESSON.
>> GRAB YOUR THINGS AND FOLLOW
ME.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
>> EVEN THOUGH ELIZABETH COMES
FULL OFEN JOY, READY TO LEARN,
IN THE BACK OF MY MIND, I KNOW
THAT THE TEST IS COMING.
>> NOPE.
>> LET'S START ALL OVER.
YOU'RE HITTING IT, BUT I DON'T
SEE THAT YOU'RE SCRAPING
ANYTHING.
REMEMBER, MAGNESIUM IS
EVERYTHING.
PUT THIS IN.
WHEN YOU THROW THE MAGNESIUM
THERE N, THERE YOU WANT IT TO BE
ONE SPOT, LIKE A BUN.
>> LIKE A BUN.
>> I'M JUST SCRATCHING IT.
SEE ALL THAT STUFF IN THERE?
BY MY THIRD OR FOURTH TRY --
>> IT'S GOING THE LIGHT.
>> IT'S GOING TO LIGHT.
THERE IT IS.
THERE IT IS, BABY.
NOW KEEP GOING.
>> LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
SANDRA!
>> WE NEED WOOD ON THERE.
WE NEED A TEPEE OF WOOD.
THROW SOME MORE HUSK IN THERE IF
YOU NEED TO.
THAT A NICE FIRE IF I EVER SAW
ONE.
>> WE GOT FIRE, BABY!
THIS IS SO COOL, SANDRA.
THAT WAS BECAUSE OF YOU.
>> HOW DID IT GO?
>> I GOT IT THANKS TO SANDRA.
OH, MAN.
>> WE TOLD YOU THERE WOULD BE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO TEST WHAT YOU
LEARNED TO GET AN ADVANTAGE IN
THIS GAME.
THERE ARE TWO FIRE-MAKING
STATIONS.
IF YOU MAKE FIRE FIRST, YOU EARN
AN IMMUNITY IDOL GOOD FOR YOUR
NEXT TWO TRIBAL COUNCILS.
IF YOU LOSE, YOU LOSE YOUR VOTED
FOR TONIGHT'S TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE QUESTION IS, ARE YOU
CONFIDENT ENOUGH TO TAKE THE
RISK OR WILL YOU PLAY IT SAFE
AND RETURN TO CAMP?
>> I NEED TO THINK.
>> I'M HAPPY THAT YOU'RE
THINKING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A TOUGH DECISION.
>> I KNOW.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE I HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON BACK AT
CAMP.
>> RIGHT.
YOU SAID YOU WERE IN A GOOD
ALLIANCE, RIGHT?
SO YOUR VOTE MIGHT NOT EVEN
MATTER TONIGHT.
>> ELIZABETH AGAINST BOSTON ROB
IS A MISMATCH.
NO ONE KNOWS THE GAME OF
"SURVIVOR" BETTER THANS BE ROB
AND MYSELF.
BUT THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
SHE'S LEARNING FROM THE BEST.
SO MAYBE SHE COULD BEAT BOSTON
WHAT IS YOUR GUT TELLING YOU?
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO FOR IT?
>> A QUICK LITTLE POWWOW.
WE SAID AT THE START WE WERE
GOING TO DO THIS AS THE TEAM, SO
THE THREE PEOPLE THAT DO THE
PUZZLE...
>> IT'S CHECK TVLY OR FAULT.
>> IT'S NOT ALL Y'ALL.
WE PROBABLY PUT MORE PRESSURE ON
Y'ALL THAN WE SHOULD.
>> LET'S GET WATER, FIREWOOD AND
IF WE HAVE TIME...
>> WE HAVE WATER.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT GOING INTO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE I STILL
FEEL LIKE MY NAME IS OUT, THERE
BUT I'M BANKING ON
RELATIONSHIPS, ON CONNECTIONS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M BANKING ON.
>> WHAT ARE WE DOING TONIGHT?
>> FOUR OF US.
>> IF YOU COULD PICK ONE PERSON
RIGHT NOW, WHO WOULD YOU WANT
OUT?
>> RONNIE.
DON'T TRUST HIM.
>> RONNIE?
>> I'M -- WE HAVE ELIZABETH, AN
WE HAVE THAT FOR SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK Y'ALL WANT STRENGTH.
I THINK THE GUYS WILL GO FOR...
>> WE THINK WE HAVE SIX FOR
SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> PUT THE SIX ON RONNIE.
>> I THINK THAT'S A GOOD PLAN.
>> AT THE MOMENT I'M WORKING
WITH TOM, CHELSEA, AND ELAINE TO
VOTE AGAINST RONNIE, BUT I FEEL
THAT MY NAME IS ON THE CHOPPING
BLOCK BECAUSE THE PUZZLE DIDN'T
COME TOGETHER, AND THAT'S WHERE
IT GETS ME REALLY WORRIED.
>> WE GOT TO TALK.
>> THIS IS ABOUT TO GET REAL.
>> WE NEED THE START TALKING.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
, KARISHMA?
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> I'M WITH YOU GUYS.
I WILL VOTE HOWEVER YOU GUYS
WANT TO VOTE.
>> WE HAVE FOUR HERE NOW.
>> HOW YOU FEELING, MAN?
WE NEED YOU RIGHT NOW TO
STRATEGIZE WITH US.
ELIZABETH WILL COME BACK FROM
ISLAND OF IDOLS.
YOU THINK YOU TAKE YOUR VOICE TO
HER?
>> I'LL TELL HER.
>> THAT'S SIX.
I FEEL LIKE ELAINE.
DOES ELAINE MAKE SENSE AT THIS
STAGE IN THE GAME?
SHE'S A SWEETHEART.
>> I WANT THE KEEP HER IN THE
LOOP.
>> ELAINE'S NAME CAME UP A
COUPLE TIME.
>> SHE IS A SOCIAL BUTTERFLY
>> I'M DEFINITELY CONCERNED
ABOUT ELAINE.
SHE IS HILARIOUS, AND SHE IS IN
THE HERE TO BE THE COMEDIAN.
SHE'S HERE TO WIN $1 MILLION.
BUT THE FIRST ALLIANCE THAT I
MADE WAS WITH ELAINE, AND THE
WOMEN.
I'M SO TORN RIGHT NOW.
>> I THINK IDEA IS CONTINUE THE
FEEL PEOPLE OUT, GET FIREWOOD.
>> THEY WANT TO TARGET ELAINE.
I DON'T WANT TO GO DOWN THAT
ROUTE WITH THEM.
THEY WERE SAYING YOU.
LIKE I'M TELLING Y'ALL
EVERYTHING THAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> NO, MAN.
I TOTALLY TRUST ELAINE.
AND I THINK SHE HAS MY BACK, AS
WELL.
SO I NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT
ELAINE DOESN'T GET THE SHORT END
OF THE STICK HERE.
>> THEY'RE THROWING OUT YOUR
NAME.
>> THEY'RE TRYING TO DO
ANYTHING.
THEY DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO COME UP WITH
ALL THESE DIFFERENT NAMES SO
PEOPLE JUMP IN WITH THEM.
>> OKAY.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
>> THE BOTTOM LINE IS THEY'RE
ALL VOTING MY NAME.
>> RIGHT.
>> I KNEW IT IN MY GUT.
I'M IN TROUBLE.
I'M GOING HOME.
I WANT THE TRY TO STAY.
I'M GOING THE PRAY TO STAY AND
PRAY THAT THINGS WORK OUT.
IT MAY NOT BE IN GOD'S PLAN.
>> WHAT IS YOUR GUT TELLING YOU?
>> ROB GIVES ME THE OFFER TO
BASICALLY GO UP AGAINST HIM IN A
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE, AND IF I
WIN I GET AN IMMUNITY-MAKING
IDOL.
IF I LOSE, I LOSE A VOTE.
SO IT'S A HUGE RISK.
>>S BE ROB IS PROBABLY THE BEST
FIRE MAKER IN THIS WORLD.
HE'S DONE HUNDREDS OF FIRES.
AND IN MY HEART, I AM JUST
THINKING, IT'S GOING TO BE VERY
HARD TO WIN.
BUT THE COMPETITOR IN ME IS
IGNITED.
>> YOU WANT TO GO FOR IT?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> LET'S GO FOR IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SHE TOOK THE FIRST OFFER, NOT
EVEN THINKING TO QUESTION IF I
MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING IN MY BACK
POCKET.
I WAS PREPARED TO UP THE ANTE,
BUT LIKE EVERY NEW "SURVIVOR"
PLAYER, THEY BITE AT FIRST
OPPORTUNITY.
YOU READY IN
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, SANDRA, COUNT US
DOWN.
>> OKAY, THREE, TWO, ONE, GO.
>> PUT THIS INTO A LITTLE NEST.
THROW SOME MORE HUSK IN THERE IF
YOU NEED TO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
KEEP GOING.
MORE MAGNESIUM.
THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO,
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT IT.
>> GOOD JOB.
VERY IMPRESSED.
>> START GRABBING THE STICKS.
ROB'S FIRE IS BIG, BUT HE'S NOT
BURNING THROUGH THE ROPE YET, SO
WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
>> CAN'T PANIC.
>> DON'T PANIC.
GET MORE HUSK IN THERE.
KEEP GOING, DON'T GIVE UP.
THIS IS IT.
ROB'S GOT IT.
>> THAT'S A LESSON LEARNED THE
HARD WAY.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING GOING
AGAINST ME?
I'VE MADE HUNDREDS OF FIRES.
"SURVIVOR" IS FULL OF PITFALLS
LIKE THIS.
SOMETIMES IF THE DEAL IS TOO
GOOD TO BE TRUE, IT PROBABLY IS.
SO UNFORTUNATELY TONIGHT YOU
HAVE NO VOTE GOING INTO TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
BUT HERE'S THE GOOD THING, YOU
KNOW HOW TO MAKE FIRE NOW.
YOU GO BACK THE CAMP, YOU
LEARNED A SKILL.
BUT DON'T FORGET THE OTHER
LESSON, ALWAYS TRUST YOUR GUT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE NEVER BATTLED ME
IN THIS.
>> IT WAS DEFINITELY A RISKY
MOVE FOR ELIZABETH TO TRY TO
MAKE FIRE UP AGAINST BOSTON ROB,
AND IN THE FUTURE, SHE CAN'T
JUST AUTOMATICALLY JUMP AT
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
OR SHE'S GOING TO BE IN BIG
TROUBLE.
>> BEFORE YOU GO, THERE IS ONE
MORE THING.
WE WANT YOU THE CHOOSE THE NEXT
PERSON FROM THE OTHER TRIBE TO
VISIT THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
PUT YOUR HAND IN HERE, DON'T
LOOK, AND CHOOSE A NAME AND GIVE
IT TO ME.
OKAY.
YOU DON'T GET TO SEE.
COME ON, LET'S GET YOU BACK THE
CAMP.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
I AM LEAVING THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS WITH SOME WISDOM FROM TWO
OF THE BEST PEOPLE TO PLAY THE
GAME.
I'M MORE NERVOUS GOING BACK TO
THE I'LL BECAUSE I LOST MY VOTE.
>> REMEMBER.
TRUST YOUR GUT.
>> THANK YOU, ROB.
I MADE A FOOLISH MISTAKE.
HOPEFULLY IT DOESN'T DESTROY MY
GAME TONIGHT.
>> I'M NOT VERY CONFIDENT.
>> WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING AFTER
US.
>> IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
LISTEN, WE STAY TOGETHER.
YOU'RE CONFIDENT IN IN MISSY,
YEAH?
>> I AM, MISSY, VINCE.
>> THEY DON'T HAVE NUMBERS.
I THINK THE KEY IS THEY THINK
THEY'VE GOT NUMBERS, BUT WE'VE
GOT NUMBERS.
>> LISTEN, IF I CAN MAKE IT
THROUGH TONIGHT, I'LL WORRY
ABOUT THAT
>> YOU ARE, YOU ARE, I PROMISE.
>> OH, YEAH, I'M NERVOUS.
IT'S PISSING ME OFF THAT I'M
EVEN ON THEIR RADAR TO BEGIN.
WITH I DON'T KNOW WHY I'M BEING
THROWN OUT THERE.
>> NOT THAT I DON'T LIKE HER.
I LIKE HER THAT MUCH TO KNOW SHE
CAN IMMEDIATELY WITHIN PEOPLE
OVER.
WE'RE PLAYING A GAME HERE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> I'M FEELING LIKE I'M IN
TROUBLE.
I'M FREAKING OUT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M FEELING LIKE.
I'LL DO WHATEVER ANYBODY WANTS
ME TO DO.
I JUST DON'T WANT IT TO BE ME.
THAT'S ALL I'M HEARING IS
BASICALLY ME.
>> YOUR NAME HAS BEEN THROWN OUT
THERE.
>> BUT THE MAJORITY IS MINE.
>> IS THERE A DIRECTION YOU
WOULDN'T VOTE IN
>> THAT YOU WOULDN'T VOTE?
>> NO.
I'D VOTE ANYBODY.
LISTEN, I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
MY NAME IS BEING THROWN OUT
THERE ANYWAY.
>> YOUR NAME IS COMING UP
BECAUSE THE LEVEL OF CONCERN,
HOW AWESOME OR LIKE THE PERSON
YOU ARE.
THAT'S LIKE YOU BOND WITH
EVERYBODY IMMEDIATELY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WHERE ARE YOU AT WITH THE
TRIBE, IN THE SWAP, ARE WE IN
THIS?
>> I'M IN THIS.
>> OUR SQUAD, ARE WE IN THIS?
>> THE RELATIONSHIPS, THAT'S
REAL, THAT'S ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I CAME INTO THIS, I DON'T KNOW
HOW NOT TO BE ME.
AARON SAID PEOPLE LOVE ME.
I'M TOO NICE.
HE WAS THROWING EVERY COMPLIMENT
HE COULD THINK OF AT ME, SO I
GUESS I FELT BETTER, BUT IT'S
COMPLETELY UNDERSTANDABLE, YOU
KNOW, LIKE I WOULDN'T WANT TO
SIT NEXT TO SOMEBODY LIKE ME IN
THE END, BUT THESE PEOPLE HAVE
THE REALIZE, THEY HAVE TO MAKE
IT TO THE END.
>> SO IF VINCE'S NAME IS THROWN
OUT, YOU'D BE ALL RIGHT?
>> I'D WILL ALL RIGHT WITH
ANYBODY THAT'S NOT ME.
LET'S MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
>> LET'S GO VINCE.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU ALL WANT.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I LOOKED ELAINE DEAD IN THE
EYES AND SAID IT ONE YOU
TONIGHT, IT'S GOING TO BE VINCE,
BUT THAT DECISION HASN'T BEEN
MADE YET.
IS IT VINCE, IS IT ELAINE?
>> COMING BACK THE CAMP I WAS
CONTEMPLATING THE WHOLE TIME IN
MY HEAD WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL
MY TRIBE MATES.
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> I'VE MISSED YOU.
>> I MISSED YOU GUYS.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEEM
UNTRUSTWORTHY.
AN I DON'T WANT THE LIE, BUT
SANDRA AND BOSTON ROB TOLD ME TO
TRUST MY GUT.
IT'S TELLING ME, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO, BECAUSE KNOWLEDGE IS
POWER IN THIS GAME.
>> DOESN'T EVERYONE WANT THE
HEAR ABOUT ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
NOW IS YOUR CHANCE.
>> IT'S UP TO YOU.
DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO
>> I'LL TALK.
>> I HATE LYING, BUT TODAY IS
GOING TO HAVE TO BE MY FIRST BIG
LIE.
>> SO YOU GO TO ANOTHER ISLAND,
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
THERE'S A PATH, AND IT BRINGS
YOU TO THE THREE URNS, AND IT'S
LIKE, THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO
PLAY.
AND YOU HAVE ONE CHANCE TO HIT
AN URN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN THE URNS,
BUT APPARENTLY ONLY ONE HAS
SOMETHING IN IT.
AND I SMASHED THE URN, AND I GET
A LITTLE CARD, AND IT SAYS, YOU
LOSE, NO GAME.
SO HERE I AM.
HOW WAS THE MORALE AFTER?
>> WE DIDN'T TALK THE EACH OTHER
AT ALL?
>> REALLY?
>> SILENCE.
>> WELL, I WOULD LIKE TO STILL
BE IN IT.
I'LL CHAT WITH EVERYBODY.
I AM THE MOST POPULAR GIRL AT
CAMP.
EVERYBODY WANTED TO TALK TO ME
BECAUSE THEY NEEDED MY VOTE.
>> ELAINE GOT TOSSED OUT.
VINCE WAS OUT THERE.
BUT EVERYBODY WAS KIND OF
GRAVITATING TOWARD ELAINE.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT BETWEEN YOU AND I, I WAS
HOPING THAT'S THE WAY WE GO.
>> AARON IS TELLING ME WE'RE
GOING TO VOTE OUT VINCE, BUT
AARON WANTS ELAINE.
OTHER PEOPLE WANT RONNIE.
>> WHO ARE YOU VOTING FOR?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> I DON'T HAVE A VOTE.
I WANT TO TELL THE PEOPLE THAT
I'M CLOSE WORK BUT YOU DON'T
TELL THEM A THING.
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
>> I WANT TO GET TO THE END.
UNFORTUNATELY IT'S GOING TO TAKE
ME LYING.
I HAVE THE WORST-CASE SCENARIO
WHERE I DON'T HAVE A VOICE IN
TONIGHT'S VOTE.
AND NOW I HAVE NINE OTHER PEOPLE
COMING UP TO ME TELLING ME NINE
DIFFERENT STORIES, BUT I HAVE TO
KEEP STRAIGHT IN MY MIND.
MY BRAIN IS FRIED.
MY BRAIN IS SCRAMBLED EGGS AT
THIS POINT.
AND THE SUN IS GOING DOWN AND
I'M HEADED INTO TROUBLE COUNCIL
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN TONIGHT.
I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU A
TORCH.
GO AHEAD AND GRAB ONE.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOU FLAME IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
YOU GUYS KNOW THAT'S GOING TO BE
THE CASE FOR SOMEBODY TONIGHT.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT THE FIRST
FEW DAYS.
CHELSEA, WHEN YOU SHOW UP ON THE
BEACH AND THERE IS NO
INFORMATION, HOW MUCH DOES THAT
AMP UP THE INITIAL PARANOIA?
>> WE WALK OUT TO THE BEACH.
WE WERE ALL JUST LIKE, WHERE'S
JEFF?
WHERE'S OUR MAROONING?
THEN WE SEE THING FROM,
"SURVIVOR: ISLAND OF THE IDOLS."
IT WAS JUST LIKE, WHAT IS THIS?
>> Jeff: ELAINE, WHAT DID YOU
NOTICE IN TERMS OF PEOPLE
CONNECTING OR SAYING, HEY, I
HAVE THAT IN COMMON?
>> WELL, I KIND OF GET ALONG
WITH EVERYBODY JUST NATURALLY,
SO I KIND OF JUST CLICKED WITH
EVERYBODY INSTANTLY.
BUT BECAUSE APPARENTLY THESE
PEOPLE SAY I'M SO WONDERFUL, MY
NAME HAS BEEN THROWN AROUND.
SO I'M PROBABLY GOING HOME
TONIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S GOT ME ON PINS AND NEEDLES.
I'M FREAKING OUT.
>> Jeff: KARISHMA, IS THERE
ANY TRUTH THAT ELAINE MIGHT BE
IN TROUBLE BECAUSE SHE'S
ACTUALLY SO LIKABLE?
>> THERE IS'S DEFINITELY TRUTH
TO THAT.
>> REALLY?
>> TOLL YOU.
>> IN THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR,"
LIKABILITY IS A LIABILITY.
I THINK WE ALL KNOW THAT.
THERE IS A CONCERN ABOUT KEEPING
SOMEBODY ON YOUR TRIBE WHO MAY
BE LIKED MORE THAN YOU ARE.
>> BUT LISTEN, WHY DO THAT THREE
DAYS IN?
YOU KNOW, LIKE GIVE ME A CHANCE.
LIKE, OKAY, I'M TOO LIKABLE TO
TAKE TO FINAL TWO OR FINAL
THREE, WHATEVER YOU GOT SET UP
AT THE END, BECAUSE WE KNOW YOU
CHANGE IT UP.
WHY BREAK ME DOWN BECAUSE I'M
GOOD PEOPLE?
CUT ME AT 20 DAYS.
TAKE A PIN, PUT IT UP HERE, COME
BACK TO IT LATER.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT IDEA?
>> Jeff: RONNIE, WHAT'S YOUR
YOU TIERA THREE DAYS IN, FIRST
VOTE?
>> FOR ME, YOU KNOW, I THINK WE
NEED TO KEEP THE TRIBE STRONG.
GET RID OF A BIG GUY IN THE
GROUP WOULD BE A MISTAKE.
IT'S VERY EARLY IN THIS GAME.
IF WE DON'T HAVE THAT STRENGTH,
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN THE NEXT
CHALLENGE.
WE'LL BE BACK HERE IN THREE
DAYS.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THAT.
>> Jeff: SO ELAINE, WE'RE
CLOSE TO VOTING.
IS THERE PART OF YOU THAT'S SAD
THAT YOU THINK IT MIGHT BE OVER,
OR IS IT YOUR ATTITUDE, IF IT'S
OVER, IT'S OVER, THAT'S WAY IT
GOES.
>> NO, I'M DEVASTATED.
YEAH, I'M DEVASTATED.
EVERYBODY HERE KNOWS WHAT IT
TAKES TO GET HERE.
AND SOME OF US GOT LONGER
JOURNEYS.
SOME OF US GOT A LITTLE MORE
PAIN WE CARRY, AND WHEN YOU
FINALLY GET TO DO SOMETHING THAT
YOU'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT FOR
SO LONG, LIKE IT'S HEARTBREAK
THANK YOU CAN'T FULFILL WHAT YOU
HAD SET IN YOUR HEART.
LIKE THE ENTIRE JOURNEY.
I WANTED TO FILL MY CUP UP.
I WANTED THE SHOW TO BUILD ME
UP, I DIDN'T WANT IT TO TEAR ME
DOWN.
AND IF I GO HOME TONIGHT, IT'S
GOING TO BE HEARTBREAK, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME, IT'S THE BEST
THING IN THE WORLD THAT'S
HAPPENED TO ME.
>> Jeff: RONNIE, WHEN YOU HEAR
THAT EMOTION, THAT HONEST,
CANDID CONFESSIONAL, WHAT'S THE
REACTION INSIDE YOU?
>> IT MEANS A LOT TO ME, EVEN
THOUGH IT COMES FROM DIFFERENT
PLACE.
I'M FROM SOUTH BOSTON, BROCKIAN,
MASSACHUSETTS AND SHE'S FROM
KENTUCKY, WE'VE LIVED SIMILAR
LIVES.
>> Jeff: IN TERMS OF HARDSHIP?
>> IN TERMS OF THE HARDSHIP.
I'VE WORKED AT McDONALD'S, A
LAY-AWAY MANAGER AT WAL-MART, AT
SEARS AUTOMOTIVE AS A CUSTOMER
SERVICE ADVISER, I BAR TEBDZED,
I HELPED MY FRIEND WITH HIS
PROTEIN BAR COMPANY, I TRIED THE
DABBLE IN THE STOCK MARKET.
I'VE DEALT WITH CRYPTO, I'M
DEALT CASINO GAMES.
I'M ATTEMPTED TO KICK OFF FROM
THAILAND A COUPLE TIMES.
WE ALL HAVE OUR STORIES, BUT
THERE'S IN COMPARISON.
THIS GAME IS ON TOP FOR ME.
THIS IS A DREAM COME TRUE FOR
ALL OF US HERE.
THAT'S WHY I FEEL HER.
TO GET VOTED OUT IN THREE DAYS,
THAT'S A HEARTBREAKER FOR ANY
ONE OF US OUT HERE.
>> IT'S IS HARD BECAUSE EVERYONE
HERE HAS A STORY, AND I THINK
THAT'S WHAT'S SO DIFFICULT ABOUT
THIS.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT MY JOB WOULD
BE CHOP DOWN COCONUTS AND DO ALL
THIS STUFF.
NOW THAT I'M HERE, I'M REALIZING
THAT, I DON'T KNOW, IT'S JUST
LIKE, I HAVE PUT IN SO MUCH TOO.
IT'S JUST... IT MAKES ME UNSURE
WHERE I AM DEFINITELY.
BUT IN TERMS OF GAME PLAY, IT'S
JUST SOMETHING YOU HAVE THE DEAL
WITH.
OF COURSE SOMEONE LIKE ELAINE
YOU WANT TO SUPPORT, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME, YOU KNOW THAT THAT
MIGHT JUST RUIN YOUR GAME.
>> Jeff: SO AARON, WHERE DOES
THIS SIT WITH YOU?
BECAUSE EMOTIONS CAN TOUCH YOU,
BUT DOES IT CHANGE YOUR
STRATEGY?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, YES THIS IS A GAME.
SOMEBODY HAS TO GO HOME, BUT
THESE ARE ALL PEOPLE WITH REAL
FEELINGS AND REAL EMOTIONS.
SO TO GO UP THERE AND WRITE NAME
ON THE PARCHMENT OF SOMEONE THAT
YOU GENUINELY DO CARE ABOUT,
IT'S NOT EASY.
>> IS THIS HARD FOR YOU?
>> Jeff: IT'S BEEN A VERY
EMOTIONAL FIRST TRIBAL COUNCIL?
VINCE, YOU'RE UP.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE VINCE.
RONNIE.
VINCE.
THAT'S TWO VOTES VINCE.
RONNIE.
WE'RE TIED.
TWO VOTES RONNIE, TWO VOTES
VINCE.
RONNIE.
THAT'S THREE VOTES RONNIE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES RONNIE, TWO
VOTES VINCE.
RONNIE.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES RONNIE.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT, RONNIE.
THAT'S SIX, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
RONNIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> OKAY, GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: WELL, THE THEME OF
TONIGHT'S TRIBAL WAS HOW
DIFFICULT IT WOULD BE TO VOTE
SOMEBODY OUT, AND YET THE RESULT
A DEVASTATING BLINDSIDE.
YOU'LL HEAD BACK TO CAMP WITH
FLINT.
GOOD LUCK MAKING FIRE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN THERE'S A BLIND
SIDE --
>> I DON'T WANT THE TALK TO
ANYBODY RIGHT NOW.
>> FOOL ME TWICE, THAT'S NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jeff: AND HEART ATTACK, YOU
CAN GO INSANE.
>> PEOPLE CAN'T JUST CREEP
AROUND.
>> LET'S JUST CHILL.
>> I'M GOING CRAZY RIGHT NOW.
>> I WAS BLIND SIDED PRETTY
HARD.
I DID NOT EXPECT THAT.
I THOUGHT I WAS CONDITION
TRIBUTEING TO MY TRIBE.
IT SUCKS.
IT'S PRETTY EMBARRASSING TO BE
VOTED OUT FIRST.
BUT I MADE SOME MISTAKES, AND IN
THE GAME OF POKER, YOU HAVE TO
LEARN FROM YOUR MISTAKES.
IT WASN'T ABOUT JUST THE MONEY.
$1 MILLION IS GREAT, BUT YOU
CAN'T PUT A PRICE ON AN
EXPERIENCE LIKE THIS.