>> Jeff: WE'RE IN LOS ANGELES
FOR THE FINALE OF "SURVIVOR:
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS."
WE STARTED WITH 20.
WE ARE DOWN TO FIVE.
HERE WE ARE, DEAN, JANET,
LAUREN, NOURA, AND TOMMY.
AND TONIGHT WE WILL CROWN A
WINNER OF OUR 39th SEASON.
THE BIG TWIST THIS SEASON WAS
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS WHERE WE HAD
TWO OF OUR MOST DOMINANT WINNERS
SERVING AS A MENTOR TO A GROUP
OF PLAYERS.
THERE WAS SANDRA, THE ONLY
TWO-TIME WINNER, AND BOSTON ROB,
THE ONLY PERSON TO APPEAR FIVE
TIMES FOR 153 DAYS, GETTING A
STANDING OVATION.
STEP OVER HERE, GUYS.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
QUICK QUESTION.
SANDRA, WHEN YOU'RE SERVING AS A
MENTOR, YOU GET TO OBSERVE AND
WATCH NEW PLAYERS.
DID YOU LEARN ANYTHING FROM
THESE NEW PLAYERS?
>> I ACTUALLY LEARNED A LOT, BUT
THE FIRST THING I HAD TO DO WAS
LISTEN TO THEM AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT I COULD HELP THEM WITH TO
HELP THEM NOT ONLY GET TO THE
END BUT WIN.
BUT MY MAIN FOCUS REALLY WAS
LEARNING FROM BOSTON ROB.
I FELT LIKE IF THERE WAS ANYONE
THAT COULD TEACH ME ANYTHING, IT
WOULD BE PAYING ATTENTION TO
HIM.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE STUDYING HIM
WHILE YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
TEACHING OTHERS.
THAT'S SANDRA.
HOW ABOUT YOU, ROB?
>> I'VE PAID ENOUGH "SURVIVOR"
TO KNOW YOU HAVE TO CONSTANTLY
BEING PAYING ATTENTION.
THE THEME OF THE SEASON WAS
EVERYTHING IS A LESSON, THE GAME
IS EVOLVING, SO MY EYES WERE
OPEN OUT THERE, AS WELL.
>> Jeff: THAT'S WHY THESE TWO
WON.
THAT'S WHY I WISH YOU WOULD COME
BECOME AND PLAY AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS ONE VISIT LEFT TO
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS, AND IT
COULD CHANGE THE ENTIRE GAME.
WE HAVE ANOTHER PACKED HOUSE FOR
TONIGHT'S FINALE.
LET'S GET TO IT.
THE FINALE, "SURVIVOR: ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS."
>> "SURVIVOR" HAS BEEN AWESOME
TO ME.
I LOVE IT.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS ABOUT
BEING OUT HERE, BUT SOMETIMES
THE PRIZE ISN'T ONLY IN THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
I KNOW THAT'S THE GOAL FOR
EVERYONE, BUT THE REALITY IS
ONLY ONE PERSON IS GOING TO WIN
IT, AND, YOU KNOW, IN MY CASE, I
FOUND THINGS IN "SURVIVOR" THAT
NOBODY HAS.
I MET MY WIFE ON THIS SHOW.
I HAVE FOUR AMAZING DAUGHTERS
BECAUSE OF THIS SHOW.
SO IF YOUR EYES ARE OPEN, THERE
ARE GIFTS HERE BEYOND JUST THE
GAME.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU FOUND HAPPINESS
AND EVERLASTING LOVE, AND I FIND
HAPPINESS, TOO, IN THE MONEY
I'VE MADE.
SO WE FIND DIFFERENT HAPPINESS.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THE PURPOSE OF THIS
ISLAND WAS INTENDED TO MAKE
PEOPLE BETTER "SURVIVOR"
PLAYERS.
I HOPE THAT FOR THOSE THAT DID
VISIT US THAT WAS THE CASE.
>> YOU KNOW, WE WERE THERE TO
LEND AN EAR, TO LISTEN, TO GIVE
THEM ADVICE.
>> Jeff:>> BECAUSE IT'S DAY 36,
REALLY IT'S ONLY THREE DAYS
LEFT, BUT THERE'S STILL A LOT OF
WORK TO DO.
WITH FIVE PEOPLE LEFT IN THE
GAME, ONLY THREE OF THEM ARE
GOING TO MAKE THE FINAL.
>> AND ONLY ONE WILL WIN THE $1
MILLION.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAD A GREAT TIME OUT HERE WITH
YOU.
>> LIKEWISE.
>> CHEERS.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
DO I HEAR A BOAT?
OH, MY GOSH, IT IS A BOAT.
WHAT?
DO YOU SEE THE BOAT, GUYS.
>> BOAT'S HERE.
NOURA IS SCREAMING, "THERE'S A
BOAT.
" I'M LIKE, WHAT'S ABOUT TO
HAPPEN.
>> HELLO AGAIN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GRAB YOUR PERSONAL BELONGINGS
AND GET ON THIS BOAT.
>> ALL OF US?
>> I THINK THAT'S ALL OF US.
>> WE ALL KNOW WHERE WE'RE
HEADED.
THAT'S ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
>> LET'S GET OUR STUFF.
>> MY MIND IMMEDIATELY STARTS
SPINNING, LIKE, DAMN, WE'RE ALL
GOING.
WHAT IT MEANS WE DON'T REALLY
KNOW.
>> MY HEART IS POUNDING, BABY,
BUT THIS IS THE FOURTH QUARTER.
THIS IS OVERTIME RIGHT HERE.
WE'RE AT THE CLOSE, THE LAST
SECOND.
NOW IT'S TIME TO TURN IT UP A
NOTCH AND CLOSE THIS THING OUT.
>> MY HEART IS POUNDING.
I'M THE ONLY PERSON LEFT THAT
HAS NOT BEEN TO THIS ISLAND.
FINAL FIVE, ISLAND OF THE IDOLS,
LET'S GET THIS GAME DONE.
>> WOW.
THAT'S SO COOL.
IS THAT THEIR HOUSE?
THAT'S NUTS.
>> I GET FIRST HUG, RIGHT?
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> I'M TOMMY.
>> HI, TOMMY.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I TOOK YOUR ADVICE.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> IT FEELS GREAT TO BE BACK AT
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
ANY CHANCE TO BE AROUND ROB AND
SANDRA IS A GIFT.
THE LESSON THEY MADE ME HAS
HELPED ME MAKE THE FINAL FIVE,
BUT IN MY HEART OF HEARTS I
ALWAYS KNEW I WOULD BE HERE.
I CAME OUT HERE TO WIN, THIS AN
I'M CLOSE.
>> WELCOME TO THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS, DAY 36.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GUYS ARE SO CLOSE.
THERE ARE FIVE OF YOU.
ONLY THREE OF YOU WILL BE ABLE
TO PLEAD YOUR CASE TO THE JURY
FOR THE MILLION DOLLARS.
>> AND ONLY ONE OF YOU WILL WIN.
>> SO THERE'S STILL A TON OF
GAME LEFT TO PLAY.
AND THERE ARE GIFTS IN THIS GAME
IF YOU'RE OPEN TO IT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, I'M SURE YOU
SAW THE HOUSE.
SANDRA AND I WORKED REALLY HARD
ON THIS HOUSE, BECAUSE FOR THE
REST OF THE GAME, YOU GUYS ARE
GOING TO LIVE HERE.
[SCREAMING]
>> WAIT!
THERE'S MORE.
>> THERE IS ONE MORE THING.
>> WHAT?
>> WE HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU.
THESE ARE SPECIAL EDITION ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS BUFFS TO
COMMEMORATE OUR TIME HERE AND TO
WISH YOU GUYS GOOD LUCK AND A
STRONG FINISH.
>> ENDING OUR CHAPTER AT ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS IS BITTERSWEET, BUT
I'M 100% POSITIVE THAT ROB AND I
MADE THEM BETTER "SURVIVOR"
PLAYERS.
ANY OF THE FIVE THAT ARE STILL
STANDING COULD EASILY TAKE THIS
GAME.
SO GOOD LUCK, MAY THE BEST MAN
OR WOMAN WIN.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
OUR TIME HERE IS DONE.
YOU FINISH STRONG, ALL RIGHT?
>> WE WILL.
>> GOOD LUCK TO ALL OF YOU.
KEEP IT TOGETHER.
>> TAKE CARE, GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> LET'S GO.
WOW, THANKS, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE DID IT.
>> THIS IS RARE.
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED ON
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS HAS BEEN
A LESSON, SO THEY SHOULD KNOW
THAT THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE GOING
THE LEAVE THEM WITHOUT ONE LAST
TEST.
>> WE JUST OUTLASTED ROB AND
SANDRA.
>> MAYBE, JUST MAYBE SOMEBODY'S
BEEN PAYING ATTENTION.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WOW.
>> THIS IS SO COOL.
>> MY PRAYERS HAVE BEEN
ANSWERED.
>> THERE'S FRUIT.
>> YES, FRUIT!
OH, YOU'RE TELLING ME, BABY.
>> THIS IS PARSLEY.
THERE'S PARSLEY HERE.
>> ROB AND SANDRA SAY, OUR LAND
IS YOUR LAND NOW, AND YOU GUYS
GET TO ENJOY THIS HOUSE WE MADE,
BEDS.
SO MUCH FRUIT, COMFORT.
>> THIS IS SO COOL.
CHICKENS, BLANKETS, PILLOWS,
HAMMOCKS.
I WAS LOVING IT.
I FELT LIKE I GOT UPGRADED TO
THE SUITE AT THE HOTEL.
NOW I CAN REALLY DRIVE HARD
UNTIL THE END OF THE GAME.
>> FINAL FIVE CELEBRATION.
I SAY WE EAT A LOT OF FRUIT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I AM IN THE FINAL FIVE RIGHT
NOW.
AND I HAVE AN IDOL, SO I AM
GUARANTEED FINAL FOUR.
AND NONE OF THESE PEOPLE CAN
BEAT ME IN FIRE.
SO I CAN SEE THE FINAL THREE.
IT COULD NOT HAVE TURNED OUT
BETTER.
>> HEY, WE ARE THERE.
WE'RE SET.
>> I WAS NERVOUS.
>> I WAS, TOO.
NOW WE'RE SOLID.
>> WE'RE SOLID.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SAY ABOUT OUR
ALLIANCE, TOMMY AND THE MOMMY.
FEELS NICE TO TAKE A BREAK FROM
TALKING.
SO WHO DO YOU THINK IS MORE OF A
THREAT, JANET OR LAUREN?
>> JANET.
>> ME TOO.
I JUST SEE HOW LOVING SHE IS.
EVERYONE IS GOING TO LOVE HER.
SHE'S GOING TO EVOKE EMOTIONALLY
FROM THESE PEOPLE IN JURY.
>> JANET IS VERY LOVED BY
EVERYONE, BUT WE HAVE ONE WEASEL
LEFT, AND THAT'S DEAN.
DEAN IS LIKE THE EX-BOYFRIEND
THAT YOU CANNOT TRUST.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO GET WITH HIM.
HE'S LIKE A MIXED BAG OF TRICKS.
QUITE SIMPLY FOR MY GAME, IT'S A
NO-BRAINER, LET'S GET RID OF
DEAN.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON MY LITTLE CHICK I CANS.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE IN MY HAND.
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M LASER FOCUSED
ON THESE BRAND-NEW BUFFS.
IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY, THEY
NEVER GIVE YOU A BUFF AT FINAL
FIVE.
THIS IS NUTS.
WE'RE ON THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS.
THERE IS SOMETHING HERE, AND IT
JUST RANG IN MY HEAD, TOMMY,
THAT'S YOUR FIRST HINT.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME SYMBOL ON
HERE.
SO I'M LOOKING AROUND, AND I
SAY, A MACHETE.
THERE'S NEVER BEEN MACHETE
ATTACHED TO THIS.
SO IT'S HARD TO SEE, BUT IT USED
TO BE A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
SO NOW I'M LOOKING AT THE
MACHETES IN A DIFFERENT LIGHT,
BECAUSE THIS IS A CLUE TO
SOMETHING.
ROB SAID, "THERE'S MANY GIFTS
THIS ISLAND HAS FOR YOU.
THERE'S PROBABLY AN ADVANTAGE.
THERE'S PROBABLY AN IDOL.
RIGHT NOW I'M SEARCHING THIS
PLACE LEFT AND RIGHT, AND I SEE
ANOTHER MACHETE.
AND THIS MACHETE IS PERFECTLY
PLACED IN THIS COCONUT.
CRACK OPEN THAT COCONUT, AND
NOTHING INSIDE.
IT'S JUST PINK OR IT'S RED.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M COLORBLIND.
SO I HAVED IN WHAT'S RED.
RED IN MY EYES IS PINKISH,
ORANGISH, SO ANYTHING ORANGE,
PINK OR RED IN THAT FAMILILY
HAVE TO SEARCH AND LOOK LIKE
CRAZY AND JUST FIGURE OUT,
MACHETE AND RED NOW.
SO I'M ON TO THE NEXT PART OF
THIS SCAVENGER HUNT.
>> WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
COME HERE.
>> I CRACKED UP THIS COCONUT,
PINK INSIDE.
>> PINK WHAT?
>> JUST PINK.
SINCE I'M COLORBLIND AND SINCE I
WANT THE BUILD MORE TRUST WITH
I SHOWED DEAN THE COCONUT.
NOTHING ELSE, JUST THE PINK.
>> I'M PUTTING A LOT OF TRUST IN
DEAN, BUT AT THIS POINT I'M
LOST.
WITH MY EYES I CAN'T SEE THESE
THINGS.
I HOPE DEAN WILL USE THIS WITH
ME, BECAUSE DEAN HAS TOLD ME
ABOUT HIS ADVANTAGES.
HE TOLD ME ABOUT THE IDOL
NULLIFIER, SO IF HE FINDS IT,
MAYBE HE'LL TELL ME ABOUT THIS
ONE, TOO.
>> MAYBE WE LOOK FOR ANOTHER
MACHETE OR ANOTHER PINK THING.
>> I'M TELLING YOU NOW, I'M
1,000% LOCKED TO TAKING YOU TO
THE END.
>> DUDE, SERIOUSLY.
>> HE'S LIKE, IT'S A CLUE, IT'S
A CLUE, ARE WE LOCKED IN, FINAL
TWO, ARE WE DOING THIS?
AND TOMMY IS TELLING ME
EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, HELL, I LOVE IT.
I GUESS HE TRUSTS ME.
COOL.
LIKE IF I KEEP MY EYES OPEN I
GUESS.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> BEING COLORBLIND IS EXTREMELY
DIFFICULT, SO I'M LOOKING ALL
OVER CAMP, BUT THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS IS HUNTING, AND DEAN'S NOT
HELPING AT ALL.
SHE'S JUST CHILLED AND RELAXED.
>> THAT AND THEN --
>> OH, GO FOR IT.
>> THERE'S AN OPENING RIGHT
HERE.
I FEEL LIKE HIP HEALTH IS VERY
IMPORTANT.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GIVE UP.
WHAT'S NEXT?
AND H.
THAT'S DEFINITELY NEXT CLUE.
WHATEVER THAT IS.
EVERYONE IS LAUGHING AND HAVING
A FUN TIME, BUT MY MIND IS GOING
NUTS.
THERE'S A SYMBOL THAT LOOKS LIKE
AN H, WHERE IS THE SYMBOL.
WHERE CAN I FIND THIS SYMBOL.
SO I'M LOOKING ALL OVER FOR
TWIGS THAT LINE UP, PATHS THAT
LINE UP.
I WAS THINKING H FOR HAMMOCK,
HEART FOR HEART, THIS SYMBOL IS
DRIVING ME NUTS.
>> I GOT ANOTHER CLUE?
>> HOW.
>> FOLLOW ME.
>> IF YOU FIND IT, IT'S GOING TO
ME.
>> WHAT?
>> COOL.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> H.
IT'S AN H WITH TWO PATHS.
>> WE'RE PAST THE RED PHASE.
IT'S THE H PHASE.
>> I REALLY NEED THE TAKE A
POOP, BUT LET ME THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I'LL BE LOOKING.
>> DON'T HAS BEEN NO HELP.
IT'S EXTREMELY NERVE-RACKING.
DEAN SEEMS LIKE NOT THAT
INTERESTED.
HE'S JUST BEING DEAN, HE'S D.K.
CHILLING.
ALL HE DOES IS SIT AROUND.
I WANT TO GET THIS THING DONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HIS HEAD IS
AT.
>> IF I WERE TOMMY, I WOULD NOT
HAVE TOLD ME NOTHING.
ONE OF MY DREAMS IN THIS GAME,
FIND A FREAKIN' HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL, A SECRET ADVANTAGE.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO CATCH ON THE
ME.
THEN IT CLICKS.
>> I'M GOING TO GO TO THE SWING
FOR A SECOND.
WHAT'S THAT SWING DOING OVER
THERE.
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE, MAYBE LIKE
THIS, AND THE SEAT, LOOKS PRETTY
MUCH LIKE THE SYMBOL.
I'M LIKE, OH, I REALLY WANT THE
FIND IT BEFORE TOMMY.
SO I'M GOING TO GO FOR A SWING.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OUT OF THE CORNER OF MY EYE, I
SEE THE FRIGGIN SYMBOL, I CAN
CONTINUE TO THE WATER, COOL AS
EVER.
I WATCH THE CUTTING BOARD, WASH
THE CUPS.
I MOSEY ON, D.K. CHILLING BACK
TO THE SHELTER.
I LOOK AROUND AND NO ONE IS
THERE.
DAMN, NOW IS MY CHANCE.
I OPEN IT UP, AND IN THE CANVAS
WRAP IS A SWEET, SWEET-LOOKING
THING.
I FOUND THE IDOL, BABY.
OH, MY GOD.
CAN THIS DAY GET ANY BETTER.
I HAVE ACTUALLY FOUND A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL ON "SURVIVOR."
REALLY IN WITH FIVE PEOPLE LEFT.
I'M FEELING GOOD RIGHT NOW.
"YOU DIDN'T THINK WE'D LEAVE
WITHOUT ONE LAST TEST, DID YOU?
YOU PASSED IT.
GOOD LUCK, SANDRA AND ROB."
I FOUND ONE.
TOMMY IS STILL OVER THERE
LOOKING, SWEATING FRANTICALLY.
HE MIGHT BE LOOKING FOREVER,
WHICH I FIND HILARIOUS.
HE'S NEVER GOING TO FIND IT.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M TELLING
TOMMY.
I'M KEEPING IT TO MYSELF.
SO I GUESS D.K. CHILLING HAS
TURNED TO D.K. DILLING.
TOMMY IS PLAYING A FOURTH GRADE
GAME OUT HERE.
I'M OUT HERE TEACHING ADVANCED
ALGEBRA.
COME ON, STEP THE GAME UP,
TOMMY.
COME ON, MAN.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
TAKE A LOOK.
YOU HAVE TO CONQUER THIS TODAY.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, DEAN, GOT
THE TAKE BACK THE NECKLACE.
NOBODY WANTS TO HELP.
>> NO ONE WANTS THE TAKE IT OFF.
>> YOU GOT THIS, TOMMY.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO RETRIEVE A SERIES OF
ROPE RUNGS AND USE THEM TO CLIMB
A TOWER.
YOU'LL THEN MANEUVER A BAG OF
BALLS UP A LADDER AND ATTEMPT TO
LAND THOSE BALLS ON A TABLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
IN ADDITION, YOU'RE PLAYING FOR
REWARD.
>> OH, WOW.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER WILL ENJOY
BACK AT YOUR NEW HOME ON ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS STEAK, BAKED
POTATO, SALAD AND IF NECESSARY
VEGETARIAN OPTIONS.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: PLAYING FOR A LOT.
SOUND GOOD?
>> AMAZING.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
HIRE -- HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY AND REWARD,
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
WE'VE GOT SEVEN ROPE RUNGS YOU
GOT TO KNOCK OFF AND COLLECT,
BECAUSE YOU NEED THEM TO GET UP
THAT TOWER.
DEAN OFF THE A FAST START.
TOMMY IS MOVING QUICKLY.
THERE GOES DEAN WITH ANOTHER
ONE.
JANET IS DOING WELCH EVERYBODY
IS DOING VERY WELL EARLY IN THIS
CHALLENGE.
LAUREN HAS ANOTHER ONE.
THERE GOES NOURA WITH ANOTHER
ONE.
TOMMY AND DEAN NOW STARTING TO
EXTEND THEIR LEAD.
DEAN HAS ALL SEVEN.
HE'S THROUGH.
TOMMY IS THROUGH.
IT IS TOMMY AND DEAN RIGHT NOW.
NOW YOU GOT TO BUILD THE LADDER
FROM BOTTOM TO TOP.
JANET HAS ALL OF HERS, SHE'S
HEADING IN.
NOURA HAS HERS.
LAUREN DOWN TO HER LAST TWO.
TOMMY WORKING ON THAT ROPE
LADDER.
DEAN WORKING ON HIS ROPE LADDER.
DEAN HOOKS ANOTHER.
TOMMY HOOKS ANOTHER.
HERE GOES NOURA.
SHE'S GETTING INTO IT VERY FAST
NOW.
DEAN WITH HIS LAST ROPE.
TOMMY ON HIS LAST ROPE.
YOU'RE GOOD, TOMMY.
YOUR GOOD, DEAN.
WE ARE STILL NECK AND NECK.
HERE COMES LAUREN.
SHE'S IN ON IT NOW.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO MANEUVER THAT
BAG OF BALLS UP THE LADDER.
ANOTHER SURVIVOR PUZZLE.
NOURA MOVING VERY FAST.
SHE'S QUICKLY GETTING BACK IN
THIS.
JANET STRUGGLING TO STABILIZE.
USE ALL THIS BODY, WHATEVER IT
TAKES, JANET.
YOU HAVE LASTED 37 DAYS.
YOU WANT TO GET TO 38.
HERE COMES NOURA.
SHE'S GOT HER LAST ROPE.
GET UP HERE.
DEAN AND TOMMY SIDE BY SIDE.
FINAL FOUR ON THE LINE.
IMMUNITY AROUND YOUR NECK IS
WHAT YOU WANT TONIGHT.
TOMMY IS UP.
DEAN IS UP.
AT THE FINAL STAGE, BOTH HAVE
UNTIED THEIR BALLS AND CAN START
ON THE MAZE.
NOURA IS MAKING A GO OF THIS.
SHE'S RIGHT ON THEIR TAIL.
NOURA IS GOOD.
START UNTYING THOSE BALLS.
LAUREN NOW IS UP.
JANET IS UP.
LAUREN AND JANET BOTH NOW ON THE
SECOND PHASE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
IT IS DEAN, NOURA, AND TOMMY ON
THE MAZE LOOKING THE LAND TWO
BALLS TO GUARANTEE YOURSELF A
SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR.
NOURA IS IN AND OUT.
LAUREN NOW IN IT.
JANET RIGHT ON HER TAIL.
TOMMY HAS HIS FIRST ONE.
TOMMY NOW WORKING ON HIS SECOND
BALL.
JANET DROPS.
HERE COMES DEAN.
YOU CAN FEEL THE INTENSITY PICK
UP NOW.
EVERYBODY NOW CHASING TOMMY.
JANET GOING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
GO.
JANET ONCE AGAIN HOVERING AROUND
THAT FIRST BALL AND SHE'S GOT
IT.
JANET HAS HER FIRST.
IT IS NOW TOMMY AND JANET
FIGHTING FOR IMMUNITY.
DEAN GOING TO SKIP THAT FIRST
HOLE.
HE'S AT THE TRICKY SPOT ON THIS
MAZE GOING FOR THAT DEEP TARGET.
THE WIND REALLY PICKING UP NOW.
TOMMY DROPS.
GOT TO START AGAIN.
DEAN GETTING VERY CLOSE TO THAT
AND HE'S GOT IT.
DEAN LANDS HIS FIRST, BUT HE
LANDS THE DEEPEST ONE, WHICH IS
MORE DIFFICULT.
DEAN HAS ONE MORE BALL TO DROP,
AND IT'S THE CLOSE ONE AND HE'S
QUICKLY GETTING THERE.
THIS WOULD BE IT RIGHT HERE.
IT'S IN AND OUT.
DEAN DROPS.
GOT TO GO AGAIN.
>> OH, OKAY, LAUREN.
>> Jeff: LAWYER DROPS HER
FIRST BALL.
SHE'S IN IT NOW.
EVERYBODY HAS ONE BALL EXCEPT
NOURA.
YOU ARE GUARANTEED A SPOT AT THE
FINAL FOUR IF YOU FINISH FIRST.
LAUREN DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
HERE GOES JANET.
SHE'S NOW EDGING CLOSER AND
CLOSER TO THAT SECOND BALL.
DEAN FOR THE WIN...
>> DAMN!
>> Jeff: MISSES AGAIN.
IT IS STILL ANYBODY'S GAME RIGHT
NOW.
TOMMY GETTING CLOSER.
JANET DROPS.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK.
HERE COMES THAT WIND AGAIN.
CAN DEAN GET IT BACK UNDER
CONTROL?
TOMMY NOW AT THE END.
DEAN FOR THE WIN... AND HE'S GOT
IT.
DEAN WINS INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY!
GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
>> NICE JOB.
>> LET'S GO, BABY.
>> AMAZING JOB.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: DEAN, COME ON OVER.
BACK-TO-BACK IMMUNITY WINS.
SAFE TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
AND GUARANTEED A SPOT IN THE
FINAL FOUR.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
TONIGHT.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE ONE MORE BIG
DECISION.
YOU HAVE LUNCH WAITING FOR YOU
BACK AT CAMP.
THE QUESTION IS WHICH ONE PERSON
ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE?
>> DEAN, I'VE BEEN SUPPORTING
YOU FOR A LOT OF STUFF.
>> AS HAVE ALL OF YOU.
>> I HAVEN'T EATEN LIKE YOU
HAVEN'T EATEN.
>> I MEAN, JEFF, TO BE HONEST,
THIS IS ABOUT THE FINAL FOUR,
WHO IS GOING TO WIN, AND
POTENTIALLY WHO IS GOING TO TAKE
ME WITH THEM IF IT'S NOT ME.
>> Jeff: AN YOU'RE ALSO
FUELING SOMEBODY FOR THE NEXT
CHALLENGE.
>> TRUE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE NOURA.
>> Jeff: REALLY?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: WHAT INSPIRED THAT
OUT OF NOWHERE?
>> I LOVE HER STOICISM, HER
POSITIVITY.
WE'VE BEEN BUTTING HEADS A
LITTLE BIT, AND I AM ONE FOR
GETTING RID OF BEAST, NO PUN
INTENDED, AND MAKING THINGS
RIGHT.
>> Jeff: SO THIS IS TO MAKE
AIMEDS?
>> YES.
>> WOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU CAN'T DENY THE ONLY DEAN
HAS ALREADY MADE UP HIS MIND,
AND IN MY OPINION HE'S JUST
DOING JURY MANAGEMENT WITH
NOURA, BUT THERE IS NO WAY THAT
SHE'LL FALL FOR IT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, DEAN AND
NOURA, IT WILL BE STEAK,
VEGETARIAN OPTION WAITING FOR
YOU BACK AT YOUR NEW HOME,
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
AS FOR THE REST OF YOU, TOMMY,
LAUREN, JANET AND NOURA, AFTER
37 VERY TOUGH DAYS IN THIS GAME,
THIS WILL BE THE END.
TONIGHT SOMEBODY WILL BE VOTED
OUT.
YOUR DREAM OF WINNING THIS GAME
WILL BE OVER.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> CONGRATS.
>> HERE WE ARE.
FINAL FIVE, D.K. CHILLING, DEAN
IS NO LONGER A GOAT.
HE'S GOT ONE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
HE'S GOT TWO, AN IDOL NULLIFIER,
THE SECOND EVER TO BE SEEN IN
"SURVIVOR."
AND THREE, A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
MAMA, LOOK AT ME NOW.
>> WE HIT THE JACKPOT.
>> NOW YOU OWE ME, HUH?
>> I DO.
>> LET'S DO IT.
LET'S DO IT.
I'M GOING TO DIG INTO IT.
>> WILL LET'S DO A CHEERS.
I WANT THE THANK YOU FOR PUTTING
OUR DIFFERENCES ASIDE AND LET'S
HAVE FUN AND INCLUDING ME IN IT,
YOU ARE A MAN IN MY EYES.
I KNOW I'VE CALLED YOU A BOY
BEFORE, AND I SEE YOU AS A MAN.
>> NOURA, CHEERS.
>> THANK YOU.
IN THIS GAME, MY RELATIONSHIP
WITH DEAN HAS BEEN CHALLENGING,
BUT WHEN DEAN CHOSE ME, I FELT
LIKE I WAS WALKING INTO A DATE.
>> I FEEL WEIRD.
>> SORRY.
I'M NEVER LOOKING DOWN ON YOU
ANYMORE.
>> ANYMORE.
>> IT'S WEIRD, FOR A GUY WHO IS
SHY, HE'S PRETTY SLICK AND WARM,
AND THIS WHOLE BEAUTIFUL
ROMANTIC DATE, THE FLIRTING, I
LOVED EVERY SECOND OF IT.
WHEN I GO TO A WEDDING OR I GO
TO A BIRTHDAY, THIS IS ALL I DO.
>> STOP TALKING.
>> OKAY.
FINE.
I AM CRAZY.
HAVE YOU EVER MET ANYONE AS
CRAZY AS ME?
>> AT LEAST YOU KNOW YOU'RE
CRAZY, AND NEW YORK I DON'T
THINK I HAVE.
>> HE'S CUTE, HE'S PLEASANT,
HE'S GENTLEMANLY.
I DON'T KNOW, HE'S GROWING ON
ME.
>> I WANT TO PUT THIS OUT THERE.
THIS IS NOT A ROMANTIC GESTURE.
PURE GAME PLAY.
>> I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YOUR SIGN IS WHAT?
>> ARIES.
>> WE GET ALONG WELL IN
>> DO I WANT TO SIT HERE AND
HEAR HER YAP THE WHOLE TIME?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
BUT DO I WANT TO BE TAKEN TO THE
FINAL THREE, ABSOLUTELY SOME
TRYING TO GET IN HER GOOD GRACES
AND SEE WHAT CAN HAPPEN WITH
NOURA AND DEAN, THE GODFORSAKEN
ROMEO AND JULIET OF SEASON 39.
>> WHAT I'M THINKING IS WE ALL
WANT TO GET TO THE FINAL TWO, I
WANT TO TAKE THAT NEXT STEP AND
SAY, IF I WIN, I WANT TO SIT
NEXT TO YOU.
IF YOU WIN, HOPEFULLY YOU TAKE
ME AND I HOPE THIS GESTURE DOES
HELP.
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT IS IF YOU
WIN TOMORROW, WHO ARE YOU
PICKING?
>> I WILL TAKE YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> I PROMISE.
I'M COMMITTED TO YOU.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
I'M TAKING YOU.
>> I HAVE A FINAL TWO PACT WITH
TOMMY AND NOW WITH NOURA, AND
DID DEAN CLOSE THE DEAL?
ABSOLUTELY, BECAUSE I GOT
EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED.
>> TODAY IS CHANGING THE FUTURE
OF THE GAME.
WE JUST NEED JANET OUT.
>> THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
LET'S SEE JANET GO HOME TONIGHT.
>> IT'S BEST FOR ALL OF OUR
GAMES.
WE'RE SMART PEOPLE.
BOTTOM LINE.
>> COOL.
>> TAKING ALL THE ROMANCE AND
FUN ASIDE, YOU KNOW, HE'S TRYING
THE SECURE HIS GAME AND BE IN
THE FINAL THREE.
HE'S BUTTERING ME UP FOR SURE,
AND I'M LIKING IT, AND SO ME IT
MAKES SENSE.
YEAH, THIS IS THE BEST.
WE NEED TO GET JANET OUT.
SHE'S TOO WELL LIKED AND
RESPECTED.
SHE'S GOT TO GO OUT AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> AT THE FINAL FIVE, THAT'S THE
LAST TIME I CAN PLAY THE IDOL.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE LAST OF IDOL PLAY.
I WANT THE USE IT TO THE BEST OF
MY ADVANTAGE.
>> IS IT AWKWARD?
>> YES.
IT IS AWKWARD.
>> BUT I HAVE AN IDOL IN MY
POCKET.
THIS WILL SET YOU UP TO THROW ME
UNDER THE BUS.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE THE BIG
MOVE.
I'M GOING TO CLAIM MY SPOT IN
THE FINAL FOUR.
I'M GOING TO LET THEM ALL KNOW
TO WATCH OUT FOR THE FIRE LADY.
>> SO WHAT WE DO IS PUT ALL THE
VOTES ON ME AND I VOTE LAUREN.
>> OKAY?
>> YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING?
WE NEED TO BE SMART ABOUT.
THIS I GOT A FRICKING IDOL, WE
NEED TO USE IT.
>> IT MAKES MY HAND CLEAN AND
YOU GET A BIG MOVE.
>> YOU GUYS ARE DONE ALREADY?
>> SO ALL THREE OF THEM GOT TO
VOTE ME, AND I'LL VOTE LAUREN.
>> OKAY.
>> TOMMY AND I MADE A PLAN.
WE'LL GET OUT LAUREN, WHO I
THINK IS THE BIGGEST THREAT.
LAUREN HAS A LOT OF FRIENDS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE LIKE HER.
SHE'S GOOD.
I GOT TO GIVE IT TO HER.
IT'S WORKED FOR HER TO GET HER
TO THE FINAL FIVE.
>> MY DATE TONIGHT WAS GREAT.
>> WHEN HE PICKED YOU...
>> I'M FEELING PRETTY CONFIDENT.
YOU CAN'T SET IT UP ANY BETTER.
>> IT'S GREAT.
>> I AM ALREADY THINKING ABOUT
WHAT I'M GOING TO SAY TO THE
JURY IN THE FINAL THREE.
AS F WE GET TO THE FINAL FOUR,
I'M PENTAGON YOU AND YOU'RE
PICKING ME.
>> OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> MY LIFE IS ON THAT
>> OKAY.
LET'S DO IT.
>> YOU TOO?
WE'RE WITH EACH OTHER?
>> IF I WIN, YEAH.
>> JANET IS MY "SURVIVOR" MOM.
WE ARE SUPER CLOSE AN WE HAVE
THIS EXTREME BOND.
IT WAS TOMMY AND HIS MOMMY.
SHE HAS A HUGE PART OF MY HEART.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I LOVE JANET.
SHE'S GREAT.
IT'S HARD THE BREAK AWAY FROM
HER EMOTIONALLY, BUT SADLY, I
REALLY NEED HER OUT OF THIS
GAME.
I HATE BEING LIKE THAT, BUT
SHE'S THE BEST FIRE MAKER, AND
SHE WOULD PROBABLY SIT AT THE
FINAL THREE AND WIN.
THIS IS OUR LAST CHANCE TO GET
HER.
>> JANET HAS I HAVE AN IDOL.
JANET WANTS LAUREN OUT.
BUT IN REALITY, LAUREN HAS BEEN
MY RIDE OR DIE SINCE DAY ONE.
HERE'S MY PLAN NOW, DEAN PLAYS
THE IDOL NULL FIRE CORRECTLY,
YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME TONIGHT
WITH DEAN PLAYING THE IDOL
NULLIFIER.
>> YOU WON'T PLAY IT?
>> HE'S NOT A DUMB PERSON.
HE WILL WANT TO MAKE A MOVE.
>> THAT'S THE THING THAT SCARES
ME.
>> HE WANTS A SPOT WITH YOU.
THEY BOTH -- NOURA AND DEAN BOTH
KNOW WE'LL TAKE EACH OTHER TO
THE END.
JANET HAS AN IDOL.
SHE THINKS I'M GOING HOME.
I CAN'T SAY THAT WITHOUT FEELING
MY HEART FALL INTO MY STOMACH.
MY GAME RESTS IN THE HANDS OF
DEAN.
>> JANET TOLD ME SHE HAS AN
IDOL.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> WITH YOUR IDOL NULLIFIER,
THAT WILL BE A GOOD MOVE FOR
YOU.
>> I WORRY BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
DEAN REALLY WANTS TO BE CLOSE
WITH TOMMY.
DEAN WILL BE LIKE, I DON'T WANT
TO PLAY MY NULLIFIER BECAUSE I
WANT TO SPLIT TOMMY AND LAUREN
UP.
>> I'M SO SCARED TO SIT NEXT TO
LAUREN OR JANET.
IF LAUREN SQUEAKS BY.
SHE'S BEATING BOTH OF US.
>> I MEAN, YOU'RE DEFINITELY NOT
KNOCKING OUT LAUREN?
>> I WOULD VOTE OUT JANET NEXT.
YOU HAVE THAT MOVE WITH THE IDOL
NULLIFIER.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE A DICTATOR
HERE.
A COUPLE DAYS AGO BACK AT VOKAI
I THOUGHT I SAW JANET FIND AN
IDO.
NOW I KNOW FOR A FACT SHE HAS
ONE.
BUT IT'S MY DECISION WHO GOES
HOME, JANET OR LAUREN.
LAUREN IS ALSO A THREAT IN THIS
GAME.
SHE JUST HAS A WAY ABOUT HER
THAT PEOPLE ATTACH TO.
>> GIRL.
>> LOOK WHAT HAPPENS WHEN NOURA
HAS SOME FUN AND SOME SUGAR.
>> I'M SO HAPPY.
>> I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW,
TOMMY AND LAUREN, THEY'RE TIED
TOGETHER AT THE HIP, SO DO I
WANT TO TRUST LAUREN SO TOMMY
HAS THE ONLY PLACE TO RUN TO IS
ME.
>> CAN I TALK ONE THING, THOUGH?
YOU'RE NOT TAKING OVER, RIGHT?
>> NO, NO, NO, I'M ABSOLUTELY
TAKING YOU, BUT NOURA, IF YOU
WIN, WILL YOU TAKE ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GETTING THIS WEIRD GUT
FEELING ABOUT DEAN.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
DEAN CAN PULL A SNEAKY ONE AND
SAY, I WANT LAUREN OUT.
>> MY BIGGEST THREAT IN THIS
GAME IS LAUREN.
WELL, IT'S JANET FIRST.
FOR ME IT'S LAUREN.
THERE IS NOTHING IN THIS WORLD
MORE FRUSTRATING THAN THIS.
>> I GOT ALL THE TOYS.
I GOT ALL THE BLING.
I GOT ALL THE POWER.
JANET HAS AN IDOL.
SHE THINKS SHE'S SITTING PRETTY.
AND LAUREN, KNOWING I HAVE THE
IDOL NULLIFIER IS FEELING GOOD.
BUT EITHER WAY YOU LOOK AT IT,
SOMEBODY IS GOING TO BE SHOCKED.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE JURY, TOO,
THEY'RE GOING TO BE, WHOO.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW BRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
SO, DEAN, YOUR SECOND IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE IN A ROW, GUARANTEES
YOU A SPOT IN THE FINAL FOUR.
IS THERE ANY SENSE OF RELIEF, OR
ARE YOU STILL IN THE SAME MODE?
>> THERE'S A SENSE OF RELIEF FOR
TONIGHT, BUT MY MIND IS STILL
THINKING ABOUT, OKAY, WHAT'S
TOMORROW'S CHALLENGE BRING OR
HOW CAN I TALK TO WHOEVER IS
LEFT TOMORROW TO SAY, IF YOU DO
WIN, CAN I COME WITH YOU?
THE MIND NEVER STOPS UNTIL YOU
SIT IN THOSE FINAL THREE SEATS
AND PITCH YOUR CASE.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, WHAT DID YOU
NOTICE AT CAMP AFTER DEAN WINS
THE CHALLENGE?
>> PANDEMONIUM SET IN, YOU KNOW?
IT JUST SPEAKS VOLUMES TO HOW
PEDAL TO THE METAL THIS GAME IS
RIGHT NOW AT DAY 37.
>> Jeff: DEAN, PANDEMONIUM,
DOES THAT DESCRIBE WHAT YOU SAW?
>> AT TIMES IT WAS LIKE THAT.
IT HELPS THAT WE HAVE A NICE
FIRE THAT JANET LOADS, THAT WE
HAVE A LITTLE FRUIT.
THAT KEEPS PEOPLE CENTRAL IN OUR
LITTLE HOUSE.
>> Jeff: JANET, WHAT IS IT
ABOUT THE FIRE?
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU ARE LIVING
ON ISLAND OF THE IDOLS?
>> OH, MY GOSH, IT'S SO AWESOME,
IT'S A STONE FIREPLACE.
I START IT IN LIKE ONE SECOND.
IT IS LIKE THE BEST.
>> Jeff: SO, LAUREN, WHEN
SOMEBODY ADORES FIRE, IT BRINGS
UP A QUESTION I'M SURE EVERYBODY
HAS TALKED ABOUT, THE FINAL FOUR
FIRE MAKING CHALLENGE IS A
PIVOTAL MOMENT IN THE GAME, AND
TONIGHT IS THE DECIDER WHOM ARE
THE FOUR PEOPLE WHO MIGHT BE
MAKING FIRE?
>> I MEAN, I DEFINITELY THINK
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE HAVE
ALL CONSIDERED.
AND WE CALL IT MAMA JANET'S
STOVE BECAUSE IT IS HER STOVE
AFTER ALL.
>> Jeff: JANET, YOU DON'T SEEM
CONCERNED.
>> I AM CONCERNED, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT?
I HAVE DEVELOPED A REPUTATION AS
FIRE LADY.
IF I LIVE PAST TONIGHT,LY TRY
AND USE IT TO MY ADVANTAGE.
BUT I CAN'T HELP IT.
YOU KNOW, I'M THE FIRE LADY.
>> Jeff: SO NOURA, WHAT DO YOU
DO?
WHAT IS THE GAME PLAY?
>> YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE
THINKING, WHO DO I NOT WANT TO
BE SITTING NEXT TO.
IT'S BECOME THAT SIMPLE, BUT
IT'S ABOUT THE JURY AND THEIR
PERSPECTIVE ON US, AND THEIR
PERSPECTIVES CREATE THE REALITY
OF THE GAME.
SO IT COMES DOWN TO WHAT DO WE
THINK THEY'LL THINK.
>> Jeff: TOMMY, IT'S REALLY
DIFFICULT BECAUSE THE JURY IS
WATCHING THE GAME EVOLVE, AND
YOU DON'T KNOW IF THEIR
PERSPECTIVE IS SHIFTING, AS
WELL.
>> YEAH.
I THINK OUR PERSPECTIVE OF EACH
OTHER CHANGE AND THEIR
PERSPECTIVES OF US CHANGE EVERY
SINGLE THING WE SAY, AS A
TEACHER, WHEN EGRADE A TEST,
THERE'S ONE RUBRIC.
I GRADE EVERYTHING TO IT, BUT
EACH AND EVERY SINGLE ONE OF
THEM HAS A DIFFERENT RUBRIC.
SOMEONE MIGHT LOVE EXTREME GAME
PLAY, BLINDSIDE, WHERE THE OTHER
PERSON, IF YOU BLINDSIDED THEM,
THEY MAY HATE YOU
YOU HAVE TO READ THEIR MINDS AND
DECIDE WHAT THEY WANT TO HEAR.
>> Jeff: JANET, EVEN WHEN IT
GETS DOWN TO FIVE, IT'S
INCREDIBLY INTENSE, BUT IT'S
THERE ARE SO FEW CHOICES A LOT
OF TIMES IT'S LIKE, I HOPE I'M
RIGHT, LET'S GO.
>> THERE ARE SO FEW CHOICE,
WE'RE ROLLING THE DICE AND
SAYING, I HOPE I COME OUT ON
TOP.
>> I'D ARGUE FLIPPING A COIN.
EVERYONE HAS WHO YOU WANT TO SIT
NEXT TO, FIVE MINUS TWO.
YOU HAVE TWO PEOPLE TO CHOOSE
FROM, WHO DO YOU WANT TO GO
HOME.
>> GIVE HIM AN "A."
>> Jeff: SO ARE WE READY TO
VOTE?
>> WE ARE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE.
NOURA, YOU'RE UP.
>> YOU'RE AN UNBELIEVABLE WOMAN.
I AM SO SORRY FOR THIS.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AUBRY YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF.
I'M PLAYING IT FOR ME.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
AND THIS IS THE IDOL NULLIFIER.
THE UNTIL PHIER BLOCKS THE POWER
OF AN IDOL ONLY IF IT IS PLAYED
AGAINST THE CORRECT PERSON.
THIS NULLIFIER WAS PLAYED
AGAINST JANET.
JANET, YOUR IDOL HAS NO POWER.
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST JANET
WILL STILL COUNT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, LAUREN.
JANET.
ONE VOTE LAUREN, ONE VOTE JANET.
TWO VOTES JANET, ONE VOTE
LAUREN.
16th PERSON VOTED OUT,
JANET.
THAT'S THREE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> AMAZING JOB, MAMA.
WELL DONE.
>> Jeff: JANET, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, JEFF.
THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> BYE, JANET.
>> BYE, GUYS.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> Jeff: WELL, YOU'VE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL FOUR.
TOMORROW YOU'LL COMPETE IN YOUR
FINAL IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
GRAB YOUR TORCH.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> I ALLOWED MYSELF TO GET
REALLY HOPEFUL BECAUSE I WAS SO
CLOSE TO HAVING A POSSIBLE DREAM
COME TRUE.
I FEEL REALLY NAIVE AND STUPID
TO THINK THAT I ALLOWED MYSELF
TO GO FURTHER IN MY HEAD THAN I
HAD IT.
BUT I'M PROUD OF THE GAME I
PLAYED.
IT'S BECAUSE IT'S WHO I AM.
>> Jeff: SHE'S ONE OF THE MOST
POPULAR WOMEN TO EVER PLAY
"SURVIVOR."
COME ON OUT, JANET.
SHE WAS THE OLDEST AND THE MOST
FEARED.
LOOK AT THAT.
ENERGY THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
HAVE A SEAT.
SO I WAS SAYING AS YOU WALKED
OUT THAT WHEN THIS STARTED, YOUR
BIGGEST FEAR WAS I'M THE OLDEST
WOMAN, I'LL BE FIRST OUT.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: AND WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE THE MOST FEARED, SO THEY
DESTROYED YOU WITH A BETRAYAL
>> I KNOW.
>> Jeff: IT'S A COMPLIMENT.
>> YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, AS MIND
BLOWING AS IT IS, IT'S JUST
LIKE, COME ON.
>> Jeff: THE NULLIFIER.
YOU HATE IT.
>> I HATE IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> Jeff: DO YOU KNOW WHO LOVES
THE NULLIFIER?
DEAN.
>> I'M SURE HE DOES.
>> Jeff: AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TOLD TOMMY.
>> MY LIFE IS TO LIVE BY MY GUT.
I WAS SLEEP DEPRIVED, HUNGRY, I
FOUND THIS IDOL.
I SHOWED IT TO HIM.
AS SOON AS I DID IT, I WAS LIKE,
OH, I DIDN'T LISTEN TO MY GUT.
>> Jeff: LISTEN TO YOUR GUT,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU WHAT THE STORY
FOR ME WAS.
YOU EVEN JUST SAID IT.
YOU SAID, STAY TRUE TO WHO YOU
ARE.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: SO WHAT KIND OF
RESPONSE HAVE YOU GOTTEN,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE INSPIRED LITTLE
KIDS AND YOU'RE INSPIRED WOMEN
YOUR AGE TO SAY, I CAN DO
ANYTHING.
>> I AM GETTING E-MAILS AND
LETTERS, SMILE MAIL LETTER FROM
TEN YEAR OLDS IN SEATTLE
WASHINGTON AND YOUNG MEN, 14,
12...
>> Jeff: SAYING WHAT?
>> I WANT TO LIVE MY TRUTH.
I'M GETTING EMOTIONAL, JEFF.
YOU DID THIS TO ME.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: JANET, YOU'RE AN
INSPIRATION.
AND THANK YOU FOR PLAYING.
>> THANK YOU.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> Jeff: DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR,
AND WITH THE FINAL FOUR
FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE, WHICH SHE
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE WON, ANYBODY
CAN WIN THIS GAME.
LATER TONIGHT, WHAT ARE WE DOING
FOR OUR 40th SEASON?
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
TAKE THAT IN.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S A LOT OF LOVE.
>> YOU STARTING THAT FIRE?
>> UP UNTIL THIS POINT I HAVE
MADE BIG, BIG, BIG-TIME MOVES
THAT WILL LIGHT UP THE JURY'S
EYES.
I HAVE MADE FINAL TWO PACTS WITH
TOMMY AND WITH NOURA, BECAUSE I
HAVE NOT MADE FIRE THIS WHOLE
GAME ONE TIME.
SO I REALLY NEED TO WIN TODAY'S
CHALLENGE.
I NEED TO HAVE THE COMFORT OF
KNOWING I AM GOING TO THE FINAL
THREE WITHOUT EVEN HAVING TO
MAKE FIRE.
>> I CAN'T MAKE FIRE.
I'M IN THE SAYING THAT BECAUSE I
WANT A GUARANTEED TWO.
I CAN'T DO IT.
>> I'M TELLING HER I CAN'T MAKE
FIRE EVEN THOUGH I CAN, BECAUSE
I'M JUST TRYING TO HAVE A PLAN
"B."
AND AT THIS POINT, MY MIND-SET
IS WIN THE CHALLENGE.
SO WHAT HAPPENS IF I DON'T WIN?
I NEED A PLAN, AND I NEED IT TO
HAPPEN NOW.
I CAN'T WAIT UNTIL AFTER THEY
WIN, BECAUSE THEN EVERYONE IS
GOING TO BE KISSING THEIR BUTT.
SO I WANT TO KISS THEIR BUTT
BEFORE THEY WIN.
I SWEAR ON MY LIVELY TAKE YOU TO
THE FINAL TWO IF I WIN THIS
CHALLENGE, AN I'VE NEVER SWORN
ON MY LIFE.
I WOULD SWEAR ON MY LIFE IF YOU
WOULD BRING ME IF YOU WIN.
I WANT TO BRING YOU THERE ON A
HEART LEVEL BECAUSE WE BOTH HAVE
THE BIGGEST HEARTS HERE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PITCH TO
NOURA BECAUSE I STILL DON'T GET
NOURA ON DAY 38.
SO WITH NOURA I'M TRYING TO MAKE
THE OTHER TRIBE MEMBERS SOUND A
LITTLE BAD.
DEAN SAID I PROMISED NOURA AND
SHE PROMISED ME.
HE SAID, I DON'T MEAN IT AT ALL.
BUT I'M JUST TELLING HER.
>> THAT COULD BE A LIE ALSO.
>> IT COULD BE A LIE, TOO, BUT I
WAS LIKE, OKAY.
I'M TELLING YOU ALL THE TRUTH,
AND I'M NOT TRYING TO PRESSURE
YOU.
>> WE NEED TO HAVE THESE
CONVERSATIONS.
>> IT FEELS NICE THAT I'M A HOT
COMMODITY RIGHT NOW.
IT'S LIKE I'M ANSWERING THE
PHONE, AND I'M LIKE, HELLO,
TOMMY CALLING.
HELLO, DEAN CALLING.
MAN, NOURA IS BECOMING POPULAR
NOW.
>> THIS IS THE THING, I HAVE
BEEN WORKING WITH YOU TO THIS
POINT, BUT NOW I TOLD MYSELF I'M
GOING TO BE SELFISH AT THE END
BUT ALSO FOLLOW MY HEART.
I'M A PEOPLE PLEASER IN MY LIFE
AND I WANT PEOPLE TO HAVE WHAT
THEY WANT SO IT'S A TOUGH
BALANCE BETWEEN WHAT DOES NOURA
WANT THE GIVE OTHERS AND WHAT
DOES NOURA WANT.
I MEAN, NOW -- SORRY, I SEE
PRETTY DEAN STRETCHING AND GOING
IN THE WATER.
HE'S FREAKIN' EVERYWHERE.
NOW I'M AT A LOSS FOR WORDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE BEEN OUT HERE A LONG TIME
AND NOT HAD ANY ROMANTICISM OR
THOUGHT OF A BOYFRIEND BACK
HOME.
I DON'T HAVE SOMETHING TO LOOK
FORWARD THE RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T SAY THERE'S NO ONE OUT
THERE, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
SAYING.
>> DEAN HAS DONE YOU WRONG THE
LAST TWO.
>> I'M ENJOYING IT.
I'M GOING TO ENJOY IT.
IT'S FINALLY ABOUT ME.
IT'S FINALLY ABOUT MY GAME.
IT'S FINALLY ABOUT WHAT SERVES
ME BEST, NOT TRYING TO MAKE
THINGS SO MUCH EASIER FOR
EVERYONE ELSE.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
A FAMILIAR CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, TAKE BACK
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
WOW, FIRST TIME.
>> WE HAVE THE CHANGE THINGS UP
FOR YOU.
>> Jeff: FOR THE LAST TIME,
IMMUNITY IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO STACK LETTER BLOCKS ON
A VERY WOBBLY PLATFORM.
FIRST PERSON TO SPELL "ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS" WINS IMMUNITY,
GUARANTEED A SPOTTED IN THE
FINAL THREE WHERE YOU WILL GATE
CHANCE TO PLEAD YOUR CASE TO THE
JURY ABOUT WHY YOU DESERVE THE
TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE
$1 MILLION PRIZE.
IN ADDITION, YOU WILL CHOOSE ONE
PERSON TO SIT NEXT TO YOU AND
FORCE THE OTHER TWO TO BATTLE
MAKING FIRE FOR THAT THIRD AND
FINAL SPOT.
MAYBE THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE OF
THE SEASON.
DRAW FOR SPOTS.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO FOR A GUARANTEED SPOT
AT THE FINAL THREE.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A STEADY HAND
TO WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
EVERY TIME YOU GET UP THERE,
YOU'VE GOT TO PRESS THAT PEDDLE
AND UNLOCK IT.
IT'S A MECHANISM WHICH MAKES IT
WOBBLY.
THEN YOU START PLACING LETTERS.
THAT'S THE EASY PART.
WHAT'S MORE DIFFICULT IS GETTING
BACK AND LOCKING IN WITHOUT
DISTURBING ANY OF THE PROGRESS
YOU HAVE MADE.
WHEN YOUR LETTERS DROP, YOU'VE
GOT TO LOCK IT BACK IN, PICK UP
THE LETTERS, TAKE THEM BACK,
PICK UP WHERE YOU LEFT OFF.
YOU CANNOT GET DISCOURAGED.
IT'S GOING THE HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO DROP.
EACH BID OF MOVEMENT.
MOVES THE ENTIRE MECHANISM.
EVERY STEP OFFERS THE
OPPORTUNITY OF DANGER.
>> REALLY?
>> Jeff: REALLY.
IT SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE THAT YOU CAN
FINISH THIS CHALLENGE.
SOMEBODY WILL.
DEAN BACK WITH THAT FIRST WORD.
DEAN TRYING TO FIND THAT FOOT
PEDDLE.
TRYING TO LOCK IN RIGHT NOW.
AND HE DOES.
DEAN HAS HIS FIRST WORD.
NOURA IS TAKING A LOT OF TIME
THAT.
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
NEVER TAKE YOUR EYES OFF THOSE
BLOCKS.
NOURA BACK WITH THE FULL FIRST
WORD.
IT IS NOW DEAN IN THE LEAD WITH
NOURA RIGHT BEHIND.
TOMMY WITH A NICE SAVE.
LAUREN NICE AND STEADY RIGHT
NOW.
AND DROPS AGAIN.
DEAN BACK WITH MORE LETTER
BLOCKS IN PLACE.
GETTING FASTER NOW.
THESE LETTERS STARTING TO GO UP
MORE QUICKLY.
NOURA RIGHT BEHIND.
NOURA HAS TWO WORDS.
DEAN HAS TWO WORDS.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
YOU'RE GOING TO EARN THIS ONE.
THE MORE LETTERS YOU HAVE, THE
MORE DIFFICULT IT BECOMES.
DEAN DROPS A LETTER.
A BIG SETBACK NOW.
HE HAS TO LOCK IN, HEAD BACK
WITH NOURA IN THE LEAD NOW,
YOU'RE ALL SLOWLY STARTING TO
REALIZE THAT IT'S A VERY GENTLE
TOUCH.
YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO BREATHE
TOO HEAVY NEAR THESE LETTERS.
IT COULD KNOCK THEM OFF.
THAT MECHANISM IS MOVING.
NOW HAS HER FIRST TWO ROWS
COMPLETE.
SHE IS DOWN TO FIVE LETTERS LEFT
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
DEAN RIGHT ON HER TAIL.
LAUREN TRYING TO STAY IN IT.
TOMMY FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A
LONG TIME KEEPS SOME BLOCKS UP
ON HIS MECHANISM.
AND THE BLOCKS DROP.
NOURA WITH THE FINAL TWO LETTERS
FOR THIS CHALLENGE, AND IT IS
DEAN TRYING THE CATCH HER.
NOURA PLACES THE LAST LETTER.
HERE COMES DEAN, GAINING ON HER.
DEAN LOSES SEVERAL BLOCKS.
"CAN YOU SEE ME NOW" JUST --
NOURA JUST HAS TO GET BACK WITH
ALL OF THEM REMAINING IN PLACE.
IT WOULD TAKE COLOSSAL MISTAKE
FROM NOURA RIGHT NOW.
>> KEEP GOING.
YOU CAN DROP.
>> Jeff: IT'S DEAD QUIET.
THE ONLY SOUNDTRACK PLAYING
RIGHT NOW IN YOUR HEAD IS THAT
HEART RACING.
CAN SHE DO IT.
HER FOOT IS ON THE PEDDLE.
NOURA WINS HER THIRD INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY AND GUARANTEES HERSELF
A SPOT AT THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL, AMAZING EFFORT ON DAY
38.
NOURA, COME ON OVER.
>> GOOD JOB, NOURA.
>> Jeff: FOR THE THIRD TIME,
INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, YOU HAVE
MADE IT TO THE FINAL THREE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU DREAM ABOUT
WHEN YOU IMAGINE PLAYING THIS
GAME.
WHAT'S THE EMOTION RIGHT NOW?
>> MY EMOTION IS LIKE WOO, WOO.
I FEEL AMAZING.
THAT'S MY EMOTION.
>> Jeff: WELL,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ARE IN THE FINAL THREE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: TONIGHT YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE A BIG DECISION.
YOU'LL CHOOSE ONE OF THESE THREE
TO SIT NEXT TO YOU AT THE FINAL
TRIBAL AND YOU'RE GOING TO FORCE
THE OTHER TWO TO MAKE FIRE.
I'M GUESSING IT WILL BE AN
INTERESTING AFTERNOON.
CONGRATULATIONS.
FINAL THREE.
EVERYBODY ELSE SEE YOU TONIGHT
AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
CONGRATS.
>> I'M PROUD OF MYSELF.
LOOK WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
LOOK WHAT YOU CAN DO, YOU KNOW?
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE GAME, I
THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE THE
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT, AND LOOK
WHAT YOU CAN DO WHEN YOU REALLY
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
I DID THE IMPOSSIBLE.
>> NOURA HAS ALL THE POWER IN
THIS GAME FOR THE FIRST TIME.
SHE'S IN CHARGE OF WHO GETS
TAKEN TO THE FINAL THREE AND WHO
IS DOING FIRE.
I'M SCARED.
SHE CHANGES HER MIND ALL THE
TIME.
SHE'S ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AND IT'S REALLY HARD DEALING
WITH THE UNKNOWN IN "SURVIVOR."
SO I WOULD LOVE TO HEAR WHAT YOU
GUYS ARE THINKING, BUT THIS IS
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
I WANT TO JUMP IN THE OCEAN,
CLEAN OFF, AND THEN I ALREADY
KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO, AND I
WANT TO TELL IT TO YOU, AND I
WANT YOU TO KNOW THE PSYCHOLOGY
BEHIND IT.
I'M GOING TO LITERALLY TELL YOU
THE LOGIC.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE US
GO CRAZY?
>> CAN WE TALK ABOUT IT NOW?
>> I WANT THE CHILL AND I WANT
TO HAVE A PINE APPLE.
WE'RE FINAL FOUR.
LET'S JUST HAVE A LITTLE FUN AND
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO YOU.
IT FEELS AMAZING TO WIN THIS
LAST CHALLENGE.
BUT RIGHT NOW I'M SITTING EVEN
PRETTIER THAN USUAL.
BECAUSE IT SOLIDIFIES ME FINAL
THREE AND MY GAME HAS BEEN BOLD,
ZESTY, FLAVORFUL, INTERESTING,
UNIQUE, HEALTHY, FUN, DIFFERENT.
>> NOURA, WE'RE WAITIN&T MY
GIRL.
>> AND THIS DECISION IS VERY
IMPORTANT, AND I AM GOING TO BE
SELFISH.
I'M GOING TO BE NOURA, NOURA,
NOURA.
NOURA, NOURA, NOURA.
SO HOW I'M GOING TO DISPENSE THE
DECISION IS GOING TO BE
DIFFERENT THAN MOST PEOPLE
EXPECT.
ARE YOU OKAY GUYS?
>> WE'RE NERVOUS.
VERY NERVOUS.
>> OKAY.
BREVITY IS NOT MY STRONG SUIT,
SO I'M GOING TO EXPLAIN WHY I'M
MAKING THIS DECISION.
LAUREN, YOU ARE MY NUMBER ONE.
AT THIS POINT IN MY LIFE, YOU'RE
MY NUMBER ONE.
YOU HAVE GIVEN ME A FRIEND IN
THE GAME WHEN I HAD NONE.
DEAN, YOU'RE THE MAN.
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU ARE ELOQUENT.
YOU'RE SMOOTH, YOU'RE CALM AND
COLLECTED AS A CUCUMBER, EVEN IN
THE HARDEST TIMES OF THE GAME,
AND YOU HAVE MADE SOME GREAT
MOVES.
WHATEVER.
KUDOS TO YOU.
TOMMY, YOU ARE LOYAL, YOU ARE AN
INCREDIBLE PERSON.
YOU LITERALLY HELPED ME DO
THINGS THAT MADE ME GET TO WHERE
I AM.
YOU COULD HAVE SAID, FORGET THIS
GIRL, SHE'S CRAZY, WE CAN'T
TRUST HER, BOOM, OUT.
THAT WOULD BE AN EASY VOTE FOR
YOU.
>> LIKE NOURA NORMALLY DOES,
SHE'S TALKING A MILE A MINUTE.
SHE'S TALKING WITH HER HEAD.
SHE'S TALKING WITH HER HEART,
HER STORIES ARE GOING BACK AND
FORTH.
>> I GAVE YOU MY NUMBER.
I GAVE YOU A WINK.
YOU STILL DIDN'T CALL ME.
OTHER PEOPLE ARE CALLING ME.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE'S
GOING.
YOU JUST WANT TO SAY, SPIT IT
OUT, WHO ARE YOU TAKING AND WHO
IS MAKING FIRE, BUT THAT'S NOT
HOW NOURA OPERATES.
>> I FEEL LIKE I HAVE GIVEN AMMO
TO MANY DIFFERENT PLAYERS WHO
HELPED THEM, BUT NO ONE HAS DONE
FOR ME, BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT I THINK.
IT MATTERS WHAT THE JURY THINKS.
SO LAUREN, YOU DO YOUR OWN THING
IN YOUR OWN WAY, AND IT WORKS.
YOU SEE IT, WHENEVER I GET YOU
ALL TO MYSELF, I'M LIKE, I HAVE
LAUREN, THE QUEEN.
BUT BECAUSE YOU ARE SUCH A
THREAT IN THE EYES OF EVERYONE,
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, IT'S GOING
TO BE YOU GOING TO FIRE.
YOU ARE THE QUEEN RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO PUT YOU TO
FIRE.
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO HAVE THE
HARDEST CASE.
>> I GET IT, NOURA.
>> THAT'S WHERE WE GO NEXT.
TOMMY, YOU TOLD ME POINT BLANK
YOU SUCK AT FIRE.
I TRUST THAT.
BUT I DO RECOGNIZE I AM STILL
HERE BECAUSE OF TOMMY.
DEAN, ON OUR LITTLE DATE
YESTERDAY, WHICH I LOVED AND WE
HAD A GREAT TIME.
I TOLD YOU I WOULD COMMIT TO
YOU, BECAUSE THAT POINT YOUR
GAME WAS AS HOT AS IT IS RIGHT
NOW.
YOU'RE ON FIRE, LITERALLY.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON FIRE
TONIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
AND I'M SORRY, MOST IMPORTANTLY,
IT'S BECAUSE YOU CAN DO AND
LAUREN IS MORE DANGER ROUSE TO
ME.
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THIS
MEANS.
I OWE YOU MY LIFE.
I REALLY DO.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
SHE'S HERE.
I HAVEN'T MADE FIRE THE WHOLE
TIME I'VE BEEN HERE.
I PRACTICED BEFORE I LEFT BUT
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
I WANT THE KEEP PLAYING.
I'M NOT GOING TO LEAVE WITHOUT A
FIGHT.
I HAVE TO STOP CRYING AND GO
PRACTICE MAKING FIRE.
>> LAUREN IS CRYING.
FULLY TEAR, FULLY YELLING, FULLY
EMOTIONAL.
I JUST PUT ON A SMIRK, BECAUSE
THAT'S WHERE YOU WANT YOUR
COMPETITION TO BE RIGHT NOW.
I HOPE SHE THINKS I'M SUPER GOOD
AT IT, BECAUSE I HAVE NEVER MADE
FIRE IN MY LIFE.
I JUST WANT THE KEEP MY COOL AND
SEE IF D.K. CHILLING CAN REALLY
RISE TO THE OCCASION.
AND IF I CAN WIN THIS, IT WILL
SEAL A GOOD-LOOKING RESUME FOR
ME.
>> THEN WHAT?
>> THEN YOU PUT YOUR LITTLE
BAMBOO ON, A LITTLE COCONUT HUSK
AND YOU'RE GOOD.
>> I'M AT THE POINT NOW WHERE I
HAVE TO HELP THEM MAKE FIRE,
BECAUSE ONE IS GOING TO BE ON
THE JURY, AND I STILL WANT THEIR
VOTE.
>> YOU GOT FLAME.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED IS A FLAME.
I'M IN THE AN EXPERT.
SO I DON'T WANT TO TELL YOU
WRONG INFORMATION AND YOU DO IT.
>> I HEAR YOU.
>> LAUREN IS MY BEST FRIEND OUT
HERE.
I WOULD LOVE FOR HER TO WIN, BUT
THAT'S IF I WAS THINKING WITH MY
HEART.
I HAVE TO THINK WITH MY HEAD.
YOU SHOULD PUT A COUPLE BAMBOOS
ON THE BOTTOM TO AIR IT OUT LIKE
THIS.
THEN YOU WANT THE MAKE A TEPEE.
>> LAUREN AND I MADE ALMOST
EVERY MOVE TOGETHER AS A DYNAMIC
DUO.
SO I DON'T WANT HER SITTING IN
THE FINAL THREE BECAUSE I DON'T
WANT TO SPLIT VOTES WITH HER.
>> THERE YOU GO.
YEAH, BOOM.
SMOKING.
THERE YOU GO.
>> IT SHOULD CATCH LIKE CRAZY.
YOU'RE GOOD.
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
SO I'M GOING TO TELL DEAN, MAKE
FIRE AND DO IT WELL.
>> THAT WAS VERY HELPFUL, THANK
YOU.
>> IF I'M SITTING NEXT TO DEAN
AND NOURA, I THINK I HAVE REALLY
GOOD CHANCE TO WIN $1 MILLION.
>> I REALLY TRULY LOVE YOU AND
IT HURTS ME THAT I HAD TO MAKE
THIS DECISION.
I KNOW YOU WANT SPACE AND QUIET,
SO I WILL GIVE IT TO YOU OKAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHENEVER YOU WANT TO TALK OR
YOU NEED SOMETHING...
>> NOURA, I CAN'T, BECAUSE I
HAVE TO FOCUS ON THIS AND YOU
PUT ME AGAINST A GUY THAT YOU
KNOW CAN MAKE FIRE.
>> BOTTOM LINE, YOU'RE THE
BIGGEST SOCIAL THREAT.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT A NUMBER ONE
MEANS?
A NUMBER ONE IS NOT SOMEBODY YOU
DON'T TAKE TO THE END.
>> WOULD YOU RATHER IT WILL ME
YOU AND TOMMY AND I HAVE NO
CHANCE TO DO WELL.
>> EXPLAIN IT TO ME.
>> YOU'RE BEING SELFISH.
>> I'M BEING SELFISH?
>> YES.
>> IF YOU WERE REALLY MY GIRL,
YOU WOULD BE HUMBLE.
>> YOU'RE TALKING TO ME AND
TELLING ME ABOUT BEING HULLABLE?
HOW DARE YOU, NOURA.
YOU SHOULD SAY GOOD JOB.
>> PLEASE, LEAVE.
>> I WILL STEAL ALL THE
CONFETTI.
>> I AM GIVING YOU THIS TIME TO
DO WHAT YOU WANT WITH IT.
>> YOU'RE NOT GIVING ME
ANYTHING.
YOU'RE TELLING ME YOUR GOING TO
STEAL THE MACHETE
>> I'M TELLING YOU THAT I'Mi
YOU IF I WANTED TO, I COULD DO
WHATEVER I WANT TO INCAPACITATE
YOU.
>> THAT'S SUPPOSED TO MAKE ME
FEELING BETTER?
NOURA IS GIVING ME LINES OF
BALONEY.
PLEASE GIVE ME SPACE AND FOR HER
TO TELL ME SHE'S GOING THE HIDE
THE MACHETES AND THE FLINTS, WHO
ARE YOU?
NOURA IS GOING TO SEE WHY SHE
DIDN'T PICK ME, BECAUSE I'M
GOING TO WIN.
>> I'M PISSED OFF, WHICH IS FUEL
THAT I'M GOING TO USE TONIGHT.
IT'S JUST A SMALL FIRE THAT'S
STANDING IN BETWEEN ME AND $1
MILLION.
THE TITLE IS SO IMPORTANT TO ME
BECAUSE IT'S LIKE WHEN YOU'RE
LITTLE, YOU LOOK UP TO SUPERMAN
AND SUPERWOMAN AND ALL THESE
PEOPLE.
AND YOU SEE THEM KEEP WINNING
AND WINNING.
TONIGHT I WANT TO HAVE THAT.
LIKE I WANT TO BE THAT
SUPERHERO.
I BELIEVE IN MYSELF.
I KNOW THAT I CAN DO THIS.
BECAUSE I HAVE TO WIN.
>> Jeff: WE'LL NOW WRING IN
THE MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
LET'S GET TO IT.
SO TODAY, NOURA, YOU WIN YOUR
THIRD INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, AND IN DOING SO
GUARANTEE YOURSELF A SPOT AT THE
FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL TOMORROW
NIGHT WHERE YOU ARE GOING TO A
DEBT CHANCE TO PLEAD YOU CASE TO
THIS JURY.
WHEN YOU GOT BACK THE CAMP, DID
YOU HAVE ANY MOMENTS OF
REFLECTION FOR WHAT YOU'VE
ACCOMPLISHED GETTING TO THE END?
FOR ME THIS JOURNEY HAS BEEN
ABOUT APPRECIATING EVERY SINGLE
STEP, AND TO COMPLETE A VERY
CHALLENGING CHALLENGE LIKE THAT
AND KNOW THAT I DID IT, IT IS
EVERYTHING.
IT SHOWS YOU YOU HAVE SO MUCH
MORE IN YOU THAN YOU KNOW, AND
I'M FEELING LIKE, YES, I'M FINAL
THREE.
THIS IS EVERYTHING.
BUT THEN YOU KNOW YOU HAVE SOME
HARD DECISIONS TO MAKE.
SO NOW YOU HAVE TO GIVE THE NEWS
TO SOMEONE THAT'S GREAT.
HEY, YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
AND TWO PEOPLE, HEY, YOU GOT TO
FIGHT FOR THIS.
>> Jeff: SHALL WE JUST GET TO
IT?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, NOURA,
WALK US THROUGH IT.
WHAT IS YOUR DECISION?
>> SO BASICALLY WE GET BACK AND
I START BY SAYING, LAUREN YOU'VE
BEEN MY NUMBER ONE MANY THIS
GAME THE ENTIRE TIME, AND I'M
NOT EVEN GOING THE LOOK AT YOUR
EXPRESSIONS RIGHT NOW, BUT YOUR
FACE REALLY IS AMERICAY AND KIND
OF RUDE.
I'M TRYING GIVE YOU LOVE AND
GIVE YOU PROMISE AND LET YOU
KNOW, REALLY, WHERE I'M COMING
FROM.
>> I'M LETTING YOU SAY YOUR
PIECE, GIRL.
SPEAK UP.
I'M LISTENING.
>> I'M TELLING YOU.
AM I GOING TO RISK MY GAME WHERE
I GOT A CLEAN SHOT AT THE
FINISH, AM I GOING TO BE DUMB
ENOUGH, DUMB ENOUGH, DID YOU
THINK I WAS DUMB ENOUGH THAT I
WOULD BRING MY LAUREN NUMBER ONE
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY NUMBER ONE?
NO.
THAT'S WHERE I HAVE A PROBLEM.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING COMBATIVE BECAUSE I
HAVE BEEN WATCHING THIS GAME FOR
18 YEARS, AND I WILL NEVER GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: NOURA, IT WOULD
APPEAR THAT ONE OF THE PEOPLE
THAT'S GOING TO BE MAKING FIRE
IS LAUREN.
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> Jeff: SO LAUREN, CAN YOU
EXPLAIN TO ME THE TENSION?
>> I PERSONALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE IDEA OF, HEY, YOU'RE MY
NUMBER ONE, YOU'RE MY BEST
FRIENDS, BUT I'M GOING TO TAKE
YOU OUT.
THOSE TWO THINGS DON'T LINE UP
FOR ME.
I WON'T TAKE THAT AS A
COMPLIMENT.
I TAKE IT AS A COP-OUT.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT NOURA SEES
ME AS THAT THREAT.
SHE BETTER HOPE I DON'T COME
BACK.
>> Jeff: WHO IS SHE GOING TO
GO UP AGAINST?
>> SHE'S GOING TO GO UP AGAINST
DEAN, BECAUSE IN TWO SECONDS HE
>> Jeff: YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
SOMEONE WHO CAN TAKE OUT LAUREN.
>> I WANT THE TAKE TOMMY YOU TO
FINAL THREE AND LET THESE GUYS
TO IT.
>> Jeff: TOMMY, HOW DOES THAT
FEEL TO BE IN THE FINAL THREE?
>> IT FEELS GREAT.
I MEAN, I OWE HER.
AND IT MAKE ME SUPER EXCITED
THAT I GET AN OPPORTUNITY TO
PITCH TO THE JURY WHY I THINK,
YOU KNOW, I HAVE A CHANCE OF
WINNING, BUT RIGHT NOW MY MIND
IS RUNNING ON WHAT'S GOING ON
NEXT, WHO IS GOING TO BE SITTING
ON THE THIRD SEAT.qi
SO I THINK IT'S STILL THE FINAL
THREE, THEN YOU CAN'T REALLY
THINK OF WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
AT THE FINAL THREE.
>> Jeff: DEAN, HOW DO YOU
FEEL?
WERE YOU SURPRISED THAT YOU WERE
SELECTED TO MAKE FIRE?
>> I WASN'T TOO SURPRISED AND I
KIND OF PUT ON MY HARD HAT AND
WENT TO PRACTICE.
I'M FEELING GOOD.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SO NOURA, TOMMY,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU WILL BE IN THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THERE IS ONE SEAT LEFT.
IT WILL BE DECIDED BY A
FIRE-MAKING SHOWDOWN BETWEEN
LAUREN AND DEAN.
TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
DEAN, YOU'RE ON THE FAR ONE.
LAUREN, YOU'RE ON THE NEAR.
YOU EACH HAVE THE SAME AMOUNT OF
SUPPLIES.
>> COOL.
>> Jeff: YOU HAVE TO BUILD A
FLAME FROM THE BASE THAT GROWS
HIGH ENOUGH TO BURN THROUGH THE
ROPE AND RAISE THE FLAG.
LITERALLY, THIS COULD BE A $1
MILLION FIRE YOU ARE BUILDING.
ARE YOU BOTH READY?
>> YOU READY?
>> READY AS I'LL EVER BE.
>> Jeff: AND BEGIN.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE A FEW
DIFFERENT WAYS YOU CAN GET
STARTED WHEN YOU'RE BUILDING A
FIRE LIKE THIS.
THE ONLY ONE THAT MATTERS IS THE
ONE THAT WORKS FOR YOU.
LAUREN QUICKLY SHAVING SOME
MAGNESIUM.
DEAN IS TRYING TO BUILD HIS
STRUCTURE FIRST.
THEN GET FIRE.
DEAN STARTING TO SAVE SOME
MAGNESIUM.
LAUREN GOING FOR IT FIRST,
TRYING TO GET SOME FLAME.
DEAN GOING FOR IT NOW.
38 DAYS COMES DOWN TO THIS, THE
MOST BASIC OF "SURVIVOR" SKILLS.
DEAN WITH A LITTLE BIT OF A
FLAME.
CAN HE KEEP IT GOING?
THAT WILL BURN QUICKLY.
THE KEY IS WHEN YOU GET A FLAME,
YOU'VE GOT TO GET SOME STICKS IN
THERE, SOME KINDLING TO CATCH.
LAUREN HAS FIRE NOW.
SHE'S IN IT.
>> COME ON, LAUREN.
COME ON.
>> Jeff: DEAN'S FLAME STARTING
TO SUBSIDE.
HE'S TRYING TO BRING MORE LIFE
TO IT NOW, BREATHING SOME LIFE
INTO IT.
LAUREN NOW TRYING TO ADD SOME
STICKS IN THERE.
YOU HAVE TO BUILD A BASE.
IF YOU KEEP JUST PUT THAT
QUICK-BURNING HUSK YOU'RE GOING
TO RUN OUT OF IT.
BOTH PLAYERS HAVE FIRE, BOTH
PLAYERS ARE IN THIS.
BOTH PLAYERS REALLY PRETTY EVEN
RIGHT NOW.
DEAN'S FIRE HAS A BIT MORE OF A
BASE.
STILL A LONG WAY FROM THAT ROPE.
LAUREN TRYING TO GET THAT TO GO.
ADDING MORE STICKS.
DEAN'S FIRE BURNING BIGGER NOW.
YOU'RE STILL IN IT.
YOU JUST GOT TO BUILD.
>> DEAN'S KILLING IT.
>> Jeff: DEAN'S FLAME STARTING
TO INCREASE.
IT'S NOT BLOWING UNDER THE ROPE.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR LAUREN.
LAUREN'S FIRE IS STILL GOING.
DEFINITELY NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
SHE JUST HAS TO GROW IT.
IT HAS TO START BURNING HIGHER.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET TO THAT
ROPE.
DEAN STARTING TO BURN THAT ROPE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
YOU'RE BURNING THE ROPE.
YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: DEAN IS RIGHT ON THE
EDGE OF VICTORY.
>> YOU'RE THERE.
>> Jeff: THE ROPE IS BURNING
LITTLE BY LITTLE.
LAUREN IS TRYING TO STAY IN IT.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> Jeff: THERE IT IS.
DEAN HAS DONE IT.
DEAN HAS MADE FIRE.
HE WILL TAKE THE FINAL SPOT AT
THE FINAL THREE.
>> FOR RECORD, THIS MORN WAS
FIRST TIME I MADE FIRE THE WHOLE
DAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT NOURA IS
TALKING ABOUT.
>> WELL DONE, GUYS.
>> Jeff: SO LAUREN, THE
TOUGHEST WAY TO GO OUT OF THIS
GAME IS TO FIGHT FOR 38 DAYS AND
THEN LOSE IN A FIRE-MAKING
CHALLENGE WHEN YOU HAD A FIRE,
AS WELL.
YOU OUTLASTED A LOT OF VOTES.
YOU GOT AS CLOSE AS YOU CAN GET.
THE DREAM OF WINNING HAS FALLEN
SHORT.
TALK TO ME, THOUGH, ABOUT THE
ADVENTURE OF 38 DAYS IN FIJI
PLAYING THIS COMPLICATED GAME.
>> I MEAN, THE FACT THAT I
STAYED OUTSIDE FOR 38 DAYS IS
AMAZING IN AND OF ITSELF.
LIKE I DON'T GO OUTSIDE FOR MORE
THAN TWO HOURS.
BUT FOR ME, WHAT THIS STORY HAS
REALLY BEEN ABOUT IS BELIEVING
IN MYSELF, AND I THINK THAT I
FAKE BELIEVED IN MYSELF AND I
TOLD MYSELF ALL THE THINGS THAT
I THINK PEOPLE SEE ABOUT ME, BUT
NOW I CAN WALK AWAY FROM THIS
GAME WITH MY HEAD HELD HIGH
KNOWING THAT I AM A STRONG
"SURVIVOR" PLAYER, AND, HEY,
GOING OUT AS THE BIGGEST THREAT
IS A GOOD WAY TO GO.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, TIME FOR YOU
TO GRAB YOUR TORCH.
>> NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD COME
TO THIS.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> OH, JEFF.
>> Jeff: LAUREN, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
>> THANK FOR PLAYING.
>> BYE.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE, TOMMY.
>> Jeff: NOURA, TOMMY, DEAN,
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'VE MADE IT TO THE END.
YOU'VE GONE AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO
IN THE GAME.
TOMORROW NIGHT YOU WILL EACH GET
A CHANCE TO PLEAD YOUR CASE TO
THE JURY ABOUT WHY YOU DESERVE
THE TITLE OF SOLE SURVIVOR AND
THE $1 MILLION PRIZE.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT IN FIJI.
I SUGGEST YOU TRY TO GET SOME
SLEEP.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> THIS SUCKS REALLY BAD.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
NOURA WAS RIGHT.
EVERYONE DOES LIKE ME ON THE
JURY, AND IF I DID MAKE IT, I
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE WON.
SO I JUST WISH SHE DIDN'T FIGURE
THAT OUT.
THAT'S ALL SHE WROTE.
I LOVE "SURVIVOR," AND I WANT TO
PLAY AGAIN.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jeff: IT'S ONE OF THE MOST
DRAMATIC MOMENTS OF THE SEASON.
LAUREN FALLS JUST SHORT OF WHAT
MIGHT HAVE BEEN A $1 MILLION
FIRE.
HERE SHE IS.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
ANOTHER POWERFUL WOMAN THIS
SEASON WHO LITERALLY WAS TOO BIG
OF A SOCIAL THREAT.
YOU HAVE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT
THIS, AS YOU SAID, SENTENCE YOU
WERE SEVEN.
THERE ARE A LOT OF SEVEN YEAR
OLDS HERE TONIGHT.
GIVE ME THE HIGHLIGHTS.
YOU WENT ALMOST AS FAR AS YOU
CAN GO.
>> I DIDN'T THINK I WAS GOING TO
GO OUT THERE, JEFF, WIN AN IDOL,
WIN AN IMMUNITY, MEET ROB AND
SANDRA WHO I HAVE IDOLIZED, BUT
I HATE TO TOOT MY OWN HORN, BUT
TOOT, TOOT, BECAUSE I DID THAT.
>> Jeff: AND SINCE YOU ARE THE
PERSONIFICATION OF A SEVEN YEAR
OLD WHO GOT ON "SURVIVOR," WHAT
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM OTHER KIDS
WHO ARE COMING UP TO YOU?
>> IT'S SO GREAT TO HEAR THAT
I'M AN INSPIRATION TO SOMEONE
ELSE.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT I EVER
THOUGHT THAT I WOULD BE.
YOU KNOW, JUST TO BE ABLE TO DO
THAT FOR SOMEONE ELSE AND GIVE
SOMEONE A VOICE AND LET THEM
KNOW THAT IF I CAN DO IT, THIS
INDOOR BARBIE THAT DOESN'T GO
OUTSIDE, YOU CAN DO IT, TOO.
AND I JUST WANT TO SAY THANK YOU
FOR GIVING ME THE OPPORTUNITY.
>> Jeff: I THINK YOU WERE
FANTASTIC.
GOT TO SAY, HERE'S THE THING,
ABOUT THREE TIMES A WEEK
SOMEBODY COMES UP AND SAYS, HEY,
I HAVE A FRIEND, THEY SHOULD BE
ON "SURVIVOR," A FRIEND OF OUR,
A MUTUAL FRIEND CAME UP TO ME,
WE HAVE SOMEBODY WHO SHOULD BE
ON SURVIVOR, THE ONLY TIME
WITHIN 20 YEARS, AND WITHIN 15
SECONDS OF HER TALKING, OH, MY
GOD, SHE'S THE ONE, SHE'S GOING
TO BE ON THE SHOW.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
TO SOMEBODY RIGHT AFTER THEY'RE
VOTED OUT, CHECK OUT OUR
PONDEROSA SERIES.
YOU'LL SEE LAUREN, JACK, ELAINE,
JAMAL.
THEY'RE ALL.
THERE IT'S REALLY COOL.
OKAY, OUR FINAL THREE.
THIS CLOSE TO CROWNING A WINNER.
MORE OF THE FINALE RIGHT AFTER
THIS.
WELL DONE.
>>ITES DAY 39 ON SEASON 39.
>> WOW.
THAT'S CRAZY, HUH?
>> WE PLAYED "SURVIVOR" AND
DIDN'T GET VOTED OUT.
RIGHT?
>> TOMMY, I FREAKIN' LOVER YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD TO WAKE
UP ON DAY 39.
I STARTED OFF FEELING I'M GOING
TO BE FIRST ONE TO GO HOME.
NOW I'M SITTING PRETTY IN FINAL
THREE.
IT'S WEIRD.
I'M PROUD OF MY GAME.
I LOOK BACK.
I CAN SEE THE STRATEGY.
I PLAYED IN THE MOMENT, AND I'M
NOT GOING OUT UNTIL I GIVE IT MY
EVERYTHING.
THAT'S WHAT I DO IN MY LIFE.
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE DONE IN THIS
GAME.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> FINAL THREE, BABY.
>> FREAKIN' AWESOME.
>> CHEESE, EGGS, SAUSAGE
>> PANCAKES.
>> DAY 39 IS GLORIOUS, BECAUSE I
REALIZE I HAVE A GOOD SHOT AT
WINNING $1 MILLION.
I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER.
I'M FIRED UP.
BACON, BABY.
THIS GAME IS THE HARDEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE IN MY LIFE, BUT
ON THE OTHER HAND, IT'S ONE OF
THE GREATEST THINGS I'VE DONE,
BECAUSE I MOVE TO MYSELF THAT
NOW I CAN CONQUER ANYTHING THAT
COMES IN MY PATH.
>> THIS VICTORY TASTES GOOD.
>> DO YOU WANT TO SAY, HEY, JUST
GIVE TOMMY THE MILLION, WE'RE
COOL.
THAT WOULD BE COOL.
[NOURA LAUGHING]
>> I'M CONFIDENT IN THE GAME I
PLAYED.
THIS MAY BE THE MOST PROUD OF
MYSELF, SWEAR TO GOD, I'VE BEEN
IN MY WHOLE ENTIRE LIFE.
TO BE HONEST, NOURA I THINK IS
SEEN AS A LONG SHOT, SO EVEN
THOUGH IT'S A FINAL EYE, IN MY
EYES IT FEELS LIKE A FINAL TWO
FOR TOMMY AND MYSELF.
SO TONIGHT IT COMES DOWN TO DEAN
VERSUS TOMMY, MAGIC VERSUS BIRD.
IT'S GOING TO BE A SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN THE TWO OF US.
MAY THE BEST MAN WIN.
>> AMAZING.
I'M PROUD OF US.
>> BOYS MAN.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO BE LIKE, YOU
TWO DID IT.
I'M GOING TO PITCH MY GAME.
>> IF IT COMES DOWN, PITCH ME
WHY YOU THINK YOU DID BETTER
THAN TOMMY.
>> GOING IN, I DO THINK IT'S A
TWO-MAN RACE.
HOWEVER, YOU CAN'T COUNT OUT
NOURA.
SHE DOES THE IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT SHE'S GOING
TO SAY.
>> WE BEAT ALL THOSE PEOPLE THAT
ARE VOTING.
>> MAY GAME IS ALL ABOUT SOCIAL
PLAY.
I ALWAYS WANT TO BE THE CENTER
POINT SOME WHEN NOURA SAYS,
TOMMY, CAN YOU HELP ME WITH MY
SPEECH, I'M LIKE, OF COURSE I
CAN, NOURA.
I CAN DEFINITELY HELP YOU CAN
YOUR SPEECH.
>> WE DEFINITELY NEED TO SHUT
DOWN DEAN'S GAME.
THERE IS A NAME CALLED A LACKEY,
YOU KNOW, THAT BECAUSE YOU'RE A
TEACHER.
>> I'M A WILL BY BECAUSE IF YOU
DO THAT, HE ATTACHES HIMSELF TO
NUMBERS, DOESN'T MAKE MY MOVES.
WHY SHOULD WE REWARD HIM IN
WE'RE LIVING IN A WORLD WHERE
YOU GOT TO MAKE MOVES AND DO
STUFF
>> WHAT A BEAUTIFUL SPEECH.
THERE'S IN HARD FEELINGS.
THE REASON HE'S SITTING HERE IS
BECAUSE NO ONE WANTED TO VOTE
HIM OUT BECAUSE EVERYONE WANTED
TO SIT NEXT TO HIM.
>> TOMMY, I LOVE YOU, THIS IS
ANOTHER REASON WHY IT WAS SO
EASY FOR ME TO CHOOSE YOU.
>> BECAUSE THEY HIGH ASK YOU.
>> I SHOULDN'T BE AFRAID TO
SPEAK UP IN THIS
>> YEAH.
TOMMY IS STROKING MY EGO AND
LIKE BEING REALLY NICE TO ME,
BUT I KNOW HE'S FEELING REALLY
CONFIDENT TODAY.
LIKE I THINK THESE GUYS THINK
THEY HAVE IT IN THE BAG AND I
THINK THEY'VE GOT ANOTHER THING
COMING.
>> IT ALL COMES DOWN TO TONIGHT.
EVERYTHING I WORKED HARD FOR
COMES DOWN PITCHING THE JURY.
I'M READY FOR IT.
I'M LIKE DEAN AND NOURA.
I HAVE BEEN PLAYING THIS GAME
PRETTY DANG WELL FROM DAY ONE.
SO BEAT THAT.
>> I TURN IT ON EXACTLY WHEN IT
MEARTLE.
I HAVE A HELL OF A RESUME, AN
IMMUNITY NECKLACE, A IDOL
NULLIFIER, A SECRET ADVANTAGE, A
FIRE-MAKING WIN.
IF THAT DOESN'T DESERVE TO BE IN
THE "SURVIVOR" HISTORY BOOKS,
THEN YOU'RE NOT A TRUE FAN OF
THIS GAME.
>> NO ONE HAS EVER PLAYED A GAME
LIKE ME.
I DID IT MY WAY.
I DID IT THE NOURA WAY.
IT'S UP, IT'S DOWN, IT'S IF YOUR
FACE.
IT'S NOT REPLICATABLE.
THAT'S HOW YOU WIN THE MILLION
BE.
A DISRUPTER.
SAY THINGS THAT PEOPLE DON'T SEE
COMING.
AND WHEN YOU PAINT A PRETTY
PICTURE AND RECAPITULATE YOUR
GAME, THEY SAY, BRAVO.
>> Jeff: WE NOW BRING IN THE
MEMBERS OF OUR JURY.
OKAY.
DAY 39 OF OUR 39th SEASON,
YOUR FINAL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THIS IS AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO.
TONIGHT THE GAME MAKES IT LAST
TWIST, AND THE JURY, TEN PEOPLE
YOU HAD HAND IN VOTING OUT, NOW
HAVE ALL OF THE POWER.
TONIGHT THEY WILL DECIDE WHICH
OF THE THREE OF YOU THEY FEEL IS
MOST DESERVING OF THE TITLE OF
SOLE SURVIVOR AND THE $1 MILLION
PRIZE THAT GOES ALONG WITH IT.
MAKE NO MISTAKE, IT IS YOUR
ANSWERS TO THEIR QUESTIONS
TONIGHT THAT WILL INFORM THEIR
FINAL DECISION.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO PREPARE YOURSELVES AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET INTO THE OUTWIT
PORTION.
THAT WOULD BE ALLIANCE AND
RELATIONSHIPS OUTSIDE OF THOSE
ALLIANCE, EMOTIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, THE SOCIAL PART OF
THE GAME.
JURY, WHO WANTS TO GET US
STARTED?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SAY SOMETHING
FIRST.
>> GO, JACK.
>> FIRST OF ALL, I HAVEN'T
SPOKEN TO YOU ALL IN A WHILE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
EACH OF YOU SHOULD BE SUPER
PROUD.
THAT BEING SAID, I WANT YOU ALL
TO KNOW THAT WE'RE ALL
TREMENDOUSLY UNDECIDED WITH WHO
WE'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR TONIGHT,
LIKE WE TRULY ARE, AND THAT
MAKES ME NERVOUS, AND I KNOW
THAT MAKES YOU ALL NERVOUS SOME
REALLY TRY TO BE CLEAR AND
HONEST ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BECAUSE IT REALLY GENUINELY AND
TRULY MATTERS.
>> WITH THAT BEING SAID, BASED
ON THE OUTWIT PORTION OF THE
GAME, WHICH I FIND EXTREMELY
IMPORTANT AND FOR THE THE MOST
IMPORTANT PART OF THE GAME, I
WOULD LIKE THE HEAR ABOUT EACH
OF YOUR STRATEGIES.
WHAT YOU WERE THINKING, HOW YOU
WERE PLAYING THE GAME, HOW THAT
EVOLVED OVER TIME AND MAYBE WE
CAN ADDRESS MORE SPECIFIC
QUESTIONS BASED ON HOW YOU
DECIDED TO PLAY THE GAME.
>> CAN WE START WITH DEAN FOR
THIS QUESTION?
>> OUTWIT, GENERAL PHILOSOPHY,
IT WAS DON'T BE THE LOUDEST GUY,
DON'T BE THE MOST ATHLETIC GUY,
DON'T BE THE SMARTEST GUY IN THE
ROOM.
GET TO KNOW PEOPLE.
FIGURE OUT WHO YOU CAN WORK WITH
AND GO FROM THERE.
SO BASICALLY JUST D.K. CHILLING
STRATEGY.
AND I THINK I DID SOMETHING
RIGHT, BECAUSE NOT ONLY DID I
SURVIVE TO THE MERGE, BUT I HAD
PEOPLE LIKE KELLEE AND JAMAL.
KELLEE GAVE ME AN IDOL.
I WOULDN'T BE IN THIS SEAT.
>> SOCIALLY ARE YOU SAYING
THAT'S A TRIBUTE TO YOUR GAME OR
KELLEE'S GAME.
>> I AM SAYING, WOULD SOMEONE AS
SMART AS KELLEE COME TO A RANDOM
PERSON.
HERE IS AN IDOL.
WHY DID SHE TRUST ME.
WE SPENT A LOT OF TIME TALKING
STRATEGY AND GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER.
>> SO YOUR SOCIAL GAME MANY
>> CORRECT.
>> EXACTLY RIGHT.
>> Jeff: NOURA, SAME QUESTION.
OVERALL PHILOSOPHY OF THE
OUTWIT?
>> SO COMING INTO THIS GAME, I'M
NOT THE TYPICAL "SURVIVOR" FAN.
I HAVEN'T WATCHED 30 SEASONS.
SO FOR ME, I CREATED THESE
MNEMONIC DEVICES.
THE FIRST ONE IS DON'T BE BLAND,
DON'T BEES BY, DON'T BE LAZY,
DON'T BE ANNOY, DON'T BE NOT
TRUSTWORTHY AND DON'T BE DEAD IN
THE WATER AT A CHALLENGE.
AS WE PROGRESSED, I TOLD MYSELF,
DON'T BE SUPER STRONG AND SUPER
STRATEGIC KELLY OR JAMAL, HE'S
INTERESTING TO LISTEN TO AND HAS
A LOT TO SAY AND SOCIALLY LAUREN
IS FRIENDS WITH EVERYONE AND
ELAINE IS FUNNY AND GREAT, AND I
HAVE LITERALLY LOOKED AT EACH OF
YOU OF AS MIRRORS OF THE GAME TO
UNDERSTAND WHO YOU ARE, WHAT YOU
ARE IN YOUR LIFE, AND A LOT OF
TIMES I'M TRYING TO GET A FEEL,
WHO ARE THEY TRYING TO GO FOR.
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY
STRATEGY TO HOW YOU PLAY THE
GAME AT ALL.
I THINK IT'S ALL EMOTIONAL.
>> BUT THIS GAME IS ABOUT
READING PEOPLE AND UNDERSTANDING
HOW THEY'RE FEELING RIGHT NOW.
FEELINGS ARE CHANGING ALL THE
TIME.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT WITH THAT, BUT
THE QUESTION WAS ABOUT STRATEGY
AND SO IF YOU'RE ROLLING OFF
YOUR EMOTIONS AND LIVING
SPONTANEOUSLY IN THE MOMENT,
THEN THOSE TWO THINGS DON'T
COINCIDE.
>> WE'RE PLAYING WITH A VERY
HEADY GROUP HERE.
EVERYONE THINKS IF I DO THIS AND
I DO THAT AND I WORK WITH THESE
PEOPLE.
SOMETIMES IT'S LIKE GOING ON A
DATE, I WANT TO ASK YOU A
QUESTION.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> I WANT TO LEARN MORE ABOUT
YOU.
>> STOP.
STOP, STOP.
>> WE'RE HELPING YOU OUT HERE.
>> WAIT, NOURA.
>> HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
GOT A QUESTION.
>> THE IMPRESSION OF THE JURY IS
THAT THESE WERE EMOTIONALLY
BASED DECISIONS, RIGHT.
I WANT TO POINT OUT THAT WE MAKE
EMOTIONALLY BASED DECISIONS IN A
GAME.
>> SURE.
>> I THINK THE QUESTION IS, WHAT
WAS NOURA'S STRATEGY?
>> OR WAS IT NOT STRATEGY, BUT
THAT'S AN ATTRIBUTE TO YOUR
SOCIAL GAME.
WE MADE US FEEL LIKE WE COULD
WORK WITH YOU.
>> LIKE SUE ME.
I ACTUALLY WANT TO KNOW PEOPLE
AND WHO THEY ARE AND WHAT THEY
ARE LIKE AND SEE HOW CAN WE
MAYBE MEET IN THE MIDDLE WHERE
IT'S BOTH.
>> Jeff: TOMMY, OVERALL
PHILOSOPHY TO OUTWIT?
>> SO FROM THE BEGINNING OF THIS
GAME, IT WAS ABOUT ME MAKING
CONNECTIONS WITH EVERYBODY.
AND THOSE CONNECTIONS ARE REAL.
IT WASN'T GAME PLAY.
I MADE SURE THAT PEOPLE ALWAYS
FIFTH AMENDMENT COMFORTABLE TO
COME TO ME, LIKE AS A TEACHER,
ALL 23 KIDS, I NEED THEM TO FEEL
LIKE THEY CAN COME TO ME FOR
HELP.
THEY CAN TELL ME THAT THEY CAN
WORK WITH ME.
AND I ALSO WANTED TO PLAY IN THE
MIDDLE AT ALL TIMES.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE VOKAI
STRONG.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE LAIRO
I WANTED TO BE GETTING
INFORMATION FROM EVERYBODY, KIND
OF LIKE EARS ON BOTH SIDES.
ALSO, I MADE BIG MOVES.
WHEN IT CAME DOWN TO EIGHT
PEOPLE, DEAN TELLS ME, HEY, MAN,
SOMEONE IS WRITING YOUR NAME
DOWN.
WELL, LET'S SHAKE THIS UP.
IN THAT TRIBAL I WAS ABLE TO GET
OUT SOMETHING THAT WASN'T MY
NUMBER AND ALSO HAVE SOMEONE
PLAY THEIR IDOL.
THAT WAS ANOTHER MOVE FOR ME.
>> TOMMY, CAN I ASK YOU A
QUESTION?
>> OF COURSE.
>> IN THE GAME, WHO WERE YOU
MOST LOYAL TO?
>> YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, YOU NEED TO KNOW, THIS
LAUREN, TOMMY IS NOT TELLING YOU
THE FULL TRUTH, AND YOU WILL
HEAR FROM ME.
I'M NOT YOUR FAVORITE PERSON
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO SAY THAT.
I'M SO PROUD OF ALL OF YOU GUYS.
>> BUT YOU KNOW, I'M ALWAYS
GOING TO SPEAK THE UNSPOKEN, AND
WHEN WE WERE WORKING ON THE
FIRE, THE FOCUS WAS ON DEAN.
TOMMY TAUGHT HIM METHODS THAT HE
DID NOT TEACH YOU.
HE WAS COMING TO YOU TO FLUSTER
YOU SO YOU WOULD BE MORE
EMOTIONAL AND NOT AT YOUR BEST
FOR THE CHALLENGE.
FOR THE FIRE-MAKING CHALLENGE.
-- YOU NEED TO KNOW THIS, BUT
HE'S NOT SAYING IT.
>> YOU GUYS ARE BEING HELD
ACCOUNTABLE FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE
TO THIS POINT IN TIME.
WE'RE GIVING YOU AN OPPORTUNITY
TO JUST OWN YOUR GAME.
ON YOUR GAME AND BE HONEST.
>> I AM.
I WANTED TO CREATE RELATIONSHIPS
AND HAVE EVERYONE LIKE ME.
THAT MEANS PROMISING PEOPLE TO
THE END AS YOU DO.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE I
DIDN'T WORK WITH ONE TIME,
JANET, KARISHMA, NOURA, WE
DIDN'T WORK EVER TOGETHER
BECAUSE MY PHILOSOPHY WAS --
>> FOLLOW THE NUMBERS.
>> I'M GOING TO WORK
STRATEGICALLY, TALK THROUGH
THINGS.
I WAS NOT GOING TO PROMISE YOU
TO THE END AND NOT TALK TO YOU.
IT'S TWO DIFFERENT STRATEGIES.
IS IT THE HONESTY, I'M NOT
WORKING WITH YOU, I'M NOT
TALKING WITH YOU, OR I WANT TO
LIKE EVERYONE AND PROMISE
EVERYONE TO EVERYTHING.
>> HE SAID HE'S WORKING WITH YOU
OR NOT.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD SOCIAL GAME,
NO OFFENSE IN MY EYES.
I WANT TO CONNECT TO EVERYONE
BECAUSE I HAD EYES AND EARS
EVERYWHERE.
I PLAYED THIS GAME HARD.
I DIDN'T C.S. CHILL.
I CAME IN HERE, I LOVE YOU.
IT DOESN'T SOUND AS GOOD, BUT
WHO WAS MAKING THE MOVES, WHO
WAS MAKING THE DECISIONS.
WHO AT EIGHT WAS PUTTING THE
NUMBERS IN WHAT ORDER AND WE HAD
DEAN COMING ALONG.
SO IN THIS GAME YOU CAN'T RIDE
COATTAILS.
>> I HAVE A QUICK CLARIFICATION.
TOMMY, WHEN WAS IT THAT YOU
DECIDED TO BETRAY ME?
>> I AM GOING TO BE HONEST WITH
YOU, PROBABLY AROUND EIGHT I WAS
SAYING, I CAN'T BEAT JANET, BUT
I WANT TO KEEP HER AS A SOCIAL
SHIELD, SAME WITH ELAINE,
BECAUSE IF YOU WENT NINE, YOU
WENT EIGHT, WELL, DANG, I'M
GOING SEVENTH.
WOULD I LOVE TO HAVE SAT HERE
WITH YOU, ABSOLUTELY, I TRULY DO
LOVE YOU AND YOU CHANGED MY
LIFE, YOU REALLY HAVE.
IT WASN'T EASY AT ALL.
>> Jeff: ANY OTHER THOUGHTS
ABOUT THE SOCIAL PART OF THE
GAME?
YOU ARE IN THE MEAT OF IT?
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
YOU'RE ALL DOING GREAT.
YOU REALLY ARE.
I'M LEARNING A LOT AND VALUING
IT AND APPRECIATING IT.
>> SO THERE ARE SOME LINES I
WASN'T WILLING TO CROSS IN THIS
GAME.
FOR ME, AND I DEFINE THEM FOR
MYSELF AND I DON'T THINK IT'S
IMPORTANT TO DEFINE THEM FOR YOU
ALL.
WHAT WERE SOME LINES FOR YOU IN
THIS OUTWIT PORTION AND THE
SOCIAL GAME THAT YOU'RE PLAYING
THAT YOU WERE NOT WILLING TO
CROSS?
WHATEVER THAT MEANS TO YOU.
>> OKAY.
I LOVE THIS QUESTION.
FOR ME, IT WAS SIMPLE.
I DON'T WANT TO DO SOMETHING
THAT LOOKING BACK I DON'T LIKE
THAT THE PERSON THAT IS THAT
STANDS BEHIND THAT MOVE.
I TRIED TO BE TRANSPARENT.
IF I'M GOING TO DO IT, I SAY IT.
SO BOTTOM LINE IS I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE A MOVE LATER AND REGRET
THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
TOMMY?
>> COMING OUT HERE WHEN I TALKED
TO MY STUDENTS, I SAID,
DISCLAIMER, THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME I'M GOING TO SOMETHING FOR
MYSELF.
I SPENT MY WHOLE LIFE SERVING
OTHERS.
SO I SAID, I WILL LIE, I WILL
CHEAT, I WILL STEAL, I WILL DO
WHAT I NEED TO DO TO GET TO THE
END, HOWEVER, I NEVER WANTED TO
CROSS THAT LINE OF BULLYING
SOMEBODY OR DOING THINGS LIKE
THAT, BECAUSE THAT HURTS.
SO I THINK THAT'S THE LINE.
>> THAT'S PRETTY AWESOME.
ALL RIGHT.
DEAN.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR YOU?
>> LET ME TAKE A SECOND TO
THINK.
>> SURE.
>> I MEAN, I NEVER REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT IT LIKE COMING
INTO THE GAME DEFINITIVE LINES
THEY WAS NOT GOING TO CROSSING.
SO I THINK FOR ME, I WAS NEVER
GOING TO PROMISE SOMEONE A FINAL
THREE IF I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN
IT.
AND I DON'T THINK THAT'S
SOMETHING I EVER DID.
>> SO WHAT I'M HEARING FROM YOUR
ANSWER IS THAT YOU HADN'T REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT ANY ETHICAL LINES
THAT YOU WEREN'T WILLING TO
CROSS.
>> CORRECT.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I REALLY GET
WHO YOU ARE.
LIKE YOUR ESSENCE.
LIKE I GET NOURA.
I GET TOMMY.
I DON'T KNOW IF I REALLY GOT
DEAN.
>> I'M JUST GO WITH THE FLOW,
CHILL KEEN.
I TRY NOT TO GET TOO HIGH.
I TRY THE STAY OPTIMISTIC.
I TRY STAY VERY POSITIVE, WHICH
I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE
SEEN, EVEN IF I AM ON THE
BOTTOM, THERE IS HOPE THAT AN
IDOL COULD FALL INTO MY HANDS,
OR, HEY, IF THERE'S NOT HOPE,
THERE'S A CHEESEBURGER WAITING
FOR ME AT PONDEROSA AND THIS HAS
BEEN AN INCREDIBLE EXPERIENCE.
NEVER BEING NEGATIVE IS MY BIG
THING.
BEING OPTIMISTIC IS MY THING.
THAT'S WHERE THE VULNERABILITY
DID LIE.
>> Jeff: LET'S MOVE INTO THE
OUTPLAY PORTION OF THE GAME.
THIS IS HOW YOU DEAL WITH THE
CONDITIONS THAT ARE PUT ON YOU.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE OUTSIDE.
YOU HAVE TO COMPETE IN
CHALLENGES.
YOU HAVE TO TRY TO FIND IDOLS OR
DEAL WITH SWITCHES OR DIFFERENT
TWISTS TO THE GAME.
WHO WANTS TO GET US GOING?
>> SO I IMAGINE I CAN ACTUALLY
SPEAK FOR ALL "SURVIVOR" FANS
ACROSS THE WORLD THAT ONE OF THE
MOST THOUGHT-ABOUT MOMENTS IS
WHEN WE WIN FINAL IMMUNITY, WHAT
WOULD WE DO.
NOURA, YOU HAVE THE HONOR OF
THAT POSITION FOR SEASON 39.
AWE SOJ.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> WHAT YOU EXPLAINED ABOUT
LAUREN, PERFECTLY SOUND.
I HAVE INTERPRETED LAUREN AS A
THREAT.
I DON'T THINK I CAN WIN SITTING
NEXT TO HER, I'M GOING TO SEND
HER TO MAKE FIRE.
GREAT.
BUT THE OPPOSITE OF THAT LOGIC
SHOULD BE THE PERSON I DO BRING
WITH ME IS SOMEONE THAT I THINK
I CAN BEAT.
SO PLEASE, HELP ME UNDERSTAND A
LITTLE BIT MORE ABOUT YOUR
THOUGHT PROCESS ABOUT WHO TO
SEND TO FIRE AND WHO TO BRING
WITH YOU.
>> SURE THING.
OKAY.
BOTTOM LINE, I BROUGHT DEAN
BECAUSE HIS GAME IS JUST
FOLLOWING THE NUMBERS.
HE HAS NEVER MADE ANY BIG MOVES,
AND IT WAS AN EASIER PERSON TO
BRING TO THE END THAT HAD A
WEAKER GAME.
>> BUT YOU DID NOT BRING DEAN,
YOU BROUGHT TOMMY.
TOMMY DIDN'T HAVE TO DO A THING.
>> IT'S SIMPLE.
I FELL I COULD BEAT TOMMY OVER
LAUREN, AND HE MADE ME FEEL THAT
HE IS SO SUCKY AT FIRE HE WILL
NOT BE ABLE TO BEAT LAUREN.
I ASKED HIM MANY TIMES.
>> THANK YOU.
I CAN FOLLOW-UP.
TOMMY, YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
SOMETHING THAT HAS NEVER BEEN
DONE IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> YES.
>> TO WIN FROM THE GOAT ROLE.
YOU GOT BROUGHT TO THE END.
THIS HAS NEVER HAPPENED.
>> I THINK IT SHOWS HOW GOOD --
>> DOESN'T DEAN HAVE A BETTER
STORY IN HERE?
HE WON HIS WAY IN.
>> HE WON FIRE AGAINST LAUREN,
BUT I WAS ABLE TO SPIN IT WHERE
SHE WAS SO FOCUSED ON LAUREN
THAT I WAS ABLE TO SAY, I
LITERALLY NEVER MADE FIRE,
NOBODY HAS EVER SEEN ME MAKE
FIRE.
THAT WAS A SOCIAL PLAY FROM DAY
ONE.
SO THAT SAVED ME TO GET TO THIS
SEAT.
>> I GOT A QUESTION.
GIVE ME A SUMMARY OF YOUR
STRATEGIC APPROACH TO INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES.
START WITH NOURA.
>> BOTTOM LINE IS IN THE
BEGINNING OF THE GAME, MY ASSETS
WERE NOT UTILIZED BY MY TRIBE.
LATER IN THE GAME WHEN WE GOT TO
INDIVIDUAL, I LOVED THAT STAGE,
BECAUSE IT'S NIKE NOW I'M IN
CHARGE OF MYSELF, AND THAT IS
WHERE I STARTED TO THRIVING.
SO LITERALLY EVERY TIME I TRIED
MY BEST AND ACTUALLY IT WARMED
ME UP TO GET THE ONE THAT REALLY
MATTERED AT THE END OF THE GAME.
>> DEAN?
>> GROUP CHALLENGES I GAVE MY
ABSOLUTE ALL, BUT THIS GAME IS
LIKE A HORSE RACE, AND IF YOU
TURN IT ON TOO EARLY, PEOPLE
WILL RECOGNIZE YOU AS A THREAT
AND WANT YOU OUT.
DID I WIN TWO OUT OF THE LAST
THREE INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
CHALLENGES, ABSOLUTELY.
DID HE WIN ANY INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY CHALLENGES?
>> YES, SO I LOST CHALLENGE, BUT
COMING IN, I THOUGHT IMMUNITY
NECKLACES AND IDOLS ARE CURSES,
BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE AN IDOL,
PEOPLE WILL ATTACK YOU.
BUT REWARDS, I BROUGHT WITH
JANET, LAUREN, AND DAN TO A
FAMILY VISIT.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH THAT
SOLIDIFIES A BOND?
IMMUNITY NECKLACE SAVES YOU FOR
ONE NIGHT AND THEN PUTS A TARGET
ON YOU THE NEXT, SO I DIDN'T
WANT THAT NECKLACE.
I WAS ALL ABOUT SOCIAL.
>> ARE YOU SAYING IN A THREE CAT
IMOIRS WHERE WE HAVE TO CHOOSE,
YOU DID RALLY WELL IN ONE, AND
YOU CAME UP WITH BANKS IN
OTHERS.
>> NO, BECAUSE MY STRATEGY WITH
THIS OUTPLAY IS I KNEW WHERE
EVERYONE'S ADVANTAGES WERE.
I KNEW JANET HAD AN IDOL AND
ALSO HER ADVANTAGE.
I KNEW THAT HE HAD AN IDOL
NULLIFYER FROM THE FLIP OF A
COIN.
HE TOLD ME THAT.
SHE TOLD ME THAT.
THAT'S THE LINK SOME THESE ARE
ADVANTAGES THAT I USED TO
CONTROL THE GAME.
>> MY MAN PLAYED A HELL OF A
SOCIAL GAME, BUT I AGREE, HE HAD
ZERO WHEN IT COMES TO ADVANTAGES
AND IMMUNITY.
SO LET ME TAKE THE FLOOR.
FIRST, JAMAL GAVE ME A LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
THE ONE I GAVE TO JEFF WAS A
FAKE.
I WENT AND RIPPED UP A TREE MAIL
AND PAINTED A FAKE ONE THAT I
GAVE TO JEFF.
SO NINE AND SIX I WAS SAFE RIGHT
HERE.
THIS IS REAL.
JAMAL, IS IT?
>> THAT IS NOT REAL, DEAN.
>> SO I WENT TO ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS AND GIVEN TO ME WAS A BANK
PIECE OF PARCHMENT WITH A
PENCIL, AND IT WAS UP TO ME TO
DECIDE HOW I WANTED TO USE THAT
IN ANY WAY I WANTED TO UNITES
IT.
SO IT HAS NO POWER IN THE GAME,
BUT THIS IS ACTUALLY PRETTY
AWESOME WHAT DEAN IS DOING, IF
HE'S SAYING HE DIDN'T EVEN NEED
TO USE IT.
AND HE'S SHOWING IT TO US AS
THOUGH IT COULD BE REAL.
>> BECAUSE HE THOUGHT IT WAS.
>> AND I GOT ONE MORE FOR YOU.
WHEN WE WERE AT FIVE AT ISLAND
OF THE IDOL, MY MAN WAS HOT ON
THE HUNT FOR AN IDOL.
SO WHO FOUND IT?
ACTUALLY, LET ME JUST SHOW YOU.
>> WOW.
I GOT A NOTE.
LET ME READ IT.
>> WOW.
>> YOU DIDN'T THINK WE'D LEAVE
WITHOUT ONE LAST TEST, DID YOU?
YOU PASSED.
GOOD LUCK.
SANDRA AND ROB.
>> WHOA.
>> COME HERE, BOY.
COME ON.
>> I WAS SITTING AT FIVE BLINGED
OUT, NECKLACE ON, IDOL
NULLIFIER, LEGACY ADVANTAGE,
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
DID I HAVE TO PLAY ANY OF THEM?
>> NO.
>> WOW.
>> HE CAN TAKE THE SOCIAL GAME,
BUT DOES HE HAVE ANYTHING ON THE
OUTPLAY?
NO.
ANYTHING YOU CAN CO, I CAN DO
BETTER, ALL OF THIS.
>> BUT HERE'S MY THING, WITH THE
NECKLACE, WITH THE NECKLACE OR
WITHOUT A NECKLACE, WAS ANYBODY
GOING TO VOTE HIM OUT?
NO.
YOU JUST HAVE A GIFT FROM THIS
ISLAND, SO YOU CAN PUT THAT IN
YOUR ROOM AS A SOUVENIR, TELL ME
THOSE ARE OUR MOVES.
>> THEY'RE IN THE MOVES.
YOU FOUND ADVANTAGES.
DID YOU USE THE ADVANTAGES?
>> I DIDN'T NEED TO
>> BECAUSE WE TOOK YOU HERE.
BRIGHT YOU HERE.
KARISHMA PLAYED AND IDOL THAT.
WAS A MOVE, AND --
>> TOMMY, YOU'RE TRYING TO
DOWNPLAY WHAT HE DID.
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULDN'T DO
THAT.
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU OUT.
>> I DISAGREE.
>> I AGREE.
>> I WANT THE HEAR IT.
>> PART OF THE RON WHY HE'S
SITTING HERE IS BECAUSE I HAD
TWO OF THOSE THREE NECKLACES.
THE.
DEAN DID SAVE YOU, TOMMY.
>> THAT'S MY SOCIAL GAME.
IS THAT NOT PARTLY MY
SOCIALGAME?
>> TOMMY, ALL THE INFORMATION
THAT YOU HAD, DID YOU SHARE THAT
INFORMATION WITH DEAN?
>> YES, I TOLD DEAN.
>> YOU TOLD HIM ALL THE
ADVANTAGES.
ON TOP OF THAT, HE GOT THE
NECKLACE.
AND EVEN THOUGH THE LEGACY
ADVANTAGE IS NOT REAL, HE PUT IN
THE WORK TO FINISH IT
>> HOWEVER, TOMMY GAVE DEAN THIS
INFORMATION BASED OFF OF HIS
SOCIAL GAME BUT ALSO BECAUSE HE
ASSUMED THAT DEAN WAS A JOKE, SO
HAD DEAN COME INTO THIS TRIBAL
AND SAID, I HAVE BEEN PLAYING
THE GOAT THIS ENTIRE TIME, THEN
I WOULD BE LIKE, YEAH, WHEREAS
DEAN'S STRATEGY WHEN WE TALK
ABOUT STRATEGY WAS, I TRIED TO
PLAY THIS MIDDLING ROLE.
THOSE ARE TWO REALLY DIFFERENT
THINGS.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, THE GAME
PLAN OF BEING IN THE MIDDLE, I
FEEL LIKE I DID EXECUTE.
I HAD MY TWO CLOSEST ALLIES,
ELIZABETH AND ELAINE.
ELIZABETH AND I WERE CLOSE FROM
DAY ONE, DAY TWO.
WE HAD LIKE A SECRET PACT TO
MAKE IT TO THE FINAL TWO
TOGETHER.
>> WAIT, WHEN JAMAL ASKED, WHERE
IS YOUR ETHICAL LINE, DEAN SAID,
I WILL NOT MAKE FINAL TWO AND
FINAL THREE DEALS
>> AGREED.
>> NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU HAD
ONE WITH ELIZABETH.
>> AND YOU HAD ONE WITH ME, TOO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHEN IT RAINS, IT POURS.
>> THIS IS INSANE.
>> DEAN, WE'RE JUST CALLING YOU
OUT BECAUSE YOU CONTRADICTED
YOURSELF.
>> YOU'RE SEEING HIM FOR WHAT HE
IS, LOOKING FOR OPPORTUNITIES,
FOLLOWING THE NUMBERS IN CASE --
>> WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US
EARLIER.
WHY IS THIS ONLY COMING UP NOW.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE ON THE HOT
SEAT AND I'M NOT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE NOW THAT
THE RAIN HAS COME AND GONE
>> I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE A CLEAN
SLATE AND ALL THE NEGATIVE
ENERGY HAS WITHIN WIPED OFF OF
US.
>> Jeff: LET'S GET TO THE LAST
PHASE OF THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL, THE OUTLAST.
THIS IS REALLY BACK TO YOU GUYS.
HAVE YOU DONE THE JOB YOU NEEDED
TO DO?
DID YOU PUT THE PEOPLE ON THE
JURY THAT ARE GOING TO VOTE FOR
YOU.
IF THERE IS SOMEBODY YOU'RE
UNCERTAIN ABOUT, NOW IS THE
TIME.
TOMMY, GO FOR IT.
>> SEASON 39 IS 39 DAYS.
YOU HAVE TO PLAY FROM DAY ONE.
I BUILT RELATIONSHIPS WITH ALL
OF YOU, AND, YES, THANK YOU FOR
THE GREAT MEMORIES, BUT WHO DO
YOU WANT TO REPRESENT THE WINNER
OF SEASON 39?
I PLAYED HARD AND I MADE A TON
OF RISKY BIG MOVES IN THIS GAME.
MY NAME CONSTANTLY CAME UP AND
WHAT I HAD V TO DO IS PUT PEOPLE
THERE UNFORTUNATELY BEFORE THEY
PUT ME THERE.
I MADE ALLIANCES.
I CROSSED LINES.
I DIDN'T NEED AN IMMUNITY
NECKLACE AND I STILL MADE BIG
MOVES AND I GOT HERE.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT "SURVIVOR"
IS ALL ABOUT.
>> NOURA?
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR QUESTIONS.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR INSIGHT.
WE HAVE LEARNED A LOT ABOUT
OURSELVES.
I KNOW I DEFINITELY HAVE.
FOR ME THIS IS NOURA.
I WANTED TO COME IN THIS GAME
AND BE SO TRANSPARENT AND TO BE
SO OPEN AND AUTHENTIC, AND YOU
LOVE ME AND MAYBE HATED ME AT
TIMES FOR WHO I AM, BUT YOU
ACCEPTED ME FOR ME AND ALLOWED
ME TO BE ME, AND I'M IN THE A
PLAYER THAT YOU'VE EVER SEEN
BEFORE.
I AM A WILD CARD.
I AM A PERSON OF LOVE, BUT I CAN
BE WEIRD AND CRAZY AND I'VE DONE
EVERYTHING I CAN IN THE GAME THE
USE TOOLS TO WIN CHALLENGES AND
I'M PROUD TO BE HERE NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT, WHEN I WAS
ME TO THE FULL ET CETERA, EFELT
LIKE I THRIVED AND I CONNECTED
SOCIALLY AND IT HELPED MY
STRATEGIC GAME, AND IT HELPED ME
GET TO WHERE I AM RIGHT NOW.
SO THANK YOU.
>> WELL DONE.
DEAN, CLOSE IT OUT.
>> SO WE THINK ABOUT SURVIVOR,
RIGHT?
WE'RE ALL LIFE LONG FANS.
I WANT YOU ALL TO THINK ABOUT
LIKE THOSE JAW-DROPPING MOMENTS
YOU SEE, THE SUCK IDOL NULLIFIER
EVER PLAYED IN THE GAME
SUCCESSFULLY, FINDING A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
THEN I WANT YOU TO COUPLE THAT
WITH THE MOMENTS IN THE GAME
THAT YOU WANTED TO RIP YOUR
HEART OUT, YOUR BACK WAS AGAINST
THE WALL.
THAT'S WHERE I WAS THIS WHOLE
GAME.
ON LAIRO BEACH, FIVE-THREE SWAT,
BOTTOM, BOTTOM, BOTTOM, BAG
AGAINST THE WALL.
I COME INTO THE MERGE.
I FIND MY OWN WAY, FIND MY OWN
LITTLE PACK, AND THEN THE FOURTH
QUARTER HITS, AND YOU SAW MY
ACCOLADES, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
I WAS SITTING AT THE FINAL FIVE
WITH ALL THAT JEWELRY, AND IF
YOU GUYS CAN'T HELP ETCH THAT
INTO THE "SURVIVOR" HISTORY
BOOKS TONIGHT, SOMETHING HAS TO
BE SAID ABOUT, I DIDN'T NEED TO
PLAY IT.
I WAS SITTING THERE SMILING
BECAUSE I KNEW I WAS GOING
BECAUSE I HAD HIM SO LINED UP
WITH ME TO BRING ME THERE.
SO I'M ASKING YOU GUYS TO HELP
WRITE HISTORY.
WITH ME.
>> Jeff: IT HAS BEEN A VERY
FULL TRIBAL COUNCIL.
GREAT JOB BY THE JURY.
THOROUGH INVESTIGATION OF THE
FINAL THREE.
THE ONLY THING NOW LEFT TO DO IS
VOTE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE THE JURY A
MOMENT TO TAKE ALL OF THIS IN,
AND THEN WE WILL VOTE FOR A $1
MILLION WINNER.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
TOMMY, NOURA, DEAN, THERE IS
NOTHING LEFT TO BE SAID.
THE ONLY THING LEFT TO DO IS
VOTE.
JURY, TONIGHT YOU'RE VOTING FOR
A WINNER.
THE PERSON YOU THINK MOST
DESERVING OF THE TITLE OF SOLE
SURVIVOR AND THE $1 MILLION
PRIZE THAT GOES ALONG WITH IT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JACK, YOU'RE UP.
>> THIS IS WHAT LOYALTY LOOKS
LIKE.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
>> MY MAN, YOU PLAYED THE GAME
THAT I WANTED TO PLAY.
HATS OFF TO YOU.
>> WOW, VOTING FOR A WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR."
THAT'S CRAZY, MAN.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO GET THE
VOTES.
TOMMY, NOURA, DEAN, JURY, THANKS
FOR PLAYING "SURVIVOR."
THANKS FOR SHARING YOUR STORIES
WITH US.
I WILL SEE YOU BACK IN LOS
ANGELES FOR THE READING OF THE
VOTES.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU HAVE.
A SEAT.
LET'S DO THIS.
FIRST OF ALL, TO ALL OF YOU
GUYS, THANK YOU FOR ANOTHER
GREAT SEASON OF "SURVIVOR."
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
TO TOMMY, NOURA, AND DEAN, NO
MATTER HOW BIG A FAN YOU ARE,
HOW OFTEN YOU WATCH, HOW MUCH
YOU HAVE DREAMED ABOUT PLAYING,
YOU CAN'T ANTICIPATE WHAT 39
DAYS IN THE JUNGLE IS GOING TO
BE LIKE, BUT YOU THREE DID THAT,
YOU ACCOMPLISHED THAT, AND
REGARDLESS OF THE RESULT, NO ONE
CAN EVER TAKE THAT AWAY FROM
YOU.
SO CONGRATULATIONS.
BUT IT IS A COMPETITION, AND
THERE CAN ONLY BE ONE WINNER.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE TOMMY.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
DEAN.
ONE VOTE TOMMY, ONE VOTE DEAN.
TWO VOTES TOMMY, ONE VOTE DEAN.
DEAN.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
TWO VOTES TOMMY, TWO VOTES DEAN.
TOMMY.
THREE VOTES TOMMY, TWO VOTES
DEAN.
TOMMY.
FOUR VOTES TOMMY, TWO VOTES
DEAN.
TOMMY.
FIVE VOTES TOMMY, TWO VOTES
DEAN.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR," TOMMY.
ALL RIGHT.
THOUGH THOSE VOTES UP THERE,
JOE, LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT WHO
VOTED FOR WHO.
THERE IT IS.
TWO VOTES FOR DEAN, ALL THE REST
FOR TOMMY.
THE REUNION SHOW IS NEXT.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK TO A VERY
EXCITED TOMMY ABOUT LOYALTY.
AN WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT
WE'RE DOING FOR OUR 40th
SEASON.
AN WE WILL SIT DOWN WITH KELLEE
AND TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED WITH HER AND DAN AND
WHAT WE HAVE LEARNED FROM IT.
THE REUNION SHOW IS NEXT.