I'M SCARED.
NOW IT'S DOG-EAT-DOG.
I THINK WE'RE DOING THIS.
AT TRIBAL, I BLOCKED JASON'S
VOTE, AND JASON WENT HOME.
I DIDN'T KNOW THINGS WOULD SHAKE
OUT LIKE THAT.
I KNEW THE OLD VOKAI WOULD HAVE
SOUR GRAPES AND BE BUTT HURT.
IT'S WHAT I HAD TO DO FOR ME AND
MY CORE.
NOW THEY'RE SHAKING IN THEIR
SHOES BECAUSE WE'RE UP ON
NUMBERS.
UNFORTUNATELY TOMMY, DEAN AND
I WERE ON THE OUTSIDE.
MISSY AND I HAD HAD BUILT A REAL
CONNECTION, SO I FEEL LIKE I WAS
LIED.
TO.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
ALL I CAN HOPE IS WE DON'T
LOSE IMMUNITY AND I DON'T GO
HOME.
NO GIRL HAS GONE HOME SINCE
THE SWAP.
YOU ARE THE ONLY CONNECTION TO
THE GIRLS ON THE OTHER SIDE.
YOU CAN'T GO HOME.
I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT FROM
YOU.
IT'S HARD TO PUT FAITH AND TRUST
IN PEOPLE WHEN THEY TELL YOU ONE
THING AND DO ANOTHER.
SO I HAVE TO DECIDE WHAT IS THE
BEST THING FOR MY GAME.
THIS IS A GAME CHANGER.
GOOD MOVE.
THAT'S WHY I DONE IT.
BY TAKING JASON OUT OF THE
GAME, WE PUT THEM ON THEIR
HEELS, AND NOW WE KNOW THEY'RE
GOING TO COME SCRAMBLING BACK,
BEGGING FOR THEIR LIVES, BECAUSE
NOW WHO IS IN CONTROL OVER HERE?
WE ARE.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THE FIRE
STARTED.
DO YOU HAVE FLINT?
WHAT KIND OF QUESTION IS
THAT?
LET'S GET IT GOING THEN.
IT WAS A TERRIBLE NIGHT.
WE HAD TORRENTIAL DOWNPOURS THE
ENTIRE NIGHT.
JAMAL TOOK THE LEAD ON WORKING
WITH THE FLINT AND GETTING THE
FIRE STARTED, AN HE TOOK A LOT
OF SHOTS AT IT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD TRY FIRE.
WHATEVER.
DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO DO IT.
SO I TAKE THE MAGNESIUM, AND
JAMAL BASICALLY STARTS TELLING
ME WHAT TO DO.
AND BASICALLY LIKE TAKES IT FROM
ME.
AND I'M LIKE PISSED OFF.
AM I OUT OF LINE?
I THINK YOU SHOULD HAVE LET
HER TRY.
LIKE I GET REALLY IMPATIENT
WITH INCOMPETENCE, ESPECIALLY
WHEN I HAVE NO FOOD AND I
HAVEN'T GOTTEN SLEEP.
IT JUST GOT TO ME AND I WAS
LIKE, OH, MY GOD, LIKE YOU
AREN'T GOOD AT THIS, LET SOMEONE
ELSE GIVE IT A TRY WHO KNOWS
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
WOW.
THERE YOU GO.
HE SAYS THINGS LIKE IT'S MY WAY
OR THE HIGHWAY, AND WHETHER IT'S
DOING STUFF AROUND CAMP OR
STRATEGY, I THINK HE'S JUST A
TOUGH PERSON TO WORK WITH.
THE PORTIONS CAME OUT SMALLER
WITH LESS WATER.
NO, THE PORTION IS SMALLER
BECAUSE IT STARTED OFF SMALLER.
OKAY, THAT, TOO.
OKAY, GOT IT.
BUT IN HERE IT'S DEFINITELY
BARELY A CUP.
I'LL GIVE YOU SOME OF MINE.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE RICE IN YOUR
HAND.
NO, I PUT IT FLAT IN THIS.
I GO, I THINK THERE'S A
PROBLEM.
THERE'S ONLY ONE SCOOP LEFT IN
THE BOWL, AND JAMAL, HE LOCKS AT
ME AND GOES, IT'S BECAUSE YOU
HAVE A HEAPING PORTION ON THAT
SHELL OF YOURS AND I'M LIKE,
YOU'RE A COMPLETE -YOU HAVE
THE AUDACITY TO TELL ME THERE'S
NOT ENOUGH IN THE POT BECAUSE
NOURA HAD TOO MUCH.
I HATE JAMAL.
I'M SO OVER HIM.
I'M OVER HIS FACE.
I'M OVER HIS REPRESSIVE REMARKS.
AT WHAT POINT DO WE NOT KEEP
COWERING DOWN TO THINGS LIKE
THAT?
AT WHAT POINT DO YOU SAY, LET'S
BRECK AWAY AND CUT HIS THROAT
OFF.
I'M GOING TO PLAY THE WOMAN
CARD HERE.
WE ARE STRONG, SMART,
INDEPENDENT WOMEN, AND WHAT
POINT IN THE GAME DO WE START
HAVING OUR OWN GAME, LIKE --
WHEN WE GET TO THE MERGE.
YOU DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE IT'S
WORTH TRYING TO GET HIM OUT
BEFORE?
I THINK IT WOULD BE TOO
DANGEROUS.
I THINK WE NEED TO WAIT UNTIL WE
GET TO THE MERGE.
NOURA IS ALL ABOUT A GIRL'S
ALLIANCE, PRO WOMEN, RAH, RAH,
RAH, AND WE'RE NOT DOING THAT.
HONESTLY, I DON'T TRUST DEAN.
YOU DON'T?
I DON'T.
THE PLAN AS OF RIGHT NOW ON
THE NEXT VOTE IS DEAN BECAUSE
HESS A PRETTY BOY, HE'S ALL
ABOUT HIMSELF.
I'M SO HAPPY I FOUND YOU GUYS
THE PLAY.
WITH YOU GUYS ARE MAKING MY
"SURVIVOR" DREAM COME TRUE.
WOW.
AND KARISHMA WILL BE A LOYAL
VOTE BECAUSE SHE'S BEEN
OSTRACIZED BY OUR OLD TRIBE.
IT'S MATTER OF KEEPING NOURA'S
HEAD WITH US.
LET'S SEE WHAT THIS IT WILL
BOAT MAN HAS TO SAY.
WE SEE A BOAT.
I KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
SOMEONE IS GOING TO ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS.
JANET MUST GET ON THE BOAT
AND HEAD TO THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS.
JANET, PRESS HER HEART,
DOESN'T TAKE IT VERY WELL.
I'M SCARED.
DON'T BE SCARED.
FORTUNATELY I HAVE FAITH THAT
SHE WILL DO THE RIGHT THING FOR
THE TRIBE.
AND OUR ALLIANCE.
MY STOMACH IS DOING
FLIP-FLOPS.
EVERYTHING IS CALLING R CRAWLING
UP IN MY THROAT.
BECAUSE GOING TO THE ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS HAS PUT A TARGETED ON
PEOPLE'S BACKS.
I DID NOT WANT THAT TO HAPPEN TO
ME.
I'M SILTING IN A GOOD SPOT.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
OH OH, MY GOD!
COME ON IN.
WELCOME, COME ON.
IT ANSWERS SO MANY QUESTIONS.
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOL, THEY ARE
THE SUPERSTAR SURVIVOR IDOLS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
JANET, I'M ROB.
I KNOW.
JANET, COME IN AND WE'LL
EXPLAIN EVERYTHING, OKAY?
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
THIS IS A BIG MOMENT FOR ME.
THIS COULD BE A TURNING POINT IN
MY GAME.
I WAS IS SCARED THAT I HAD TO GO
TO THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
USUALLY THAT'S LIKE HUGE TARGET
ON YOUR BACK, BUT MY TRIBE, THEY
TRUST ME.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
SO IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE IN A
PRETTY GOOD SPOT RIGHT NOW.
I AM.
BUT SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO
THINK BEYOND RIGHT NOW.
THE BETTER PLAYERS THINK TWO OR
THREE MOVES AHEAD.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO.
LET ME EXPLAIN HOW IT WORKS.
EVERYBODY WHO COMES HERE GETS A
LESSON, AND TODAY'S LESSON IS
ABOUT CALCULATED RISK.
SO IN "SURVIVOR," THERE ARE
COUNTLESS OPPORTUNITIES TO APPLY
THIS COME COLLATED RISK.
YOU DON'T MAKE MOVES IN THIS
GAME WITHOUT KNOWING WHY YOU DO
IT.
TONIGHT I AM OFFERING UP MY
IMMUNITY NECKLACE, AND I WILL BE
MAKING FIRE AGAINST RICK DEVENS.
THE POINT OF THIS ENTIRE
LESSON IS ABOUT CALCULATING
RISK.
IT'S THE BIGGEST RISK
I'MCATION.
WOW.
THE MINUTE YOU STOP ANALYZE,
THAT'S THE MINUTE YOU FALL
ASLEEP AT THE WHEEL AND YOUR
GONE.
THE WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR: EDGE OF EXTINCTION"
CHRIS!
IF YOUR BACK IS AGAINST THE
WALL, YOU MIGHT HAVE TO THIS
SOMETHING THAT YOU NORMALLY
WOULDN'T DO.
SO TODAY WE'RE GOING THE PLAY A
LITTLE GAME.
THIS GAME WILL HELP YOU TO START
TO UNDERSTAND CALCULATED RISK.
IT'S A RISK VERSUS REWARD GAME.
JUST LIKE IN SURVIVOR, THE
GREATER THE REWARD, THE HIGHER
THE RISK.
IF YOU WIN, YOU EARN A SAFETY
WITHOUT POWER ADVANTAGE.
THIS ADVANTAGE PROTECTS YOU FROM
BEING VOTED OUT AT ONE TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU WILL LEAVE TRIBAL COUNCIL
BEFORE THE VOTE AND RETURN TO
CAMP.
SO YOU CAN'T BE VOTED OUT.
THE LAST TIME YOU CAN USE IT IS
WHEN THERE ARE SEVEN PLAYERS
LEFT IN THE GAME.
BUT IF YOU LOSE THE GAME, YOU
LOSE YOUR VOTE AT THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY THE GAME, OR
DO YOU WANT THE PLAY IT SAFE AND
RETURN TO CAMP?
LET'S SAY I WIN AND I WALK
AWAY BEFORE THE VOTE, KEENING ME
SAFE, BUT DOES THAT PUT A BIGGER
TARGET ON ME AT THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL?
BECAUSE I COULD POTENTIALLY BE
SCREWING MY ALLIANCE AND NOT GET
THE PERSON OUT THAT I AGREE ON,
BUT THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT IS I
COULD GET VOTED OUT.
I'M GOING TO NOT PLAY.
WHY?
BECAUSE I THINK IT WOULD PUT
A BIGGER TARGET ON ME IF I LEFT
A TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR THE
FOLLOWING TRIBAL.
I'M SMILING, BECAUSE YOU
REALLY UNDERSTOOD THIS LESSON.
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY AT THE FACT
YOU'RE ABLE TO RUN THE SCENARIO
IN YOUR MIND, CALCULATE THE
RISK, AND MAKE A DECISION.
THAT'S WHAT THIS GAME IS ALL
ABOUT.
SHE WAS FIRST PERSON TO COME
HERE AND JUST SAY NO TO OUR
OFFER.
EVERYONE ELSE, THEY WERE JUST
CHOMPING AT THE BIT TO ACCEPT
ANYTHING THAT ROB AND I PUT IN
FRONT OF THEM.
HANG IN THERE.
BYE.
I KEEP SAYING THE WINNER THIS
SEASON WILL BE A FEMALE.
I'M WAITING FOR YOU TO TAKE ME
UP AT THAT BET.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
I WAS BEEN AT NIGHT BUT NOT LAST
NIGHT.
JANUARY SET A VERY LOGICAL
PLAYER.
SHE HAS WISDOM.
SHE HAS AGE.
SHE'S DONE THIS FOR YEARS
ALREADY.
SO RIGHT THERE IT TELLS ME THAT
HER LONGEVITY IN THIS GAME,
SHE'S GOT THE MAKINGS OF A
WINNER.
WE NEED AN OLDER WINNER.
JANET'S HERE.
JANET!
IS SHE CRYING OR HAPPY?
SHE'S GOT THUMBS-UP.
THAT'S GOOD.
SHOW US THE IDOL.
JANET FLASHES HER FRONT TO
CONFIRM I'VE GOT NOTHING ON ME,
BUT SHE'S ALSO LIKE A FREE WOMAN
AND A FREE SPIRIT AND SHE'S
LIKES BEING NAKED APPARENTLY.
IT'S ALWAYS A LITTLE
NERVE-RACKING BECAUSE I NEED
THEIR STORY TO BE CONSISTENT
WITH MINE.
WE'RE HALFWAY THROUGH THE ENTIRE
SEASON OF "SURVIVOR" AND ONLY
THE PEOPLE AT THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS SEEM TO KNOW WHAT'S
EXACTLY THERE.
SO I GOT TO THE ISLAND.
MINE WAS A GAME OF CHANCES.
IT SAID, YOU CAN TAKE A GAME OF
CHANCES, THIS IS 50% CHANCE THAT
YOU WOULD WIN AND A 50% CHANCE
THAT YOU WOULD LOSE.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO SOLVE ANYTHING.
SO LUCKILY JANET TELLS ALMOST
THE EXACT SAME STORY THAT I TOLD
ABOUT ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
IF I LOST, THERE WOULD BE A
CONSEQUENCE.
I CHOSE NOT TO PLAY.
WE RESPECT YOUR DECISION.
WHEN PEOPLE COME BACK FROM
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS, THEY'RE
IN THIS SECRET CLUB, AND IT WAS
A RELIEF THAT THE SECRET HAS
STAYED A SECRET.
LAST NIGHT WAS HE LYING ON
HIS BACK?
IT WAS A WILD ANIMAL.
IT WAS A DANGER ZONE.
I FEEL VIOLATED.
OH, GOD.
I MEAN, LAST NIGHT IT WAS.
IS THIS OKAY?
NEW YORK NO, IT WAS --
I WAS LIKE, SURE.
IS THIS OKAY.
BONDING I THINK IS ALMOST
LIKE 95% OF THIS GAME.
AND WE ALL SEEM TO GET ALONG
FINE, BUT THERE ARE SOME PRETTY
WEIRD, UNCOMFORTABLE THINGS.
RIGHT NOW IT'S A GAME BETWEEN
DAN, TOMMY AND I.
WE'RE ON THE BOTTOM OF THE
NUMBERS.
WE ALL KNOW THAT ONE OF US IS
GOING TO HAVE TO GO HOME.
BUT MY NUMBER ONE RIGHT NOW IS
TOMMY.
HE'S LIKE A BROTHER TO ME.
THERE'S THREE CHICKENS.
THERE'S THREE VOKAI.
ONE OF US IS GOING TO HAVE TO
GET CHOPPED.
WHICH ONE?
THAT ONE.
YOU'RE RED LIKE ME.
YOU CAN STAY.
THAT ONE IS BLACK LIKE ME.
DAN IS UNFORTUNATELY THE
PERSON THAT IS GOING TO BE THE
ONE THAT HAS THE TARGET PAINTED
ON HIS BACK, SO RIGHT NOW IT'S
OPERATION SAVE LAURAN AND TOMMY.
OKAY.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME TO FREAK
OUT.
NOW IS THE TIME TO GET OUR HEADS
IN THE GAME.
THING THAT SCARES ME IS THEY
KNOW YOU ANDRY CLOSE, AND THEY
PROBABLY WANT THE BREAK US UP
BEFORE WE GO TO THE MERGE, SO
NOW WE HAVE TO PUT A PLAN INTO
ACTION THE MAKE SURE THAT
DOESN'T HAPPEN AND TO PAINT DAN
AS A FLIP-FLOPPER.
RIGHT NOW I'M IN A BAD, BAD
SPOT, BECAUSE NOW IT'S
DOG-EAT-DOG.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME
BEFORE MERGE.
I KNOW, TOMMY.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU GO HOME.
IT'S OKAY.
I KNOW YOU'RE SCARED, BUT
THERE'S GOING TO BE TIMES WHEN I
FEEL THE SAME WAY, AND WE HAVE
TO BE ABLE TO HAVE EACH OTHER
AND REASSURE EACH OTHER THAT
IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
YEAH.
OKAY.
SO IT'S TIME TO LIE, CHEAT,
STEAL.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I NEED TO DO TO
MAKE DAN LOOK LIKE A VERY, VERY
SNEAKY PLAYER.
I THINK I GOT AN IDEA.
DAB CAME TO US AND SAID LET'S
VOTE OUT AARON.
THERE ARE ALWAYS PLANS.
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMETHING.
UNFORTUNATELY DAN IS THAT CRACK.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
LAURAN AND TOMMY ARE TRYING TO
GET RID OF DAN, BUT LAURAN AND
TOMMY, THEY ARE TIGHT.
SUPER TIGHT.
I DON'T CARE WHICH ONE OF THE
THREE IT IS.
DAN?
TOMMY AND LAURAN ARE CLOSE.
LAURAN CAN PULL THOSE PEOPLE
WITHOUT TOMMY.
IF TOMMY IS GONE, LAURAN IS MORE
LIKELY TO WORK WITH US.
I THINK IT'S BRILLIANT.
I THINK WE'RE DOING THIS.
LAURAN'S CONNECTION TO TOMMY
IS DANGEROUS.
SO I'M THINKING, TAKE TOMMY AWAY
FROM LAURAN, AND SHE'LL HAVE NO
WHERE ELSE TO GO.
I DON'T WANT LAURAN AND TOMMY TO
BECOME THE SUPERPAIR THAT'S
UNSTOPPABLE.
THAT'S CATASTROPHIC.
COME ON IN, GUYS!
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
JACK, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
TAKE BACK THE IDOL.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING THE RACE TO SHOOT COCONUTS
INTO A BASKET.
WHEN THE BASKET BECOMES HEAVY
ENOUGH, IT WILL TRIGGER THE
PUZZLE PIECES TO DROP.
YOU'LL THEN USE THE PIECES TO
SOLVE A VERY LARGE AND HEAVY
SURVIVOR PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SEVENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
TAKE A MINUTE THE STRATEGIZE.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO IT!
ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER DAY IN FIJI.
RAINING ONE SECOND, CLEAR THE
NEXT.
ARE SURVIVORS READY?
LET'S GO, MISSY.
YOU HAVE THREE
SHOOTERS ROTATING, TRYING THE
LAND COCONUTS IN YOUR BASKET.
OH, IT'S HEAVY.
IT'S HEAVY, THE HEAVY.
NICE TOSS BY JACK.
TOMMY LANDS ONE.
ELIZABETH TRIES.
SHE SCORES.
EVERYONE THAT DROPS MOVES YOU
CLOSER TO DROPPING THOSE PUT L
PIECES.
JACK WITH ANOTHER.
YOU'RE KILLING IT, JACK.
WITH YOUR LEGS, WITH YOUR
LEGS.
THERE GOES JANUARYET.
GOT TO GET IT HIGHER THERE,
JANET.
THIS SECTION HAS A LEARNING
CONSERVE.
IT'S ABOUT THE SIZE OF THE
COCONUT AND HOW OFTEN YOU CAN
CAN GET IT IN THAT BASKET.
TOMMY WITH ANOTHER.
THERE YOU GOSH, TOMMY.
MISSY, THAT'S WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO.
VOKAI IS ON FIRE.
VOKAI IN THE LEAD.
LAIRO STRUGGLING IN THE
CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT, TOMMY.
TOMMY LAUNCHES AGAIN.
HE'S GOOD.
VOKAI INCHING CLOSER.
BIGGER, ELIZABETH.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT,
ELIZABETH!
THAT MIGHT DO IT.
THERE THEY GO.
VOKAI, YOU'RE DONE.
VOKAI CAN START MOVING THEIR
PUZZLE PIECES.
JACK LAUNCHES AGAIN.
HE'S GOOD.
KILLING IT, JACK.
LOOKING FOR ONE MORE.
YES!
THAT'S GOING TO DO IT.
LAIRO IS GOOD NOW.
GO, GUYS.
START MOVING YOUR
PIECES.
HERE WE GO.
THESE PIECES ARE
HEAVY.
SOME OF YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO
WORK TOGETHER TO MOVE THEM.
THESE PIECES ARE TOUGH.
THEY'RE LARGE.
DEAN ROLLING TWO AT A TIME.
NICE WORK.
ELIZABETH AND LAURAN WORKING
TOGETHER.
VOKAI IN THE LEAD.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
YOU'RE GOOD, VOKAI!
START ON THE PUZZLE.
LET'S GO.
STAND IT UP.
VOKAI, W
LANE.
DAN, AARON AND LAURAN.
THIS IS OUTWIT.
THIS IS ON THE TOP RIGHT.
YOU KNOW THE SYMBOL.
IT'S THE LOW GO OF THE SEASON.
THE QUESTION IS HOW QUICKLY CAN
YOU FIGURE OUT WHERE EACH PIECE
GOES AND HOW EFFICIENTLY CAN YOU
GET THOSE PIECES IN THEIR SPOT.
OUTWIN, OUTPLAY, OUTLAST.
LAURAN BARKING OUT
ORDERS FOR VOKAI NOW.
SURVIVOR RIGHT THERE.
DAN AND AARON, SWITCH YOUR
PIECES.
I GOT IT.
HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
LET ME STEP OVER.
LAIRO TRYING TO STAY
IN IT.
THAT GOES ON TOP.
MOVE YOUR FOOT.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO HOME
TONIGHT.
KEEP WORKING.
THIS IS OUTPLAY.
OUTWIT, OUTPLAY.
RIGHT THERE.
LAURAN STILL IN
CHARGE FOR VOKAI.
LET'S GO!
LAIRO MAKING UP TIME
NOW.
SUDDENLY WE HAVE CHALLENGE.
COME ON, BABY, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO!
VOKAI INCHING CLOSER
TO A VICTORY.
COME ON, BABY.
RIGHT HERE.
LET'S GO!
JEFF!
IT ABLE RIGHT.
RIGHT HERE IS WRONG.
THEY DO NOT.
SOMETHING IS WRONG FOR VOKAI.
THOSE TWO PIECES.
THE TWO SIDE PIECES.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR
FOR LAIRO.
COME ON, GUYS.
WE CAN DO THIS.
THE MIDDLE ONE.
GET IT OUT OF THE WAY.
THEY'RE TRYING TO
SWAP PIECES.
WILL THAT DO IT.
LAIRO MOVING THEIR LAST PIECE.
PUT IT DOWN.
PUT IT DOWN!
ROTATE IT.
WE CAN DO THIS.
JEFF!
VOKAI WINS IMMUNITY.
BY ONE PIECE.
LAIRO WAS SECONDS AWAY.
WOW.
VOKAI IMMUNITY.
NOBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT.
GOOD JOB, LAURAN.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
GOOD JOB, Y'ALL.
LAIRO, TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SEVENTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
LAIRO SUCKS.
WE LOST LITERALLY BY A SECOND.
IT'S REALLY BAD, BECAUSE RIGHT
NOW I HAVE THIS IDOL.
I HAVE NOW BEEN TO TWO TRIBALS
AND IT'S ONLY GOOD FOR ONE MORE
TRIBAL, BUT IF OLD VOKAI IS
GOING TO STAY STRONG, I DON'T
THINK I NEED IT.
IT SUCKS TO LET AN IDOL GO TO
WASTE.
WE CAN ONLY DO WHAT WE KNOW IS
SAFE FOR US RIGHT NOW
WE'RE CONSIDERING GETTING RID OF
DEAN BEACUSE HE IS THE MORE
UNKNOWN ONE. AND THAT SUCKS FOR
ME TO SAY BECAUSE I REALLY LIKE
DEAN. SO THE PLAN IS TO
UNANIMOUSLY
VOTE OUT DEAN TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
HE'S HARD THE READ.
HE'S A LITTLE SMARMY.
SO I THINK THAT HAS PEOPLE ON
EDGE AND A SMARTER MOVE TO GET
RID OF THAT THREAT.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING
FOR TONIGHT'S VOTE?
IT'S GOING TO BE DEAN.
I TRUST YOU.
YEP, THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
I BRING MY HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
TO EVERY SINGLE TRIBAL, BUT THIS
VOTE COMING UP IS PROBABLY THE
SAFEST I HAVE FELT GOING INTO
TRIBAL.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO WHEN YOU HAVE
THE MAJORITY.
CONGRATS FOR MAKING IT TO THE
MERGE.
THANKS.
WHAT WE'RE ALL FEELING IS
THAT THIS IS THE VOTE RIGHT
BEFORE THE MERGE.
THIS VOTE IS GOING TO SOLIDIFY
US TO MOVE FORWARD INTO THE
MERGE, AND NOURA IS HANDFUL, BUT
I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE AN
EMOTIONAL VOTE IN THIS GAME, AND
I DON'T THINK HOW IT MAKES SENSE
TO ANYONE ON THIS TRIBE TO
DEVIATE FROM THIS PLAN.
AM I GOING HOME TONIGHT?
AM I WRITING DOWN NOURA?
NOURA.
SHE'S SUCH A LOOSE CANNON.
I'LL PROBABLY GIVE MY PITCH
AGAIN AT TRIBAL, BUT MOVING
FORWARD, YOU HAVE TO REALIZE,
IT'S A GUY THING.
WE HAVE TO TRY TO STICK
TOGETHER, TOO.
DEAN IS CONCERNED, OF COURSE,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE EXPECTS TO
GO HOME BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN VERY
FERVENT IN SAYING WE WANT YOU TO
WORK WITH THE GUYS, AND NOURA
DOESN'T FIT IN WITH US.
I DEFINITELY WANT TO.
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO OWE YOU MY
ASS.
TONIGHT I THINK IT'S EITHER
ME OR NOURA, BUT IF I'M ON THE
HOT SEAT, THESE ARE GUYS ARE
MAKING IT AWFULLY COMFORTABLE
FOR ME, SO UNLESS THEY'RE RALLY
GOOD POKER FACES, I FEEL OKAY.
THEY KNOW NOURA.
THEY KNOW SHE'S INSANE.
I THINK HE'S IN FOR A BIG BLIND
SIDE TONIGHT OR ELSE I'M THE ONE
BEING LAUGHED AT.
WE'RE GUARANTEED THE MERGE.
AFTER THE MERGE YOU CAN BACKSTAB
ME.
I WOULD REALLY JUST LIKE THE GET
TO THE MERCHG.
BACKSTAB ME AFTER A COUPLE.
THAT'S FINE.
LET'S SHAKE HANDS.
I HAVE THIS IDOL FROM ISLAND
OF THE IDOL, AND IT'S REALLY
ONLY GOOD FOR ONE MORE TRIBAL
COUNCIL THAT I GO TO, AND THAT
TRIBAL IS TONIGHT.
RIGHT NOW, THE VOTE IS DEAN.
BUT WE HAVE THIS CONNECTION OF
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND, WHO IS A
MUTUAL FRIEND, AND I REALLY LIKE
DEAN.
I WANT TO WORK WITH HIM.
AND IDEALLY I DON'T LET THIS
IDOL GO TO WASTE.
OH, MY GOD.
I JUST HAD A MOMENT OF
INSPIRATION.
OKAY.
MOMENT OF INSPIRATION.
I THINK I COULD GIVE DEAN THE
IDOL.
CAN I TRUST
DEAN ENOUGH WITH THIS IDOL AND
HE ACTUALLY WRITES DOWN A NAME
THAT I WANT TO GO HOME.
AND ESSENTIALLY IN MY MIND THERE
ARE TWO OPTION, EITHER JACK OR
JAMAL.
JACK, HE'S EXTREMELY GOOD WITH
PEOPLE, VERY EMPATHETIC, SUPER
FUN, AND I KNOW I CAN TRUST HIM.
I'M SO COMMITTED TO YOU.
DITTO.
BEYOND QUESTION.
DON'T EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
BUT IT'S NOT THAT SMART TO
KEEP HIM IN THE GAME WHEN HE'S
SO CONNECTED TO SO MANY PEOPLE.
JAMAL AND I HAVE A HARDER TIME
CONNECTING, AND I TRUST JAMAL
LESS.
JAMAL I THINK ALSO DOES NOT WANT
TO GO TO THE END WITH ME.
SO I'M TRYING TO THINK OF
CREATIVE WAYS TO USE THIS
WITHOUT ANYONE KNOWING THAT I
HAVE AN IDOL, BECAUSE IF ANYONE
FINDS OUT THAT I HAVE AN IDOL,
THEY WILL KNOW I WAS LYING ABOUT
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS OR I WAS
LYING TO THEM, SO I WOULD GIVE
DEAN THE IDOL BEFORE TRIBAL.
THE DOWN SIDE RISK IS IF DEAN
WRITES DOWN MY NAME, I'M GOING
TO GO HOME, AND I GO DOWN AS THE
BIGGEST SUCKER IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY, HOWEVER, IF I CONVINCE
NOURA THAT IF DEAN HAS AN IDOL
SHE'S GOING HOME AND GET NOURA
TO WRITE DOWN JACK OR JAMAL'S
NAME, THEN I'M A LOT SAFER.
THAT WOULD BE SO BRILLIANT.
I'M TRYING THE TAKE A BIG RISK
AND YET RISK MITIGATE ALL AT THE
SAME TIME.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH TIME.
WE'RE ABOUT TO GO TO TRIBAL.
YOU'RE THE NEXT VOTE.
FROM WHO?
FROM EVERYBODY.
JANET?
EVERYBODY.
EVEN JANET, JAMAL, AND JACK.
YES.
1,000%.
TELL ME YOU HAVE AN IDOL.
I DON'T.
I'M JUST COMPLETELY MIND BLOWN.
THAT'S CRAZY.
LITTLE DID I KNOW, ALL ALONG
THEY WERE COMING FOR ME.
WELL, I HAVE AN IDOL.
DO YOU?
UH-HUH.
AND I AM GOING TO GIVE IT TO
YOU.
WENDELL YOU GIVE AN IDOL TO
SOMEONE AND YOU MAKE SUCH A BIG
MOVE LIKE THAT WITH SOMEONE, IT
WILL AUTOMATICALLY CLI BOND YOU,
AT LEAST FOR A LITTLE BIT HE'S
GOING TO BE LOYAL TO ME.
DO YOU WANT TO PULL SOME
STRINGS.
I THINK WITH EVERY BIG MOVE,
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS THAT
CAN GO WRONG.
NOTHING IS FOOLPROOF IN THIS
GAME, BUT IF THIS PLAN GOES OFF
IN THE WAY I HOPE IT GOES OFF,
IT REALLY WILL SHIFT THE COURSE
OF THE GAME.
LY LITERALLY BE SETTING OFF AN
ENTIRE STRING OF DOMINOES WITH
THIS MOVE.
♪
LET THE SHOW BEGIN.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, KELLEE, IF YOU THINK
"SURVIVOR" IS A NUMBERS GAME,
THEN IS IT FAIR TO SAY IT WOULD
BE A LEAP FOR AN ORIGINAL VOKAI
MEMBER THE SAY, I'M GOING TO GET
RID OF MY TRIBAL ALLIANCES AND
I'M GOING TO PAIR UP WITH LAIRO.
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
I THINK SPEND FIRST 12 DAYS WITH
A GROUP OF PEOPLE MAKES A HUGE
DIFFERENCE IN TERMS OF MAKING
BONDS, HOW PEOPLE VOTE.
THAT I THINK MAKES A REALLY,
REALLY BIG DIFFERENCE IN THIS
GAME.
I THINK PEOPLE REALLY
UNDERESTIMATE THAT
I'D ADD ALL THE SUCCESSES
THEY HAD EARLY ON, TOO.
NOURA, YOU ARE
NODDING.
YES, WE ARE A GROUP BASED ON
INDIVIDUAL PARTNERSHIPS.
BECAUSE THOSE PARTNERSHIPS ARE
STRONG, IT'S KEPT US TOGETHER,
AND YOU'RE THINKING, WELL, WHO
IS THIS GUY?
LIKE I DON'T KNOW HIM.
HE BARELY CAN MAKE EYE CONTACT
WITH ME WHEN I TALK TO HIM
SOMETIMES.
AND SO FOR ME, I'M LIKE, AM I
GOING TO TRUST THIS, OR AM I
GOING TO TRUST THIS?
DEAN, THAT SEEMED
PRETTY CLEAR.
I MEAN, WHAT'S WORSE, ME
POTENTIALLY GOING BACK TO A
TRIBE THAT PLIEBDSIDED ME OR
KEEPING SOMEONE AROUND THAT
BROUGHT UP ONE OF YOUR FELLOW
VOKAI MEMBERS?
NOURA BRINGING UP JAMAL.
AM I WRONG IN SAYING THAT?
YOU KNOW THAT HAPPENED.
IT'S VERY APPARENT THAT WE
ARE BIG PERSONALITY, THE TWO OF
US.
THIS IS NOT NEW TO ANYONE.
IT'S DEFINITELY GREAT FOR
SOMEONE LIKE DEAN TO SAY, OKAY,
LET ME CAPITALIZE ON THIS.
AN YOU DID JUST SAY,
YOU HAD NO LOVE FOR DEAN.
THE OPPOSITE OF LOVE ISN'T
HATE.
IT'S INDIFFERENCE.
SO IF I MIGHT HATE HIM
SOMETIMES, THAT CAN HAPPEN, YOU
CAN HATE YOUR OWN LOVED ONES,
YOUR OWN FAMILY, BUT IF I HAVE
INDIFFERENCE FOR YOU, THAT'S A
LOT WEAKER THAN ME HATING HIM
SOMETIMES.
WOW.
ONE STICKING POINT,
YOU HAVE BEEN TRYING TO GET ME
OUT, IS THAT RIGHT?
IS DEAN RIGHT?
LISTEN, DEAN IS DOING AN
EXCELLENT JOB TO DO WHAT HE CAN
TO GET IN BETWEEN US.
THAT'S NOT AN ANSWER.
I'LL TELL YOU, IT'S GONE
THROUGH MY MIND, BUT THE BOTTOM
LINE IS, I PUT WAY MORE EFFORT
INTO MAKING SURE WE CAN BE A
COHESIVE UNIT, WHICH IS WHAT WE
WANT, AND WE DON'T WANT PEOPLE
WE CAN'T TRUST, AS WELL TO, GET
IN THE WAY OF THAT, SO I HAVE
BEEN VERY OPEN AND HONEST, AND
THAT'S WHERE I'M AT RIGHT NOW.
JACK, THE ONE THING
ABOUT NOURA BEING SO OPEN IS YOU
CAN TRUST THAT SHE'S GOING TO
TELL YOU WHAT SHE THINKS SO YOU
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GETTING.
YEAH, KNOWING WHAT NOURA
FEELS IS GREAT.
THAT BEING SAID, WHEN YOU GET
INTO A MERGE-TYPE SITUATION, IF
YOU'RE TRYING TO KEEP A SEEN RAT
FROM PEOPLE, OBJECTIVELY IT IS
MARGINALLY SCARY, BUT KELLEE
POINTED OUT, WE HAD A COUPLE
WEEKS TOGETHER TO DEVELOP MORE
TRUST WITH NOURA, SO I'M LEANING
STRONGLY IN FAVOR OF NOURA,
BECAUSE I THINK IT BENEFITS MY
GAME THE WAY THAT SHE IS ABLE TO
HAVE MY BACK.
THANKS.
ABSOLUTELY.
SO JAMAL, HOW
CONFIDENT ARE YOU THAT IF THE
MERGE HAPPENED TOMORROW YOU HAVE
THE TEAM IN PLACE AND AFTER
TONIGHT'S VOTE IT WILL EVEN BE
STRONGER?
I'M NOT CONFIDENT I'LL BE
HERE TOMORROW.
BASED ON WHAT?
BASED ON WHAT NOURA SAID.
I'M VERY FEARFUL OF AN ALL-GIRLS
ALLIANCE RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, JEFF, I WORK AT AN
ALL-GIRLS SCHOOL.
I KNOW THE POWER OF WOMEN WHEN
THEY GET TOGETHER AND THEY
UNDERSTAND THE COLLECTIVE POWER,
AND IN THIS TRIBE, 4-3, WE'RE
OUTNUMBERED.
SO I'M NOT SURE IF IT'S GOTTEN
INTO THESE GIRL'S HEADS THAT I'M
THE ONE THAT NEEDS TO GO HOME
AND THEY'RE THE TEAM THEY WANT
TO TAKE.
SO I HAVE NO IDEA.
I FIND THIS IDEA OF A WOMAN'S
ALLIANCE SO SEXIEST, SORRY.
I KNOW THAT YOU DIDN'T MEAN IT
THAT WAY.
BUT IT'S REALLY OFFENSIVE TO BE
LIKE, OH, THE WOMEN OUTNUMBER
THE MEN, THEY CAN JUST TAKE
OVER.
LIKE THE AMOUNT OF FEAR IN
"SURVIVOR" ABOUT A WOMEN'S
ALLIANCE OUTPACES THE NUMBER OF
TIMES THERE HAS ACTUALLY BEEN A
WOMAN'S ALLIANCE, NOT TO MENTION
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT MEN'S
ALLIANCE, WE DON'T FEAR MEN'S
ALLIANCE, AND YET THREE MEN HAVE
BEEN SITTING AT THE VERY END.
THAT'S NOT A THING.
FOR SOME REASON IT WOULD BE A
THING FOR THREE WOMEN TO SIT AT
THE END.
WE'RE SPLITTING THIS ARBITRARILY
BY GENDER.
WHY IS THAT?
SORRY, I FEEL REALLY STRONGLY
ABOUT THIS.
LET IT OUT, KELLEE!
THE KEY WORD IN KELLEE'S
BEAUTIFULLY WORDED SPEECH THAT I
BACK 100% IS ARBITRARY.
AN I DON'T THINK IT IS
ARBITRARY.
I'D LOVE FOR YOU TO ASK NOURA IF
SHE HAS EVER CONSIDERED AN
ALL-WOMEN'S ALLIANCE.
I THINK YOU SHOULD THROW THAT
OUT AND SEE WHAT'S HAPPENED.
HAVE YOU EVER
CONSIDERED AN ALL-WOMEN'S
ALLIANCE?
IT SOUNDS COOL, WHY NOT?
YEAH, OF COURSE I HAVE.
WOW.
WE ALL THINK ABOUT MANY
THINGS.
I WOULD BE A DUMB PLAYER IF I
DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT AT SOME
POINT.
I BELIEVE IN CONFIDENT WOMEN.
I LIKE WOMEN THAT ARE MAKING
THINGS HAPPEN IN THE WORLD, AND
I RESPECT IT.
IF YOU'RE A WOMAN, YOU'D BAND
WITH US, TOO
AND I'M NOT, SO I'M AFRAID.
AN YOU'RE ALLOWED TO BE.
KARISHMA.
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT THERE'S SO
MUCH THOUGHT ABOUT A WOMAN'S
ALLIANCE BECAUSE OF THE SEISMIC
CULTURAL SHIFT THAT'S HAPPENING
IN THE WAY WE VIEW GENDER?
"SURVIVOR" IS A MICROCOSM OF
AMERICA.
IF WE LOOK AT WHAT'S BEEN GOING
ON IN AMERICA THIS PAST YEAR
ESPECIALLY WITH THE ME TOO
MOVEMENT.
, WITH WOMEN FEELING EMPOWERED
TO SPEAK UP FOR THEMSELVES AND
TELL THE STORIES OF TIMES THAT
THEY HAVE FELT SHUT DOWN AND SO
BACK HERE IN "SURVIVOR" WORLD,
IT'S GOING THE MY A PART IN HOW
YOU PLAY "SURVIVOR."
EXACTLY.
I DON'T BLAME JAMAL FOR BEING
CONSIDERED THAT THIS IS A
POSSIBILITY, BUT WITH WHAT
KELLEE SAID, IT IS ARBITRARY.
JANET, THIS IS A
REALLY POWERFUL TOPIC,
ESPECIALLY FOR YOUNG WOMEN WHO
WATCH "SURVIVOR," THE EIGHT,
NINE, TEN, 11 YEAR OLDS.
THIS IS THE WORLD THEY KNOW NOW.
HAVE A VOICE, STAND UP, BE WHO
YOU ARE.
AS THE OLDEST WOMAN IN THIS
GROUP, YOU HAVE PERSPECTIVE HERE
THAT NO ONE ELSE DOES.
RIGHT.
TO ASSUME THAT WOMEN ARE
GOING TO BOND BASED ON GENDER IS
VERY NEGATIVE.
THAT'S PUTTING WOMEN DOWN.
THAT'S SAYING WOMEN DON'T HAVE A
BRAIN TO SAY, MAYBE JAMAL HAS
SOMETHING TO OFFER ME AS A HUMAN
BEING.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT BASED ON
THEIR SEX OR ON THEIR EDUCATION
OR THEIR SOCIOECONOMIC
BACKGROUND.
IT'S WHO THEY ARE, YOU NO, AND
TO THINK THERE ARE SOME
WONDERFUL THINGS THAT HAVE
HAPPENED WITH WOMEN IN THE LAST
YEAR, AND TRUST ME, THAT
REFLECTS ON THE MEN THAT ARE
SUPPORTIVE OF WOMEN, BECAUSE IN
MY EXPERIENCE, YOU CAN'T BE A
POWERFUL WOMAN WITHOUT MEN AND
WOMEN BACKING YOU.
YOU NEED TO EARN YOUR RESPECT,
YOUR DIGNITY, YOUR POSITION, WHO
YOU ARE AS HUMAN BEINGS TO EACH
OTHER.
I MEAN, I HAVE LIVED IT.
SORRY.
THAT'S WELL SAID.
JANET, I THINK THAT WAS A
REALLY BEAUTIFUL WAY OF PUTTING
IT, REALLY TRYING THE TAKE THE
INDIVIDUAL AND HUMANIZE EACH
PERSON.
THAT'S WHAT THE THEME SHOULD BE
ABOUT.
I THINK THAT'S HOW GAME WINNERS
GET TO THE END.
THAT'S ANOTHER LESSON TO TAKE
AWAY FROM THIS GAME.
LOVE YOU.
JAMAL, NEVER HAD A
TRIBAL LIKE THIS EVER.
IT'S TALKING ABOUT THINGS
THAT I'M IS PASSIONATE ABOUT AND
I AM JUST BEAMING WITH PRIDE FOR
THE WOMEN IN FRONT OF ME TO
SPEAK ABOUT THEIR PERSPECTIVES
AND EXPERIENCES AND I'M GETTING
PERSPECTIVES ABOUT MYSELF FROM
DIFFERENT PEOPLE AND LEARNING
ABOUT DIFFERENT KINDS OF PEOPLE,
SO IT'S REAL.
IT'S WHAT WE HAVE JUST BEEN
LIVING FOR 19 DAYS.
JACK, ON ONE HAND,
BEAUTIFUL BONDING, POWERFUL
CONVERSATION, AND ON THE OTHER
HAND, SOMEBODY IS GOING TO BE
VOTED OUT.
HOW DO YOU POSSIBLY BALANCING
THAT ON A NIGHT LIKE TONIGHT?
WE ARE PLAYING A GAME.
THESE RELATIONSHIPS THAT WE'RE
BUILDING ARE VERY TRUE.
JUST BECAUSE I'M GOING TO WRITE
YOUR NAME DOWN DOES NOT MEAN I
DON'T CENTRAL YOU THAT
RELATIONSHIP THAT I MADE.
I EXPECT EVERYONE AND I HOPE
EVERYONE TO HAVE THE SAME
PERSPECTIVE AT THE END OF THE
GAME.
KELLEE, IS THAT
POSSIBLE, THAT YOU CAN HAVE A
BOND THAT'S REAL AND STILL
BETRAY EACH OTHER?
I MEAN, I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
AS WE GO INTO THE MASTERING, I
THINK THAT WILL LIKELY HAPPEN
MORE AND MORE, AND YET IT IS AN
EMOTIONAL ROLLINGER COASTER TO
GO BACK AND FORTH BETWEEN THE
TWO.
I CAN IN THE BELIEVE
AFTER THIS TRIBAL THAT WE'RE
GOING TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT, BUT
WE ARE.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
JANET, YOU'RE UP.
YOU TOOK THREE SHOTS AT ME
AND YOU MISSED AND I'M NAILING
YOU ON MY FIRST TRY.
STAY DRY, SWEETHEART.
I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
THE ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU WANT THE
PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE THE TIME
TO DO SO.
JEFF, I THINK I GOT A LITTLE
SOMETHING.
GIVE ME A SECOND TO FISH IT OUT.
JUST TRYING TO MAKED TO THE
MASTERING.
I'M PLAYING IT FOR MYSELF.
WHY WOULDN'T HE HAVE PLAYED
IT LAST TIME?
THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR DEAN WILL NOT
COUNT.
ALL RIGHT.
JEFF, HOLD ON.
THEY GOT ALL KINDS OF IDOLS.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M LAYING THIS FOR NOURA.
YOU ARE?
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR NOURA WILL
NOT COUNT.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
OH, MY GOD.
FIRST VOTE DEAN.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DEAN.
WILL NOT COUNT.
DOES NOT COUNT.
DEAN.
JACK.
ONE VOTE JACK.
SEVENTH PERSON VOTED OUT AND
FIRST MEMBER OF OUR JURY, JACK.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
DANG.
THEY GOT HIS ASS.
JACK, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
BYE, JACK.
LOVE YOU.
SEE YAW ALL.
WELL, IT'S NIGHTS
LIKE TONIGHT THAT HAVE KEPT
"SURVIVOR" RELEVANT FROM GOING
ON 20 YEARS.
BECAUSE YOU TICK A GROUP OF
PEOPLE AND YOU FORCE THEM TO
MAKE THEIR OWN SOCIETY AND QUITE
OFTEN THAT SOCIETY THAT YOU FORM
IS A REFLECTION OF THE GREATER
SOCIETY, AND THEN THE TWISTS,
YOU GOT TO VOTE 'EM OUT.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON "SURVIVOR," A
MILESTONE IS HIT.
WHAT, WHAT?
WE'RE ALL REALLY EXCITED TO
BE HERE AT THE MERGE.
NOW IT'S GAME ON.
AND ALL HELL BREAKS
LOOSE.
ALL OF THOSE OLD LAIRO HAVE
TO GO.
WE SPLIT YOU AND KELLEE UP.
SHE TOLD US TO VOTE YOU.
THE PLAN IS TO VOTE YOU.
I CAN'T GO OUT LIKE A PUNK.
I'M REALLY SAD I'M OUT OF THE
GAME.
MAYBE DNCS ME AS A THREAT, WHICH
IS COOL.
BUT EVERYONE THAT WAS THERE
WANTED ME TO BE THERE EXCEPT FOR
ONE OR TWO PEOPLE.
OVERALL THIS WAS WAY FREAKIN'
HARDER THAN I THAWING IT WAS
GOING TO BE, BUT I'M HAPPY WITH
HOW I DID.
I THINK I WAS ABLE TO SHOW MY
TRUE COLORS, AND I'M FREAKIN'
PUMPED TO BE ON THE JURY.