>> HOW DO YOU TALK ABOUT THIS?
>> AT TRIBAL COUNCIL I WAS
COMPLETELY BLIND SIDED BY THE
CHELSEA VOTE OUTK I ABSOLUTELY
FELT LEFT OUT, OS TRA
ADVERTISE-- OS TRA IDENTIFIES,
IT IS A WAKE-UP CALL, MY BOYS AT
HOME WOULD SAY I GOT GOT.
DEAN WOKE UP AND IMMEDIATELY
TURNED TO DETECTIVE DEAN K OW
ALSKY.
THE GOAL BEING WHO ORDERED THIS
HIT.
DETECTIVE DEAN IS LOOKING FOR
MOTS NIF THE CHELSEA WALKER
CASE, I DON'T THINK IT'S ME,
CLEARLY, I DON'T THINK IT IS
CHELSEA, SHE IS HOME EATING
OREOS MY MAN TOM WANTED OUT
FOREVER.
MY MAIN SUSPECTS ARE ELIZABETH,
ELAINE, MISSY AND.
SO I CERTIFICATE GATE THEM WHO
DID YOU HEAR.
>> I'M JUST CURIOUS WHO CAME UP.
>> DON'T KNOW WHERE IT
ORIGINATED?
>> IT WASN'T ME.
>> KARISHMA, YOU KNOW WHERE IT
STARTED.
>> TO BE FILLED IN.
>> I WOULD ARGUE I WAS THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT'S FAIR, CAN'T DISAGREE
WITH THAT.
>> WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
WHO DID I GET IT FROM.
I GOT IT FROM-- ELAINE.
WITHOUT DO YOU THINK.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
I WANT TO FIND OUT WHO IS THE
STRATEGIC MASTER MIND THAT CON
VINSDZ THE TRIBE AWAY FROM
KARISHMA TOWARD CHELSEA BECAUSE
THEY ARE SUPER, SUPER GOOD AT
THIS GAME AND NEED TO BE NOT
ONLY WATCHED BUT NEED TO GO.
>> NOBODY ORDERED A HIT.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHERE CHELSEA CAME FROM.
>> I AM NOT SAYING I HAVE NO
IDEA.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT IT DOES MAKE
SENSE AND THE SHOWMANCE BETWEEN
YOU AND CHELSEA, ESPECIALLY IF
PEOPLE WANT YOU OUT.
>> YOU ARE TALKING A LOT OF
NONSENSE.
>> I'M TALKING NONSENSE.
>> YEAH.
>> I AM STILL NOT GETTING A
STRAIGHT ANSWER OUT OF YOU,
WHERE THIS CAME FROM.
>> YEAH, DEAN, IT WAS ME.
I TOOK YOUR GIRLFRIEND OUT OF
THIS GAME.
IT WAS TOO SCARY, THEY WERE A
PAIR, THEY ARE DANGEROUS.
>> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT THAT BLIND
SIDE.
I PUT IT TOGETHER QUICKLY AND
PEOPLE FULLED IT OFF.
BUT DEAN DOESN'T TAKE "THE BLIND
SIDE" WELL.
HE'S MAD.
WELL, CRAP, DEAN, I KEPT YOU
HERE TODAY.
YOU DON'T BITE THE HAND THAT
FEEDS YOU.
YOU REALLY DON'T.
YOU SHOULDN'T.
YOU REALLY, REALLY SHOULDN'T.
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> GOOD MORNING, GUYS!
NESS.
>> ONE OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
SPOTS IN FIJI.
VOKAI GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW LAIRO TRIBE, CHELSEA
VOTED OUT AT THE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> WOW.
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE GET TO IT?
>> YES.
>> EVERYBODY, DROP
YOUR-- SWITCHING TRIBES.
ELAINE WHAT IS THE FEELING RIGHT
NOW, YOU ARE ROCKING BACK AND
FORTH.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M ON THE OUTS
ALREADY AND I DIDN'T EVEN DRAW
THE BUCK YET, I'M NERVOUS, I GET
ITCHY.
>> NOW WAIT A MINUTE AM HOW CAN
YOU FEEL YOU ARE ON THE OUTS
BEFORE THE EVENT HAS HAPPENED.
>> BECAUSE I'M NOT LUCKY.
I'M NOT LUCKY.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S PUT AN END
TO THE MYSTERY.
>> WHAT IS THE EVENT?
>> WHEN JEFF SAYS EVERYONE DROP
YOUR ABOVE, I WAS CRINGING
BECAUSE NOTHING IS SET IN STONE.
YOU HAVE TO START ALL OVER AGAIN
FROM SQUARE ONE AND SOLIDIFY
YOUR POSITION IN A NEW TRIBE AND
THAT SCARES ME BIG TIME.
>> HERE WE GO, EVERYONE REVEAL
YOUR NEW BUFF AND SAY HELLO TO
YOUR NEW TRIBE.
>> WE OPEN UP OUR BOXES AN HAVE
I PURPLE,nd I COULD BREATHE
AND STARTED LOOKING AROUND FOR
WHO WILL BE PURPLE AND
IMMEDIATELY I SEE THAT OUR TRIBE
IS FOUR AND FOUR SO THIS IS A
DOOMS DAY SENORIO, ELIZABETH,
MISSY.
>> DAN, DO WE HAVE AN EVEN SPLIT
OVER THERE ON VOKAI.
>> A 4/4 SPLIT, JEFF.
>> LET'S SEE, WILL THE NEW VOKAI
WE HAVE FOR FOURER VOKAI WITH
DAN, JASON, TOMORROWY AND LAUREN
AND FOUR FORMER LAIRO WITH
AARON, MISSY, ELIZABETH AND
ELAINE.
ELAINE, LUCKY, UNLUCKY?
>> LUCKY, JEFF, I GOT REAL LUCKY
BECAUSE WE ARE 4-4 ON VOKAI, WE
HAVE STRONG PEOPLE TO WIN
CHALLENGES, I GOT IN A TRIBE
WITH MY ALLIANCE.
I GOT REAL LUCKY AND I WAS SO
HAPPY.
>> FOR THE NEW LAIRO TRIBE WE
HAVE FIVE FORMER VOKAI, NOURA,
KELLEEE, JAMAL, JACK AND JANET
AND THREE FORMER LAIRO WITH TOM,
DEAN AND KARISHMA.
KARISHMA, BRAND NEW TRIBE, BRAND
NEW GAME, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THIS GROUP OF EIGHT?
>> YEAH, I LOOK AROUND AND I'M
REALLY LIKING THE FACES THAT I'M
SEEING.
I'M FEELING REALLY GOOD VIBES,
EVERY DAY ON SURVIVOR IS A NEW
OPPORTUNITY.
SO YOU JUST GOT TO EMBRACE IT.
>> I WAS EXCITED TOR A NEW
CHANGE BECAUSE I WAS BLIND SIDED
BY THE WHOLE TRIBE ON THE
CHELSEA VOTE OUT BUT WHERE I
LANDED I'M DOWN 5-3 AND ALREADY
THINKING TO MYSELF NOT A GOOD
SPOT TO BE.
>> NOW THAT WE HAVE OUR TWO NEW
TRIBES LET'S GET TO OUR FIRST
REWARD CHALLENGE.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOUR FEET
ARE GOING TO BE TIED TOGETHER.
YOUR ARMS BOUND AT YOUR SIDE.
ON MY GO YOU WILL SLITHER
THROUGH A SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
YOU WILL THEN RACE TO FINISH A
FIRE PUZZLE.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET IT DONE WINS
REWARD.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU ARE
PLAYING FOR?
>> YES, TELL US.
>> ST THE BIGGEST REWARD OF THE
SEASON.
AND WE WANTED TO MAKE IT
SPECIAL.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> COME ON.
>> WE BROUGHT APPLEBEE TO FIJI!
>> OH MY GOD.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> OH, OH MY GOD.
YOU WILL ENJOY APPLEBEE'S
LOADED, SIZZLING FAJITAS,
SMOTHERED IN HOT QUESO, WE'VE
GOT STEAK, CHICKEN, SHRIMP, PLUS
THE CLASSIC COMBO, BUFFALO
CHICKEN WINGS.
>> WAIT, WAIT, ALL THE
FIXININGS.
>> WITH ALL THE FIXININGS.
>> YES, SPINACH, ARTICHOKE DIP,
QUESADILLAS, GOT ROOM FOR
DESSERT.
>> WE DO, JEFF.
>> HOW ABOUT THE BLUE
RIBON-- RIBBON BROWNIE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
>> AN APPLEBEE'S SIGNATURE DRINK
THE SHARK BOWL.
>> OH, THE SHARK BOWL.
>> I LOVE APPLEBEES, APPLEBEE'S
IS BY FAR MY FAVORITE SIT DOWN
RESTAURANT.
>> OH MY GOD, YES.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST REWARD AND
WE ARE GOING TO GET THIS.
>> WORTH PLAYING FOR?
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT, STRATEGIZE WITH
YOUR NEW TRIBE, WE'LL GET
STARTED.
HERE WE GO, FOR THE BIGGEST
REWARD OF THE SEASON.
APPLEBEE IN FIJI, SURVIVORS,
READY?
GO!
>> LET'S GO, GUYS.
>> ST ELIZABETH AND DAN AND TOM
AND JANET, YOU HAVE TO SLILTER
ON YOUR BELLY-- SLITHER ON YOUR
BELLIES AND ST NOT EASY, THAT
SAND IS HOT.
DAN AND ELIZABETH MOVING QUICKLY
BUT TOM AND JANUARY RECEIPT
STAYING IN T INCH BY INCH.
DAN AND ELIZABETH WITH THE EARLY
LEAD FOR THE NEW VOKAI TRIBE.
A HUGE REWARD ON THE LINE.
>> GET OVER THAT LITTLE PUMP.
>> DAN IS GOOD, YOU GOT TO GET
ELIZABETH.
>> ARE YOU GOOD.
>> SECRETARY PAIR GOING, TOMMY
AND MISSY GOINGK TRYING TO
EXTEND THE LEAD FOR VOKAI.
TOM USING ALL THAT MUSCLE, TOM
IS OVER NOW, KEEP GOING!
>> TOMMY INCHING OVER NOW.
>> ARE YOU THERE, MISSY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
>> .
>> TOMMY IS GOOD.
>> WIGEL WIGGLE WIGGLE.
ARE YOU GOOS MISSY.
>> IT IS NOW LAUREN AND ELAINE,
THE FINAL PAIR FOR VOKAI.
>> YOU GOT IT, LAUREN, GO.
>> YOU'RE GOOD, GO.
>> AT HE JACK AND DEAN FOR
LAIRO.
>> I CAN'T MOVE.
>> JACK AND DEAN TRYING TO GET
OVER THAT SECOND MOUND.
LAUREN FACE DOWN.
THEY CAN TASTE THAT REWARD.
ELAINE IS THERE, ARE YOU GOOD.
A.
>> A COUPLE MORE, ARE YOU GOOD.
>> START WORK ON THE PUZZLE IT
IS NOW JASON AND AARON ON THE
PUZZLE FOR VOKAI.
BIG LEAD FOR VOKAI.
A VERY FAMILIAR STORY FOR THE
TRIBE WEARING PURPLE.
>> ARE YOU GOOD.
GO, KARISHMA, GO NOURA.
NOW ARRON AND JASON FEEL THE
PRESSURE, THAT FINAL PAIR FOR
LAIRO, LAUREN MOVING QUICKLY,
KARISHMA IS STRUGGLING.
YOU HAVE TO GET UP THAT MOUND.
THAT IS THE TOUGHEST PART.
EVERY SECOND YOU TAKE IS ANOTHER
SECOND OF A LEAD FOR VOKAI.
>> STAY STRAIGHT.
>> NOURA CONTINUES TO WORK,
KARISHMA CONTINUES TO STRUGGLE.
>> I CAN'T PUT MY HANDS.
>> PIECE BY PIECE JASON AND
AARON ARE CLOSING IN ON THE
FINISH OF THIS FIRE PUZZLE.
>> COME ON, GIRL, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
EVERYTHING YOU GOT, COME ON.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
NOURA IS PULLING KARISHMA UP THE
HILL.
THAT'S HOW YOU WORK TOGETHER.
>> COME ON KARISHMA.
>> OKAY, BABY.
>> VOKAI GETTING CLOSER AND
CLOSER TO A ONCE IN A LIFETIME
REWARD ON SURVIVOR.
NOURA CONTINUES TO FIGHT, USING
EVERY PART OF HER BODY TO PULL
HER PARTNER TO THE FINISH.
>> COME ON, KARISHMA.
>> SHE'S THERE.
>> GO, COME ON, KELLEEE, NOW THE
PUZZEL.
>> YES.
>> JAMAL AND KELLEEE QUICKLY GET
A PIECEMENT AND ANOTHER PIECE.
THEY ARE NOT GIVING UP THRARKS
IS FOR SURE, AARON AND JASON ARE
DOWN TO THREE PIECES.
MAKE IT TWO PIECES.
ONE TEASE LEFT.
>> YES, YES.
VOKAI WINS APPLEBEES IN FIJI!
ONE THING'S CLEAR, EVERYBODY
HERE WORKED IN THAT CHALLENGE.
BUT THERE WAS A DECISIVE VICTORY
BY VOKAI.
APPLEBEE' IN FIJI WAITING FOR
YOU, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT
AND ENJOY.
ALL RIGHT, LAIRO, GOT NOTHING
FOR YOU, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP.
>> WE HAD A CHANCE AT A GREAT
REWARD AND I HATE TO KEP PUTTING
IT ON THE SAME PERSON BUT CAR
YOU WERE MA WAS JUST NOT GOING
TO BE ABLE TO PERFORM GOING
THROUGH THE SAND.
THE SAD THING IS SHE HAD BEEN ON
PUZZLE, HE HAD TRIED DOING THE
PHYSICAL ROLE AND HASN'T BB ABLE
TO DO ANYTHING.
SO WE HAVE OUR WORK CUT OUT FOR
US.
QUNS OH MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> WALKING UP TO APPLEBEE'S WAS
UNBELIEVABLE BECAUSE FIRST THING
WE SAW WAS THE SHARK BOWL.
CLEAR OCEAN BLUE WITH THE GUMMI
SHARK ON TOP.
WE'RE IN THE FIJI ISLAND AND
THAT IS JUST THE ISLAND DRINK
YOU WANT.
>> LET'S EAT.
>> LOADED FAJITAS, WE HAVE
STEAK, WE HAVE SHRIMP.
>> THIS IS THE BEST THING I EVER
DRANK IN MY LIFE.
>> AND ALL THIS FOOD IN THE
BACKGROUND, THE BUFFALO WINGS,
THE SPINACH ARTICHOKE DIP.
>> CHICKEN, STEAK, SHRIMP OR THE
TRIO.
>> THE TRIO.
>> OH MY GOD, THIS IS SO GOOD.
>> APPLEBY'S I LOVE YOU.
THE FAJITAS WAS AMAZING.
MY MOUTH WAS WATERING, IT WAS
UNBELIEVABLE.
SO IT WAS ONE OF THE GREATEST
MOMENTS AND SOMETHING I WILL
NEVER FORGET FOR THE REST OF MY
LIFE.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> WE ARE A NEW TRIBE, A NEW
FAMILY, THANK YOU FOR COMING.
AND THANK YOU FOR APPLEBEE'S FOR
MAKING THIS MEAL FOR US
TOGETHER.
>> APPLEBEE'S.
>> THE DANGERS TO A 4-4 SPLIT T
IS EVEN HARD TO PUT INTO WORDS
BECAUSE THERE IS SO MUCH DANGER
AND THERE IS SO MUCH THAT COULD
POTENTIALLY HAPPEN.
FOR EXAMPLE, WE COULD HAVE A TIE
WITH TRIBAL COUNCIL AND THERE IS
A CHANCE THAT WE HAVE TO DRAW
ROCKS TO SEE WHO GOES HOME.
SO WE REALLY HAVE TO THINK OF A
WAY TO GET ONE OF THESE NEW
VOKAI MEMBERS OVER WITH US.
>> I LIKE WIN THE NECK THREE.
>> WHY WOULD WE LOSE.
>> I LIKE THE NEW TRIBE MEMBERS,
THIS IS LIKE THE HONEYMOON
PHASE, PRETTY SOON THAT MAY FADE
AND THE ALCOHOL FACE, THEN WE'LL
SEE.
>> MELT IN YOUR MOUTH, YOU KNOW
WHAT IT TASTES LIKE, IT TASTES
LOOK A W, BRO.
>> IT TASTES LIKE A WITH.
>> LAYERA CAN GO TO BED.
>> MY TRIBE, THEY IMMEDIATELY
WERE CHITCHATTING AND CUTTING UP
WITH THE VOKAI PEOPLE.
I DON'T LIKE THAT, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T KNOW THESE PEOPLE, THEY
COULD BE LYING THROUGH YOUR
TEETH, YOU CAN'T TRUST THEM, SO
WE DEFINITELY NEED TO STAY FOUR
STRONG.
>> I LOVE YOU APPLEBEE'S.
>> APPLEBEE'S.
>> THIS SOUR CAMP FIRE AND THAT
IS OUR SHELTER.
>> THIS IS THESE.
>> WHERE DO Y'ALL SLEEP.
>> WE TRIED BAMBOO AT FIRST.
>> THE SMOKE COMES THROUGH HERE
SO IT KEEPS ALL THE BUGS AWAY.
>> HI BEEN REALLY HATING MY
TRIBE FOR A LONG TIME.
THEY ESSENTIALLY BULLIED ME,
REFUSED TO WORK WITH ME.
AND WROTE MY NAME DOWN AT TWO
TRIBAL COUNCILS IN A ROW.
>> I LOVE THIS.
>> ON TOP OF THAT, I JUST SHOWED
MY ENTIRE NEW TRIBE HOW WEAK I
AM IN CHALLENGES PHYSICALLY.
SO I'M SCREWED.
>> LET'S GO SWIMMING.
I HAVE ONE CHOICE TO STAY ALIVE.
I HAVE ONE CHOICE TO KEEP
BREATHING AND THAT IS TO FLIP ON
OLD LAYERA.
>> KELLEEE, HAVE I SO MUCH TO
TELL YOU GUYS.
MY NAME HAS BEEN AT EVERY
TRIBAL, I WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU
GUYS.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE DONE A BETTER
JOB.
WE KNEW KARISHMA WAS NOT GOING
TO BE--NESS I ASSUME YOU KNEW
THAT BEFORE.
>> YEAH.
>> FROM THE OLD TRIBE WE HAVE
DEAN, WHO HI A PRETTY GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH.
AND CHAR-- KARISHMA WHO I WOULD
SAY HER AND I ARE NOT BEST
FRIENDS AND ON TOP I AM IN THE
TRIBE DOWN NUMBER 5-3.
IT IS NOT A GREAT FEELING.
COMING INTO THE GAME THAT IS THE
WAY ST, YOU CAN'T MOAP ABOUT T
YOU HAVE TO GET TO WORK.
>> KARISHMA IS THE ONE, I FEEL
BAD, AND I THINK ABOUT IT NOW, I
SHOULD HAVE STEPPED UP NOW AND
SAID SHE JUST CAN'T DO IT.
>> WE HAD THE CHANCE OF VOTING
HER OUT LAST NIGHT.
WE DECIDED NOT TO.
>> WE WERE SHOCKED.
>> WE WERE JUST FIGURING SHE
COULD BE VOTED OUT ANY TIME WE
WANTED TO.
>> RIGHT.
>> WE GOT TOGETHER LIKE
SOPHOMORE YEAR IN COLLEGE.
>> THAT IS SO FUNNY.
OH MY GOD.
>> WE GRADUATED.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE WENT TO KOREA TO TEACH
ENGLISH.
KELLEEE AND I HAVE BEEN VIBING A
BIT, FUNNY THING S I COME TO
FIND OUT, WE HAVE A MUTUAL
FRIEND, A VERY SPECIAL MUTUAL
FRIEND, MY ONLY LONG-TERM
GIRLFRIEND.
>> SO WHY ARE YOU GUYS STILL NOT
TOGETHER.
>> ONE THAT I DATED FOR SIX PLUS
YEARS.
AND THEY LAP TO GO TO BUSINESS
SCHOOL TOGETHER.
BEING ABLE TO TALK ABOUT SHARED
EXPERIENCES AND FRIENDS BRINGS
THE RELATIONSHIP TO ANOTHER
LEVEL THAT YOU DON'T NECESSARILY
HAVE WITH CERTAIN PEOPLE.
SO GOING TO TRY TO WORK THAT
ANGLE.
>> GOING INTO LAST TRIBAL AS FAR
AS I KNEW, EVERYONE LITERALLY
WAS GOING FOR KARISHMA EXCEPT
FOR CASHISH MA, AND THEY WERE
LIKE CHELEE CHEM SEE CHELSEA.
OH MY GOD, THAT IS LIKE SO
CRAZY.
>> THAT IS THE DRAMA WE WERE
MISSING OUT ON.
>> DEAN AND I REALLY-- AFTER OUR
CONVERSATION I WAS LIKE THIS
SOUNDS LIKE A GUY I COULD WORK
WITH.
BUT KARISHMA WANTS TO FLIP, I
THINK SHE'S WITH US.
>> IT IS FIVE VOKAI, 3 LAIRO,
THESE THREE PEOPLE SEEM TO BE AT
THE MERCY OF THE FIVE OLD VOKAI
MEMBERS.
>> THE THING IS ARRANGE MARRIAGE
IS LIKE A LOADED TERM.
ARE YOU NOT LIKE BOUND TO THE
ALTAR BUT IT IS ALSO NOT LIKE
YOU ARE GIVEN COMPLETE FREEDOM.
SOMEWHERE IN THE MIDDLE.
>> WERE YOUR PARENTS ARRANGED.
>> THEY KNEW EACH OTHER FOR TWO
WEEKS BEFORE THEY GOT MARRIED.
>> WOW.
>> I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT MY
NEW FAMILY IT SIN CREDIBLE TO
OPEN UP AND BE VULNERABLE AT
THAT LEVEL AND TO TALK ABOUT MY
MARRIAGE.
>> I GOT MARRIED BECAUSE MY
PARENTS WANTED ME TO GET MARRIED
BECAUSE I WAS SUPPOSED TO.
>> MY PARENTS, THE DAY BEFORE I
GOT MARRIED, THE DAY AFTER I WAS
MARRIED, I SPENT TEN QUEERS
BEING TOLD I'M A BURDEN AND
SHAME TO MY FAMILY.
BECAUSE I WOULDN'T AGREE TO GET
MARRIED.
I GAVE IN.
SO HOW DO YOU TALK ABOUT THIS.
>> NO, I.
>> YOU JUST DID.
>> LIKE.
>> JUST LIKE THAT.
>> I HAVE BEEN MARRIED FOR FOUR
AND A HALF YEARS BUT I HAVE BEEN
QUESTIONING MY LIFE CHOICES.
AND I REALLY, REALLY NEED TO
UNDERSTAND WHAT THIS NEXT
CHAPTER IS GOING TO ENTAIL THASM
IS MY PURPOSE HERE IN THIS GAME.
>> I NEED TO LIKE SHARE MY
FEELINGS WITH MY HUSBAND.
I DON'T THINK I ALWAYS TELL HIM
HOW I AM DOING.
I QUEENED OF HIDE BEHIND A
SMILE.
AND FOUR YEARS LATER WE ARE LIKE
ROOMMATES.
>> YOU KNOW, HAVE I HAD REALLY
MEANINGFUL CONVERSATIONS WITH
THE VOKAI MEMBERS.
I CAN RELATE TO THEM MORE.
THEY MAY UNDERSTAND ME ON A
LEVEL THAT OLD LAIRO JUST COULD
NOT UNDERSTAND ME.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> WE'RE GLAD YOU ARE IN OUR
TRIBE.
>> SO I THINK I MAY BE ABLE TO
GET A FOOTING IN THIS GAME AM I
IN AM NO LONGER LAIRO.
I AM MOVING OVER.
-- LET'S GO.
>> OH, WE HAVE A THROWDOWN.
>> WE HAVE TO BATTLE THIS OUT,
WE HAVE ATLANTA, GEORGIA, VERSUS
KENTUCKY.
>> OH!
OH!
>> SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT.
>> WE'RE FUN RIGHT.
>> ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS GET A
HOLD OF IT.
>> ELAINE IS DOING WHAT SHE
DOES.
SHE'S DOING AN INCREDIBLE JOB AT
THE SOCIAL GAME.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY WAY THAT YOU
ARE GOING TO WIN THIS GAME IS TO
GET PEOPLE TO GENUINELY, TRULY
LIKE YOU.
>> SHOULDERS DOWN, ONE, TWO,
THREE.
>> YES!
>> WE HAVE A WINNER.
>> DING DUNG DING.
>> SO I HAVE TO FORM REAL
RELATIONSHIPS AND REAL BONDS
WITH PEOPLE.
AND SAY YOU KNOW WHAT, LET'S
JUST TALK ABOUT OUR KIDS.
LET'S JUST TALK ABOUT OUR
FAMILY, BECAUSE THEY DON'T LIKE
YOU, WHY ARE THEY GOING TO KEEP
YOU AROUND.
>> HOW ABOUT THESE.
>> I WAS LIKE CAN I WEAR THESE
SOCKS.
HE IS SLIEK ABSOLUTELY NOT, WHY,
EVERYONE IS GOING TO LAUGH AT
YOU.
>> WITH THE SOCKS.
>> YEAH.
HE SAID THEY ARE PURPLE AND HAVE
MY FACE ON THEM.
I AM LIKE EXACTLY, THAT IS WHY I
SHOULD WEAR THEM.
>> HE WILL BE THE COOLEST KID IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
>> I'M VERY FORTUNATE THAT I GET
TO EXPERIENCE SURVIVOR WITH MY
SON.
I MEAN VISUALLY TO SEE YOUR
CHILD EVERY DAY, AND HIS SMILE,
IT'S LIKE-- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY,
LIKE WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS MAN.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING.
>> FROM A PROTECTION STANDPOINT,
YOU AND I MUTUALLY HAVE TO HAVE
EACH OTHER'S BACK LIKE 100
PERCENT BECAUSE IT DOES NO GOOD,
YOU COME OUT OF THE GAME, THEN
IT IS GOING TO BE HARDER ON ME
FROM A PHYSICAL STANDPOINT SO WE
ARE BOTH HAVE TO MAKE THE MERGE
AND HAVE THAT WHEN THEY COMING
LIKE YO, SAY I WIN IT AND YOU
LOST IT, I STILL HAVE TO PROTECT
YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I'M EXCITED.
>> WHO DO YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT.
>> I'M LIKE, YOU LOVE YOUR FOUR.
>> I LOVE MY FOUR.
>> BUT OBVIOUSLY SOMEONE IS
GOING TO HAVE TO GO SO.
>> ST 4-4, WE CAN PLAY THE
GAMING TO NOW.
>> AARON AND MYSELF, WE ARE LIKE
BROS.
SO DING.
I'M WITH HIM NOW.
I KNOW HE WANTS TO WORK WITH ME.
AND I HOPE WE WILL VOTE OUT ONE
OF THE OLD LAIRO.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING IF HE
WITH DON'T WIN.
>> WE'RE IN A GOOD PLACE, WE'RE
IN A GOOD PLACE.
>> YOU THINK SO.
>> I KNOW WE ARE.
>> YOU THINK THEY WILL EAT ONE
OF THEIR OWN BEFORE US.
>> THEY ARE NOT GOING TO FLIP.
WHAT WE ARE DO IS WE WILL TALK.
I AM NOT ON A DRY ROCK.
>> YOU AGREE IT IS DEAD, ED.
>> DEAD IN THE WATER.
>> THIS SWAP KILLED ORANGE BUT
IT GAVE US.
>> THEY NEED US TO YOU.
>> I AGREE WITH AARON, LAIRO HAS
BEEN DEAD, ORANGE DOES MOT EXIST
ANY MORE.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS READY TO
GET TO YOUR FIRST IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE AS A NEW TRIBE.
FIRST THING FIRST, TOMORROWEE,
TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN, IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU SWIM
OUT TO A LADDER, CLIMB UP AND
LEAP OFF.
YOU WILL THEN RELEASE THREE
BUOYS TO MANEUVER THEM ACROSS A
SET OF BALANCE BEAMS.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE END YOU WILL
ATTEMPT TO LAND THOSE BOYS
ON-- BUOYS ON THE THREE TARGETS.
FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIFTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE,
WE'LL GET IT ON.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO, FOR
IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY.
GO!
EVERYBODY IN THE WATER, GOT TO
GET EVERYBODY TO THAT PLATFORM
BEFORE YOU CAN START UP THE
LADDER.
ARE YOU GO, PURPLE, YOU ARE
GOOD, ORANGE.
>> ELIZABETH GOING UP FOR VOKAI,
KELLEEE FOR LAIRO.
>> LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> HERE COMES JASON FOR VOKAI.
HE'S IN.
KARISHMA TAKING A LOT OF TIME ON
THAT LATTER.
ELAINE IS GOING TO CATCH HER.
>> COME ON KARISHMA.
>> ELAINE DIVES IN, THERE GOES
DAN, HE LAPS NOURA.
VOKAI HAS BEEN REALLY QUICKLY.
LAIRO HAS THEIR BUOY.
YOU ARE LOOKING FOR TWO PEOPLE
TO TRANSPORT THOSE BUOYS, ONE
HAND ON EACH ROPE, NOW THEY ARE
GAINING A BALANCE TEAM.
LAIRO NOW STILL STRUGGLING.
THERE YOU GO, LAIRO.
>> SLOWLY.
>> CAR YOU WERE MA HAS BEEN SLOW
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR VOKAI TO
HAVE AN EARLY LEAD.
>> NOW LAIRO IS STRUGGLING TO
GET A SYSTEM GOING FOR EVEN
GETTING THEIR BUOYS ON.
>> VOKAI MAKING THIS LOOK EASY.
VOKAI ONCE AGAIN WITH AN EARLY
LEAD IN THE CHALLENGE.
A FAMILIAR STORY FOR LAIRO.
GOT TO GET THEM ALL IN THE
BASKET.
YOU GUYS DROPPED, YOU HAVE TO
START OVER.
>> VOKAI, ARE YOU GOOD.
LET'S GO.
>> MISSY WITH THE FIRST BUOY.
FOR VOKAI, MISSY JUST MISSES.
LAIRO HAS WON EXACTLY ONE
CHALLENGE THIS SEASON.
VOKAI WOULD LIKE TO EXTEND THAT
STREAK.
JUST SHORT, LAIRO TRYING TO STAY
IN THIS.
YOU'RE GOOD, GO.
JAMA DSH DSH JAMAL AN KARISHMA
HAVE TO GET ACROSS THE BEAM.
>> COME ON, KARISHMA, WAITING ON
YOU, GIRL.
LET'S GO.
YOU GOT IT.
>> NOW YOU HAVE TO GET THE BUOYS
AND EVERYBODY OVER HERE.
MISSY JUST MISSES.
KELLEEE RACES BACK, GOT TO GET
THEM IN THE BASKET AND EVERYBODY
ON THE PLATFORM, WAIT.
>> COVER UP, COVER UP, WAITING
ON KARISHMA, ARE YOU GOOD, GO
LAIRO.
LAIRO DOWN ONE BUCKET, IT
TOMORROWEE GOING TO GIVE IT A
SHOT TOK VIE, TOMMY THE SECOND
FOR VOKAI.
DEAN THE FIRST FOR LAIRO.
TOMMY TRYING TO GET THAT BUOY,
TOMMY FOR THE WIN FOR VOKAI.
>> JUST MISSES.
DEAN TIES IT UP T IS 2-26789
DEAN HAS THE BUOY.
JUST SHORT, WE GOT A SHOWDOWN.
LAIRO IS BACK IN THIS.
TOMMY'S SHORT, CAN DEAN WIN IT
RIGHT HERE?
NO, SHORT.
>> TOMMY CAN WIN IT FOR VOKAI.
AND HE DOES!
VOKAI WINS AGAIN.
SENDING LAIRO BACK TO TRIBAL
COUNCIL FOR THE FOURTH TIME THIS
SEASON.
WITH A BRAND NEW TRIBE.
WHO KNOWS WHO IS GOING TO HAPPEN
IN TRIBAL.
VOOK AYE, ONCE AGAIN IMMUNE SIT
ALL YOURS.
NOBODY GOING HOME TONIGHT, AND
NOBODY GOING TO ISLAND OF THE
IDENTIFYOL.
>> GRAB YOUR STUFF, SWIM OUT,
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT, LAIRO, TRIBAL
COUNCIL TONIGHT, SOMEBODY WILL
BE THE FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT.
SWIM OUT.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP, A UNITED
TRIBAL.
>> THANKS, JEFF.
>> TOM, KARISHMA AND DEAN, I
FEEL LIKE I'VE CONNECTED WITH
THEM ALL VERY, VERY WELL.
BUT KARISHMA DID NOT DO HERSELF
ANY FAVORS.
SHE HAS AN ABILITY TO PERFORM A
CHALLENGE.
I'M READY FOR A W IN ORANGE.
WE WERE ONE AWAY, ONE BASKET
AWAY.
>> I APPRECIATE EVERYONE SENDING
ME POSITIVE VIBES.
BUT THE FACT IS I DIDN'T MAKE IT
HAPPEN SO.
>> BUT YOU STEPPED UP.
IT IS WITH IT IS.
I AM GOING TO GO ON A WOOD RUN.
>> I'M A DIVISION 1 BASKETBALL
PLAYER, THAT WAS MY MOMENT AND I
BLEW TMENT I CAN'T BELIEVE TOW
THAT LONG, PALE, REDHEAD GOOF
BALL LOOKING GUY, SO ADD TO IT,
ME, TOM AND KARISHMA ARE REALLY
AT THEIR WHIM STRKS UP TO ME TO
MAKE THE BEST IN LAIRO Y MOT ME.
>> SHOULD WE PUT OURSELVES IN
THEIR SHOES.
>> TO BE HONEST YOU ARE PROBABLY
SAFE BECAUSE ST EITHER LET'S GET
A THREAT OUT, ME OR LET'S CUT
THE FAT, KARISHMA.
>> WHAT CAN WE DO.
>> I AM THINKING WE HAVE TO-- WE
ARE KIND OF LIMITED WHAT WE CAN
DO.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO SEND ONE OF
THEIR PEOPLE HOME T WILL BE ONE
OF US THREE THAT WILL GO HOME
TONIGHT BUT WHAT I AM ENCOURAGED
BY IS THEY DON'T WANT TO LOSE
ANY MORE CHALLENGES AND THAT
REALLY POINTS THE FINGER AT
KARISHMA.
>> TALKING ABOUT EASING YOUR
MIND.
>> EASING YOUR MIND.
>> THERE ARE GUYS THAT PROBABLY
WANT TO WIN, WILL IS ONE WAY TO
DO THAT.
>> IT IS SO CLEAR.
>> YEAH, EVERY CHALLENGE IT IS
GOING TO BE HOW TO MINIMIZE THE
DAMAGE SHE CAN DO TO OUR ABILITY
TO WIN.
>> I KNOW.
>> WILL IS NOT MUCH KARISHMA CAN
DO AT THIS POINT TO MAKE A GOOD
CASE FOR HERSELF IN ANY
CHALLENGE CAPACITY.
WE ALL SEE IT WE'VE BEEN SEEING
IT ALL GAME LONG.
SHE SAY LIABILITY.
>> I DON'T HAVE
LAIRO.
I WANT TO WORK WITH YOU GUYS.
I WANT-- I AM NOT AN ATHLETE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I AM NOT.
I AM JUST NOT.
I KNOW MY OWN WEAKNESS.
>> IF WE VOTE OUT KARISHMA, THEN
WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT IN
THE NEXT FEW CHALLENGES HOW TO
MINIMIZE THE DAMAGE THATxD SHE C
CAUSE BY THE PHYSICAL
LIMITATIONS THAT SHE HAS.
NOTHING MEAN ABOUT THAT.
IT IS JUST A REALITY.
>> I'M GOING TO WAIT UNTIL YOU
GUYS TELL ME WHICH ONE TO WRITE
AND I WILL WRITE IT.
>> I WILL GO BACK THIS WAY.
>> CONSIDERING HOW I WAS VIEWED
AS WEAK IN THE CHALLENGE, IT IS
DEFINITELY NOT CRAZY TO ASSUME
THAT THE TRIBE WANTS TO LET GO
OF ME.
SO I'M OUT HERE NOW WITH THE OLD
VOKAI PLAYING UP THE SOCIAL
GAME.
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
EVERYTHING?
>> I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I GUESS YOU
GUYS HAVE TO DECIDE IF YOU WANT
A STRONGER, TRY TO WIN
CHALLENGES OR GET TO MERGE WITH
SOMEBODY WEAKER THERE.
>> TOM IS OLD SCHOOL MAN.
>> VERY TYPICAL OF MEN OF THAT
AGE.
>> I WANT TO WIN, FIRST OF ALL,
I WANT TO GO THE TO MERGE WITH
YOU TOO.
>> HE CAN JUST GOING TO SAY IT
THE WAY ST, THERE IS GOING TO BE
NO HIDDEN AGENDAS WITH HIM,
WHICH I APPRECIATE.
HE, HOWEVER, HAS MORE OF A
TRIBAL MENTALITY AND I BELIEVE
IF WE GOT TO A MERGE I WOULD
LOSE HIM TO HIS OLD TRIBE.
>> YOU THINK IT'S CAR SHALL
THAT-- KARISHMA'S NIGHT.
>> I THINK SO.
>> HE IS A TERRIBLE-- SHE SAY
TERRIBLE CHALLENGE PERSON.
>> I AGREE.
>> I WANT TO WORK WITH YOU BUT
LIKE I DON'T WANT TO BECOME THE
NEXT CHELSEA.
>> THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
THERE IS NOT GOING TO BE
CUDDLING.
>> I REALLY LIKE-- I WANT TO
WORK WITH HIM, BUT THERE IS
SOMETHING ABOUT DEAN THAT MAKES
YOU WANT TO WORK WITH HIM, THAT
MAKES YOU WANT TO TRUST HIM.
BUT ALSO THAT MAKES ME VERY,
VERY WARY OF DEAN AND MAKES HIM
A HUGE THREAT IN THIS GAME.
SO DEAN IS NOT THE RIGHT PERSON
TO BRING INTO THE MERGE.
>> SO I HAVE BEEN GETTING A
LOT OF INFORMATION FROM DEAN,
AND-- TOM IS ALREADY WITH ME.
>> I CAN SEE THAT.
>> DEAN IS KIND OF ALREADY WITH
ME AND KARISHMA WANTS TO WORK
WITH US FOR SURE.
>> SO WHO WOULD BE THE FIRST
VOTE OUT THEN.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> TONIGHT IS SOME WHAT SIMPLE.
THE ONLY MONKEY WRINCH IN THERE
IS WHEN I GO TO THE ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS I LOST MY VOTE FOR
TONIGHT.
>> I WANT SOME REAL FOOD.
>> SO THAT PUTS US 4-3.
BUT THANK GOD WE STILL HAVE THE
NUMBERS.
I FEEL SO LUCKY AND EVEN THOUGH
I DON'T HAVE A VOTE, I STILL
HAVE A SAY, I AM STILL ANALYZING
THE GAME, LIKE WHAT WOULD BE THE
BEST FOR MY GAME, OUR GAME, SOME
PEOPLE ARE THINKING KARISHMA
BECAUSE SHE'S WEAKER.
DEAN IS A PHYSICAL THREAT AND
TOM IS A LIKABLE GUY, BUT HE'S
NOT AS PHYSICAL A THREAT AS I
THOUGHT.
SO NOW YOU HAVE THESE THREE
PEOPLE.
DO WE GO WITH THE WEAKEST
PERSON, OR DO WE DO BETTER IN
WINNING AS A TRIBE OR JUST GET
RID OF THE THREATS NOW SO WHEN
WE GO TO THE MERGE WE DON'T HAVE
TO DEAL WITH THEM THEN.
I AM REALLY GOING TO HAVE TO
THINK ABOUT IT.
IN ORDER TO MAKE THE BEST
DECISION FOR THIS VOTE.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO WE DO A TRIBE
SWAP, VOKAI HAS THE NUMBERS,
5-3.
SO IT WOULD SEEM LIKE FROM A BIG
PICTURE THAT EITHER THE VOKAI
GROUP STAYS STRONG OR LAIRO FIND
A CRACK.
TOM, WHAT WERE THOSE EARLY
MOMENTS LIKE WITH VOKAI, WHAT
DID YOU FEEL?
>> WELL, THE VOKAI TRIBE, ALL
FIVE OF THEM ARE FANTASTIC AND
OPEN TO TALKING ABOUT DIFFERENT
THINGS MOVING FORWARD.
I DO NOT SENSE THAT WE FOUND A
CRACK THOUGH RIGHT NOW.
>> I'VE BEEN THERE.
>> JACK, DID YOU SEE THE LAIRO
THREE DOING THEIR BEST TO FIND
OUT WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
>> YEAH, AND I THINK EVERYONE IS
OPEN TO A CONVERSATION.
WHETHER THAT IS GOING TO CHANGE
MY MIND, I DON'T KNOW.
>> KARISHMA, IT IS LIKE THEY ARE
THE ONES THAT HAVE THE JOB
OPENING AND THEY ARE JUST
SITTING BACK, I DON'T KNOW, TELL
ME ABOUT YOURSELF, MIGHT HAVE
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
>> YEAH, IT'S LIKE COME ON IN,
LET ME KNOW HOW YOU CAN HELP ME
AND I WILL DECIDE WHETHER IT IS
GOOD ENOUGH, YOU KNOW.
AT THE ENDS OF THE DAY, THE NAME
OF THE GAME WHEN ARE YOU IN THE
MINORITY IS SELF-PRESERVATION.
>> SO JANET T IS NOT JUST PICK
ONE, THERE HAS TO BE A PURPOSE
BEHIND THE VOTE WHAT IS YOUR
CRITERIA.
>> FOR ME WE NEED TO WIN IN
ORDER TO AVOID SITTING HERE WITH
YOU.
AND TO DO THAT, WE HAVE TO BE
STRONG.
WE NEED TO BE ABLE TO WIN.
>> NOURA, NOT ONLY DO YOU NOW
HAVE A CHANCE TO WORK WITH THREE
OF THE LAIRO.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
>> BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE YOU SEE
THE REAL TURN AND YOU SEE LIKE
THE WAY I'M INTERRUPTING OVER
HERE.
>> WHAT WAS HAPPENING, YOU WERE
CHURNING, WHAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO MISS YOUR
QUESTION.
>> NO, I GOT MORE.
>> OKAY.
BUT YOU KNOW, IT IS TRUE WE
DON'T KNOW WHAT CHALLENGES ARE
COMING UP, BUT SOME PEOPLE ARE
MORE WELL-ROUNDED THAN OTHERS.
SOME PEOPLE ARE PHYSICAL AND
YOUNG AND GREAT AT PUZZLES AND
SHOOTING.
SOME PEOPLE ARE MAYBE OLDER AND
THEY CAN PULL THEIR WEIGHT
AROUND CAMP AND STUFF BUT THEY
DON'T HAVE THE ENDURANCE AND ARE
NOT GOOD AT PUZZLES AND THEY
DON'T LIKE THE WATER AND THAT
MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
>> TBOW COMES THE FUN PART,
KARISHMA, WHO IS SHE TALKING
ABOUT, WHO IS FUN, GOOD AT PUZZ
ELEVATORS.
>> ME.
>> WHO IS OLDER, MAYBE GOODS
AROUND CAMP BUT NOT SO GOOD AT
PUZZLES AND CHALLENGES.
>> TOM.
>> WHO IS SHE SAYING IS OLD,
FIRST OF ALL.
>> I'M 36, I'M OLD RELATIVE TO
ALL OF THESE 20 YEAR OLD
SOMETHINGS SO IT IS ALL
RELATIVE.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND KARISHMA, NOURA ONLY
MENTIONED THE TWO GUYS, DOES
THAT BODE WELL FOR YOU?
>> WELL, HER DESCRIPTION SEEMED
TO FIT THOSE TWO GUYS BUT I
COULD ALREADY HAVE BEEN SWEPT TO
THE SIDE AND JUST BE AN
AFTERTHOUGHT AND NOT EVEN WORTH
CONSIDERING.
>> TOM F IT IS
SELF-PRESERVATION, HAVE YOU EVER
HAD TO PLEA TO BE KEPT IN A
GROUP EVER?
>> NO, I THINK YOU SHOW PEOPLE
WHO YOU ARE.
YOU HAVE TO QUAREE YOURSELF A
CERTAIN WAY, IF YOU HAVE
CHARACTER, YOU HAVE TO HAVE
LEADERSHIP, YOU HAVE TO SAY
THERE IS WHO I AM.
YOU HAVE TO DECIDE EITHER YOU
WANT ME AS PART OF YOUR GROUP OR
NOT.
>> JANET, THE COMPLENLT TOM MADE
AND I SAY THIS NOW WITH RESPECT
THAT ONLY ARCH OLDER PERSON
COULD SAY IN THAT IT IS A VERY
CONFIDENT COMMENT.
>> I DON'T THINK ST AN AGE
THING.
FOR ME I AM JUST WHO I AM.
AND TORM IS JUST WHO HE IS.
HE IS A STRAIGHT SHOOTING GUY.
AND YOU KNOW, I RESPECT THAT.
>> DEAN, HOW ABOUT FOR YOU.
IS THIS A POSITION YOU ARE
FAMILIAR WITH OR UNFAMILIAR
HAVING TO SORT OF PITCH YOURSELF
AND SAY HEY, YOU SHOULD WANT ME.
>> YES, YOU HAVE A PRODUCT, AND
YOU WANT SOMEONE ELSE TO USE IT.
AND TO MARKET IT TO THEM.
SO I AM PITCHING MYSELF TO BE
THE SIXTH MEMBER OF THE BAND BUT
ALSO PITCHING MYSELF FIVE
DIFFERENT TIMES TO SAY HEY,
THINK ABOUT YOUR OWN GAME.
CAN I BE BENEFICIAL TO YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHEN YOU SPOKE
WITH ME, AND MADE A CONNECTION
WITH ME.
I MEAN I KNOW TOM DID.
I KNOW KARISHMA DID.
I DON'T KNOW DEAN, WHEN WE DID
THAT.
>> I DON'T REALLY PULL KARISHMA,
AT OUR OLD CAMP, SHE WAS LAKE
HEY, DO YOU WANT TO GO FOR A
WALK, DO YOU WANT TO GO FOR A
WALK, LIKE EVERY TRIBAL COUNCIL,
A ONE-ON-ONE FORGED
CONVERSATIONS FEELS AWKWARD TO
ME.
>> BUT YOU DID THAT WITH THE
OTHER GUYS.
>> I WOULDN'T SAY EXPLICITSLY
HEY, JAMAL LET'S GO FOR A WALK.
>> BUT YOU MADE TIME TO DO THAT,
THAT IS ALL I AM SAYING.
>> OKAY, NOT GOING TO ARGUE.
>> JAMAL WHAT IS YOUR CRITERIA?
>> MY NUMBER ONE
CRITERIA-- CRITERIA IS
CONNECTION TO THE OTHER SIDE.
IS IT A POSITIVE THAT ONE OF
THESE PLAYERS HAS STRONG
CONNECTIONS TO THE OTHER SIDE.
OR IS IT MORE OF ARCH-- AN
ADVANTAGE THAT THEY DON'T HAVE
CONNECTIONS TO THE OTHER SIDE SO
THEY WILL STAY WHERE US COME
MERGE TIME.
>> DEAN, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
JAMAL'S ANSWER?
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HAS
RELATIONSHIPS THAT ARE MORE OR
LESS LOYAL.
>> PERSONALLY, JEFF, I VERY MUCH
THOUGHT IT WAS A UNANIMOUS
KARISHMA VOTE LAST TRIBAL
COUNCIL, SOMEONE, I DON'T KNOW
WHO, BROUGHT KARISHMA IN,
FLIPPED THE ENTIRE TRIBE AND NOW
SOMEONE AND KARISHMA ARE VERY,
VERY LOYAL TOGETHER.
I'M OUTSIDE.
>> THERE YOU GO, DEAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO THAT IS, BUT
KARISHMA DOES OWE SOMEONE BIG
TIME.
>> AND I WILL SAY I DONE EVEN
KNOW WHO I OWE.
I GOT A WHISPER A MINUTE BEFORE
TRIBAL AND I THOUGHT MAYBE THIS
IS MY.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE, THAT IS NOT
TRUE AT ALL.
>> THERE IS MY SAVING GRACE.
>> SHE KNOWS WHO IT IS.
>> TOM, I SWEAR TO GOD, I
ABSOLUTELY DO NOT KNOW WHO WAS
IN CHARGE OF THAT, I GOT THAT
WHISPER RIGHT BEFORE TRIBAL.
YOU KNOW I DON'T KNOW WHO WAS IN
CHARGE OF THAT.
AND I DIDN'T CARE WHO IT WAS.
>> KELLEEE INTERESTING, JUST
BEFORE THE VOTE AND THE TENSION
STARTS TO PERMEATE, AND SOMEONE
STARTS TO SAY A LITTLE MORE.
SO HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN SOMEONE
IS ON THE BOTTOM WHAT THEIR REAL
TRUTH IS?
>> THERE CAN BE MANY TRUTHS THAT
EXIST SIMULTANEOUSLY.
EVERYONE HAS A DIFFERENT
PERCEPTION.
EVERYONE HAS A DIFFERENT TRUTH.
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW AND AT THE
END OF THE DAY SURVIVOR IS ABOUT
TAKING LITTLE LEAPS OF FAITH AND
HOPING THE PEOPLE YOU PUT TRUST
IN ARE ACTUALLY TRUST WORTHY.
>> THAT IS MY GIRL.
>> ALL RIGHT T IS TIME TO VOTE,
TOM, YOU ARE UP.
>> I WILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, TOM.
KARISHMA.
TOM.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES KARISHMA.
TWO VOTES TOM.
TOM, THAT'S THREE VOTES TOM, TWO
VOTES KARISHMA.
TOM, THAT IS FOUR VOTES TOM.
FIFTH PERSON VOTED OUT, TOM,
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> GOOD LUCK, EVERYBODY,
SERIOUSLY, GOOD JOB.
>> TAKE CARE, TOM.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> LOVER YOU.
>> LOVE TO MEET YOU.
>> TOM, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> TIME TO GO.
>> THANK YOU, SEE YOU GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE TOM.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING TO WIN ANY
CHALLENGES NOW.
>> WELL, SOMETIMES THIS GAME
COMES DOWN TO SURVIVING JUST THE
MOMENTS, LIKE TONIGHT'S TRIBAL.
AND IF THEY CAN,
TOM'S-- TOMORROW'S A NEW DAY.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, GOOD
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> IF YOU STEP INTO THE RING.
>> I WANT ONE OF THOSE TWO GONE.
>> HAVE I TO KILL THEM BEFORE
THEY KILL ME.
>> AND PUT ON THE GLOVES.
>> THEY ARE WILLING TO GO TO
ROCK.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY IS
GOING TO FLIP.
>> THEN YOU BETTER BE READY TO
FIGHT.
>> IF YOU WANT ONE OF MY GIRLS
OUT, IT IS TIME TO CUT ONE OF
THEIRS, THEY ARE SCRAMMABLING,
FIGHTING FOR THEMSELVES.
>> WORTH BE OF US GOING HOME,
KARISHMA WAS HOLDING PEOPLE BACK
IN CHALLENGES BUT THERE ARE ALL
KINDS OF STRATEGIES TO THE GAME
AND THEY HAVE A STRATEGY FOR WHY
THEY KEPT HER AM I LOVE BEING
OUT HERE PLAYING SURVIVOR, I
TOTALLY FRIED MYSELF.
I'M TAKING CREDIT TO BE THE FIRS
CANADIAN TO PLAY AND IF I HAVE
TO TAKE THAT I GUESS HAVE I TO
BE TAKE CREDIT FOR BEING VOTED
OUT AS WELL.