NO ONE CAN KNOW.
I LITERALLY SCOOP UP HER BAG.
THIS IS GOING TO CHANGE PIE
GAME.
THAT WAS BE TENSE.
TONIGHT'S DOUBLE TRIBAL SHOWS
YOU CANNOT BE TOO COMFORTABLE IN
THIS GAME.
AARON HAS PROVEN TO BE ONE OF
THE BIGGEST THREAT SO IT WAS
IMPORTANT TO ELIMINATE THE
THREAT.
BUT MI SUPERNERVOUS BECAUSE I
DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON AT
THE OTHER TRIBAL AND MISSY IS
PLAYING SO HARD.
AND MY BIGGEST FEAR IS THAT THE
GIRLS ARE GOING TO ALIGN AGAINST
TOMMY BECAUSE TOMMY IS MY NUMBER
ONE IN THE GAME.
OH MY GOSH.
TOMMY.
AND THEN I SEE TOMMY,'S BIG
LANKY BODY CLIMBING UPSTAIRS AND
A RUSH OF CALM JUST CAME OVER
ME.
I'M LIKE OKAY.
AND NOW IT'S MORE OF A QUESTION
WHERE WE GO FROM HERE.
MISSY?
SHUT UP.
MISSY WAS SO GOOD THAT WHEN
SHE HAD HER CONVERSATION WITH
KARISHMA, SHE SETS HER DOWN ON
THE BEACH.
THE FIRST SHING SHE DONE WAS
START TELLING KARISHMA TO TELL
ME WHAT TO DO TO VOTE TOMMY OUT.
TONIGHT WAS INCREDIBLE.
I JUST WANT TO DO A HAPPY DANCE
WAWS MY TOP TWO TARGETS WENT
ONLY, AARON AND MISSY.
BOTH OF THEM WERE GUNNING FOR
ME.
BOTH GONE IN ONE SWOOP.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO USE MY IDOL.
I STILL HAVE IT HERE IN MY TUSY
LITTLE ARM PILT.
SO I COULD NOT BE HAPPIER.
THE GAME HAS JUST OPENED
COMPLETELY WIDE FOR ME.
AND NOW I FINALLY HAVE SOME
OPTIONS.
TODAY SUCKED FOR ME, YOU
KNOW.
IT SUCKED HARD.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, IT NEEDED
THAT.
SO IT HAPPENED.
I FEEL A LITTLE STRANDED
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE MY CLOSEST
ALLIES ARE GONE.
THEY OFFERED ME A LOT OF
PROTECTION.
AND NOW I DON'T HAVE THAT FROM
EITHER OF THEM ANY MORE.
YOU CAN BUILD RELATIONSHIPS
THAT YOU COULDN'T BUILD.
RIGHT.
BUT NOW WITH THEM BEING GONE,
I AM ON MY OWN.
AND I AM GOING TO DO WHAT I HAVE
TO DO TO STAY HERE.
LAST NIGHT I WENT FROM THE
MOST NERVOUS I'VE BEEN IN MY
LIFE TO PROBABLY THE HAPPIEST,
NOT ONLY WAS A SAFE BUT BLIND
SIDING MISSY WITH A HUGE MOVE ON
MY RESUME.
YOU REALLY SHOOK ME LAST
NIGHT, I GUESS.
YEAH, IT WAS FRIGGING.
LAST NIGHT WAS HUGE, SICK.
CRAZY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT, YOU STILL
WARRANT.
I AGREE I JUST THINK IN TERMS
OF ME, I KNOW WHO I CAN'T BEAT.
WHO.
>>.
CAR SHALL MA IS AN EASY VOTE,
THEN SITTING THERE IN FINAL
THREE AND WE ARE ALL LOOKING AT
EACH OTHER.
KARISHMA IS THE ULTIMATE
GOAT, HAVE I BEEN WANTING HER
OUT FOR A LONG LONG TIME.
AND WITHOUT MISSY AND AARON AS
THE TWO BIGGEST THREATS IN FRONT
OF ME, IT IS ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE MYSELF, TOMMY AND
ELIZABETH ARE TARGETED.
THE ARMY HAS ASSEMBLED.
IT IS ME, YOU AND HER GOING
NEXT.
WE'RE NOT LETTING YOU GO.
IT SIN CREDIBLE.
RIGHT NOW IT IS LIKE
ATTENTION, GOAT NUMBER ONE,
KARISHMA REPORTING FOR DUTY,
ATTENTION, GOAT NUMBER TWO,
NOURA REPORTING FOR DUTY.
AND THEN THEY ALL LINE UP, A
ESSENTIALING THE GO ARMEY TO
KNOCK OUT ONE OF THESE BIG
THREATS, ELIZABETH, TOMMY.
IT IS NOT HAPPENED.
IT IS SOMETHING I DEFINITELY
SUBSCRIBE TO BUT ELIZABETH IS AN
OLYMPIC ATHLETE, ALSO ELIZABETH
WROTE MY NAME DOWN SO ELIZABETH
IS GOING TO BE ON MY RADAR AND
SHE MIGHT HAVE TO GO NEXT.
LET'S GO.
COMING.
READ THE NOTE, TOMMY.
HERE WE GO.
WHOA.
CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO COME TO
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS TRK MUST
BE UNANIMOUS.
IF YOU CANNOT AGREE, DRAW ONE
NAME FROM THE BAG.
THAT PERSON MUST GET ON THE BOAT
IMMEDIATELY.
I WANT TO GO.
I VOTE LAUREN.
MY INITIAL THOUGHT IS I AM
HOPING IT IS ME.
I HAVEN'T BEEN THERE YET.
I COULD CERTAINLY USE AN
ADVANTAGE.
BUT BEFORE I CAN EVEN TAKE A
BREATHE TO SAY A WORD LAUREN
CHIMES IN AND IS LIKE I WANT TO
GO.
CAN I GO?
THE PEOPLE WHO THINK THEY RUN
THIS TRIED HAVE SPOKEN UP AND
HAVE DECIDED WHO IS GOING.
WHOOO.
BUT IF I WERE TO SAY I DON'T
AGREE, THAT WOULD JUST PUT A
BIGGER TARGET ON MY BACK SO I
HAVE TO TAKE A STEP BACK AND
KEEP MY MOUTH CLOSED.
NO, GO.
THIS IS YOUR FRIEND, THE
CHICKEN.
NO, CHICKEN.
THIS IS FOR ME.
GO, GO CHICKEN.
SHE IS STUBBORN, SHE REMINDS
ME OF BOSTON ROB.
RIGHT?
OH MY GOSH, SHE'S SO CLOSE TO
ME I CAN FEEL HER FEATHERS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
SHE BIT MY FINGER.
THIS BITCH BIT MY FINGER.
NOW SHE IS EATING THAT
PAPAYA.
ALL THAT LOYALTY ALL THESE
DAYS.
IT AIN'T FUNNY.
YEAH, IT IS.
SHE BIT MY FINGER.
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS IS
DEFINITELY A PART OF THE GAME
THAT I AM MISSING.
AND I'M SO EXCITED THAT I AM
ABOUT TO EXPERIENCE IT.
OH MY GOD.
THIS IS CRAZY.
OH MY GOD!
OH MY GOD, OH MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, GIRL?
ARE YOU WAY TOO EXCITE.
GRAB YOUR BAG AND THEN WE'RE
GOING TO GO INTO AND EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING.
OHMIGOD.
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON IN.
YOU GUYS ARE THE REASON
PEOPLE PLAY THIS GAME.
WE WANT TO KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH YOU BACK AT CAMP AND HOW
ARE YOU DOING SO FAR IN THE
GAME?
I'M DOING OKAY IN THE GAME.
I DEFINITELY AM THE LEAD IN
ATHLETICS BUT I'M A VERY STRONG
SOCIAL PLAYER.
I DIDN'T REALIZE I WAS GOING TO
HAVE AS MUCH STRATEGY AS I DID.
LET ME EXPLAIN HOW IT WORKS
WHEN PEOPLE COME TO THE ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS.
EVERYONE THAT COMES HERE GETS A
LESSON.
TODAY YOUR LESSON IS ABOUT
SITUATIONAL AWARENESS.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A CHANCE TO
PREDICT WHO WINS THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
IF YOU ARE RIGHT, YOU EARN AN
IMMUNITY IDOL GOOD FOR THE NEXT
TWO TRIBAL COUNCILS.
IF YOU ARE WRONG, YOU LOSE YOUR
VOTE.
HOW WELL DO YOU KNOW YOUR TRIBE
MATES.
AFTER PLAYING THIS GAME WITH
THEM, DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
ACCURATELY PREDICT WHO'S GOING
TO WIN IMMUNITY?
IF ANYONE KNOWS THE TRIBE
IT'S ME.
I AM SUCH A PEOPLE PERSON.
AND THAT'S HOW I FIGURED OUT WHO
TO ALIGN MYSELF WITH.
BUT ALSO THE ODDS AREN'T THAT
GREAT TO CHOOSE ONE OUT OF NINE.
IF I DON'T PULL IT OFF, THEN I
LOSE MY VOTE AT THE NEXT TRIBAL.
IN WORST-CASE SCENARIO, I COULD
GET VOTED OUT.
FOR YOUR NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE YOU WILL ALL BE ON
SEPARATE STATIONS.
IT WAS ON BOTH SIDES.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT YOUR ARMS.
THERE WILL BE A BAR AND WILL
YOU HAVE TO APPLY UPWARD
PRESSURE TO KEEP A BALL FROM
ROLLING.
IT'S NOT SO MUCH STRENGTH AND
ENDURANCE AS IT IS
CONCENTRATION.
OKAY.
YOU HAVE TO BE FOCUSED.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ALSO GOING TO
HAVE AN EAT OR PLAY COMPONENT.
IF YOU SIT OUT THERE WILL BE
FOOD WITHIN PANCAKES, BACON,
HASH BROWNS AND ORANGE JUICE.
BREAKFAST?
BREAKFAST.
SO THERE ARE CERTAINLY GOING
TO BE SOME PEOPLE THAT NO MATTER
WHAT, IF THEIR BACKS ARE AGAINST
THE WALL THEY MIGHT SAY I'M
GOING TO COMPETE.
BUT LET'S TALK ABOUT WHICH ONE
YOU YOU THINK MIGHT NOT BE IN IT
TO WIN IT.
DEN HAS NO ENDURANCE SO-AND
HE'S TOLD ME THAT.
DEAN DROPPED HIS THIRD BALL,
HE'S OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
THIS IS UNCOMFORTABLE.
DEAN DROPPED.
SO I DON'T THINK THAT HE
COULD CHALLENGE.
AND DAN, I THINK DAN'S HUNGRY.
AND I ALSO THINK HE FEELS REALLY
SAFE AND COMFORTABLE, AND JANET
AS MUCH AS I WOULD LOVE FOR HER
TO FIGHT FOR THIS.
JANET DROPPED.
I DONE THINK THIS IS HER
CHALLENGE.
KARISHMA, HER ABILITY TO FOCUS,
I DON'T SEE IT.
KARISHMA, THE FIRST TO DROP.
SO WHICH ONES DO YOU THINK
MIGHT WIN?
SO I DEFINITELY THINK NOURA
COULD WIN THIS CHALLENGE.
BECAUSE SHE IS LIKE A YOGI
THROUGH AND THROUGH.
AND HER ABILITY TO FOCUS SOWT OF
THIS WORLD.
NOURA WINS IMMUNITY FOR
PURPLE.
WOO.
AND IF THAT IS WHAT THIS
CHALLENGE IS ABOUT, THEN SHE HAS
A REALLY GOOD SHOT.
AND SHE'S VEGAN, SO SHE IS NOT
INTO THAT.
AND I ALSO THINK ELIZABETH WILL
WIN.
SHE'S AN A LIMB MEAN, SHE'S AN
AMAZING PERFORMER AT EVERYTHING
CHALLENGE.
THAT'S THE WAY TO WORK,
ELIZABETH.
ELIZABETH IS FIRST FOR VOKA.
AND HER ALLIES WERE VOTED OUT
AT THE LAST TWO TRIEBL.
HER NECK IS ON THE LINE.
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU WOULD
RISK YOUR VOTE ON?
OH MY GOD.
I WILL TELL YOU WHAT, WHAT IF
I LET YOU CHOOSE TWO PEOPLE.
SO NOW YOU GOT TWO HORSES IN THE
RACE, BUT IF ONE OF YOUR TWO
DOESN'T COME IN, YOU LOSE YOUR
VOTE.
ONE OF THE TWO, IT IS AN
IMMUNITY FOR UP TO TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS.
NOW YOU HAVE GOT-HE JUST GAVE
YOU BETTER ODDS.
I DOUBLED YOUR ODDS.
IF YOU PICK TWO, DO YOU THINK
YOU COULD FIGURE IT OUT.
I DO.
AND TEMPT THE OTHER ONES TO
SIT OUT.
YES.
SO YOU HAVE TO TELL US WHAT
YOUR DECISION IS.
I AM GOING TO GO WITH MY
GUTTED AND SAY-MY GUT AND SAY
NOURA AND ELIZABETH.
THAT IS WHAT YOU SAID THE
WHOLE TIME, IF YOU GAVE ME
ANOTHER NAME, I WOULD BE
CONCERNED.
SO LET'S GO NOURA.
LET'S GO ELIZABETH.
LAUREN SEEMS TO HAVE A GOOD
GRASS PARAGRAPH ON ALL OF HER
TRIBE MATES, THAT IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING, GET A HORSE AND
GO WITH IT.
AND THE FACT THAT THERE IS AN
EAT OR PLAY IN THIS CHALLENGE
ONLY HELPS LAUREN.
IF YOU GET IT RIGHT THE IDOL
IS GOING TO BE UNDER THE BIG
ROCK AT TREE.
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST.
GOOD LUCK.
BYE.
THE MORE PEOPLE SHE CAN GET
TO SIT OUT, THE BETTER HERODS
GET, AS LONG AS HER HORSES
AREN'T THE ONES GRAIZING.
AS FAR AS YOU KNOW THE-IS
REAL OR FAKE.
IT'S REAL.
I'M JUST GOING TO PLAY.
JAMAL GAVE ME THIS THING,
WHEN HE RETURNED FROM ISLAND OF
IDOLS HE PRESENTED A LEGACY
ADVANTAGE TO MYSELF.
THIS ADVANTAGE IS GOING TO GO
TO THE-I-THIS FAKE LEGACY
ADVANTAGE, BUT THIS NOTE HAS NO
POWER.
GET IT OUT OF THE WHICH.
THAT IS WHAT I WANT TO DO,
I'M TIRED OF IT.
IS IT FAKE, IS IT REAL, I
DON'T KNOW.
THE TRIBE DOESN'T KNOW BUT I
THINK IT'S REAL.
IT SAYS THIS SERVES AS AN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT CAN ONLY BE PLAYED WITH NINE
PEOPLE LEFT OR SIX PEOPLE LEFT.
WE'RE AT NINE RIGHT NOW.
SO WHILE EVERYONE WAS SNOOZING,
I WENT AHEAD AND GOT MY LITTLE
PICASSO ON AND MADE MYSELF A
LITTLE FAKE LEGACY.
THE IDEA HERE IS THIS, KEEP THIS
POTENTIALLY REAL ONE WITH ME,
USE MY FAKE ONE IN THE NEXT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
DOES IT LOOK EXACTLY, EXACTLY
ALIKE?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
SO IT IS A BIT RISKY.
BUT IF I CAN GET BY WITH THAT,
THIS ONE WILL STILL BE LEFT IN
MY POCKET AND I WILL BE
POTENTIALLY SAFE AT SIX IF IT IS
REAL.
I'M EXCITED TO PLAY A LITTLE BIT
AND BE A LITTLE SCHEMEY.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN UNDER THE
RADAR.
BUT THIS IS MY CHANCE TO KIND
OF, YOU KNOW, SHAKE THINGS UP A
BIT AND GET A LITTLE-GET A
LITTLE SHIFTY WITH IT.
HELLO!
WELCOME, MADAME.
HAVE I NEVER SEEN A SMILE SO
BIG.
WHEN I COME BACK FROM ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS I DO BELIEVE THAT
THERE IS WORK TO BE DONE.
I NEED TO CONVINCE MAY TRIBE
TO BASICALLY EAT AT THE NEXT
CHALLENGE.
AND I NEED TO CONVINCE THE
TWO PEOPLE THAT I BET ON,
ELIZABETH AND NOURA THAT THEY
NEED TO COMPETE, WHICH ARE TWO
OF MY HORSES IN THE RACE.
SO BASICALLY I KNOW THAT
TOMORROW IS AN IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
I KNOW WHAT THE CHALLENGE IS.
IT'S THE ONE WHERE YOU HAVE TO
HOLD THE BAR UP AND THERE IS A
BALL ABOVE YOU.
AND IF YOU RELEASE PRESSURE, THE
BALL FALLS.
AND THE TWIST, I GOT TO DECIDE
IF WE MADE IT AN EAT OR PLAY
GAME BECAUSE I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
ARE HUNGRY.
SO GUESS WHAT IT IS.
PANCAKES, ORANGE JUICE, BACON
AND HASH BROWNS.
THE LESSON THAT I LEARNED FROM
ROB AND SANTA IS SITUATIONAL
AWARENESS.
IT IS JUST PERFECT FOR ME.
I STUDY PEOPLE, I OBSERVE
PEOPLE.
AND I FEEL CONFIDENT IN WHO IS
GOING TO SIT OUT AND EAT
BREAKFAST AND WHO IS GOING TO
COMPETE.
IF YOU DROP YOU ARE OUT, YOU
DON'T GET TO EAT.
THE ONLY PERSON I PLAN ON BEING
EXACTLY HONEST WITH IS TOMMY,
TOMMY IS MY WINGMAN IN THIS
GAME.
BASICALLY, THE-THEY HAVE TO
WIN, IF THEY WIN I GET IMMUNE.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BET.
BECAUSE THEY BET ON US, WE
NEED TO DECIDE WHAT TO DO.
I SAY WE DE TELL NOBODY.
IN THIS GAME YOU WANT THE
IDOL.
RIGHT NOW I'M LAUREN'S WINGMAN,
I WILL DO WHATEVER I CAN TO MAKE
SURE LAUREN GETS THAT IDOL.
OKAY.
NO ONE CAN KNOW ABOUT THAT
IDOL.
SO I WANT TO GET AS MANY PEOPLE
I CAN TO NOT PLAY, SO WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO TALK ABOUT ALL DAY
LONG RIGHT NOW, PANCAKES, SYRUP,
BACON, COFFEE.
THE MORE I TALK ABOUT T THE MORE
LAUREN TALKS ABOUT IT, THE LESS
PEOPLE COMPETE AGAINST OR
ELIZABETH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT.
IF YOU COULD PICK, WITHOUT
FEELING THE PRESSURE.
OH, I WOULD EAT.
YOU SHOULD EAT.
I ALWAYS FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO
PLAY.
BUT IT IS GOING TO BE HARD TO
SMELL THOSE PANCAKES AND BACON.
I'M THINKING BACON, PAN KICKS
AND SYRUP.
I'M EXCITED.
ARE YOU GOING TO PLAY?
MIMOSA IS MY FAVORITE DRINK
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
IF I COULD GO TO A BAR AND ORDER
A DRINK I WOULD ORDER AN MIMOSA,
THAT IS HOW I LOVE IT.
THE KEY IS NOT TO FILL UP ON
PANCAKES.
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE THE
CHANCE TO GET VOTED OUT FOR
FRICKING BACON.
ST ALL CARBS, IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHAT YOU EAT I WILL KEEP
GOING.
BACON IS NOT A CARB.
IT IS AS IMPORTANT THAT AS
MANY PEOPLE SIT OUT AND EAT BUT
I NEED TO BE SURE ELIZABETH AND
NOURA COMPETE.
BUT KNOWING NOURA AS A VEGAN,
SHE IS NOT GOING TO WANT TO SIT
DOWN AND EAT BREAKFAST.
I THINK I'M GOING TO EAT.
HOW ABOUT YOU.
I AM WILLING TO TAKE ONE FOR
THE TEAM AND PLAY.
YOU WILL LAST A LONG TIME.
AND OF COURSE ELIZABETH HER
TWO GREATEST ALLIES WERE VOTED
OUT AND I KNOW SHE WILL FIGHT
TWO AND FAIL TO WIN.
NOURA IS GOING TO BE IN THE
ZONE.
PEOPLE DO SEEM TO BE BUYING
IT.
BUT JUST GOT TO SEE.
IN IS A HUGE DEAL.
THIS IS GOING TO CHANGE MY GAME
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
AND I AM A READY.
I'M READY FOR MY GAME TO BE
ACCELERATED.
BRING ON THE BACON AND BRING
ON THE IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
LET'S DO THIS.
COME ON, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THINGS FIRST,
TAKE BACK THE IMMUNITY
NECKLACES.
COME ON, ELAINE.
REALLY?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE IT,
JEFF.
IT WON'T BE THE FIRST TIME.
THANK YOU.
THIS MAKES ME SAD.
WIN IT AGAIN.
TRUE STORY.
SORRY.
KNOCK ME OUT, I CAN'T WIN
NOTHING.
ONCE AGAIN, INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY
IS BACK UP FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE YOU ARE
GOING TO PULL UP ON A HANDLE,
PLANTING A BALL BETWEEN A SET OF
JAWS.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU LOWER THE
HANDLE, THAT BALL WILL DROP,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CHALLENGE.
LAST PERSON LEFT STANDING WINS
IMMUNITY, GUARANTEED A ONE IN
EIGHT SHOT OF GETTING TO THE
END.
LOSERS, TRIBAL COUNCIL, SOMEBODY
WILL BE VOTED OUT.
AND IF ON DAY 30 HERE IN FIJI IN
OUR 39th SEASON YOU FEEL
COMFORTABLE ENOUGH, YOU CAN
CHOOSE TO SIT OUT, GIVE UP YOUR
SHOT AT IMMUNITY AND INSTEAD
FEAST.
WAIT A MINUTE, I DIDN'T HEAR A
SINGLE REACTION TO PANCAKES,
HASH BROWNS, BACON, I GOT TO
CHECK IN, WAIT A MINUTE, DID WE
GUESS WRONG S THIS NOT
APPEALING.
THEY MAY HAVE HAD A LITTLE
TIP AS TO WHAT WE WERE GOING TO
BE EATING TODAY.
OH REALLY.
YEAH.
TELL ME.
I GOT SOME INFORMATION AND AT
ISLAND OF THE EYE DLOLS AND LET
THEM KNOW THAT WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE BREAKFAST.
YOU STOLE MY THUNDER.
OKAY.
JUST A LITTLE BIT, JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
NOW IT MAKES SENSE.
YEAH.
THIS IS WORTH PLAYING FOR,
RIGHT?
YES, YEAH.
SO BIG DECISION, YOU EITHER
COMPETE OR YOU EAT.
LET'S MAKE IT.
ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE A RED ROCK
AND A YELLOW ROCK.
ONE OF EACH.
IF NOURA OR ELIZABETH WIN THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE, I WIN AN
IMMUNITY IDOL THAT IS VALID
THROUGH THE NEXT TWO TRIBAL
COUNCILS.
SO AS LONG AS THE TWO WERE TO
STAY IN THE RACE, I'M GOLDEN.
OKAY, RED MEANS YOU WANT TO
COMPETE, YELLOW MEANS YOU WANT
TO EAT.
EVERYBODY REVEAL.
TOMMY GOING TO EAT, DAN'S GOING
TO EAT, DEAN'S GOING TO EAT,
LAUREN'S GOING TO EAT, JANET'S
GOING TO EAT, ELAINE IS GOING TO
EAT, WOW, SIX PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO EAT, ONLY THREE PEOPLE,
KARISHMA, NOURA AND ELIZABETH
WILL COMPETE.
OH MY GOD, DID WE ACTUALLY
JUST PULL THIS OFF?
ALL RIGHT, TAKE YOUR SPOTS,
WE'LL GET STARTED.
EVERYBODY'S MADE THEIR DECISION,
CHOOSING TO COMPETE.
KARISHMA, NOURA AN ELIZABETH,
ONLY THREE OF NINE ARE FIGHTING
FOR IMMUNITY.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
WHEN THE CHALLENGE STARTS YOU
CAN EAT.
WHEN THE CHALLENGE IS OVER, YOU
HAVE TO STOP EATING WHICH MEANS
SHOVE AM THOSE LAST FEW BITES.
ENJOY IT GUYS.
GOOD LUCK GIRLS.
DO IT.
GOT IT.
WE OWE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, PUT YOUR HANDS
UNDERNEATH THAT HANDLE, AND WHEN
I TELL YOU TOO YOU WILL LIFT UP
AND RELEASE YOUR BALL AND THIS
CHALLENGE IS ON.
THREE, TWO, ONE, LIFT UP.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD, START EATING.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ON.
IMMUNITY ON THE LINE 30 DAYS
INTO OUR 39th SEASON.
YOU ARE PULLING UP ON THAT
HANDLE, TRYING TO KEEP PRESSURE
ON THAT JAW.
MAKE SURE THAT BALL DOESN'T
START HEADING OUT.
WE DID THIS CHALLENGE ON GHOST
ISLAND WITH NEARLY 45 MINUTES.
IT IS A DECEIVING CHALLENGE.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT YOUR ARMS.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP THAT
PRESSURE.
QUICKLY KARISHMA DROPS.
SHE IS OUT.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO.
YOU CAN JOIN THEM, YOU JUST
CAN'T EAT.
OKAY.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
YOU CAN HANDLE WHAT.
SMELLING THE FOOD AND NOT
HAVING ANY FOOD AND FEELING LIKE
-FAILURE.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
I'M STRONGER THAN THIS.
WHY ARE YOU FEELING-ARE YOU
ONE OF THE THREE PEOPLE TO STAND
UP FOR THE TEST.
I PROMISED MYSELF I WOULD
ALWAYS TRY NO MATTER WHAT,
BECAUSE MY MIND IS STRONGER THAN
ANYTHING AM BUT WHY IS MY BODY
NOT COOPERATING?
COULD BE 30 DAYS PLAYING
SURVIVOR.
IT WILL DO IT TO THE STRONGEST.
EVERYBODY IS OUT HERE FOR THEIR
OWN JOURNEY, KARISHMA GOING
THROUGH HERS RIGHT NOW.
SIX OTHER PEOPLE, NOT A CARE IN
THE WORLD.
HANG IN THERE, GIRL.
YOU GUYS GOT IT.
ANOTHER HOUR.
WE'RE DOWN TO TWO NOW, NOURA
AND ELIZABETH, SIDE-BY-SIDE.
ONE WILL WIN IMMUNITY, BE GLAD
THEY GAVE UP THE FOOD.
THE OTHER MAY QUESTION IT.
EITHER WAY, SOMEBODY GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
TWO VERY DIFFERENT STORIES.
TWO PEOPLE COMPETING, SIX PEOPLE
EATING, AND THEY HAVE PUT THEIR
GAME ON THE LINE FOR A BREAKFAST
BOTH WOMEN BATTLING FOR
IMMUNITY.
YOU CAN FEEL THE TENSION ON THAT
BAND.
DON'T LOSE YOUR FOCUS.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, ELIZABETH
DROPS.
OH MY GOD.
NOURA WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY AGAIN.
AND NOURA, THE CHALLENGE IS
OVER.
NOURA, YOU WON.
YOU WON, NOURA.
I'M PLAYING FOR ALL Y'ALL.
YES, NOURA, GOOD JOB.
I KNOW, UNFORTUNATELY IT
DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY.
THE CHALLENGE IS OVER.
SHOVE YOUR LAST BITES IN.
NOURA, YOU CAN DROP, IT'S OVER,
YOU'VE WON.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
NOURA, ONCE AGAIN, SAFE
TONIGHT AT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
CANNOT BE VOTED OUT OF THIS
GAME.
FEELS SO GOOD AND SHOULD, AFTER
30 DAYS, SOMEBODY GOING HOME
TONIGHT, GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD
BACK TO CAMP, SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
THAI SO MUCH.
I DECIDED TO EAT AND THAT WAS
PROBABLY ONE OF THE SCARIEST
THINGS I DECIDED TO DO.
I HAVE TO TRUST MY ALLIANCE THAT
THEY ARE NOT GOING TO THROW ME
TO THE WOLVES.
BUT ELIZABETH DROPPING REALLY
SURPRISED ME.
SO NOW I THINK THE SMART
DECISION WOULD BE TO GET RID OF
ELIZABETH BECAUSE SHE'S A
PHYSICAL THREAT.
I
THAT'S CRAZY.
HOLY-THIS IMMUNITY IDOL IS
ONLY GOOD FOR THE NEXT TWO.
SO HERE IS THE THING.
RIGHT NOW IT IS EITHER
KARISHMA, THE EASY VOTE, OR
ELIZABETH, THE OLYMPIC ATHLETE
THAT CAN WIN EVERYTHING.
I THINK IT SHOULD BE
ELIZABETH.
OKAY.
WE CAN SPLIT VOTES SO WE
DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ANY
ADVANTAGE ON KARISHMA AND
ELIZABETH.
OKAY.
AT THE CHALLENGE KARISHMA
LASTED 45 SECONDS, YOU CAN GET
HER OUT WHENEVER YOU WANT.
BUT ELIZABETH CAN GO ON AN
IMMUNITY RUN AT ANY TIME.
I THINK WE HAVE TO DO
ELIZABETH.
WHY WOULD I VOTE OUT SOMEONE
THAT I CAN EASILY BEAT AT THE
END, WHERE YOU CAN TAKE A SHOT
AT ELIZABETH WHILE YOU CAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU ARE DOING,
RIGHT?
ARE YOU OKAY WITH IT?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
IF I HAD MY WAY I WANT
KARISHMA TO GO HOME.
SHE IS HE'S THE KARISHMA WITH
NINE LIVES, SHE'S ALMOST BEEN
VOTED OUT ABOUT FIVE OR SIX
TIMES.
BUT IF MY ALLIANCE DECIDES
ELIZABETH IS NEXT, I CAN'T SHOOT
MYSELF IN THE FOOT JUST TO SAVE
HER BECAUSE IT IS TOO LATE FOR
THAT I DON'T WANT TO DAMAGE MY
OWN GAME TO KEEP HER IN.
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN, MIKE
LIKE, A WEIRD SPOT WHERE.
SORT OF FLOATING RIGHT NOW.
HOPING THAT I JUST DON'T GO
HOME TONIGHT.
I WAS JUST UPSET AT THE
CHALLENGE.
WE SHOULD HAVE SHOWED DOWN FOR
LIKE 30 MINUTES.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
SO AT TODAY'S CHALLENGE, I
BLEW IT, MY NAME HAS BEEN ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK THE LAST THREE
DAYS AN ST A VERY EASY
OPPORTUNITY FOR ALL OF THESE
PEOPLE TO TAKE A BIG THREAT LIKE
MYSELF OUT OF THIS GAME.
I JUST HOPE I WAKE UP HERE
TOMORROW MORNING.
YOU ARE, I'M TELLING YOU.
I KNOW, BUT-KARISHMA
PLAYED-AND SHE WAS TOLD TO
VOTE FOR ME AND I'M THE ONE VOTE
THAT GOES HOME.
I DON'T HAVE AN IDOL.
I DON'T HAVE AN IMMUNITY
NECKLACE.
I'M JUST PRAYING TO THE SURVIVOR
GODS THAT KARISHMA DOES NOT HAVE
AN IDOL TONIGHT.
YOU OKAY, KARISHMA?
IT'S NOT NECESSARILY
PHYSICAL.
IT'S EMOTIONAL THAT IS MAKING ME
DIZZY.
JUST DOWN IT BECAUSE YOU WILL
FEEL BETTER.
WE GET BACK TO THE CAMP AND
KARISHMA IS JUST LIKE-ON THE
HAMMOCK AND I'M TELLING HER TO
DRINK HER WATER BECAUSE I KNOW
SHE IS NOT IN GREAT SHAPE.
LITERALLY I SCOOP UP HER BAG TO
TAKE IT TO THE BEACH AND SAY
ELIZABETH, COME WITH ME.
WE GO THROUGH IT TO SEE IF
WILL IS ANYTHING THERE THERE.
A CRUMPLED UPNOTE, TWO THINGS
THAT HAVE SHELLS ON THEM.
WE DON'T NEED TO WORRY ABOUT
THEM.
ELIZABETH IS LIKE THOSE ARE
BOTH NOTHING.
I HAVE SEEN FOR MY OWN EYES SHE
DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING.
FOR ME THE REACTION OF ELIZABETH
AND KARISHMA IS ENOUGH FOR ME TO
KNOW WITH MY OWN GUT FEELING
THAT THEY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
I THINK IT'S POSSIBLE THAT
ELIZABETH HAS AN IDOL.
LET ME TELL YOU WHY.
WE'RE SPLITTING IT.
BETWEEN TWO.
YOU SHOULD THROW YOUR VOTE
AND TAKE OUT JANET.
OKAY.
>>.
ELIZABETH SON THE OUTS BUT IF
SOMETHING CRAZY HAPPENS TONIGHT
THEN WE'RE SPLITTING THE VOTE.
IT IS REALLY ELIZABETH BUT WITH
KARISHMA, BUT KARISHMA IS
SUPPOSED TO THINK IT IS A SPLIT
BETWEEN JANUARY ELEVATOR AND
ELIZABETH.
SHE'S LIKE OH, OKAY.
AND SHE GETS UP, IMMEDIATELY
WALKS OVER TO ELIZABETH, BUT
THEN LAUREN COMES TO SIT WITH ME
AND SHE WATCHES KARISHMA TALK TO
ELIZABETH.
HE'S CALLING THE SHOTS.
UH-HUH.
HE WANTS YOU OUT SO BAD.
KARISHMA DOES NOT HAVE ALLIES
IN THIS GAME.
SO SHE IS A FREE AGENT AND THOSE
PEOPLE ALWAYS ARE DANGEROUS
BECAUSE THEY CAN GO EITHER WAY.
I'M VERY OBSERVANT.
I AM READING LIPS.
I'M PICKING UP VIBES.
I'M LOOKING AT EYE CONTACT.
SHE'S-SHE IS GOING HOME.
YEAH.
GO OVER THERE.
NO.
IT IS ME, YOU, JANET AND
ELAINE, IF WE COME TOGETHER AND
ALL VOTE DAN.
>>-I GO OVER THERE AND SAY I
HEARD MY NAME.
DO IT, DO IT, DO IT PLEASE.
LAUREN SEES HER LIPS SAY DAN
IS AFTER YOU.
SO IT IS JUST, IT IS MADDENING.
YOU SAID DAN.
JAN.
I DID HERE DAN, I THOUGHT I
HEARD DAN.
NO, I AM TALKING TO ELIZABETH
ABOUT IT.
I THOUGHT WE ALREADY TALKED
ABOUT THAT.
I KNOW, I WAS TALKING TO HER
ABOUT IT.
THAT'S COOL, ABSOLUTELY.
100 PERCENT.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO-I THOUGHT I
HEARD DAN.
NO, YOU CAN STAY.
I JUST WANTED TO JUST TALK TO
HER ABOUT HER THOUGHTS ABOUT
JANET, THAT IS ALL.
YEAH.
KARISHMA IS DOING EVERYTHING
WRONG YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO DO.
THAT WAS IT FOR ME.
I FEEL LIKE WE CAN'T ALLOW
KARISHMA TO GO ANY FURTHER.
BUT IT MIGHT BE TOO LATE TO
WORRY ABOUT SWITCHING UP AND
COMPLICATING A VOTE, ESPECIALLY
AT THIS POINT.
COULD YOU PLEASE GET RID OF
HER.
YEAH.
CAN WE COME BACK.
I AGREE WITH DAN ABOUT
KARISHMA, SO IN MY MIND IT MAKES
COMPLETE SENSE.
I WAS UNDER A LITTLE STRESS
SEEING THEY GO TO ARMY ASSEMBLE
BUT IF THERE ARE PEOPLE ON BOARD
TO DISASSEMBLE IT BEFORE IT GETS
ROLLING, IT IS MUSIC TO MY EARS
AND I'M HOPING KARISHMA IS THE
VOTE THAT IS GOING HOME TONIGHT.
NOW HE'S GOING TO FREAK OUT.
OH YEAH.
I WAS ABSOLUTELY TALKING
ABOUT DAN.
BUT DAN HAS NO RIGHT TO TELL ME
I AM NOT ALLOWED TO TALK TO
ELIZABETH OR I NEED BABYSITTING.
THAT PISS ME OFF.
HOWEVER, EVEN THOUGH I WOULD
HADE TO LEAVE ELIZABETH BECAUSE
HE COULD HAVE BEEN A NUMBER TO
MAKE A BIG MOVE FOR ME, AT THIS
POINT IN TIME, I FEEL LIKE ME
VOTING DIFFERENTLY IS NOT GOING
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
I HAVE THE IMMUNITY IDOL SITTING
IN MY POCKET AND NOBODY KNOWS
ABOUT IT.
NOW HERE IS THE ISSUE THAT I
HAVE.
PLAYING IT CORRECTLY, AND MAKING
IT COUNT.
I HAVE TO WEIGH THAT AGAINST
POSSIBLY BEING VOTED OUT WITH AN
IDOL IN MY POCKET.
NOURA, NOURA GOT IMMUNITY.
NOW BRINGING THE MEMBERS OF
OUR JURY.
ALL RIGHT, SO WITH TODAY'S
CHALLENGE, THE TWIST WAS IF YOU
FELT COMFORTABLE YOU COULD OPT
TO SIT OUT, NOT COMPETE AND
INSTEAD EAT.
SIX PEOPLE CHOTION TO EAT,
LEAVING US WITH NOURA, ELIZABETH
AND KARISHMA AS THE ONLY THREE
PEOPLE COMPETING.
ELIZABETH, WHAT WAS THE CENTRAL
REASON THAT YOU COMPETED.
WELL, JUST THE FACT THAT I
LOST MY MAIN ALLIANCE, THEY'RE
SITTING OVER THERE.
AND YOU KNOW, I WAS HOPING TO
HAVE A GOOD SHOWDOWN TODAY AND
EVERYBODY COULD EAT WHILE WE
WERE PLAYING BUT MY MAIN REASON
WAS TO WIN IMMUNITY.
HOW ABOUT YOU, KARISHMA.
MINE WAS A SECRETARY ET, I
KNEW I WAS AT THE BOTTOM, TWIEB
TRIBAL COUNSELLITY AFTER TRIBAL
I'M ALWAYS AT RISK OF GOING
HOME, BUT ALSO FOR ME I WANTED
TO CHALLENGE MYSELF.
I WANTED TO SEE WHAT I WAS MADE
OF AND TRY MY HARDEST AND I FELT
THIS WAS AS GOOD A TIME AS ANY.
NOURA, ARE YOU THE SEVEN THAT
OPTED TO HELP THE SIX EAT OR ARE
YOU WITH ELIZABETH AND KARISHMA
THE THREE ON THE OUT?
I BELIEVE-I FEEL STRONGLY,
ACTUALLY, SO I'M NOT GOING TO
SAY IT LIGHTLY.
I FEEL THAT I HAVE A VERY GOOD
FOOTING IN THE GAME.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT, I WAS
WILLING TO STEP UP TO MAKE SURE
THAT MY TRIBE COULD EAT.
SO I CHOSE TO PLAY.
DAN, SO WITH SIX PEOPLE
SITTING OUT DOES THAT IMPLY WHAT
IT WOULD APPEAR TO WHICH IS SIX
PEOPLE ARE NOT WORRIED TONIGHT.
AND I THINK THE CORE ALLIANCE
AS IT GETS STRONGER THAT LINE IN
THE SAND GETS DEEPER AND IT
BECOMES LIKE A TRENCH.
AND IF SOMEONE IS ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THAT LINE STRKS WAY TOO
MUCH ENERGY TO DRAG SOMEONE
THROUGH THE SAND OVER TO YOUR
SIDE.
BUT ALSO I JUST WANT TO POINT
OUT THAT THIS IS AN INDIVIDUAL
GAME.
AND SO YEAH, THERE MIGHT BE SIX
PEOPLE OR SEVEN PEOPLE OR
WHATEVER ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF A
TRENCH BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, IT MAY
JUST BE SWB ON YOUR SIDE OF THAT
TRENCH WHO SLIT YOUR THROAT
BEFORE YOU WOKE UP AND THOUGHT
TO SPLIT THEIRS.
TOMMY S THIS SORT OF LIKE IF
YOU ARE IN AN INDIE RACE AND YOU
HAVE TO DECIDE AT WHAT POINT DO
I JUST PUT MY FOOT ALL THE WAY
ON THE PETAL AND I'M JUST GOING
FOR BROKE NOW.
YEAH, EXACTLY.
THIS IS THE TIME.
SOME PEOPLE NEEDED THAT PIT STOP
AT 30 TO FUEL UP.
WHERE SOME OTHERS WERE SAYING I
DON'T NEED THAT FUEL.
I CAN EAT IN TEN DAYS AND
HOPEFULLY MY TIRES DON'T BURN
OUT ON THE WAY.
DEAN, THE PIT STOP, DID THAT
FACTOR IN FOR YOU.
I WAS IN A PECULIAR
SITUATION, AS YOU WILL SEE LATER
TONIGHT.
I HAVE A LITTLE LEGACY ADVANTAGE
THAT EVERYONE KNOWS ABOUT, THAT
WAS GIFTED TO ME FROM SOMEONE
OVER THERE.
I SO I FELT IN A PRETTY
COMFORTABLE SITUATION.
SO YOUR CHOICE WAS IN SOME
SENSE A FREEBY.
YES.
LAUREN, HOW IMPORTANT IS IT
TO NAVIGATE AND MANAGE
RELATIONSHIPS THAT MAY OR MAY
NOT BE ON THE SIDE OF THE TRENCH
AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT LIKE MAYBE
ELIZABETH, SHE DOESN'T SEEM
CERTAIN WHERE SHE FITS.
ST SUPERIMPORTANT TO
NAVIGATE.
LIKE YOU SAID OR TOMMY SAID,
SOMEONE SAID, IT IS DAY 30, WHAT
WAS I SAYING?
YEAH, IT IS SUPERIMPORTANT TO
TRY TO NAVIGATE THROUGH THESE
RELATIONSHIPS.
THE PROBLEM IS, EVERYBODY HAS
THEIR OWN PLAN, A, B, C, D, E,
F, G, H, I, J, LMT THEY THINK
THIS WILL BE A VERY EASY TRIEBL,
AND I THAT I IS VERY NAIVE,
TRIBAL IS NEVER EASY.
KARISHMA, WHAT DOES AN EASY
TRIBAL MEAN.
AN EASY TRIBAL MEANS EVERYONE
HAS NODDED THEIR HEAD.
BUT WE LOOK AT ALL THE BLIND
SIDES THAT HAVE HAPPENED
ALREADY.
IT'S NEVER AS SIMPLE AS EASY
TRIBAL, EVERYBODY IN?
TOMMY, WHY ARE EASY TRIBALS
SO HARD TO PULL OFF?
WHEN I ASKED MY GIRLFRIEND
WHERE DOES SHE WANT TO EAT, THAT
IS ONE PERSON AND WE CAN'T
FIGURE IT OUT.
SO NOW TRY TO GET EIGHT PEOPLE
TO AGREE ON THEIR FAVORITE
RESTAURANT OR THEIR FAVORITE
PERSON.
SO NOTHING IS I, EVEN OUT OF
THIS GAME TO CHOOSE ONE PERSON
OR ONE THING.
ELAINE, YOU HAD A PRETTY BIG
REACTION.
MY PERSONAL OPINION IS YOU
HAVE TO PICK A CORE AND ROW WITH
THOSE PEOPLE, PERIOD.
IF YOU SWAP BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN ALL THOSE PEOPLE, AIN'T
NOBODY GOING TO TRUTHS YOU, SO
WHO THE HELL IS GOING TO TAKE
YOU TO THE NEXT STEP, I'M
BANKING ON THE RELATIONSHIP WITH
THESE INDIVIDUALS I CALL MY
CORE, AND MI GOING TO ROW WITH
THEM OR I'M GOING TO ROW HOME,
STORY.
-SORRY.
SO ELIZABETH MAY NOT BE THE
FIRST CHOICE FOR TO YOU GO IF
SHOW SAY SHOW ROWS WITH HER
CORE, BUT IF YOU FIND THE RIGHT
PERSON WHO MIGHT THINK
DIFFERENTLY, WHO KNOWS.
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
AND YOU HAVE TO PLAY AS WHO YOU
ARE.
AND FOR ME I'M A LOYAL PLAYER.
IF I PLEDGE YOU MY A A LEGANCE,
I WILL BE WITH YOU FOR AS LONG
AS YOU WANT ME, BUT TO THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE COIN IT IS FLUID AND
PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS CHANGING THEIR
MINDS AND THEIR AGENDAS AND YOU
DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU FALL IN
THEIR GAME.
THEY COULD BE TELLING YOU ONE
THING BUT IT IS COMPLETELY
OPPOSITE FOR ANOTHER PERSON.
ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME TO
VOAVMENT ELAINE, YOU ARE UP.
I WILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
SO THIS IS A LEGACY ADVANTAGE.
I AM PLAYING IT FOR MYSELF.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
THIS IS NOT AN ADVANTAGE AND
HAS ABSOLUTELY NO POWER.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR DEAN WILL
STILL COUNT.
OKAY.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
JEFF.
THERE IS SOME INSURANCE
BECAUSE I AM CERTAINLY ON THE
WRONG SIDE OF THE TRENCH.
AND I HOPE THAT WE CAN START
FILLING THAT TRENCH IN.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
ANY VOTE ITS CAST FOR KARISHMA
WILL NOT COUNT.
JEFF THERE IS ONE MORE.
I'M NOT GOING HOME EITHER.
THIS IS ALSO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR LAUREN WILL
NOT COUNT.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KARISHMA, DOES NOT
COUNT.
KARISHMA, DOES NOT COUNT.
JANET, ONE VOTE JANET.
ONE VOTE LEFT.
ELIZABETH.
WE HAVE A TIE.
SO HERE'S WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
WE ARE GOING TO REVOTE, JANET
AND ELIZABETH, WILL YOU NOT
VOTE, EVERYBODY ELSE, YOU CAN
ONLY VOTE FOR JANET OR
ELIZABETH.
ELAINE, ARE YOU UP, WILL YOU
COME GRAB THE UN.
THIS IS SO TOUGH.
OH, THIS SUCKS SO BAD.
I WILL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
I WILL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTES, ELIZABETH.
ELIZABETH, TWO VOTES ELIZABETH.
ELIZABETH.
THREE VOTES ELIZABETH.
129 PERSON VOTED OUT AND THE
6th MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
ELIZABETH, THAT'S FOUR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BINGE ME YOUR TORCH.
ALL WELL AND GOOD UNTIL
SOMEONE PLAYS AN IDOL.
ELIZABETH, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
I AM TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
BYE.
GOOD LUCK.
LOVE YOU.
AND THEN THERE WERE EIGHT.
WELL, ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
IT WASN'T AN EASY VOTE.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
NEXT TIME ON SURVIVOR.
IN AN UNPREDICTABLE GAME.
THIS IS A BREAK I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
THERE IS NO ONE TO TRUST.
I AM HONEST AND LOYAL TO A
FAULT.
NOURA IS SUCH A FRUIT LOOP.
EXCEPTED FAMILY.
TIME FOR SOME LOVE.
I MADE A MILLION DOLLAR
MISTAKE AT THE CHALLENGE.
BUT AS AN OLYMPIAN I GAVE IT MY
ALL.
ANY TIME YOU GET TO PLAY
SURVIVOR AND MAKE IT 30 DAYS,
THAT IN ITSELF IS AN INCREDIBLE
FEET.
SO I THINK IN MY OWN WAY HAVE I
GOTTEN A LITTLE BIT OF GOLD
INSIDE OF ME JUST FOR DOING THIS
ENTIRE EXPERIENCE.
SO BITTERSWEET RIGHT NOW.