THEY'RE TOO DAMN CLOSE
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> KARISHMA, DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT?
>> I DO.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
NO, I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
IT'S A GAME.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GREAT.
>> TONIGHT AT TRIBAL, I HAD A
GUT INSTINCT THAT THERE WAS SOME
PLAN IN PLACE TO TAKE ME OUT.
FORTUNATELY I WAS THE PLAN "B,"
BUT I STILL GOT THREE VOTES.
WHAT THAT TELLS ME IS THAT TO
THIS TRIBE I AM EXPENDABLE.
SO UNLESS SOMETHING DRASTIC
CHANGES, MY LIFE IN THIS GAME IS
ABOUT TO GO OUT.
THESE PEOPLE HAVE ALREADY MADE
THE DECISION, EASY PEASY DONE.
>> YEAH!
>> KARISHMA FEELS LIKE SHE IS ON
THE OUTSIDE, AND I KNOW HOW
SHE'S FEELING.
THAT WAS ME AFTER THE FIRST
VOTE.
BUT I'VE BEEN ABLE TO PICK
MYSELF BACK UP, AND NOW I FEEL
LIKE I'M CALLING THE SHOTS.
SO, YEAH, KARISHMA, SHE'S AN
EASY VOTE.
HOWEVER, THERE ARE OTHER PEOPLE
THAT MIGHT BE BETTER.
IN THIS GAME, ONE OF THE THINGS
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL OF IS
WHEN PEOPLE ARE COUPLED
TOGETHER.
AN DEAN AN CHELSEA, THEY'RE TOO
DAMN CLOSE.
WHEN YOU'VE GOT TWO PEOPLE
SLEEPING ON TOP OF EACH OTHER,
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
WHAT YOU HAVE THERE IS A
POTENTIAL POWER COUPLE.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT HAS TO GET
SQUASHED.
>> HOWL DID YOU SAY YOU WERE?
>> 28.
>> 28?
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 27.
OH, THIS IS PERFECT.
>> I MEAN, WE DID SLEEP TOGETHER
LAST NIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS WHEN
YOU SLEEP NEXT TO EACH OTHER.
>> ON THE FIRST DATE.
>> CHELSEA, SHE'S GOT SOME SPUNK
TO HER.
SHE'S A CUTIE FOR SURE.
SHE CAN COME BACK AT YOU WITH A
QUIP.
SHE CAN HANG IN THERE WITH THE
BOYS, AND I REALLY THIS LIKE
THAT ABOUT HER.
SO, YEAH, I'M SUPER DRAWN TO
HER.
>> HE'S A CUTE BOY, BUT, NO, I'M
NOT HERE FOR NO SHOWMANCE.
THAT ALWAYS MESSES UP PEOPLE'S
GAMES.
>> IS DON'T WITH CHELSEA OR NOT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WELL, IF HE DOESN'T HELP YOU
IN SOME WAY, THEN...
>> BASED OFF OF HIS PERFORMANCE.
>> HE DON'T HELP.
>> EXACTLY.
IF WE REMOVE THAT CONNECTION,
EVEN BETTER.
DEAN AND CHELSEA ARE SNUGGLING
UP, AND THAT COULD MESS UP THE
GIRLS' ALLIANCE.
SO IN "SURVIVOR," YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO HAVE MORE THAN ONE PLAN.
SO ME AND AARON, WE HAVE A LOT
IN COMMON.
WE BOTH WENT TO THE MILITARY
ACADEMY.
WE BOTH HAVE HAD SOME EXPERIENCE
IN THE OUTSIDE WORLD AND BEING
AFRICAN AMERICAN, AN WE'RE BOTH
VERY COMPETITIVE, SO WE'RE
WILLING TO MAKE A BIG MOVE.
SO MAYBE WE DO GET RID OF DEAN,
BECAUSE WITH DEAN OUT OF THE
WAY, IT WOULD BREAK UP THE PAIR.
AN CHELSEA WILL COME BECOME TO
ME AND ELIZABETH.
WE'LL GET THE SORORITY SISTERS
BACK TOGETHER.
>> I THINK KARISHMA, AS LONG AS
SHE STAYS ANOTHER DAY, SHE'LL DO
WHATEVER.
>> WE LET HER GO WHEN WE NEED TO
LET HER GO.
SHE'S ANNOYING AS HELL RIGHT
NOW, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S "SURVIVOR."
>> WITH THE RAFT?
>> WITH THE RAFT.
>> WE'LL KEEP THE RAFT SHALLOW
UNTIL EVERYBODY IS READY.
>> YOU GOING?
>> I'M NOT.
I'M STAYING UP HERE.
>> OH.
>> THE SUN AT HIGH NOON DOESN'T
APPEAL TO ME.
>> THIS MORNING IN THE VOKAI
TRIBE, I COULD NOT SHAKE THIS
FEELING THAT GETS IMPLANTED INTO
YOUR BONES WHEN YOU'RE ONE OF
TWO PEOPLE LEFT OUT OF A VOTE.
>> SEE YOU AROUND.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> HAVING BEEN LEFT OUT OF THE
MOLLY VOTE REALLY KICK STARTED
ME INTO MAKING SURE I'M
PROTECTING MYSELF.
EVERYONE IS GOING OUT TO THE
WATER.
JASON WAS GOING FOR A WALK, AN
I'M LIKE, IF I DIDN'T LOOK FOR
THE IDOL RIGHT NOW I WOULD BE
STUPID.
THIS IS THE PERFECT SCENARIO.
DEALING WITH CHANGE HAS BEEN ANY
WHOLE JAM FOR THE PAST FEW
YEARS.
I WAS IN A ROUGH RELATIONSHIP.
I WAS NOT TREATING MYSELF WITH
GRACE, AND I WAS NOT FEELING
GREAT ABOUT MYSELF.
THE END OF THAT RELATIONSHIP WAS
REALLY TRYING FOR ME.
BUT THE LESSON THAT I LEARNED
FROM THAT WAS HOW TO TAKE THINGS
IN STRIDE TO MOVE REALLY SLOWLY,
TO NOT GET TOO WORKED UP ABOUT
THINGS, BE IN TUNE WITH MY
SURROUNDINGS AND BE HERE IN
SPACE AND TIME.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU'RE PRESENT,
WHEN YOU'RE OBSERVANT, WHEN
YOU'RE CONNECTED IN THE HERE AND
NOW, MOMENTS REVEAL THEMSELVES
TO YOU.
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU HAVE FOUND A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
WHEN PLAYED AT TRIBAL COUNCIL,
ANY VOTES CAST AGAINST YOU WILL
NOT COUNT."
THERE IT IS IN ALL ITS GLORY.
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS IMMUNITY
IDOL.
PRETTY, HUH?
IT IS REALLY AWESOME TO FIND AN
IDOL, ESPECIALLY WITH THE TRIBE
WHO IS STARTING TO GET LULLED
INTO A SENSE OF COMPLACENCY THAT
THEY'RE IN CONTROL OF ME.
WRONG.
>> DO I HEAR A BOAT?
>> BOAT'S COMING.
BOAT'S COMING.
>> SERIOUS?
>> THE BOAT'S COMING.
>> IT'S A BAG.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SHOULD WE READ IT HERE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ONE OF YOU MUST COME TO THE
ISLAND OF THE IDOLS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> IT MUST BE UNANIMOUS
DECISION.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> DISSENSION FROM A SINGLE
MEMBER REQUIRES YOU TO DRAW FROM
THE BAG.
THE NAME CHOSEN GETS ON THE BOAT
IMMEDIATELY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD JUST
DRAW.
>> JUST DRAW.
>> WHOEVER GOES TO THE ISLAND OF
THE IDOLS IS GOING TO KNOW WHAT
I KNOW AND CAN BLOW UP MY GAME
OR GET CLOSER, AND WE BETTER GET
CLOSER.
>> I DON'T KNOW, CHOOSING OUT OF
THE BAG SEEMS LIKE A COP-OUT.
>> WOW, I LIKE IT.
>> HERE'S A QUESTION: DOES
SOMEBODY WANT TO GO?
>> MOST "SURVIVOR" PLAYERS KNOW
THAT JUST THE ACT OF GOING, JUST
LIKE THE ACT OF SEARCHING FOR
THE IDOL, IS GOING TO PUT A
TARGET ON YOUR BACK.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO.
I WAS LIKE, I'M NOT GOING.
I'M STAYING RIGHT HERE.
>> MY "SURVIVOR" FAN SIDE OF MY
BRAIN IS LIKE, YOU HAVE TO GET
THAT IDOL, YOU GOT TO GO, DUDE.
AND THEN MY MOM SIDE OF THE
BRAIN IS LIKE, YOU DON'T NEED TO
GO, YOU'RE GOING TO BE BY
YOURSELF OUT THERE, JUST STAY,
YOU'RE SAFER WITH NUMBERS.
NO ONE WANTS TO GO, REALLY IN.
>> REALLY?
>> MY WHOLE GAME IS ABOUT
LOWERING MY THREAT LEVEL AND
MAKING OTHER PEOPLE MORE
THREATENING, SO THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GOING TO VOLUNTEER.
>> I WOULD GO.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE HERE THE PLAY THIS
GAME, AN I'M A RISK TAKER.
I QUIT MY JOB AS A P.T.A. TO
BECOME A ENTREPRENEUR, SO TO ME
IT WAS A IN BRAINER.
I WANT TO GO.
I'M GOING TO THE ISLAND OF THE
IDOLS, AND I GET TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
I'M EXCITED.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME FUN.
I SEE FIRST A MAN'S FACE.
IT'S A KIND OF HANDSOME MAN'S
FACE.
TO ME IT KIND OF LOOKED
FAMILIAR.
>> WELCOME.
>> HI!
>> HOW'S IT GOING?
>> I FEEL SO LOVED RIGHT NOW.
HI.
I'M NOURA.
>> I'M ROB.
>> OF COURSE I KNOW WHO YOU GUYS
ARE.
WOW, BOSTON ROB AND SANDRA.
I'M SUPER EXCITED TO SEE THEM
AND MEET THEM IN PERSON.
SANDRA IS A TWO-TIME WINNER.
BOSTON ROB IS A WINNER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE NO ONE ELSE
JUMPED ON THIS.
THESE ARE EXPERTS THAT ARE
COMING TO YOU.
>> HOW IS IT GOING?
>> IT'S GOING WELL.
>> HAVE YOU EATEN ANYTHING?
>> I'M OPENINGEN COCONUTS LIKE
CRAZY.
>> HAVE YOU HAD WATERMELON?
>> WE HAVE WATERMELON.
>> YES!
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN SOMEONE SO
EXCITED.
>> WATERMELON IS MY FAVORITE
THING.
THEY WELCOMED IN ME.
MAYBE I CAN TALK TO THEM ACT
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH MY GAME AND
THEY CAN GIVE ME SOME ADVICE.
>> CHEERS.
>> CHEERS, GUYS.
OH, MY GOSH, THIS IS SO AMAZING.
WHY IS THIS SO SMALL.
I AM NOT A TYPICAL "SURVIVOR"
PLAYER.
I FEEL LIKE A NOVICE, AND IF
ANYONE, I NEED THESE GUYS.
IN THAT MOMENT, I'M LIKE, I'M IN
THE RIGHT PLACE AT THE RIGHT
TIME.
>> LET ME FELL YOU IN A LITTLE
BIT.
>> OKAY.
>> SO EVERYBODY THAT COMES TO
THE ISLAND OF THE IDOLS GETS A
LESSON.
AND YOUR LESSON TODAY IS ABOUT
THE ART OF PERSUASION.
>> OH, WOW.
I NEED THAT.
>> PERSUADING PEOPLE IN THIS
GAME IS A VERY IMPORTANT SKILL
THAT EVERY PLAYER NEEDS TO HAVE.
IN ORDER TO PERSUADE SOMEONE
EFFECTIVELY, YOU HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND THAT PERSON'S
MOTIVATIONS.
IF YOU WERE TO GIVE IMMUNITY
IDOL IMMUNITY, THEN I WOULD
BELIEVE YOU, THAT WOULD CUE ME
THAT WE'RE ALL GOING TO VOTE
AMANDA.
>> IT HAS TO LINE UP WITH
SOMETHING THAT THEY WANT.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A
PIVOTAL MOVE IF YOU WANT A JURY
VOTE.
>> IF YOU CAN FIGURE OUT WHAT IT
IS THAT THIS PERSON WANTS,
PERSUADING THEM SHOULD BE EASY.
>> I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
>> ERIC, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> I THINK THAT IS WHAT YOU CALL
A LIFE LESSON.
>> DIFFERENT PEOPLE NEED
DIFFERENT TYPES OF PERSUASION.
YOU COULD APPEAL TO SOMEONE'S
EGO.
>> YES, THAT HELPS.
>> BABY MONKY.
>> I'M GOING TO FLIRT WITH HIM.
GET HIM ON MY GOOD SIDE.
THAT'S WHAT I DO BEST.
>> YOU CAN TRY TO SCARE SOMEONE,
PUT FEAR INTO THEM TO GET WHAT
YOU WANT.
>> THIS IS THE IDOL.
I'M ASKING YOU FOR BOTH OF OUR
SAKES TO BECOME MY ALLY.
>> BASICALLY VOTE WITH US OR
YOU'RE GOING HOME TONIGHT.
>> OR FOR ME, RUMOR, YOU START A
RUMOR.
>> I KNOW, YOU'RE SO GOOD AT
THAT.
>> I HEARD COACH WAS SAYING HE
WANTED TO GET RID OF YOU.
>> HE'S GOING BEHIND MY BACK
SAYING STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> HE'S SO STUPID.
HE DON'T KNOW WHAT HE GOT
HIMSELF INTO.
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS FOR THAT,
YOU'RE OFFERING THEM SOMETHING
IN RETURN FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
>> THAT'S MORE ME.
MINE IS MORE INTELLECTUAL OF A
CONNECTION.
>> RIGHT.
I CAN THINK OF LIKE AN EXAMPLE
FROM WHEN I PLAYED, WHEN I ASKED
LEX TO SAVE AMBER.
I KIND OFEN TIESED HIM WITH, IF
YOU CAN DO SOMETHING, I'LL TAKE
CARE OF YOU LATER.
>> LEX, MOVE IT OUT.
>> IT'S VERY EFFECTIVE, BUT IN
HINDSIGHT, I ULTIMATELY DIDN'T
GET HIS VOTE AT THE END OF THE
DAY, SO SOME WOULD ARGUE THAT HE
HAD THE LAST LAUGH.
WHEN YOU FIRST GOT HERE, WE TOLD
YOU THERE WOULD BE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO TEST WHAT YOU
LEARNED.
>> OKAY.
>> WE HAVE SOME INSIGHT INTO
YOUR NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
SO LISTEN UP.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
>> OKAY.
>> FOR YOUR NEXT IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE, THE TRIBE WILL BE
BLINDFOLDED.
ONE PERSON WILL BE THE CALLER.
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT ROLE IN
THE CHALLENGE.
IF YOU CAN PERSUADE YOUR TRIBE
TO LET YOU BE THE CALLER, YOU
WILL EARN AN ADVANTAGE THAT
ALLOWS YOU TO BLOCK THE VOTE OF
ANOTHER PLAYER.
IF YOU FAIL TO END UP IN THE
CALLER ROLE, YOU LOSE YOUR VOTE
FOR THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> I LOVE THIS.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO ACCEPT THE
TEST?
>> I'M DOING IT.
>> THINK ABOUT IT, CHEW ON YOUR
WATERMELON.
>> I'M DOING IT.
I'M DOING IT NO MATTER WHAT.
I'M GOING TO PUSH TO BE THE
PERSON THAT CALLS IT OUT.
>> OKAY.
YOU THINK YOU CAN PULL IT OFF?
>> WHEW!
>> OH, MY GOD, THIS IS SO MUCH
FUN.
>> SHE DIDN'T GIVE IT MUCH
THOUGHT.
SHE JUST TOOK THE OFFER AND WENT
WITH IT.
THAT'S A MENTALITY THAT SHE HAS.
THAT WILL GET HER IN TROUBLE IN
THE GAME.
>> OKAY.
IN MY OPINION, NOURA IS THE LAST
PERSON YOU WOULD WANT IN THE
CALLING POSITION.
SHE CANNOT COHERENTLY COMMUNE
KATE ANYTHING TO ANYONE.
SHE'S LIVING IN NOURA WORLD.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
YOU GOT TO BE IN "SURVIVOR"
WORLD.
>> BY, NOURA.
YOU GOT THIS.
>> SHE DEFINITELY IS PERCEPTIVE.
THE QUESTION IS, IS HER
PERCEPTION REALITY?
>> NOURA'S BACK.
>> NOURA!
>> HI.
I HAVE A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
WHEN I HIT THE BEACH, I ALREADY
AM GETTING A LITTLE BIT OF
ANXIETY, BECAUSE YOU GTD A BIG
GROUP, AND THEY'RE JUST LIKE
WAITING FOR THE NOURA TV SHOW TO
START AND QUICK PLAY.
SO BASICALLY I GET THERE, AND I
GET AN ADVANTAGE IN THE NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE THAT WILL
BENEFIT YOU AND YOUR TRIBE.
THEY BASICALLY GAVE US WHAT'S
NEXT IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IS IN
DETAIL.
THERE'S ONLY ONE TWIST, IT SAYS
YOU HAVE TO UNANIMOUSLY AGREE ON
THE ROLE THAT I PLAY IN THAT
CHALLENGE.
>> OKAY.
THEN I CAN TELL YOU ALL THE
DETAILS.
>> THIS IS ALL A LIE, BECAUSE I
HAVE THE INFORMATION, AND I
COULD HAVE JUST GIVEN IT TO
THEM, BUT WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO
IS SECURE THAT CALLER POSITION,
BECAUSE IF I CAN PERSUADE MY
TRIBE TO LET ME BE THE CALLER, I
WILL GET AN ADVANTAGE IN THIS
GAME.
IF THEY DON'T LET ME, I WILL
LOSE MY VOTE AT THE NEXT TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> HOW CAN WE --
>> BASICALLY SAY YES, WE
UNANIMOUSLY DECIDE THAT NOURA
CAN PICK THE ROLE TO DO, AND I
GET TO TELL YOU THE WHOLE
DETAIL.
YOU'LL SEE THAT'S WHY I NEED
THAT ROLE?
I'M DOING THE THIS FOR THAT.
THE IDEA IS, YOU WANT TO KNOW
THIS INFORMATION, WELL, I NEED
THIS COMMITMENT FROM YOU GUYS.
DOES EVERYONE AGREE?
>> EVERYONE AGREES?
EVERYONE'S FINE?
>> OKAY.
SO READY?
OKAY.
SO EVERYONE IS GOING TO BE BLIND
FOLD AND THERE IS A CALLER, SO
THAT WOULD BE ME.
SO I CALL OUT, SO NOW THERE'S A
CALLER, AND PEOPLE GO OUT AND
WHATEVER WE'RE RETEEFG, I HAVE
TO GUIDE EACH OF YOU TO GO OUT
ON THE COURSE AND BRING IT BACK.
WHOEVER GETS BACK FIRST WIN,
THAT'S IT.
>> DID YOU WANT TO BE THE
CALLER.
>> IT'S THE ROl
IS THE CALLING PERSON.
>> NOURA PRESENTS US WITH THIS
BIZARRE SCENARIO IN WHICH WE
HAVE TO CHOOSE HER ROLE IN AN
UNKNOWN GAME TO HAVE HER REVEAL
TO US WHAT THE GAME IS WE'RE
GOING THE PLAY TOMORROW FOR THE
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
IF I COULD DO FULL CIRCLES
WITHOUT BEING IN A CARTOON, OUR
EYES WOULD BE DOING FULL
CIRCLES.
>> CAN YOU EXPLAIN TO THE TRIBE
WHY YOU THINK YOU'RE THE BEST
PERSON TO BE THE CALLER?
>> IT'S ALREADY DONE.
I GAVE YOU THE INFORMATION, SO I
ALREADY HAVE THAT ROLE.
IT CAN'T -- IT'S DONE.
>> WAIT, THIS IS WHAT I'M
ASKING, YOU GOT TO DECIDE WHAT
ROLE YOU WANTED, THAT'S THE ONLY
ROLE, THE CALLER.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THE QUESTION.
>> WE HAD TO UNANIMOUSLY DECIDE
THAT YOU COULD PICK YOUR ROLE,
SO COULD YOU PICK YOUR ROLE AS A
RETRIEVER.
>> I GUESS I COULD, YEAH,ER
GUESS I COULD.
>> THIS IS NOT A GOOD LIE, BUT
IT'S GOOD NOURA IS SO IN THIS
LIE THERE IS NO WAY SHE'S GOING
TO TALK ABOUT WHAT'S ON ISLAND
OF THE IDOLS.
SO PRESSURE IS OFF OF ME.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER IF I'M THE
BEST OR NOT, IT'S THAT I COULD
NOT TELL YOU GUYS THIS
INFORMATION UNLESS I PICKED THE
ROLE.
IN MY MIND I DECIDED I'M GOING
TO BE THE CALLER, THAT SIMPLY,
BECAUSE I HAVE ALL THE
INFORMATION.
IT IS WHAT IT IS, WE CAN'T
CHANGE IT.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE NOT BELIEVING
IN ME.
THEY'RE QUESTIONING ME.
I DON'T THINK I'M THAT BAD OF A
CALLER.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A BIG MOUTH,
A BIG VOICE, EVEN IF I WAS THE
WORST CALLER, IF WE'RE
PRACTICING AHEAD OF TIME AND WE
KNOW WHAT WE'RE GOING INTO, I
THINK WE SHOULD BE FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
DAN, I'M GOING TO WALK YOU
THROUGH THE COURSE.
GET ON YOUR KNEES.
CRAWL ON YOUR KNEES.
OKAY.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO CRAWL LIKE
TEN STEPS FORWARD.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR --
>> NOURA, GET BACK TO YOUR
PERCH.
DAN, STAND UP.
WALK TO MY VOICE.
TEN STEPS FORWARD.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO BE BEHIND ME.
>> I CAN'T WALK TO YOUR VOICE.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE BEHIND ME.
IS THIS FORWARD, LEFT, RIGHT?
>> OKAY.
I GOT IT.
DAN, WALK TEN STEPS FORWARD TO
ME.
>> NOT TO YOU.
>> LET ME STAND BEHIND YOU THEN.
>> THE BLIND MAN COULD SEE THAT
NOURA DOES NOT BELONG ON THAT
PERCH.
SHE DOES NOT BELONG UP THERE.
>> DIDN'T, TAKE FIVE STEPS
FORWARD.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
STOP.
>> DON'T COUNT OUT HIS STEPS,
LET HIM DO IT AND CALL THE NEXT
PERSON.
I'M SITTING HERE DOING NOTHING.
>> IF NOURA IS THE CALLER AND WE
LOSE, THEN SHE'S 100 ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK.
>> TAKE THREE STEPS FORWARD AND
KEEP GOING, NOTHING IN FRONT OF
YOU.
TAKE ONE STEP TO YOUR RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IF SHE INSISTINGS ON BEING
THE CALLER, THEN SHE BETTER
FOLLOW THROUGH, BECAUSE THAT'S
GOING TO BE HER ASS.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
VOKAI GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW LYRSA TRIBE.
VINCE VOTED OUT AT THE LAST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO TODAY'S IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, GOT THE TAKE
IT BACK.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, A CALLER
WILL LEAD BLIND FOLDED TRIBE
MEMBERS THREW A COURSE, CHECKING
THREE KEYS ALONG THE WAY.
YOU'LL THEN USE THOSE KEYS TO
UNLOCK PUZZLE PIECES.
THE CALLER WILL THEN DIRECT A
STILL-BLINDFOLDED TRIBE MEMBER
TO SOLVE THE PUZZLE.
FIRST TO FINISH WINS IMMUNITY,
SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FOURTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
VOKAI, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
YOU HAVE TO SIT SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> NOURA.
NOURA IS SITTING OUT.
>> YOU'RE SITTING OUT.
>> WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> NOURA.
TAKE A SPOT ON THE SITOUT BENCH.
>> MY TRIBE TOLD ME TO SIT OUT.
SO AFTER ALL THAT, I LOST MY
VOTE AT THE NEXT TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THIS MIGHT BLOW UP ANY GAME,
THIS IS A FREAKIN' MIGHT MEYER.
-- NIGHTMARE.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY ELSE TAKE A
MINUTE TO STRATEGIZE AND WE'LL
GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS ELIZABETH, THE CALLER FOR
LAIRO.
>> TO YOUR RIGHT, TO YOUR RIGHT.
ELAINE, YOU NEED TO GO TO THE
RIGHT.
ELAINE.
>> WALK STRAIGHT AND START
CLIMBING THROUGH THE WOOD.
>> SENDING EVERYBODY OUT
TOGETHER.
ELIZABETH GOING WITH THREE
PAIRS.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> TOM, FOLLOW ELAINE.
>> Jeff: IT'S ALL ABOUT
COMMUNICATION.
>> I'M HERE, IMHERE.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: TOMMY JUST TOOK ONE
IN THE GROIN.
IT IS ELAINE AND TOM TOGETHER,
CHELSEA AND DEAN, MISSY AND
KARISHMA TOGETHER.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> Jeff: JASON CALLING FOR
VOKAI.
HE SENT EVERYBODY OUT TOGETHER.
THAT'S GIVING THEM AN EARLY
LEAD.
LAUREN AND JAMAL.
NOW THEY HAVE TO FIND THAT KEY
AND UNCLIP IT.
>> ELAINE, THERE IS A ROPE.
PUT YOUR HAND UP.
OTHER HAND, PULL, PULL, PULL.
THERE.
>> Jeff: VOKAI HAS THEIR FIRST
KEY.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK.
>> TOMMY, TO YOUR LEFT, TO YOUR
LEFT.
STRAIGHT, TOMMY, STRAIGHT!
>> Jeff: TOMMY AND JACK HAVE
THE SECOND KEY FOR VOKAI.
>> DEAN AND CHELSEA, UNDER.
>> NO, DEAN, DEAN, UNDER, UNDER,
UNDER.
DEAN AND CHELSEA, UNDER.
>> DEAN AND CHELSEA WENT OVER.
THE UNDER OBSTACLE, BIG SETBACK
FOR LAIRO.
>> CAN WE GO BACK UNDER?
THEY STILL NEED TO GET TWO KEYS.
JANET WORKING TOGETHER, LOOKING
FOR THAT THIRD KEY.
>> I GOT THIS.
>> Jeff: THEY GOT IT.
>> WORK YOUR WAY BACK.
>> Jeff: VOKAI HAS ALL THREE
KEYS.
THEY'RE HEADING BACK NOW.
THEY GOT OUT THE A FAST LEAD DUE
THE GREAT LEADERSHIP BY JASON.
JAMAL AND LAUREN HEADED BACK FOR
VOKAI.
LAIRO ONLY HAS ONE KEY.
THEY'RE STILL LOOKING FOR TWO
MORE.
A LOT OF PLAYERS MEETING FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
>> THAT'S THE OTHER TEAM, BRO.
>> FOLLOW MY VOICE.
>> DEAN!
LISTEN, WE'RE GOING TO NEED YOU.
HEY, MISSY AND KARISHMA --
>> SHUT UP.
>> DEAN, DEAN!
>> MISSY, LISTEN, TURN TO YOUR
LEFT.
>> Jeff: ONE SIDE IS HEADING
BACK AND ONE IS STILL GOING OUT.
MISSY AND KARISHMA TRYING TO GET
SOMETHING GOING.
YOU GOT TO GET THEM ALL THE WAY
BACK TO THE MAT.
YOU'RE GOOD!
JASON HAS EVERYBODY BACK FOR
VOKAI.
NOW YOU GOT THE LEAD THEM ALL
THROUGH THE COURSE AGAIN.
>> MISSY, CLIMB UNDER THAT WOOD
AND YOU'RE GOING TO GRAB A ROPE.
MISSY AND KARISHMA LOOKING FOR A
KEY.
>> YES, CHELSEA AND DEAN, KEEP
WALKING.
>> Jeff: KARISHMA AND MISSY
HAVE THE SECOND KEY.
THEY HAVE TO GET BACK.
IT'S NEW DEAN AND CHELSEA
LOOKING FOR THAT THIRD AND FINAL
KEY.
VOKAI HAS ALL THREE AND IS
HEADING BACK TOWARD THAT FINAL
STAGE OF THE CHALLENGE, THE
PUZZLE.
>> COME ON.
EVERYONE IS HERE.
WE HAVE A STRAIGHT SHOT.
>> Jeff: MISSY IS PULLING ON
KARISHMA.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO FOLLOW MY
VOICE.
>> DEAN AND CHELSEA STILL
WORKING.
>> DEAN, STOP, STOP, STOP.
>> I FEEL SOMETHING.
>> GO TO YOUR RIGHT.
DEAN, GO TO YOUR RIGHT.
DEAN, GO TO YOUR RIGHT!
>> Jeff: VOKAI IS BACK.
THEY HAVE TO GET THOSE PUZZLE
PIECES FREE.
>> THE OTHER WAY, BEHIND YOU,
DEAN.
DEAN AND CHELSEA STILL LOOKING
FOR THAT THIRD PIECE FOR LAIRO.
>> DEAN, THE OTHER WAY, TURN
AROUND, DEAN.
WALK FORWARD.
>> Jeff: DEAN HAS THE PIECES
OUT.
NOW IT'S UP TO KELLEE TO UNTIE
THEM AND FREE ALL THE PIECES.
>> WALK FORWARD, WALK FORWARD.
THERE YOU GO.
>> THERE IT IS.
THAT'S THE THIRD KEY FOR LAIRO.
GOT TO UNCLIP AND YOU GOT TO
HUSTLE BACK.
JASON AND KELLEE NOW WORKING FOR
VOKAI.
>> WALK A LITTLE FASTER.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH AND LAIRO
STRUGGLING.
THEY'RE IN TROUBLE RIGHT NOW.
VOKAI ALREADY WORKING ON THE
PUZZLE.
>> SLIDE IT, SLIDE IT, THERE YOU
GO.
>> Jeff: DEAN AND CHELSEA
ALMOST BACK TO THE MAT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
NOW ELIZABETH HAS TO GET HER
ENTIRE TRIBE ALL THE WAY BACK TO
THE PUZZLE TABLE AS FAST AS SHE
CAN.
>> VOKAI WITH A HUGE LEAD.
THEY RALLY TAKE THEIR TIME ON
THAT PUZZLE.
IT WOULD BE AN AMAZING COMEBACK
IF LAIRO COULD GET BACK AND WIN
THIS CHALLENGE.
>> THAT PART ALL THE WAY OVER.
>> Jeff: THEY'VE BEEN VERY
CALM DURING THIS PHASE OF THE
CHALLENGE.
ANOTHER PIECE FOR VOKAI.
HERE COMES ELIZABETH.
SHE'S MADE QUICK WORK OF GETTING
HER TRIBE BACK.
>> YOU'RE ON THE MAT.
KARISHMA, GET ON THE MAT.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE GOOD.
IT'S GOING TO BE AARON NOW
SOLVING THE PUZZLE.
>> OKAY.
STAND RIGHT HERE.
>> SLIDE TO YOUR RIGHT.
>> Jeff: COMEBACKS DO HAPPEN
ON "SURVIVOR."
THIS WOULD BE A HUGE ONE.
LAIRO FIGHTING TO GET BACK IN.
>> YOU HAVE TO LEFT IT UP AND
PUT IT IN.
NOW SLIDE IT ALL THE WAY TO THE
RIGHT.
YES, YES!
>> RIGHT NOW I'M GOING TO HAVE
YOU ROTATE THEM.
>> FEEL THE NOTCH ON THE TABLE.
>> Jeff: IT IS VOKAI WITH A
BIG LEAD.
JASON HAS LED THIS TRIBE VERY
CALMLY FROM START TO PRESENT.
>> THIS IS NOT PERFECT.
HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
>> I FEEL IT.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH HAS NOT
PANICKED EVEN THOUGH THEY'VE
BEEN VERY FAR BEHIND.
>> OKAY.
>> Jeff: JASON EXAMINING HIS
PUZZLE.
NO, I'M NOT SURE THE OUTSIDE IS
CORRECT.
>> TAKE THAT PIECE IN YOUR HAND.
>> Jeff: LAIRO NEEDS VOKAI TO
MAKE A MISTAKE.
>> YES, VERY, VERY GOOD.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH VERY
QUICKLY WORKING ON THIS PUZZLE.
>> I THINK WE GOT IT.
>> Jeff: AARON WITH ANOTHER
PIECE.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT EITHER.
>> Jeff: JASON DOESN'T LIKE
ONE OF THE PIECES, HE'S GOING TO
PULL IT OUT.
ELIZABETH HAS SHOWN GREAT
LEADERSHIP UNDER PRESSURE.
THEY ARE BACK IN THIS RIGHT NOW.
IT WOULD BE ONE OF THE BIGGEST
COMEBACKS IN A "SURVIVOR"
CHALLENGE.
JASON STILL WORKING ON HIS
PUZZLE.
>> RIGHT NEXT TO THAT ON THE
RIGHT.
ELIZABETH PUT DOWN ANOTHER
PIECE.
SHE'S LYING WHAT SHE'S GOT
GOING.
JASON WILL HAVE TO PICK IT UP.
LAIRO WITH TWO PIECES LEFT.
>> CENTERPIECE.
LAST PIECE NOW.
>> FIND THAT TRIANGLE.
FIND THAT TRIANGLE.
>> Jeff: THIS COULD BE IT.
>> YES!
YES!
>> NO, NO.
KEEP GOING.
>> Jeff: LAIRO THOUGHT THEY
HAD IT.
>> THERE ARE TWO PIECES THAT WE
HAVE TO SWITCH.
>> PUSH IT BACK, PUSH IT BACK.
THERE YOU GO.
THE MIDDLE PIECE.
FIND THAT NOTCH.
>> Jeff: JASON THINKS HE HAS
IT THIS TIME.
WILL THIS BE RIGHT?
>> YES!
>> YOU GOT IT?
VOKAI HAS IT.
VOKAI WINS IMMUNITY.
>> YOU NEVER GAVE UP!
>> Jeff: AN EPIC CHALLENGE
THAT CAME DOWN TO JUST A FEW
PIECES.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> VOKAI, CONGRATULATIONS.
IMMUNITY ONCE AGAIN IS YOURS.
NO TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT.
ENJOY IT.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
TAKE THE NIGHT OFF.
>> THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
LAIRO, TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT,
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FOURTH
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT TRIBAL.
>> EVERYBODY THINKS THAT
KARISHMA IS A DEAD FISH IN THE
WATER, AND HONESTLY SHE IS, BUT
IF I HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY ABOUT
IT.
I'M GOING TO KEEP KARISHMA NICE
AND FOLDED UP IN MY POCKET AND
USE HER VOTE.
IF I CAN HAVE TWO VOTES INSTEAD
OF ONE, THAT'S A GOOD DAY.
>> GUYS, I JUST WANT TO SAY I'M
SORRY.
I WAS THE LEADER TODAY AND I LET
YOU GUYS DOWN.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU SAYING, THAT
BUT WE PUT YOU IN THAT POSITION.
YOU DID FANTASTIC JOB.
>> ONCE AGAIN WE LOST THE
CHALLENGE.
I'M AT THE BOTTOM, SO I'M
EXPECTING IT TO BE UNANIMOUS
VOTE AGAINST KARISHMA, AND IT'S
KILLING ME.
THERE ARE CERTAINLY BIGGER
THREATS THAN ME, BUT THIS TRIBE
ARE A BUNCH OF PANSIES.
ALL THEY'RE DOING IS WHO IS THE
COMMON DENOMINATOR EVERYBODY CAN
LIVE WITH, AND TODAY IT'S ME.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
NOT LIKE THIS.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT ON THIS ONE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO TALK ABOUT.
THERE'S NO DISCUSSION.
>> NOT FOR ME.
>> KARISHMA'S NAME HAS BEEN OUT
THERE FOR A WHILE NOW.
SHE HASN'T DONE MUCH AROUND
CAMP.
SHE HASN'T CONTRIBUTED TOO MUCH
WHEN IT COMES TO PUZZLES OR
ATHLETICALLY IN CHALLENGES.
I FEEL LIKE SHE'S GOT TO SEE IT
COMING.
I DON'T THINK TONIGHT WILL BE A
BLIND SIDE.
>> I WANT TO STAY IN THE GAME
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, AT TRIBAL I'M GOING TO
SWING FOR THE FENCES.
>> DO IT.
GO OUT SWINGING.
PEOPLE CHALLENGE THEIR MINDS.
I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN BEFORE.
>> KARISHMA IS MAKING HERSELF AN
OUTSIDER AND KNOWS HER TIME IS
COMING TO AN END, AND I KNOW
SHUE DOESN'T HAVE AN IDOL
BECAUSE I'M THE ONE THAT HAS IT.
SO I'M IN A REALLY GOOD SPOT.
I HAVE REALLY GOOD RELATIONSHIPS
WITH PEOPLE, ESPECIALLY WITH
DEAN, AND I THINK THAT'S GOING
TO TAKE ME FAR IN THIS GAME.
>> I JUST FEEL SO BAD.
EVERYBODY ELSE'S FATE IS ON THE
LINE BECAUSE OF ME.
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> WE WORRY TICKLY IS FAR
BEHIND.
THE GAME NEEDS TO GET BLOWN UP
RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'RE GETTING EMBARRASSED.
>> THIS IS THE THING, I KEEP
LOOKING AT IT AND TODAY'S
PERFORMANCE, WHY ARE YOU HOPPING
OVER THE THING INSTEAD OF GOING
UNDER THE THING.
DEAN IS THE ONE I WANT GONE.
HE'S UNDERPERFORMING IN
CHALLENGES.
YOU'VE GOT CHELSEA IN HIS BACK
POCKET, AND HE'S PLAYING A SMILE
AT YOU, MAKE YOU FEEL GOOD KIND
OF GAME, TRYING TO FLY UNDER THE
RADAR.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
SO HE'S GOT TO GO.
>> TERRIBLE.
IT'S GARBAGE.
>> I'M FINE WITH IT.
>> SO AARON PITCHES VOTING OUT
DEAN.
AND I WAS ABSOLUTELY SHOCKED.
MAYBE HE HASN'T SHOWN UP FOR THE
CHALLENGES, BUT WHY SHOULD I
GIVE KARISHMA THE PRIVILEGE OF
MAKING IT FURTHER IN THIS GAME
WHEN DEAN IS AT LEAST GATHERING
FIREWOOD, HELPING COOK, BUILDING
THE SHELTER, WHILE KARISHMA
TAKES A NAP.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> YOU HAVE TO BE ON BOARD.
>> I'M ON BOARD.
>> OKAY.
>> I SORT OF WAS GOING ALONG
WITH IT, BUT I'M NOT READY TO
SEE DEAN GO, NINE TEN DAYS AGO I
WOULD HAVE SAID, YES, WHATEVER
YOU NEED, HERE'S MY VOTE, I'LL
WRITE IT DOWN RIGHT NOW.
BUT WHILE I WAS ON THE ISLAND OF
THE IDOLIOUS BOSTON ROB SAID TO
ME, YOU HAVE TO LOOK BEFORE YOU
LEAP.
AND RIGHT NOW IVDON'T THINK
GETTING DEAN OUT IS GOOD FOR MY
GAME.
>> I'M NERVOUS.
DEN'S NAME IS BEING TOSSED
AROUND.
>> WHY?
AARON DOESN'T THINK HE COMPETES
IN THE CHALLENGES.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GET RID
OF HIM.
>> I DON'T EITHER, BUT MISSY IS
FULL ON BOARD.
>> HOLY CRAP.
AARON IS WANTING TO GO FOR DEAN,
AND I WAS LIKE, WHAT THE HELL?
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND.
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE AARON IS
SHADY.
>> KARISHMA IS GOING TO JUMP
SHIP.
AND THE PLAN IS TO NOT TELL
THEM.
>> I KNOW.
THAT'S INSANE.
>> AARON, YOU SNEAKY BASTARD.
IF HE'S WILLING TO CUT THE
THROAT OF HIS FRIEND, THEN
WHAT'S HE HE GOING TO DO TO ME
LATER ON?
I DON'T WANT TO VOTE DEAN, AND
IF THEY DON'T HAVE ME AND
ELIZABETH, THEY CAN'T PULL THAT
OFF.
>> SHE'S NOT ON BOARD?
>> THIS WILL ALIENATE CHELSEA
AND TOM.
>> THIS IS THE TARGET.
IT SEEMS LIKE I'M THE ONLY ONE
IN THIS TRIBE THAT WANTS THE
PLAY THIS GAME.
EVERYBODY ELSE, THEY'RE TRYING
THE PLAY EVERYBODY'S TOGETHER
AND NO HURT FEELINGS, BUT AT
SOME POINT IN TIME, THIS GAME
HAS TO GET BLOODY.
THIS "KUMBAYA" NONSENSE HAS GOT
US INTO A HOLE AFTER TONIGHT.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE HEADED, DOWN
A ROAD OF DISASTER.
>> SHE'S NOT WILLING TO ROCK THE
BOAT YET.
>> THIS TRIBE HAS A LOT OF
PEOPLE ON IT.
THEY'RE TOO WEAK AND AFRAID TO
MAKE A MOVE.
IT'S REALLY FRUSTRATING.
>> WE GO BACK THE KEEPING
STRENGTH AROUND.
I'M LIKE, YOU DIDN'T COME HERE
TO PLAY "SURVIVOR."
YOU CAME HERE FOR A VACATION,
BUT I'M HERE TO PLAY THIS GAME
AND KIK SOME BUTT.
SO WE CAN'T AGREE ON DEAN.
WE CAN'T AGREE ON KARISHMA.
SO I NEED A NAME THAT NO ONE IS
COMPLETELY ATTACHED TO.
I WANT THE MAKE SURE WE DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR US.
>> I AGREE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS IS IN MY
OPINION DEAN AND CHELSEA.
YOU AGREE?
>> I AGREE.
>> THIS IS OUT OF THE BLUE.
IF IT'S TOO SCARY TO GET RID OF
TEEN, WOULD IT BE CHELSEA?
BECAUSE THEY'RE A PAIR.
THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
GIRLS KEEP MAJORITY, WE KEEP
THREE BIG GUYS AS PROTECTION FOR
US, AND THEN KARISHMA IS STILL
ANOTHER EASY VOTE TO GO LATER?
>> MISSY WITHIN TEN MINUTE FLIPS
THE TARGET ON THE CHELSEA, AND
HER ABILITY TO DROP NAMES ON A
DIME SCARED ME.
>> SHE WANTS TO GET CHELSEA OUT?
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
>> RIGHT NOW IT'S A BIG CLUSTER.
PEOPLE ARE HAVING SIDE
CONVERSATIONS WITH EVERYBODY,
AND THEY'RE ALL WHISPERING.
WITH THESE YAHOOS, YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT THEY'RE GOING TO DO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT'S GOING TO
GO DOWN.
THIS ONE IS GOING TO DRAW THE
LINE IN THE SAND AND IT'S GOING
TO LET PEOPLE KNOW WHERE THEY
STAND.
WE'LL SEE HOW IT GOES, BUT IT'S
GOING TO BE REAL GUT CHECK TIME.
>> THEY JUST LOVE TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
>> Jeff: SO, CHELSEA, DAY 11,
TWO TRIBAL COUNCILS, TWO
DEVASTATING BLIND SIDES.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY ABOUT THIS
GROUP?
>> IT'S LIKE WHAT YOU SAID LAST
TRIBAL, WE SUCK AS PUZZLES, BUT
WE'RE REALLY GOOD AT BLINDSIDES,
SO IT'S TRICKY BECAUSE THERE
HASN'T BEEN THAT LINE DRAWN IN
THE SATURDAY TONIGHT.
WILL IT BE DRAWN TONIGHT?
MAYBE, MAYBE IT WON'T.
>> Jeff: KARISHMA, SOUNDS VERY
FAMILIAR TO LAST TIME YOU WERE
HERE WHEN THERE WAS ANOTHER
BLINDSIDE.
>> I HAD A DIFFERENT EXPERIENCE.
I WAS A CONTINGENCY PLAN IN CASE
VINCE PLAYED AN IDOL.
BASED ON THAT, NOBODY WANTS THE
TALK TO ME.
>> Jeff: YET, YOU'RE STILL
HEAR.
>> "SURVIVOR" GODS.
EVERY DAY IS A NEW DAY.
THAT'S ALL I CAN HOPE FOR.
PRAYING TO THE "SURVIVOR" GODS.
>> Jeff: ELAINE, IS THAT YOUR
PERCEPTION, THAT SHE'S SITTING
AT CAMP GOING ANYONE, ANYONE,
BUELLER?
>> LISTEN, THESE PEOPLE ARE
MOVING SO FAST, I CAN'T EVEN
SEE.
THEY'RE LIKE EVERYWHERE.
TALK TO ONE PERSON, OH, YEAH,
THIS IS WHAT WE'RE DOING.
TEN MINUTES LATER IT'S SOMETHING
TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> THIS ONE NEVER KNOWS
ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: DEAN, IS IT A GOOD
THING OR A BAD THING FOR
KARISHMA, WHO FEELS LIKE SHE'S
IN TROUBLE THAT THERE WAS SO
MUCH CHAOS.
>> IF I WERE IN KARISHMA'S
SHOES, THAT CHAOS SHOULD MEAN
POSITIVES THINGS.
BECAUSE IF EVERYONE IS
SCRAMBLING, THERE ARE PROBABLY
PLANS THAT DON'T INVOLVE
KARISHMA.
>> ?OO CHELSEA, IT LOOKED LIKE
YOU WERE NODDING IN AGREEMENT.
>> YOU SHOULD NEVER THROW THE
TOWEL IN.
CONVERSATIONS ARE GOING ON UP
UNTIL TRIBAL.
IF YOU STOP FOR A SECOND, YOUR
NAME COULD BE UP THERE, SO TALK
TO ANYONE, BECAUSE YOU CAN PUT
THAT LITTLE SEED OF DOUBT IN
SOMEONE'S MIND AND EVERYTHING
CAN CHANGE.
>> Jeff: AARON, IS THAT REALLY
ALL IT TAKES IS A TINY LITTLE
SEED OF DOUBT?
>> SURE.
I MEAN, THE RIGHT PERSON, THE
RIGHT SITUATION, THE RIGHT
CRACK, YOU SAY ONE LITTLE THING,
THAT LITTLE THING CAN BLOSSOM
INTO A FLOWER.
SO, YEAH.
>> Jeff: ELIZABETH, HOW DOES
THAT EQUATE TO STRATEGY?
BECAUSE IF YOU REACT TO THE
CHAOS, THEN YOU'RE LOST.
YOU'RE SPINNING OUT OF CONTROL
LIKE ELAINE GOING YES, NO, HUH?
>> THAT'S -- YOU HIT THE NAIL ON
THE HEAD WITH THAT.
THAT'S EXACTLY HOW CAMP WENT
TODAY.
I THAWING WE WERE GOING IN WITH
A VERY CLEAR PLAN.
THAT EVOLVED INTO TWO, THREE,
FOUR, PLANS.
I NEED TO THINK ABOUT MOVE
THAT'S BEST FOR ME.
SOMETIME THAT'S THE LAST PLAN
THAT'S TALKED ABOUT AND THAT'S
THE ONE YOU GO WITH.
>> Jeff: ELAYNE, THAT HAS TO
BE UNNERVING.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE WHAT IF YOU'RE
THAT LAST PLAN THAT WAS TALKED
ABOUT.
THAT IS UNNERVING THAT PLAN "B"
COULD BE THE ONE IF THAT'S YOU.
>> Jeff: MISSY, NEVER HEARD
ANYONE PLAY PLAN Z, BUK THAT IS
WHAT IT SOUNDS LIKE?
>> WE'RE PLAYING RUSSIAN
ROULETTE.
WE LOADED THE GUN.
IT'S GOING TO HIT SOMEBODY THAT
MAYBE IS NOT EXPECTING IT.
>> Jeff: WOW, KARISHMA, THAT'S
A PRETTY DARK BUT ACCURATE
METAPHOR?
>> I'M LOVING WHAT I'M HEARING
HERE AT TRIBAL TODAY.
>> I DON'T WANT HER TO LOVE WHAT
SHE'S HEARING BECAUSE THE STRAY
BULLET DOESN'T HIT SOMEONE, THAT
DOESN'T MEAN SHE CANNOT GET HIT
AND THAT DOES NOT MEAN SHE'S NOT
WITHOUT FAULT IN THIS GAME.
IF YOU OPEN UP AND SAY YOU'RE
THE PUZZLE MAKER, BE THE PUZZLE
MAKER.
IF YOU SAY YOU CAN SHOOT HOOP,
SHOOT HOOPS.
IF YOU SAY YOU'RE AN OLYMPIAN,
BE AN OLYMPIAN.
ALL OF US ARE PLAYING EQUALLY,
AND SHE'S GETTING LAPPED.
>> NICE.
GOOD JOB.
>> WOW.
>> ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS THERE
WAS CHAOS, GREAT.
BECAUSE CHAOS IS A LADDER, AND
MAYBE I CAN CLIMB OUT OF MY
TRENCH.
>> Jeff: SO IF YOU'RE VOTED
OUT, WOULD YOU RATHER IT WAS A
BLINDSIDE OR TO BE, YEAH, I KNEW
THE ENTIRE TIME BECAUSE NOBODY
TALKED TO ME.
>> I WOULD RATHER BIT A
BLINDSIDE, BECAUSE THE SITUATION
I'M IN NOW, IF I'M VOTED OUT,
I'M EXPECTING IT.
IT WOULD HURT MORE.
>> Jeff: DEAN, WHAT'S THE
LETTER YOU WRITE TO SOMEBODY
AFTER YOU HAVE BLINDSIDED THEM.
>> DEPENDS HOW CLOSE YOU WERE.
BUT THERE'S SOME SORT OF SORRY
IN THERE AND THANKS FOR PLAYING.
>> Jeff: WOW.
WHY IS THAT SO FUNNY.
I'M LAUGHING, TOO.
SORRY, THANKS FOR PLAYING.
>> EVERYBODY THINKS IT'S GREAT
TO BLINDSIDE PEOPLE.
THAT'S PART OF "SURVIVOR" AND
THE THRILL, BUT WHEN YOU'RE ON
THE OTHER SIDE AND YOU'RE
WALKING OUT, YOU AIN'T GOING TO
BE LAUGHING.
>> Jeff: MISSY, WOULD YOU BE
SHOCKED IF IT WAS YOU TONIGHT?
DID YOUR NAME COME UP?
>> I DIDN'T HEAR MY NAME FROM
ANYONE, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN MY
NAME WASN'T OUT THERE?
IF THEY'RE PLAYING A GOOD
BLINDSIDE, I WOULDN'T HEAR MY
NAME?
BUT I DON'T THINK ANY OF US
WOULD BE SHOCKED.
IF I WERE TO CUT HIM TO, CUT
ANYBODY, CAN YOU BLAME THEM?
WE DON'T KNOW THESE PEOPLE, AND
YET WE'RE LITERALLY LYING IN THE
DIRT LIKE DOGS TOGETHER.
IN SOME WAY WE'RE FAMILY, BUT IN
OTHER WAYS WE'RE COMPLETE
STRANGERS.
IT'S HARD.
>> Jeff: CHELSEA, IF YOU CAN
SEPARATE THE EMOTION, WHAT'S THE
PLEASURE IN A BLINDSIDE FROM A
PLAYER STANDPOINT?
>> I MEAN, IT'S A LITTLE SICK,
BUT WHEN YOU PULL OFF A
BLINDSIDE, THAT INNER PART OF
YOU SMILES BECAUSE YOU'RE LYING
LIKE, I'M PLAYING "SURVIVOR,"
BUT I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
BLINDSIDED BECAUSE SOMEONE CLOSE
TO ME WAS LYING AND THAT HURTS.
IT'S NOT FUN TO CRUSH PEOPLE'S
DREAMS, BUT THAT'S PART OF THE
GAME, SO IT DEFINITELY IS FUN.
I LIKE IT.
>> IT COULD BE ANYBODY.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
DEAN, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, KARISHMA.
KARISHMA.
CHELSEA.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES KARISHMA,
TWO VOTES CHELSEA.
>> SHE'S LOOKING AROUND.
>> Jeff: CHELSEA.
THAT'S THREE VOTES CHELSEA, TWO
VOTES KARISHMA.
CHELSEA.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES CHELSEA.
FOURTH PERSON VOTED OUT,
CHELSEA.
THAT'S FIVE, THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU
NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> YOU WANTED A BLINDSIDE, YOU
GOT YOU ONE.
>> Jeff: CHELSEA, THE TRIBE
HAS SPOKEN.
>> GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: WELL, I GUESS THAT
WAS PLAN Z.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
Captioning funded by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," IN A GAME OF LIES --
>> YOU'RE TALKING NONSENSE RIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH, DEAN, IT WAS ME.
I TOOK YOUR GIRLFRIEND OUT OF
THIS GAME.
>> Jeff: NEW BATTLE LINES ARE
DRAWN.
DROP YOUR BUFFS.
>> WE DON'T KNOW THESE PEOPLE.
YOU CAN'T TRUST THEM.
>> THERE IS SO MUCH DANGER.
>> I NEED TO FLIP ON OLD LAIRO.
>> I'M COMPLETELY AND UTTERLY
BLINDSIDED.
I'M A HUGE SUPER FAN.
I DREAMED OF PLAYING "SURVIVOR"
SINCE I WAS EIGHT YEARS OLD.
I THOUGHT I COULD WIN THIS GAME.
I HAVE AN IDOL IN MY POCK AND
COULD HAVE SAVED MYSELF, SO
OBVIOUSLY I'M JUST EMBARRASSED.
TO NOT EVEN MAKE THE MERGE, UH,
THIS IS SO DISAPPOINTING.