>> Jeff: IN THE SUMMER OF
THE000, AUDIENCES WERE
INTRODUCED TO THE CRAZIEST IDEA
SEEN ON TELEVISION IN YEARS.
YOU ARE WITNESSING 16 AMERICANS
BEGIN AN ADVENTURE THAT WILL
FOREVER CHANGE THEIR LIVES.
GO!
>> THIS ISLAND IS PRETTY MUCH
FULL OF SNAKES AND RATS.
WE OWE IT TO THIS ISLAND TO LET
IT BE IN THE END THE WAY MOTHER
NATURE INTENDED IT TO BE.
>> Jeff: THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> FOR THE SNAKE TO EAT THE RAT.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF THE
FIRST "SURVIVOR" COMPETITION
IS... RICH.
>> ONE OF THE HOTTEST REALITY
SHOWS EVER ON TV.
>> IT WAS A SOCIAL EXPERIMENT
MADE FOR TV THAT BECAME A POP
CULTURE PHENOMENON.
>> "SURVIVOR" HAS TAKEN US TO
ALMOST EVERY CORNER OF THE
WORLD.
>> PEOPLE HAVE VOLUNTEERED TO BE
STRANDED IN SOME OF THE WORLD'S
MOST REMOTE AREAS.
>> Jeff: TONIGHT WE CELEBRATE
20 YEARS AND 40 SEASONS OF
"SURVIVOR" FEATURING NEW
INTERVIEWS AND NEW INSIGHTS FROM
YOUR FAVORITE PLAYERS AS THEY
RELIVE THEIR MOST MEMORABLE
MOMENTS.
>> IT WILL BE THE HEIST OF ALL
HEISTS.
>> YOU HAVE TO PICK UP YOUR IDOL
WHEN 19 PEOPLE ARE WATCHING YOU.
>> Jeff: PLUS A SNEAK PEEK AT
EPISODE ONE OF "WINNERS AT WAR."
>> SEEING MY COMPETITORS, I'M
LIKE, OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: THIS IS "SURVIVOR AT
40".
Captioning funded by CBS
and FORD.
We go further, so you can.
>> CAN YOU HEAR ME?
I DON'T WANT TO TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
JUST PUT IT THIS WAY, WE'RE ALL
VERY EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> WE ARE PRIORITIES, SO WE
PIRATED.
>> PIRATED.
>> DON'T JUMP ALL OVER ME,
SWEETHEART.
>> I CAN GET LOUD, TOO.
WHAT THE...
>> SOMETIMES SHE MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE THE DEVIL HERE.
>> I MAY BE A LOT OF THINGS, BUT
I AIN'T NO HERSHEY BAR.
>> FRANCESCA.
>> FRAN...
>> CESCA.
>> FRANCESCA.
>> I SAY STICK TO THE PLAN.
>> WE HAVE ZERO CHANCE OF
WINNING THE GAME.
>> NICE, GUYS.
I HOPE YOU GUYS ALL GET BIT BY A
FREAKIN' CROCODILE.
>> Jeff: WELCOME, GUYS.
THIS IS "SURVIVOR: PEARL
ISLANDS."
"PEARL ISLANDS" INTRODUCED US TO
ARGUABLY OUR MOST NOTORIOUS
VILLAIN.
>> WHAT IS THAT ABOUT?
>> THAT'S JOHNNY FAIR PLAY.
THAT'S THE F, THAT'S THE Y.
I'M ALL IN BETWEEN, JOHNNY FAIR
PLAY.
>> Jeff: CEMENTING HIS STATUS
WITH THE BOLDEST LIE IN
"SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> IT'S EITHER GOING TO BE MY
BUDDY OR MY GRANDMOTHER COME,
AND MY GRANDMOTHER IS NOT HERE
FOR A REASON.
MY GRANDMOTHER IS SITTING HOME
WATCHING JERRY SPRINGER RIGHT
NOW.
I SWEAR ON MY GRANDMOTHER THAT'S
A BIG FREAKIN' DEAL.
>>
I SWEAR ON
MY GRANDMOTHER.
I SWEAR, I SWEAR, I SWEAR.
>> Jeff: THIS IS YOUR
GRANDMOTHER, RIGHT, JOHN?
>> YEAH, THAT'S MY GRANDMOTHER.
>> Jeff: WERE YOU IN ON THIS?
>> NO.
[LAUGHTER]
NO IDEA.
>> NO IDEA.
>> Jeff: WHILE FAIR PLAY
TRUSTED THE BOUNDARIES OF TRUST
AND MANIPULATION, FOR OTHERS
"SURVIVOR" OFFERS THE CHANCE FOR
A DIFFERENTTIST, THE CHANCE TO
GO BEYOND PERSONAL COMFORT ZONES
TO SEE WHAT'S POSSIBLE.
CIRIE IS AT THAT SECOND OBSTACLE
AND SHE'S CLEARLY EXHAUSTED.
>> I CAN'T GIVE UP.
>> Jeff: "SURVIVOR" EXPOSES
YOUR STRENGTHS AND YOUR
WEAKNESSES AND CAN MAKE YOU FEEL
VERY VULNERABLE.
CIRIE, YOU ARE THE WOMAN WHO
OVER A DECADE AGO GOT UP OFF THE
COUCH TO COME TRY THIS GAME
"SURVIVOR."
THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER, BUT WE
WILL STAY HERE WITH YOU IF YOU
WANT TO TRY TO CONQUER THIS.
>> I'M NOT LETTING MY MIND TELL
ME BE AFRAID, DON'T DO IT, JUST
GIVE UP ANYMORE.
I CAN DO IT.
>> THERE YOU GO, GIRL!
>> YES, CIRIE!
>> Jeff: THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
>> THROUGH OUR GREATEST
ADVERSITIES COME OUR GREATEST
SUCCESSES.
INSIDE HERE, UNBREAKABLE,
UNBENDING, UNYIELDING,
IMMEASURABLE, IMPROVABLE,
INVINCIBLE.
>> ONE OF MY BIGGEST FEARS IS
BEING OSTRACIZED.
THE FACT THAT I AM BECOMING THIS
PERSON PEOPLE LIKE TO TALK TO
AND HANG OUT WITH IS VALIDATION
THAT THIS WORK HAS BEEN PAYING
OFF.
>> CHRISTIAN, YOU'RE SAFE, I'M
NOT.
>> I HEAR YOU.
I JUST... I MIGHT NEVER GET THIS
OPPORTUNITY AGAIN.
I'M BECOMING A GOLIATH-LIKE
FIGURE FROM THESE DAVID ORIGINS.
>> Jeff: CHRISTIAN HAS JUST
WON INDIVIDUAL IMMUNITY AFTER
FIVE AND A HALF EPIC HOURS.
COME ON, DONATHAN.
COME ON, BUDDY.
>> PEOPLE IS ALWAYS WANTING TO
PUT ME DOWN.
THEY WOULD SAY, HE AIN'T GOT NO
TOUGHNESS IN HIM, BUT FOR ME
THIS WAS CHANCE TO PROVE MYSELF.
>> Jeff: IT WOULD BE
REMARKABLE IF DONE THAN --
DONATHAN COULD PULL THIS OFF,
AND HE DOES IT.
DONATHAN AMAZES HIMSELF.
>> IF AT ANY POINT YOU WISH TO
END YOUR ADVENTURE, RAISE THE
SAIL.
WHAT?
>> Jeff: REEM, 32 NIGHTS OUT,
THERE YOU NEVER ONCE RAISED THAT
SAIL AND SURRENDERED.
>> I CAME OUT HERE THE PROVE
SOMETHING TO MYSELF, AND I AM
PROUD OF MYSELF.
AND I HOPE THAT MY FAMILY IS
PROUD OF ME.
>> OF COURSE THEY ARE.
MY WHOLE LIFE I HAVE HAD THIS
GIGANTIC FEAR OF DEATH, BUT OVER
THE YEARS IT BECAME SOMETHING
FAR WORSE.
IT MORPHED INTO A FEAR OF LIFE.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I'M HERE LIKE TO START TAKING
CONTROL OF MY LIFE, AND I REALLY
BELIEVE THAT IF ANY EXPERIENCE
CAN GIVE ME THAT POWER, IT'S
THIS GAME OF "SURVIVOR."
>> Jeff: IN SEASON ONE FIRST
ALLIANCE WAS FORMED.
>> THE WHOLE IDEA OF AN ALLIANCE
IS TO MAKE SURE WE'RE ALL VOTING
THE SAME WAY.
>> SO ARE WE GOING TO STICK TO
IT?
>> I'M GOING TO STICK TO IT.
>> Jeff: CREATING A
CORNERSTONE FOR ALL "SURVIVOR"
GAME PLAY TO FOLLOW.
>> COOL?
>> Jeff: SOME LED TO BETRAYAL.
15th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH AND FINAL MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, MALCOLM.
OTHERS WERE BUILT THE LAST.
>> IF I WIN, I TAKE YOU.
YOU WIN, YOU TAKE ME.
WE GOT A FINAL TWO.
WELL, YOU'VE GONE AS FAR AS YOU
CAN GO IN THIS GAME.
BUT ONE ALLIANCE HAS PROVEN TO
BE STRONGER THAN ALL THE REST.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DO YOU WANT TO MAKE AN ALLIANCE,
COVER OUR OWN ASSES?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN TAKE
YOU SERIOUSLY OR NOT?
>> I'M BEING 100% SERIOUS.
>> Jeff: WHAT STARTED AS
SIMPLE STRATEGY ESCALATED TO
SOMETHING MORE.
>> IT'S GUESSING MUCH EASIER AND
EASIER TO FLIRT WITH BOSTON ROB.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO KISS ME,
KISS ME NOW.
I'M NOT KISSING YOU WITH NASTY
BREATH LATER ON.
>> WHOA.
IT WOULD BE NICE HAVE $1 MILLION
AND TAKE THE GIRL AWAY, TOO.
>> Jeff: WITH ROB AND AMBER'S
BOND SOLIDIFIED, THE COMPETITION
DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
>> MAKE NO MISTAKE, THE WORD I
GAVE YOU WAS THAT IF I CAN TAKE
CARE OF YOU, I WILL.
I'M SORRY, I CANNOT.
>> Jeff: THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> IT SUCKS.
>> Jeff: AN ALLIANCE THAT
STARTED ON DAY ONE CARRIED ALL
THE WAY THROUGH DAY 39,
GUARANTEEING ROB OR AMBER THE $1
MILLION PRIZE.
>> I LOVE YOU WITH ALL MY HEART.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> THE FACT THAT ROB HAD BEEN
PLANNING TO ASK ME TO MARRY HIM
THAT NIGHT, IT'S COOL TO SHARE
SUCH AN AMAZING MOMENT WITH SO
MANY PEOPLE.
>> Jeff: WE STILL HAVE THIS
LITTLE THING CALLED THE VOTE TO
GET TO.
>> YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: A $1 MILLION VOTE.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY I WAS
HAPPY BECAUSE I FOUND SOMEONE I
WAS GOING TO BE IN AN ALLIANCE
WITH FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
15 YEARS LATER AND FOUR
WONDERFUL GIRLS, STILL GOING
STRONG.
>> Jeff: STILL TO COME --
NO, SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
>> I MEAN, YOU GAVE IT YOUR BEST
SHOT, BUT THAT "U" WILL HAUNT
YOU FOR THE REST OF YOU LIFE.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE MANY
REASONS "SURVIVOR" IS SO FUN AND
SO COMPLICATED TO PLAY IS YOU
CAN NEVER ANTICIPATE WHEN A NEW
TWIST IS GOING TO FLIP THE GAME
ON ITS HEAD, BUT THE GREAT
PLAYERS ADAPT, AND IT OFTEN
LEADS TO GREAT "SURVIVOR"
MOMENTS.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: IN "SURVIVOR
"CAGAYAN," TONY TOOK THE IMMENSE
POWER OF A SUPER IDOL AND TURNED
IT INTO SOMETHING MUCH MORE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A SPECIAL
POWER.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DO?
>> BUT YOU CAN'T USE BOTH?
>> UH-HUH.
>> NORMALLY I WOULD POINT OUT
THE BIGGEST THREAT RIGHT NOW WIN
THE GAME, TONY, AND CAST MY VOTE
THAT WAY, BUT THIS KIND OF
COMPLICATES THINGS.
>> BOTH THE IDOLS I HAVE NOW,
EVEN THE IDOL WITH THE SPECIAL
POWERS HAS TO BE USED WHEN IT'S
DOWN FIVE SURVIVORS LEFT.
MY INTENTIONS ARE TO ACT LIKE
THE SPECIAL POWER IDOL I'M
ALLOWED TO USE IT WHEN THERE'S
FOUR SURVIVORS LEFT.
IF THEY DO BELIEVE MY BLUFF, I'M
GUARANTEED FINAL THREE.
>> WE CAN'T GET RID OF TONY
TONIGHT.
HE HAS HIS MAGIC IDOL.
WE'RE STILL WAITING TOO HAVE THE
POWERS REVEALED.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
>> RIGHT NOW THIS IDOL IS
NOTHING MORE THAN A SOUVENIR.
THE ONLY THING THAT I HAVE GOING
FOR ME RIGHT NOW IS MY BLUFF.
>> JEFF, I JUST WANT TO EXPLAIN
THE SPECIAL IDOL.
IT CAN ONLY BE PLAYED WITH FIVE
REMAINING PLAYERS LEFT, SO THIS
IDOL IS ABSOLUTELY USELESS
TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, SPENCER.
WU.
14th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE EIGHTH MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
SPENCER.
EVERYONE LOVES A GOOD TWIST,
UNLESS, OF COURSE, IT DOESN'T
WORK IN YOUR FAVOR.
>> I'M LOOKING OVER AT MICHAELA,
AND I SEE A ROLLED-UP PIECE OF
PAPER THAT SAYS "SECRET
ADVANTAGE," AND I CAN'T BELIEVE
MICHAELA DIDN'T SEE THAT.
>> Jeff: IN SEASON 34,
MICHAELA HAD AN ADVANTAGE PULLED
RIGHT OUT FROM UNDERNEATH HER.
>> YOU NOW HAVE THE RIGHT TO
STEAL A VOTE FROM SOMEONE AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
HOLY... YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF, I'M
GOING TO USE MY ADVANTAGE.
>> Jeff: AND IT ENDED UP BY
THE REASON MICHAELA WENT HOME.
>> Jeff: 14th PERSON VOTED
OUT AND THE SEVENTH MEMBER OF
OUR JURY, MICHAELA.
SOME TWISTS WERE BORN TO LAST.
IT IS THE KEY TO SURVIVAL, THE
ABILITY TO MAKE FIRE.
IN OUR TENTH SEASON, THE
FIRE-MAKING TIEBREAKER CHALLENGE
WAS INTRODUCED.
>> SURVIVORS READY?
BEGIN.
WHEN STEPHANIE AND BOBBY JOHN
FACED OFF TO SEE WHO WOULD BE
THE LAST REMAINING MEMBER OF THE
ULONG TRIBE.
STEPH'S STORE.
IS LIT, THIS CHALLENGE IS OVER.
STEPH WINS IMMUNITY.
SINCE THEN WE'VE SEEN FIERCE
BATTLES AS PLAYERS FOUGHT TO SAY
IN THE GAME.
BECKY, SANDRA, WHO WILL GET
FIRST FLAME?
THERE'S AN INFERNO GOING RIGHT
NOW.
THIS MAY BE AS FAR AS IT GOES
FOR CYDNEY.
THERE IT IS!
AUBRY SURVIVES TRIBAL COUNCIL.
BUT IN OUR 35th SEASON, FIRE
TOOK ON EVEN BIGGER STAKES, THE
THIRD SEAT AT THE FINAL TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
FOR BEN IT OFFERED HOPE WHEN IT
SEEMED THERE WAS NONE TO BE HAD.
>> AT THIS POINT IN THE GAME, I
WAS DONE.
I WAS DEAD IN THE WATER, NO MORE
IDOLS.
I KNEW I HAD TO WIN IMMUNITY OR
I WAS GOING HOME.
>> Jeff: BEN THINKS HE HAS IT.
>> I THOUGHT I HAD IT WON.
I HAD ALL THE BLOCKS UP THERE.
BUT I DON'T KNOW THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN AN UPSIDE-DOWN "U" AND A
RIGHT-SIDE UP "U."
>> Jeff: NO!
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
CHRISTIE WINS INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY
>> I WAS COMPLETELY WRECKED.
I REMEMBER LOOKING AT THE OCEAN
AND THINKING, YOU GAVE IT YOUR
BEST SHOT, BUT THAT U WILL
HAUNTED YOU THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE.
>> Jeff: THERE'S ONE MORE
THING THAT COMES WITH THE WIN.
TONIGHT YOU ARE IN CHARGE.
YOU WILL CHOOSE ONE PERSON TO
SIT NEXT TO YOU AT THE FINAL
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THE TWO REMAINING PLAYERS WILL
EARN THEIR WAY TO THE END BY
BATTLING IT OUT IN A FIRE-MAKING
CHALLENGE.
>> Jeff: SO CHRISSY, HAVE YOU
MADE A DECISION?
>> I HAVE.
I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE RYAN TO THE
FINAL THREE.
>> Jeff: CHRISSY PULLS OUT AN
ADVANTAGE.
I HAD THE MAKE FIRE AGAINST
EVAN, WHO WAS THE STRONGEST FIRE
MAKING OUT THERE.
>> Jeff: BEN HAS THE FIRST
FLAME.
HE'S GOT SOME STICKS ON THERE.
DEVON CONTINUES TO STRIKE.
BEN'S FLAME IS BURNING HIGH NOW
AND IT'S STARTING TO HIT THAT
CORD.
YES!
BEN EARNS THE FINAL SEAT AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IN SEASON 38, EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, CHRIS UNDERWOOD USED
FIRE MAKING IN A WHOLE NEW WAY.
CHRIS HAS EARNED HIMSELF A SPOT
BACK IN THE GAME.
>> COMING BACK FROM THE EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, I AM GOING TO DO
EVERYTHING IN MY POWER TO WIN
THIS GAME.
I'VE GOT SO MUCH ON THE RHINE.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST DECISION I
HAVE TO MAKE.
I'M WEARING THE NECKLACE.
I HAVE TOTAL CONTROL, BUT I'M
AFRAID.
IF DEVONS GOES TO PLEAD HIS
CASE, REGARDLESS OF WHO IS
SITTING THERE, I MIGHT LOSE TO
DEVENS.
I MIGHT HAVE TO BE FLAT-OUT
DARING.
I WANTED NO REGRETS.
I WOULDN'T WANT THERE TO BE ANY
OTHER WAY FOR THIS SEASON TO
END.
IT'S THE BIGGEST RISK I'M
TAKING, SO TONIGHT I AM OFFERING
UP MY IMMUNITY NECKLACE AND I
WILL BE MAKING FIRE AGAINST RICK
DEVENS TONIGHT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
CHRIS'S FIRE CONTINUING TO GROW.
FIRST BITS OF ROPE STARTING TO
BURN.
IT'S OVER.
CHRIS HAS EARNED HIS WAY INTO
THE FINAL THREE IN AN HISTORIC
MOVE.
STILL TO COME, YOUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE PREMIER OF "WINNERS AT
WAR."
>> Jeff: SO IMAGINE YOU'RE
PLAYING "SURVIVOR" AND YOUR GAME
IS IN TROUBLE AND THE ONE THING
THAT CAN SAVE YOU IS HIDDEN
SOMEWHERE IN A DENSE JUNGLE.
>> THERE'S SMALL, INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY IDOL HIDDEN IN THE
WOODS.
>> IMMUNITY IDOL, WHERE WOULD
YOU BE?
>> PEOPLE WHO FIND IDOLS IN THIS
GAME ARE THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
WORKING HARDEST.
>> DING, DING, DING.
>> BREAKING NEWS, ANOTHER IDOL
FOUND.
>> YOU KNOW HOW POWERFUL THAT
IS?
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
POWERFUL THAT IS?
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT TO PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF?
>> A NEW SPECIAL ONE.
>> MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME,
BETTER BE SAFE THAN SORRY.
>> I GOT IT.
>> Jeff: THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> HOLY HELL.
>> ALL RIGHT, BABY.
>> Jeff: HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOLS
WERE INTRODUCED IN OUR 11th
SEASON, "SURVIVOR: GUATEMALA"
BACK IN 2005.
IN THE HANDS OF A GREAT PLAYER,
THEY CAN CHANGE THE COURSE OF AN
ENTIRE GAME.
PERHAPS THE MOST ICONIC IDOL
MOMENT HAPPENED IN OUR 20th
SEASON WHEN WE BROUGHT TOGETHER
OUR MOST POPULAR HEROES AND
NOTORIOUS VILLAINS.
WITH SO MANY DANGEROUS PLAYERS,
THERE WAS NOWHERE TO HIDE.
MAKING IDOLS OF PARAMOUNT
IMPORTANCE.
AN PUTTING BIG MOVES ON
EVERYONE'S MIND.
>> YOU DON'T HAND THE ENEMY THE
IDOL.
>> Jeff: AT THE MERGE, NUMBERS
HAD DWINDLED, BUT THE RIVALRIES
REMAINED THE SAME.
FIVE HEROES VERSUS FIVE
VILLAINS.
>> ONCE WE MERGE, NO ONE WAS
TALKING TO ME.
THEY WERE LOOKING AT ME AS THEIR
NUMBER-ONE TARGET, BUT RUSSELL
MADE ME A PROMISE THAT HE'S
GOING TO GIVE ME HIS IDOL
BECAUSE HE DOES NOT KNOW THAT I
ALREADY HAVE AN IDOL.
OH, YOU.
GIVE ME A HUG.
NOW, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO WITH
MY TWO IDOLS?
THE FIRST ORDER OF ATTACK IS
LET'S FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING
ON ON THE HEROES SIDE.
SO I GO AND TALK TO MY OLD
FRIEND AMANDA.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE IT'S
NOT ME THAT GOES.
>> WELL, YOU BETTER PLAY THAT
THING JUST IN CASE.
>> I WAS LISTENING TO HER, AND
I'M LIKE, YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
THE HEROES KNOW THAT I HAVE AN
IDOL, SO THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
VOTE FOR ME, BECAUSE IT COULD
VERY EASILY BACKFIRE ON THEM.
DANIELLE IS SAFE BECAUSE SHE HAS
THE IMMUNITY NECKLACE.
RUSSELL IS SAFE BECAUSE THEY
THINK HE'S WORKING WITH THEM.
SO THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE THAT ARE
NOT SAFE ARE SANDRA AND JERRY.
IN MY MIND THE ONLY WAY THAT I
CAN MAKE IT ALL THE WAY TO THE
END OF THIS GAME IS IF OUR GROUP
SURVIVES THIS DEADLOCK.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT THE PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF?
I THINK IT WOULD BE DOWNRIGHT
DEPRESSING ABOUT MY DEBAUCH
ROUSE LITTLE VILLAIN, SO,
SANDRA, FOR YOU.
>> GET OUT OF HERE?
FOR REAL?
>> AND, JEFF, I WOULD JUST LIKE
TO INCREASE OUR ODDS, SO JERI,
THAT ONE IS FOR YOU, TOO.
>> Jeff: FIRST VOTE, JEFF
JERI, DOES NOT COUNT.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT AND
THE THIRD MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
J.T.
>> Jeff: WITH THAT ONE MOVE,
PARVATI SET THE REST OF THE GAME
IN MOTION, DIPPING THE SCALES IN
FAVOR OF THE VILLAINS AND
OPENING THE DOOR FOR SANDRA TO
BECOME FIRST AND ONLY TWO-TIME
WINNER.
THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR: HEROES
VERSUS VILLAINS," SANDRA.
IN SEASON 15, JAMES LEARNED THE
HARD WAY THAT KNOWING WHAT TO DO
WITH IDOLS IS JUST AS IMPORTANT
AS FINDING THEM.
>> I'M GOING TO TRIBAL WITH TWO
IDOLS.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> I LOOK IN JAMES' BAG AND
THERE WAS TWO OF THEM.
>> AND HE'S THE GUY FAVORED TO
WIN EVERY CHALLENGE FROM HERE
OUT.
>> THERE'S NO OTHER CHANCE THAN
TO GET RID OF HIM.
>> HE DOESN'T EXPECT IT RIGHT
NOW.
>> HE'S THE ULTIMATE THREAT.
>> Jeff: IF ANYONE HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL, NOW WOULD
BE THE TIME TO PLAY IT.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
JAMES.
>> I HAVE TWO IDOLS.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE PLAYED
THEM.
I'M KIND OF DISAPPOINTED IN
MYSELF.
YOU CAN'T BE ANGRY WITH ANYBODY.
IT'S A GAME.
THEY PLAYED THEIR BEST HAND.
THEY DID WHAT THEY WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO.
I ROLLED THE DICE TOO MANY TIMES
AND I GOT CAUGHT UP.
>> Jeff: TENTH PERSON VOTED
OUT AND THE FOURTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY, JAMES.
AS IDOLS BECAME MORE ESSENTIAL,
FINDING T-EM BECAME MORE URGENT.
RUSSELL CHANGED THE GAME WHEN HE
STARTED LOOKING FOR IDOLS
WITHOUT A CLUE.
>> THESE PEOPLE ARE SOIC
NORNGHTD.
I'M IN A BIG OLD HOLE IN A TREE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SUSPICIOUS.
SO I LOOK IN THE TREE, I LOOK
UP.
I ALMOST PASSED OUT.
A WONDERFUL IMMUNITY IDOL.
BACK TOBOOYAH!
THAT EASY.
I JUST FOUND A SECOND HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL WITHOUT A CLUE.
THERE IT IS.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M ENJOYING.
THIS I'M HAVING MORE FUN NOW
THAN I'VE EVER HAD.
THIS GETTING WAY TOO EASY.
>> Jeff: RUSSELL MADE IT LOOK
EASY, BUT FINDING IDOLS IS FAR
FROM IT, ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY'RE
HIDDEN WHERE YOU'D NEVER EXPECT.
>> IN SEASON 31 OF "SURVIVOR,"
"SECOND CHANCE," I NEVER FOUND
AN IDOL BEFORE.
CONGRATULATION, YOU HAVE FOUND A
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR NEXT
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE IS MY HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
THIS IS NOT AN IDOL.
YOU HAVE TO PICK UP YOUR IDOL
WHEN 19 PEOPLE ARE WATCHING YOU.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> IN "SECOND CHANCE," THE
PUBLIC HAD TO VOTE FOR US, AND
BECAUSE THE AUDIENCE VOTED ME
IN, I WANTED TO PLAY FOR THEM.
I WANTED THEM TO BE PROUD, AND I
JUST WANTED TO GIVE THEM A GOOD
SHOW.
SO IT WAS LIKE EXTRA PRESSURE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> IN THE CHALLENGE, IT WAS SO
MUCH GOING ON.
>> Jeff: JEREMY WORKING ON THE
LOCK NOW.
UNLOCK THAT CHEST AND GET IT ON
THE CART.
>> BUT YOUR HEART IS RACING.
YOU WANT TO DO WELL IN THE
CHALLENGE, BUT YOU WANT TO GRAB
THIS IDOL.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE SEEN.
IT'S A WHOLE LOT GOING ON IN
YOUR MIND.
>> WATCH THE WHEEL.
>> JEREMY?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I KNEELED DOWN AND I GRABBED IT
AND I PUT IT RIGHT IN MY PANTS.
AND IT WAS LIKE, OH, I GOT IT.
I LOVE IT.
>> Jeff: AND WITH HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOLS BECOMING SUCH A
BIG PART OF THE GAME, THE ART OF
MAKING AND HIDING A FAKE IDOL IS
REACHING NEW LEVELS OF
SOPHISTICATION.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO CREATE A
FAKE IDOL.
GOD, I HOPE SOMEONE FINDS IT AND
TRIES TO PLAY IT.
HERE WE GO, BABY.
IT'S PRETTY INCREDIBLE.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE THEY'RE
VOTING FOR ME.
>> THAT'S NOT THE IDOL.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
>> THIS IS NOT A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
>> COME ON.
THAT TOOK HOURS TO MAKE.
>> A FAKE IMMUNITY IDOL CAN
REALLY MESS UP SOMEONE'S GAME.
I NEED TO FIND THIS IDOL.
I'M LOOKING, I'M LOOKING, I'M
LOOKING, AND I SEE AN EMBLEM.
OH, MY GOD, I CAUGHT THE FISH
THAT I WANTED TO CATCH.
JEFF, I'M NOT GOING HOME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THIS IS NOT A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
>> I TOOK TWO FAKE IDOLS AND I
HID THEM.
HOPEFULLY THIS WOULD THROW THEM
OFF THE TRAIL OF THE REAL IDOL
AND GIVE MAE CHANCE TO FIND IT
FIRST.
>> WELL, JEFF, JUST IN CASE I
FOUND A LITTLE SOMETHING THAT
I'D LIKE THE PLAY FOR MYSELF.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS FAKE.
>> JEFF, HERE'S HOPING THIS ONE
IS REAL.
>> Jeff: THIS IDOL IS FAKE.
>> WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING.
ANYBODY ELSE?
>> Jeff: STILL TO COME, FOR
THE FIRST TIME IN 36 SEASONS
"SURVIVOR"...
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Jeff: THIS IS YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT THE TRIBAL COUNCIL FOR
OUR 40th SEASON.
TRIBAL REMAINS THE MOST
DANGEROUS PART OF THE GAME, AND
IT'S BEEN HOME TO SOME OF
"SURVIVOR'S" GREATEST MOMENTS.
IN SEASON 31, "SECOND CHANCE,"
ONE TRIBAL COUNCIL WAS SO CRAZY
WE BROKE IT DOWN AT THE LIVE
REUNION.
ONE OF THE CRAZIEST TRIBAL
COUNCILS EVER, AND I KNOW THERE
ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE AT HOME
RIGHT NOW AND IN THE AUDIENCE,
EVEN SUPER FANS WHO ARE SAYING,
WAIT A MINUTE, WHAT HAPPENED?
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JEFF, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON
TONIGHT, BUT I DON'T TRUST
ANYBODY HERE, SO...
>> Jeff: THIS IS A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR WENTWORTH
WILL NOT COUNT.
>> HOLD ON, JEFFREY.
>> Jeff: THIS IS ALSO A HIDDEN
IMMUNITY IDOL.
ANY VOTES CAST FOR JEREMY WILL
NOT COUNT.
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
>> Jeff: WE COME TO TRIBAL,
SPENCER HAS IMMUNITY.
HE'S SAFE, RIGHT?
WE VOTE.
I ASK, DOES ANYBODY HAVE AN
IDOL.
WENDELL WORTH, YES.
JEREMY, YES.
SO THEY'RE ALL SAFE.
WENDELL WORTH, DOES NOT COUNT.
JEREMY, WILL NOT COUNT.
>> WHAT THE HELL, GUYS?
>> Jeff: WE DID OUR HISTORIC
THING WHERE NO VALID VOTES CAST.
THAT BLEW EVERYBODY'S MIND.
WE STILL HAVE TO VOTE SOMEBODY
OUT, SO WE'LL REVOTE AND START
OVER.
NOW YOU CAN ONLY VOTE FOR KIMMI,
TASHA, AND KEITH.
TASHA, THAT'S THREE VOTES TASHA,
THREE VOTES KIMMI.
KIMMI.
WE'RE TIED AGAIN.
WE HAVE ANOTHER TIE.
THESE TWO HAVE VOTES.
I ASK, ANYBODY WANT TO CHANGE
THEIR VOTES?
>> I'M GOOD WITH MY VOTE.
>> I'M NOT CHANGING MY VOTE.
>> I'M GOOD WITH MINE.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> Jeff: WE'RE DEADLOCKED.
THIS IS WHERE IT GETS
INTERESTING, PER THE RULES OF
"SURVIVOR," IF YOU CAN'T COME TO
UNANIMOUS DECISION, THEN KIMMI
AND TASHA BECOME SAFE.
THAT WOULD MEAN KEITH, BY
DEFAULT, YOU WOULD GO HOME.
>> THAT'S A HECK OF A WAY TO HIT
THE HIGHWAY.
>> WOULD YOU RATHER KEITH GO
HOME OR KIMMI?
>> KIM PI.
>> Jeff: SPENCER AND JEREMY,
YOU'RE SAYING IT'S KIMMI.
>> CORRECT.
SO ARE WENDELL WORTH AND KEITH
GOING TO JOIN YOU AGAINST KIMMI?
>> I THINK HE NEEDS TO STAY
>> SURE.
I'LL STAY.
>> SPENCER, WHO DO YOU SAY?
>> KIMMI.
>> KEITH?
>> WHAT A CRAZY TRIBAL.
>> Jeff: THAT'S REASON NUMBER
322 WHY SURVIVOR IS SO TOUGH TO
WIN.
VOTING OUT AN ALLY IS NEVER
EASY, BUT IN OUR 27th
SEASON, "BLOOD VS. WATER,"
THINGS WERE MADE MORE
COMPLICATED WHEN CIERA PLAYED
AGAINST HER OWN MOTHER.
>> WE HAVE A GOOD RELATIONSHIP,
AND I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING THAT'S GOING TO BLOW
YOUR MIND...
>> YOU'RE GOING TO VOTE MY MOM.
I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO AT THIS POINT.
>> Jeff: THERE IS ONLY ONE
PAIR LOVED ONES LEFT, THEY ARE
BLOOD, MOTHER, DAUGHTER.
>> THEY WILL PROBABLY HAVE A
SIMILAR MIND AND SWING THE SAME
WAY.
SINCE DAY ONE WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
AT THAT.
>> Jeff: IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO VOTE
MY MOM OUT.
I CAME INTO THIS WANTING TO SIT
AT THE END WITH MY MOM, BUT MY
HEART IS BEING TUGGED BECAUSE
NOBODY WANTS TO DO THAT, I LOVE
MY MOM, AND I DON'T WANT HER TO
THINK THAT I DON'T WANT HER TO
SUCCEED IN THE GAME, BUT I MEAN,
I WANT TO SUCCEED IN THE GAME.
>> Jeff: FIRST VOTE LAURA.
LAURA.
11th PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: BLOOD VERSUS WATER,."
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Jeff: IN "SURVIVOR: GAME
CHANGERS" AN UNPRECEDENTED
NUMBER OF ADVANTAGES TURNED WHAT
LOOKED LIKE A STRAIGHT-FORWARD
VOTE INTO AN ASTONISHING TRIBAL
TRIBAL MOMENT.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT TO PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
>> JEFF, I WOULD LIKE THE PLAY
THIS IDOL FOR MYSELF.
I HAVE ANOTHER ONE, I WOULD LIKE
THE PLAY FOR AUBRY.
>> HEY, JEFF, I'VE GOT A LEGACY
ADVANTAGE.
THERE YOU GO.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
>> JEFF?
[LAUGHTER]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I WANT TO GET ON THE IMMUNITY
TRAIN AND GIVE YOU THAT.
>> Jeff: SO ANY VOTES CAST FOR
TODD, AUBRY, SARAH, TROYZAN WILL
NOT COUNT.
YOU COULD NOT VOTE FOR
CULPEPPER.
HE HAD IMMUNITY, WHICH MEANS
CIRIE...
>> IT'S ME.
>> Jeff: AND FOR WHAT IT'S
WORTH, NOT A SINGLE VOTE IN HERE
HAS YOUR NAME ON IT.
THIS IS AN HISTORIC TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU BECOME THE FIRST PERSON IN
34 SEASONS TO BE VOTED OUT
SIMPLY BECAUSE THERE LITERALLY
IS NO OTHER CHOICE.
>> I'M GOING OUT IN GRAND TRIAL.
IT NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE.
>> Jeff: CIRIE, I HAVE TO SAY,
YOU HAVE PLAYED EVERY DAY OF
"SURVIVOR" WITH GRACE, AND IT
HAS BEEN AN HONOR TO HAVE YOU BE
A PART OF THE "SURVIVOR" FAMILY.
[APPLAUSE]
CIRIE, YOU WANT TO SAY IT?
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> Jeff: IN OUR 36th
SEASON, DOM AND WENDELL STARTED
AN ALLIANCE.
>> THERE'S THIS GUY DOM.
I STARTED FEELING GOOD VIBES
FROM HIM.
HE SEEMS LIKE A FRIENDLY GUY.
>> Jeff: THAT GREW INTO ONE OF
THE STRONGEST PARTNERSHIPS WE'VE
EVER SEEN.
>> LEADING TO THE MOST DRAMATIC
FINAL VOTE IN "SURVIVOR"
HISTORY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO READ THE VOTES.
>> WHAT?
>> Jeff: FIRST VOTE, DOMENICK.
WENDELL.
DOMENICK.
THAT'S FIVE VOTES DOMENICK, FOUR
VOTES WENDELL, ONE VOTE LEFT.
WENDELL.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 36 SEASONS
OF "SURVIVOR," WE HAVE A TIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
HERE'S WHAT HAPPENS.
LAUREL, YOU BECOME THE 11th
AND FINAL MEMBER OF OUR JURY,
AND YOU WILL CAST THE DECIDING
VOTE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR: GHOST ISLAND,"
WENDELL.
IN OUR 16th SEASON, "FANS
VS. FAVORITES," THE WOMEN WERE
RUNNING THE GAME.
>> FIETS BLACK WIDOW BRIGADE.
ALL THE GIRLS ARE SPINNING THE
GUYS AROUND AS MUCH AS WE CAN SO
THEY DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY IS UP,
AND THEN WE'RE DEVOURING THEM
ONE AT A TIME.
>> THE ONLY THING STANDING IN
THEIR WAY WAS SUPER FAN.
>> Eric: .
>> Jeff: ERIC WINS IMMUNITY
ONCE AGAIN.
BUT THE WOMEN WOULD STOP AT
NOTHING IN THEIR QUEST FOR A
FINAL FOUR.
>> ERIK'S GUARANTEED FINAL FOUR.
HE'S WALKING AROUND FEELING HIGH
ON LIFE.
MEANWHILE, THE WOMEN ARE SITTING
ON THE EDGE OF THE BEACH KIND OF
SAD, AND CIRIE LOOKS OVER AT ME
AND GOES...
>> I WONDER IF HE WOULD GIVE US
HIS NECKLACE.
>> NO.
WE COULDN'T?
COULD WE DO THAT?
>> I MEAN, I'LL TRY IT.
I'LL SAY I TALKED TO CIRIE ABOUT
IT.
>> I HAVE TO SEE HIM SAVE YOU
BUT TO BELIEVE HE'LL VOTE AMANDA
BECAUSE OF ALL THE STUFF HE'S
BEEN SAYING.
>> PERFECT.
>> THIS WOULD BE THE HEIST OF
ALL HEIST.
IN ORDER TO PULL THIS OFF, EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF US HAS THE PLAY
OUR PART PERFECTLY.
>> I HAVE THE MOST HAIR BRAIN
IDEA.
>> HAIR BRAIN.
I CAN RELATE.
>> YOU GIVER ME YOUR NECKLACE.
>> I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO
CONSIDER THAT.
>> JUST HEAR ME OUT.
>> YOU GIVE ME YOUR NECKLACE
TONIGHT, TERESA SAID HANDS DOWN
SHE'LL VOTE FOR AMANDA.
>> NATALIE IS THROWING THE BAIT
IN TO SEE WHAT KIND OF BAIT SHE
CAN GET.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A PIVOTAL
MOVE IF YOU WANT A JURY VOTE.
>> NOW ERIK HAS THE SEED
PLANTED, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN
WIN BECAUSE PEOPLE AREN'T GOING
TO RESPECT YOU.
>> WHAT'S THE PROBLEM WITH ME
KEEPING IMMUNITY AND STILL
VOTING AMANDA?
>> BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW IF I
WOULD BELIEVE THAT YOU WOULD
VOTE AMANDA.
>> RIGHT.
>> CIRIE'S ROLE IS TO TALK TO
ERIK LIKE A MOTHER WOULD TALK TO
A SON.
ERIK, ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER THAN
WORDS.
>> IF YOU WERE TO SAVE NAT,THEN
I WOULD BELIEVE YOU, AND THAT
WOULD CONVINCE ME THAT WE'RE ALL
GOING TO VOTE AMANDA.
>> IN MY MIND WE'RE GOING TO
TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND IT'S STILL
SUPER FAR-FETCHED, BUT EVERYONE
IS PRIMED AND READY TO EXECUTE.
AND I AM BAD COP.
>> I HEARD ABOUT ERIK RUNNING
AROUND AND MAKING ALLIANCES WITH
EVERY SINGLE PERSON AND THEN
BREAKING ALLIANCE AND SWITCHING
BACK UP AND SWITCHING BECOME
OVER WHEN HE DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO
DO THAT.
HE HAD WON IMMUNITY.
HE'S JUST LOST A LOT OF
RESPECTED AMONG THE WOMEN HERE.
>> I'M LYING LAYING INTO HIM IN
FRONT OF THE JURY, AND IT SEEMS
LIKE HE'S ACTUALLY STARTING TO
CONSIDER HE MIGHT NOT HAVE THE
RESPECT OF HIS IDOLS.
>> YOU'VE BEEN DISCREDITED, THE
WORDS YOU SAY MEAN ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING.
IT'S YOUR ACTIONS THAT WILL SHOW
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
>> HE HAS TO DO SOMETHING TO
REDEEM HIMSELF, AND THE BEST
THING THAT HE CAN DO TO REDEEM
HIMSELF IS TO SHOW THAT HE'S
LOYAL TO SOMEONE IN THIS GAME.
>> I WANT TO GIVE INDIVIDUAL
IMMUNITY TO NATALIE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
WE PULLED OFF THE IMPOSSIBLE.
WE DID IT.
>> Jeff: SUDDENLY, NATALIE,
YOU ARE SAFE.
>> IT WAS BEYOND BELIEF.
THIS WAS THE GREATEST GIRL POWER
MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
>> Jeff: 13th PERSON VOTED
OUT AND THE SIXTH MEMBER OF OUR
JURY, ERIK.
>> MY BIGGEST TAKEAWAY WAS HOW
MUCH EVERYONE NEEDED TO PLAY
THEIR PART IN ORDER FOR
SOMETHING LIKE THIS TO WORK.
>> Jeff: ERIK, THE TRIBE HAS
SPOKEN.
>> IN THE GAME OF "SURVIVOR,"
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A SENSE OF I'M
CAPABLE OF PULLING OFF THINGS
THAT ARE ABSOLUTELY IMPOSSIBLE.
>> Jeff: I THINK THAT IS WHAT
YOU CALL A LIFE LESSON.
UP NEXT, YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
"SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT WAR."
>> Jeff: WELL, IT'S CLEAR,
GREAT MOMENTS COME FROM GREAT
PLAYERS.
TO CELEBRATE OUR 40th
SEASON, WE'RE BRINGING BACK 20
OF THE GREATEST WINNERS WHO WILL
BATTLE IT OUT FOR THE LARGEST
PRIZE IN REALITY SHOW HISTORY,
$2 MILLION.
HERE'S YOUR FIRST SNEAK PEEK AT
"SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT WAR."
GO!
YOU BETTER BE READY
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BIG BATTLE
I'M COMING FOR YOU
LIKE THE DAYS, 20 WINNERS.
EVERYBODY WANTS ITS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
YOU ARE WITNESSING 16 AMERICANS
BEGIN AN ADVENTURE THAT WILL
FOREVER CHANGE THEIR LIVES.
THE NEXT 39 DAYS, THEY'LL BE
MAROONED, LEFT TO FEND FOR
THEMSELVES.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEY'RE VOTED OFF.
IN THE END ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
AND WILL LEAVE THE ISLAND WITH
$1 MILLION IN CASH AS THEIR
REWARD.
>> I HAVE A BIG REPUTATION IN
"SURVIVOR," BUT SEEING MY
COMPETITORS, I'M LIKE, OH, MAN.
FANS OF FOOTBALL WAIT ALL YEAR
TO SEE THE SUPER BOWL AT THE
END.
FANS OF "SURVIVOR" HAVE BEEN
WAITING 20 YEARS TO SEE "WINNERS
AT WAR."
>> I HAVEN'T HAD AN OPPORTUNITY
TO BE MY DIABOLICAL SELF.
I'VE BEEN BUSY BUILDING A
FAMILY.
BUT I'M LIKE A PHOENIX RISING
FROM THE ASHES, READY TO BURN
DOWN YOUR HOUSE.
>> I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
HODGKIN'S LIMB LYMPHOMA.
I REMEMBER DREAMING AND PRAYING
THAT I WOULD BE ALIVE LONG
ENOUGH TO PLAY "SURVIVOR" AGAIN.
SO IT IS A MIRACLE THAT I'M
SITTING HERE TODAY.
>> I WAS A KID THE FIRST TIME I
PLAYED THE GAME.
LITTLE DID I KNOW THEY WAS GOING
TO FALL IF LOVE, MEET MY
HUSBAND, GET ENGAGED AT THE
FINALE, WIN THE SHOW, BUT NOW TO
BE BACK FOR SEASON 40, ALL
WINNERS, I WANT TO WIN THE GAME.
TO COME OUT HERE AND WIN TWO
TIMES AND BEAT MY HUSBAND AGAIN,
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IT'S THE BIGGEST
BATTLE IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING TO BE
LAYING IT ALL ON THE LINE.
>> Jeff: WHO WILL HAVE WHAT IT
TAKES TO OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, AND
OUTLAST ALL THE REST?
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A BLOODBATH.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A WAR.
>> Jeff: AND BE CROWNED THE
GREATEST PLAYER OF ALL TIME.
>> LET THE FIREWORKS BEGIN.
>> Jeff: 49 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE,
ONE SURVIVOR.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE THE MEN.
HERE COME THE WOMEN.
>> HERE THEY COME.
HERE THEY COME.
>> THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING.
>> Jeff: YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
WHO YOU ARE PLAYING AGAINST AS
THEY GET THEIR FIRST LOOK AT WHO
THEY ARE PLAYING AGAINST.
>> LOOK AT THEM.
>> WELCOME, LADIES.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
YOU GUYS HIT THE OCEAN YET?
>> I'M SHOCKED TO SEE ROB AND
AMBER.
I SPENT 36 DAYS WITH BOSTON ROB
ON ISLAND OF THE IDOL, AND
BOSTON ROB NEVER TOLD ME THAT HE
WAS PLAYING AGAIN.
AND SO I DEFINITELY FEEL
BETRAYED.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: THE STAGE IS SET FOR
THE BIGGEST BATTLE IN SURVIVOR
HISTORY.
JOIN US NEXT WEEK FOR THE
PREMIER OF "SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT
WAR."