♪ ♪
(crickets chirping)
TONY: Well, good news is that
there's stars out tonight.
-ADAM: Yeah, and a lot.
-So, sky's clear.
MICHELE:
I'm really, really annoyed.
I hate getting blindsided,
to be perfectly honest.
And the fact is is that
I wanted Wendell out.
I wanted him out
since the beginning.
I've told these people that I
was on board with that, and yet
here we are, me blindsided,
on the wrong side
of the votes again.
I feel like déjà vu
from day two.
NICK:
I do, too.
These people are all, like,
bumbling, fumbling idiots.
I can't stand them.
I don't...
-I can't either.
-I-I am over...
Nobody will say a name.
I'm over it.
Do you think
that they want me next?
Your name was
on the block today.
-It was?
-It was between you and Adam.
It could've--
It was probably all a facade.
Every single person
probably knew
-except us.
-Yeah.
I think I'm just
gonna let 'em have it.
-Don't even do that. Don't...
-I'm next anyways.
-What's it matter?
-No, you're not. No, you're not.
Don't sink your own game.
NICK: I feel like Wendell
was kind of the first shot.
This is ruthless and cutthroat,
and...
there's gonna be bloodshed.
And I'm gonna like it.
I'm-I'm gonna get
on that train now,
to where I love blood.
-TONY: Nick, you all right?
-It is what it is, you know?
-Yeah, yeah.
-I'm the only person
that didn't know, man.
-What am I supposed to think?
-MICHELE: I didn't know.
-TONY: Michele didn't know
either, but...
-Well, Michele, but...
But you-you know-- you know--
Sit down, man.
Nick, come on.
You know how
to play the game, man.
You can't--
you can't act like that.
Nobody's coming after you
because we got rid of Wendell.
-All's fair...
-No, but everybody's coming
after me always.
-Always. Every vote.
-No. No.
NICK:
I feel like
it is now my duty to take
every one of these people out
that have double-crossed me.
I'm ready for some revenge.
MICHELE:
I'm okay.
I'm a little pissed,
but I'm okay.
ADAM:
Oh, man.
Tribal Council tonight,
my heart was beating so fast.
(chuckles): Literally,
like, out of my chest.
It was outrageous.
I was so incredibly nervous.
But I'm here.
I'm here.
I'll smile to their face.
I'll tell them it's all kumbaya.
Meanwhile, I think
they're all dingbats.
ADAM:
Right now, Michele is feeling
incredibly low.
But I see it as an opportunity.
I'm not telling
a single other solitary person.
The little thing--
There's a little thing at--
A little sword.
Mm-hmm.
-A little thing like this.
-Mm-hmm.
...but I'm--
I feel very confident
that it is.
I think
that there may be an idol
in Jeff Probst's podium.
I recognize
the fleur-de-lis symbol from
the idol that Denise found,
so the fact that
there is a fleur-de-lis
right in front of us
at Tribal Council
makes me think that that
might actually be a live idol.
In the chance that I'm right,
it'd be a pretty epic way
to save myself.
♪ ♪
YUL:
Whoa.
What do we have here?
"Open when everyone is present."
Anyone order pizza?
-Yes!
-Yeah!
-Kind of small for a pizza box,
-but...
-PARVATI: Is there a token
in there?
-I don't know. It's...
-Cool. Wendell.
-WENDELL: Thank you, sir.
-ROB: What does it say, Yul?
ETHAN:
History?
-So, basically, this means...
-There's something
on top of the mountain.
PARVATI:
When there's something
hidden somewhere.
AMBER:
There's something hidden
somewhere.
So, we got a clue
that said something about
history repeats itself.
So we're all thinking,
"Oh, it's all the past clues
that we've been given
while we're here on the Edge."
It's maybe
the combination boxes,
you know,
maybe it's the trails.
ROB:
Yo, yo, we got to go! The tide!
Step back and assess.
AMBER:
Let's step back and assess
once we get up here.
NATALIE:
We could break off into twos
-or threes, too, guys.
-Yeah.
-NATALIE: What do you think?
-ETHAN: I'm going this trail
-up to the left.
-I'll go with you, Ethan.
NATALIE:
Let's break off.
I'll go with the boys.
WENDELL:
I need to come with somebody.
AMBER:
Yul's got ya.
NATALIE:
You go with Yul.
I'll go with Rob.
WENDELL:
All right.
NATALIE:
Once we were at the top
of the mountain,
I was like, "Let's go
split off into groups,"
because if we find tokens,
I want to spend it
to buy food.
Wendell just had a merge feast,
so he's good.
And Yul just got here.
He hasn't been suffering
like the rest of us.
And so I just wanted
to make sure that Wendell
and Yul are completely left out
of this advantage.
Did you guys check out
this tree?
DANNI:
"History repeats itself."
Would it be something
from the last time
they had Edge of Extinction?
PARVATI:
Oh, maybe.
Where did they find it?
Aubry found one at the steps.
"Step back, assess, 'cause
history will repeat itself."
-Yep.
-'Cause that's what Aubry did.
That's exactly what it is,
isn't it?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
DANNI: As a fan, the wheels
started turning, and I thought,
"Maybe this is something from
a past season on Extinction"--
when Aubry stepped back
and looked up at the steps
and found where the clue was.
This is mine.
So, it's, like--
See these little holes here?
Oh, got it.
I got it, I got it,
-I got it, I got it.
-Oh, yes. Yes. Yes.
Okay, come over here.
Yes.
Oh, my God! I did something!
Survivor--
I'm playing the game!
-Here, open the clue.
-Yes.
PARVATI:
I feel like a mouse
trapped on
this mouse experiment.
And finding the prize
was, like, my piece of cheese.
-Oh!
-Oh! Now you go.
Wow.
It was, like,
a safe or unsafe coin.
And if you flip and it lands
on "safe," you have immunity.
That's huge.
-Okay, what do you think?
-Should we sell it to Michele?
-She has the most fire tokens.
-And get money
-to buy our food?
-Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
-Like, should we sell it
for four tokens?
-Okay.
Somebody's coming down.
Oh, here they come.
Shh, shh.
PARVATI:
For a moment, I was thinking
we could keep this
just between us
and then we could have
a jar of peanut butter
just for me and Danni.
(chuckles)
Did you guys find anything?
AMBER:
No!
ROB:
You guys have it?
-PARVATI: All right,
let's tell 'em.
-Okay.
PARVATI:
But then I was thinking...
-ROB: They got it.
-...I've got people out here
who I trust,
and a lot of people
have been here
way longer than me.
So I'm like--
My heart just can't
not want them in on the secret.
They could win immunity.
-At Tribal Council.
-But we-we have to
-sell it to someone.
-Now we have to sell it
to someone in the game.
I know that you can buy
peanut butter with fire tokens,
and we have six people
in our group
who are looking
to eat something.
♪ Calm before the storm ♪
♪ Get ready for the thunder. ♪
♪ ♪
Come on in, guys!
All right, let's get
to today's reward challenge.
For today's challenge, you'll be
divided into two teams of five.
On my go,
you'll swim out and retrieve
a net filled with wooden fish.
You'll untie those fish,
put 'em on a pole,
get the pole to the finish,
and you will use the fish
to solve a puzzle.
First team to finish
wins reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Of course.
-Oh, yeah.
PROBST:
A little taste of home.
Chinese takeout.
-Oh!
-(chuckles): Oh, yeah.
-PROBST: Waiting for you
back at camp.
-Ooh.
We're gonna do
a schoolyard pick.
There are 11 of you.
Only ten will run.
That means one won't.
-Wow.
-War is not pretty.
Let's do this.
♪ ♪
All right,
we have our two teams.
Running for Red,
it is Tyson,
Adam and Tony in the water.
And on the puzzle,
Nick and Jeremy,
who was the captain.
He chose this team.
Running for Blue,
Kim was the captain.
She has Sarah and Ben
with her in the water,
and she put Sophie and Michele
on the puzzle.
Denise was not chosen.
No shot at reward.
Let's see who chose
the best team.
For reward, survivors ready?
Go!
♪ ♪
First, it is a race
to your fish.
Got to untie that net
and get it back to shore.
Tyson first there.
Ben is there.
Once you have all the knots,
start pulling it back to shore.
Ben has one side down.
Kim has the other.
-Blue's good.
-Go, go, go, go, go.
-Red's free. They're good.
-Let's go, guys!
PROBST:
Now comes the heavy lifting.
The net and those wooden fish
weigh a lot.
There are 14 of them.
-You good? Let's go.
-MICHELE: Good job, guys!
PROBST:
You got to drag it
all the way back to shore.
It is Blue out
to the early lead.
Tony, Tyson and Adam
trying to stay in it.
-Clear!
-PROBST: Blue, you're good.
Red, you're good.
Now you've got to untie the fish
and put 'em on the hooks.
Adam gonna hang for Red.
Sarah starts to hook the fish.
Adam hooks another piece.
Tyson has another piece untied.
Blue, you're good.
Head out.
Blue still in the lead.
DENISE:
Go!
Red down to their last piece.
Got one left.
Got to get it on there.
-You're good. Go, Red.
-TONY: Go!
-Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-KIM: (grunts) Pick it up.
MICHELE:
Go, guys, go, go, go.
PROBST: Once you get it up here,
puzzle solvers take over.
You're good.
You guys are good.
You're good, Red.
-Soph, you want to start?
-Let's start.
It's Michele and Sophie working
on the puzzle for Blue.
Jeremy and Nick for Red.
All these pieces
will fit in flush.
You will know when you have it,
and you'll know
when it's not right.
This is a puzzle
that will come together quickly,
and, out of nowhere,
you will have it.
Nice job.
Fit just like this one.
PROBST:
Two teams picked by two people,
Jeremy and Kim.
That's good.
-That's good. No.
-This one fit somewhere?
PROBST:
Red thinks they're getting
somewhere close.
One piece left to fit.
Where does it go?
Nick moves another piece around.
Is this the right combination?
-(groans)
-That's not right.
Yep.
Nick and Jeremy are gonna swap
pieces out now.
Sophie liking
what she's seeing over here.
Michele trying
to put in another piece.
Will it fit?
Is it right?
Another swap.
-(cheering)
-And they have it!
-Kim, Sophie, Sarah...
-BEN: Good job, girls.
-...Michele and Ben win the war.
-Good job, girls. Mwah! Yes.
Chinese takeout waiting for you
back at camp.
I don't know
what we were doing wrong, dude.
All right,
Sarah, Kim, Ben, Michele,
Sophie, waiting for you back
at camp, Chinese takeout.
-Grab your stuff,
head out, enjoy.
-Jeff.
Can I give up my reward
to someone?
-Really?
-Yeah.
Sure.
-Thank you so much.
-Happy birthday, Nick.
-KIM: That's sweet, Sarah.
-Oh, thank you.
-(applause)
-KIM: Welcome.
PROBST:
So, Sarah, you're fighting
for $2 million in this game,
and you gave this up to Nick
because it's his birthday?
I'm giving it up, but
I'd rather see him happy than...
me miserable,
'cause I'll eat too much.
So, I hope you feel miserable.
-(chuckling)
-I'll do my best.
-SOPHIE: Good job, Sarah.
-PROBST: All right.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Denise, you can join 'em.
ADAM:
Sarah made a mistake
by switching out with Nick.
Look, Sarah came
into this game
with quite a reputation.
The way she played
Game Changers,
she blindsided friends
left and right.
So if Sarah's move puts
a bigger target
on her back, fine with me.
I don't trust her
as far as I can throw her.
And I can't throw very far.
♪ ♪
NICK:
I'm so sorry, Sarah.
-I will pay you back.
-No, no. It's--
-I didn't do it to be paid back.
-I know you didn't.
SARAH:
I gave Nick my reward
as a human being
to human being. There was--
No gameplay was in it.
It was
a complete genuine decision.
We're gonna go out where we ate
the merge feast, guys.
SARAH:
Nick's birthday was yesterday.
Nick got completely blindsided
yesterday.
-Bye, guys.
-SARAH: This game
is very tough.
We're all away from our loved
ones. He just got engaged.
So I hope
it taught everybody a lesson.
Just as a world,
we can be nicer to each other.
What did you do, man?
What? It's okay.
-No, Sarah.
-Yes.
-I'm not-- I'm not scolding you
or preaching to you.
-Yeah. No.
-I'm just giving you my opinion.
-I-I personally think
-it was the right move.
-Okay.
TONY: Wow. Sarah got caught up
in the moment,
and that one moment on Survivor
is what costs you the game
sometimes,
when you can't get out
of that emotional,
realistic, humane moment
to be that barbaric survivor
that you need to be.
You won, you were happy,
and you became human.
-You know what I mean?
And that's what, you know...
-Yeah, I know.
And then everybody's
probably saying,
-"That was a strategic move
on Sarah's part."
-No.
-"Sarah's playing a great game."
-That's fine. That's fine.
"Sarah's got to go."
Because I gave up a reward?
That's how it happens.
ADAM:
Why were you help...
-Of course, of course.
-Right?
Of course, of course.
-Of course, of course.
-Yeah. For real.
-Like, yeah.
A horse is a horse, of course.
JEREMY:
Sarah gives up her reward
and gives it to Nick,
one of the main guys
I want to talk to
because he's on the outs.
I'm like, "Come on, Sarah."
And I've done that before.
I've given up reward.
And you know what they did?
They voted me out.
After that move,
what she just did right there...
-Yeah.
-...I think that's the move.
BEN:
Kim, thank you for picking me.
Thank you for picking me.
BEN:
Look at this.
NICK:
Sarah gives me the reward.
And I appreciated it, but...
I don't feel like
I owe her anything.
I don't trust her
any more than I already did,
and it wasn't much,
because I know
the game Sarah plays.
And if Sarah was told to write
down my name tonight, she would.
KIM:
You just, like...
NICK:
But, hopefully, there are
some clues hidden somewhere
for a hidden immunity idol
or a Steal a Vote advantage
or something.
And hopefully I can find it.
Should we, like,
open all the fortune cookies?
-BEN: Oh, yeah.
-We should.
-(Michele chuckles)
-BEN: Here we go.
-KIM: Well, this is it.
Yeah.
Everyone can go around.
"Your skill will accomplish
what the force
of many others cannot."
NICK:
Mm. (chuckles)
"You will make changes
for the better."
(chuckles)
MICHELE:
Okay.
Aw.
MICHELE:
This game has been such
an emotional roller coaster.
Last night was a seriously
low point in the game for me.
And then, this morning, I
received Wendell's fire token,
which puts me
at four fire tokens.
And I think that makes me
the richest person out here.
So, I get back to camp
and I notice something
in my bag.
So I scurry off
and I pull out...
♪ Dun, dun, dun ♪
This beautiful
50/50 coin advantage. (chuckles)
Okay.
Oh, my God.
That's all my fire tokens.
This coin is 50/50,
and I truly feel 50/50
on whether or not
I should take the advantage.
Let's see what happens.
(laughs) I want to see
how many times I can get "safe."
"Not safe." 50/50.
(laughs)
Living up to its name.
But...
at the reward today,
we had fortune cookies.
And two of mine were,
"As the purse is emptied,
the heart is filled."
And the other is, "Don't be
afraid of taking that big step."
All right, well,
since you're not gonna help,
I'm gonna have to do it alone.
So now I feel like
the Survivor gods came down
and put these fortunes
in my fortune cookie to say,
"Michele, jump on this
"and get yourself
some god-darn power
in this game of Survivor."
So I'm gonna
trade in my four fire tokens
for this beautiful advantage.
Wow.
♪ ♪
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first,
Denise, Jeremy,
got to take back the necklaces.
-Thank you.
-Yep.
Once again,
individual immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna balance
on a triangular platform,
with your feet perched
on very narrow footholds.
At regular intervals,
we'll move up,
making it more difficult.
If you fall off, you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
safe from the vote.
In addition, earns a fire token.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the 11th person
voted out of Survivor:
Winners at War.
Draw for spots.
We'll get started.
♪ ♪
All right.
Here we go.
For immunity.
Everybody put your feet
on that first bottom perch.
Try to find a spot
for your toes.
Here we go.
Everybody stand
into your first position
and let go.
And this challenge is on.
And already it is difficult.
There's nothing to hold on to.
Very little room for your toes.
We will be in this spot
for five minutes.
(grunts)
Michele suddenly just drops,
loses her balance.
Michele is first out.
Swim over.
Michele, no shot
at immunity tonight.
-Ah.
-PROBST:
Jeremy with a nice save.
Denise with a nice recovery.
No, Denise can't save it.
Denise is out.
We are down to nine.
On day 23,
there is nobody
that doesn't want immunity.
♪ ♪
(groans)
15 seconds left in this round.
Get through this,
you get to reset.
Jeremy with another nice save.
Five seconds left in this round.
Jeremy struggling to hang on.
-You are safe. You can sit down.
-(groans)
(groaning, sighing)
You have survived round one.
-ADAM: Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God. (hisses)
-So hard.
-(exhales)
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right,
everybody move your feet
one perch higher now
for round two.
It's gonna be
a lot more difficult.
All right,
I'm gonna count you in,
and you got to be up
when we get to one.
Five,
four, three,
two, one.
Everybody let go.
And we are back on.
We'll be here for ten minutes.
(creaking)
Tyson drops. He's out.
-(shouting)
-Jeremy with another nice save.
(shouts)
That is how you stay alive
in this game.
(whimpers)
(groaning)
Jeremy can't hang anymore.
Jeremy's out,
with one of
the craziest dismounts ever.
(laughter)
That wind's starting
to pick up now.
It's already tough enough
out there.
-Tony with a wobble.
-(exhales)
Saves it.
-(groans)
-Tony can't hang in there
anymore.
-Tony is out.
-DENISE: So close.
PROBST:
We're down to six--
three women and three men.
-(exhales)
-PROBST: It is Sophie,
Sarah, Kim, Nick,
Adam and Ben.
-(grunts)
-Season called Winners at War,
you have to assume
everybody's coming for you.
It is a war.
♪ Winners at war,
hungry for more ♪
♪ Winners at war ♪
♪ Winners at war,
hungry for more ♪
♪ Winners at war ♪
♪ They're coming for you. ♪
Ten seconds left
in this section.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
You are good.
Everybody can sit down.
You've made it through
the second section.
Good job, guys!
(exhales)
PROBST:
All right, everybody move
to the top
of the triangular platform.
You're gonna have
both feet now on the top.
Let everybody get settled.
I will count you in,
and we'll be back on.
This could go quickly.
Adam really struggling
to even get in position to begin
this final section
of the challenge.
All right, Adam.
You got to give it a go.
Here we go.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
-Adam, you're out.
-Damn it.
-(Sophie yelps)
-PROBST: Sophie is out.
Nick is out.
We're down to three.
It is Sarah, Kim and Ben.
-Sarah's out. We're down to two.
-Stay.
Stay.
-PROBST: It is Kim and Ben
fighting for immunity.
Both now got their legs.
Dig in right here. Let's go!
Find it!
These are the kind of showdowns
you want on Survivor.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
(Kim mutters)
(Ben grunting)
(screams)
PROBST:
Ben loses it!
-Kim wins individual immunity!
-(applause)
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
-Cannot be voted out
of this game.
-MICHELE: Good job, Ben.
That was awesome.
-Good job, Kim.
-Wow.
Kim, come on over.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
-Ah.
-Oh.
-And in addition...
-I do want that. (laughs)
-...a fire token is yours.
-Thank you. Thanks.
-(Michele chuckles)
-PROBST: Have a seat.
DENISE:
Nice job.
As for the rest of you,
after 23 days,
somebody voted out tonight,
sent to the Edge of Extinction.
Swim out.
-See you tonight at Tribal.
-Yes, sir.
TONY:
My big concern from day one was
that the lower-profile players,
as I would call
the hyenas of the game,
will all start coming after
the higher-profile players
and pick us off one by one.
So right now I want to try
to get rid of the hyenas
because they're gonna wait
for the lions to go at it,
and then they're gonna come in
and clean up shop.
♪ ♪
KIM: Feels amazing to have
the immunity necklace
walking into Tribal tonight.
-So much respect.
-Yeah, buddy.
-I got lucky.
-No.
KIM:
But really, tonight's vote
is not, like, a huge, crazy vote
unless something goes down
and an idol gets played.
Do we try and split the votes?
Do we have enough
to split votes?
KIM:
We have enough, and it seems
that the easy vote
would be between Nick and Adam
and that we would split
the vote.
-We got to find out
how Jeremy's feeling.
-Okay.
KIM:
What appears to be
the easy vote tonight would be
sticking with
this larger group of people,
and then
you've kind of got Nick,
Adam and Michele that are
a bit outcasted from the group.
And I think
if that large group of people
were to stick together
and vote out one of those,
everybody makes it
through the night.
What about Nick and Michele?
Why not split it between
those two because they were in
with Wendell. Yeah.
Okay, so make Michele
the backup vote?
-BEN: Yeah.
-Okay.
KIM:
I think Nick's just
not to be trusted,
from my perspective.
I don't have a relationship
with him. I think he's also
a-a challenge threat
moving forward.
So Nick would be
my preference tonight.
-Your name is out there again.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
-Who's putting it out there?
I think Sophie.
NICK: I'm gonna take this game
over. I'm tired of being
told what to do,
and I'm tired of my name
getting thrown out
as a easy vote.
NICK:
If there's gonna be
tons of chaos,
that's good for me.
I want more and more names
thrown around.
I want more and more people
to turn on each other.
You don't want to do Sophie?
I know. I know that.
ADAM:
What do you think?
-Yes.
-NICK: Sarah
gave me the reward,
but she's tighter
to a lot of people
than she is to me.
-MICHELE: Good luck.
-Yeah. Yeah.
NICK:
So I don't feel bad
if I can send Sarah home.
-Anything new?
-Um, yeah.
So, there's basically
one group saying...
saying the Nick or Michele.
Then a different group
that wants to go Sarah.
Oh, my God.
-Would you go Sarah?
-Wow.
-I'm just mind-blown.
-I know.
-Okay. I'm fine with it
if that's the plan.
-Okay.
-Right?
They came to me.
Adam was the only one
that could convince everybody
to go with the Sarah direction.
So I'm thinking Adam,
if he has that type of power
to be able to control people
like that and say--
put his foot down
and people listen,
we should plop it all on him.
We agree to Sarah,
but I think Adam's
more dangerous as a player.
So I think,
"Okay, I have to do something."
Huh? Are you?
-(laughing):
What the hell is going on?
-That's what I think.
TYSON:
I've never loved
confusion
in the game of Survivor.
I've always wanted it
to be straightforward.
-Adam.
-Adam?
Adam. He was trying
to turn it all on Sarah.
-So... Yeah, so here's the deal.
-What?
-We're all voting Adam.
TYSON:
But I'm learning that
if you create enough confusion,
people start forgetting
about you a little bit.
Adam tried to rally everybody
against you,
-and Kim told...
-Against me?
TYSON:
Shh. Yes.
So now we're voting Adam.
All of us are.
SARAH:
Literally, a bomb went off
when my name came out
of someone's mouth,
and now I'm like, "Hold up."
This is not happening.
Adam, you threw my name out.
Mistake, brother.
You don't throw my name out,
okay?
And you're gonna learn
the hard way,
and you're gonna learn why
you don't throw my name out,
because your ass
is gonna go home.
-Really?
-Yeah. So...
BEN:
It's hard to rope
a bunch of winners
into a single direction.
The group's decision
has changed today.
I think the group's decision
will change more times today.
will probably change
at Tribal tonight, too.
So...
I just hope the target
doesn't end up on me tonight.
Who said that me and Sarah
were too close?
-A lot of people have said that.
-Like who?
-Like, everybody.
-Like...
-Did you say it?
-I-I've been in part...
-You did say that?
No, I didn't say it,
but I've been...
-I've heard people say it.
-Who?
Ben, it doesn't matter.
-It does matter.
-Why does it matter?
-Because people are telling me
it was you. Cool.
-No.
-Ben. Ben, it doesn't matter.
-No, fine. All I needed to know.
-That's fine. It does matter.
-It doesn't matter.
It matters to me, okay?
So, that's all I need to know.
If you don't want to tell me it,
that's your prerogative.
I'm glad we had
this conversation.
Okay? But if you don't want
-to tell me, that's fine.
-You're gonna f...
-force me to tell you.
-No, I'm not forcing you
to do anything.
You... I just...
That's why I'm walking away.
'Cause I'm not gonna stay here
and, like, try to force you.
If you don't want to tell me,
that's fine.
-I'll tell. I'll tell.
-No.
-I'll tell you.
-I don't need to know.
ADAM:
Ben talks to me
like I'm a child
that needs to be scolded.
You know, he plays
a lot more like Boston Rob
than he would ever
want to admit.
This is madness.
This conversation
pisses me off more than
any other conversation
I've ever had on Survivor.
Then all hell breaks loose.
Have you heard
my name at all yet today?
-Yes.
-Really?
I've heard so many plans today.
-Do you know what I heard, Tony?
-TONY: What?
Is that you're the one
that said...
-threw my name under the bus.
-No!
-Who told you that?
-Michele.
What's going on?
Same plan. Sarah.
-Who are we voting for?
-Adam.
-Who are we doing?
-(laughs)
Huh?
Yeah.
-TYSON: Yeah.
-Sarah?
-Yeah. Sarah.
-Okay.
I feel like every time
we decide something,
I see everybody go off
and talk more.
Tyson told Sarah it was her?
Yeah.
I'm afraid he's going for me
because he keeps telling
everybody different ....
I wouldn't mind writing Tyson.
She just told me to write Tyson.
They're saying Nick.
-Huh?
-Tyson?
-Let's do Sarah.
-Sarah.
-I honestly don't know.
-Oh, my God.
My plan right now
is to vote Sarah unless
these guys are coming up with
a new plan at camp as we speak.
So, then that means that
I need to go for
what I think might be an idol.
I don't even know
if it's anything.
I could be completely wrong.
(groans):
Oh, my God.
I am imagining
myself watching myself,
and I'm going like this.
(groans)
"He's playing with so much fire.
Please, don't let it burn him."
(laughs):
This is a high stakes game,
and I'm playing it
on the edge.
I just don't want to be
on the other Edge.
♪ ♪
Now bring in the members
of our jury.
All right.
Sarah, this has been,
thus far, a very cagey game
of cat and mouse,
where nobody says anything
and then there's
another blindside.
What did you see
happening today?
Um, it's definitely
not cagey anymore.
It was chaotic.
Everybody's name
seems to appear.
People that you're working with,
they're throwing your name out.
I mean, it's kind of like
a solo game right now.
Tyson, I was gonna go
down the road thinking you guys
weren't gonna talk
about anything.
And Sarah says, "Oh, no, it was
the Wild, Wild West today."
TYSON:
Yeah. It was a game
of running in circles,
meeting back around,
meeting in camp,
pulling people aside.
-Really?
-For sure.
JEREMY:
Jeff, it was like
on one side of the highway,
you see a fire.
And then the wind picks it up,
whips it across the other side
of the highway
and explodes. Boom.
It was crazy. I played this game
three times, Jeff.
I've never seen it
like this today.
PROBST:
Denise, what was your take?
DENISE:
Jeff, oh, my God. It's like
so many names are getting
thrown out, and so you're saying
yes to this plan and yes to that
plan and yes to another plan.
And you can't
keep them straight.
And all I can tell you is
I aged a few years today.
PROBST:
Nick, day 23.
Why this Tribal
does it break open?
I think what's happened is there
are some "easy" votes here.
I guess it's me or Tyson
or Adam, and now today,
other names come up,
and then all of a sudden,
all hell breaks loose.
But I'm tired
of my name coming up.
I was blindsided last time.
I feel like
I'm not being treated
like a player in this game,
and I'm ready to join somebody.
Make a push.
If this is Winners at War,
this is the saddest war
I've ever seen.
Everybody's afraid
to say anything.
Everybody's afraid to
say a name,
and everybody's afraid
to go after anybody, so...
Let's fight. I'm ready.
PROBST:
So, Adam,
if you believe
that in this moment in the game,
you are an "easy" vote,
that means you have to be
in some sort of
constant state of
assessing and trying
to make sure
where the vote's going.
What do you do?
ADAM:
Sorry.
-Yeah.
-I'm just trying
to pay attention
-to everything that's...
-Do your thing, man.
...that's going on.
(whispering)
-No.
-Okay.
I'm good.
-Everything's good.
-I'm good.
Let's do it. I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good.
I'm good.
What's going on, man?
Whispers at Tribal
get attention, Ben.
BEN:
As they should.
It's kind of like what happened
at camp today.
Everyone whispered,
and someone heard a name,
and then it was like,
"Oh, heck no!"
There was feuds
that were brought up
and then extinguished
and then brought up
and things that were addressed.
And it's still happening
right now as we speak, Jeff.
ADAM:
Look, all I know is,
when we left camp,
Ben would not talk to me
or look me in the eye,
and I'm concerned...
Did I ask you a question?
I'm concerned that maybe
you're voting for me.
I-I asked him a question,
and he chose not to answer it.
And that was on him.
And so I turned and walked away,
because a fair
and honest question
by an alliance member
should be answered.
-So I was concerned...
-Not if it means
having to throw somebody else
under the bus.
When you were
throwing me under the bus.
-I was not.
-Okay.
So, see, Jeff, this is how
this roundabout has gone.
ADAM:
I have had Ben's back
-in this game since the get-go.
-I have had your back
-in this game from the get-go.
-Have you? Have you?
-Yes. Have you gone home?
-Why did Wendell vote for me
at the last Tribal Council?
Why did Nick vote for me
Is it maybe because you said
I was causing chaos
at the Yara camp?
That I'm not to be trusted?
You have been causing chaos
from day one.
ADAM:
And I still was not
coming after...
BEN: You created chaos
this whole time.
-I speculated
that Sarah might have an idol.
-We said that...
How many times
have you said sorry?
How many times have you
said sorry for...
-Because you're
so sensitive, Ben.
-Okay, Adam.
-(laughter)
-ADAM: Because...
Because you get angry at me.
I'm sorry that I speculated
that she had an idol.
I'm playing Survivor, Ben.
-BEN: Okay. Adam.
-ADAM: And I wanted
to go very, very far
in this game with you.
-I hear you.
-But if I feel like
you're the reason
that votes are coming my way...
BEN:
If you got to tell yourself
that I'm the reason for that,
-that's fine.
-I still wasn't
coming after you.
-What'd you do at Sele?
-ADAM: What I did
-at Sele was I told Rob...
-Rob.
...what was gonna happen
because I was loyal to Rob.
Rob said he would never
write my name down.
-And you had an alliance
with Jeremy and I, too.
-I've explained this many times.
-Right?
-And have I written
your name down?
-And have I ever caused anybody
to write your name down?
-And have...
Have I written your name down?
-Okay.
-No, you have not,
but I'm worried
that it might happen tonight,
and so I'm doing
wh-what I think
I need to do maybe
-in order to make sure
that that doesn't happen.
-Okay.
Are you writing my name down
tonight?
No.
(sighs)
-Are you guys voting for me?
-Who are you writing down?
Who are you writing down?
My vote doesn't matter.
-It's all yours that do.
-JEREMY: It does matter.
-It does matter.
-ADAM: Does it matter? Why?
-Yes, it matters.
-We already talked
about it, man.
ADAM:
Well, then-then
what's all the...
Then what's all...
Then what's the whispering?
TONY:
Should we not go up and vote?
Just say it out loud?
Adam, what do you want us to do?
That's the game.
We got to go up there,
we got to write the name down
and then come back down,
and then he reads the votes.
(chuckles):
I-I know that's how it works.
But I'm concerned that-that
my name is coming up tonight.
PROBST:
So, Nick,
-that felt like war.
-NICK: Yeah, I mean,
now I trust my place better,
and I can see where I stand.
So, yeah,
I feel like this is better.
ADAM:
I mean, if...
if Nick feels better
and he was told to vote for me,
I don't feel better.
And I'm trying to figure out
is it me, is it him,
or is it somebody else?
Anybody?
Okay.
PROBST:
All right.
It is time to vote.
Nick, you're up.
♪ ♪
Most chaotic day ever.
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
a hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
Damn.
Nothing, huh?
Not anything?
Looked like maybe
it was something.
Worth a shot.
-(laughs)
-What are you doing?
ADAM:
I don't know.
But maybe that was an idol.
You're convinced it's not?
Is it? Can I play it?
I want to play that.
-You want to play this?
-Yeah. Can I play that?
PROBST:
This thing that you can't get
-off of the voting podium?
-Yeah.
I... Yeah.
I want to play that.
PROBST:
So, if that is an idol,
it would be historic.
-Yeah.
-The first idol
ever hidden at Tribal Council
in plain view of all players,
selected by you
and played for you.
Exactly.
That is...
-...not a hidden immunity idol.
-Oh, God.
-Worth a shot.
-PROBST: That is just
part of the voting podium.
-(laughs)
-Any votes cast
for Adam will still count.
First vote:
Sarah.
Adam.
Nick. One vote Adam,
one vote Nick,
one vote Sarah.
Adam.
Nick. Two votes Adam,
two votes Nick, one vote Sarah.
Adam.
That's three votes Adam,
two votes Nick, one vote Sarah.
Adam. That's four votes Adam.
Five votes Adam.
11th person voted out of
Survivor: Winners at War:
Adam. That's six. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Really thought it might be
something. (chuckles)
It was worth a shot.
Always.
Adam, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
-Bye, Adam. See you.
-Good luck, guys.
♪ ♪
One too many mistakes.
Damn it.
"Bequeath your fire tokens
to any player
still in the game."
I'll give it to Denise.
Even if you knew
I was going home.
Screw all of you.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
PROBST: Survivor's
looking for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
SOPHIE:
The war is happening tonight,
and the question is:
Who's gonna be dead
in the trenches?
Tonight, there will be blood.
I'm ready to go to the Edge
trying to make a move.
This is a crucial decision.
This is going to end badly.
There he is. Welcome to
the Edge of Extinction.
-Aw, man.
-DANNI: Welcome to the Edge.
-PARVATI: Nice try
-on that immunity idol
at the end there.
-Yeah.
ADAM:
I made one too many mistakes.
Three strikes and you're out
in this game, and, uh,
the thought that there was
an idol at Tribal
allowed me to play
more aggressively
than I should have.
And it cost me.
(roars)