>> GO!
♪ YOU BETTER BE READY ♪
>> Jeff: IT'S GOING TO BE A
BIG BATTLE.
THIS IS LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
20 WINNERS.
EVERYBODY WANTS IT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
YOU ARE WITNESSING 16 AMERICANS
BEGIN AN ADVENTURE THAT WILL
FOREVER CHANGE THEIR LIVES.
FOR THE NEXT 39 DAYS, THEY'LL BE
MAROONED, LEFT TO FEND FOR
THEMSELVES.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEY'RE VOTED OFF.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
AND WILL LEAVE THE ISLAND WITH
$1 MILLION IN CASH AS THEIR
REWARD.
>> I HAVE A BIG REPUTATION IN
"SURVIVOR," BUT SEEING MY
COMPETITORS, I'M LIKE, OH, MAN.
>> FANS IN SUPER BOWL WAIT ALL
YEAR TO SEE THE GAME AT THE END.
FANS OF "SURVIVOR" HAVE BEEN
WAITING 20 YEARS TO SEE "WINNERS
AT WAR."
>> I HAVEN'T HAD AN OPPORTUNITY
TO BE MY DIE POLL CAL SELF AT
ALL IN THE PAST COUPLE YEARS.
I HAVE BEEN BUSY BIDDING A
FAMILY, BUT I'M LIKE A PHOENIX
RISING FROM THE ASHES READY TO
BURN DOWN YOUR HOUSE.
>> I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
HODGKIN'S LYMPHOMA.
I REMEMBER DREAMING AND PRAYING
THAT I'D BE ALIVE LONG ENOUGH TO
PLAY "SURVIVOR" AGAIN.
AND SO IT IS A MIRACLE THAT I'M
SITTING HERE TODAY.
>> I WAS A KID THE FIRST TIME I
PLAYED THE GAME.
LITTLE DID I KNOW I WAS GOING
THE FALL IN LOVE, MEET MY
HUSBAND, GET ENGAGED AT THE
FINALE, WIN THE SHOW.
BUT NOW TO BE ASKED BACK FOR
SEASON 40 ALL WINNERS?
I WANT TO WIN THE GAME.
TO COME OUT HERE AND WIN TWO
TIMES AND BEAT MY HUSBAND AGAIN,
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
>> Jeff: IT'S THE BIGGEST
BATTLE IN "SURVIVOR" HISTORY.
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING TO BE
LAYING IT ALL ON THE LINE.
>> Jeff: WHO WILL HAVE WHAT IT
TAKES TO OUTWIT, OUTPLAY, AND
OUTLAST ALL THE REST?
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A BLOODBATH.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A WAR.
>> Jeff: AND BE CROWNED THE
GREATEST PLAYER OF ALL TIME?
>> LET THE FIREWORKS BEGIN.
>> Jeff: 39 DAYS, 20 PEOPLE,
ONE SURVIVOR.
>> HERE WE GO, BOYS.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> WOW.
>> WE'RE BACK.
>> Jeff: WE HAVE THE MEN.
HERE COME THE WOMEN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HERE THEY COME.
HERE THEY COME.
>> THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING.
>> OH, MAN.
>> YOU GOOD?
>> Jeff: YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
WHO YOU ARE PLAYING AGAINST AS
THEY GET THEIR FIRST LOOK AT WHO
THEY ARE PLAYING AGAINST.
>> WELCOME.
>> Jeff: WOW.
[APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME, LADIES.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
YOU GUYS HIT THE OCEAN YET?
>> THE QUEEN.
>> I'M SHOCKED TO SEE ROB AND
AMBER.
I SPENT 36 DAYS WITH BOSTON ROBB
ON ISLAND OF THE IDOL, AND
BOSTON ROB NEVER TOLD ME THAT HE
WAS POLITICIAN AGAIN.
>> GOT YOU WIFE HERE, HUH?
>> SO I DEFINITELY FEEL
BETRAYED.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WOW.
LET ME TAKE THIS IN.
20 WINNERS, 20 YEARS IN THE
MAKING.
THIS IS AWESOME.
WENDELL, YOU APPLIED MANY TIMES
TO GET ON THIS SHOW, AND THEN
YOU FULFILLED THE DREAM OF EVERY
PLAYER.
YOU ACTUALLY WON.
WHAT'S THE FEELING?
>> IT'S GOT TO BE THE GREATEST
FEELING IN YOUR LIFE.
I'M AMONGST THE GREATS RIGHT
NOW.
I SEE SOME LEGENDS.
A LOT OF LEGENDS.
19 LEGENDS OUT HERE.
IT FEELS GOOD, MAN.
IT'S THE BEST FEELING.
>> Jeff: YUL, YOU PLAYED 14
YEARS AGO.
>> YEP.
>> Jeff: THE iPHONE DIDN'T
EVEN EXIST.
[LAUGHTER]
DO YOU SEE THIS GAME TODAY
THROUGH A DIFFERENT PRISM AS A
MORE MATURE HUMAN?
>> YEAH.
I FEEL LIKE A DINOSAUR THAT'S
BEEN TIME BOMBED INTO THE
FUTURE.
THE WORLD HAS CHANGED.
THE PEOPLE HAVE CHANGED.
"SURVIVOR" HAS CHANGED.
I THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
CHANGE.
>> Jeff: AMBER.
>> JEFF.
>> Jeff: YOU FIRST PLAYED 20
YEARS AGO.
LITTLE PERSPECTIVE.
NOT ONLY HAD THE iPHONE NOT
BEENEN VETTED, iTUNES DIDN'T
EXIST, TWITTER, FACEBOOK.
YOU WERE THIS YOUNG WOMAN WHO
CAME ON THE SHOW.
YOU END UP MEETING ROB.
YOU GET ENGAGED ON THE SHOW, AND
NOW YOU'VE CREATED A FAMILY WITH
FOUR BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN FOR YOU THIS
TIME AS A VERY DIFFERENT WOMAN
THAN YOU WERE THE FIRST TIME?
>> IT'S HONESTLY KIND OF LIKE A
NICE VACATION.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
WHAT'S FOR DINNER.
I'M NOT COOKING IT.
I'M NOT GOING GROCERY SHOPPING.
THIS IS AWESOME, BUT TO BE
HONEST, TO BE A PART OF SEASON
40, IT'S GOING TO BE THE
BIGGEST, MOST EPIC SEASON YET.
HOW COULD YOU PASS UP THIS
OPPORTUNITY?
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
BEFORE WE GET TO IT, LET'S HAVE
A LITTLE TOAST TO CELEBRATE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: COME ON NOW.
>> WHOA.
>> YEAH.
[APPLAUSE]
>> ARE WE PLAYING "SURVIVOR"?
>> Jeff: THIS IS A
ONCE-IN-A-TV-SERIES MOMENT.
WE GOT TO CELEBRATE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> DO IT UP.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
>> MY COMPETITION HERE IS THE
GREATEST OF THE GREAT, AND IT'S
A GOOD FEELING, BECAUSE WE'RE
ALL HERE TO BE PART OF SOMETHING
SPECIAL.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> BUT EVERYONE WILL BE GUNS
A-BLAZEIN', EVERYONE WILL BE
SWORDS A-SWINGING.
THERE WILL BE LIMBS AND HEADS
FLYING EVERYWHERE.
>> Jeff: I JUST WANT TO SAY,
WE ARE PROUD TO HAVE YOU HERE AS
REPRESENTATIVES OF OUR 40th
YOU HAVE EARNED IT, BUT THIS IS
STILL "SURVIVOR."
AND EVEN THOUGH YOU HAVE ALL
WON, THERE WILL BE TOUGH TIMES.
YOU WILL BE CHALLENGED.
YOU WILL BE VULNERABLE.
WHEN THOSE MOMENTS HAPPEN, JUST
REMEMBER, YOU BELONG.
TO "SURVIVOR," BECAUSE A DRINK
BEFORE WAR IS ALWAYS A GOOD
IDEA.
[CHEERING]
>> CHEERS, GIRLS.
>> CHEERS.
>> GET RID OF THAT.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
"SURVIVOR" 40, "WINNERS AT WAR."
YOU ARE DIVIDED INTO MEN AND
WOMEN, AND THIS IS NOT HOW WE
ARE GOING TO PLAY.
>> OH, WOW.
>> Jeff: LET'S REVEAL OUR
TRIBES.
FIND YOUR NAME AND TAKE IT.
>> THANKS, SIR.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M THE MOST
RECENT FEMALE WINNER OUT HERE,
IT'S PRETTY NERVE-RACKING,
BECAUSE I HAVE NINE OF THE MOST
INTIMIDATING WOMEN RIGHT NEXT TO
ME.
I MEAN, "WINNERS AT WAR"?
IT JUST SOUNDS NASTY.
>> Jeff: EVERYBODY OPEN YOUR
BUFF.
LET'S SEE WHAT'S UP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BLUE, BLUE.
>> BLUE.
>> Jeff: TAKE YOUR SPOTS.
BLUE IS OVER HERE.
BLUE IS OVER HERE, JEREMY.
ROB, BLUE IS OVER HERE.
AMBER, RED IS THIS WAY.
>> SORRY, ROB.
>> "WINNERS AT WAR."
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
WEARING RED, WE'VE GOT TONY,
WENDELL, AMBER, KIM, SOPHIE,
NICK, SARAH, YUL, SANDRA, AND
TYSON.
WEARING BLUE, SELE, WE'VE GOT
NATALIE, ROB, ETHAN, PARVATI,
BEN, MICHELE, DANNI, DENISE,
JEREMY, AND ADAM.
TONY, THIRD TIME OUT HERE.
>> THIRD TIME.
>> Jeff: WHAT'S THE FEELING&
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS GROUP?
BECAUSE YOU WILL, FOR BETTER OR
FOR WORSE, NEED THESE PEOPLE TO
TRY THE STAY IN THE GAME.
>> I LOVE THE PEOPLE I'M WITH.
I'VE PLAYED WITH SARAH IN SEASON
28.
SANDRA VOTED ME OFF THE SECOND
TIME AND I LOST THE GAME.
SO I LOVE HER FOR THAT.
RED MEANS WE'RE RED HOT.
WE'RE ON FIRE.
LET'S SEE.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT THIS SEASON.
WE'RE INTRODUCING A NEW
"SURVIVOR" CURRENCY IN THE FORM
TOKENS HAVE VALUE.
YOU WILL EACH TART THE GAME WITH
ONE FIRE TOKEN.
IF YOU ARE VOTED OUT, YOU MUST
WILL OR BEQUEATH YOUR TOKEN TO
ANOTHER PLAYER AS YOU HEAD TO
THAT ISLAND RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
THE ISOLATED AND UNFORGIVING
EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
>> OH, BOY.
>> Jeff: WHERE YOU WILL AWAIT
YOUR CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THIS
GAME.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: AND ONE LAST THING.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Jeff: LET ME JUST SAY THIS:
IF BEING CROWNED THE WINNER IN A
SEASON OF ALL WINNERS AND
EARNING $1 MILLION IN THE
PROCESS IS NOT ENOUGH TO INSPIRE
YOU, HOW ABOUT $2 MILLION?
[CHEERING]
THE LARGEST CASH PRIZE IN THE
HISTORY OF REALITY SHOWS.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS
WIN.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU BARELY GOT YOU FEET
WET.
WE HAVE A CHALLENGE RIGHT HERE.
IT SEEMS LIKE A GOOD TIME TO
DIVE IN.
LET'S GET TO YOUR FIRST
CHALLENGE RIGHT NOW.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS: YOU WILL
RACE OUT IN PAIRS TO RETRIEVE A
RING.
YOU'LL HEN BATTLE YOUR WAY
BACK.
THE FIRST PERSON WITH ONE HAND
ON THE RING, ONE HAND ON THING
FROM POLE SCORES A POINT.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO THREE WINS.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT, STILL THE FUNDAMENTAL
FOUNDATIONAL BUILDING BLOCK OF
ANY TRIBE.
IT CAN GET YOU OFF TO A VERY
FAST START, BECAUSE FOR THE
LOSERS, NO FIRE AND NO RICE
UNTIL AFTER THE FIRST TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
THAT COULD BE A VERY BIG
SETBACK.
OH, ONE LAST THING.
>> WHAT ELSE?
>> YEAH?
>> ENOUGH THING.
>> Jeff: THIS CHALLENGE IS
ALSO FOR IMMUNITY.
>> OH.
>> Jeff: OUT OF THE GATE,
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL, AND JUST
LIKE THAT, SOMEBODY WILL BE THE
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT WAR."
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE WITH YOUR NEW TRIBE,
AND WE'LL GET IT ON.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT
WE HAVE OUR FIRST MATCHUP.
IT IS TYSON AND YUL TAKING ON
JEREMY AND ETHAN.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: "WINNERS AT WAR" IS
UNDER WAY.
>> GO, YUL.
>> Jeff: TWO BIG GUYS BATTLING
FOR THAT RING.
TYSON HAS IT.
ETHAN GETTING IN ON IT NOW.
YUL AND JEREMY TYING EACH OTHER
UP.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET BACK WITH THE
RING AND HAND ON THAT FLAGPOLE.
JEREMY NOW IN.
HERE COMES YUL.
YUL DIGGING.
YUL INCHING CLOSER AND CLOSER TO
THAT FLAGPOLE.
AND HE'S DONE IT.
DAKAL SCORES THE FIRST POINT IN
"WINNERS AT WAR."
DAKAL LEADS 1-0.
NEXT ROUND IS TWO WOMEN.
IT'S GOING TO BE SARAH AND KIM.
>> COME ON, GIRLS.
>> Jeff: TAKING ON PARVATI AND
NATALIE.
HERE WE GO.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
>> LET'S GO.
>> Jeff: NATALIE SWIMMING OUT
QUICKLY.
KIM SWIMMING.
NATALIE AND KIM RACING FOR IT.
NATALIE'S GOING TO GET IT.
NATALIE HAS IT.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> Jeff: NOW EVERYBODY IS IN
ON IT.
KIM FIGHTING TO TAKE IT FOR
DAKAL.
IT IS KIM AND SARAH WORKING
TOGETHER.
AND NATALIE AND PARVATI INCHING
CLOSER.
THAT SWELL IS GOING TO HELP.
SELE GETTING CLOSER.
NATALIE VERY CLOSE.
KIM PULLING HER AWAY NOW.
PARVATI TRYING TO GET THERE.
>> COME ON, PARVATI.
>> Jeff: KIM FIGHTING.
PARVATI HAS ALMOST GOT IT.
NO!
ANOTHER BIG SURGE FROM KIM.
KIM HAS SINGLE-HANDEDLY PULLING
THIS RING CLOSEER TO DAKAL.
PARVATI AND NATALIE TRYING TO
PULL IT BACK.
KIM GETTING VERY CLOSE.
SHE'S GOT IT.
DAKAL, WHAT AN EPIC BATTLE.
DAKAL LEADS 2-0.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> Jeff: THE MEN ARE UP AGAIN.
IT IS WENDELL AND TONY FOR
DAKAL.
IT IS BEN AND BOSTON ROB FOR
SELE.
THEY HAVE TO SCORE TO STAY IN
IT.
DAKAL LEADS 2-0.
WE'RE PLAYING THE THREE.
TONY AND WENDELL CAN WIN IT
RIGHT HERE FOR DAKAL.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BIG BATTLE
THERE ARE FOUR BIG, STRONG DUDES
OUT THERE FIGHTING FOR IT.
BEN ALL OVER WENDELL.
THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE EASY FOR
ANYBODY.
ROB NOW IN ON IT.
TONY NOW IN ON IT.
BEN IS PULLING EVERYBODY BACK
TOWARD THE SELE FLAG.
TONY TRYING THE TAKE ROB OUT OF
THIS, BUT IT'S NOT WORKING.
ROB CONTINUES TO PUSH FORWARD,
GETTING CLOSER TO THAT FIRST
BUOY.
ROB TRYING TO GET THERE.
TONY PULLING HIM BACK.
ROB GOT IT!
SELE SCORES, AND IT'S 2-1.
ANOTHER HUGE BATTLE.
IT'S GOING TO BE DENISE AND
NATALIE TAKING ON AMBER AND
SARAH FOR THE WIN FOR DAKAL.
IF THEY SCORE, IT'S OVER.
DENISE AND NATALIE HAVE TO SCORE
TO STAY IN IT.
TRIBAL COUNCIL IS ON THE LINE.
SURVIVORS READY.
GO!
THIS COULD BE IT.
SARAH AND AMBER COULD WIN IT
RIGHT HERE FOR DAKAL.
>> LET'S GO, SARAH.
>> COME ON, SARAH.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: IT IS AMBER AND
NATALIE TIED UP QUICKLY.
DENISE HAS SARAH TRYING TO TAKE
HER OUT OF THIS.
IF BLUE DOES NOT SCORE, IT'S
OVER.
NATALIE AND DENISE ARE ON THE
RIGHT SIDE OF THIS CHALLENGE.
THEY'RE INCHING CLOSE AND
CLOSER, BUT HERE COMES SARAH AND
AMBER TRYING TO WIN IT FOR
DAKAL.
NATALIE DIGGING IN AGAIN.
DENISE DIGGING IN.
>> SARAH!
SARAH!
>> Jeff: DAKAL GETTING SOME
SUPPORT FROM THEIR TIME.
>> AMBER, AMBER!
>> Jeff: HERE COMES DENISE
TRYING TO GET AMBER OUT OF IT.
SHE IS NOT GOING TO BE DETERRED.
AMBER CLOSER AND CLOSER.
SARAH REACHING.
NO!
NATALIE PULLS IT BACK.
SARAH'S GOT IT.
DAKAL WINS IMMUNITY, SENDING
SELE THE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
EPIC FIRST CHALLENGE.
WOW.
EVERYBODY PLAYING FOR KEEPS ON
THIS SEASON.
WELL, FIRST CHALLENGE OF THE
SEASON LIVED UP TO THE TITLE OF
THE SEASON, "WINNERS AT WAR."
DAKAL, YOU PULLED IT OUT.
IMMUNITY IS YOURS.
[APPLAUSE]
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT, AND
MORE IMPORTANTLY, NOBODY FROM
DAKAL GOING HOME.
HERE'S MAP THE YOUR NEW HOME.
NICE CATCH, SOPHIE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT, AND
GOOD LUCK.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
SELE, HEADING BACK THE CAMP,
YOU'LL HAVE NO FIRE.
YOU WILL ALSO HAVE NO RICE
WAITING FOR YOU.
BIGGER THAN, THAT SOMEBODY FROM
YOUR TRIBE WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF WINNERS AT
WAR, AND TO COMPLICATE THINGS A
LITTLE MORE, TRIBAL COUNCIL WILL
NOT BE TONIGHT.
IT WILL BE TOMORROW NIGHT.
YOU ALL CAME TO PLAY, THIS GIVES
YOU PLENTY OF TIME TO MAKE
THINGS HAPPEN.
HERE'S MAP TO YOUR HOME.
HEAD OUT, GOOD LUCK.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TRIBAL COUNCIL
TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> THE LOSE THE IMMUNITY
CHALLENGE ON DAY ONE,S THAT MY
WORST FEAR, BECAUSE WE'RE
PLAYING WINNERS AT WAR
"SURVIVOR," WHICH MEANS THERE IS
NO EASY TARGET.
BUT SOMEBODY HAS TO GO.
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> YEAH, RIGHT?
>> GOOD JOB.
>> WE GET TO OUR ISLAND, AND I'M
THINKING, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS
IS HAPPENING.
I WAS JUST SUPER HAPPY TO BE ON
"SURVIVOR" AGAIN, ESPECIALLY AN
ALL-WINNERS EDITION, BUT SEEING
ALL THESE PEOPLE AND REALIZING
HOW LONG AGO I PLAYED, IT'S DIE
OF OVERWHELMING.
>> CHECK THIS OUT.
>> IT SAYS, "USE YOUR FIRE
TOKENS TO PURCHASE ANY OF THESE
ITEMS.
PRESENT FIRE TOBINS AT ANY
CHALLENGE, COFFEE AND PASTRY,
SMALL BAG OF BEAN, TWO PILLOW,
TWO BLANKETS.
THE ADVANTAGE IN THE CHALLENGE
IS MORE TOKENS."
>> WE'RE GIVEN AN IN-GAME
CURRENCY CALLED A FIRE TOKEN.
IN MY OPINION, THESE TOKENS ARE
GOING TO END UP BEING A HUGE
PART OF THE GAME.
>> THIS FIRE TOKEN CANNOT BE
STOLEN FROM YOU.
IF VOTED OUT, YOU MUST BEQUEATH
IT TO ANY PLAYER STILL IN THE
GAME.
>> I THINK THE WINNER OF THIS
SEASON WILL BE THE PERSON WHO IS
ABLE TO USE THE CURRENCY
CORRECTLY.
I AM FROM THE NEWER SEASONS
WHERE WE'RE USED TO TWISTS.
WE UNDERSTAND THERE'S
UNPREDICTABLE FACETS OF THE
GAME, SO I THINK MY CHANCES TO
WIN THIS GAME GOT MUCH HIGHER.
>> SO WE'RE LOOKING FOR BAMBOO
AND WOOD.
>> YOU COULD DO LOG CABIN STYLE.
IT RAISES IT EASIER.
>> DO YOU WANT US TO FIND
BAMBOO?
>> I WASN'T SIGNING UP FOR THIS.
>> FURNITURE MAKER WENDELL?
>> AFTER WINNING "SURVIVOR"
SEASON 36 "GUEST -- GHOST
ISLAND," I THINK PEOPLE KNOW ME
AS SOMEONE WHO KNOWS HOW TO
BUILD.
THIS SEASON I WAS TRYING TO COME
OUT HERE AND NOT BUILD AS MUCH.
I WANTED TO BUILD RELATIONSHIPS.
I DIDN'T NECESSARILY WANT TO
BUILD THE WHOLE SHELTER AGAIN.
I THINK WE'RE GOOD.
WE'LL HAMMER A STAKE IN RIGHT
HERE.
THIS ISN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU'RE BUSY
BUILDING, YOU'RE STUCK AT CAMP.
IT'S LIKE BEING STUCK IN A
CORNER AT PARTY.
>> MADE BY WENDELL DESIGN?
>> SOMETHING LIKE THAT
>> BUT I ALSO KNOW THIS TALENT
POOL IS DIFFERENT.
IT'S ALL WINNERS.
SO I'M GOING TO PLAY MY POSITION
AND BE COOL, CHILL OUT A LITTLE
BIT, JUST GET A READ ON
EVERYONE.
>> I DID NOT THINK I'D SEE YOU
OUT HERE.
>> REALLY?
>> WELL, I MEAN, YOU GOT FOUR
LITTLE ONES AT HOME.
>> I KNOW.
IT WASN'T -- IT WAS AN EASY
DECISION, BUT IT WASN'T EASY.
I GOT THEM ALL CALENDARS
>> I DID THE SAME THING,
EXCEPT --
>> I MADE A DAISY CHAIN?
>> WHAT'S THE DAISY CHAIN?
>> THE PIECES OF PAPER ALL
LOOPED AN YOU PULL ONE LINK OFF
EVERY DAY
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US ALL
THIS?
>> HONESTLY, "SURVIVOR" HAS BEEN
MY PROFESSION THE LAST 12 YEARS.
THE THING THAT HAS MADE WINNING
THE $1 MILLION SO GREAT IS I'M
ABLE TO SPEND TIME WITH MY KIDS
AT HOME EVERY DAY, AND I DON'T
WANT THE CRY ON DAY ONE HERE,
BUT IT'S LIKE I KNOW EVERYBODY
DOES THE 9:00 UNTIL 5:00, BUT I
CAN'T.
NOT TOO MUCH, GUYS.
>> JUST WHEN I THINK YOU'RE ONLY
HERE FOR GOOD LOOKS AND LAUGHS,
YOU DO THIS
>> I GET TO GET UP EVERY MORNING
WITH MY DURING AND HANG OUT
PRETTY MUCH ALL DAY EVERY DAY.
SO EVEN COMING OUT HERE FOR A
WHILE IS A BIG DEAL BECAUSE I'VE
NEVER LEFT THEM FOR MORE THAN A
COUPLE DAYS AT TIME.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR THAT.
>> HOW YOU DOING, QUEEN IN
>> DON'T THIS THAT
>> LOOKING GOOD.
>> DON'T CALL ME "QUEEN."
IT WILL PUT A TARGET ON MY BACK.
YOU ASK ANYBODY THAT'S A
"SURVIVOR" FAN WHO IS THE QUEEN,
AND THEY WILL TELL YOU IT'S ME.
I'M THE ONLY PERSON HERE THAT
KNOWS WHAT IT'S LIKE TO WIN
TWICE.
THE HISTORY OF "GAME CHANGERS"
IS I GOT TONY VOTED OUT AND
SARAH.
"WINNERS AT WAR."
>> WELCOME TO SEASON 40.
>> I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO GO
UP AGAINST TONEY.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO GO UP
AGAINST SARAH.
I PLAYED ON GAME CHANGERS WITH
THEM, AN ME AND TONY HAD IT OUT.
>> SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: GAME CHANGERS," TONY.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR
PLOTTING AGAINST ME.
AND QUEEN STAYS QUEEN.
I KNOW EVERYONE WANTS A PIECE OF
ME.
>> YOU HAPPY TO BE HERE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> EVEN WITH ME?
>> NO HARD FEELINGS, YOU KNOW
THAT?
>> WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE?
>> STILL UNDER THE BRIDGE.
>> THEY ALL WANT WHAT I ALREADY
HAVE, WHICH IS MY CROWN.
>> HOW ABOUT IT FOR SEASON 40,
HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> SEASON 40!
>> OBVIOUSLY I HAVE A HUGE
TARGET ON MYSELF.
I JUST WAS ON SEASON 39 WHERE
THEY BUILT AN IDOL OF ME.
>> YOU'RE SORT OF OUR SHELTER
EXPERT.
>> RESIDENT BUILDER.
>> BY LOSING IN THE BEGINNING,
I'M ALREADY PUTTING MYSELF AT A
HUGE DISADVANTAGE.
>> IT'S GOING TO TAKE SOME WORK.
IT WILL TAKE ALL OF US, BUT WE
CAN DO IT.
WORK AS A TEAM, YOU KNOW.
FORTUNATELY NOW WE HAVE TO BUILT
A SHELTER AND VOTE SOMEBODY OFF.
THE GAME IS ON ALREADY.
>> CONGRATS ON THE BABY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, MAN.
>> HI, ROB, MICHELE.
>> HI.
DON'T MAKE ME TALK ABOUT ITFUL
OR I'LL IMMEDIATELY START
CRYING.
>> IT'S BEEN TEN YEARS SINCE
I'VE PLAYED THE GAME.
AND IT'S A LITTLE STRANGE TO BE
PLAYING THIS GAME CONNECTING
OVER BABIES.
>> YOU HAVE FOUR KIDS.
>> I HAVE FOUR, TOO.
ONCE WAS.
THE LAST TWO TIMES I WAS A
SINGLE GIRL.
>> DO YOU WANT A PICKINGY BACK?
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I'M A MOM NOW.
I'M MARRIED.
AND I LEFT MY TEN-MONTH-OLD BABY
AT HOME WITH MY HUSBAND.
OH, MY GOSH, IT'S JUST... IT
HITS ME WHEN I THINK ABOUT HER.
I'M GOING TO NEED YOUR SUPPORT.
BEING A MOM IS A NEW LIFE CHANGE
THAT CAN HELP ME TO RELATE THE
PEOPLE IN A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
WAY.
SO I'M TOTALLY USING THE MOM
CARD.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS HAVE
FOUR CHILDREN.
>> SOMEBODY FOUND SOMETHING THEY
WERE GOOD AT.
>> IT'S NICE TO BE HERE.
>> I'M HAPPY HERE, BRO.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
EVERYTHING GOOD IN
>> EVERYTHING'S GOOD, MAN.
GOING THROUGH CANCER, IT'S HARD,
BUT LIFE AFTER CANCER, THAT'S
WHEN IT REALLY GOT TOUGH.
THE FEAR OF RELAPSE, THE FEAR OF
DEATH, IT'S WITH YOU ALL THE
TIME.
IT'S NOT A WAY TO LIVE YOUR
LIFE.
AND BEING HERE, SAYING YES TO AN
ALL-WINNERS EDITION OF
"SURVIVOR," THIS IS LIVING.
>> WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
PLAYED?
>> 2004.
>> OH, WOW
>> AND I WANT THE RESURRECT THAT
27 YEAR OLD YOUNG, INNOCENT, GUY
TO COME BACK AND PLAY THIS GAME,
THE GAME THAT I LOVE.
THE GAME THAT CHANGED MY LIFE.
>> NICE, ETHAN.
[GROWLS]
>> I DID PUSH-UPS YESTERDAY.
I'M REALLY HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE HOW I PLAY IN
THIS NEW ERA OF "SURVIVOR."
LIKE WE PLAYED WITH LIKE NO
IDOLS, NO HIDDEN IMMUNITIES, NO
CHANCE TO GET BACK IN THE GAME.
SO I'M BACK AND I'M READY TO
PLAY, AND EVERYONE BETTER WATCH
OUT.
>> IS THAT A TRAIL UP THERE?
>> ARE WE ON THE TRAIL?
THERE'S NO TRAIL THAT GOES THAT
WAY, THOUGH, SO I THINK WE HAVE
TO KEEP GOING THIS WAY.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I WOULD LIKE TO NOT GO.
I'M WEARING BLUE AGAIN.
AND...
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
>> I WAS THINKING --
>> LOSING THAT VERY FIRST
CHALLENGE, I WAS LIKE, OH, MY
GOD, HERE WE GO AGAIN.
I HAD FLASHBACKS.
>> MATSING LOSES FOR THE FOURTH
STRAIGHT TIME.
>> WE LOST EVERY CHALLENGE, SO I
WENT TO EVERY TRIBAL COUNCIL.
AT LEAST I HAD THAT ALLIANCE
WITH MALCOLM.
>> IF I COULD BE YOUR MALCOLM,
IT WOULD BE MY DREAM COME TRUE.
>> MY JUNGLE BOY NUMBER TWO.
>> CAN THAT HAPPEN?
>> I HAVE TO BE ABLE TO READ
SOMEBODY AND HAVE THAT GUT
FEELING.
>> DO YOU HAVE THAT WITH ME?
>> I DO.
>> I HAVE THAT WITH YOU, BECAUSE
I LOVED WATCHING YOU ON
TELEVISION, SERIOUSLY.
>> WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
>> LET'S COUNT.
ONE, THE WORK THREE, FOUR, FIVE.
>> WHERE'S ADAM?
>> WHERE'S DENISE?
>> WE'RE MISSING ADAM.
>> AND DENISE.
>> DENISE AND ADAM, THEY WALK
OFF.
REALLY COOKIE MOVES FOR WINNERS
TO DO THAT IS UNHEARD OF.
>> EASY TARGET, ADAM.
>> PEOPLE ARE JUST LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING, AND IT'S SO EARLY IN
THE GAME, YOU DON'T WANT THE
ROCK THE BOAT.
WHEN YOU ROCK THE BOAT,
SOMETIMES YOU FALL OUT.
>> TEAMWORK MAKES THE DREAM WORK
>> YUL, SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU HAVE TO MAINTAIN A LOW
PROFILE LIKE MYSELF?
I CAN'T GO NOWHERE.
>> IS THE PRATSLY WANT THE
IMMUNITY IDOL, ESPECIALLY FOR A
SEASON LIKE THIS, AND OH, MY
GOD, IT TOOK EVERYTHING OUT OF
ME NOT TO JUST TAKE OFF RUNNING
AND LOOK FOR AN IDOL.
>> I KNOW YOU WANT TO --
>> NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> I SEEN WHAT HAPPENED TO ME ON
"GAME CHANGERS" MY FIRST 30
SECONDS I RAN AROUND THE WHOLE
ISLAND THREE TIMES.
HEY, YOU GUYS DO NICE-NICE.
I'M LOOKING FOR THE IDOL.
I NOVI TO STAY HERE BECAUSE I'M
ON PROBATION.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
I GOT A BRACELET ON.
HOUSE ARREST.
BUT RIGHT NOW I DON'T WANT TO
PUT A TARGET ON MY BACK BY
SHOWING THEM THAT I'M BACK TO
THE OLD TONY ANTICS.
SO I WANT EVERYBODY TO GET NICE
AND COMFORTABLE WITH ME, BECAUSE
THEIR GUARD IS SLOWLY COMING
DOWN AS THEY SEE TONY AROUND THE
CAMP ALL DAY, ALL NIGHT.
WHEN IT GETS DOWN TO HERE,
THAT'S WHERE THE SUCKER PUNCH
COMES IN.
>> PEOPLE SEEMED PRETTY
COMFORTABLE WHEN WE GOT HERE.
THEY WANTED TO WORK ON THE
SHELTER AND DO THIS AND DO THAT.
I'M THINKING, AM I SUPPOSED TO
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I DO HAVE A
BIG TARGET ON MY BACK, THE FACT
THAT ROB AND I ARE BOTH OUT
HERE.
I HAD A HARD TIME AT FIRST
CHALLENGE.
I WAS ROOTING AT MY TEAM -- I'M
GETTING EMOTIONAL -- BUT IT WAS
HARD THE ROOT AGAINST MY
HUSBAND.
I'M HIS BIGGEST FAN.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE THINK WE HAVE
THIS HUGE ADVANTAGE BECAUSE
WE'RE OUT HERE TOGETHER, BUT I
FEEL LIKE IT'S PROBABLY MORE A
DISADVANTAGE THAN IT IS AN
ADVANTAGE.
BUT I LEARNED A LOT FROM MY
HUSBAND.
THIS GAME NEVER STOPS.
AS SOON AS YOU SIT BACK AN
RELAX, THAT'S WHEN SOMETHING
GOES WRONG.
SO I'VE GOT THE TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS TIME.
I'VE GOT TO DO IT.
>> I'M SUPER GLAD YOU'RE IN MY
TRIBE.
I WOULD LOVE TO WORK WITH YOU.
>> REALLY?
YOU CAN PUNCTUATE THAT WITH
MORE.
>> WHAT?
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN ASKED
OUT ON A DATE.
I WANT TO WORK WITH YOU.
>> WHEN I PLAYED COOK ISLAND, I
TRIED TO PLAY A VERY RATIONAL,
STRATEGIC GAME.
I USED A LOT OF GAME THEORY.
>> IT'S SO NICE TALKING TO YOU.
YOU'RE A SANE HUMAN.
>> BUT THIS SEASON I THINK MY
BIGGEST CHALLENGE WILL BE COMING
IN DISCONNECTED.
I HAVEN'T BEEN PART OF THE
"SURVIVOR" COMMUNITY.
A LOT OF THESE PEOPLE HAVE
PLAYED WITH EACH OTHER, THEY
KNOW EACH OTHER SOME KIM PLAYED
POKER WITH ROB AND TYSON, SO
THERE'S THAT CONNECTION.
SOME PEOPLE PLAY MULTIPLE TIMES.
WE HAVE BOSTON ROB.
YOU HAVE TYSON.
THEY PLAYED TOGETHER.
THEY'RE LIKE BEST FRIENDS.
AND THEY NOT ONLY PLAYED
"SURVIVOR" TOGETHER, THEY PLAYED
POKER TOGETHER.
THEY ALSO PLAYED WITH KIM AND
JEREMY.
I REMEMBER WATCHING ONE VIDEO
WHERE TYSON ACTUALLY SAID
SOMETHING TO THE EFFECT OF, HEY,
IF WE'RE EVER ON AN ISLAND, THIS
IS GOING TO BE THE POUR
ALLIANCE.
>> IF WE ALL FIND OURSELVES ON
THE ALLIANCE, WE'LL DEFINITELY
WITH THE POWER ALLIANCE.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
>> DUH
>> BUT I THINK THERE ARE ENOUGH
PEOPLE LIKE US WHO ARE NOT SUPER
CONNECTED.
>> IT'S ALMOST LIKE ME, NICK,
AND WENDELL ARE MORE OF THE FREE
AGENTS, AN YOU HAVE SANDRA,
TOBY, -- TONY AND SARAH WHO ALL
PLAYED TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE KIM, TYSON AND AMBER.
RIGHT NOW I THINK YOU HAVE THE
COOL PERSON ALLIANCE OF KIM AND
AMBER AND TYSON, WHO ALL ARE
TELLING JOKES ALL THE TIME AND
LOOKING PRETTY.
THEN YOU HAVE ON THE OTHER SIDE,
THE GRITTY GROUP, WHICH IS TONY,
SANDRA, AND SARAH.
THEY HAVE ALL PLAYED TOGETHER IN
THE PAST.
AND THEN YOU HAVE A COUPLE OF US
IN THE MIDDLE.
I WOULD PUT PIETION AND YUL IN
THAT POSITION.
>> EVERYTHING I HEARD ABOUT YOU
FROM OTHER PEOPLE HAS ALL BEEN
POSITIVE.
EVERYONE SAYS GREAT THINGS
>> YOU, TOO.
>> PEOPLE TALK ABOUT HAVING
SHIELDS AROUND.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A NERD SHIELD
IN YUL.
LY NEVER BE THE SMARTEST PERSON
AS LONG AS I HAVE YUL THERE
TALKING ABOUT PHYSICS OR
WHATEVER.
BUT I THINK THE NUMBER-ONE THING
ON MY MIND IS NOT WHO I WANT TO
WORK WITH, IT'S WHO I WANT OUT.
>> I GOT AN OCTOPUS AND CRAB,
TWO OF THEM.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SO DO YOU WANT TO WORK
TOGETHER THIS SEASON IN
>> THAT WOULD BE A CHANGE,
WOULDN'T IT?
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M ASKING YOU TO
PROM.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GIVE ME A
CORSAGE, TAKE SOME TIME AND GET
SOME FLOWERS AND MAKE IT
OFFICIAL.
>> I THINK YOU AND I ARE
PROBABLY KNOW THE GAME BETTER
THAN ANYBODY ELSE, AND I THINK
IF WE WORK TOGETHER --
>> ROB AND I HAVE A HISTORY THAT
IS A CHECKERED PAST, TO SAY THE
LEAST.
ROB WENT AFTER ME IN "HEROES V.
VILLAINS."
AND I WAS PARTLY RESPONSIBLE FOR
HIM GETTING OUT PREMERGE.
SO I DON'T KNOW HOW ROB IS GOING
TO WANT THE PLAY WITH ME?
>> WE HAVE AN UPHILL BATTLE.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD LET THE
NEW SCHOOL PEOPLE DICTATE HOW
IT'S GOING TO GO
>> OH, YEAH?
I LIKE ROB.
I THINK HE'S SOMEONE I CAN
TRUST, BECAUSE I DOUBT THAT HE
HAS VERY MANY OTHER OPTIONS.
>> SO LAST TIME YOU WERE COMING
AT ME.
>> BECAUSE WE DIDN'T GET ON THE
SAME PAGE FROM THE BEGINNING.
SO I SAID THE MYSELF, SEE IF WE
GET ON THE SAME PAGE FROM THE
OUTSET.
>> I'M DOWN.
>> LET'S HAVE FUN.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> THESE KIDS AIN'T GOING TO
KNOW WHAT HIT 'EM.
>> THIS IS "SURVIVOR."
WE HAVE TO THINK LONG-TERM TOO,
WHAT CAN BE ESTABLISHED.
>> HE HAD A STATUE BUILT.
WOULD BE YOU LIKE TO HAVE A
STATUE?
>> NOT YET.
>> "SURVIVOR: GUATEMALA," IT WAS
A WHOLE DIFFERENT STYLE PLAY.
COMING INTO THIS I WAS A LITTLE
NERVOUS.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE VERY
CONNECTED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU ALL ARE,
I'M NOT.
TYSON AND ROB ARE PRETTY CLOSE.
>> I KNOW WE WON'T GET VERY MANY
OPPORTUNITIES TO GET RID OF
MAJOR TARGETS LIKE ROB.
WHEN YOU GET THAT OPPORTUNITY --
HE'S WELL LIKED.
HE'S CONNECTED.
AND HE KNOWS HOW TO PLAY THIS
GAME.
IF YOU HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
REMOVE THAT FROM YOUR GAME, WHY
WOULD WOW NOT TAKE IT?
>> NAMES ARE GETTING THROWN OUT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I FOUND MYSELF
WITH ALL THESE WINNERS.
IT'S VERY HUMBLING TO BE AROUND
ALL THESE GREATS.
>> WHOSE NAMES HAVE YOU HEARD?
>> I'VE HEARD YOURS.
>> WHO SAID MY NAME?
>>S BE ROB IS PHENOMENAL AT WHAT
HE DOES?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL ME?
WHY ARE YOU NOT TRUSTING ME?
>> I'M TRYING TO REMEMBER WHO
SAID IT
>> COME ON.
>> IT'S JUST INSANE TO SEE HIM
WORK IN REAL LIFE.
RIGHT, YOU WATCH HIM ON TV, OH,
MY GOD, HOW IS THIS GUY DOING
IT.
>> ONE OF THE GIRLS.
>> SEE THIS RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE
NOT TELLING ME, MAKE ME FEEL
LIKE I CAN'T TRUST YOU, BRO.
>> THEN YOU'RE ON THE RECEIVING
END OF BOSTON ROB'S MAGIC, AND
IT'S LIKE, YEAH, YEAH, BLAH.
>> DANNI.
>> DANNI THREW OUT MY NAME?
WHY?
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE BOSTON ROB.
>> HERE'S MY INFORMATION.
THERE YOU GO, BUD.
YOU GOT IT.
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
YOU'RE GOOD.
>> I'M JUST ASKING WHAT SHE
SAID, MAN.
>> YOU PLAYED FOUR OR FIVE TIMES
>> I WAS STAR STRUCK AND TOLD
HIM EVERYTHING.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
>> SO LET ME ASK YOU, IF I ASK
YOU A QUESTION RIGHT NOW, WILL
YOU TELL ME THE TRUTH?
SOMEBODY CAME TO ME AND TOLD ME
THAT YOU ALREADY THREW MY NAME
OUT.
IS IT TRUE?
>> WELL, I THREW EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY IS A TARGET, YEAH.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S COOL.
>> BECAUSE ONE OF MY CONCERNS
WOULD BE ALL THE CONNECTIONS.
I HAVE NO CONNECTIONS.
I HAVE NONE.
>> I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND IT, AND
I CAN SEE THAT YOU'RE COMING
FROM A PLACE OF BEING OUT HERE
AND DON'T HAVE ANYBODY EITHER.
>> I RESPECT THE FACT THAT DANNI
TOLD ME THE TRUTH.
HAD SHE LIED TO ME IN THE
MOMENT, I WOULD KNOW WITHOUT A
SHADOW OF A DOUBT THAT I
COULDN'T TRUST HER.
>> I WOULD BE WILLING TO WORK
WITH YOU.
>> THE FACT THAT YOU TOLD ME THE
TRUTH, I RESPECT THAT SO MUMP,
AND I'M TOTALLY WILLING TO WORK
WITH YOU, BUT I NEED.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THERE MIGHT BE
AN OLD-SCHOOL ALLIANCE COMING
TOGETHER, ETHAN, PARVATI, DANNI,
MYSELF.
THE OLD-SCHOOL GUY, WE GOT A
RAPPORT WITH EACH OTHER.
SEE, THIS IS WHAT THEY DON'T DO,
THE NEW SCHOOL PEOPLE.
THEY DON'T HAVE FUN.
THEY DON'T GET TO KNOW ANYBODY,
YOU KNOW.
>> IF WE CAN GET THROUGH THIS
VOTE TOMORROW, IT WOULD BE
MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL FOR US TO
WORK TOGETHER, SHOWING THE NEW
KIDS THE ROPES.
>> I DID NOT SLEEP ONE WINK LAST
NIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
TONIGHT.
>> WE HAVE THE MAKE A DECISION
BY TONIGHT.
>> I KNOW
>> AND ONE OUT OF THE TEN OF US
IS GOING TO BE THE FIRST PERSON
VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME, AND
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THE LIVE
ALONE ON THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
I AM SCARED
>> I AM SCARED.
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> PEOPLE ARE PARANOID.
>> INCLUDING ME.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I FEEL SO PARANOID.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I KNOW
>> PLAYING WITH WINNERS MAKES
EVERYONE MORE PARANOID.
I ALSO THINK IT'S JUST SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT FIRST PERSON BEING
VOTED OUT OF THE GAME THAT YOU
JUST DON'T WANT TO BE THAT
PERSON.
>> WE'RE GOING TO PULL SOMEONE
IN TO VOTE AT BOSTON ROB
>> ME, YOU AND NAT HAVE A GOOD
CONNECTION.
>> I'M SO DOWN WITH THAT
>> I DON'T TRUST ANYBODY.
>> THE PACE OF THE GAME IS WARP
SPEED.
I AM SO UNACCUSTOMED TO THIS.
I HAVE NO CLUE THAT'S GOING ON.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO
THROW UP RIGHT NOW.
AT THIS POINT I'M WITH ROB.
>> I THOUGHT WE'D HAVE MORE TIME
TO GET INTO THE GROOVE, BUT
THERE'S IN TIME FOR THAT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> WHAT DO I THINK?
>> YEAH?
>> MY RELATIONSHIP WITH JEREMY
STARTED BEFORE
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I TRUST
HERE.
NOBODY ELSE
>> I CONNECTED WITH HIM RIGHT
AWAY.
HE WAS MY NUMBER ONE UNTIL HE
GOT BLINDSIDED AND THEN I PLAYED
FOR JEREMY THE REST OF MY
SEASON.
SO IT'S NOT BLOOD, BUT IT'S
PRETTY CLOSE WITH JEREMY.
IF I HAD TO PICK ONE NOW, I
THINK ADAM.
>> MORE THAN DENISE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHEN ADAM AND DENISE
DISAPPEARED TOGETHER, THAT WAS
STRIKE ONE.
I DON'T NEED A SECOND REASON TO
TRY AND SAY NO, NOT THEM.
PICK ONE, LET'S GET IT DONE.
>> WHO YOU VOTING OFF?
>> DENISE AND ADAM ARE THE ONES
THAT WALKED OFF.
>> THEY GOT LOST, BUT THEY HAD
THE MAP.
>> TAKE YOUR PICK.
>> NAMES ARE BEING THROWN OUT.
NOBODY REALLY WANTS TO PIN 'EM
DOWN, BUT LIKE DENISE IS BEING
THROWN OUT.
ADAM IS BEING THROWN OUT.
ONE, NOT ME.
TWO, IT'S NOT ME.
THREE, IT'S NOT ME.
FOUR, IT'S NOT ME.
IT'S A GOOD TIME TO TALK.
BUT MY GUT IS TELLING ME TO KEEP
ADAM SAFE BECAUSE HE KNOWS THE
GAME, AN HE NIGHT KNOW HOW THE
MANEUVER THROUGH THIS.
SO I GOT TO GO WITH MY GUT.
>> YOU AND DENISE WENT OFF
LOOKING FOR --
>> WE DIDN'T GO LOOK FOR AN
IDOL.
>> YOU KNOW HOW THIS GAME GOES.
THAT'S GROUP CONSENSUS.
EVERYBODY NEEDS A TARGET.
THE EASY TARGET FROM THE GET-GO
WAS YOU AND DENISE.
>> I WENT TO LOOK FOR THE WATER
WELL WITH DENISE.
WERE WE HAVING A STRATEGIC
CONVERSATION ALONG THE WAY?
OF COURSE.
THAT SHOULDN'T BE LIKE THE END
OF THE WORLD.
>> ADAM OR JEREMY?
>> THEY SHOULD BE WAY MORE
WORRIED ABOUT NATALIE AND
JEREMY'S EXISTING RELATIONSHIP
COMING INTO THIS GAME, ROB AND
AMBER'S MARRIAGE THAN ME GOING
OFF WITH DENISE.
>> THEY SAID YOU AND ME AS THE
POTENTIAL TARGET
>> OH, GREAT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO FIX THAT
PROBLEM TONIGHT.
>> JEREMY AND NATALIE?
>> NOT SURE, WHICH BUT BETWEEN
JEREMY AND NATALIE.
>> OKAY.
>> WOULD YOU BE WILLING THE TAKE
A BIG SHOT?
>> AT WHO?
>> SPLITTING UP JEREMY AND
NATALIE
>> ADAM CAME UP TO ME AND HE
SAID, WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS OF
SPLITTING THE VOTES BETWEEN
JEREMY AND NATALIE.
>> I DON'T MIND, THAT YOU KNOW,
I'M TELLING YOU, HE'S LOYAL.
>> YOU THINK?
>> ADAM?
>> I MEAN, BECAUSE WE GOT A LOT
RIDING ON THIS.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
>> ADAM AND DENISE, NEITHER ONE
OF THEM ARE TRUSTWORTHY, RIGHT?
WHEN ADAM AN DENISE RAN OFF, IT
PUT TARGET ON THEIR BACK, BUT
NATALIE AND JEREMY ARE LIKE
THIS.
THEY'RE THING AS THIEVES.
THEY'VE PLAYED TOGETHER.
AND I REALIZE THAT'S IRONIC
COMING FROM ME, BECAUSE MY WIFE
IS IN THIS GAME WITH ME.
BUT THE DIFFERENCE IS SHE'S ON A
WHOLE OTHER ISLAND.
BUT FOR REAL, THE THREE OF US
WORK TOGETHER UNTIL THE END?
>> YEAH.
I'M IN
>> I'M IN A UNIQUE POSITION.
I COULD BASICALLY CHOOSE WHICH
WAY I WANT TO GO.
>> ROB DOESN'T CARE?
>> NEW YORK I DON'T THINK ANYONE
CARES.
>> WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
>> I'M THINKING ADAM.
>> OKAY.
WE JUST DECIDING, RIGHT?
>> NO, WE DID NOT.
>> DANNI OR ADAM
>> THERE'S CASES FOR BOTH.
>> NEW YORK WE GOT TO THINK THIS
THROUGH.
>> RIGHT NOW WE'RE VOTING OUT
EITHER ADAM OR DENISE, BUT THERE
IS THIS OTHER PLAN WHERE IT'S
GOING TO BE NATALIE OR JEREMY.
>> SO IT'S WHAT?
>> WE'RE LITERALLY ABOUT TO GO
THE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
THEY STILL HAVEN'T CHOSEN
BETWEEN DENISE OR ADAM.
IS IT ME?
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
>> DUDE, EVERYONE IS LOSING
THEIR MINDS.
>> I KNOW THEY ARE.
>> DO YOU THINK EVERYONE IS JUST
DUMB OR REALLY SCARED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW, BECAUSE LIKE LOOK,
YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW STUPID THIS
FEELS?
LIKE YOU AND I ARE PROBABLY THE
BIGGEST TARGETS, AND I DON'T
THINK FEEL TOO WORRIED
>> ME EITHER.
>> LIKE WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
THAT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE THE%
WAY IT IS.
I KNOW, USUALLY WHEN YOU FEEL
>> ROB AND I ARE LIKE, ARE WE
BEING PUNKED?
>> THIS IS PRETTY BAD.
WE HAVE THE PLAY "SURVIVOR" FOR
EVERYBODY.
THE TWO OF US ARE PLAYING FOR
TEN PEOPLE.
>> WE ARE VERY OBVIOUSLY THE TWO
BGGEST THREATS THIS THIS GAME,
AND WHAT IS GOING ON?
PEOPLE ARE SO TERRIFIED TO SAY
THE NAME OF SOMEBODY, BUT PAST
CHICKEN.
WE HAVE TO GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
IF YOU DON'T TELL WHITE HOUSE
THE VOTE IS GOING TO BE, THEN
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN AT
TRIBAL?
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM TO BE A
VERY FULLY BAKED PLAN.
SADDLE UP, KIDS.
IT'S GOING TO BE A BUMPY RIDE.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH.
GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN, AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL, BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE STILL REPRESENTS YOUR
LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE IS GONE, SO ARE
YOU.
THAT IS GOING TO BE THE CASE FOR
SOMEBODY TONIGHT.
SO ETHAN, LET'S START WITH JUST
THE CULTURE SHOCK OF BEING BACK
OUT LIVING IN A JUNGLE SLEEPING
ON BAMBOO.
WHAT'S IT BEEN LIKE?
>> I MEAN, THE PACE OF THIS GAME
IS SHOCKING TO ME COMPARED TO
THE LAST TIME I PLAYED.
THAT WAS LIKE GLACIAL SPEED.
>> Jeff: YOU'RE NOT EVEN
TALKING ABOUT SHELTER.
YOU'RE JUST TALKING ABOUT
STRATEGY?
>> OH, YEAH.
WERE YOU TALKING ABOUT SHELTER?
>> Jeff: ROB, LIKE ETHAN, IT'S
BEEN A WHILE SINCE YOU PLAYED.
ARE YOU FEELING, THAT AS WELL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THE GAME HAS EINVOLVED.
IT'S NOW AT PACE THAT'S
LIGHTNING FAST, AND YOU GET IN
LINE OR GET OUT.
>> Jeff: WOW.
>> JEFF, WE LANDED ON THAT
BEACH, AND THERE WERE PEOPLE
THAT WERE GONE, LITERALLY GONE.
>> Jeff: JEREMY, WHO WAS
MISSING?
>> I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> Jeff: DENISE, THE TRIBE
LIVES TOGETHER, KNOWS WHAT
HAPPENED, AND THERE'S RELUCTANCE
TO TELL ME.
I JUST WANT TO BE A PART.
IT'S ME.
IT'S ME
>> YES.
YES.
WELL, I'LL THROW MYSELF UNDER
THE BUS BECAUSE I WAS ONE OF THE
DUMMIES THAT TOLD -- PULLED THE
WORST "SURVIVOR" MISTAKE.
ADAM AND I HAD THE MAP.
WE TRIED THE FIND THE WATER
WELL.
WE GOT LOST.
WE WERE GONE WAY TOO LONG.
AS INNOCENT AS IT MAY HAVE BEEN,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
PERCEPTION IS EVERYTHING.
SO I'M NOT STARTING ON A GRAND
NOTE.
>> Jeff: ADAM, IN A SEASON OF
WINNERS, IT'S TOUGH TO USE AS
THE EXCUSE, I GOT LOST.
>> DENISE AND I MET YESTERDAY.
AND THIS IS THE RELATIONSHIP
THAT YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT?
THERE ARE PEOPLE HERE WHO GO
BACK YEARS.
WE HAVE ONE PERSON HERE WHO IS
MARRIED TO SOMEBODY ELSE ON THE
CAST.
>> THERE'S A REASON TO VOTE OFF
EVERY SINGLE PERSON UP HERE.
EVERYBODY HERE HAS WON THE GAME.
EVERYBODY HAS A TARGET.
>> Jeff: NATALIE, THE FIRST
TRIBAL OF ANY SEASON COMES WITH
ONE CLOUD THAT JUST LOOMS OVER,
WHICH IS, OH, JUST PLEASE NOT
FIRST.
DOES THAT GO THROUGH YOUR HEAD,
BECAUSE IN YOUR SEASON, YOUR
SISTER WAS VOTED OUT FIRST.
>> YEAH.
I CAN PUT MY FEET IN NADIYA'S
SHOES, BUT I THINK I HAVE IT WAY
WORSE.
ONE, I HAVE EDGE OF EXTINCTION
WAITER FOR ME, AND TWO, THIS IS
"WINNERS AT WAR."
THERE'S A LOT MORE PRESSURE ON
ALL OF US SO WHETHER IT'S A
SCAPEGOAT EXCUSE OR NOT, ONCE
THAT SEED HAS BEEN SET, THAT
PICKS UP SPEED.
BEFORE THEY KNOW IT, THAT
HAPPENED, THEY WENT OUT
TOGETHER, AND IF THAT'S THE
REASON I CAN USE, THAT'S PART OF
THE STRATEGY.
>> Jeff: ADAM.
YOU CAN'T BE FEELING ANY BETTER
AT THIS POINT.
>> NO.
>> WE'RE WINNERS AT WAR, JEFF.
EVERYONE IS HOLDING A LOADED
REVOLVER BEHIND THEIR BACK, SO
NO ONE SHOULD FEEL COMFORTABLE,
AND PROBABLY A LOT OF PEOPLE DO
FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> Jeff: NOBODY SHOULD AND A
LOT DO.
JEREMY, THERE IT IS.
>> YEAH, I DON'T LIKE THAT
ANSWER THAT SHE GAVE AT ALL
ACTUALLY.
I THINK WHEN YOU COME TO TRIBAL,
THOUGH, THIS IS WHERE YOU FIND
OUT WHO HAS YOUR BACK AND WHO
YOU CAN COUNT ON LATER ON.
>> Jeff: SO BEN, WHAT DO YOU
DO, KNOWING TRIBAL IS LOOMING
BUT NOBODY WANTS TO SAY WHO THEY
THINK IT SHOULD BE?
>> MY HEART IS RACING RIGHT NOW.
IT'S JUST HONESTLY POUNDING.
I KNOW YOU JUST ASKED THE
QUESTION, AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT IT WAS.
>> Jeff: MICHELE, EVEN AS I
ASK BEN, YOU PUT YOUR HANDS IN
YOU FACE.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M A CALM PERSON
IN MY REGULAR LIFE, THAT'S HOW I
PLAYED THE LAST GAME, BUT EVERY
WORD CAN BE SKEWED AND TWISTED.
MY HEAD IS ON A SPINNER.
I FEEL LIKE I'M TRYING TO HOLD
ON.
>> JEFF, I'M NOT THE CALMEST
PERSON ON THE OUTSIDE OF THE
GAME, AND YOU PUT ME IN HERE AND
IT'S WAR OF THE WORLDS GOING ON.
YOU'RE JUST FREAKING OUT.
I THINK THERE ARE PLANS IN
PLACE, PEOPLE THAT WERE OUT HERE
TELLING ME, BUT NOW WHEN PEOPLE
ARE LIKE, MICHELE'S DROPPING
BOMBS LIKE ANXIOUS PEOPLE, NOW
IT'S ALL IN MY HEAD.
IT'S PARALYZING.
>> Jeff: THAT'S A FASCINATING
THING.
SO EVERYBODY HERE HAS WON THIS
GAME, AND EVERYBODY HERE IS
SAYING THEY'RE PANICKED.
>> BUT I HAVE NEVER FELT THIS
NERVOUS
>> THAT'S COMFORTING.
>> MY ENTIRE SEASON.
>> NOT TO MENTION IT'S $2
MILLION.
WE DIDN'T BRING THAT UP FOR
CONVERSATION.
LIKE THE BIGGEST PRIZE EVER IN
THE HISTORY OF "SURVIVOR."
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT'S GOING
THROUGH PEOPLE'S MINDS, AS WELL.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
ADAM, YOU'RE UP.
>> OKAY.
PLEASE LET THIS NOT BE ME
TONIGHT.
>> IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
>> Jeff: IF ANYBODY HAS A
HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL AND YOU
WANT THE PLAY IT, NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE DENISE.
ADAM.
DENISE.
TWO VOTES DENISE.
NATALIE.
WE'RE TIED, TWO VOTES DENISE,
TWO VOTES NATALIE, ONE VOTE
ADAM.
NATALIE.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES NATALIE, TWO
VOTES DENISE, ONE VOTE ADAM.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT WAR,"
NATALIE.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
NATALIE, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> BEQUEATH YOUR FIRE TOKEN TO
ANY PLAYER STILL IN THE GAME.
I DON'T THINK IT'S HIT ME THAT I
JUST GOT VOTED OFF FIRST.
IT'S REALLY WEIRD.
HOLDING MY OWN TORCH, I HAVE
NEVER PICKED UP A TORCH AT
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
I HAVE NEVER GOT VOTED OFF, BUT
AFTER SO MUCH EXPECTATIONS FOR
MYSELF HERE ON EDGE OF
EXTINCTION, I THOUGHT I WOULD BE
CRYING, BUT I'M JUST MAD.
THIS IS THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
YOU WILL HAVE TO WORK HARD FOR
EVERYTHING.
IF LONLINESS SETS IN, YOU MUST
FIND RESOLVE TO OVERCOME.
IF YOU ARE INDUSTRIOUS, YOU CAN
EARN FIRE TOKENS TO HELP YOU GET
BACK IN THE GAME.
IF AT ANY POINT YOU WISH TO END
YOUR ADVENTURE, RAISE YOUR SAIL
AND THE BOAT WILL PICK YOU UP.
THE TOKENS ARE COOL.
THE SIGN SAYS "BACK IN THE
GAME."
THAT MIGHT BE IN LIMBO FOR NOW,
BUT THERE IS STILL A CHANCE FOR
ME.
>> SO YUL, HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
ARE YOU A FREE AGENT?
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY.
I WOULD BE HAPPY TO WORK WITH
ANYONE WHO WANTS TO WORK WITH
ME.
>> THAT'S MY PHILOSOPHY.
>> ME, TOO, ESPECIALLY IF PEOPLE
ARE ALREADY LIKE FAMILY OUTSIDE
THE GAME.
HOW DO YOU INFILTRATE THAT?
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M MOSTLY
WORRIED ABOUT.
>> WHAT?
>> FAMILY.
>> THEY ARE.
>> IT'S VERY RARE FOR ME THE
TAKE SOMETHING SO PERSONAL, AND
TO FEEL SO HURT ABOUT IT, BUT
BACK ON ISLANDS OF THE IDOL,
BOSTON ROB TOLD ME THAT HE WOULD
NEVER COME OUT HERE.
AFTER SPENDING 36 DAYS WITH
BOSTON ROB AND LISTENING TO HIM
SAY THAT HE WOULD NOT COME OUT
HERE --
>> WAIT, HE FLAT OUT SAID "I
WON'T PLAY?
>> FTS
>> HE SAID, "I WILL NOT PLAY.
>> HE LIED TO YOU FOR 36 DAYS.
>> I SAID I DIDN'T WANT THE PLAY
WITH MY EMOTIONS.
I WANTED TO PLAY A STRATEGIC
GAME.
BUT IT'S JUST THAT EVERY TIME I
SEE AMBER, WHICH IS ALL DAY, I
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
SO IF THE OPPORTUNITY ARISES,
AMBER WOULD BE THE AMONG THE
FIRST TO GO IF I HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
>> WE HAVE THE STICK TOGETHER.
>> I AGREE.
I THINK WE SHOULD GROUP THE ODD
ONES OUT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M THE ODD ONE OUT.
>> SO WOULD YOU HAVE ANY
PROBLEMS TRYING THE BREAK UP
THAT WHOLE THING, THAT POKER
THING?
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO RECRUIT
SOLDIERS INTO THEIR ALLIANCES.
SARAH AND SANDRA, THEY'RE TRYING
TO ALIGN ALL THE UNCONNECTED
PEOPLE, BUT THAT ALLIANCE, WHICH
IS BASICALLY PEOPLE WHO ARE
ONE-TIM PLAYERS AND FAIRLY
DISCONNECTED FROM OTHER WINNERS,
IS ACTUALLY THE ALLIANCE THAT
I'VE BEEN ORGANIZING, AND THAT
IS ME, NICK, WENDELL, AND
SOPHIE.
WENDELL, SO ARE YOU TOTALLY ON
BOARD WITH US?
>> 100%.
I'M LOCKED AND LOADED.
>> WE'RE IN A WAY BETTER
POSITION THAN I EVER THAWING WE
WOULD BE COMING INTO THIS GAME.
THE FACT THAT I WAS WORRIED THAT
BEING UNCONNECTED WE WOULD BE AT
A DISADVANTAGE.
THE FACT THAT WE ARE UNCONNECTED
AN WE'RE IN THE CENTER GIVES US
ALL THE LEVERAGE, SO THAT'S
HELPFUL.
I THINK SANDRA REALLY IS GUNNING
FOR ROB.
>> I BELIEVE THAT AMBER AND ROB
SHOULD DEFINITELY GET TO THE
EDGE OF EXTINCTION AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE
>> YEAH.
>> I AM LOCKED AND LOADED WITH
OUR FOUR.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I AM WARY ABOUT EVERYONE ELSE
OUT OF OUR FOUR.
>> THE GREAT THING IS I DON'T
THINK PEOPLE EVEN KNOW THIS
ALLIANCES EXISTS.
WITH SANDRA AS WELL AS WITH
SARAH, WE'LL HAVE THE NUMBERS.
IN FACT, WE'LL CONTROL THE GAME.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> ALL RIGHT.
BETTER THAN I WAS LAST NIGHT I
SUPPOSE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TRIBAL PROBABLY COULDN'T HAVE
GONE WORSE.
IT SUCKED THAT NATALIE WENT
HOME, BUT IT SUCKED MORE THAT I
WAS LEFT OUT OF THE VOTE.
I WENT INTO THIS FEELING LIKE SO
MUCH PRESSURE, BECAUSE I FEEL
LIKE I HAD SOMETHING TO PROVE.
PEOPLE WERE A BIT SURPRISED BY
MY WIN WHEN I WAS UP AGAINST
PEOPLE WHO PLAYED BIGGER,
TRASHIER GAMES THAN ME.
>> THE WINNER OF "SURVIVOR,"
MICHELE.
>> AND NOW TO NOT HAVE THE
NUMBERS IS THE WORST POSSIBLE
CASE SCENARIO.
>> ROB AND PARVATI ARE PULLING
THE WOOL OVER OUR EYES
>> ROB IS PRETENDING HE'S NOT
RUNNING THE SHOW, AND HE'S
RUNNING THE SHOW.
>> THIS OLE-SCHOOL CAMP IS
INTIMIDATING.
THEY'RE GOOD AT WHAT THEY DO.
SO MYSELF, MICHELE, JEREMY, AND
ADAM, WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO STOP THIS LEASH LEADING,
BECAUSE WE'RE LIKE A BUNCH OF
GOATS.
WE CAN TAKE CONTROL OF THIS PART
OF THE GAME.
>> OKAY.
COOL.
>> IT REALLY SUCKED LOSEING.
BUT THIS SEASON WHEN SOMEBODY
GETS VOTED OUT, THEY CAN
BEQUEATH A FIRE STOKEN WITH
ANYONE IN THE GAME.
WE ALL STARTED OFF WITH ONE FIRE
TOKEN.
THIS MORNING I SEE A FIRE TOKEN.
YEAH, NAT.
I KNEW YOU HAD MY BACK.
I'M GOING TO GET 'EM FOR YOU,
THOUGH.
SO NOW I GOT TWO FIRE TOKENS.
TWO IS BETTER THAN ONE.
I HAVE THE MOST OUT OF ANYBODY
HERE.
SO I'M THE RICHEST ON THIS
ISLAND.
NOBODY KNOWS HOW VALUABLE THEY
ARE, SO IT'S GOOD TO HAVE TWO OF
THEM.
AND LET'S JUST WAIT ON IT AND
SEE WHERE THIS GAME STARTS GOING
TO SEE HOW IMPORTANT THEY ARE.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
EDGE OF EXTINCTION KIT.
USE FIRE TOKENS TO PURCHASE ANY
OF THE FOLLOWING.
IDOL WITH FULL POWER THREE
TOKENS.
ONE PIZZA, PEANUT BUTTER, BOTTLE
OF WINE, SIX PACK OF COLD BEER.
ALL RIGHT.
I HAD ONE TOKEN.
I HAD TO GIVE IT UP BEFORE I GET
HERE, SO I'M THINKING ABOUT
WHAT'S THE KEY TO ME
ACCUMULATING ENOUGH TO EITHER
GET AN IDOL OR GET AN ADVANTAGE
IN THE CHALLENGE?
AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW THE
BOTTLE.
THIS IS YOUR FIRST OPPORTUNITY
TO GET BACK IN THE GAME BY
EARNING A FIRE TOKEN.
JOURNEY TO THE LAST SPOT YOU CAN
SEE THE SUN SET.
IT DID MAKE ME EXCITED THAT I
MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET BACK INTO
THE GAME AND HAVE A SHOT AT THAT
$2 MILLION.
THAT'S STILL UP ON THE TABLE FOR
ME.
RISES IN THE EAST, SETS IN THE
WEST.
I'M NOT GOOD AT RIDDLES.
MY NIZ CAL STRENGTH IS SOMETHING
I ALWAYS RELY ON, BUT I'M
EMBRACING TESTING MY MENTAL
STRENGTH.
I REMEMBER THE SUN RISING IN ONE
SPOT.
SO I THOUGHT IF I GET HIGHER I
WOULD SEE THE SUN SET.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS LIKE A MILE.
AT THE TOP OF THE ISLAND, MY
QUADS ARE JUST BURNING.
IT SAID THAT YOU WOULD HAVE TO
WORK HARD FOR EVERYTHING, BUT
I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH HARDER IT
CAN GET OUT HERE TO GET TOKENS.
KEEP GOING UNTIL THE LAST PLACE
I CAN SEE THE SUN SET.
MY FIRST TIME AROUND PLAYING IN
NICARAGUA, NADIYA, MY TWIN
SISTER WAS THE FIRST VOTED OFF.
THAT FORCED ME TO GRIND UNTIL I
WON THAT SEASON.
>> Jeff: THE WINNER OF
"SURVIVOR: SAN JUAN."
>> THAT FORCED ME TO WORE HARD.
I DIDN'T COME HERE.
>> YOU CAN SELL THIS TO ANY
PLAYER FROM A LOSING TRIBE FOR
ONE FIRE TOKEN.
>> ON THE PLAQUE WAS
INSTRUCTIONS ON HOW I COULD GET
MY FIRST TOKEN ALONG WITH THIS
LITTLE POUCH.
THE POUCH WAS AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
EVEN THOUGH I WANT THE KEEP THE
IDOL, IT HAS NO VALUE ON THIS
BEACH.
I HAVE TO PICK A PERSON FROM THE
LOSING TRIBE, AND THEN THEY WILL
HAVE THIS OPPORTUNITY TO BUY MY
IMMUNITY IDOL IN EXCHANGE FOR
THEIR TOKEN.
I'M FIRST PERSON HERE, AND I'M
ALREADY AFFECTING THE GAME.
THAT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT FROM
THE LAST EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
SO ALTHOUGH I DON'T GET THE
EXCITEMENT OF HAVING AN IDOL AND
POLITICIAN AN IDOL, THINGS I DO
HERE HAVE A RIPPLE EFFECT ON THE
GAME.
IT CAN END UP CHANGING THE
ENTIRE COURSE OF THE SEASON.
DURING THE GAME, STILL PLAYING
FROM THE OTHER SIDE.
AMAZING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS.
DAKAL GETTING YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE NEW SELE TRIBE.
NATALIE VOTED OUT IN THE FIRST
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO TODAY'S
IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> Jeff: FIRST THINGS FIRST,
SANDRA, GOT TO TAKE IT BACK.
THANK YOU.
ONCE AGAIN IMMUNITY IS BACK UP
FOR GRABS.
FOR TODAY'S CHALLENGE, YOU'RE
GOING TO PADDLE OUT AND RETRIEVE
A BAG OF NUMBER TILES.
YOU'LL THEN RACE BACK OVER A
SERIES OF OBSTACLES.
YOU'LL THEN USE THOSE TILES TO
RELEASE THREE RINGS AND ATTEMPT
RELEASE O LAND THOSE RINGS ON TH
PADDLES.
THE FIRST TRIBE TO FINISH WINS
IMMUNITY, SAFE FROM THE VOTE.
LOSERS TRIBAL COUNCIL WHERE
SOMEBODY WILL BE THE SECOND
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR"
WINNERS AT WAR.
DAKAL, YOU HAVE ONE EXTRA
PERSON.
YOU'RE SITTING SOMEBODY OUT.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
SANDRA GOING TO SIT OUT.
>> SURPRISE.
>> Jeff: TAKE A SPOT ON THE
SITOUT BENCH.
EVERYONE ELSE TAKE A MINUTE TO
STRATD JIEZ.
WE'LL GET STARTED.
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY, SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
FIRST STAGE, YOU GOT TO PADDLE
OUT.
LET'S SEE HOW WELL YOU WORK
TOGETHER AS A TRIBE.
>> COME ON.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE!
>> Jeff: SELE QUICKLY INTO THE
WATER.
DAKAL RIGHT BEHIND.
>> KEEP MOVING.
>> GO, GO, GO GO, GO,!
>> GO!
>> Jeff: NOW IS WHERE YOU MOVE
IT RIGHT HERE.
SELE RUNS INTO THEIR FIRST
OBSTACLE.
THAT OPENS THE DOOR FOR DAKAL,
WHO IS VERY CALM.
>> GOOD JOB, DAKAL, GOOD JOB.
>> RIGHT SIDE.
RIGHT SIDE HARD.
>> Jeff: DAKAL IS GOING TO GET
TO THEIR STATION FIRST.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE UNTYING.
SELE CAN'T GET TO THEIR STATION.
THEY'RE CLOSE.
BUT THEY'RE STILL TOO FAR.
SARAH HAS THE NUMBER TILES FOR
DAKAL.
THEY'RE HEADED BACK.
DAKAL NOW WITH A NICE LEAD.
ROB TRYING TO PULL THEM CLOSER.
>> HARDER!
>> Jeff: DAKAL THERE.
THEY START UNTYING.
SELE TRYING TO MAKE BACK TIME.
PARVATI TRYING THE HOLD ON.
ROB STILL WORKING ON THE KNOT.
ROB BACK ON THE BOAT.
GOT THE START PADDLING AGAIN.
DAKAL, YOU GOT A LOOSE END.
YOU'RE GOOD.
EVERYBODY OVER THE CRATES NOW.
>> LEFT SIDE HARD.
RIGHT SIDE HARD, RIGHT SIDE
HARD, RIGHT SIDE HARD!
>> GO!
>> KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING, KEEP
GOING.
>> GO!
>> Jeff: THERE GOES DAKAL.
KIM IS IN THE WATER.
YOU'RE GOOD, SELE.
START GETTING UP THOSE STEPS.
DAKAL IS ALL IN.
THEY'RE HEADING TO THE BARREL
ROLL.
THERE GOES DENISE.
THERE GOES DANNI.
THERE'S ADAM.
DAKAL FIRST TO THE BARREL ROLL.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET EVERYBODY
OVER.
>> OKAY, PUSH ME OVER.
>> Jeff: SELE IS ALL IN.
THEY'RE TRYING TO CLOSE THIS
GAP.
TYSON FIRST OVER FOR DAKAL.
THERE GOES TONY.
SAFE -- SARAH IS OVER.
IT'S GOING TO BE ETHAN TRYING TO
GET OVER FOR SELE.
AND HE'S OVER.
DAKAL STILL IN THE LEAD.
IT IS VERY TOUGH TO GET PEOPLE
OVER THIS BARREL.
SELE STRUGGLING AGAIN AS DAKAL
ONE PERSON AT A TIME, WOW, ROB
LAUNCHES PARVATI OVER, LITERALLY
THREW HER OVER THE BARREL.
THERE GOES DANNI BEING LAUNCHED.
ROB IS SINGLE-HANDEDLY LAUNCHING
ONE TRIBE MEMBER AFTER ANOTHER
OVER THE BARREL.
DAKAL HAS EVERYBODY OVER.
NOW IT'S UP THE NET CRAWL.
>> GOOD JOB, DAKAL, GOOD JOB!
COME ON, GUYS, YOU GOT IT.
WE MEAD THIS HEAD START.
WE NEED IT.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
>> Jeff: SELE DOWN TO FOUR
GUYS LEFT TRYING TO GET ADAM
OVER.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING FABULOUS.
THEY'RE STILL SPINNING.
HEY, TONY, PAY ATTENTION.
LET'S GO.
EYES OVER HERE.
>> Jeff: DAKAL WORKING ON
THEIR COMBINATION.
>> THEY'RE STUCK ON THE WHEEL.
LET'S GO.
WE NEED THIS LEAD.
>> Jeff: THERE ARE THREE SETS
OF NUMBERS.
ONCE YOU FREE THOSE RINGS, YOU
CAN START TOSSING.
>> GET ON MY SHOULDERS, READY?
>> Jeff: ROB AND JEREMY THE
LAST TWO.
JEREMY TRYING.
HE CAN'T DO IT.
JEREMY GETTING ON THE SHOULDERS
OF ROB, WHO HAS BEEN A WORKHORSE
IN THIS CHALLENGE.
HE HAS EITHER LIFTED OR
SUPPORTED EVERYBODY.
YUL WORKING ON THE COMBINATION.
NO, GOT THE TRY ANOTHER.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
>> Jeff: BEN GOING TO HOIST
ETHAN ON HIS BACK IS JEREMY CAN
REACH.
GREAT TEAMWORK BY SELE.
WOW.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO IT.
>> PULL ME!
PULL ME!
>> Jeff: SELE HAS EVERYBODY
ACROSS.
LET'S GO.
YUL STILL WORKING ON THE
COMBINATION.
AND HE'S GOT IT.
DAKAL HAS THEIR RINGS FREE.
IT'S GOING TO BE TIE ISN'T AN
WENDELL TOSSING RINGS FOR DAKAL.
SELE TRYING TO GET BACK.
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED.
THEY STILL HAVE TO SOLVE THEIR
COMBINATION LOCK.
YOU'RE GOOD, SELE.
START SOLVING.
TYSON GOING TO SWITCH OUT AND
GIVE IT TO WENDELL.
>> YES!
>> Jeff: WENDELL HAS THE FIRST
PADDLE.
NOW ADAM TRYING THE SOLVE THAT
COMBINATION.
EVERY PART OF ADAM'S BODY IS
TWITCHING TRYING TO FIGURE THIS
COMBO OUT OUT AND GIVE DAK DOING
A CHANCE TO REALLY GET IN ON
THIS.
JUST MISSES.
TWO LEFT FOR DAKAL AS ADAM
CONTINUES TO STRUGGLE ON THE
COMBINATION.
HE'S GOT IT.
THE RINGS ARE FREE.
IT'S GOING TO BE BEN AND JEREMY
TOSSING THE RINGS FOR SELE.
THEY HAVE SOME WORK TO DO.
JEREMY STICKS THE FIRST ONE AND
WE ARE TIED JUST LIKE THAT, 1-1.
THIS IS WHY YOU ALWAYS DIG IN
EVERY CHALLENGE EVERY STEP OF
THE WAY.
YOU ARE NEVER OUT OF IT.
AND JEREMY DOES IT.
SELE HAS THEIR SECOND RING.
ONE RING LEFT.
>> COME ON, JEREMY.
>> Jeff: WENDELL TO TIE IT UP.
IT'S ON AN OFF AGAIN FOR
WENDELL.
>> YOU GOT THIS, JEREMY.
>> Jeff: JEREMY FOR THE WIN.
AND HE DOES IT!
SELE WINS IMMUNITY, SENDING
DAKAL TO TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
GOOD JOB.
YOU GUYS GAVE IT ALL.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> Jeff: SELE, NICE JOB.
NOBODY WANTS TO GO TO TRIBAL
BACK-TO-BACK.
>> GET THAT.
>> YEAH, BABY.
>> Jeff: SELE, SAFE FROM
TRIBAL COUNCIL.
NOBODY GOING HOME FROM YOUR
TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD OUT.
ENJOY THE NIGHT OFF.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
DAKAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP, AND SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE
THE SECOND PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: WINNERS AT WAR."
>> WINNING THE CHALLENGE, IT'S A
GREAT MOMENT, BUT IN THE BACK OF
MY HEAD I'M WORRIED ABOUT HAVING
MY WIFE ON THE OTHER TRIBE.
AMBER HAS A HUGE TARGET ON HER
BECAUSE OF ME.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING TO HELP HER.
SO IN THIS MOMENT, THIS IS
POSSIBLY MY WHIFF'S LIFE IN THIS
GAME.
>> STUPID QUESTION, ANYONE WANT
TO KEEP NATTILY COMPANY,
VOLUNTEER FOR THAT?
>> DO YOU?
>> HELL NO.
>> I HAVEN'T DONE THIS IN 13
YEARS, WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
WE GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL?
ANYONE WANTS TO TALK TO ANYBODY
SHOULD JUST BE CIVILIZED ABOUT
IT
>> THAT WOULD BE A FIRST.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GUYS AT?
>> SO WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I WOULD RATHER GET OUT AMBER
>> I THINK IT NEEDS TO BE NICK
OR SANDRA
>> I DO, TOO.
>> AM I GOING TO GET IN TROUBLE
FOR SAYING PEOPLE?
I THINK SANDRA OR NICK.
>> THAT WILL START A WAR.
>> SANDRA OR TONY?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> TONY OR SANDRA.
WE GOT TO DECIDE.
>> EVERYBODY IS RUNNING AROUND
LIKE A CHICKEN WITH ITS HEAD CUT
OFF.
THE FIRST TRIBAL IS WHERE THINGS
ARE REVEALED, WHO IS WORKING
WITH WHO.
>> I'M WITH YOU GUYS.
I WANT THE PLAY WITH YOU GUYS.
>> YOU KNOW, I FEEL TOTALLY
SOLID WITH KIM OR TYSON.
BUT OTHERWISE I'M LOVES.
I'M NOT USED TO THIS STYLE OF
PLAY, BUT I BETTER DIVE IN.
>> THE SMARTER MOVE IS AMBER FOR
HER TIE, BUT I WEAVE TYSON IS A
HUGE THREAT
>> I HAVE NEVER SEEN THIS MUCH
SCRAMBLING.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
>> THIS FEELS DIFFERENT.
>> THIS SEASON EVERY SINGLE
PERSON IS A THREAT.
SO EVERYBODY IS RUNNING AROUND
TRYING TO MAKE AS MANY PLANS AS
POSSIBLE.
>> EVERYBODY DITCHED ME.
>> AND THE FAR GET IS CONSTANTLY
SHIFTING.
>> WENDELL, NICK, TONY, SANDRA,
THE WHOLE CREW.
>> EVERYBODY IS SO OUT FOR
BLOOD, I THINK SOME OF THESE
PEOPLE THINK IT'S A REWARD TO
GET TO GO TO TRIBAL, BECAUSE
THEY GET TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT.
>> ARE WE CRAZY NOT TO GET
SANDRA OUT FIRST.
>> WHEN NAMES ARE THROWN OUT,
SHE'S THE PERSON WHO GOES TO
THAT PERSON AND SAYS, YOUR NAME
HAS BEEN THROWN OUT.
>> THEY'LL GET RID OF YOU
BECAUSE YOU'RE SHADY.
>> I'M GOING TO SPREAD TRUTH,
LIES AND RUMORS.
IT WORKS FOR ME, AND I CAN
AFFORD TO DO THIS, BECAUSE WHEN
WE GOT BACK TO CAMP FROM THE
CHALLENGE, I REACH IN MY BAG,
AND I FIND THIS LITTLE BABY.
MY FIRST IMMUNITY IDOL ON
WINNERS AT WAR.
THIS IS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL.
IT IS GOOD FOR YOUR NEXT THREE
TRIBAL COUNCILS, BUT IT WILL
COST YOU ONE FIRE TOKEN.
THERE'S NOTHING TO THINK ABOUT.
I'M BUYING THIS HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL WITH MY ONE FIRE TOKEN.
REGARDLESS.
NOW I'M STARTING TO REALIZE THE
EXTREME IMPORTANCE OF FIRE
TOKENS, AND I'M MAKING THE DEAL.
I WANT TO THINK THAT NATALIE
MIGHT HAVE SENT IT TO ME SOMEHOW
FROM THE EDGE OF EXTINCTION.
I'M NOT SURE, BUT I'M SO
RELIEVED THAT I HAVE THIS.
IF I GET A BAD FEELING ON THE
PIT OF MY STOMACH, I'M GOING TO
PLAY THIS IDOL, BECAUSE THERE'S
A LOT OF NAMES THROWN OUT THERE.
>> THEY'RE OKAY WITH TONY GOING
TONIGHT.
>> DISCUSSIONS ARE CONSTANTLY
BEING HAD, AND EVERYTHING IS IN
FLUX.
>> NOW IT'S YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> NOW IT'S ME.
TYSON JUST SAID --
>> TYSON WANTS TO VOTE ME OUT.
COME ON, MAN, REALLY?
LET'S GO.
THEY SEE ME CALM AND COOL AND
LAID DOWN AND RELAXED.
WHEN I KNOW IT'S GAME ON, I GO
STRAIGHT TO TEN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TELL TYSON NO
VOTE FOR AMBER TO SPLIT THAT
VOTE.
WE'LL TELL EVERYBODY WE'RE GOING
FOR AMBER, BUT WE'RE ALL VOTING
FOR TYSON.
>> WE'RE VOTING OUT TYSON.
>> HE WILL GET SO BLIND SIDED.
TYSON IS VERY POWERFUL AND
DANGEROUS.
HE'S A FUNNY GUY.
PEOPLE LOVE HIM.
>> DOES ANYONE WANT THE MARVEL
AT THE SPLENDOR WHEN WE SAY OUR
PRAYERS?
ALSO BE SURE TO INCLUDE ME,
BECAUSE THANKING ME FOR HOW
DELICIOUS THIS RICE WILL
PROBABLY BE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> WE GOT TO BREAK UP THE POKER
LINES.
TYSON, AMBER, KIM, AND I WANT TO
GET TYSON OUT OF THE GAME.
AMBER IS NOT RUNNING AROUND
DOING ANYTHING.
PLUS YOU LEAVE THE BIGGEST
TARGET, HUSBAND AND WIFE, IN THE
GAME STILL AS BIG SHIELDS.
SO TYSON GOES HOME.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> MY THOUGHTS ARE I THINK
BASICALLY THE SINGLE BIGGEST
FEAR THAT EVERYONE HAS IN THE
GAME IS THAT ROB AND AMBER AND
THIS WHOLE POKER ALLIANCE ARE
GOING TO DOMINATE.
THAT'S THE THING THAT SEEMS TO
BE GALVANIZING EVERYONE.
>> I HAVE YOUR BACK 100%.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THE POKER ALLIANCE IS COMING
BACK THE BITE ME.
THE SECOND I REALIZE THAT THINGS
WEREN'T GOING THE DIRECTION I
WANTED THEM TO, MY STRATEGY
SWITCHED FROM DICTATING THE
DIRECTION OF THE GAME TO PURE
SURVIVAL MODE.
>> MAYBE AMBER AND KIM OR --
>> THEY'RE SUPER CLOSE.
>> BREAK THEM UP ONE WAY OR THE
OTHER, BUT I'M WITH YOU GUYS, IF
YOU'RE TELLING ME THIS THE WAY
WE'RE GOING.
>> COOL.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYWHERE TO GO
BUT INTO THEIR WARM POKEY
POISONOUS EMBRACE.
I FEEL BAD FOR KIM AND AMBER,
BUT IT'S WORTH IT TO ME TO
FORFEIT THIS BATTLE TO HOPEFULLY
WIN THE WAR.
>> DO YOU GUYS HAVE SOMEONE IN
MIND?
>> IT'S ME.
>> DO YOU HAVE SOMEONE?
>> NEW YORK BUT I FEEL LIKE IT'S
ME.
>> THAT'S FUNNY.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO SAY IT?
>> I'M NOT SAYING NOTHING.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN I'M GETTING A
VERY BAD VIBE FROM EVERYONE.
I KNOW THAT I AM NOT SOMEONE
THAT PEOPLE WANT IN THEIR
CONVERSATIONS RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S MOMENTS OF PARANOIA
WHERE LOTS OF PEOPLE ARE TALKING
AND I WALK UP AND IT STOPS.
THEY WANT TO DO SOMETHING AND
THEY DON'T WANT ME TO KNOW ABOUT
IT.
GOD, IT'S JUST AWKWARD.
>> DO YOU WANT...
>> SO... WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
NOBODY WILL TALK.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN IN THIS
POSITION BEFORE.
MY SEASON I WAS MAKING THE CALLS
EVERY SINGLE TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> COME ON.
YOU CAN TELL ME.
PLEASE TRUST ME.
>> THIS IS SUCH A BAD FEELING.
>> GIVE ME A HUG.
>> I DON'T THINK I REALLY
UNDERSTOOD TODAY WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO BE ON THE OUTS.
THIS IS NOT THE WAY I ENVISIONED
MY COMEBACK.
I THINK WHAT'S GOING ON IS I
THINK TIE ISN'T AND AMBER AND I
ARE IN TROUBLE FOR THE SAME
REASON, AND I THINK IN THIS CASE
THE POKER ALLIANCE HAS BECOME
WHAT THAT IS.
>> TYSON SAYS HE'S GOING TO VOTE
AGAINST AMBER OR KIM.
>> HE'S NOT WITH US.
>> HE'S ACTING, MAN.
HE'S ACTING.
WE'LL SEE TONIGHT.
>> ONE OF THE THREE OF US ARE
BEING VOTED OUT.
THAT'S JUST IT.
I THINK THERE'S REALLY NOTHING I
CAN DO TO CHANGE THAT.
I FEEL LIKE THIS IS A LARGE
GROUP OF PEOPLE VOTING TOGETHER.
TO START THIS GAME THE WAY I DID
HONESTLY, IT'S BEEN THE BIGGEST
MESS.
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF YOU IS
A TORCH GO.
AHEAD HEAD AND GRAB A TORCH.
DIP IT IN AND GET FIRE.
SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
AMBER, YOU FIRST PLAYED 20 YEARS
AGO, BUT THE LAST TIME YOU
PLAYED WAS 16 YEARS AGO.
KIDS THAT WERE BORN THE LAST
TIME YOU PLAYED ARE NOW DRIVING
CARS.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING WITH THE
GAME GIVEN ITSELF FULL-ON?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, I LOOK
EXACTLY THE SAME, I HAVEN'T AGED
A BIT.
>> Jeff: 100%.
>> THAT FEELING OF BEING ON EDGE
IS DEFINITELY FAMILIAR, HOWEVER,
IT WAS HAPPENING MUCH QUICKER
THAN WHAT I'M USED.
TO I FEEL LIKE IF I'M NOT ON MY
TOES MOVING AT ALL TIME, I'M
BEHIND.
>> Jeff: TYSON, WHEN THE GAME
MOVES AS FAST AS IT MOVES NOW,
CAN YOU SEE A TASTE OF DIFFERENT
ERAS?
>> YEAH, FOR SURE.
I THINK THE OLDER ERA,
ESPECIALLY LIKE YUL, HE KIND OF
OBSERVES BEFORE HE ACTS.
SOME OF THE NEWER PLAYERS
IMMEDIATELY ACT.
>> Jeff: TONY, IS HE TALKING
ABOUT YOU?
>> I HOPE NOT.
I'M NICE AND SLOW, MAN.
I'M STEALING A PAGE OUT OF HER
BOOK TODAY.
>> Jeff: AMBER YOU DON'T SEEM
TO AGREE WITH THE IDEA THAT TONY
WAS SLOW
>> NOT AT ALL.
HE WAS RUNNING AROUND FROM
PERSON TO PERSON TODAY.
IT WAS QUITE NERVE RACKING.
>> WEREN'T YOU?
WASN'T EVERYBODY?
I CAME THE PLAY.
THE FIRST TWO DAYS I DIDN'T
NEED.
TO WE WON.
TODAY I NEEDED TO TALK ABOUT
SURVIVAL.
>> Jeff: SO TODAY YOU WERE
SPAR, GETTING READY, AND YOU
THINK SHE THINKS THAT'S CRAZY?
>> EXACTLY MY POINT
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S CRAZY.
I'M MORE COOL, CALM, AND
COLLECTED
>> AMBER HASN'T BEEN AROUND FOR
A VERY, VERY LONG TIME.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP UP WITH THE
PACE OR YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE THE
MOVE OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT'S JUST HOW IT IS.
>> Jeff: SO SOPHIE, WHAT WAS
THE FEELING AS YOU GUYS STARTED
TO GET CLOSER AND CLOSER TO
TRIBAL.
WAS IT GOING LIKE THIS, OR DID
IT REACH A FLOW AND WE GOT A
PLAN?
>> NEW YORK I'D SAY THE DAY WENT
LIKE THAT.
AND IT TOTALLY DROPPED OFF.
BUT IT WAS SCARY BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T KNOW, DID I HAVE THE
RIGHT LAST CONVERSATION, BUT
SOMEBODY HERE DID NOT.
>> Jeff: SANDRA, WHAT DID YOU
SEE HAPPENING TODAY?
>> THERE WAS PANIC, BECAUSE
THERE WERE SEVERAL NAMES THROWN
OUT.
BUT THEN THE NAMES WERE NARROWED
DOWN TO A VERY SMALL GROUP.
>> Jeff: KIM, YOU'RE NODDING
>> YEAH, I'M THE SMALL GROUP
THAT IT GOT WHITTLED DOWN TO.
>> Jeff: HOW DO YOU KNOW YOUR
NAME GOT BROUGHT UP
>> GOSH, IT'S A LONG STORY.
>> Jeff: GIVE ME THE SHORT
VERSION.
GIVE ME THE HEADLINE.
>> THE HEADLINE IS: POKER PLAYER
ALLIANCE.
WHICH DOESN'T EXIST.
I PLAYED IN A POKER GAME AIER
AGO OUTSIDE OF THE GAME, WHICH
IS GOING TO TURN OUT TO COME
BACK AND BITE ME
>> TYSON, DID YOU HEAR YOUR NAME
LIKE KIM?
>> FOR SURE.
I HEARD MY NAME.
I HAVE TO HOPE THAT WHAT I DID
WAS ENOUGH TO PROVE TO PEOPLE
THAT I'M HERE TO BE WITH THEM.
>> BUT HE'S PART OF THAT POKER
CREW, TOO.
>> THAT'S WHAT'S INTERESTING TO
ME.
THERE ARE SO MANY CLOSE
RELATIONSHIPS THAT ARE SO MUCH
CLOSER THAN THE POKER PLAYER
ALLIANCE THAT MET FOR THREE
HOURS.
POKER PLAYER ALLIANCE IS NOT A
THING.
IT'S IN THE A THING.
IF IT IS, I'M NOT IN IT.
>> Jeff: WENDELL, IT'S AN
INTERESTING LAYER.
"SURVIVOR" HAS BEEN AROUND SO
LONG THAT SOME OF YOU GUYS HAVE
GENUINELY BECOME FRIENDS.
>> YEAH, IF THERE WAS A DIAGRAM,
IT WOULD BE ALL OVER THE PLACE,
BECAUSE THERE ARE THESE FOUR
PEOPLE FROM HERE AND THESE TWO
PEOPLE MET HERE AND THESE PEOPLE
PLAYED ON THIS SEASON AND THAT
SEASON.
SO WE DON'T KNOW HOW TIGHT
PEOPLE THAT PLAYED POKER ONE
TIME A YEAR AGO WOULD BE.
>> NOT CLOSE.
>> NOT CLOSE ACCORDING TO KIM,
NOT CLOSE, BUT YOU HAVE TO TAKE
THAT INTO CONSIDERATION.
>> BUT WHEN $2 MILLION IS AT
STAKE, I THINK FRIENDS ARE
NOT -- WE'RE WILLING TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> Jeff: WOW.
NICK, DOES THE CANDOR FROM AMBER
SURPRISE YOU?
JUST FLAT OUT SAILING, IT'S $2
MILLION, LET'S DON'T PRETEND.
WE'LL KILL EACH OTHER.
>> YEAH, THAT DOES SURPRISE ME.
BUT I UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, ONCE THEY HEARD $2
MILLION, THEY STARTED THINKING
ABOUT PUTTING THAT CHECK IN
THEIR OWN POCKET, NOT THEIR
FRIEND'S POCKET AND NOT ANYBODY
ELSE'S POCKET.
>> Jeff: SOPHIE, YOU'RE
NODDING.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT THE MONEY.
>> IT'S $2 MILLION, JEFF.
I MEAN, THAT IN ITSELF WILL
CAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE TO JUST DO
ANYTHING, AND IF FRIENDS HAVE TO
BE LOST ALONG THE WAY, THEN I
THINK IT'S A PRICE EVERY SINGLE
PERSON OUT HERE WILL BE WILLING
TO PAY.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT.
IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
NICK, YOU'RE UP.
I'LL GO TALLY THE VOTES.
IF ANYBODY HAS A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL AND YOU WANT THE PLAY IT,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME TO DO SO.
OKAY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, NICK.
KIM.
THREE VOTES KIM, ONE VOTE NICK.
AMBER.
TWO VOTES AMBER.
WE'RE TIED.
THAT'S THREE VOTES AMBER, THREE
VOTES KIM, ONE VOTE NICK.
AMBER.
THAT'S FOUR VOTES AMBER, THREE
VOTES KIM, AND THE SECOND PERSON
VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR: WINNERS
AT WAR," AMBER.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
AMBER, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
>> I HAVE ONE.
>> Jeff: STAY TUNED FOR SCENES
FROM OUR NEXT EPISODE.
"SURVIVOR" IS LOOKING FOR NEW
PLAYERS.
IT COULD BE YOU.
APPLY NOW.
>> Jeff: NEXT TIME ON
"SURVIVOR," WHEN THE ENEMY
STRIKES...
>> IT COULD BE SANDRA.
IF SHE VOTED MY WIFE OUT, THIS
IS WAR.
>> Jeff: AND BLOWS UP YOUR
GAME.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> Jeff: YOU'LL NEED TO CLIMB
OUT OF THE RUBBLE.
>> IT'S LIKE 20 FEET TALL.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THE
FIRST.
>> HOW IS THIS GUY STILL ALIVE?
>> I BET YOU'RE HAPPY TO SEE ME.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE ANYMORE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE MY TRIBE WON.
I WANTED THEM TO LOSE SO BAD.
>> I KNEW I HAD A HUGE TARGET ON
MY BACK.
I PUT MY TRUST IN PEOPLE HOPING
FOR THE BEST, AND IT WASN'T THE
BEST.