Tribal Council was a disaster,
as usual.
I think the votes
are all going to Jeremy,
so I gave Jeremy
the 50/50 advantage,
and he decided to not play it.
-Want to chat? Okay.
-Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Let me put this down.
But I guess this Tribal Council ended with a positive outcome
because Jeremy is still here.
On the flip side...
-All right.
-...people know
that I was willing
to play my advantage for him,
so now everybody knows
about my advantage.
I feel like...
that was a ... cluster ...,
-"A."
-It was, it was.
I've been wanting to play
this really aggressive game,
but I sort of feel like I took
a butter knife to a gunfight,
and I don't really know
how I can recover.
Every single person,
including Tony,
came up to me today,
saying that it was you.
Oh, my God.
This isGroundhog Day
for me here.
Three Tribals in a row that
everybody is coming after me.
I-I wish I knew why
I was so popular around here.
I genuinely am like,
"Why would they not tell me
to not vote for you?"
Because I obviously
would've jumped on board
-to not vote for you.
-I don't know. I don't know.
-I'm gonna give you this back.
-Okay.
But I have
a connection with Michele,
and Michele gave me that 50/50
coin to play if I needed it.
But I give that 50/50
back to Michele.
I want nothing to do with that.
My game is not coming down
to a 50/50 coin flip.
-What could I have done?
-No, no, you're fine.
You're fine,
you're fine, you're fine.
So, who do we trust?
-No one.
-Nobody.
This is the penultimate step
of the war.
This is right before
we take off, and...
it's gonna get
really, really ugly.
-How'd you sleep, Denise?
I slept so well.
-Did you?
-Did you, really?
-It was-- I-- Yeah, no.
I don't know that I slept
that much last night.
-Oh, you didn't sleep?
-Oh, I'm being sarcastic.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
-No.
Oh. You didn't?
Last night at Tribal Council,
I just said to Jeff,
like, "I'm done."
But when I say I'm done,
it's not
I'm done with the game--
it's I'm done with dealing
with things the way
that I've been dealing
and getting myself as upset as
I have been about the process.
What are you gonna write
on there?
Mm, I got a,
I got a little plan.
-Yeah?
-Mm. Just for my-- Just...
Like, one of those,
like, moments--
like, it's all good.
-For your own sanity here?
-Yeah.
I'm not a tattoo gal.
I don't have any tattoos.
Probably never will.
But then I was laying
in the shelter last night,
and I thought,
"No, I need two tattoos."
I need the one on the left handthat says, "Endure,"
to remind me I can.
I'm capable of staying out here for another nine days.
But then I also know
that it's okay to let go.
Like, "endure" and "let go"
and know that both of those
are totally okay.
-A lot of work in front of us.
-I know.
-Yo, we got to get here.
-Well...
All I got is about
a week left, yo.
-Two.
-That's it.
Two? Two what?
-Two weeks.
-Uh, how is that two weeks?
-You...
-Nine days, bro.
Five days of working.
-Working week.-Yo, that's not two weeks, man.
This isn't a work week.
That's why police officers
need to go back to school.
-Why?
-'Cause you just said
nine days is two weeks.
-Ten days is two weeks.
-14 days is two weeks.
No. I work five days a week.
But you're
not getting any days off.
-You're not going home
on the weekends here.
-No, but I'm...
You're still working
on the weekends,
-so you count those days.
-Not on the...
-not on the off days, my friend.-Listen,
-you're here for 39 days.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-You don't go home
on the weekends.
-No, but I'm chilling
-on the off days. Off day, offday, off day, off day. I mean...-You're still working.
-You're still working.
Yes, you are.
-No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
-No, I'm on a vacation in Fiji.-What are we doing right now?
-We're working.
We're working right now.
-I'm on vacation.
-No, it's not working.
-We're talking about strategy.
-No, we're talking about a game.It's a game.
-That's work. That's work.
-It's a game. We're playing.
-It's work though.
-It's still work.
-No, for you it is.
See, 'cause you work hard.
I work smart.
I'm not gonna keep
telling you that, man.
This thing, right,
with Jeremy--
he's a fireman.
I'm a police officer.
We're always feuding, and-andwe have a little rivalry going.
It's for fun over here
on Survivor.
But I know
Jeremy is a number for me.
I know he trusts me.
So, right now, my plan is
to try to keep Jeremy around.
Because if Jeremy goes home,
the hyenas are gonna come out
in a full pack
and start attacking us.
Strategically, what do you thinkis the right move next?
If we get rid of Jeremy,
then the other...
-hyenas pull together...-And they decide, yeah. Mm-hmm.
-...then it's gonna be
problematic.
-It's not gonna be fair.
This part of the game is tricky.
Cops-R-Us, man.
We got to stick together.
We're trying.
You know, how many years has
it been since we first formed?
-Six.
-Six years?
I said-- That's why I said,
"Six years in the making."
So, Sarah and I,
we've played this game.
Six years ago, we formed
an alliance, Cops-R-Us,
and I burned her.
-And this was the plan
in the first...
-I know.
Right. And I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
It took six years
to get to that.
-It's crazy.
-Three seasons.
This is a tiebreaker, Sarah.
Oh, my God.
Cops-R-Us.
Let's see who...
-I'm gonna have
to blindside you, man.
Try it.
-Try it.
-No, stop.
Now I got to know Sarah,
and we said,
"Let's just stick together
and just keep this Cops-R-Us
going all the way to the end."
And we've been doing good
so far.
I mean,
that's our plan right now,
is to take Cops-R-Us
all the way to the end.
So, this is what's scary, is,
-okay, Ben hates Jeremy.
-I know that.
-That's a problem.
-Yeah.
We take out Jeremy,
and we're sitting ducks.
And-and Ben
won't not take him out.
Mm-hmm.
Ben, Sarah, Tony.
We're in a lock solid
final three.
Period. No ifs,
ands, buts about it.
Here's our problem
that we're running into is
Ben wants Jeremy gone.
But if we got rid of Jeremy,
Tony and I are sitting ducks.
Nick's with us, but he doesn't
want to go to the end with us.
I know that. I know that.
So, at this point,
getting rid of Nick
would be the smarter option
for my game.
But what's smart for my game
is not the smartest for Ben's.
And, at this point,
Ben's pretty stubborn,
and he's not gonna budge.
So I figured I would have
my work cut out for me
this afternoon,
to have to try to convince Ben
to get rid of Nick.
Jeremy is
actually Tony's number.
-Right.-When we're thinking about it--
no emotions,if it's just written on paper...
-Yeah.
-...Jeremy is Tony's number.
-Jeremy wants to work
with you and me also.
-Right.
-And I believe that.
And so we need to take outpeople who are not our numbers.
-I know.
-And, uh-- But-but I told you
that I-I would let you make
that decision.
If you want Jeremy gone,I will write Jeremy's name down.
If Ben never gets
a turn at driving,
Ben's not gonna go
to the end with me.
So if we make Ben believe
that this is his decision,
then everything's good.
But this is just a ploy
so we can vote Nick out.
The only personwho's not our number is Michele
and then Nick.
So, what if we just
blindside Nick?
Uh, that's up to you, bro.
-I-I got your...
-And we have Denise.
Are you okay to work with Jeremymore than you are
-with Nick at this point?
-One more round, I could.
As long as it's me,
you and Sarah.
Jeremy is more beneficial
for my game at this point.
So there's this thought
of keeping
Jeremy, Tony and Sarah.
With seven people left,
keeping them around
is a shield for me.
They're bigger threats.
Nick's not gonna want to go tothe end with me, you and Sarah.
-Yeah, he wants
to go with Michele and...
-Yeah.
Where Nick, on the other hand,
he's walking around frantic.
He's trying to play both sides,
and he's not doing
a very good job,
'cause everybody's seeing it.
I trust Denise more
than I trust Nick.
And Denise,
she's lockstep with me,
and she'll vote any way
that we want to vote.
If you wanted to get rid
of Nick, you just let me--
Whatever you want, you
let me know. We talk about it.
-We say, "Okay..."
-I just don't know
if he's fully with us, dude.
-I don't think he is.
This right now,
in this war,
is the hardest mission yet.
The reason why is because it's gonna be a huge blindside.
I'm scared that Michele will
play her advantage for Jeremy.
Plus, there's a 50/50 immunity
that we have to flush
and do this correctly.
At this point in the game,
if this goes screwed up,
our squad
and this mission is blown out.
Come on in, guys!
All right.
Let's get to
today's immunity challenge.
First things first,got to take back the necklaces.
I know, Denise.
-Sad face.
It is.
Tony with the kiss.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna race out with a ball,
toss it into an overhead track,
and then catch it
on the other side.
Once you have
both balls through,
you'll dig under a bar
and race to the finish,
where you must solve
a slide puzzle.
First to finish wins immunity--
safe from the vote.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the 15th person
voted out and sent to the Edge.
In addition,
winner earns two fire tokens.
Take your spots.
-We'll get started.
-Cool.
All right, here we go,
for immunity
and two fire tokens.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
First job,
you got to get a good toss,
and it's got to get
all the way down the track.
Jeremy's got his first.
Tony drops his.
Michele drops hers.
Ben's ball drops.
Got to go back.
Sarah does a nice job
out of the gate.
Nick drops.
Got to find your ball.
-Oh.
-Ben's still looking for it.
There goes Denise.
Denise with a nice job.
Nick gets his first.
Ben is right there.
He's got one.
Jeremy going for that second.
He falls but makes the catch!
Jeremy can start digging.
Tony has his first.
Sarah has her second.
Nick has his.
There's Ben with his second.
It's Tony, Denise
and Michele still going.
Tony has his second.
-Michele yet to get one.
Denise looking for that second.
God.
It's Jeremy first through.
Now you got to get rid
of that fatigue
and get to your
mental part of the game,
solving the slide puzzle.
Ben is through.
Tony digging through.
Sarah's through.
Day 31.
Immunity on the line right here!
Nick is through.
On the puzzles, Jeremy,
Tony, Ben, Nick and Sarah.
Huge stakes.
That $2 million is within sight.
You want that necklace tonight.
Denise with her second.
She can start digging
through the sand.
-Michele had it.
Couldn't catch it.
Can't even get one ball in.
Everybody on the puzzle
except Michele,
-but she's still fighting.
Tony facing his nemesis,
the slide puzzle.
He did this in Cagayan,
moving pieces around
at a furious pace
but getting nowhere.
Spencer caught him and won.
Tony, is this making
any more sense this time?
Yeah.
Sarah continues to slide.
Ben moving pieces around
quickly.
Denise nodding to herself.
Jeremy down on the end.
He's been moving consistently.
Tony moving much more slowly
this time,
as though he actually
understands what he's doing.
Once you track in
on this slide puzzle,
you can get a rhythm
and solve it quickly.
Jeff, Jeff, Jeff!
Nick thinks he has it.
-That came together quickly.
And he does!
Nick wins individual immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council--cannot be voted out
-of this game.
Thank you, thank you.
Nice job.
-I didn't even get one ball.-It's okay. Michele, it's okay.
-Michele, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's so frustrating.
-Smile.
Yeah.
-You're fine.
It's okay.
-What happened? You did great.-I couldn't even get a ball up.
-It's okay.
-You tried.
You didn't give up, honey.
-You didn't give up, 'kay?
-It's all good. We all got second place.
-It don't matter.
-You played awesome.
-You're good. 'Kay?
-You're fine.
-You're good.
Nick, come on over.
Finally.
First individual immunity
win this season.
Safe from the vote tonight.
In addition,
-two fire tokens are yours.
-All right.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
As for the rest of you,
31 days in.
We are so close to the end.
And yet, tonight,
somebody will be voted outof this game, sent to the Edge,
where you will have to fight
your way back in
for a shot
at the $2 million prize.
Grab your stuff. Head back tocamp. See you tonight at Tribal.
-Congrats.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Nice work.
-Appreciate it.
Nick gets immunity.
The one person
that we'd been hoping initiallywouldn't get immunity
so that we could vote him
got immunity.
So then it was instantly like,
"I wonder what the plan B
is gonna be."
Nice job.
Nick winning
was a bad thing for us.
You know, we were trying to
target Nick and blindside him,
and so now we have to come back to camp and rethink
how we're gonna pull this off.
As of right now, I say Denise.
I'm down.
Easy.
Are you good with that?
I mean, yeah.
So, it would be easy
to take Denise out.
However, Denise is my friend
and a number right now.
And I've been debating
on whether or not
to push Jeremy to go
or whether or not to keep him.
It takes one of the shields out for me, but,
in the same breath, it
breaks up Michele and Jeremy.
So, at this point,
I'm trying to create
a little distrust
between Jeremy and Michele
and also make sure
we know where
that 50/50 idol's going.
I don't want a 50/50 to ... us.
Unless you can get the 50/50, J.
Want me to get it?
I can get it.
-You can?
-Yeah.
I started planting seeds
in Jeremy's head
and being like, "Hey,
can you get that 50/50
from Michele?"
Let's start--
Let's try to vote out Michele.
I don't know.
Those are my thoughts though.
About Denise?
Yeah.
You know,
they're tight as hell,
so, yeah, that's fishy.
-I don't believe it at all.
-What do you...
what do you think
they'll want to do then?
...but I don't believe that.
Everybody's saying Denise's name'cause this is the easiest one.
Denise was the one
that was, like, checked out
last Tribal Council.
But that's the thing.
It's never an easy vote,
especially Winners at War.
So, right away,
I'm like, "Nah,this doesn't sound right to me."
They want me
to get Michele's 50/50
-and then...
-Who does?
-Ben.
-Oh.
-But I don't want that.
-Yeah.
-I don't want Michele
to go home.
-No, not at all.
Denise is definitely
a smoke screen.
I don't know
who they're putting
their votes on,
whether it's me or Michele.
But I don't trust Ben
at all.
That's what I'm saying.
I will say no.
I have a feeling...
He said to me,
"Can you get the 50/50?"
I said,
"I'll talk to her. I'll see
if I can get the 50/50."
He just said to me, he goes,
"Watch, Jeremy's sketchy.
-He's gonna ask you
for the 50/50."
-See that?
Ben is saying,
"Keep an eye out for Jeremy.
He's gonna ask you
for your advantage."
And then Ben is going to Jeremyand saying,
"Ask Michele for her advantage
and see if she'll give it
to you."
So he's playing both sides.
Listen, we got to get Nick,
-and we got to get Tony.
-Tony.
-Get Ben?
-Yes.
I'm down.
Ben going-- that's great for me.
And Jeremy going--
that's worse for me, because
me and Nick
are gonna be picked off next.
So...
I have a best-case scenario,
a worst-case scenario,
and I'm just hopingit leans more towards this side
than towards Jeremy.
If we keep it quiet,
he'll be in the dark
and we can blindside him.
He wants both of us gone,
so why not go after him?
Yo, listen, me, you, Michele
-and Nick.
-Vote who?
Ben.
So, Jeremy, he wants
to vote out Ben.
Jeremy and Ben
been clashing for a while now.
Right now,
are you 100% Ben or Denise?
-I'm Ben. Ben.
-That's it?
-You?
-Okay. Yeah, I'll do it.
That's it, then.
So, he wants Ben out of the game for his best interest.
That's not my best interest.
Not for the cop.
I really don't want to get rid
of Jeremy, but, at this point,
Sarah and I think
that our best thing to do
would be to stay strong
with Ben.
So, listen, Jeremy thinkshe's super tight with me, right?
Us four are supposed to go--
you, me, Jeremy, Michele
and-and Nick,
-right-- we're supposed
to get you out.
-It was Jeremy's plan.
-Wow.
Yeah, just now.
Yeah, just now. All right?
But the truth is it's me,
you, Nick voting Jeremy.
You, you vote Michele.
Them two are voting Ben.
It's over. Three.
Okay.
So, we're gonna split the votesbetween Michele and Jeremy.
So, the guys-- me, Nick
and Ben-- we're voting Jeremy.
Denise and Sarah,
they're voting Michele.
And then Michele
can play her advantage
that she has, a 50/50.
And whether
it's "safe" or "not safe,"
our real votes tonight
are going to Jeremy.
For sure? Okay.
Just saying,
what if this happened?
If Nick went with Jeremy,
Michele,and they put three votes on Ben,
-he could've just flipped it
and takes Ben out.
-Yeah.
-Do you think
he's gonna do that?
-No.
Right now, the plan
is to vote out Jeremy.
But I also
don't fully trust Nick.
He's a hard one to read.
I think Nick definitely wants
to build a résumé for himself.
And I guess
tonight's gonna tell
whether he's with us
or if he's against us.
As long as we're all together, Idon't really care what they do.
We... We're good.
If we don't mess it up,
then we're gonna
come back here tomorrow.
There's two plans going on,
one to get Jeremy out
and one to get Ben out.
And I'm in a bit
of a power position.
Mm-hmm. We'll be fine.
-Yeah. Absolutely.
-Mm-hmm.
-You have to. You have to.
-Yep. I know.
In a season like this.
I have Ben's fate in my hands,
and I have Jeremy's fate
in my hands.
But I'm not making my decision
based on what I want to happen
tomorrow or the next day.
I'm making my decision
based on day 39.
How do I get there?
Who can I beat?
How do I win this $2 million?
I am just trying
to win this game,
period.
All right, let's start with
today's immunity challenge.
Michele, you struggled.
A lot. That happens.
Sometimes people struggle.
But what's unique
about struggling on a show
like Survivor
is that everybody is watching.
And is that part of it,
the vulnerability
of being exposed?
Thanks for pointing it out,
that now
everybody is gonna be watching
at home.
But I try not to think
about what other people
are gonna perceive,
and I just try to focus
on where my headspace is at.
Ben, you're always
being watched.
You're being watched
by the other players.
You're being watched by me.
Now you're being watched
by the jury.
Does it become
a little schizophrenic,
trying to remember
which persona
to use in this moment
to this person or this group?
I think it's hard
to be someone you're not
when you're not eating,
when you're emotional
after vote-outs,
physically drained
from challenges.
You're mentally, physically
and emotionally just broke.
And that's where the truth
comes out.
Sarah, you've talked a lot
about being a police officer.
Police officer
has similar situations,
in which you have to walk
into something cold
and decide who you're going
to be in that moment
to try to defuse a situation.
There cannot be hesitation
when we go on a call.
You have to go in and you haveto be confident in your answers.
You have to be confident
in the way that you speak.
And when I played
the game before,
I definitely relied on that.
This season, it's different.
When you play with people youknow and you really care about,
you don't want to be a jerk.
Nick, Sarah's really talking
about "it's personal."
But can you win this season
by saying,
"Not personal to me"?
I think you can probably win
this season like that.
But I feel like, this season,
people are more truthful.
I guess the question is
Does that leave the door open
for somebody
to play like a first season
and do whatever they got to do
to make it to the end?
I'm not sure. It-It's tough.
Jeremy, you play the first timewith your wife.
You play the second time,
your wife comes out
and tells you about a new baby
that's coming.
You play the third time,
your entire family's here.
How can this game be anything
but personal?
I mean,
th-this game is personal.
But I think you have to find
a middle ground.
I don't thinkyou can use everybody as robots.
And you can't play
totally with your heart.
You have to find some type
of sweet spot there.
So, Ben, you're trying
to thread that needle,
which says,
"I do respect you
and I do like you
and I'm probably going
to betray you at some point."
Yeah.
It's an emotional
and tactical crossroad.
I mean, we've all heard
each other's stories.
We've talked about our children
and what are we gonna do
to better ourselves
as-as humans
when we get back home, right?
And so trying to focus
on the personal side
but realize that
we're still in a tactical war
-is the hard part.
-Michele,
this all sounds genuine,
that there's respect
and friendships.
And yet there's still lies.
When the game is over,
what does that do
to your ability
to trust just in the world?
Yeah, it's hard.
I remember getting home
from my last season
and having my guard
all the way up,
double-checking
and triple-checking people,
and, like,
they were just telling you
that you should turn right up onthis corner to get to the bar.
Ben, I noticed you nodding
while she was talking.
I remember coming back
from my first season
and having, like,trust issues with my wife and...
The person who you had credited
with saving your life.
Absolutely. That's why
I just want to come in here
and be able to trust people.
You know? I'm not gonna let
the game change who I am.
I'm not gonna let the money
change who I am.
I'm gonna leave here
a better man,
regardless of what happens.
How 'bout you, Jeremy?
I remember, Cambodia,
I went home and I wasn't right
for three months.
-Wow.
-And I remember going
to the fire station,
talking to the guys
that I trust with my life,
and I didn't believe
some of the things they said.
So, this time,I want to have more fun with it,
and I don't want it
to get in my head.
Nick, you're the most recent
winner that's out here.
What was your experience like
when you went back home,
in regards to trusting people?
It was hard for me
to come back so quickly.
I mean,
it does take a toll on us.
You know, people talk about
numbers, strategy.
And it's not a strategic game.
It's a social strategic game.
Like, we're not blocks of wood.
We're not chess pieces
to be moved around.
And I feel like, this season,
there is more emphasis
on the social relationships.
So, Tony,
we now have this foundation
that we all understand.
And yet there are seven of you.
There's about to be six.
Yeah, at this point
of the game, we know
which soldiers we're gonnamarch forward with in this war.
We're locked and loaded,
and we're just ready
to march forward.
Jeremy, that sounds like
there's a group
that thinks they've got
something going.
Um, I think everyone has
their idea of a group, yeah.
Their idea?
Their idea of a group, yeah.
Sarah, you agree with that?
I mean, three Tribals ago,
we thought
this group was with this group
was with this group.
The Tribal after that,
it was a different group
with a different group.
And then,
after last Tribal Council,
there's at least one advantage
that's pretty out in the open.
Which one is that?
Um, the one that Michele has,
which is the 50/50.
You flip a coin, you're either
safe or you're not safe.
So, Michele, were you
a popular person today
with this 50/50 coin?
I don't know.
I gave it to Jeremy
last Tribal Council.
It created a little bit of fear.
I have it. It's the last day
that I can use it.
I expect it to be
played tonight.
Wow. Tony, cryptic answer.
"I expect it to be
played tonight."
I would play it tonight if I hadsomething that I have to play,
whether I needed it or not.
But tonight, we're gonna make
the bed that we want to lay in
for the rest of the game.
Denise, do you have
a pretty solid idea
of what you would like
to see happen?
I-I would like to not feel like
I'm walking down the end
of the gangplank.
I have an idea and a hope of
what I would like to work out,
whether or not
that'll happen tonight.
Again, without the necklace,
as I was reminded
last Tribal Council,
we're not safe.
So, just want to make sure
I have this straight.
The 50/50 coin
is out in the open.
There's no chaos.
Everybody seems
very calm right now.
So, Jeremy, are you optimistic
or pessimistic that the vote's
gonna go your way?
I mean, I don't know about
everybody else,
but every time I see your face
here, Jeff, I'm nervous.
-Except when I have this on.
All right, it is
time to vote.
Michele, you're up.
Mama D needs a win tonight.
I had enough of you.
Sorry, bro.
It's nothing personal.
I have to put my emotions
to the side and play the game.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunityidol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Uh, Jeff, I guess,
since everybody
knows about it,
I should just play it.
Okay.
This is the 50/50 coin.
"Safe" on one side,
"not safe" on the other.
You're gonna flip it
and land it here.
If it comes up "safe," any votescast against you will not count.
If it comes up "not safe,"
any votes cast against you
will still count.
And are you playing it
for yourself?
Yes.
-Okay.
-I think I am.
You think you are?
-Is that a yes?
Yeah, I'll play it
for myself tonight.
Okay.
-Okay.
All right.
"Safe."
"Not safe."
Oh, my God.
Please, please, please.
Yes!
Landed on "safe."
Any votes cast for Michele
will not count.
Can I keep that?
-No. Sorry.
Oh, God.
All right.
I'll read the votes.
First vote
Michele.
Does not count.
Ben.
That's one vote Ben.
Jeremy.
One vote Jeremy.
Ben.
Two votes Ben.
Jeremy.
We're tied. Two votes Ben,two votes Jeremy, one vote left.
15th person voted out of
Survivor: Winners at War:
Jeremy.
Need to bring me your torch.
Jeremy, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
"Bequeath your fire tokens to
any player still in the game.
Grab your torch
and head to Extinction."
Does anybody need...
does anybody need water?
I do. Anybody else?
Yeah. Here it is.
Oh, yeah, I'll get it. Michele?
I'm good, thanks.
Tribal was intense.
It came down to Jeremy or I,
and we both took our shots.
It's been like
an old Western, right,
where we've each had
our-our revolvers
in our holsters,
standing on the street,
and haven't
pulled them yet, right?
And tonight,
the draw went and it feels
fantastic that
I finally got him out.
Thank goodness
Michele didn't give it to him.
-Oh, my gosh.
-I was so upset.
- That was...
-I appreciate it, dude.
-Appreciate what, man?
-Well, just, like, I just--
I have, like-- I full-- I know.
Bro, w-we're 100% together, man.
-I know. I know. It's just...
-You know?
-Like, it's just nice to be...
-Yeah. No, no.
-I've never had this before.
You know what I mean, dude?
-Oh, no. Are you kidding me?
You have-- you never had
two cops work with you.
Exactly, dude.
Tribal worked out
exactly as planned.
This whole entire game,
I've been on the right side
of the votes.
This whole entire game.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, but...
And then you have Michele
that's always been
outside every vote.
She has no idea
what's going on in the game.
In other seasons,
you would call that a goat
and you would want to go
to the end with them.
Not on the Super Bowl season
of Survivor.
You don't, you don't
want that around.
The only scary part is Nick
keeps winning those challenges
-with the puzzles, man.
-I know. I know.
I know. Yeah, I agree.
But I think Michele
needs to go before Nick.
-Oh, 100%.
-Yeah, yeah.
She's a hyena in the game.
And you know what?
Time for you to go home.
You okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
I was wondering
if you'd have the balls
to come down and talk to me.
-Of course I want
to talk to you.
-Mm-hmm.
Honestly, I mean...
you know we can't beat Jeremy.
I know we can't beat Jeremy.
But I'm genuinely curious
what you think
our path to the end
is from here.
I think
I made the right decision,
because the vote for me is aboutbuilding allies moving forward.
Michele-- she wanted
to work with Jeremy.
I have no interest
in working with Jeremy at all.
And she keeps wanting to go
a different direction
than I want to go.
You know what's gonna happen?
I'm public enemy number one,
and you're right after me.
We are on the bottom
of the pecking order.
Now that Jeremy's gone,
ideally, I would love to
get Ben out of here.
Ben is hotheaded, emotional.
He's, like,
an impulsive player.
So...
I definitely feel like
playing with Ben
is like playing with fireworks
or a stick of dynamite.
And I just don't want it
to blow up in my own hands.
There's no path
to the end for us.
Literally none.
Do you think Sarah will
flip on Tony or Ben? No.
-No. But-but they want...
-Do you think Denise will
flip on Ben? No.
Me and Nick are on the bottom,and Nick is too naive to see it.
And you're not gonna get
to the end with this crew.
We are literally
on the bottom here.
But I have to try to find
an avenue for myself,
because nobody out here--
nobody wants to take me
any further than
where I am right now.
Unless I win immunity, I'm out.
But I know that I do
some of my best workwhen my back is against a wall.
It sucks.
And my back is against a wall,
and they haven't seen
the sassy Michele from Jersey.
So it's time for me
to kick it into high gear.
They better buckle in, because
I'm about to go out fighting.
Can't wait to go back
and be with people I like,
eat some food.
I have been mad more times
in this game than I've been madin a year of my life.
But last night might have been
the peak of anger for me.
I don't trust anybody.
Nobody trusts me.
And I'm very frustrated,
because right now,
everybody's playing scared.
And I'm the only one out here
who's willing
to throw things at the wall,
because I have nothing to lose.
What do you think's
going on today?
I don't know. Nothing.
Nobody's gonna strategize today.
Well, what's there
to strategize about?
I know.
It's just get Michele out next.
Shut up.
Nobody's talking to me.
-Oh, BS.
-I'm blackballed.
-No, I'm...
-You are not.
Yeah, I am.
-You are not.-I see the writing on the wall.
-Oh, Michele.
-When you're not in,
the only alternative is out.
It's one thing
to get to the end;
it's another to win it
at the end.
-You know?
-Yeah.
You want to win it, right?
Well, of course.
That's the goal.
So, I just might
throw a Hail Mary in that
direction and see if anybody
bites on it.
There are some people
you just can't beat though.
Who?
You don't think so?
-Hell no.
-And you have
Tony over here who's controlled most of the votes.
He is a huge threat.
-Why?
-Anybody who goes over to
the jury at this point is gonnatell who's running the show.
How do you know
who's running the show?
Perception is everything.
I think when you look at
who you should target,
me or Tony, I would think
go with the bigger threat.
Well, I'm keeping my door opento literally anybody who needs--
who will walk through it, so...
Goes, "Nobody beats him."
Michele's the easy vote-out.
Michele's on the outs.
And Michele has no allegiance
to anybody.
She's going,
"Tony's running the show."
She's trying to pit
me against you.
She's trying to
pit you against him.
I mean, at least she's trying.
-"A" for effort.
Michele can't
keep her mouth shut.
She's completely unpredictable.
So that's why
Michele needs to go.
-Come get your rice.
-Watch out for the lids.
Look at this.
Look how much rice we got.
-Oh, my God. Wow.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
One scoop.
And that's pretty much
all there is today.
Welcome to the Edge, Jeremy.
Wow. Look at that, huh?
The Edge of Extinction--
I hate this place.
This place sucks.
It drains you.
Morale is down. It's tough.
And just being out of the game,
your mind just wanders.
The whole night, I was
running through my mind like,
"What did I do wrong?
What could I have done
to change my situation?"
But, I mean, you know what?
What am I gonna do?
Like, this is
the situation I'm dealt.
I just got to think about
one day at a time,
just getting back
into this game.
Okay.
We got something new.
Yul, stop reading it.
He's already got it.
He should just drop it and run.
-Yeah.
Scoot.
Every time we get a clue,
it's like a bomb goes off,
and everybody just-just darts,
just takes off.
Here we go!
It's like
when a bunch of teenagers
are hanging out in front of,
like, a convenience store
and a cop pulls up, they--
you just start running,
because why wouldn't you?
That stone right out there.
Danni's going for it.
I have been to
the top of the mountain,
and I know that there are
two places that have,
like, stone that you can
overlook everything.
And I was just thinking,
"All right, that might be
the stone throne."
I know I'm the fastest sprinter on the island.
And, uh, and Natalie--
she's a tremendous runner
and challenge threat.
So I'm like, "Man, I need
to get to this throne first."
Having spent so much time
on Extinction,
I knew exactly
where I was going.
I was just worried
that Wendell did, too.
Wendell was so ahead of methat I didn't see where he went.
But once I got to the clearing,
I noticed the beach
was completely empty.
I knew Wendell had taken
a s-strong left up the hill,
and I knew it was all mine.
Yes! Oh, my God.
I was dying,
but I was so excited
that I got the advantage.
It felt really good.
The shortest challenge
we've had so far.
There's a few perksof being here as long as I have.
Natalie knew exactly
where the throne was.
She's the queen of Extinction.
I'm constantly just watching herjust, like, shift and move.
She's become part of the island.
He went up the mountain.
Finding the advantage
didn't come from me
just being able to run fast.
It came from being out here
as long as I have,
keeping my head in the game
and never giving up the reins
on this island.
What is it? Open it.
I need to catch my breath.
Initially, my gut reaction was, like, walk it back to camp,
take myself away
from the group.
But I said, you know what?
It's fine.
I'll go with the flow.
Everybody's kind of, like,
miserable here together.
And we can have it be, like,a group activity for Extinction.
All right. So, an advantage.
Box is cool.
-Oh.
...which I don't have
a lot of time...
That's pretty cool.
Wow.
That is cool.
That's exciting.
You could sell it to Denise, whoyou know has a ton of coins...
Yeah.
Basically.
-Or anybody that I think...
Anybody.
Because they're all together,
so they'll all pool.
They're all together,
so they'll pool tokens.
Going into this next
battle-back challenge,
obviously, I want to do well.
At this point,
the only goal that I have
is get as many fire tokens
as possible.
And that's all I care about.
I'm a little
discouraged because
I have six fire tokens.
I've been saving these puppies
the whole game.
I have all the demand
and none of the supply.
But today is the day.
I look in my bag, and Iactually see something in there.
Hey, look. Yes!
Oh, my God. This is so exciting.
Oh, man.
Oh, this is crazy.
So, my immediate reaction
to this is
I need someone's help.
I only have six fire tokens.
So, I thought I was rich,
but I guess--
You know,
I've landed on Boardwalk here.
I can't even afford this.
So I got to pull in somebody
that has enough tokens
to help me out.
Tony's been my main man,
but he don't have any tokens.
And Michele is the other person I've been working with.
She does have
enough fire tokens
to help me out here,
and I think
if I reach out to Michele
with this,
it will keep me
in her good graces,
even though I voted out Jeremy.
Hey, Michele.
I'm her last hope.
I'm-I'm her only prayer
of staying in this game,
and I think she's a partner
I can really work with.
I have in the past,
and I think I can with this.
That's why I can't say...
That's why I can't say
I could buy rice today,
because I actually
got something.
Okay, well, I can give you...
If, like, need be
and you need to keep
your facade,
-I can give you coins.
-Okay.
-In case...
-But it costs eight.
-I have six.
-Oh, great.
-I'll give you.
-Yeah, okay.
Uh...
It's kind of tough.
All it does is it gives
somebody a disadvantage
in the next immunity challenge.
Nick betrayed me
on the Jeremy vote.
So I wouldn't be here
on the bottom, struggling
to keep my fire alit
if Nick didn't turn on me.
But I have
absolutely nowhere to go.
At this point,
if I'm voted out tomorrow,
then the fire tokens
are souvenirs in my pocket.
All I can do is try to work
with what I have,
and this is what I have
right now.
It would give them
a disadvantage
-at the next challenge?
-One person a disadvantage.
They won't know
who it came from?
No, they'll have no idea
who it came from.
And I'm, obviously,
only telling you.
Okay. Let's think.
So, we just have to think.
I definitely have a lot
to consider,
because this isn't just about
one disadvantage
at an immunity challenge.
It could definitely
go deeper than that.
-Let's cause
a little chaos here.
-Yes.
We have to.
-No.
-No way.
This decision for me
is about the endgame
and about winning this game.
We just have to try to use it
in a way that causes
the most chaos possible.
More money, more problems.
You know what I mean?
Come on in, guys!
All right.
Let's get to today's
immunity challenge.
-First things first,
Nick, got to take it back.
-Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna stack blocks
on a beam
while attempting
to avoid trip obstacles.
The first person
to stack their blocks
so they fall like dominoes
hitting the gong...
...wins immunity.
Safe from the vote.
In addition, the winner
earns two fire tokens.
The last time
you can earn fire tokens.
Today is the last day
you can spend fire tokens.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the 16th person voted out
and sent to the Edge.
In addition,
one thing to deal with today.
There's an advantage
being played.
This advantage comes in the formof a disadvantage.
-It is being played
against one of you.
The disadvantaged player
will have
30% more beam,
30% more blocks to stack.
Wow.
The player receiving
the disadvantage is...
...Ben.
Ooh.
Wow.
A smile.
Yes, sir. Um, you know,
I've yet to receive a token.
Uh, I've yet to receive
an advantage.
So, I mean,
I guess I'm not making
too many friends this season.
I decided to give the disadvantage to Ben because
if he loses this challenge,
that might be the final straw.
And I hope to start some chaos,
maybe get people wanting Ben
out of here so that Michele
can stay, and then Ben
could definitely go.
All right,
we're gonna draw for spots.
We'll get it on.
Wow.
All right, here we go,
for immunity
and two fire tokens.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Day 34. Six people left.
Ben with a 30% more difficult
challenge.
And your first block
dropped, Ben.
Got to get it and come back.
If your blocks hit the sand,
you got to bring them back.
Stop what you're doing
in that turn,
head back
and then come back out.
You can only bring
one block at a time.
The first part
of this course is easier.
You can move more quickly.
But the farther down you go
on this course,
the tighter those steps
will become.
You're trying to balance speed
and precision.
Ben leaps, and it cost him.
Ben's got to get two blocks
and go back.
Every mistake you make
costs you time.
So the question becomes,
"Do I go slow and steady
and hope everybody else fails,
or do I go for broke
and try to pull it out?"
It is Michele
and Tony in the lead.
Sarah right behind.
But Ben is quickly
getting back into it.
Nick has been very steady.
Denise really taking her time.
Like so many
Survivorchallenges,
one mistake, and suddenly
you go from last to first.
We are almost dead even
with Michele,
Sarah and Tony.
-Got to have
your blocks stacked...
Go faster.
...just right.
You don't want to use
any more than you need to,
but you don't want to have
too much space
that they don't connect.
This is gonna
come down to the wire.
If nobody makes a mistake,
this could be over shortly.
Michele dropped one.
That's the setback
you're looking for.
Michele has to go back now.
Tony trying to take advantage.
Sarah trying
to take advantage.
Everybody sprinting on day 34.
That is going
to even things up now.
Michele has to come out
and fill a hole,
which is a wasted turn.
Tony with another block.
Sarah with another block.
Ben with another block.
Even with a 30% penalty,
Ben is in this.
It is now Michele,
Ben, Sarah and Tony.
Who will get it done first?
Immunity on the line.
Safety at
Tribal Council tonight.
Michele has enough blocks.
-She's gonna go for it.
Sarah dropped a block.
You've got to go back.
Ben with another block.
He's got one left.
Going for it.
Michele's gonna go for the win
right here!
It's looking good.
-She's done it!
--Michele has pulled out immunity
on day 34!
-Safe tonight at Tribal Council.-Wow.
Wow.
They ... me. ... disadvantage.
Congrats, babe. You earned it.
That was tough.
Damn.
-Michele, come on over.
-No claps. Notice?
-Right here.
Notice? I needed this, Jeff.
"No claps," meaning from them?
Yeah.
Really, you...
Sorry, Michele.
We didn't know
it was time.
-Michele, no,
hang-hang here for a minute.
-Sure.
-So, you had a huge reaction.
-Yeah.
What is it about this win?
Is it any win
or today in particular?
It's today in particular,because I think the conversation
that was happening at camp was,
"Anyone can win,
just not Michele."
So I needed this so bad.
Um, and I'm grateful.
I'm so, so grateful.
Michele, two fire tokens.
Last day you can spend them,
as well.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
You are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
As for the rest of you,
day 34 will not be enough
for one of you;
it will be the end.
You're voted out,sent to the Edge of Extinction,
where you will have to fight
your way back into this game.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
-See you tonight at Tribal.
Congrats.
-Thank you, Jeff.
Hey, Jeff. Any chance onwho the disadvantage came from?
-No.
- Got to ask.
I was on a funeral march
to my own funeral
these past few days.
So today, I was ready to fight
blood, sweat, tears,
to the death for that win,
and that's what I did.
So, nah-nah-nah-nah-nah.
You can't get me.
I won immunity.
Got to put it on so you
can meet and greet everybody.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
That was all... You earned it.
That was hard.
So, going into
the immunity challenge today,
we had this hope that Michele
was gonna be a locked-in vote.
Unfortunately,
Michele pulled it out
when she needed to,
and Michele won immunity.
So now it's on to plan B.
-Can I put out a proposal?
Sure.
I am pretty sure
I'm on the block tonight.
I'm okay.
I'm not scrambling.
But I'd love to go to the Edge
with rice in my belly.
I know we weren't
gonna do rice today,
but here's my proposal:
to make a nice big pot of rice,and by dusk,
I will buy that bag of rice.
Are you being serious right now?
I'm being very serious.
So, my game plan
coming back into camp was kind of to take on the role
of dejected Survivorplayer
a little bit.
The one that kind of sets up
the proposal of, "Hey,
"I know there's a good chance
I'm on the block,
"but if I'm going to the Edge,
I'd love to go to the Edge
"with a fully belly,
and in order to do that,
"I'll give up my tokens
to make sure that you guys
also stay strong."
And so we got
an extra bag of rice.
But I'm trying
to roll with the idea,
especially for Michele
and for Nick,
that I'm the plan B
without overplaying my hand
with the hopes
that Ben and Sarah
and Tony and I
are all still in lockstep,
and we'll vote out Nick,
barring any other surprises.
Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-Of course. Of course.
And we're all there. No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-That's cool.
-Bring it here.
Okay, okay.
-Okay.
All right.
Prior to Michele winning,
she was a target.
But my game plan now is
to get the vote swung on Nick.
Nick's just got to go.
He's good at puzzling,
and he's creating more chaos
around camp.
I love her.
She's amazing.
But I don't want to go
to the end with her.
-Same.
-Denise?
-Like, at the... Yeah.
-For this... For this reason.
Why?
-She's so lovable.
-Yeah.
She got out the queen.
She's played two idols
at one Tribal.
She just did that. Yeah.
We're telling Nick
and Michele that it's Denise.
Denise played a heck of a "poor me, why me?" and bought rice.
And I think
that, hopefully, they buy it.
We're writing Nick.
-Yeah.
-But we're playing it off
like it's Denise.
-So, so, I... Yeah.
I don't think I'll play
the idol tonight, you know?
I-I think
we're pretty locked solid
with Tony and Sarah,
so I feel pretty safe
in our alliance tonight.
What's up, Nick?
-You just talk with Ben there?
-Yeah, he said Denise.
My plan worked today.
I feel like I'm a genius.
Ben lost.
Michele won. Like, unbelievable.
Everything worked out perfectly.
Michele is in the game
because of me
buying that advantage.
I feel like I'm in
maybe the best position
I've been in this entire game.
So, now I would love to see
Ben go home tonight.
But can I get Tony on board?
What's your read
on the situation?
-Yeah.
-I'll-I'll tell you
what worries me about Ben
is he made the fire to get to
the final three on his season.
He could do that again.
-Exactly. Against any of us.
-I know. That twist, man.
-That fire making twist.
It's brutal.
Can you make fire, Michele?
-No.
No.
It'd take Ben two minutes.
Wow.
Me, you and Nick make a move
to get rid of Ben.
And then we say,
"Sarah, come with us."
-Because now we have
the-the majority.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think it's a bad idea.
There's definitely
a big consideration
to get rid of Ben.
Ben won his season
with a fire-making challenge.
I don't want to go up against Ben. I played a very hard game.
I don't want
to lose it to fire.
I know Ben has an idol now.
So if I'm gonna make a move,now's the time to make the move
and get rid of Ben.
But in the meantime,
I want to open up
the spy nest again.
I want to open it up
for business.
My spy nest is...
I-I built it so nice.
It's up there collecting dust.
So I say, you know what?
I got to put it back to use,
because intel in this game
has been the key.
'Cause this is war. And in war,the more intel you have,
the more you can prepare
yourself for a counterattack.
So...
here's my thoughts.
I anticipate
that you and Tony and Ben
already have a solid three.
Here's my proposal.
I would love nothing more
than to be sittingin the final three with you two.
So, I was open for business,
and the spy nest?
It came through for me big-time,
because I got to hear
a lot of stuff.
Tony's the biggest onethat I do worry about with jury,
only because of his ability
to do that duplicitous...
You know what I mean?
Like, that...
in over here
and totally working over here.
That ability to do that
and the challenge wins.
Denise was like, "Hey, guys,
"what are you thinking
about the final four?
Because I don't think
we can beat Tony."
So, once I heard that,
I knew Denise has to go,
because she doesn't
want me in the finals.
If you don't want me
in the finals,
that means I don't
want you in the finals.
So you got to go.
Let's see who gets
the first punch first.
So, i-if it's me,
you and-and Nick
voting for Ben, we need
somebody else, and, uh...
I was tossing the idea
of blindsiding Ben,
but now no more.
So, right now
the pecking order has changed,
and it went straight to Denise.
So, maybe we actually do
do Denise.
Yeah, that's what
I was thinking, man.
'Cause if Sarah...
Tony and Nick
both seemed pretty receptive
to get out Ben.
But Denise is here offeringherself up on a silver platter,
saying, "All right. Take me."
If I mention it to Sarah
and she doesn't say anything,
then I can't...
I got to let it go
and just go with Denise.
All right, so stick with the...
Let's stick
with the Denise plan.
Let-Let's just see. Let... Yeah.
But we might be able
to get Ben next time.
I don't necessarily want Denise to be the next vote.
I would love
if we could shake things up.
But getting people on board
with a logical plan
in this season
is not as simple as it sounds.
So, again, we're at square one, and it's back on Denise.
I'm gonna give you something
so you can think about it,
-and you come back to me
and let me know.
-Okay.
-'Cause you're my partner.
-I know.
I-I will lose the game for you.
-Yeah.
-For nobody else.
So, this is what I was thinking.
Denise is no good
because she'll pick Ben.
-I heard her talking
to the well.
-Yeah.
-She will go with Ben.
So me and you are gonna be
doing... duking out over fire.
Uh, we got to get Nick
to the final four.
Yeah.
So, at this point,
Denise is an option
and Nick is an option.
Denise is a good option
to vote out
because she slayed the queen,
she found an idol.
Denise has won
two immunities at this point.
She's gotten tons
of fire tokens from the Edge.
She hasn't made anybody mad.
And so she could be tough
to beat in the end.
Do you think
Nick's the right vote?
Uh, I-I don't know.
And then you've got
Nick, who...
He's won immunity.
He has come from the bottom
all season and had to play
at the bottom.
I mean, everybody loves
the underdog story, right?
And that is Nick.
And so you can't
not like the guy,
because he's playing
his butt off,
and he's fighting
every day he's out here.
-We're doing this, all right?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-We're partners. We're partners,and we have to...
-I'm good.
-We're partners forev... Yes.
-...we have to survive.
-You're my partner in crime.
I got this.
-Okay.
-We have to survive. All right.-Yes, we will.
Tony and I are totally
the swing vote on this.
And I'm hoping that we pick
the right road to go down,
but everything about
this season's been difficult.
You're playingthe season
ofSurvivor.
The greatest players
who've ever played.
Mistakes are not allowed
in this.
So this vote tonight
is the biggest one yet.
We'll now bring in the members
of our jury.
All right.
So, let's start
with the immunity challenge.
Michele, you pulled it out,
and your reaction at the end
was pretty big.
Walk me through
why this was such a big win.
Uh, it's been no secret to me
that I'm very, very much
on the bottom.
And how do you know that?
How do you find that out?
Well, nobody would
strategize with me.
Pretty much everybody's like,
"Keep hope alive, Michele."
It's not really
the best thing to hear
when you're trying
to find an in.
So I need this necklace today
like a fish needs water,
like you need a blue button-downand khakis.
-I-I need it.
It's as simple as that.
So, Sarah, reason number 57
that you don't let
anyone in the game
ever know they're in trouble,because that little bit of juice
could have been
the difference today.
100%. You know, I think
when you think you're safe,
you maybe take your foot
off the gas a little bit.
And when you know
you're not safe,
it's pedal to the metal.
Ben, you had
a different experience.
You had a disadvantage
played against you.
30% more challenge
that you had to run.
-That might have been
what cost you.
-Yes, sir.
Uh, you know, a day late,
a block short, right?
It's been the story of my
block career here on Survivor.
You know, it's that adrenaline,
like you were talking about,
that extra push
to-to push towards the end.
And-and I think me and Michele
shared that today.
Do you wonder who
put that disadvantage on you?
Uh, I do, you know?
And you kind of look
at everyone over there,
and you-you wonder
if it came from that Edge
or if it came from somewhere
over here, you know?
You just... You don't know.
But I felt I did my best,
and-and, uh,
like I said, a block short.
Nick, are we at the point
in the game
where you start to think
as much about who you want
to take with you as you do
who you want to get rid of?
I think we're definitely
at that point.
And the hardest part
of the twist with the Edge
and the fire tokens
and everything
is all the unpredictability
and all the question marks.
But after tomorrow,
all those X's and Y's
should be filled with numbers
to where we can actually
solve the equation
of who we want to be
at the end with.
Sarah, how does this idea
of fire tokens and advantages
coming from the Edge
shift how you have to think
of Survivor?
I mean, you have to manage
not just your coins
but everybody else's coins.
So it just addsanother element to the game of:
Who has enough that-that they
could do something with them?
Michele,
what did you notice
about the fire token
and how it impacted
the way you had to play?
I have gotten emotional over
fire tokens that I've gotten
just because I felt down
over some vote-outs.
It's no surprise here that I'vebeen left out of a few of those.
So, when I get that
the next morning,
after a really rough night,
sometimes it is
the hope that I need
to keep me going.
So, you know, everybody talks
about how much they're worth
and what they can buy,
but for me,
they were priceless
in this game.
Ben, the tricky part
of having somebody come back
from Extinction is, right now,
everybody's trying to hold tightto an alliance.
But if anybody in that group
is at all rocky,
they could break everything openand say, "I got my own idea,
and I've been waiting for
this person to come back in."
How much fear does that add
to the game?
About as much fear as a lion
breaking out of a cage
and one person holding the steak
and then pinning it
to two people's back, right?
And so it's
a very scary situation
in the next couple days
about who's coming
and what they're coming with.
Tony, the tough part is
you're desperately trying
to convince
other people that they've gota final three they can count on.
So what do you doto manage what is happening now
in anticipationof what's going to happen soon?
That's a tough question,
and, uh,
the people that are together,
there's a fourth
and there's a fifth
and there's a sixth today,
right?
So, we-we're thinking
about everything.
But, you know,
it's just gonna boil down
to the bonds that we have
and the trust we have tonight.
Denise, how about for you?
You know, not having won
that immunity,
the moves that I have
have become limited.
And coming back and just saying,"Hey, here's where I'm at."
It's been a great,
incredibly stressful 34 days.
I don't want to be done playing,
but if I am done playing,
I'd like to go to the Edge
with a full belly of rice
so that I can at least try
and battle my way back in.
And let's just eat and let it bewhat it's gonna be.
Nick, did that surprise you
that Denise would openly say,
"I think it's me.
And if it is, that's okay,
but can I please have
a last meal"?
I mean, it's always
surprising to hear
somebody say that in Survivor.
But we've had some hard,
hard Tribal Councils
in the past week or so,
and I think everyone
has probably felt that way
over-over the past week or so.
But nobody else has come back
and said, "I'm good.
-Just let me eat. I'm ready."
-No.
-And...
-And it's not...
-Go ahead.
And it's not,
"I'm good. I'm ready."
It's, "I don't want to go,
but I can only do so much."
And it's-it's, again, it'sthe saying of endure and let go.
It's an acceptance of what is.
It's-it's that gut intuition
of saying,
"I just don't want
to scramble anymore."
I just can't do
the cat and mouse.
And I don't want
to be the choice,
and you hope that some alliancesor some ideas that you...
you put out there can stick.
But that's it.
-No.
Nick, any of you guys
that have played this game know
how demoralizing it can be
at times
and how much mental fatigue
it takes.
So when you hear Denise say,
"I'm not giving up,
but I'm not gonna
scramble today,"
as a player,
is that a little bit of,
"Wow, this might be
the easy vote, finally"?
Yeah.
I think
whatever the game hands you,
you kind of have to go with it
and use it to your advantage
to move forward in the game.
And, uh, that's what
it handed me today.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Denise, you're up.
You're still the Queenslayer.
I guess I get to slay
the Queenslayer
even though
I didn't slay the queen.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has
a hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,now would be the time to do so.
Okay.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Nick.
Denise.
One vote Denise, one vote Nick.
Two votes Denise, one vote Nick.
Nick.
We're tied.
Two votes Denise,
two votes Nick.
Nick. That's three votes Nick,
two votes Denise.
16th person voted out of
Survivor: Winners at War:
Nick.
Well done, you guys.
Nick, the tribe has spoken.
Well, you've made it
to the final five.
Tomorrow, somebody from
the Edge of Extinction
will fight their way
back into this game
and back into contention
for the $2 million prize.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
It's the first time
I've ever been voted out.
It feels different
than I expected.
I was starting to see
my path towards the end,
but it was all just
a bunch of lies and deceit.
I made it 34 days in the game.
To make it to the final six,
I mean, I-I'm really proud
of myself.
I got a shot tomorrow,
so we'll see what I can do.
I'll fight to the end.
-How are you, brother?
-Good, man. Last day.
Yeah, man.
Hey, man.
I know. It's amazing.
We don't have to collect
any firewood.
-I'm ecstatic.
-Yay.
We might be back in though.
You never know.
I might be back in, and that
would be best-case scenario.
Either way, we're never
coming back here.
Mm-mm.
-Never setting foot again...
-Ugh.
-...on the Edge.
-Yeah.
It's insane that
I've been here a month.
And it seems like ages ago
that I got here.
However... crazy as it sounds,
it's kind of
gone by quickly, too.
I mean...
as much as I hate this place,
I'm sort of gonna miss it.
It's not really the people.
It's just, um...
I'm gonna miss
this amazing view.
Anybody want to climb up the
mountain and see the sunrise?
For the very last time.
You know,
it's beautiful out here.
It's peaceful.
Even though my husband is here-- thank God he's here--
it's forced me to slow down,
take a break.
I don't do that at home.
I never sit around.
I'm just go, go, go.
So, it's... it's a weird way
to force yourself
to sit down
and just think about life
and what matters most
and what you miss.
A 360 view.
Because what I miss
about home are my kids.
But I think what I'm gonna
miss about here
is the simplicity of it all.
You know, we don't have
any distractions or--
There's nothing here.
It's simple.
But that's the blessing.
You don't get to do that
at home.
Oh, people about
to get emotional.
Uh-oh.
Oh, man.
It's game day.
Yes. It's the last day.
A hundred percent.
Man.
I'm ready for the challenge.
Oh, my God, 35!
Last day on the Edge.
This is it, do or die.
I'm ready.
I have a hidden immunity idol
that I purchased
before the last
bring-back challenge.
Luckily, it's still good.
Yeah!
-Yeah.
Seeing the people
that have been out here
from the beginning is
a good reminder for me, like,
that I'm gonna have to bring itat this battle-back challenge.
It's not gonna be a cakewalk.
...two, three.
I got my two tokens.
I worked hard at that.
All right, friends,
we got some scrolls.
This can buy me one advantage
in the challenge,
and that will give me
some sort of edge up.
I know that I got to put
my war paint on
and go to battle.
And that's what I'm best at.
Now that I've had a chance
to see the fire tokens
actually used and in play,
I think it adds
a really interesting dynamic.
It adds a layer of
nuance and complexity
and flexibility
that didn't exist before.
So I'm inclined to use my tokens
for an advantage
in the challenge.
Get my warrior hairstyle.
I'm on the Edge,
but there's still a gamebubbling underneath the surface.
So I think that's what's given
me a lot of spark to continue.
The Edge is really
the hard fight.
I'm using my two fire tokens onan advantage in the challenge.
For me, I've got my eye
on the prize, and the prize is
getting into this battle-back
and winning it.
I'm gonna
approach the challenge
like I approach any challenge:give it 100%, hope for the win,
and just do my best.
But it's a little unnerving
knowing that
there's a few people
that have one advantage.
Natalie's gonna have
three advantages and an idol,
plus a surplus of tokens.
I got nothing.
You guys ready to play?
Let's go.
It took me a long time
to get over
being voted off first
and feeling that worthlessness.
I feel like I've been grinding slowly and quietly for so long,
but all this hard work
is worth it.
It's not one day's work.
This is 32 days
of being on Extinction,
keeping my head in the game,
never giving up here,
and fighting for
everything I have.
I feel like I've proved myself
out here.
And I fully feel likeI deserve one of the spots to be
fighting for
that winner's title
and a shot at being
the best of the best.
My token count
before making my purchases
for this final battle-back
was 14 tokens.
I bought peanut butter.
I bought three advantages.
So I'm going in stacked
in advantages-- three total.
That's the max I can get.
I basically have
six tokens left, plus
I bought this idol
way back when.
Um, it's still good,
and it's still ready
to be put to use.
But I can only
walk into the game with one.
So that's why I decided
to buy a second idol--
not for me, it is for Tyson--
and spread the protection
between Tyson and I,
hoping that one of us get back
in and wreck shop back there.
-Cheers.
Isn't it crazy?
It's so simple.
-It's kind of cool though.
-It is cool.
Get back in the game,
I'm gonna put it to good use.
If I don't get back in the game,
I'm saving it for you to have
after you win.
Yeah, exactly.
Either way,
good luck today, dude.
Thanks, Natalie.
I really appreciate it.
I played the game four times,
and it's very rare.
I don't think
I've ever experienced
that type of generosity
from another player.
And, yeah, it-it does
mean something, because
even though everybody's trying
to fight for the same prize,
you know, when you feel
that somebody is
also rooting for you, it gives
you a little more motivation
to push, to focus,
to just stretch to your limit.
The real final hurdle
to the endgame is today.
If I get back in the game,
I'm winning this thing.
It has been the greatest season in the history ofSurvivor.
20 winners.
-20 years in the making.
And from day one,
it has been a war.
Let the fireworks begin.
Guns a-blazing,
swords a-swinging,
limbs and heads
flying everywhere.
It's gonna be a bloodbath.
Natalie was the first casualty,
blindsided at Tribal
and sent to the Edge.
I'm gonna do everything
that I need to do
to get back in the game.
There's literally no rest
until I'm back there.
Early divisions
forced the old-school players
back into familiar strategies.
-Parvati was
my high school crush.
I'm like a phoenix
rising from the ashes,
ready to burn down your house.
So I'm just gonna spread
truth, lies and rumors.
It works for me.
I use something called
the buddy system.
Nobody can leave,
nobody can talk.
This is the buddy system
on steroids.
I'm sorry, but you ain't
putting me in a playpen.
Let's all open our bagsand let's see who has the idol.
Go through my stuff,if that's how you want to play.
But the new-school players
had a message.
It would take more than
old tricks to win this season.
There is a old-school,
new-school thing
-happening right now.
-Whoa.
Being able to get them out
is my main objective.
-Yul.
-The new-schoolers
got the old-schoolers.
Even Sandra, the game's only
two-time winner, was taken out
with an astonishing blindside
by Denise.
I'm giving you an idol.
So I took it.
I played that to save myself,
and I happened to have another hidden immunity idol...
-Oh!
-...that I played for Jeremy.
I was the only one
that voted for Sandra.
Whoa!
-The Queenslayer.
Queenslayer!
You don't have to convince me.
I already know
this is not for me.
Sorry, y'all, I can't be here.
Fire tokens gave birth
to aSurvivor economy,
which added another layer
of complexity to the game.
"Bequeath your fire tokens to
any player still in the game."
I'd rather just swallow it.
Would you barter fire tokens
for something?
"This advantage will cost you
four fire tokens."
Oh, my God.
First word I read is
"extortion."
This is great.
"This advantage is being playedagainst you."
This is illegal, man.
For those living on the Edge,
every day has been
a demanding and at times
brutal struggle to survive...
Feel defeated, but you got to
find that hope someplace,
because, without it, you're
just gonna destroy yourself.
I just kept thinking,
"I want this to be over with.
I want this to be over with."
Everything hurts.
That was it for me.
I was toast.
Some mentalities can handle it
and some can't.
...as they compete
to earn fire tokens
to help them
get back in the game.
I'm captive right now,
but I'm plotting
a way to escape.
The war is not over.
That's what makes
this game so good
is that it is so hard.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever done,
but everything that I'm doing
is to get off
this bloody island.
And then,
when they needed it most...
Even in a war like this,
it's important
to take a moment andremind yourself what and who...
What?
-...you are playing for.
No way.
What?
-Surprise!
Surprise!
The biggest loved one visit
ever seen
reignited the fire
of every player.
This is the reason why
I almost didn't play,
and this is the reason
why I'm playing.
This is not a dream come true,
man, it's a fantasy come true.
Oh, my God, it's our families!
All these families
you see here,
that's what made us all bond.
That's what made us be strong
throughout this game, man,
these guys right here.
I felt so filled up with love,
it breathed new life into me.
Let's kick this into high gear. You know, it's crazy.
For 35 days, the pace
has been unrelenting...
My spying has evolved.
It's called the spy nest.
There is a Steal a Vote hidden
at the other tribe's camp.
I'm going for it.
...the level
of gameplay unprecedented.
Can I play it?
I want to play that.
This thing that you can't get
-off of the voting podium?
-Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
That is...
-not a hidden immunity idol.
-Worth a shot.
Well, that's for you.
This is safety without power.
The safety is "I'm leaving."
-Wow.
-The without power is
"I will not vote."
What the hell happens now?
The tribe has spoken.
Again.
-No.
Sophie.
Need to bring me your torch.
Oh.
Now only five remain:
Ben...
This isn't the end of the work.
I'm gonna win this game
by having an alliance
and keeping everybody safe.
And when the gun smoke settles, hopefully I'm sitting there
with a couple more rounds inmy pocket, not one in my chest.
...Denise...
I've crossed my T's,
dotted my I's--
the alliances that I've made,
the relationships
that I've built.
I've won
two immunity challenges.
I got to take out the queen,
and I found an idol.
My Survivorbucket
is full and overflowing.
...Michele...
I want to prove to
all those people who doubt me
I did deserve my first season.
It wasn't a fluke.
I'm a good player,
and I do belong here
with the best of the best.
...Sarah...
I want a battle at the end.
I want to go out
with a legacy,
knowing Sarah was not scared.
And I want to teach my son
your mom's not scared
to go against the threats,
because I believe
I can beat them.
...and Tony.
If I can pull this off
and get that two million
at the end,
and they crown me
the king ofSurvivor,
and I sit in Sandra's throne,
the queen, I sit on her throne
and I have the crown on...
What?
I'll be the happiest person
in the world.
Plus, one player will return
from the Edge
and join in the final battle
for the title of Sole Survivor
and the $2 million prize.
Join us next week
for the finale
ofSurvivor: Winners at War.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Survivor's
looking for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
Next time, on the
season finale ofSurvivor...
-Sarah, please think about it.
-Well, damn it, Tony.
I'm trying to shake up
this game.
Now I go into panic mode,
you, Ben, go into panic mode.
This battle is not over.
Join us next week
for the finale
ofSurvivor: Winners at War.
Okay, ready?
-Yep.
"Now is the time
for the comeback,
"with a serious vengeance,
you can bet.
"Another joined
your tribe today.
Come see who you will get."
Season 40,Winners at War,
you need to prove
that you're the best.