♪ ♪
PARVATI:
I had zero people
that would work with me
after you guys were gone.
I could not believe it.
It was three of them
versus me and Michele.
Like, that's how the tribe
was split.
Getting voted out
before the merge--
that's so lame.
I've never done that before.
But Ethan's over here.
Rob's over here.
And much to my...
utmost joy...
-Guess who!
-(others exclaiming)
...Sandra's here.
(chuckles):
Sandra! Oh, my God!
I didn't expect to see you here.
Sandra getting voted out was
a little, small consolation
to my horrible night.
-SANDRA: Denise was going home.
-Yeah.
And to save her from being
another female
at the Edge of Extinction,
I gave her my idol.
-(gasps)
-She saved Jeremy
with her own idol,
saved herself with my idol,
and wrote my name down.
PARVATI:
No.
-So, that's why I'm here.
-What?
ROB:
Why not just figure out
who to vote for yourself
instead of giving her
all that power?
AMBER:
Yeah, that's very unlike you,
to give somebody
-that-that much power.
-You let her decide
your fate in the game?
SANDRA:
It sucks that I played
with my emotions.
I said I would just play
a strategic game.
But, in hindsight,
at the end of the day,
I'm still human,
just like everybody else.
I have feelings.
I felt something for Denise.
And it just bit me in the butt.
PARVATI:
How are you guys making it?
Are you starving?
Fishing equipment is not good.
Really? So,
you're just not eating anything?
-We have rice.
-Like, a cup
of rice a day, and that's it.
You don't have to convince me.
I already know
this is not for me.
Sorry, y'all.
I can't be here.
I can't.
I'm not gonna sit here
for 23 days,
trying to fight my way through
a challenge to get back in.
Ain't gonna happen.
(logs clacking)
-Whoa!
-Oh, watch out.
-Ah!
-(chuckles)
SANDRA:
You'll get burned.
I don't want to stay,
'cause I feel like
I-I can't do anything else,
you know?
Like, my time here i-is-is done
and I've done everything that
I could possibly do in the world
and in the game of Survivor
and I don't need to do
anything else but move on.
So, I wish you luck.
-Thanks, girl.
-Take care.
-Rob, good luck.
-Thanks, Sandra.
SANDRA:
I have no interest
in running up the mountain
for a little scoop of rice,
sleeping in a raggedy shelter,
being bitten by rats.
Knock 'em dead.
I don't want to deal with it.
And get Denise for me!
♪ ♪
I'm not very good
at the challenges.
Everybody knows that.
So I feel
I would be wasting my time
just for an opportunity
to go back into the game,
which I'm not gonna succeed a.
I got voted out,
and now it's time for me to go.
I've gained a lot
because of Survivor.
It has changed my life.
It's given me opportunities
that I might not otherwise
have had.
I'm happy to go into retiremet
and know that I did the best
I could with what I had.
At the end of the day,
I'm still the queen,
and I'll always stay the quee.
♪ ♪
YUL:
Tribal Council
kind of sucked.
Wendell got into it
with Parvati,
which was
completely unnecessary.
And then, at one point,
he basically said,
"Make me an offer.
Tell me who to vote out,
and I'm open
to working with you."
And I'm sitting there,
thinking, like,
"What the hell are you doing?!"
Hey, can we, um... can
we maybe just chat for a bit?
-Yeah, yeah.
-YUL: He created
a lot more drama,
a lot more uncertainty,
and almost kind of
blew things up for no reason.
I wanted to just have
a talk with you about Tribal.
For me, like,
the part where you and Parvati
were talking
and you said, like,
"Hey, I'm willing
to entertain a proposal.
Like, who do you want me
to vote for?"
I was thinking, like,
"Whoa, what is going on?"
And I know that the other guys
were thinking that, too.
It immediately puts a target
on your back, right?
Because people are like,
"What is going on?
"Like, is Wendell flipping?
Man, we got to, like,
get him out." So--
I hope this is okay, man.
-A-Again, I'm just doing this
because...
-Yul. Yul.
-I respect people
that give me their honesty.
-Yeah.
And I-- In the real world,
that's how I treat my friends.
-Good, bad or ugly, I tell them.
-Yeah. Cool.
YUL:
After our conversation,
I just got to watch him.
I'll see how he-- what he does
in future Tribal Councils.
WENDELL:
If I made you uncomfortable
in Tribal last night,
I just want to apologize.
I wasn't
necessarily uncomfortable.
But I think it could
create chaos amongst allies.
-Well...
-And, also,
I've seen every single person
who's created that chaos
walk out the door.
-I think, in the future...
-I understand.
Thank you for, uh, schooling me
about how to interact at Tribal.
Do you think I didn't know
what I was doing last night?
I'm here to play.
Michele played a few years
before me. She did very well.
I played two years ago,
and I did pretty well, too.
Let me play my game.
MICHELE:
You're killing me, dude.
You're killing me.
WENDELL:
If you want to put me
on some kind of leash
and tell me
how to play my game,
I might turn around
and bite you.
YUL:
How did your conversation go
with him?
-MICHELE: Not well.
How did yours go?
-I-I heard it.
Mine went fine, but
he definitely has a different...
tone and demeanor
with you than he does with me.
-MICHELE: Huh.
-Like, he was very--
He was like, "Thank you.
I appreciate you
telling me this stuff."
Very... respectful.
And what I could overhear
seemed defensive,
kind of telling you how it is
and being
sort of passive-aggressive.
I heard the schooling thing,
-and I was like, "What?"
-Yeah.
How the hell
do you move forward
-with somebody like that?
-Yeah.
MICHELE:
Wendell acted
extremely defensive
and confrontational.
I'm a little bit surprised,
because...
-Thank you.
-YUL: All right.
-...I gave Wendell
one of Parvati's fire tokens
to repair
some of our relationship.
But it didn't work.
I think he thinks that
it's gonna be me and him always,
until the end,
and that I'm gonna
blindly stay true to that.
But the reality is
I don't want to move forward
in this game with Wendell.
♪ ♪
ETHAN:
Life on Edge of Extinction is
a battle.
Every day's a battle
with the elements and nature.
Every day's a battle with
my own personal struggle of
"Why am I here?
Why am I sticking it out?"
and how to exist
in this in-between world.
So it's just...
It's depressing.
I feel defeated.
I just feel
there's, like, no hope.
We got to find that hope
someplace,
because, without it, you're
just gonna destroy yourself.
Days are long,
nights are longer.
-If we were catching fish...
-Think about how good
it's gonna feel
when you're done.
I know. I'm so excited for that.
Mm-hmm. And it's only just
a matter of time.
Yeah. I'm fine. I'm good.
-I just had moments...
-Yeah.
You've gone through
harder things than this.
I know.
Doing this?
No. But I think about it.
You know what, it's--
Actually, fasting
is actually incredibly good
for your body.
Like, not eating, not sleeping.
-Do we need to do some yoga?
-Your cortisone-- your cortisone
is skyrocketing.
It couldn't be good.
Well, it'd probably be better
if you started thinking
about things
that were more positive.
-Well, there's a lot of time
to think up here.
-(laughs)
ETHAN:
I can talk to Parvati.
I feel really comfortable
with her,
so that's a big help,
because, you know,
she keeps me strong.
It gives me a little bit
of inspiration to keep going.
You don't need to go there.
It's like this place
is already dark enough.
We're gonna stay positive.
Yeah.
It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
-You're gonna make it.
-I know.
I want a chance to win,
get back in the game,
and have a shot
at that $2 million.
It's not out of the question.
Look, I've come back from
the edge of extinction twice
due to my health,
so I know what that's like.
I came to play Survivor.
I want to give it 100%
and see it through to the end,
because it's important to me.
"Must open together."
-(rattling)
-So I got to, like,
pick myself up
and kind of come back stronger.
-I got a present.
-Ooh.
What do you got?
"Must open together."
PARVATI:
Okay.
-ETHAN: One scroll each.
-TYSON: One scroll each?
ETHAN:
Pick a scroll, pass it on.
Scroll.
TYSON: We got another clue
on Edge of Extinction,
and...
we each got our own clue.
Reading to ourselves?
I don't know. All it said,
"Must open together."
So, on three.
One, two, three, open.
PARVATI:
'Kay.
Oh, my gosh.
TYSON:
And this is what it said.
-All right. Game on.
-ETHAN: All right.
-See ya.
-Let's go.
We're gonna take the rice
-off the fire?
-No.
TYSON:
The second
that got finished being read,
there really was
an all-out sprint.
We left the rice on the fire.
♪ ♪
I knew this was coming.
ROB:
Immediately, the race was on.
I took off first
and just sprinted.
I've been running these paths
for the past three days,
up and down this mountain,
everywhere.
So I thought if I could get
there first, I'd have an edge.
♪ ♪
(groans)
I can't breathe.
TYSON:
Boston Rob just takes off
in a full sprint.
But me,
knowing he is a portly chap,
figure I have time
to make up ground when I need to
as soon as it hits the uphill.
So I sprint up
to the dead ending
that I'm most familiar with,
and I immediately find
a fire token,
'cause I am amazing.
-You have one?
What's it look like?
-Yeah.
How-- But--
Where was it hang--
-It was just like that,
on the ground?
-Where was it?
The very far lookout.
-In the-- in the tree or...?
-Wait.
Just sitting on the ground,
in the middle.
-Really?
-Are you kidding me?
-No.
Nothing.
ROB:
Nothing. Nobody has any?
-Can we see those again?
-Tyson.
Yeah, this is
where I found this one.
-Oh, you found it here?
-Oh, you already found it.
-Yes.
-Does it look like this?
-No.
-You promise you don't have any?
-I promise, dude.
(Parvati laughs)
You guys don't have any?
-I don't have any.
-PARVATI: Nothing.
-TYSON: The consensus
is that
the other three fire tokens
were never found by anyone.
You don't have anything?
I have nothing. Promise.
-AMBER: I don't have anything.
-(Parvati chuckles)
Tyson, talk to us, dude!
I only have one!
Nobody else has one?
Zero.
I have nothing.
The thing is all of
these people have no idea
that I have the fire tokens.
They believe
that I wasn't the one
to the first of any trails.
But I was, bro.
I followed the trail
that ends at the tree.
The token's sitting right
in the middle
of the crux of the tree.
I grab it,
stick it in my pocket,
and run to the next one.
Then I make my way up
to the small rock.
Ethan's already there.
I know what the fire token
wrapping looks like now
'cause I just found one,
and I see it sitting
right there.
I quickly stick it in my pocket
and run the other way
before he even knows I'm gone.
Then I start making my way
to the big lookout.
I stop at the rock at the left
and, what do you know,
nobody's been there yet
and I got my third fire token.
Three out of four.
If we're in the majors,
I'm batting .750.
I'm the best that's ever played.
♪ ♪
(chuckling)
-Go.
-(groans)
(Jeremy laughing)
-Whoa!
-He runs like an old man.
(laughs):
Whoa.
Dang.
DENISE:
Oh!
TONY:
Today, I feel like I'm
in a good position right now,
even without Sandra,
who I've been close with,
because right now we have
two Seles, two old Dakals.
I-I'm close with Kim.
I'm hoping
I'm getting close with...
Jeremy.
So I think
we formed a nice bond
between the three of us,
and I'm just
so grateful that Denise
pretty much did me a favor
by making a flashy move
at Tribal.
And she took out the queen.
She dethroned the queen.
She used two idols.
So-so that makes her
a big target,
and that's good news for me,
because I need protection
in front of me.
I need shields in front of me.
So, Denise, in my book,
she's A-OK.
I'm gonna tell everybody.
I'm gonna say,
"She's a high profile.
She dethroned the queen with
-her own bullet."
-(laughs)
-DENISE: No! You're gonna...
-"Shot her down and paid half...
-You're gonna be voted out
after the merge.
-...and paid her half price
for that bullet."
-See, you're gonna get me
-voted out.
-Yeah, yeah. I'm gonna say,
"No, she's a threat.
-Keep her around."
-They'll all be like,
"Thanks, Tony.
Thanks a lot."
TONY:
High profile right here.
JEREMY:
Tony thinks Denise is,
like, growing on...
that target echelon.
But Tony is clearly still
the biggest threat out here.
He's still a big name.
He's still crazy, wild Tony.
I do like Tony,
but he is the bigger threat
in this game.
Not about this.
I think
if we're back on our heels
when we merge and we don't have
a plan and don't come for it,
like, we're gonna
get picked off.
Yeah.
And-and, I mean,
Denise is still--
-Denise is with us. You know?
-Yeah. Yeah, I agree.
KIM:
I feel good
with this group of people.
It's a bit of
an interesting dynamic.
Like, I have this relationship
with Tony.
I love Tony.
However, I really feel good
with Jeremy and Denise.
You know? Like, Jeremy and I
particularly have a great bond,
and I really like Denise
a lot as a player.
I trust her.
I think she's well-meaning.
I think
we could play well together.
So if push came to shove,
I think I could be convinced
to go with them, at this point.
And I haven't been dominating
this game.
And so I like being in charge
of my own fate out here
and getting the chance
to make new bonds with people.
I think
it gives me more options.
When that all went down
like that, like, I had a moment
where I'm like, "We're
gonna merge in a few days,
-"one way or the other...
-Yep, and we've got, like-- Yep.
-...and we need to have a plan."
-Plan.
So, in that, are you-- how are
you feeling about the three?
-Me, you and Jeremy?
-Jeremy-- Yeah.
-Super awesome.
-Just-- Awesome.
-Like, that is...
-I-I just want to make sure
-you still feel super awesome
after yesterday.
-Yes. 100%.
-I don't want to be the person
that's trying to catch up.
-Right, right.
-I want to go with a plan.
-And march forward.
-Yeah.
-Right.
DENISE:
I singlehandedly took out
the queen,
and now there's a solid three,
I think,
that really wants
to move forward,
with Kim and Jeremy and mysel.
So it's like
everybody comes
into Survivor playing
a different style
and a different way to play.
Who do you see yourself wanting
to go deep in this game with?
-I mean,
I know that feels like...
-Besides you?
-Do you really see that?
-Yes, I do.
-Okay.
-100-- Like, I just--
It feels right.
And I know
that my way of playing
can be viewed under the radar,
can be viewed
as riding coattails--
however you might look at that.
But, hey, there are big targets
in very small places,
and you better be watching out,
you know?
Because I am.
I'm here to play.
I'm here to play,
just like everybody else.
♪ ♪
BEN:
♪ Peanut butter jelly time ♪
♪ Peanut butter jelly ♪
♪ Peanut butter jelly,
peanut butter jelly ♪
♪ Jelly, jelly, jelly. ♪
(chuckles)
SOPHIE:
So, for the first time ever
on Survivor, I can say that
we have leftovers this morning.
And I'm hoping
that the peanut butter
can kind of stick us together,
because there is real tension
bubbling beneath the surface.
I really don't think
anything's out there.
Did you find something?
-No, I didn't find anything.
-Adam.
SOPHIE:
The boys are saying, "Where is
the hidden immunity idol?"
But they have no idea
I have the idol,
you know, in my bag.
-You're, like, interrogating me.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if it feels like that.
I'll stop asking you questions.
No, no, no.
You can ask me questions.
It was the tone
when you asked me the question.
(high-pitched):
Okay. Um, it just seems
like you might have something
in your bag.
-Is that a better tone?
-(chuckles)
BEN:
I'm asking Adam
if he has the idol,
and, you know, he's saying,
"No, I don't have it."
Okay. Well, let's go
looking for the idol.
ADAM:
It's just such a charade.
I'm convinced that,
between Ben and Sarah,
they have an idol.
...walk through the jungle,
just in case there's something
still out here.
Okay.
I'm gonna look really hard.
Actually, can I just look in
your bag and then I'll find it?
It's so obvious to me
that they're pretending
to look for an idol.
BEN:
One of 'em was in a clay pot.
-Um...
-ADAM: In a clay pot?
-Yeah.
-ADAM: I'm not an idiot, guys.
I can't stand it.
U-Unless you have it.
Adam is convinced
that Sarah has the idol.
My Spidey senses are just like,
"Bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing, bing, bing."
SOPHIE:
So I told Ben and Sarah
everything that Adam says
to make sure
they don't think that I am--
have some kind of side alliance
with Adam.
That pisses me off.
SARAH:
I know where the idol is.
It's in Sophie's bag.
So I say I am going
to set this straight.
You can go through all my ....
I don't have it.
So, I will dump all my crap out
right now.
-You do not need to do that.
-I believe you.
I just hope that one of us
has it. For real. Like...
-Honestly, we would--
I would tell you.
-I don't.
-I would.
-Every single one of us
would tell you, Adam.
I speculate about
Sarah having an idol,
so now it's all out in the open.
And now I have to do
damage control,
when I'm convinced
that they are the ones
that are lying to me.
This is ridiculous.
I honestly think that
we should give up the idol talk.
-ADAM: Okay.
-'Cause it's just dividing us.
-Yeah, I agree.
-SARAH: It's pissing me off,
'cause I don't ... have it.
ADAM:
There's a chance that I'm wrong
and, between Ben and Sarah,
they don't
have an idol.
If I'm wrong,
I'll feel like a real idiot.
But I-I--
There are few times in Survivor
where I've felt as confident
about something
as I do about this.
♪ ♪
Come on in, guys!
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first, Sophie.
Wow.
Really?
Won't even take a step.
I like it.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna carry
a large saucer
to a water tower,
fill it with water,
then race
through a series of obstacles.
You'll empty what's left
into the well,
head back, do it again.
Once you fill the well,
puzzle pieces will drop.
You will use them
to assemble a puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the ninth person
voted out of
Survivor: Winners at War.
Let's do this.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get going.
♪ ♪
All right, here we go!
For immunity!
Survivors ready?
Go!
First thing you got to do
is go get that saucer.
Got to go over every obstacle.
-Uh-oh. You okay?
-(laughs): Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Michele takes a big hit.
-WENDELL: Let's go, girl.
-You all right?
Yes.
PROBST:
Yara back quickly.
Here comes Dakal.
Now it's gonna get
a little more difficult.
Got to have somebody
on every section of that beam.
-Sarah, get set.
-WENDELL: Jump in the middle.
-Jump up high.
-Ooh.
-KIM: Why am I so high?
-TONY: Yeah, you're too high.
Do you want me to-- Whoa. Okay.
These are very heavy saucers.
-TONY: Come on, guys.
-Are you guys okay
if I carry it like this?
-PROBST: As Nick knows.
-Wait, wait.
-No, Sophie.
-PROBST: He did this
in his season,
-regarded one of
the worst performances...
-Yo, let's go, let's go.
...in the history of Survivor.
They didn't even get
to the puzzle.
Looking for some redemption.
-Okay, Sarah, go ahead.
-PROBST: Gonna be Dakal
back first, getting water.
Yara now getting water.
-Fill it.
-Sele finally back,
getting water.
The more water you get
in that saucer,
the better shot you have
of some of it
making it back to the well.
-Slow, slow, slow.
-PROBST: Dakal is heading out
with their first saucer
full of water.
Here comes Yara.
-Fill it.
-KIM: I think I need to be
-on the low end, y'all.
-PROBST: This is where teamwork
-is crucial.
-Be careful.
PROBST:
Dakal losing massive
amounts of water...
All right,
I'm stuck on the beam.
-Okay.
-...as they try
to work together.
-More water's spilling out.
-KIM: All right, I'm good.
Here comes Sele.
-WENDELL: Watch the water, guys.
-We are. We are.
-PROBST: They're losing water.
-Lift it higher on your...
PROBST:
Yara very slowly.
-Trying to conserve that water.
-ADAM: Good job, guys.
The faster you go,
the more water you risk losing,
which makes
all your effort to get
to the well less fruitful.
-Everybody has...
Somebody has to be on each beam.
-Yeah.
Denise, why don't you
go in the middle.
PROBST:
Dakal is moving quickly,
but they have lost
-a lot of water.
-Come on. Come on.
Oh!
PROBST:
Sele.
Disaster.
Loses a lot of water again.
-PROBST: Here comes Yara.
-Step back.
-Slow and steady.
PROBST:
They've been slow and steady,
trying to keep that water,
but they're losing some of it.
-Okay, got it.
-Go to her side. We got this.
-PROBST: Dakal coming back
-with the first water.
-Slow down.
-Okay.
-Nice and slow.
-PROBST: You go to all that work
to get back here,
you want to get
whatever you have in the well.
-Take your time.
-PROBST: But will it be enough
to drop those pieces?
-Lift, lift, lift, lift, lift.
-No.
-They're gonna have
to go back again.
-All right, let's go.
-Let's go back.
-PROBST: Sele coming back
with a saucer full of water.
Will it be enough
to drop the pieces?
No! Sele gonna have
to head back.
-Just one more trip, guys.
-Let's level it.
PROBST:
Yara taking
a very slow approach.
-Start shuffling your feet back.
-ADAM: Higher.
PROBST:
Hoping that that extra water
in the saucer
-will be enough versus...
-Slide your--
Yeah, slide your feet.
...sprinting and trying
to get another run in.
-We're doing good, guys.
Really good.
-All right.
-We got to hustle this time.
-PROBST: A strategic decision.
-Is it a good one?
-Okay, hold on.
You got to keep as low as...
PROBST:
Dakal coming back again now
with more water.
Have they learned anything?
Sele heading back now.
-Dakal and Sele
both heading back.
-ADAM: I got it up.
-I got it up.
-PROBST: Yara's taking
a long time
to get off this beam.
Easy, easy. Easy.
-Keep all of this water. Okay.
-PROBST: Question is:
Will it make a difference
or have they just
been wasting time?
Dakal and Sele
close to nearly lapping Yara
with their second saucer.
-Slower.
-PROBST: Will this
be enough for Yara?
They're hoping
those puzzle pieces will drop.
-SARAH: There!
-And they did! You're good.
-Go.
-PROBST: Somebody get
-the puzzle pieces.
-Okay? Good, good, good.
PROBST:
Strategy paid off for Yara.
It only took them
this first run.
All right. Who's on the middle?
PROBST:
Sarah untying.
You're good.
Dakal coming back.
Sele coming back.
-Both tribes trying
to stay in it.
-Slow. Slow. Slow, guys.
PROBST:
Yara out to the early lead.
-All right, here we go.
-Slow. Slow.
Will this be enough for Dakal?
-Yes! You're good.
-I got it.
PROBST:
Will it be enough for Sele?
-JEREMY: Go, Denise! Get it!
-PROBST: Yes!
You're good. Untied.
Michele now untying.
Big immunity on the line.
-Everybody fighting right now.
-Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
-PROBST: You're good, Dakal.
-Watch out. Watch out, Denise.
PROBST:
You're good, Michele.
-Go, Sele.
-Move, move, move!
-Move out of the...
Good.
-(whoops)
-PROBST: You got
to get it in there
-before you can start working.
-Got it.
-PROBST: Seat it. You're good.
-Okay. Go, go.
-Good job, you guys.
-You got one
on the ground, Ben.
PROBST:
It's Jeremy and Denise.
-Sophie and Ben.
-Sophie, that's on the bottom.
Right there.
Wendell and Michele for Sele.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay.
PROBST:
This is Yara's challenge
right now.
They had the right strategy
with the water.
It gave them an early lead
at the puzzle,
and they are moving quickly.
-No, we're okay. We're okay.
-PROBST: Jeremy trying
to place another piece.
Denise getting in on it.
Michele trying to place
a big section.
Sophie with a big section
for Yara.
Good job.
PROBST:
Sophie with another piece
for Yara.
Nice job, guys.
PROBST:
Dakal catching Sele now.
There we go. Got it.
PROBST:
Ben with another piece.
-Another piece by Sophie.
-SARAH: Yes, yes, yes, yes.
PROBST:
Ben has the last piece.
-(cheering)
-That'll do it!
Yara wins immunity!
Safe from Tribal!
We're looking for one more now.
It is Dakal and Sele.
Watch out.
Do these go right here?
PROBST:
Wendell trying to move
a big section in.
Dakal has made
a lot of progress quickly.
Another piece by Jeremy.
Go, let's go.
PROBST:
Michele trying to find a spot.
-She's got one for Sele.
-NICK: The 40. There's the 40.
Five pieces left for Dakal.
Six pieces for Sele.
Make it five.
-We're tied.
-MICHELE: Right there.
WENDELL:
Where does that one go?
Find where it goes.
Wendell with another piece.
-Sele in the lead now.
-You guys got it.
Help her get it in, J.
There you go.
-PROBST: Another piece by Dakal.
-NICK: Go, let's go.
Shut up. Shut up.
Wendell getting close.
Jeremy trying to find
another piece.
-KIM: That's it, yes.
-PROBST: He's got it for Dakal.
Another piece! We're down
to two pieces for Dakal.
-YUL: Come on, guys.
-PROBST: Two pieces for Sele.
-Denise has it.
-KIM: Yes, yes, yes.
PROBST:
Jeremy versus Wendell
and Michele.
-(cheering)
-And they've got it!
Wow!
By seconds.
Maybe a second.
Dakal pulls it out.
Wow, what a battle.
Yara, great strategy
out of the gate. Paid off.
Immunity is yours.
Nobody going home from
your tribe. Grab your stuff.
Head out. Enjoy the night off.
The all-important second place.
That was about
as close as it can get.
It was probably
less than a second.
Dakal pulled it out.
Safe tonight.
No Tribal Council.
Nobody going home.
Grab your stuff. Head out.
Tribe stays intact.
Nick, this is
a familiar feeling,
losing the exact
same challenge again.
What is going through your mind?
This is absolutely
the most brutal loss
I've ever had in Survivor.
This is...
I mean, that was... That sucked.
Sucked.
And the fact
that it is this challenge,
it's like salt in the wounds,
it's...
It makes it so bad.
All right, Michele, Yul,
Nick, Wendell,
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be
the ninth person
voted out of this game.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
YUL:
The four of us are tight,
but Wendell is
a little bit of a showboat.
He's a little bit
of a trash-talker.
And if he had
just maintained his focus,
that could have made
the difference
between winning
and losing today.
So he's basically
dug his own grave.
♪ ♪
MICHELE:
Sorry, guys.
YUL:
It was the closest finish
-I've ever seen.
-I apologize.
I'm sorry. Wendell,
you were doing great
at the puzzle.
-Sorry.
-NICK: I'm so frustrated
with Wendell
over us losing today.
He should be focusing
on the puzzle,
not showboating, talking trash.
We lose this challenge
by a second,
and if it wasn't for Wendell
screwing up the challenge,
-we would have won.
-MICHELE: I'm gonna
go wash shoes.
WENDELL:
Let's go.
NICK:
It was my goal to keep
this four together
to the merge,
and if it wasn't for Wendell,
we would've done that.
That really just got
under my skin.
We shouldn't be
in this situation.
-Yeah, I agree.
-But...
All right, so real quick,
just while they're talking.
-The plan is Wendell.
-Yeah.
But we're gonna tell Wendell
that we're voting Michele.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Right? Okay.
-I do.
-Are we 100%
gonna vote together?
-I want to vote with you.
-Yul's gonna try
to work some magic.
-I know.
-We have to make
this conversation very fast.
I think Yul's voting for me,
but if you and I stay strong...
I think Yul is coming after m.
Maybe it's because I talk
a little too much in Tribal.
It's weird because I thought
we were really like-minded.
I thought we were locked in.
I guess we're not.
-Let's vote for Yul.
-Okay.
He's gonna try to pit us
against each other.
I will vote
wherever you want to vote.
WENDELL:
Me and Michele have been
a little wishy-washy,
but she's the one
that I have the most
of a rapport with,
so I'm banking on Michele
tonight to vote with me,
and I'm banking on Nick
to do the same.
-Yeah, I feel okay.
-Okay.
I mean...
-You know I'm 100%.
-I know. I know.
-YUL: 100%.
-I know that.
It's not about that.
It's about...
YUL:
So, an interesting dynamic
with the fire tokens
being a thing this season
is that fire tokens,
we know, have some value.
I mean, they're currency.
And everyone believes,
including me,
that they're gonna have
more value later on in the game,
probably after the merge.
So, I came up with a plan.
NICK:
Mm-hmm.
Yul wants to backstab Wendell
and get the fire tokens
that Wendell has.
It's definitely kind of
a dark, strange situation,
and I'm slowly realizing
that siding with Yul
is super dangerous
i-in this game.
We got a decision to make.
MICHELE:
Yeah, I know.
Yul's trying to do
all this crazy ....
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm like,
"Dude,
there's four people here."
We need to get
on the same page...
-Yeah.
-...three of us,
-and just vote one way.
-Yeah.
Is there any part of you
that wants to keep Wendell
-over Yul?
-MICHELE: Yeah.
-I'm open.
-NICK: Amen.
-I'm truly open.
-Yeah.
NICK:
Wendell today really got
under my skin talking trash
-when we lost by one second.
-Yeah.
NICK:
But I think going forward
with Yul,
we're gonna be, like,
locked in these set plans
where he's running everything.
We're gonna have
less flexibility.
MICHELE:
I agree.
If you feel strongly
about one way or the other,
I will follow you.
-Okay.
-Okay?
MICHELE:
For this vote,
there are pros and cons for
who we should vote out tonight,
Yul or Wendell.
(Nick laughs)
MICHELE:
I have been
really looking to get Wendell
out of this game,
because I'm thinking
about my past
with Wendell
and how I've been hurt by him.
So I would love some revenge
and to go that direction
just to make sure that
I don't fall
for his tricks twice.
MICHELE:
But it makes sense
to get rid of Yul
because he's super strategic,
and he will probably win
at the end of this game.
So this vote is so difficult.
But I went four years
feeling like
I might not have deserved
to win my first season,
and every single day
and every decision that I make,
I'm proving it,
that I deserve it this time,
and I deserved it that time.
♪ You better be ready ♪
♪ They're coming for you ♪
♪ You. ♪
♪ ♪
(exhales)
What, Wendell?
-That smirk, Probst.
-(chuckles)
What do you mean?
I'm just looking at you.
Yeah.
It wasn't the best of days.
We gave the, uh, the challenge
our best, but, uh,
we lost by a second. It sucks.
And it sucks to be here.
But because you were so close,
does it change the afternoon
when you think about
who to vote out?
No. No. It doesn't change who...
the group decided to vote out.
No.
Yul, all of the old-school
players are gone
-with the exception of you.
-(chuckles)
But I wonder,
is there something to the idea
that Survivor has grown so much
in terms of twists and pace
and that it really is
just older-school players
have a tougher time
with the new game?
I mean, it's entirely true.
The game has evolved.
It's much more complex,
much more fast-paced.
I'm playing
a very different game
than I played
the first time around.
I've had to lie more
in this game already
than I did the entire time
on Cook Islands
because you're
voting someone out,
but now you want them
to like you
and not think that you were
part of voting them out
so that they will give you
their fire tokens.
That adds
yet another layer of duplicity
that did not exist before,
and this is now, like,
three notches
above where I played before.
This game sounds fantastic!
It is. I-I think it's really
interesting. The fire tokens
give you an opportunity to have
this kind of market economy
to align incentives.
So, for example,
you might say, "Okay,
I think we should do this."
But the person says, "No,
this is too risky.
I don't want to do it."
"But what if I gave you
a fire token to do it?"
Then, at that point,
the economics work out.
They're thinking,
"Okay, the reward
is worth the risk,"
and that adds
a whole new layer of options
that didn't exist before.
PROBST:
So, Wendell,
you do have to lie to people.
You have to blindside them.
You might want their fire tokens
to be given to you.
How do you combat that?
You try to find somebody
or some people
that you can trust
in this game
of not a lot of trust.
PROBST:
And, Nick, that connects to
preexisting relationships,
because they have
had time to form
-a trust.
-Yes.
Yul, you're... I asked Nick,
-but you're nodding.
-YUL: Look,
that's exactly the case.
When you land on the beach,
you have a finite amount of time
to reach out
to as many people as you can,
to get to know them,
build trust and then strategize.
If you have
a preexisting relationship,
all that stuff
has already been done.
PROBST:
So, Wendell,
we've already talked about
you and Michele
having
a preexisting relationship.
WENDELL:
Yeah, it's scary.
But just because
I know Michele
from outside the game,
that doesn't necessarily mean
I want to go far with her
or sit next to her at the end.
I'm playing to win this game,
so I would like to work
with anyone to get me
to the end of this game.
PROBST:
Michele,
what are you smiling at?
Wendell has made it very clear
that he's here for him
and not for anybody else.
And as
a preexisting relationship,
to hear
that you don't really care
about what happens to me
in the future,
then I don't know
how I can potentially work
with that.
So, everybody sees the tension
that is me and Wendell.
-It's not lovers' paradise
going on here.
-(laughs)
And it's not going super great
for us at all times,
and I think
that's pretty apparent.
Let me correct you briefly.
I do care about
what happens to you.
-Okay?
-I think he said
let him correct you.
-Yeah, yeah. No, he...
-Let me correct what I said
-or how you interpreted it.
-(chuckles)
My sincerest apologies,
Michele Fitzgerald.
-Mm-hmm.
-I care for you and your future.
-Okay.
-All right.
PROBST:
All right.
So, Nick,
you do have to decide
who's going home.
Was today different?
Or was it just another day
on the beach,
trying to strategize?
NICK:
Uh, I think today
was definitely different,
at least for me,
because the person
that gets voted out tonight
will go to the Edge.
So, look, if it's me,
you know,
no burnt bridges on my part,
'cause this is my final four,
and I would want
to just come right back in
and work with them.
PROBST:
Wendell, I have
never heard anybody
say that in that way, which is,
"We're so tight, I will
come back and join you guys."
Are you down with that, as well?
It might sting a little bit
if I'm sent to the Edge tonight,
and it might be
a little more difficult for me
to win my way back in and join
this alliance that just...
-Everyone just lied to me.
-(laughs)
You know what I'm saying?
It's like,
"Y'all just lied to me
and sent me to the Edge,
"so I'm not so gung ho about
working with you guys again."
PROBST:
So, Yul,
Nick says no hard feelings.
Wendell says,
"Who are we kidding?
You guys would've
just been lying to me."
I will be very bitter
at you guys
if you blindside me tonight,
but I want to leave the option
of working with you,
because that may be
my only option.
And so far,
I feel like I know you better
-than I know anyone else
in the game.
-PROBST (chuckles): Wow.
Michele, that's tough.
It's basically saying,
"Oh, yeah,
I'll try to get over it,
but you'd be better off
to not do it."
-(chuckles)
-MICHELE: Yeah. I mean,
I love every single one
of these boys,
and I don't want to have
to make a decision like this.
But this is the game,
unfortunately.
And we were blessed at first
to all be on a tribe together,
and now we're cursed
by the same blessing,
and we know that.
PROBST:
All right.
It is time to vote.
Wendell, you're up.
♪ ♪
You'll be on
the Edge of Extinction tonight.
I thought we were cool, bro.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay. I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Yul.
Wendell.
That's two votes Yul,
one vote Wendell.
Ninth person voted out:
Yul.
Wow.
-Good one, guys.
-So sorry.
All right.
Yul, the tribe has spoken.
All right, see you guys.
-Good luck, Yul.
Ah.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
Everybody, drop your buffs.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
-We are merged.
(cheering)
He says, "I don't know
what it is. Uh..." Like, dude.
YUL:
Getting so close to the merge
and just literally being
a split second away
from winning immunity
and making it
and being blindsided
is a bitter pill to swallow.
Yul.
YUL:
Oh, I was the last one.
I assume that we'll have
an opportunity
to battle back soon,
and just try to remind myself
this is an adventure
and I feel lucky to be here.
(roars)