Wow, big move, Tony.
Well played, sir.
It was  it was
it was a last-minute thing, man.
Yeah?
-Yeah.
Tribal Council was crazy.
Ben tried to make a move on me, but Sophie went to the Edge.
So there's hard feelings.
Ben is pissed.
He's not even talking to me.
It's so crazy.
He's such a child.
Like, grow up, Ben.
Come on, man.
The game goes up and down. Just chill out and let's play.
You guys had us duped.
You want to go talk, Sarah?
This was Tony's idiotic move.
But I told myself, "Sarah,
just keep your cool
and don't be pissed."
-You just sunk my game.
-No.
-I'm done. Those guys
don't want to work with me.
-Yo.
-It's me that flipped, not you.You didn't flip. I did.
-Oh  Okay
-I wrote Michele's name down.
-I know. That's fine...
-Jeremy don't want
to work with me.
-That's fine.
-You don't need them.
I'm with you. I'm...
-I swear. I swear.
-You're not with me.
To have Tony come up with this all alone,
I'm absolutely infuriated
with him.
It's ridiculous.
It's a $2 million game.
What are you doing, dude?
We were fine.
And now do we even have
the numbers?
You think we do,
but you don't know if we do.
I have an idol
and I can pay up fine.
-I understand that.
-You're not going anywhere,
Sarah.
-All right.-If I jeopardize anybody's game,it's mine.
I swear to my family,I didn't want to blindside you.
-I'll tell you this right now.
-Yeah.
I will let all of this go...
-Under what condition?
-...until it sinks me.
-Aw, man.
-Then it's not gone.
-Yeah.
-I get voted out,
-do not talk to me ever again.
-No, come on.
Wow, man.
Usually,
you blindside somebody,
you go back to camp,
you hash it all out,
and everybody's like,
"It's okay. It's all good."
Not this time. This time,
it's like deep wounds, man.
But, come on,
give me a break.
I'm playing the game, too,
you know?
This is war. Stop crying.
Put your man panties on
and go to war.
I am with you 100%.
It was just tonight,
-and I wanted to make that move.-Okay.
And I promise to you,
I did not want to hurt you
-or go with that side.
-Right.
And I'm gonna tell you
something.
I have an idol. Okay?
-You have one?
-I have an idol.
-Where'd you...
-I found it on the rock.
-Really?
-Yeah.
So, I'm telling you
the truth, guys.
I want to go
to the end with you guys.
Tony's telling me
about all his advantages
and all his idols,
so he's gaining trust.
But I don't know if I trust him,because he's
blindsided me hugely.
-The reason why I'm so upset...-Yeah.
...is because
Jeremy's still here.
-And because I'm...
-What the ... is that?
-You just got ... on.
-By what?
-A bird.
A  What bird
is in the nighttime?
I still want Jeremy
out next.
He is a challenge beast,
right?
He is a jury threat.
He's gonna get all the votes.
Like, there's just no way
for me to work with Jeremy,
so I am not talking
to Jeremy right now,
and I don't want to talk
with Jeremy right now.
-Are you sure that's a bird?
-I'm po  Where else  Or bat.
-A bat?
- Yes, dude.
Is that good or bad?
That's some karma.
Oh, my God.
I made a big power move,
which was blindsiding Sophie.
The backlash was unbelievable, so I think I'm in trouble.
My wife told me, "Tony,
this time you can't play wild.
You can't play crazy.
You can't play flashy."
But I got the itch,
and now this is the time
for another
undercover operation.
In my first season,
season 28 inCagayan,
I made a spy shack,
and it worked.
You know, he lied to my face.
And then,Game Changers,
my second season,
I made the underground bunker.
It was a failure,
but it was fun.
Right now,
my spying has evolved,
and now I'm up in the air.
It's called the spy nest.
It's like a bird nest
that I perch myself on, just
like a bird, and I sit there
and I wait
to hear conversations
that are going on.
The only person
that knows I'm undercover
is my partner, Sarah.
It's only me,
and nobody's coming.
No, I can't see you at all,
dude. It's... golden.
If we were in the real world
and Tony and I were partners,
one of us would be fired, okay?
Tony's back to the old Tony,
and it's nonstop  go, go, go.
And he doesn't let up.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah. Okay.
-All right.
He's got my back
and I got his back
and we're not gonna turn
on each other.
But if he's not willing
to back off
a little, then he's gonna
get himself voted out.
How are you today?
How'd you sleep, Ben?
-What's that?
-How'd you sleep?
It was all right.
You want to talk?
No.
-No?
-Nah.
-I don't.
-Why not?
'Cause I said no.
That's all.
I just don't want to.
-Never seen anything like it.
-Yeah.
Last night was emotional
and a little bit crazy.
And it's super clear
people are thinking
Jeremy's gonna go next.
But hell no.
I mean, I'm not doing that.
For me, it's really obvious
that Tony and Sarah
are a problem right now.
But I still have a relationship
with Sarah
that can be salvaged.
I'd so much rather
see Tony go than Sarah.
And I'm done
with the sitting around,
hoping that I'm on
the right side of the votes.
-This is where I'm at.
-We have to  Okay.
-Tony has to go.
-He has to.
Yeah.
Right.
Wow. I think you're right.
Yeah.
-What are we gonna do?
-Yeah, exactly.
-Sit and wait?
-Yeah.
-Just get picked off eventually.-Uh-huh.
This is by far the riskiest
move I've ever had to make,
but I have to do something.
I mean, I have to turn
this around or go out trying.
To me, this is the point where
you flip the light switch on
-and go, "Okay, here we go."
-Mm-hmm.
-Like, and then hope
you make it.
-Yeah.
Amen. I agree.
-I'm 100% with you...
-I'm 100% in with you.
Tony has been running the show,
and we've been left out
of the loop.
We've been made fools of.
And I think a lot of us are feeling that way right now.
I... agree.
This game is about power.
And this seems like
a perfect opportunity
to gain a little bit of control in this game
and take out Tony.
Ooh, boy.
What you got there?
What is this?
-What you got there, Rob?
All right, you ready?
-Yeah.
-Yay!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God. I don't want to do
a tremendous effort challenge.
Oh.
Here we go!
Just a nice marathon pace, guys.
The mad dash was on.
Out of everybody here,
I think I'm pretty physical.
I feel like I have an edge
in this challenge.
I knew this challenge
is gonna really, really suck.
It's gonna be a marathon, just like the log challenge was.
And so I knew I wanted
to pace myself.
I got out to the lead
the first couple laps.
It was probably not a good idea
if I'm setting the pace.
I should probably
slow down and let somebody else take the lead.
The stakes are really high
for this challenge.
Only six people
are gonna be able to win tokens.
This is pretty stiff
competition.
Wendell's really strong.
Tyson's an endurance athlete.
Yul's really strong.
Natalie is a superhero.
It was more brutal
than I expected it to be.
And when I see how fast these girls are going, I'm thinking,
"I can't, even if I wanted to,
keep up with them."
This does not suit
my strengths.
Like, I have never, ever been
a good runner.
People are passing me
left and right.
I'm in last place already.
What the hell?
Did you really just do that?
How did he do that?
Oh, my God.
It was incredibly difficult,
and the tide started coming in.
And then your feet are
ankle-high in-in ocean water.
Oh, my God.
I slipped and fell
and cracked my elbow.
I just felt it.
Like, I tried to shake it off,
but, like...
...I knew I was done.
That was it for me.
I was toast.
Natalie and Sophie lapped
every single other person
at least twice.
I was back and forth with
Natalie the whole challenge.
And Natalie's a beast.
But I just kept running
the whole time.
Sophie was in the lead
for a majority of the time,
but I knew that I had
a little bit more in the tank.
I just pushed
and I was like,
"Why not beat her?"
And I beat her.
That was fun.
Oh, my God.
-There's four more spots.
-Tyson.
-Yul.
-Yul's next.
Tyson. Parv.
-Tyson.
Never thought
I'd be so happy to leave
-a pile of coconuts behind.
Let's go, guys!
This is your last push!
Yes, Yul. Good work.
-Yeah, Yul!
To my big surprise,
I ended up in third place.
-You did it!
-Did it.
I am so elated that I finished, and I finished
with Tyson, an ultra-endurance
professional athlete.
I was like, "Yeah!
I still got it."
-Everything hurts.
Wendell? Or is Danni
-I can't tell if Danni's in it.-Danni's good.
-Is she in it?
-She's endurance queen.
I feel like it'll come down
to Danni and Wendell.
Yeah.
Seven.
Once I got
to those final coconuts,
I'm like, "Okay, here I am.
Pick up the pace.
"You've got to fight.
"You're further out
than you thought you were.
"Go for it.
You've got to go for it
to get those tokens."
I knew Danni was
the next person behind me.
She was in seventh place.
I was in sixth place.
And then she was gaining on me.
I just kept running
and picking up the pace
and thought
I could catch Wendell,
and I started
to close the gap on him.
Yeah. Yeah.
Unfortunately,
I started out way too slow
and just couldn't gain
enough ground.
And I finished seventh,
just one short
of winning two fire tokens.
I said I wasn't gonna care
if I didn't win, you know?
But I do.
Yeah.
I feel like it was important
for me to finish.
I didn't want to feel
like I was quitting.
That's what makes this game
so good,
is that it is so hard.
It was hard to see him
still going to get
those coconuts well after
it was finished.
That shows you
that he's not a quitter
and that...
he's gonna keep on fighting.
I don't get it.
Yeah.
-Me and Ben were like this.
-Yeah.
-He called me his ride-or-die.
It's a mess right now.
Your game is not over, right?
My game is not over.
Put yourself in my shoes
and you would be going,
"What did you do?"
The more people are fighting,
the more there is a war,
the more crossfire
and friendly fire going on,
the more
I can really crank it up.
Now is the time to start trying
to figure out who I want to sitat the end with
and finding a way
to get everybody else out.
We need a tight three.
-Just three?
-Like, at the e  Like...
-I think so.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-I would love that.
-Three of us working with...
-Kim. It's possibly tight, four.Four.
Yeah.
And I don't know
that anyone would totally
expect that either.
-I would be so down with that.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm done just making it
one step farther.
I got my eye on the prize
at this point,
and that's why
I have to make big moves.
I have to do something
to stand out.
It's nice when you can
get with a group of people
that you mutually benefit
each other.
-Can run with the numbers
for once.
-Yeah. Right.
-For once.
-Or two.
Aiming for one.
I know.
In my opinion,
there's three people
in this game still
that certainly beat me
at the end,
at least three.
That's Jeremy,
Sarah and Tony.
We'll have to get rid of 'em.
-Tony, we're in trouble now.
-Okay.
Now we don't know
where an idol's at.
-So-so...
-And one of them gets an idol
-and I get voted out,
I am not gonna be happy.
-Right.
Sophie's idol is
gonna get put back in play.
We've got to find it.
Sophie went out with an idol.
So now it's gonna be out here.
I need to save myself.
If I don't find it,
if Tony doesn't find it,
we could be in hot water.
There's been
a mad dash already,
and there's a lot of hands
out here digging.
There may be another hidden
immunity idol in the mix,
which complicates everything
all over again.
Everybody's looking
through the dirt
and the cobwebs
and digging around trees.
We really want to get Tony out.
So we need to get the hidden
immunity idol before Tony
so that he doesn't have
something else up his sleeve.
Kim is, like,
ready to make a move now.
-She doesn't want
to be blindsided anymore.
-Yeah.
So what kind of moveyou think she's trying to make?
-Trying to get in with Jeremy?
-Well, trying to...
-Probably, yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah, right? Yeah, yeah.
-Jeremy and Michele.
-Yeah.
And Nick, too, I'm assuming.
No, Nick, I trust him 100%.
'Kay.
Well, she's just  She's
just ready to play her game.
You know what I mean?
She's just ready.
See that? You see that?
You see that? You see that?
Well...
I saw him try to sneak it
from me. Hello? Ben?
I'm right next to you, man.
What are you doing?
I-I'm watching you
try to hide the idol.
I found the idol.
And the first reaction is,
"Oh. Oh, no. Got to turn it around. Don't let anybody see."
And then Tony's
standing right there.
He's like, "Come on, Ben."
You found the idol
in front of me.
You're trying to hide it
in front of me, man.
Y  Are you okay?
All right, I found it.
You know?
He's like, "Why did
you do that to me, man?
You got to trust me.
I'm sorry. I-I'm really
-I'm sorry for that moment.
-It's okay, Ben.
It's okay. It's okay.
I got caught red-handed.
Gold-handed, right?
But you still don't
trust me, man?
Well, now you
we trust each other.
-Tony, listen,
we're in lockstep now.
-I know. I just got nervous
-when you were trying
to hide it from me, man.
-Well...
-Come on.
-You  Look at what you did
to me.
Yeah, but that's over though.
I thought we were okay.
-I know. But it's, like,
four hours later, dude.
-All right.
What am I supposed to do?
-"Tony, look."
-'Kay.
You know, I was trying
to hide it from Tony, right?
Because I barely
trust Tony right now.
-Good job, man.
-Listen,
-we're good, 'kay?
-So now  so now we're good.
-Don't start getting paranoid.
-I'm  No, I'm not paranoid.
Kim wants to take out Tony,
but Tony has an idol.
So I need him
to be comfortable.
-We have control in this game.
As long as...
-Thank goodness.
Yeah. So it doesn't matter.
We can start picking 'em off.
Here we go.
He thinks he has me in his pocket, and that's perfect,
because I need
to figure out
what route I'm gonna take
whether or not to go with Kim
and start targeting Tony...
No, no, you're good, man.
...or if I can work
with the guy, right?
Oh, my God.
Tony, I can't believe it.
No. No-no, seriously, stop.
Come on in, guys!
All right, let's get to
today's immunity challenge.
First things first, Tony.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna stand
on a very narrow perch
with your hand above you,
tethered to a bucket.
When your hand drops,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing
wins immunity.
And today it will be
the last woman...
and the last man.
-Ooh.
-Both will win immunity.
Both will earn two fire tokens.
Big stakes in this game.
Take your spots.
We'll get started.
All right, everybody's inposition, with their arms above.
Now you have to take your hand
off the structure in three,
two, one.
And this challenge is on.
First time we did this challengewas season three.
In its original version,
it went
-six hours.
Then we modified it.
We added that beam
you're standing on,
which made it
a lot more difficult.
That went an hour.
And now we have made it
even more difficult.
We've removed your ability
to support that arm
that is tethered to the bucket
with your other hand.
The most difficult version yet.
Let's see
how long this one goes.
-Been up there five minutes.
You gonna offer us food, Jeff?
Not this early.
Got to earn it
a little bit, Ben.
It's really not that early,
Jeff.
I mean, I feel my shoulder's
-on fire already.
-What is it
-you would love, Ben?
-Peanut butter
-and cookies, Jeff.
-Of course.
Just to get down off this.
I'm in pain, Jeff.
Jeremy drops.
-And Ben touched the structure.-
-Did you touch it?
-Yes, Jeff, I touched it.
Ben, I'm sorry.
You're out. Ben is out.
Cannot touch the structure.
We're down to two guys left.
-Sorry, Ben, but thanks
for the integrity.
-Yes, sir.
Sarah drops.
It is now Denise,
Kim and Michele
competing for one immunity.
Nick and Tony
competing for the other.
You can feel the intensity
kick in right now.
Toughest version
of this challenge we've done.
And you're seeing why.
I'm gonna try to go
for three in a row, Nick, man.
-You are?
-Record-break
Yeah, record-breaking, man.
-I'm sorry.
-Okay.
I'm gonna do my best, too,
all right?
Yeah, yeah. I got you, Nick.
We're good.
Given how crazy Tribal has been,
one after another after another
stunning blindsides,
having that necklace,
as Tony knows from the
previous two Tribal Councils,
is a great feeling.
Been up there 15 minutes.
Now I'm gonna try to tempt you
to come down
with some food.
-Jeff.
-Damn it.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Ben, I promise you,
this was coming out
at 15 minutes
no matter who was up there.
There's a mound of peanut butterwith chocolate.
Cookies and milk.
Exactly what Ben had asked for.
Damn, do you see all that?
-Yeah.
If you want
to opt out now,
this will be yours.
If more than one of you,
you will share it.
And you will eat
until the challenge is over.
Yep, I'm gonna do it.
Kim's gonna step out.
Anybody gonna join her?
The window is closing.
All right, I'll do it.
Michele's out,
which means Denise wins.
Yes.
You'll give me
-one token? I'll do it.
-Yes. Yes.
-I'll do it.
Nick is dropping,
which means
Tony wins.
Insane.
-Take it.
Wait.
I got it. I got it?
-I got it?
You got it, Denise.
-... yeah!
Just take this.
Hold it? I can't eat it
if I hold it.
Wow! What an ending.
-Tony, you're good.
-Can I eat, too?
You cannot eat.You just won immunity, brother.
We're done, man.
Can you come and help me out
so I don't get wet?
One of the craziest finishes
in any Survivorchallenge.
How fast security
in this game went out the windowfor chocolate, peanut butter,
cookies and milk.
Denise, come on over.
- Thank you.
Wow.
Individual immunity is yours.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
In addition,
two fire tokens are yours.
-You are safe. Congrats.
Thank you.
-Thanks.
Tony,
come on over.
-Three times in a row.
-Wow.
-You went from nothing...
-I know. Thank you.
-...to a streak.
-Thank you so much.
-Tony once again
safe in this game.
-Thank you.
Cannot be voted out.
-Two fire tokens for you.
-Thank you, sir.
As for the rest of you,
Tribal Council tonight,
where one of you
will be voted out,sent to the Edge of Extinction.
Grab your stuff, head back tocamp. See you tonight at Tribal.
-Congrats.
-Thank you, Jeff. Thank you.
What?! I won three in a row.
Back-to-back-to-back.
It's amazing,
'cause anything can happen.
I could've sneezed
at that moment.
Mosquito could've bit me
in the eyeball.
So, thanks, Nick.
One token
for an immunity necklace?
I'll take it. That's a bargain.
-Yeah.
Congratulations, Denise.
They had to give cookies
and milk away
-so Tony could win.
The immunity challenge
was a son of a "B."
My plan has been
majorly foiled
to blindside Tony tonight.
-Can you try to win
a damn immunity?
I'm kind of winning
all the time.
- Right.
-Ow, man.
Yo, you got heavy hands, man.
Yo.
-That hurt?
-Yeah, that hurt.
No, it didn't.
I'm so mad that he's
won three immunities in a row.
He has tons of fire tokens.
He's driving me crazy
in the game.
Right. Right.
And then it hit me.
-I was like, "Oh, crap."
No, I know.
That's got to go
on the back burner,
so what's going on
the front burner?
After last night, I want
-to prove my loyalty to Ben.
Okay.
I will vote Jeremy tonight.
-Okay. Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yes.
I know that you guys
-have been going at it.
Wait, Ben.
Yes. Mm-hmm.
Yep.
We'll have to put
our plan on the back burner.
I tried to do my best to win that immunity challenge,
and I was falling off.
At least I get
one of Tony's fire tokens,
peanut butter
and chocolate chip cookies.
And Jeremy goes home, anyways, and there's no harm.
So I think it's a win-win.
Like, I can't help
but just be, like,
sad that it would be Jeremy.
Yeah. Well, I'm...
I really do think
you, me, Nick and Denise
-could be a thing.
-Same.
I am distraught.
I've been close with Jeremy
since day one in this game.
He's kind of been, like,
my true family out here.
But I don't know
how we get out of this pickle.
Okay.
-So, they're all
voting Jeremy tonight.
-Mm-hmm.
-You... But you won immunity.
-Yeah.
So they can't do that now.
Yeah, yeah. You heard them
say "Tony," though?
Who's they?
Oh, Kim is.
I just found this news out.
Kim was chirping
in everybody's ear,"Maybe it's Tony's time to go."
And it's a big deal to me.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Oh. Oh, uh...
Trying to remember. Uh...
I'm talking to Nick,
and he's looking at me,
and he's fumbling his words.
I keep asking him, "Nick,
what's going on?"
He's always lost.
Like, come on, man. Nick is
lying to me right in my face.
Are they really trying
to get me out, you think?
-She just mentioned it to me.
-Who's she?
-Kim. Yeah, yeah.
-Oh, Kim said it?
But...
Okay. Okay.
-Oh.
-Here you go. Yeah, yeah.
-Thanks for doing that, man.
So, now I'm 100%
worried about Kim
trying to get these
lower-tier threats together.
So, if Jeremy goes home,
we're screwed,
'cause the ladies
are gonna stick together
and possibly use Nick.
So, at this point,
we're writing Jeremy down.
At this point, we-we might
have to work with Jeremy, man.
No, but we can't piss Ben off.
Well, this is what happened.
Ben told me
that the girls were
talking about me
this morning,
a-and Nick didn't even come
-tell me that.
Mm-hmm.
-See? 'Cause he ain't with us.  And he was.
Okay.
-He told Tony about...
-No.
-Yeah. And-and...
-Damn it.
-Yeah.
- That's so frustrating.-I know, it sucks.
When I heard it...
If Kim stays in the game
and Jeremy goes,
next vote,
Nick goes with the girls.
-And it's done.
It's done. We are done.
-I-I think...
But we got to vote out
Jeremy because
we got to try and preserve Ben
as our number
because we don't have
any other option.
I don't think... I-I think
Ben is gonna destroy our game
-if we're scared of what to do.-I know.
Okay, so you got to talk
to Ben, then.
Hey.
-We're good, right?
-I'm good with you.
-Okay.
-Right? Now, now, now, Ben,
you're-you're 100% on Jeremy?
-Yes. Right?
-Okay, okay.
No, I-I was thinking if-if therewas any way I could beg you
or pay you, even, a fire token
if you could just hear me out
with the Kim thing.
-Yes. Okay.
-Okay.
We get rid of Jeremy tonight,
Kim is gonna get
Michele, Denise.
-They're gonna get Nick.
Nick just...
-No.
I just talked to Nick right now.
He's playing me like a fiddle.
-He's lying to me.
-Nick made his bed
with you today.
Right? He gave you immunity.
He didn't give it to me. He wasfalling off the challenge.
He can go to the end with Kim.
-That's what he wants to do.
-Well, that's...
-what he thought.
-That's what he wants to do.
So, once-once Jeremy's gone,
they're coming after us.
They have the numbers.
Me, you, Sarah.
Ping, ping, ping. Gone.
And then we... Hey, listen.
The-the soldier and the two copsand the fireman
-will stick together and get ridof these little rats.
-Right.
I don't think
Nick's gonna do that.
I don't honestly think so.
-I mean, I...
-Please, bro.
Jeremy is the number one horse
to win this frickin' game.
We can get him out...
get her out next time.
Okay.
-We can't.
-Okay.
Do you think it's on you or me?
You, I think.
If I give the advantage to you,then you play it for yourself,
-and if it doesn't work,
then doesn't work.
Everybody is voting Jeremy,
and I don't think that I can
shift the tides and save him.
I have to write
Jeremy's name down,
but it doesn't mean
that I can't try
to throw him a bone
to help him out.
-Word?
-Kim's got to go, bro.
And we don't have...
And we can't trust...
Oh. So, who are you voting for?
Michele was gonna
give me something.
Okay.
I want to talk to you about
-us moving forward.
-Right.
Like, I don't want to butt headswith you no more.
-Like, I feel like
we need each other.
-Right.
So, who would you
take out, then?
I mean, we can go after Kim.
-Yeah.
-Listen, I'm trying
to build trust
-back with you. I'm trying
to give you a little bit.
-I know.
-All right?
He can't even talk to me.
And I could still see him,
like, stewing.
Like, okay. What do I do now?
Something's going on.
I don't know. I don't know.
I can't even figure it out.
All right, play it tonight.
Let me have it. Let me have it.Let me have it. Let me have it.
Oh, my God.
I don't feel in control
of my game.
I have the 50/50 idol
in my pocket.
If all else fails,
I can use that.
But it could be an idol,
it could be nothing.
It's a flip of the coin.
I might not be coming back
to camp tonight.
Starting to get paranoid.
This is... This is not good.
This is the part of the war
that's gonna get really ugly.
This is gonna be
more like friendly fire.
So, Denise,
last Tribal Council,
it was really calm.
And then the vote happened,
and I'm guessing
when you went back to camp,
-it wasn't as calm.
Oh, yeah.
It was like watching
bad family therapy.
Fighting, yelling,
betrayal, anger, hurt.
It was mass chaos.
Kim, is it one of
those situations where,
in the heat of the moment,
people might have been willing
to say something,
but once a new day begins,
you go, "Okay,
maybe we all need to calm down"?
Absolutely.
Everything changes
almost every day.
The person that was
on the bottom yesterday
can be the one
calling the shots today.
I think if you can make it
through another day,
-it's like a clean slate
in a lot of ways.
Jeff,
it's shifting a lot faster
than day by day.
I think it's shifting
minute by minute,
hour by hour,
much more fluidly than
-day by day.
Jeff, we're running
on an endless treadmill.
-No matter what time
you put on that thing,
it's exhausting.
Michele,
let's talk about
today's challenge.
Kim, yourself and Nick
all dropped outfor peanut butter and chocolate.
Denise and Tony win immunity.
What happens in that moment?
It can't simply be,
"I'm just really hungry."
No. And me and Kim
were just torn up with regret.
We didn't feel confident
that we could last any longer.
But then when you step down,
you're like,
"Well, what if somebody
makes a mistake
the next minute,
and now we just stepped down?"
So, every decision
that you make,
of course you're riddled
with regret and anxiety.
Kim, agree with that?
Yeah. I mean,
the truth is
I completely regret it.
I felt like
my bucket was tipping,
and so I heard myself say,
"I'm coming down."
At this moment, I would
so much rather have fallen
two seconds and not gotten
the peanut butter
than have stepped down,
and then I know
for sure that it wasn't falling.
Nick,
how about for you?
-Well,
Tony gave me a fire token
to step down,
so I feel like I got
the food temptation
and then also
the fire token temptation.
But...
I mean,
stepping down
from a challenge...
I got to interrupt.
Is this so common
that you can actually answer
my question
while it's still going on?
I guess it's... Yeah,
I think it's becoming common.
I mean, I thought everybody
was on the same page.
And this is an argument
to not step down
no matter how confident
you are in your place
in the game
and how much
you trust your allies,
because it can...
change like that,
even at Tribal.
Denise, everything was
going just fine.
Oh, my God.
We cannot even get through
one Tribal Council
and just freaking focus.
It's like a tribe
of crazy, paranoid players,
and it's driving us nuts.
And we're ringside.
They're coming
around the first turn.
They're all up.
Except for Sarah, still seated.
Ben in the middle, seated.
Tony and Jeremy talking.
Kim.
Okay. Okay.
I don't.
Sarah, is there a...
-What?
-Sorry.
What was that, Jeff?
Is there a point
when you just say, "I can't have
any more conversations;
if it's me, then it's me"?
I would say I'm, like,
at my peak at this point.
I mean, it is just mentally
and emotionally exhausting.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
And you have people
on the Edge of Extinction
-who are losing their mind
in a different way.
Right.
Uh, here's the thing.
They sit there and would give
anything to be us,
and we would like
to be able to shut off.
It's the price you pay. I mean,I don't want to trade seats
with anyone,but I'm definitely not enjoying
sitting in this seat very much.
Maybe we just wait
till you're done and we vote.
Maybe there's nothing
to be said tonight.
Right?
-I'm done.
-You're done with what?
I'm ready to vote.
I'm seriously like...
-Are you-you...
You sure you want to do that?
-Yeah.
You know you're just
-safe tonight, though, right?
-I-I...
-You sure
you want to do that?
-I fully realize that.
-Okay. Okay.
-I've got it.
Wow. Everybody sitting.
Should we vote?
Yep.
All right, it is time to vote.
Jeremy, you're up.
I hope you put
my 50/50 coin to good use.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has
a hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,now would be the time to do so.
Just give me one minute, Jeff.
Sarah, you feel good?
How do you feel?
-Hey, Jeff, I'm just gonna...
I'm-a play it.
-Well...
I'm-a play for Sarah.
No, wait.
-Tony, you don't have to.
-Yeah.
-You sure?
Yeah.
So no play?
-No play. No, no.
Nothing?
-I'm-a do it.
-Yeah.
I'm-a do it.
If you didn't do that, man,
then play it. If you...
If you gave me your word...
-Go.
-Wait, wait.
-Are you sure?
-Yes!
-Go.
Okay. Okay.
We're good?
Yeah.
All right.
I'll read the votes.
First vote
Jeremy.
Kim.
Two votes Jeremy, one vote Kim.
Jeremy.
-Three votes Jeremy.
-Damn it.
Kim. That's three votes Jeremy,two votes Kim.
Kim.
We're tied. Three votes Jeremy,three votes Kim.
Kim. Four votes Kim,
three votes Jeremy,
one vote left.
14th person voted out
Kim.
Need to bring me your torch.
Kim,
-the tribe has spoken.
-Thanks, Jeff.
Time for you to go.
Sheesh.
"Any player still in the game."
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Survivor's
looking for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
Next time on a two-hour episode of
Survivor...
-It's like a bomb goes off.
-Danni's going for it.
Yes.
-He doesn't want
to go to the end with us.
-I know that.
Tony and I are sitting ducks.
This right now in this war
is the hardest mission yet.
The feeling of being
voted out was weird,
but I'm not sorry for trying to
gather the troops
to take out Tony.
I think it was the right move, and the game's not over.
-Kim.
-Hi.
I won't step down for peanut
butter on the battle back.
-I want a hug.
-Hi.
Do you have
peanut butter breath?