Come on in, guys!
All right.
Day 24.
Survivor Winners at War.
You know, sometimes,
even in a war like this,
it's important to take a moment,lay down your weapons
and remind yourself what and who
-you are playing for.
What?
-No way.
No, no, no.
This is one of those moments.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-Shut up.
Kim, here's your husband,
-Bryan...
Oh, my gosh!
...and your three kids.
-I thought it.
Oh, my God.
Come on out, Bryan.
All right, go. Go, go, go, go.
-No way.
-Oh, my...
Guys!
It's me! Come on!
Oh, you're so big.
Are you guys feeling shy?
Hug? Yeah.
Hi, babe.
Oh, my God.
Aw.
- Hey, kid.
Oh, my gosh.
This is unbelievable.
I just miss you guys so much.
It's so good to see
You guys can't know
how much I'm happy to see you.
I think about you all day,
every day.
Hi, baby.
So, Kim,
-this is
a really unusual moment.
Oh, yeah.
To see firsthand why you left,
-who you're playing for
this is it.
This is the family.
This is the best moment.
This is way sooner
than any of us
were expecting it.
And so to know
that these guys are here
and to see
their actual little faces,
not in my mind but in person,
and for them to know
that I'm well
and that I'm coming home soon,
I'm sure they've been wonderingwhere I've been for so long.
-It's just everything.
I don't know.
It's one of the best moments
of my life.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Well, you're all together
right now.
-Have a seat over here, Kim.
-Oh, my gosh.
-You go with them.
-You sure are.
-I can't believe
you guys are here.
Let's get to some more love.
-Ben, here's your wife Kelly
and your kids.
-Yes, sir.
Aw.
-Yes!
Surprise!
-Surprise!
-Come here.
You guys look so good. Oh, wow.
I love you.
-Hey, my guy.
-So, Ben.
-Yes, sir.
We remember the last time
you played.
You were so open
about how Kelly had,
as you said, saved your life.
-Yes, sir.
-So to be back here now again
and to have
the complete unit here,
what is this moment for you?
It's-it's the full circle, Jeff.
Now everybody gets to see
my two beautiful kids
and my beautiful wife
and the reason
why I'm here on this earth,
you know,
and why I strive so hard
to be a good man
and a good husband
and a good father.
It's 'cause of-of these three
right here, you know?
And the opportunity that you
and Survivorhave given us
and the platform
to help others and
I'm so glad that the decisions
I've made in life
-have gotten me to this point.
-Mm. Wow.
-Beautiful. Join Kim's family.
Find a spot.
Sophie, you burst into tears
when you realized
it was a loved one.
Who do you want to see?
My fiancé.
All right, Bobby, come on out!
Aw!
That's a hug.
A game this tough,
nothing feels better
than a trusting hug.
You smell so good.
Sophie, talk to me
about this guy.
What is it about Bobby?
Bobby is just, like,
the most loving,
open, caring person.
And I don't think
I got it for a while,
that Bobby is
the most trusting person.
And to have somebody coming
right now, at a time when,
like, I feel likeeven the people I like out here
I don't know
what to make of them,
there's, like, only one person
in this whole world
who wants to marry me,
-and I wish he was
on the beach with me.
-He is now.
-Yeah.
All right, head over.
Join the other loved ones.
-Reese's Peanut Butter Cups,
a hamburger...
-Uh-huh.
-...a massage.
-All right, Sarah,
-you ready for some love?
Here's your partner Wyatt
and your son.
Oh, he's so cute.
There's Mommy.
-So proud of you.
I can hold you.
It's okay.
Sarah, does it get any better
than that right there?
No.
Sarah, talk to me
from a mom's point of view.
How hard is it
to leave such a little one,
knowing he's in good hands
but you're gonna miss out?
Um, you know... it's so hard.
And Wyatt went through this
once.
And, you know,
when people out here ask me
my favorite thing about Wyatt,
it's that he loves me
no matter what.
He sees me at my best
and my worst,
and I have
his unconditional love.
And I-I'm just
so thankful for that.
All right, take a spot over
there with the other families.
Come here, buddy.
She doesn't want
to give him up, Wyatt.
-Hi.
Sit up here.-Denise, you ready?
-Here's your husband Brad
and your daughter.
My peeps. Oh, my peeps.
-Love my peeps.
-They need some love.
Wow.
That is a family hug.
Look at you.
Oh, my God, you look so good.
You look so clean. Beautiful.
-Oh, my God.
So, Denise, you're in
this unusual situation
where you have a daughter
who's now a young woman,
-so she doesn't need you
to take care of her.
-Yeah.
-But she's still your child.
What is this moment about?
-She may be 15 and a half,
almost 16,
but we need each other
as much as we did day one.
-I need this guy
as much as I did day one.
There are a lot of parents
very hopeful right now
when they hear your mom
say that,
as a 16-year-old,
you still need your parents.
-Hell yeah.
-Definitely.
-What is this like for you
to be out here and see your momin such a different environment?
It's just been hard, 'cause
she's, like, my best friend.
I tell her everything.
And so knowing
that she's out here
and I can't, like,
see how she's doing,
it's just really hard.
-Text me. Just text me,
and I'll get it later.
All right,
join the other loved ones.
Oh, my.
Nick, let's get
your fiancée out here.
-Yes.
Grisel, get out here.
Hey.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Really?
-Yes.
You do.
-So do you.
-Thank you.
- Oh, my God.
-You're doing awesome.
-Nick, talk to me
about the moments
when you're out here
on the beach...
-Mm.
-...and you think aboutthe people that you care about,
how did that impact you
going home?
At home, everything's so fastwork and school.
Your phone's always buzzing.
And it's hard
to sometimes put all that away
and see what's right
in front of you.
And out here, that happens.
And I thought, "This is
the woman I want
to spend the rest of my life."
And I never wanted
to take it for granted again.
It's like
It was so much clarity,
and I just never wanted it
to get blurred again.
All right,
join the other loved ones.
-Let's go. Here, at the top.
-The families growing
over there.
But we're not done.
Tony, let's get your wife
out here.
Come on, Marissa!
Bring the kids.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness.
Don't cry, baby.
Let me see you.
Oh, my God.
This-this is this is not
a dream come true, man.
-It's a fantasy come true.
-Mm.
I fantasize about this, man.
Tony, tell me about the part ofyou that we don't see out here,
-which is this guy, the dad.
-Oh.
No, I'm-I'm sure We
All these families you see hereand the ones we're about to see,
that's what made us all bond.
That's what made us be strong
throughout this game, man
these guys right here.
You know? And my wife
never got a chance
to come out, man.
My first season, the loved ones,she couldn't make it 'cause,
this little babushka here,
she was in her little swaddle.
And then, for the finale,
she couldn't come see me
in the finale
'cause this little guy
was in her tummy.
-And here we are today, man.
It finally all worked out.
They're here now, man, Jeff.
This is so real, man.
Go join
all the other loved ones.
Thank you so much, Jeff.Don't cry, my little baby cake.
-All right, Michele,let's get your sister out here.-
Kim, come on out.
-Hey!
Hey.
-How are you?
-Hey, girlfriend.
So proud of you.
You smell good.
-I'm so proud of you.
Michele, the sister bond,
even though,
when you're little,
sometimes it can be tough.
When you grow up
and become women,
it's so often
such a powerful bond,
-and I see that in you guys.
What is it about your sister,
Michele,
that connects you so much?
Well, we're a year
and a week apart,
-so we are like twins.
-She's my roommate, she'smy best friend, she's my sister.-Wow.
She's everything. She's
the best human that I know.
And they have
their soul mates here,
and this is my soul mate.
And I just, like, feel good.
It reminds me that
I'm supposed to be out here.
And she says
that she's proud of me, and...
it makes me proud of me,
to hear her say that,
-'cause I lose track sometimes.-
Mm-hmm. All right,
join the other loved ones.
-Glad you're here, Kim.
-Oh, my God. I missed you.
All right, Tyson.
Let's get Rachel out here,
along with one of your kids.
Come here.
-Come here.
-Oh!
Oh, she's so beautiful.
-Oh.
Come on out, Rach.
Oh.
-I love you, too.
-Love you.
Be strong.
How are you?
-Have you been good for Mommy?
-Who is that?
Do you remember me
or did you already forget?
Come on, Rachel.
Come right here.
-You're in this.
I lo I love watching this.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Tyson,
last time you played,
you played with Rachel.
You want to go to Mom?
You hadn't made a baby.
And now here you are again,
sort of a full circle moment,
where you have
almost your entire family here
with you.
I've dreamed about
this moment for
a long, long time.
'Cause I've never experienced
a family visit
in the four times I've played.
And... I
One of my motivations
for coming out here this time
was to share it with Bergen,
so that she could see
what Daddy does.
This is what I do.
I run around in an island on
-in my underwear. This is my...-
-This is my work uniform.
-Look at him.
Do I look the same?
Am I stinky?
-I am?
We only shower in the ocean.
That's my bathtub and my toilet.
All right,
join the other loved ones.
Sit right there.
Jeremy, you're ready.
Let's do it.
Val, come on out!
Let's go!
-Bring the Collins group.
-Let's go!
- Oh, God.
Wow.
-You can do it, Daddy.
Jeremy,
last time you were out here,
Val came out
for the loved one visit
and she whispered
in your ear what?
She's like, "The baby's fine,
and he's a boy."
-And that's my guy, Remy.
And since then, Val,you guys have had another child.
-Yep. This is Lenyx.
Add him to the Foxborough tribe.
And your two daughters.
And Jordyn and Cam, yeah.
So, Jeremy, if you had a diary
and you were gonna write down
what this moment is about,
what would you write?
I miss 'em so much.
I think about 'em every day.
I dream about 'em.
And I This is what I need.
This is
-this is the reason why
I almost didn't play.
-Mm.
And this is the reason
why I'm playing.
Like, I feel like I'm missing
so much, you know?
And, uh...
and I needed this, Jeff.
We're glad you guys
are all out here.
All right, Jeremy,
go join the other loved ones.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Are you happy, Dada?
This is a beautiful
Survivormoment.
This is better than we hoped,hearing all of you guys talking
and hugging
and loving each other.
And I just want
to thank Fiji Airways.
They made this possible.
They flew all of
-the loved ones out here
to Fiji...
-Oh, my God.
-Wow.
-...to create this truly
once-in-a-lifetime Survivor
family bonding experience.
And I'm so happy
you guys are here.
-Thank you, Fiji Airways.
Thank you, Fiji.
-Thank you, Jeff!
-Thank you.
-All right, let's get
to the loved one challenge.
-Oh.
For today's challenge,
all the adults
and the teenagers
are gonna swim out to
the deepest part of the ocean,
leaving all the kids behind
-to dig in the sand.
Yay! Yay.
All right,
I saw some worried parents,
but I saw some very excited
young people.
Future Survivorplayers.
Actually, we're gonna do
something historic.
For the first time ever,
there is
-no Survivorloved one
challenge.
-Thank you.
-What?
-Sorry, I hit you.
-Yay!
Everybody's going back to camp.
-Everybody's gonna experience
Survivor
and create more memories
together.
Grab your tribe and head out!
Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God. You're Michele.
Hi, Auggie.
Today was the biggest  blindside in
Survivor history.
Here, should we catch up?
You want to run up there?
We had no clue that there was
gonna be a loved ones visit.
-And the best part
about it was there was
no catch to it.
No one had to compete
for their loved ones.
for their children.
I think that this is
our reward for giving
so much to this game
that we love...
-Yeah!
...that Jeff was like,
"Hey, good job, guys."
-Mwah!
-And so today
was a full-on celebration.
-Ah!
Hey, you.
It was like everybody put
their guns down
for a minute and
the war was called to a halt.
It didn't matterif someone wrote your name down
last night or not.
My son's playing with
the enemy, but that's okay,
because we're humans right now.
And it was really cool
to see everybody
in their element.
Oh, you're gonna make
some sand soup for us?
I'm making it for both of you.
Oh, that sounds so delicious.
To have kids out here
for the first time like that,
whole families
out onSurvivor,
I think it was
-definitely something
really special.
-Oh, my...
I was genuinely
happy for everyone,
that they got that moment.
Oh, my God! It's our families!
-What the hell?!
-Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, Natalie.
You bring family members here,
it's like you never knew
we were suffering,
ever.
Everybody's so happy.
Everybody has energy. Every
Nobody's thinking
about hunger.
about anything else.
Like, we've escaped
-for a few moments,
and we're as happy...
-Mwah!
...as can be.
To have
my husband here, who I met
because of Survivor,
and our baby here,
where we should not even
be having a family visit,
my mind was exploding.
This is so crazy.
I needed my dad to be here,
to get some sense of closure
for my mom's passing.
The most important thing
was giving
my dad that opportunity
to be here,
where she was with me,
where she iswith me.
Like, I just was talking
about y-you and Mom
and how Karen and Jeff met
at your wedding and...
...and how good Survivorwas
for our family
and what it meant for Mom and...
Him being able to come here,
it made everything okay.
-Ooh!
My dad, he's the best.
He's my hero, and it was
just so good to see him.
I-I can't describe
how much sheer joy
and happiness I felt
in that moment.
Bye-bye, Daddy.
There's nothing
'cause you are the most
important thing in my life
like, there's nothing
on this planet
that is more important than you,and, like,
I don't want to ever be
away from you ever again.
-No.
-Ever.
-Not for a day.
-Like...
-No.
-I love you so much.
-I love you, too.
I will always have
that moment that I shared
with my wife here on
Edge of Extinction.
And that is, like,
so special.
This is the one time
onSurvivor when you are
yourself with your family  and you can see people just be
themselves with the people
that they love the most.
It was a magical moment.
It was amazing,
having my kids here.
They got to come out here
and experience what we've been
doing for almost 20 years.
-You gonna give me some good
vibes for my last challenge?
"I am, Auntie Nat.You have to be strong like me."
-I know. I'm trying.
-"You have to be strong
like me."
I love you!
Come on in, guys!
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first, Kim,
-thank you for having it ready.-You got it.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna pull on a rope,
balancing a wobbly table,
while you attempt
to stack letter blocks
one at a time.
First person
to spell "immunity"
wins immunity,
safe from the vote.
In addition, today,
the winner earns
-two fire tokens.
-Ah.
-Ooh.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the 12th person voted out
and sent
to the Edge of Extinction.
Draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity
and two fire tokens.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
First thing,
you're simply looking
for that letter.
It's gonna be on the bottom.
Place it
and then start coming back.
Now's where you got to balance
the table.
There's a learning curve
to that slack.
How much play can you give it
before a block drops?
Everybody working
on their first letter.
Michele did this challenge
in Cambodia.
It lasted over an hour.
Sarah did this challenge
in Game Changers.
It was over in 14 minutes.
Nick reaching
for his second block.
And that is where
it can get dangerous.
You reach back your right hand,and your left hand drops.
Nick heading back.
Kim, Michele,
Sophie, Sarah
and Denise
all taking a lot of time
to get back
with that first block.
Tyson back with
his second block. Tony's back.
Here comes Nick
back with his second block.
Right now it is Tyson,
Tony and Nick in the lead.
We're getting down to it now,
winners at war.
After that loved one visit,
there is no doubt
this game
kicked into another gear.
Tony places his fourth
and heads back.
Kim with her fourth.
It is Tony and Kim
almost side by side.
Then Tyson, then Nick.
Here comes Ben
with his fourth block.
Jeremy now getting into it
Jeremy's made up a lot of time.
Tony reaches
for his fifth letter.
Now it gets tougher.
You have to be precise,
your movements thought-out.
Jeremy reaching for his fifth.
Jeremy playing loose
with that slack.
Jeremy, out of nowhere,
is in this now.
Jeremy moving quickly
and dangerously
with his fourth block.
Jeremy playing risky,
and it cost him.
Jeremy loses everything.
He's got to start over.
It is Tony and Kim heading backwith their fifth.
Tyson and Nick coming out
with their fifth.
Now the strategy
kicks into the next gear.
How fast do you move
with the lead
while trying not to risk
losing it?
Kim holding slow and steady.
Waiting.
Everybody in the lead
has slowed down,
and everybody chasing
knows that's the opportunity.
Kim has her sixth letter.
Moving very slowly.
- Oh!
Kim loses everything.
Kim has to start over.
-That's what you're hoping for.-
Somebody in the lead to lose it.
It's Tony in the lead,
then Tyson,
then Nick, then Ben.
You cannot waver much
with that table.
Tyson moving very slowly now.
Not wanting to risk
losing what he's built.
Tyson drops everything.
Tyson has to start over.
Now Tony and Nick and Ben.
Jeremy drops again.
Nick drops everything. Wow!
Disaster all at once
for a lot of people.
It is now Tony in the lead
with Ben
right on his tail.
Neither one has made a mistake
in this challenge.
Tony with his seventh.
Tony down to one letter left.
Checking that spelling.
-Making sure it's right.
Ben knows from a misspell.
Ben heading back
with his seventh.
Trying to catch Tony.
Ben near disaster.
Saves it.
When you are seven letters high,that stack will fall
with very little movement
of that rope.
Tony back,
ready to reach for that eighth
and final letter.
Tony has his eighth
He's got to get all the way out,
place the letter,
get all the way back.
Ben reaching for that eighth.
And he's got it.
Ben has to pick up his pace.
-Tony places
his eighth and final letter.
Still has to get
all the way back
without dropping.
This would be his first
individual immunity win
in his Survivorcareer.
Ben places his eighth
and final letter.
Ben has a big decision to make.
He's either got to hope
for Tony to drop,
or he's got to try to catch himright here and go for broke.
Ben moving quickly.
He's starting
to close the gap now.
Tony dead still now.
Ben loses everything.
That is a massive advantage nowfor Tony.
This is Tony's challenge
to win or lose right now.
Can he do it?
-Jeff.
And he's done it.
Tony wins immunity!
Oh, my God!
Safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
I can't believe it.
-Wow! I won a game of patience.-Congrats, bro.
Tony, come on over.
Oh, man. Oh, my God.
Big moment.
Oh, my God, man.
-Thank you so much, man.
You are safe tonight.
-Oh, my God.
-Two fire tokens are yours.
Thank you so much.
As for the rest of you,
you know the drill.
-25 days is a long time.
-Oh, my God.
Tonight, one of you
will be voted out,
sent to the Edge of Extinction,where you will await your chance
-to get back in the game.
Whew.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
-See you tonight at Tribal.
-Oh, my God.
With ten people left,
this is a huge vote
because tonight will prove
who's in control of the tribe.
Like the fog is settling
on the battlefield.
There's gonna be a lot
of close fire
zinging by our heads,
and someone will
get hit tonight.
Tonight, there will be blood.
Good job, Tony.
-Ben, dawg.
-Proud of you.
-I can't believe it, man.
-I'm proud of you.
-Oh, man, I can't believe it.
Nice job, Tony.
Congrats.
Man, that's so awesome.-Thank you so much, man.
-This is an amazing feeling.
Good job, you.
-Good job.
This is the first time  in three seasons I get to wear
the bulletproof vest right here.
I have it.
To win it on a game
that requires patience,
that's not my style of game.
Slow and steady is not
what I'm made of.I'm made out of fast and sloppy.
-Wow, man. That's beautiful.
There you go.
I am so happy.
This is more powerful
than any hidden immunity idol.
And when you have the power,
people come to you.
So, what-what are
your thoughts, man?
I know he would.
Just wait.
I mean, we still have a lot ofpeople to talk to, so let's see.
It's getting down
to the nitty-gritty,
and more than anything,
I would love to break up
Sarah and Sophie.
They're too close,
and that's dangerous
for people like me
who's by himself,
basically, you know?
But Tony's like,
"We can't do that."
And it's frustrating.
I don't get a voice,
and that's not
how it should be.
Okay. So, here's the thing.
We just need to make her
feel comfortable...
-No. Why...-...that it's Denise or someoneand ... vote her out.
I'd rather see Tyson go. No, dude.
-Kim is way more dangerous.
This is what...
This is what I would like to do.
-Just listen. Let's go.
-Okay. I am. I am.
-You're getting frustrated.
You got to listen.
-No, I-I know.
We don't have a lot of time.
-We have a lot of time.
-Okay. Okay.
I want to vote out Kim.
Kim is gonna win this game
if we don't vote her out.
But talking to Tony right now
is like talking to a rock.
Kim has everybody
in her back pocket.
She can win immunity.
She was right up there today.
She doesn't have everybody
in her back pocket.
-All right. All right.
-No. No. Listen.
-That's just what
I'm telling you.
-I know.
-You don't have to agree.
-Why are you acting
like that, man?
-What do you mean,
-acting like that?
-You're getting frustrated
with me.
-Just chill.-I'm not, Tony. I'm just saying,
-this is a crucial decision.
-Yeah.
He's not even listening
to what I'm saying.
He tells me
stop freaking out at him,
but then he freaks out at me,
and it's just a mess.
And it's like, geez Louise,
how can we even work together?
This is going to end badly
if we can't get this
straightened out.
I personally feel like
Kim's the right vote out.
We just need
to make her feel comfortable.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I'll do it.
-Yeah.
-You want to blindside Jeremy?
-I'm down for it. I'm down.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
There's something fishy
about Jeremy.
He's sneaky. I don't trust him. Every time
we tell him something, he wantsto go against the grain.
He would even vote Sarah out
if he could,
so he's got to go.
Okay.
We need to talk and spread
this thing around.
-Yes.
-I think so, too.
Because I feel like we...us three need to stick together.
That's the guy
I need to talk to.
It's just chaos at camp.
There's lots of conversations
going on,
and we're not a part of it.
So I need to start getting
a different plan.
Look, here's the deal.
I don't think
I have any friends out here.
-You don't have
any friends out here.
-I know.
You don't have
any friends out here.
-I'm sure you know that.
-I know that.
They want us ... gone.
Yeah.
But I'm done with it.
I'm gonna play with you guys
-as hard as I can to the end.
-Okay.
Us three,
-Denise and Michele.
Okay.
You know what?
-Do you have one?
-Yes.
I am worried that it could be
me going back
to the Edge tonight.
I've already been
voted out once.
But Kim has an idol,
and if we play it right,
maybe I can save myself
for at least one more vote.
I'm ready to go to the Edge
trying to make a move.
Well, you're not going down
'cause you have an idol.
-Okay.
-I'm not playing it for myself
-if I'm not getting votes.
-Okay. Okay.
So, us three,
Tony and Sophie
are blindsiding Jeremy.
Oh, my gosh.
They've changed the vote again.
Are you serious?
Nick and Ben just said
the five of us are writing
-Jeremy.
-And I'll tell you why.Shots were fired at my partner.
-At me?
-Yeah.
-Who?
-Jeremy.
-He was telling me
you or Sophie.
-Oh, yeah.
-So, once I heard that,
it's over.
-Yeah.
-Okay. Hey.
-All right? All right.
That I can just leave Tribal.
If I feel like it's coming downto it, I'm out of there.
Then we don't have enough.
You have to stay there.Otherwise, we're gonna get ....
I have my safety
without power advantage,
so I can leave Tribal Council.
I don't get a vote,
but I cannot be voted out.
But now my alliance needs me
for a vote.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know yet.
If I did leave,
I would be turning my back
on my alliance.
But I'm a firefighter,
and we take care of people.
Why-why do you think...
Sarah has the Steal a Vote.
I would prefer if she just
played it tonight to be safe,
because if all five  of those people vote together,
we will potentially
go to rocks.
The war is happening tonight,
and the question is
When the smoke clears,
who's gonna be dead
in the trenches?
Nick, let's get right into it.
How are you feeling
about this game?
Because last Tribal,
you were very vocal in saying,
"This is the most pathetic war
I've ever seen."
Yeah, I was frustrated.
The two biggest allies
I had in the game
were Yul and Wendell,and they went out back-to-back.
But it feels like
we're playing Survivornow,
so that's good, in my opinion.
Jeremy, Nick says
people are ready now to play.
Even now, whispering going on.
It's, uh...
Jeff, man, this is chaotic.
This is legit. Like, it's...
So, it's not a ruse?
It's not a ruse, man.
This is legit.
-And it's back on again.
This is what
I'm talking about, man.
I'm so glad I got this
around my neck tonight.
-People can go home
with idols in their pocket.
People can play
a idol nullifier.
But I'm the only onewith a bulletproof vest tonight.
Sophie, if we just stayed here,
this would go on all night.
Yeah.
Wow.
Kim, what I can't figure out
is what triggers that.
It just seems to just
spontaneously happen.
You know, because you can't everreally know what's going on.
And before you know it,
you feel really paranoid,
you know?
So it's kind of
a Survivorinsanity.
That's a good word for it,
"insanity."
And, Jeremy,
everybody here is a player,
and so it's impossible
to manage a game like
each of you did
when you won your season.
Yeah, this is a lot different
than our-our original seasons.
This is our seasons on steroids.
I thought
Second Chancewas crazy,
but this is madness.
Well, once again,
a lively Tribal.
Is there anything left unsaid?
All right.
-It is time to vote.
-Jeff. Jeff. Jeff. Jeff.
-Jeff?
-What are you doing?
-Go ahead. You go first.
-You go first.
Wow.
Ladies first.
No.
What's happening? You both said
-my name when I said
it's time to vote.
And neither of youappear to have anything to say.
So, should we vote?
Okay.
It is time to vote.
Hey, Jeff.
-What are you doing?
-All right.
-I'm ready to vote.
You're good.
-Jeremy, are you good?
-Nope.
-You coming over here?
-Yes. I'm coming to see you.
-Come to see me. All right.
-I mean,
Tony feels good,and that's the only certainty...
Uh-oh.
...in this game right now,
so that's for you.
It's not... it's not an immunitynecklace nullifier, is it, man?
Okay.
Well, I know
what this note says,
so I can cut to the chase on it.
This is an advantage
that allows Jeremy
to leave Tribal Council
right now.
He cannot be voted out tonight.
And in exchange for leaving,
he will not vote
in tonight's Tribal Council.
This is safety without power.
The "safety" is "I'm leaving."
The "without power" is
"I will not vote."
Jeremy, you can grab your torchand head out.
Hey, guys. Why don't the five
of us just go make a decision.
Damn.
Wow, battle lines
are literally being drawn.
-That was his squad right there.-Mm. Yeah.
He left his squad.
So, how we feeling now?
Shall we vote?
Yeah. But, Jeff,
before we vote...
Another visitor.
I am going to use
my Steal a Vote advantage
tonight.
Okay.
And I am gonna take
Denise's vote.
Okay.
This is a Steal a Vote
advantage.
Denise will not vote tonight.
Sarah, you will vote twice.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Sophie, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
-If anybody has
a hidden immunity idol...
-Yeah.
Yeah, I'll go ahead.
Wow.
I'm gonna play it for Denise.
-Wow. Wow.
-Holy crap.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Kim is playing it for Denise.
Any votes cast against Denise
will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote
Denise. Does not count.
Denise.
-Does not count.
-Whoa.
Sophie.
That's one vote Sophie.
That's two votes Sophie.
Tyson.
Two votes Sophie,
one vote Tyson.
Tyson.
We're tied. Two votes Sophie,
two votes Tyson.
Tyson.
-Damn it.
-That's three votes Tyson,
two votes Sophie.
12th person voted out
-Tyson.
-Sorry, Ty.
That's four.
That's enough.
-It's okay.
Need to bring me your torch.
Tyson, tribe has spoken.
Again.
See you guys soon.
Time for you to go.
Bye, Tyson.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Survivor's
looking for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
Next time onSurvivor...
Everybody's been lying
to everybody.
I don't know what's going on.
I want to do damage, man.
-...this is what
we're doing. Period.
Yes.
Everybody. I'm gonna be golden
if I can pull this off.
Jury, thanks for coming.
You can head back
-to the Edge of Extinction.
-Hey, Probst.
Thank you.
Get in here! Yay!
-Thank you for the gift!
Thank you.
It meant so much to us.
-Thank you.
-You guys are awesome.
-Thank you so much.
-That was a thank you
to you guys.