♪ ♪
Oh, boy.
DANNI:
This is the moment
we've been waiting for,
the battle to get back
in the game.
We get this little scroll
that gives us
the layout of how to spend
fire tokens.
I need to see myself
winning that challenge
and see myself
back in the game.
NATALIE: I decided,
with my four fire tokens,
to go for one advantage
in this challenge
and then put the last three
on an idol.
Trying not to let my nerves
get to me and just kill it.
ROB:
So, Amber let me have
her fire token
so I can have an advantage in
the challenge and buy an idol.
-You can do this.
-I know.
I love you.
I think if I win
the next challenge,
I can win this game.
I believe it.
♪ Come and get it,
come and get it ♪
♪ Come and get it ♪
♪ Come and get it. ♪
♪ ♪
Come on in, guys!
Dakal and Yara,
getting your first look
at the new Sele tribe.
Yul voted out at the last
-Tribal Council.
-(gasps)
Big day on Survivor.
Because, once again,
the game is about to change.
Everybody, drop your Buffs.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
-We are merged.
(whooping)
-(applause)
-DENISE: Yes!
Here you go.
-All right!
-Pass 'em around.
-NICK: Aw, baby.
-(whoops)
BEN:
This merge is the most
exciting moment in the game,
because this is
where the battle starts.
And it's time to find out who
is the champion of champions.
It gives me chills
just talking about it.
All right, we have 11.
We're about to have 12.
Come on in, guys!
Returning from
the Edge of Extinction,
Natalie, Amber,
Danni, Ethan, Tyson...
-Good luck, guys.
-...Rob, Parvati and Yul.
And missing from the group,
a Survivor legend.
Sandra raised the sail
and brought
her Survivor adventure
-to an end.
-Wow.
PROBST:
All right.
You guys have been on Edge
of Extinction for a long time.
Natalie, you're the first winner
ever sent to the Edge.
You've proven
you can last in the game.
You survived 39 days in one.
The Edge is a different thing.
Yeah, to be honest,
that first night,
getting to Extinction and having
nobody to kind of give you a hug
and come to this, like,
blackout island was...
rock bottom.
PROBST:
Tyson,
-you're known for having
a great sense of humor.
-Yeah.
You can find a joke
in the darkest times.
-Right.
-How do you use that
on Extinction?
Uh, I think...
I try to find humor
in everything,
but it's not always because
it's humorous.
It's...
(voice breaking):
maybe a mask or a wall.
PROBST:
Is maybe the reason
you're feeling the emotion
connected to Extinction?
Yeah, I think so.
And when you look at the mast--
and I have two little daughters
at home-- and I think
giving up the pursuit
of a cash prize for your family
is maybe even more paramount
than sticking it out
for a cash prize.
And that's the...
struggle I'm having.
Rob, you met your wife
on an island.
Then you go off and create
this beautiful family.
And now you come back,
once again,
living together on an island.
Is there anything--
if you set aside the game--
romantic about that?
Not on the Edge, there isn't.
It's the worst place
I've ever been to.
It's terrible.
And I got to know
all these people
sent her there first,
maybe 'cause of me.
It stinks. I don't like it.
We never got off the ground,
any of us.
Look at everybody here.
It's all the old-school players.
But none of us here
are quitters.
We're all gonna fight
to get back in this.
PROBST:
All right, you guys
have been enduring Extinction
for this moment right here,
a shot to get back in.
Let's get to it.
For your return challenge,
you're gonna race
through a series of obstacles.
When you get to the finish,
you must maneuver a ball
to the top
of the long, windy track.
First to finish
gets back in this game,
with a shot at winning
the title of Sole Survivor
and the biggest prize
we've ever had,
$2 million.
Take your spots.
We'll get started.
Let's do it. Good luck.
♪ ♪
All right,
before we get to the challenge,
while you were living
on Extinction,
you were working very hard
to try to earn advantage
in this challenge.
Natalie, Danni,
Ethan, Tyson and Rob
each earned one advantage.
When you get to the dig section,
you will not have
to dig up your string.
It will be sitting
on top of the sand.
Amber, Parvati, Yul--
no advantage.
You're running
the entire challenge.
Here we go.
For a shot back in.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First stage,
you've got to untie
three bags of sticks.
Every single second
in this challenge
could be a $2 million second.
Tyson has his first bag.
Rob has his first.
Parvati has one.
Natalie has one. Yul.
There's Danni with one.
Living on Extinction
for this moment right here.
Tyson with a second bag.
Rob has his second.
Ethan has his.
Natalie has hers.
Everybody fighting right now.
Tyson is through
this first section.
Rob's through.
Rob next to Tyson now.
Ethan is through.
Here comes Danni and Parvati.
Everybody getting in on this.
Tyson uses his advantage.
Does not have to dig.
His string is waiting for him.
Rob is through.
He does not have to dig.
There's his advantage.
Ethan is through.
He doesn't have to dig.
Parvati-- she's through, but
she has to dig up that string.
(grunts)
Now you're fashioning
a pole long enough
to retrieve a key,
and that'll get you
to the final phase
of this challenge.
Natalie's through.
She doesn't have to dig.
Danni's through.
She does not have to dig.
-It is Amber digging,
-(grunting)
Parvati digging,
and Yul is gonna have to dig.
This is the time difference
right here.
-(grunting)
-(pants)
-This is the advantage
you worked so hard for,
and it's paying off
with a big time advantage.
Yul has his string.
He's through.
Yul now in on it.
Amber has her string.
She's through.
-(groans)
-Parvati not giving up.
Parvati has her string.
-She's in it now.
-Good job, Parv.
That a way to stick with it,
Parv.
PROBST:
Here goes Rob.
He's gonna be the first
to give it a go.
Can he get there?
Rob really stretching.
Will it be long enough
and strong enough?
Rob is there.
Can he hook it?
Rob has it off.
It's in the sand.
Rob's gonna have it.
Rob can unlock that door.
He's through.
Rob moving on
to the final phase.
Here goes Natalie.
Tyson right behind.
Natalie's very close.
She has it hooked.
Tyson has his hooked.
We got a challenge going now.
Rob has his ball.
All he has to do is
drop that little white ball
at the top of this track.
Natalie is through.
Tyson's through.
Yul has his ring.
Danni has her ring.
Yul is in there now.
Yul had no advantage.
But he is in
with everybody else.
Now the learning curve starts.
How quickly can you figure out
this part of the challenge?
Rob dropped.
Has to start again.
Tyson dropped.
It is Natalie in the lead
right now.
She's a third of the way
up this track.
Natalie--
all that progress dropped.
Parvati's through.
She's in on it.
Ethan's through.
Everybody but Amber is in this,
with a shot to win it.
-(crack)
-Darn it.
♪ ♪
There are so many ways
this can get you.
So hard. Two handles.
You've got to move that ball
up, down, left, right.
-(groans)
-Danni drops.
Yul-- slow and steady.
Cannot get too aggressive
or you risk losing everything.
Natalie giving it another go.
Ethan still working
to get in this.
This is why you suffered
every night on Extinction,
for this moment to get back in.
Right now,
it is Tyson in the lead,
then Yul and Rob
at the same spot,
trying to catch up.
Tyson's making nice progress.
TONY:
Ooh.
PROBST:
Trying to maneuver a curve
requires a lot of touch.
-WENDELL: He got it.
-ADAM: Wow.
-Oh, a nice save by Tyson.
-ADAM: Oh, my God.
PROBST:
It is Tyson
with the last stretch,
with Yul and Rob
trying to catch him.
Nobody else close.
YUL:
No, no, no.
-PROBST:
Yul thinks he's in trouble.
-No.
-Can he save it?
-Oh.
-Aw! Geez.
-No, Yul loses everything.
-(gasping)
-Has to start again.
-(Yul groans)
It is Tyson and Rob now,
fighting for a shot
to get back in.
♪ You better be ready ♪
♪ ♪
Rob's catching Tyson.
PROBST:
Tyson inches away
from being back in this game.
Rob right on his tail.
♪ ♪
This is it.
Both guys have to be perfect.
The end is in sight for Tyson.
Rob within striking distance.
This is gonna be close.
We are dead even right now,
neck and neck.
-Oh, my goodness!
-PROBST: Both guys
hovering very close to the edge.
Who will get it to drop
for the win?
♪ It's coming for you. ♪
-And he's done it!
-Yeah!
-(applause)
-(whoops)
Tyson is back in!
-Yeah!
-(whooping)
PROBST:
Huge challenge.
Good job, bro. Good job.
PROBST:
Wow.
That was insane.
TONY:
Now we know
why Sandra went home.
-She wasn't doing this.
-Yeah.
-(chuckling)
PROBST:
Tyson,
congratulations.
You are back in this game.
Here's your merge Buff.
Join your new tribe.
Good luck, Tyson.
-Good luck, buddy!
-Good job, Tyson.
PROBST:
Natalie, Amber,
Danni, Ethan, Rob,
Parvati, Yul heading back
to the Edge of Extinction,
where you'll be waiting for one
final shot to get back
in this game.
And you will immediately begin
coming to Tribal Council
as the first seven members
of our jury.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to Extinction.
Good luck, guys.
-(applause)
-YUL: Bye, guys.
-Good job, guys. Good job.
PROBST:
All right.
You guys have made the merge.
Day 19.
Basically the halfway point.
You will be merging
at the Sele beach.
Congratulations.
Grab your stuff and head out.
TYSON: The Edge of Extinction
was tough,
and it made me think,
"You know,
"maybe I'm not cut out
for this game anymore.
Maybe fatherhood
has made me soft."
And so winning it boosted
my confidence a little bit
that maybe I can still do
the things out here
that I've always known I could.
♪ ♪
Whoa.
TONY: So we come into
the merge tribe,
and I see the new menu,
and prices have gone up.
I can't buy anything.
I'm looking at the menu--
three tokens, two tokens.
I got one. I can't do nothing.
-Oh. Look at that, huh?
-Oh, wow.
I'm just like a little poor kd
going into the bodega,
and I don't have enough money
to buy a little bubble gum.
-Yeah, baby. Yes.
-Oh, my God.
TONY:
But, thankfully, the feast
doesn't cost you anything,
and I'm very grateful for that.
I love it.
-Tony! Come here, bubba.
-Big, Big Ben!
(grunts, chuckles)
-Congratulations today.
-Welcome back.
SARAH:
To be one of 12 sitting
at that table,
one of the 12 greats,
it's unbelievable.
But the lines
are so blurred right now
that it looks like
a big bowl of spaghetti,
and you don't know where
one relationship starts
and one ends.
Do you want a glass of rum?
(laughter)
SARAH: Everyone's a lion
that's sitting at the table.
It's just who has
the biggest mane right now.
What happened with Sandra?
Jeremy and I were...
on the bottom.
And Sandra, she's like,
"If you give me two fire tokens,
I will give you an idol."
So I took it.
I played that to save myself.
And I happened to have another
-hidden immunity idol...
-Oh!
...that I played for Jeremy.
I was the only one
that voted for Sandra.
They all voted for me.
-So, yeah, that is
the story of the queen.
-NICK: Wow.
-TONY: Yeah.
-SOPHIE: Denise's story felt
a little bit like we were
all in a bar and she was
-telling us old war stories.
-(gasping, cheering)
-Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
-TONY: The Queenslayer!
-The Queenslayer!
-(laughter)
SOPHIE:
It just made her look
really good.
But I have to imagine
everybody at the table thought,
"Hmm, like, one person has a
résumé out here. Good to know."
Did you think, like,
at the start of this,
-that you'd be sitting here?
-Mm.
ADAM:
I definitely didn't expect it
to look like this,
with every single
old-school player
-getting-- Right?
-DENISE: Right. No. Very true.
-MICHELE: Yeah.
TONY: Was that intentional,
you think, guys?
-Or just happened that way?
-MICHELE: No.
-It really wasn't.
-Not on my part.
-MICHELE: I don't think so.
TYSON:
I am honestly the only O.G.
left on this beach.
It's all
new-school players here.
I played three times
before most of these people
even put their
Survivor diapers on.
Are the kids that are coming up
now changing the game so much
that I can't adapt?
I don't think so.
-Cheers to the merge.
-NICK: Absolutely. Absolutely.
-OTHERS: Cheers.
-BEN: Tyson, hell of a job.
-NICK: Tyson.
-Thanks, guys.
-That's so impressive.
TYSON:
If I were these people,
I would get rid of me day one
every single time
I ever played Survivor.
Because if you let me
get my roots
into whatever cracks are ther,
I'm gonna build a home.
ADAM:
This is awesome!
There's a real shelter!
We got a swing set, workbench,
kitchen area.
WENDELL:
At this point in the game,
you want to have the right tem
around you and have
the right people protecting you.
I have Michele and I have Nic,
two people
that I can really trust.
But we need more numbers.
Good to see you, young man.
I met Jeremy outside the game
once or twice.
I know he's a great guy,
and I can work with him.
So, at this point in the game,
I really want to work
on my relationships.
WENDELL:
Not too much, man.
-I'm good with Nick.
-All right.
JEREMY:
Who do you not like?
Sophie is playing.
-But I'm cool with her.
-All right.
Denise is kind of the same way.
Denise is playing a better game
than you think.
Yeah.
JEREMY:
I like Wendell.
We have a mutual respect
for each other, so...
I want him to come
and work with me.
You could say that.
JEREMY:
Wendell has Nick
as his right-hand man.
I want to be that person.
So I wouldn't mind
to see Nick go.
If I get rid of Nick,
I could be his number one.
If I ever hear anything
about you...
-Same thing.
-And you won't see me
writing your name down.
Same thing.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
♪ ♪
BEN:
It sounds like no joke
out there, dude.
I am glad you're back though,
honestly.
TYSON:
I tried to get
-the big targets together early.
-Yeah.
And it just backfired.
And then everybody afterwards
was like,
"Uh-oh, that was a mistake."
-And all the big targets
just started getting popped.
-Just-- Yeah, yeah.
BEN:
Tyson is right.
Big players,
big names have been taken out
left and right.
I mean, you look at
Tyson, Rob, Parvati, Sandra.
There's four right there,
and after that,
it'll keep going.
What are you looking at
as the big targets?
We got me, you, Jeremy, Tony.
-Yeah.
-There's four.
I think the big targets
are already outnumbered.
-Yeah. Well, yeah.
-So we have to take control
before they realize that.
BEN:
We're drawing lines.
It's gonna be big threats
versus little threats.
So that's where we need
to start putting the targets.
Tyson and I went down there.
We were talking about
keeping the threats in.
So the smaller target,
less threatening,
-are the ones he wants...
-Are the lower profile people.
-Low-profile. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
TONY:
That's music to my ears,
because this is
exactly what I wanted.
People like Wendell, Nick,
Adam and Michele--
they're good players,
but they're lower profile.
They're not in the spotlight.
We have to break up that...
-Y-- Oh, that's 100%.
-Okay.
There's no target
on these people.
So now's the time for me to try
to get rid of all of them.
♪ ♪
TONY:
Oh, my God.
I think it's raining.
-This is how you know
you're alive...
-Yeah.
-...when you feel miserable.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, man.
ADAM:
Some of these people,
you'd think they'd never played
Survivor before.
They're dying in this rain,
but this is nothing.
I went through a cyclone.
We're having fun now!
♪ ♪
NICK:
Yeah.
KIM:
We truly are in survival mode.
It's hard out here. I mean,
you either laugh or cry.
Like, it's almost comical
how miserable we are.
We're freaking freezing.
TYSON:
How long does this have to go
before people
talk about buying a tarp?
I'll wait for one of
those rich people to buy one.
Mm-hmm.
WENDELL:
I've heard Denise...
Okay.
NICK:
That's who I would choose
if I had my choice.
Denise took down the queen.
That places
a lot of eyes on Denise.
And I want to vote people out
that are playing
a winner's game right now.
Man, get them away
from this island.
♪ ♪
Come on in, guys!
PROBST:
Nothing easy about Survivor.
Nothing warm about this rain.
(teeth chattering)
It is a cold day in Fiji.
Sophie, I got to ask,
are you okay?
Because your entire body
is convulsing.
I'm really cold.
KIM:
It's gonna be--
You're gonna be okay.
-It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
-You got this, Sophie. Come on.
-Body warmth.
-We're okay.
(crying)
PROBST:
Sophie's trying to not cry
-through it.
-You got this.
And yet we have
a challenge to run.
Let's get to it.
Your first individual
immunity challenge.
It's a Survivor classic.
You are going to hold on
to a pole
for as long as you can.
When you drop, you're out.
Last person left hanging
wins immunity.
This is what you want:
-individual immunity
in this game.
-Ooh.
In addition,
-you earn a fire token.
-TONY: Mm, all right.
PROBST:
And to make your first
Tribal Council as a merged tribe
a little more interesting,
it will be the first woman
-and the first man.
-Oh! What?
PROBST:
So we have
two individual immunities,
-two fire tokens up for grabs.
-Wow.
Everybody else, Tribal Council,
where somebody
-will be the tenth person
voted out...
-Wow.
...and sent to
Edge of Extinction.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
-Here we go.
-(Sophie shudders)
♪ ♪
All right.
This challenge is on.
♪ ♪
I'm so scared.
It's already difficult.
In addition to being hard
to hold on to
in normal conditions,
now the pole is wet.
PROBST:
Today, we will have
one man and one woman
win this challenge
and be safe at Tribal Council,
and they will each earn
a fire token.
Adam already starting
to move down on the pole.
(grunts)
-Michele is first out.
-(Adam groans)
-Big fall. Are you all right?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
-You sure?
-MICHELE: Yeah.
PROBST:
Do you want medical to come in?
No.
PROBST:
Michele is first out
with a hard fall.
(grunts)
Sarah starting
to inch her way down now.
Tyson, who has
won this challenge,
is also struggling.
(groans softly)
Sarah coming down
to the last toehold.
-(grunts)
-Tony is about halfway down.
Wendell starting
to come down a little.
-(grunts) Whoa!
-PROBST: Adam goes down.
He is out.
-(Sarah exhales)
-Sarah drops.
She is out.
(exhales)
Tyson is out.
Wendell now starting to slip
a little more.
Tony slipping more.
Wendell's gonna opt out.
(exhales)
Tony is out.
We have Denise,
Kim and Sophie
fighting for the women.
It is Jeremy,
Ben and Nick for the men.
(grunts)
Dang it.
Sophie's down.
We are down to two women left.
It is Denise and Kim.
And Kim has started
to inch down.
Denise shows her first signs
of slipping.
Denise sliding down
a little more.
Kim can't get her toe in.
Kim drops.
She is out.
-BEN: Good job, Denise.
-Denise has won
individual immunity
for the women
and a fire token.
Yeah!
PROBST:
We are down now
to the three men.
Ben dropped.
And we have a showdown.
It is Jeremy and Nick.
The last two people up there
fighting for immunity
and a fire token.
We could be here for a while.
(exhales)
(sighs)
(grunts softly)
Nick with his first movement
in a long time.
-(exhales)
-Sliding down the pole now,
looking for a new grip.
(exhales)
(Jeremy exhales)
Jeremy doing a lot
of adjusting
but staying in the same spot.
(Jeremy exhales)
-Good job, guys.
-Hang in there.
(chuckles)
PROBST:
Both guys looking down
at each other,
trying to get a sign
of weakness.
(exhales)
-(groans)
-Nick on the move again.
See Jeremy's toes
just barely wedged in there.
Nick sliding again.
He's got one last toehold.
(grunts)
Nick cannot hang out any longer.
-Nick drops.
-(applause)
-ADAM: Very good, guys.
-Jeremy wins immunity
and a fire token.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Joins Denise.
-Will not be going home tonight.
-Good job, bro.
DENISE:
Good job, you two.
BEN:
Good job, guys.
Denise, come on over.
-BEN: Denise!
-SOPHIE: Good job, Denise.
(inhales sharply)
Thank you.
PROBST:
Well-earned.
Denise safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
In addition,
this fire token is yours.
You're not going home. Congrats.
-Thank you.
-PROBST: Jeremy, come on over.
-BEN: J!
-DENISE: Good job, J.
-PROBST: Still hobbling.
-Yeah. Mm.
PROBST:
Jeremy safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted
out of this game.
This fire token is yours.
Congrats. Head on back.
As for the rest of you,
after 21 tough days,
somebody voted out tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
JEREMY:
When you have this necklace,
you have power.
So, my plan is
to go after Nick.
But I don't want to be the one
that's looked at as the boss.
Don't get me wrong.
I want to drive this thing,
but I don't want
everybody else to know
that I'm driving this thing.
♪ ♪
BEN:
Oh, my gosh.
We're gonna need some wood.
TONY:
We're doing a wood run?
BEN:
Yeah, let's do it.
(grunts)
(laughs)
So, who are you guys thinking?
BEN:
I think either Nick
or Wendell. Unfortunately.
JEREMY:
I do want to break up
-Nick and Wendell.
-BEN: Okay.
I would say take out Nick.
I just think I could...
I feel like...
-We could work with Wendell.
-Okay.
TONY:
I want to keep
the higher profile threats,
us lions, in the game.
And Nick is a player that is
that hyena that I talked about.
He just stays on the outskirts.
He just waits
for the lions to go at it,
and that's when he comes in
to see what he can get.
He's like a scavenger.
And Nick runs around
and just butts into
everybody's conversations.
-Yeah. Yeah, see,
but that's what I don't like.
-Right.
BEN:
It's Nick, right? Socially,
his game is
actually pretty good.
But lately,
he's just butting in
on everybody's
conversation now,
which is very weird.
You want your hair braided?
(chuckles)
I wish I could.
BEN:
It's very concerning,
because you never know
when it's gonna happen.
And it was like, "Dude."
But it's nice. We were trying
to get the school year...
BEN:
Nick is killing me, though.
If the group
decides Nick tonight,
I'll write Nick's name down.
So, what's the word?
What are we thinking?
-What do you...?
-I think Adam.
I haven't been talking game
with him.
Everybody who ever has
has said they don't trust him,
-so why should I?
-Yeah.
NICK:
Denise is immune tonight,
but she's super close
with Adam.
So I said, "All right.
Let's vote out Adam.
That's easy."
Everybody that has
worked with him says,
"Don't trust Adam."
I'm gonna try to scoop up...
Yeah.
ADAM:
Okay.
Um, I'd probably prefer Wendell.
ADAM:
Mm-hmm.
SOPHIE:
Between Nick and Wendell,
who would be more likely
to work with me in the future?
And I see Wendell,
and Wendell and Jeremy
are constantly broing out.
Was that just
from, like, this morning?
That wasn't there yesterday.
That was definitely
not there yesterday.
Yes, it was.
SOPHIE:
My sense of what's happening
is that a bunch
of the "big guys,"
Jeremy, Tony, Tyson and Ben,
all got together and said,
"Maybe Wendell, maybe Nick."
But a lot of power
in this tribe
is coming from Jeremy,
and I think
Wendell is Jeremy's man.
-I'm down for Wendell.
-Okay. Okay.
-Okay.
-Kind of don't mind
cutting Jeremy
-off at the knees
a little bit, you know?
-Oh, really?
I don't know.
They're, like, best friends,
aren't they?
TONY:
I don't know, man.
See, that's what I don't know.
So it's shifting to Wendell now?
Not...?
But can we get Jeremy
to go along with that?
It's like...
So, the group
is wanting Wendell.
I'll just come out and say it.
I know. I know. I know.
And I knew you weren't
gonna be happy about it.
Like, if Wendell's here,
he's another shield for us.
-That's our thing.
-I know. It is our thing.
I just think
it's a bad decision.
-You do?
-I do.
-So, we'll just...
-What's up, man?
-NICK: Just getting water.
-Water? Cool.
-Yeah.
-Oh. All right.
You know what I mean?
Like, that's...
And that's why...
-Who does he say?
-It's Adam.
JEREMY:
Wendell's on
the chopping block.
It's horrible.
I don't want that.
I want to work with him.
Wendell and Nick
are voting for Adam.
So, as long as Wendell's safe,
I would love to see Adam go.
Let's just vote for Adam.
When you keep letting
people like Adam
-skate around...
-Yeah.
...like, that's when they--
He bites you in the end.
If you're that adamant...
Listen, I don't want
Wendell to go, either,
and if we want
to change it,
it's gonna be a lot of work.
I-I just don't... I don't think
it's the right move.
-Who do you trust more?
-SARAH: Wendell.
I mean, I'll change
the last minute if we have to.
-My trust level
is all I care about. Like...
-KIM: Yeah. Same.
I don't trust Adam.
KIM:
Yeah. It's just tricky.
TONY:
If you and Kim
were saying Adam,
hey, I could jump on board
with you and go Adam.
(chuckles):
Adam is a...
-is a little snake, I think.
-JEREMY: Yeah.
Then let's do Adam.
The only one who probably isn't
is Denise.
I think we might
have to just look
-at Nick and Adam...
-DENISE: Adam.
So, then,
are you guys
wanting to keep Wendell?
-JEREMY: Yeah.
-DENISE: Okay.
If we take out Nick, there's
not a huge ripple effect.
-JEREMY: No.
-DENISE: Right?
If we take out Adam,
there's not
a huge ripple effect.
-No.
-I mean,
I would have been the ripple.
-And I'm saying...
-Yeah. And you're saying
-you're all right? Yeah, yeah.
-I'm saying...
-I'm smooth. I mean...
-(laughs): Yeah.
Even though
you're so close with Adam?
-I could go either way.
-Yeah.
DENISE:
You know, Adam's been
one of my closest
alliance members.
But at the same time,
you just have to
kind of go with the flow
or go with the tide.
So, Adam and I
created a day one alliance.
But that may not be
a day 39 alliance.
I have a weird feeling.
No. I would not have
a weird feeling if I were you.
Then why's Jeremy still, like...
I seriously think you're fine.
SOPHIE: My understanding
is that Nick and Wendell
are voting you.
Okay.
I really hope
you're not blindsided tonight,
'cause if you are,
I'm blindsided, too.
ADAM:
Of course I'm nervous.
Nick and Wendell think it's m.
The people who I think
do have my back
are telling me, "Stay calm.
Stay cool." Easy to say when
it's not your name on the line.
I think you're getting paranoid
about people deciding
between Nick and Wendell.
-Okay.
-It's not about you.
ADAM:
What I'm hearing is
either Nick or Wendell
but nobody being able
to make up their mind.
What is the plan? I don't know.
I don't know.
Okay, well, I just got back,
-so I have zero clue
about what's going on.
-Welcome back.
I don't know. I...
So the answer
-to your question would be no.
-Okay. Okay.
Then I go to Ben, and he says,
"I don't know what it is."
(grunting mockingly)
Like, dude.
I'm trying to stay alive here.
Like, why are you upset?
Crazy man.
Okay. Got you.
ADAM:
Tonight is about survival.
And I'm scared.
(voice breaking):
I don't want to go home.
(laughs):
And I don't want
to go to the Edge.
I need to be here tomorrow.
Rain or shine, I don't care.
I need to stay in the game.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Tyson gets a torch
because Tyson is back
in this game.
We'll now bring in
the members of our jury.
So, let's start with Tyson.
When you've been voted out,
you go to the Edge,
and then you get back in,
does the game
feel different emotionally?
-Are the stakes different?
-TYSON: Yeah.
I mean, I don't want to go back
to the Edge of Extinction.
And getting voted out
the first time,
I definitely was a little
loosey-goosey with my filter,
and now I've, uh,
definitely tightened up.
PROBST:
Sophie, was there
any talk that, "Look,
"Tyson was already
voted out once.
Let's just get rid of him"?
Survivor is not as simple
as that. You know, Tyson
comes in with
a lot of relationships,
and he comes in,
in some ways, with less baggage
than we've all
been accumulating.
So I didn't hear
Tyson's name today.
TONY:
And, Jeff, the thing is
we're-we're doing things
on a strategic point of view,
not on a personal level, right?
So, Tyson, for example.
The argument that got him
voted off the first time
doesn't hold any weight this
time around because the dynamics
of the game-- not only the game
but the players-- has changed.
PROBST:
So, Denise,
first individual immunity.
You know
you're coming to Tribal.
Why is it so important
to win this one?
This is, like,
the defining vote tonight.
It's the vote where you're
finding out if the relationships
that you've been building
are solidified.
So, we're fighting for our life
out there on that pole today.
PROBST:
Wendell, 12 people
is still a lot of people
for this to be a defining vote.
Is it necessarily defining?
Um... (sighs)
It will tell some things.
I mean, generally,
we've been able to point
in a particular direction.
But you try to check in
with certain people,
and you also hope
that you have the right ears
in the right conversations,
so it's tricky.
It's a... it's a
difficult balance, Jeff.
PROBST:
Adam, is it as tricky
as literally walking
past somebody
as you're gathering wood,
going, "Plan 'A'"?
Yeah, absolutely.
Some of the conversations
that I've had here
have been like... that.
They happen,
and then they're over,
and you don't even know if you
just had a conversation or not.
And I'm the type of person
that wants to have
that conversation
with everybody.
PROBST:
Nick, is there a risk
that you can go back too many
times to say, "Are we sure"?
And at some point,
people might just say,
"Hey, you know what?
Let's just make it him.
-Keeps asking if we're sure."
-It's tough
because I want
to double-check, too.
I mean, that's the way
I've always played.
But, yeah,
you don't want to look like
the guy that's paranoid
or the guy
that's questioning
all your allies.
SOPHIE:
You know, Jeff,
I feel like the hardest thing
on Survivor is
being okay not being
in every conversation,
being a little bit
out of the loop.
I mean, in my head,
I turn into a 12-year-old girl
in high school who wants
to follow every single group.
But instead, I have to prove
to people who are
in my alliance, in those groups,
that I trust them
and that I don't
have to be
in every conversation.
PROBST:
So, Sarah,
if it's impossible to have
a conversation with everybody,
how fast can you tell
if a name's
gathering steam,
getting traction?
It takes a while to figure out
if that name
is actually the name.
Like, in past seasons,
you would see the punch coming.
This season,
people are gonna get sniped.
Everybody's holding
their cards so close.
Nobody really believes that name
even up until the last
few minutes we're at camp.
PROBST:
So, Jeremy, that sounds
like people don't want
to throw the name out,
but they'll gladly listen
to a name.
Jeff, we're all playing a
little sparring match right now.
We're testing people out.
We don't want to give them
the whole thing yet,
so we're just getting our reach.
PROBST:
And yet, Adam, somehow,
moves get made,
blindside after blindside.
I... I'm still not sure
how-how things
may or may not have-have
come together tonight.
I mean, people did not
want to talk.
Tony, with the cagey level
of gameplay,
is the easy thing just to say,
"As long as it's not me"?
Well, that-that's how I think
we're all looking at it.
Like, this is a body
of water right here.
This is the ocean,
and you just got to stay
with the flow,
and if you want to swim
against the current, you're
putting yourself in danger.
So right now,
I think we're all willing
to go with the current.
PROBST:
So, before we vote,
everybody's willing to go
with the current,
but nobody knows
which way the current's going.
Is the tide coming in?
Is it going out?
It is fascinating.
All right, then. Time to vote.
Jeremy, you're up.
♪ ♪
(whispering): Your reputation
in the game has preceded you,
made you a target.
I'm just gonna roll with it.
♪ ♪
It's either you or me tonight.
I know that, but do you?
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
a hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay. I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Adam.
Wendell.
Three votes Adam,
one vote Wendell.
Wendell.
That's two votes Wendell.
We're tied.
Three votes Adam,
three votes Wendell.
Wendell.
That's four votes Wendell.
That's five votes Wendell.
Wendell.
That's six votes Wendell,
three votes Adam.
Tenth person voted out:
Wendell.
That's seven. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Wendell, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Good play, guys.
♪ ♪
"Bequeath your fire tokens
to any player
still in the game."
Who stabbed me in the back?
I don't know.
Michele, good luck, girl.
Nick, keep fighting, brother.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
PROBST: Survivor's looking
for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
NICK:
It is now my duty
to take every one
of these people out
that have double-crossed me.
Mistake, brother.
Your ass is gonna go home.
(groans)
He's playing with so much fire.
Please, don't let it burn him.
WENDELL:
I'm captive right now,
but I'm plotting a way to escape
this wretched prison that they
call the Edge of Extinction.
Let's go see everybody.
Once I get out of here,
I'm gonna do what I need to do.
The war is not over.
What happened, man?
They got me out of there;
that's what happened.
(roars)