♪ ♪
(crickets chirping)
(blowing)
JEREMY:
At Tribal, I said,
"I'm not going to Edge
with a advantage in my pocket."
Everybody's been lying for
the past two weeks to everybody.
No one's telling the truth.
I don't know what's going on.
So, I have my advantage,
my Safety Without Power.
So I said, "I'm out of here."
Like a... (snaps fingers)
flash in the night.
Boom. Like a Houdini trick.
I just-- Poof and I'm gone.
You know? It was beautiful.
Oh, man.
And then I come back to camp,
and I am losing my mind,
waiting to see
who's coming back.
And then I start seeing people
come back one at a time.
Ben comes.
Sophie comes.
Denise comes.
And then I see Tony and Kim.
I was like, "Wow,
Tyson is back on the Edge."
This is not good.
I-I just want
to put on some pants.
I know. I see he's not here.
What happened?
-TONY: I thought we had a plan.
-SARAH: What'd you think
was gonna happen?
-JEREMY: Tell me what happened.
-BEN/SARAH: What'd you think
was gonna happen?
JEREMY:
I don't know.
Tell me what happened.
No one's gonna say
what happened?
Are we just gonna play
this game,
-"What do you think
was gonna happen?"
-BEN: Yeah. Yeah.
BEN:
Going into Tribal Council,
we had a real clear-cut plan.
Sarah, Sophie,
Nick, Tony and myself,
we were gunning for Jeremy.
But Jeremy gets up
and leaves Tribal.
So there goes our target, right?
Like, that's our target,
and he just walked out,
safe as can be.
BEN: Ever been. I've never
seen anything like it.
I've never been in
anything like it.
Going forward,
Jeremy's obviously
public enemy number one.
And this is
an actual group of five
that I think we can move forward
and-and take control
of the game with.
And so my gut is telling me
stick with the five
and go for the biggest threat,
which is Jeremy.
Do you think
your game is better
with Tyson here or without him?
No matter
if he's causing drama or not.
You're on
the chopping block now.
Because guess who's
the biggest, baddest dude here.
You.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You've won immunities.
You just played advantages.
-Don't-- Listen, don't think...
-(scoffs)
-Jeremy, I-- Don't.
Don't. No. Listen.
-I'm sorry. I don't have
to listen right now, dude.
-Listen, don't think that
I'm the guy that everyone's
gonna be looking at
as a big and bad guy.
-Don't look at it like that.
-Okay. All right.
Well, in my eyes, I think you're
a lot bigger threat than I am.
All right. So...
JEREMY:
Tyson's the biggest shield
around.
So I wanted
Tyson here as a shield for me.
That's my meat shield s-syste.
That's how I win this game.
And as soon as
I'm out of Tribal,
oh, it's time to jump on Tyson.
I mean, I got played hard.
-I can't tell what's real
and what's fake.
-Yeah.
I-I mean, it's just
so many levels of chaos.
I can't play this game
like that.
I know.
MICHELE:
The obvious situation
when you're left out of a vote
and nobody seems to trust you
is that you're probably
on the bottom.
Mm-hmm.
MICHELE:
So, me, Kim,
Jeremy and Denise
are spinning around
like tops, trying to figure out
what the heck is going on.
Because, obviously,
we are gonna be picked off.
♪ ♪
TONY:
The beginning of the season,
I couldn't go
and look for idols.
I didn't want
to put a target on my back
by leaving camp at all,
so I stayed in camp
all the time.
I was drooling.
I wanted to go look,
but I couldn't do it,
'cause it would
jeopardize my game.
And look what happened.
I'm still in the game.
I made the merge.
Everything's working out
wonderfully,
because I've been patient
and I haven't been
causing any paranoia at camp
by looking for idols.
Everybody's always tired after
Tribal. They're exhausted.
They sleep like logs.
So now I'm at a point
where I'm saying,
"You know what? Now's my time
to go out and go to work."
Historically, on Survivor, when
you play an idol at Tribal,
it goes right back
into the game.
That means the idol's
back out there now.
So, first thing in the mornin,
I went to the area where I knew
I wanted to target first
and I said to myself,
"This is where I'm gonna look
before anybody else
gets up to look."
♪ ♪
-No.
-And then, while I'm looking,
Nick shows up.
And he's cramping my style.
I'm like, "This is my area, man.
I want you out of here."
I think we just need
to comb this whole area, man.
-Yeah, okay.
-You know?
I mean, the water well, too.
NICK:
Yeah, that's where
I was gonna go.
TONY: I already looked
at the water well area.
So I said, "Nick,
"go to the well.
Let's split up.
"It's a perfect strategy.
You search the well first.
I'll search this area first
before anybody else does."
So he says, "Good idea,"
and he goes off.
And I was so happy, so delighted
that he did that.
So I continue my search.
I went right to work.
I was looking, looking,
looking, looking,
looking, looking, looking,
scratching, scratching,
looking up, going in the hole,
looking, looking, looking.
No! No.
♪ ♪
I picked up a rock
behind a big root,
and there was a little package.
I grabbed that little package,
and I ran
-full force into the jungle...
-No way.
...to a nice spot where I knew
I was safe to look at it.
Please, please, please.
-I open it up. I peel it open.
-Please, please, please.
Yes. Yes.
And then, sure enough,
it's a idol.
I am so excited.
I really didn't think I was
gonna find an idol this season
because of the way
I was playing.
But say hello
to my little friend.
Mwah. Oh, my God.
Thank you so much.
This is season 40.
These are all veterans,
so you got to,
you got to think of everything.
And I woke up early
in the morning.
I made sure
I was the first one looking.
That's somebody that knows
how to play the game Survivor.
So now I got the real deal.
Mwah. I love it so much.
(birds chirping)
♪ ♪
SARAH:
This morning, I thought,
"You know, what happens after
Sarah Lacina's a cop?"
A lot of people think
I'm just smart and funny and...
pretty,
but I'm actually
really creative.
And I can, you know,
make clothes.
While I've been out here,
I started my own clothing line.
Turn around.
Wow. Yeah.
KIM:
Right?
-So, do you like it?
-JEREMY: Oh, geez.
-BEN: That is awesome.
-SOPHIE: Oh, my God, I want one.
That's so cute.
-That's pretty cool.
-That's actually really good.
SOPHIE:
I want a piece
of the Sarah Lacina Fiji line.
SARAH:
I love Tony to death,
but he and I play this game
two completely different ways.
Could you guys walk a runway
for me?
-TONY: I'm out of here.
I'm not watching this.
-No, you're watching...
-Hell no.
-Yes, you are.
-JEREMY: Come on, Tone.
-Where you going, dude?
-No way.
SARAH:
Tony wants this flashy,
"I'm playing idols for them,"
but not really playing
a social game.
As you walk down,
you get your jacket off...
(laughing)
-...and then walk back.
-MICHELE: Oh,
-that's perfect!
-Right. Yeah.
My social game is really great.
-♪ ♪
-Oh, my...
Yeah!
(lively chatter)
♪ I think
I'm making myself crazy ♪
(Ben laughs)
Yeah!
♪ Oh, na-na-na-na... ♪
Let's all give a warm welcome
-to Miss Sarah Lacina.
-(cheering and applause)
-BEN: Yay!
-TONY: Sarah wanted
to put on a fashion show,
but I want to do damage, man.
BEN:
Well done, ladies. Well done.
TONY:
I want to play the game.
Jeremy was my target
at the last Tribal.
Jeremy's very likable.
I can't go to the end with him,
so there's no point
in keeping him around.
Where's your shoes, dude?
TONY:
I was doing laundry
this morning,
and I put 'em in the trees.
So, obviously,
I need to go undercover
right now.
Ah, bro.
It was, it was rough.
Kim is whispering in my ear,
"Vote for Sophie."
Tyson's telling Michele,
"Vote for Denise."
And I got blindsided
by all that.
You know what?
I think it's fine.
Tyson was all jacked up,
but I think it's fine.
TONY:
What I have to do is pretend
that I'm on a side
that I'm really not.
MICHELE:
Who's, like, your number one
person out here?
-I guess right now
would be Jeremy.
-Mm-hmm.
TONY:
I'm undercover, so I can keep
infiltrated in the group
that I really want out.
-How are you guys doing?
-Good.
Just trying
to figure things out.
Which is Jeremy, Michele,
Denise and Kim.
-You wanted Sophie out.
-Sophie. Yes.
-What do you think I would do?
-I think you were
-gonna vote Jeremy.
-Oh, my God, bro.
-You tell me if I'm wrong.
-You're wrong.
I'm not voting for Jeremy.
I was with Jeremy.
I have to continuously pretend
I'm on their side,
because that's the only way
we can blindside them.
Now I'm getting nervous,
because they might try to do
-something to me.
-I don't think so.
-Well, I don't know.
-In my real job,
I never went undercover
like this.
The real world
is way more dangerous
than getting blindsided
on Survivor, so, right now,
I'm having all the fun out here
on Survivor land.
(chirping)
Okay.
We had a really good talk,
and...
MICHELE:
Yeah.
-You know what I mean?
-Mm-hmm.
JEREMY:
I think this group
is solid-- Michele, Kim,
Denise and Tony.
MICHELE:
It's gonna be
the scrappiest vote for us.
-It's gonna be crazy.
-We're gonna be scraping
through.
-Good talk, lady.
-We'll get out of this.
-I know we will.
-(laughs)
JEREMY:
So I'm thinking
we have five out of nine.
This is good for me.
This is good for my game.
Right.
Yeah.
-Okay, well,
we can't let that happen.
-Right. Right.
KIM:
Tony has got this whole act
going right now,
where he's trying to salvage
this relationship with Jeremy.
He is doing
this whole psychotic
double agent act,
where, like, I'm not supposed
to know what Tony is doing.
But I do know.
So I feel like Tony's my biggest
enemy out here right now.
♪ ♪
TYSON:
Some mentalities can handle it.
And some can't.
It can ruin people's lives,
to lose the game.
There's a lot of people
that go home
and struggle with it for year.
For reals.
-Yeah.
-You gonna be okay, Wendell?
-I think so.
-Good.
-All day, every day.
-You're strong.
Adam's gonna have a hard time.
♪ ♪
AMBER:
Whoa. Workhorse right there.
ETHAN:
Yeah.
Feeling good.
PARVATI:
I'm very hungry.
-Wow, somebody had
a bottle of wine?
-Oh, my God, there's...
(quietly):
What the-- Oh, my--
Oh, my God,
did you just find a clue?
I just found this.
What the hell?
PARVATI:
Natalie and I
are looking for firewood
around the rocks,
and, all of a sudden,
Natalie digs something up
out of the sand.
And it's this wine bottle,
and I'm like, "What is that?"
NATALIE:
Okay. I wish.
PARVATI:
Now we have this clue.
So we're like,
"What is happening?"
Okay, so how 'bout
we don't tell anyone?
-Let's don't tell anyone.
-Yeah.
-Just me and you.
-Okay.
-Let's just do a quick walk.
-Yeah.
PARVATI:
"I'll crawl if I must,
I'll never rest.
'Cause to lay down and rest
would be the end."
-NATALIE:
"Crawl" and-and "crown."
-"Crown."
Crowns are at the top.
Yeah.
Do you think "rest" has anything
to do with, um, rest...
"I'll never lay down,
I'll never rest."
So do you think that has
anything to do with our camp?
Like, lay down, like sleeping?
I just think
the crawling has something...
Like around our bed?
-Dude, it's under the bed.
-The bed. That's what I said.
-I was like, "Under."
-That's exactly where it is.
It's under the bed.
Crawling under the bed
where everyone's laying.
That's exactly it.
This is where
we're gonna find this thing.
Now we have
to strategize
how we're gonna get this thing,
because everyone
lays on that all... day...
long.
God, they haven't left even
at all.
I know.
Literally, all day,
the shelter
was never unoccupied, so...
we were just happy that people
eventually migrated away
from the main shelter
to watch the sun going down,
which felt like
it took forever.
YUL:
Yeah.
It's really pretty over there.
It's purple.
-YUL: (sighs) Yeah.
-(chuckles)
NATALIE:
Parv distracts everybody,
and I knew I had
a very short period of time
to actually get eyes
on this thing before dark.
And I just started looking
for a medallion,
something big, similar
to the clues we've received
in the past, but under
the one side of the bed,
tied up to the top plank,
was a really small scroll.
And I grabbed it,
and I ran away.
(laughs)
(gasps)
(laughs):
Oh, my God.
-Crazy.
-(laughs)
So, the actual advantage
is an extortion advantage,
which I've been waiting
for some way to kind of mess up
people's game, because I have
no alliances anymore.
PARVATI:
I'm thinking
we could really disrupt
the game if we give it
to someone that no one expects
and someone that we know is
totally chaotic already
and someone that I think
would stop at nothing
to get those tokens
and not sit out of a challenge
and not sit out of a vote.
And we'll get paid
whatever price we want.
♪ ♪
MICHELE:
You do kind of have
vampire features.
-BEN: You have vampire teeth.
-KIM: His teeth.
-And the blue, blue eyes.
-MICHELE: Yeah, you kind of,
like, look like...
-BEN: You-you would make...
-KIM: You could be in Twilight.
-BEN: Yeah, you-you'd make
a good vampire.
-MICHELE: Yeah,
you do look like
a Twilight character.
Did you shape your teeth
like that?
(laughing)
♪ ♪
(chuckling)
Oh, man.
This morning,
I looked in my bag
and I seen something like this
in my bag.
And I know
I didn't put it in there.
So I got to see what it is.
I'm hoping
it's an advantage from the Edge.
So I'm gonna read it right now.
I ran far away from camp,
so nobody knows I'm gone.
And here it is right now.
Oh, my God.
(scoffs)
Oh, my-- First word
I read is "extortion."
This is great.
The first word I saw
that popped out
to me was "extortion."
I'm like, "Yes!
Yes, I'm gonna extort somebody."
'Cause, in real life,
I can't do that.
But I know it sounds like fun.
When I watch in the movies,
the mobsters extort people
for money
or they're gonna break your legs
or they break your kneecaps
if you don't give me this
and that.
So I'm s-- I'm excited.
This is illegal, man.
That's a extremely powerful
advantage,
and I can't wait to use it.
And then I'm reading more
and I'm reading more
and then it says...
"This advantage is playing
on you."
Six tokens?
I'll tell you what, man,
if-if this in real life,
you're doing some prison time.
This is extortion,
Code 2C-something.
I know it's
a criminal code that--
Extortion is illegal
in the States.
I don't know why
it's not illegal here in Fiji.
This is, this is ludicrous.
I got three tokens.
They want six.
I'm being extorted
for six tokens.
That's double of what I have.
And they're saying
if the person cannot come up
with the extortion payment,
they don't get
to play
in the immunity challenge,
so they have no shot
at winning immunity.
And at Tribal, they can't vote.
-(sighs)
-My deadline is
before the immunity challenge.
So if we get tree mail
and it says
it's time for
immunity challenge,
I have to have
the tokens in place,
ready to pay up the vig.
(Ben crows)
-Tree mail.
-Pray, you guys.
-Aw, man.
-(groaning)
All right, you guys ready?
Do we have everybody?
-TONY: Yeah.
-Okay.
DENISE:
"Crazy how losing
a little challenge
"can destroy your game
as a whole.
"This next one
is especially precarious.
I wouldn't touch it
with a ten-foot pole."
TONY:
Denise comes
with the tree mail,
and, sure enough,
it's an immunity challenge.
And I'm like,
"Not only are they extorting me
for fire tokens,
they're also putting
a time limit on it."
-DENISE: Game on.
-TONY: Th-They're like,
"You need to pay
this extortion fee
right before
the immunity challenge."
So I'm like,
"The pressure's on."
So, my plan in my head is
to approach my fake alliance
and tell 'em I'm in trouble
and they need to help me so
I can help them with the vote.
Look.
The demand is six tokens.
So I need help.
I got to talk to J.
Because if I don't get it,
I can't vote with you guys.
MICHELE:
Tony asks me for fire tokens,
and I'm like, "Oh, crap,"
because, in actuality,
I have zero fire tokens left
at this point,
'cause I spent it
on my 50/50 coin.
I just need to borrow.
I-I got--
If I win it,
I'll give it back, you know?
MICHELE:
But I don't want people knowing
about my advantage.
So I have to piece together,
scramble together
some kind of cock-and-bull story
about me using my fire tokens
for an advantage
on Edge of Extinction.
I don't have any tokens.
-I got an advantage that...
-Oh.
...basically, when I get
to the Edge of Extinction,
it gives me an advantage
in the challenge.
-So I don't have an advantage
right now.
-Oh.
-Yeah, yeah. Oh.
-It's when I get over there,
if I get voted out.
-How much did that cost, two?
-Four.
TONY:
And then she comes clean
and says,
"Tony, I spent my tokens
on a advantage."
I said,
"Wow, that's great, Michele.
How much did it cost you?"
She said, "Four fire tokens."
I'm like, "Whoa,
the price of milk just went up."
How-- What's going on here?
I'm getting extorted six tokens.
She just paid four tokens
for an advantage.
I-It's-- I guess it's inflation
on Survivor island.
Inflation just...
(stammers)
I don't know
what Survivor's doing to me
to-- this time around.
Well, if you could talk to him,
'cause I don't want them
-seeing me talk-- All right.
-I'll talk, I'll talk to him.
-I'm-a walk this way.
-Okay. All right.
Hey. (stammers)
Could you imagine that?
-Do you want me to hold it,
so I can show Jeremy?
-Just--
All right.
But don't show nobody.
MICHELE:
He needs the six tokens
by the immunity challenge.
Time is tickin'.
So, he has to pay
six fire tokens?
Oh. (laughing)
JEREMY:
Trust is huge out here.
And Tony trusts me,
and I want him to know
I need him
as much as he needs me.
So I'm willing
to give one fire token.
I would give another one,
but then I'll have zero,
and I don't want to have zero.
All right.
TONY:
Jeremy gave me one fire token.
So now I have four tokens.
I need two more,
because I can't vote if I can't
come up with these six tokens.
So I'm thinking I have to go
to my real alliance members.
-What?
-(shushing)
TONY:
So I go to Nick.
I say, "Nick, I'm in trouble."
He said, "No problem, Tony.
I'll help you."
So then I said, "I need
to talk it over with Ben."
Might not-- Yeah.
Ben's like, "Tony, I got you.
I got your back."
And I have the six on me
right now
to pay the price
for the extortion.
I am loaded.
I am wealthy.
So this is an official payment
for that...
disgusting disadvantage
that somebody sent me.
Come on in, guys!
TONY:
So I'm officially paying
for it.
I will compete
in this immunity challenge.
I will have a vote tonight.
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first, Tony,
take it back.
-(kisses)
-Thank you.
Yeah.
-I miss it already.
-(chuckles)
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna stand on a narrow beam
while balancing a statue
at the end of a long pole.
At regular intervals,
you will move farther away
from the statue, making it
more difficult to balance.
If at any point you fall off
or your statue drops,
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity--
safe from the vote.
In addition, the winner
earns two fire tokens.
Everybody else,
Tribal Council,
where somebody will be voted out
of Survivor: Winners at War.
Draw for spots.
We'll get started. Here we go.
♪ ♪
All right,
everybody step up on your beam.
Get your pole ready.
All right.
I'll count you in.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
Everybody has their pole
on their statue,
and this challenge is on.
♪ ♪
Two things going on:
your feet
on that very narrow beam,
and then that long pole,
trying to balance a statue.
This is all about touch.
Poles in lots
of different spots.
Some people very low,
some in the middle.
It's gonna want to tip.
You're the only thing
keeping it from falling.
Kim, with very little movement,
first casualty
of this challenge.
And we are down to eight.
Like so many
Survivor challenges,
you have such little room
for error.
It's day 28.
You're exhausted.
It's hot.
And if, for one moment,
you lapse,
that little flinch
is all it takes
to drop that statue
and, with it,
your shot at security tonight
at Tribal Council.
15 seconds,
we will move farther away
from that statue.
Three, two, one.
Everybody's good.
You can relax.
Well done.
All right, everybody
has moved back on the beam.
You're now gonna have
to balance that statue again.
If you knock it off
during this transition,
you're out.
Everybody lift your poles.
Three, two, one.
Everybody make the transition
to this last section.
Denise drops.
Michele can't do it.
Both out.
It's a live transition.
You are a long ways away
from that statue.
That pole is heavy.
Sarah drops.
Everything just got
very difficult.
We're down to five,
just like that.
Tony, Nick, Ben,
Sophie and Jeremy
fighting for immunity.
(creaking)
Jeremy looking very solid.
Tony with a little movement now.
The longer you're in this,
the harder it is
to keep your concentration.
You cannot relax.
Nick is out.
No shot at immunity.
We're down to four.
Sophie.
Sophie loses her balance,
loses her statue,
loses her shot at immunity.
Sophie's out.
We're down to three men:
Tony, Ben and Jeremy.
28 days into this game.
$2 million prize on the line.
That's a life-changer.
♪ ♪
We'll go until it's over.
Now it's Jeremy with movement.
Been up there 32 minutes.
Longest we have ever gone
in this challenge.
Everybody fighting
to stay in it.
Ben with a nice save.
Ben can no longer do it.
Ben is out.
-We're down to two.
Jeremy drops!
-SARAH: Oh, my gosh, Tony.
-Tony wins...
-Ah, come on, man.
-...his second
individual immunity!
-Oh, man.
-What the hell? Whoa.
-Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Safe again at Tribal Council.
Two more fire tokens
coming his way.
Dramatic finish.
-Tony, come on over.
-Oh, man.
-The second time in a row.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Go from nothing...
-Thank you so much.
-...to dominating.
-Thank you.
-D-Don't say that, man.
-(laughter)
Tony, once again,
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
In addition, two fire tokens.
Cannot be voted
out of this game.
As for the rest of you,
you know the drill.
28 days,
somebody going home tonight,
will be sent to the Edge,
where you will wait for your
shot to get back in this game.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
Congrats.
Thank you, man. Oh, my God.
This is perfect.
I won two fire tokens.
I can pay my debt.
And had I not played
that immunity challenge,
Jeremy would have won
that necklace.
So, what's happening today is
we're gonna be
voting for Jeremy.
I'm loving it.
♪ ♪
(Tony crows)
KIM:
I didn't want
Tony to win today.
-Oh, my God. That's amazing.
-(laughs) Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
KIM:
But Tony winning two in a row
back-to-back is not bad.
It puts a target
on Tony's back.
So, yay for Tony.
TONY:
J, get out of here, man.
I'm not even giving you
a hug, man.
KIM:
Tony is completely
playing Jeremy,
and I clearly know about it.
But at this point in the game,
I don't have the numbers
on the Jeremy side.
Jeremy has Michele,
and that's it.
-JEREMY: Yeah, yeah.
-KIM: My only option
is to go back
with this other group,
who I don't really
trust anyway.
It's a precarious position.
It's not my favorite.
Who are we voting out,
so it's not extreme chaos?
-Jeremy.
-SARAH: For sure? For sure?
-Yeah.
SARAH:
Okay, so do we want
to throw votes
-at Michele, too?
-BEN: Yes.
-Yeah.
-SOPHIE: Just in case,
we have to.
Okay. Let's get two votes
thrown at Michele.
-Okay.
-You and I write Michele.
-And then everybody else
on Jeremy.
-NICK: So I vote Jeremy.
-Yeah.
-SARAH: And then
we send Michele home
if Jeremy plays something.
-That's fine.
-SOPHIE: Going into tonight,
I have the idol in my pocket.
But I know there have to be
oth-other idols floating around.
BEN:
Okay, cool.
We'll just come home
-and make a big old
fat pot of rice.
-SARAH: Yeah.
SOPHIE:
We have enough people
to split the vote,
so, yes, Jeremy will go home,
but Michele will get
a couple of votes
just in case
Jeremy plays an idol.
-Hey, family.
-Hey.
Meet you around the water well.
-I can feel...
-You need water?
-I do because...
-So what are we,
what are we thinking?
-What are we thinking?
-They're each-- I'll ask you.
They're coming after me.
You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-So, like, I...
Okay. 'Cause I think
if we ask-- Yeah.
-I'm down to do it.
-Then let's do it.
-Okay.
DENISE:
I feel like I'm playing
double agent,
because on the one hand,
I'm working with Jeremy,
Kim, Michele and Tony
to vote out Ben.
That's not really my plan.
-So, we got us three,
Michele and Tony.
-Yeah.
-For sure Tony. Okay.
-For sure Tony.
-Tony is for sure-- 100%.
-100%.
-Okay.
-We have to trust each other.
-Mm-hmm.
-And do this.
-It's all we have.
-That's all we have.
DENISE:
I've tried to save Jeremy
in the past,
but I think it's time.
-Let's don't overcomplicate it.
-All right, yeah.
DENISE:
Kim and I are both in
cahoots together
to blindside Jeremy tonight.
-Okay.
-All right?
-Okay?
-Okay.
JEREMY:
At the start of this game,
I was like, "You know what?
I like Ben.
He's a good guy.
That's my friend."
And now, like,
everything he does annoys me.
Like, every little thing
he does bothers me.
The dude-- he doesn't
want to work with me.
He doesn't want to play with me.
MICHELE:
Do you guys need the stir stick?
-No.
-JEREMY: And Denise and Kim
would love to see Ben go.
So, my intended target
right now is Ben.
I'm... I am tight on it.
I am tight on it.
All five of us are in.
-Great.
-All right?
It's crazy how much
things cost now.
I know. I know.
-It's crazy
how quick a million goes.
-I know.
TONY:
Everybody's very calm
and cool and quiet,
and they're tired of all
the talking, the chattering.
Like, "Guys, we're solid.
Let's just stop talking."
If they want to stop or slow
down, that's better for me,
because I'm not stopping
or slowing down.
I'm always thinking
when they're not.
I have the immunity necklace,
so I'm safe for tonight.
I've been patient long enough.
Now I have an opportunity
to flip-flop.
It's time for me
to blindside somebody.
And Sophie is getting too close
to my partner, Sarah.
So, I'm thinking
my target should be Sophie.
Because my real alliance
is splitting the votes,
that creates
a huge opportunity for me,
because you don't need
that many numbers.
Jeremy and Michele
don't have a choice.
Once I tell them a name,
they're gonna go for it.
So all I need is Nick.
But I'm just watching the sun,
as it's starting to set.
I want to hit them, like,
maybe minutes before
we have to go to Tribal.
-Yeah.
-You have Kim and Sarah--
-those two...
-Oh, they're splitting.
...are voting for Michele.
And then you have
Sophie, Ben and Denise
voting for Jeremy.
-Yeah.
-So, if me and you
tell Jeremy and Michele,
"Yo, guys,
me and Nick are gonna save you.
You owe us."
-Mm-hmm.
"We're gonna vote for Sophie.
You two, vote for Sophie."
We got the numbers.
We get Sophie out, blindside.
-Tonight?
-Yeah.
Would you be willing
to make that move?
-It's tough.
-Yeah.
-I'll do it.
-That's it?
-Yeah, I'll do it.
-Oh, wow.
TONY:
Me, Jeremy, Nick, Michele.
'Cause that four is stronger
than their three and their two.
So, I'm gonna be golden
if I can pull this off.
All right.
Kim and Sarah
are voting for Michele.
Everybody else,
including me and Nick,
were supposed to vote for you.
Okay?
So now I'm taking Nick
away from their numbers,
I'm taking myself away
from their numbers,
and I'm giving them to you.
It's that simple.
I prom-- Listen to me.
Why?
Because they were gonna
blindside you, kid.
-Who's they?
-Everybody.
Everybody.
JEREMY:
Tony comes to me late with
a plan to take out Sophie.
And I'm like,
"Come on, we have a plan."
Like, I didn't want to do
anything different.
I want Ben gone.
And then he said, "Listen,
Kim and Denise aren't with you.
You got to just
trust me on this."
And the first thing
I thought was,
"No, Tony, you're wrong,
you're wrong."
So...
I really don't know
if people are coming after me.
I don't know.
TONY:
Can you please trust me
and believe me?
I know you, I know you want me
to give you a lengthy answer
right now, kid, and I'm telling
you the specifics of it,
but I can't sit here too long
because they're gonna know
I'm trying to blow them up.
Oh, man.
Jeremy doesn't believe me.
J, please believe me, kid.
JEREMY:
Did you already talk
to Michele?
TONY:
No, I didn't talk to her.
You have to tell her.
-Oh, my God.
-'Cause I-I don't
want to be seen.
Just tell her, last minute, say,
"Put down Sophie. Trust me."
-Please believe me on this one.
-Oh, man.
TONY:
I can't believe it.
Jeremy's reluctant.
I'm trying to save him.
I'm begging him to save him.
"Jeremy, this is
your only opportunity
"to stay in the game.
"I'm telling you,
Kim and Denise jumped ship.
"They are coming after you.
"If you don't believe that,
"and you want to go
with your plan
and vote Ben,
you'll be going home tonight."
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Sophie,
last Tribal, two advantages
and an idol played.
How unnerving is that when
you go back to camp realizing
people are using their weapons?
SOPHIE:
I think it was a kick
in the pants to everybody
that you can never
go into Tribal
thinking that you know the plan,
because nobody's telling each
other about these advantages.
They were all popping up
out of nowhere.
And I think it just put
everybody even more on edge,
you know, this Tribal Council.
PROBST:
Ben, it's a reminder
that there are land mines,
and you just don't know
where they are.
BEN:
Yeah. Last Tribal,
I had no clue about
either advantages or the idol,
and so I think the seriousness
from everybody right now is just
waiting for
that nother bomb to drop,
because not all the information
is being shared at all times.
JEREMY:
Jeff, I feel like everybody is
telling half-truths.
-Always.
And, uh, you just
have to pick through
who you trust more than others.
PROBST:
So, Sarah,
when you have people
who have all won the game,
they each have
their own approach
to how you make a move
that might be a blindside
but can still allow you
to use it on your résumé.
SARAH:
Right. And that's what people
are trying to do
is they're trying to start
building their résumés.
They're trying to make
flashy moves and do things
to win favor because
they want to win the $2 million.
PROBST:
Nick, are there moves
where you wouldn't want credit,
even though it was a great move,
because it's just
such a big move
that that one might backfire?
NICK:
I think that can
definitely happen,
especially depending on
who's in on the move,
who's left out of the move.
Or you could just claim it
and become a bigger target,
and hopefully
it doesn't backfire,
and then you make it to day 39,
and you can claim
this great résumé.
It's a paradox,
one of the biggest ones
in Survivor, for sure.
PROBST:
Sophie, it's like you're on
one of those lazy Susans and
you're just constantly spinning.
This game gets you
no matter where you are.
If you make a big move
and you want credit for it,
somebody's mad.
If you make a big move and
you don't take credit for it,
-you don't have a résumé.
-SOPHIE: Totally.
I think we talk a lot
about résumés out here,
but nobody wants a résumé
that's, like, super, super long
but doesn't have
any quality to it.
You don't want to be like
that annoying girl in school
who's in Girl Scout
and debate and mathletes
and, like, volunteers
after school.
Like, it's just very obvious
that you're padding your résumé
for no reason.
So I think the hardest thing
out here is figuring out,
"Is this really a move
that makes sense for me,
or am I just trying
to tick something off?"
JEREMY:
It's also timing.
If you want to make
a-a good move,
you got to make sure
you're not making it too early,
because you can't
beat anybody at the end
if you don't get to the end.
PROBST:
Is that why you left
at the last Tribal?
Listen, I did my detective work.
I took a page out of
Tony and-and Sarah's book.
And it came to
my realization that
if I didn't play that advantage,
I would be sitting
in Tyson's seat right now.
PROBST:
So, how comfortable
are you tonight?
I'm not comfortable at all.
It was real quiet today,
and that's not
a comfortable feeling.
Ben, how fast can you tell
when the tone or the mood
around you changes?
Like Jeremy says,
it was real quiet today.
It was also quiet
around me today.
-Unusual?
-Uh, very unusual.
And very uneasy.
Michele, quiet or busy?
Very quiet today as well. Yes.
I got told a plan,
and instead of running around,
scrambling like
a crazy person, I'm like,
"All right, let's-let's move
forward with that vote."
So, Sophie,
-unusually quiet
for you as well?
-SOPHIE: Oh, yeah.
It was a really quiet afternoon.
Um, and I-- uh, my feeling is
that's because
every single person sitting here
is probably feeling
comfortable tonight.
So, it's a weird war tonight.
TONY:
And-and the-the reason,
too, Jeff,
is the last Tribal Council
we had was a bit hectic.
Everybody was mentally
exhausted, physically exhausted.
So, we put a plan in motion,
and we were like,
"Okay, let's just stick to it."
And that's what happened today.
Everybody: "Are we good?
Are we good?
Are we good? Are we good?"
Everybody said,
"Yes, yes, yes, yes,"
and we took it easy for today.
PROBST:
Sarah, what's brilliant
about that is that the game
level is so high that you've now
convinced each other
that everybody's good.
SARAH:
Yeah. I mean, it's like
mass psychological warfare
going on.
But I feel like
everybody sitting here
is smart enough to catch on,
so if you continue
to do things the same way,
they'll pick up on stuff.
So, you got to change it up
for the next Tribal Council.
PROBST:
So, Sarah,
what is the feeling when you
pull off a masterful blindside?
I mean, in a season with
all winners sitting here,
who's the best player out here?
And when you pull off
a blindside on someone
and it was your blindside,
I mean, it's a sense of pride
and-and you feel good like,
"Am I the best?
That move says I'm the best."
PROBST:
All right.
It is time to vote.
Michele, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has a hidden immunity
idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay. I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Jeremy.
Michele.
Michele. We're tied.
Two votes Jeremy,
two votes Michele.
Jeremy.
That's three votes Jeremy.
Sophie.
That's three votes Jeremy,
two votes Michele,
two votes Sophie.
Sophie.
That's three votes Sophie,
three votes Jeremy,
two votes Michele.
One vote left.
13th person voted out of
Survivor: Winners at War...
-No.
-...Sophie.
Need to bring me your torch.
Oh.
-SOPHIE: (groans) Damn it.
-(Sarah groans)
I don't know how I do this.
(chuckles)
(laughs):
Clumsy at this.
-Sophie, the tribe has spoken.
-Okay.
Good job, guys.
I did not see it coming.
We love you, Soph.
SOPHIE:
Need to take the idol
out of my crotch now.
Boom.
(exhaling sharply)
Four votes.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
PROBST: Survivor's
looking for new players.
It could be you. Apply now.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
JEREMY:
This is the part of the war
that's gonna get really ugly.
-You just sunk my game!
-No.
I'm done!
I'm absolutely infuriated
with him.
TONY:
My spying has evolved,
and now I'm up in the air.
It's called the spy nest.
This is by far the riskiest move
I've ever had to make.
SOPHIE: I've never been
blindsided before.
I think it's
a traumatic experience.
-PARVATI: Sophie.
-Hey.
-Aw.
-Hey, girl.
SOPHIE:
I played as best as I could,
and it's a bummer to go out
with an idol in your pocket.
Hey. I'm sad. (sobs)
I probably came into
this game feeling like
I was a bottom-tier winner,
and it's been fun
realizing that I can
hold my own.
(roars)