-♪ ♪
-(thunder cracking)
SHAN: Coming back from Tribal
was not a good feeling.
It obviously did come down
to Genie and Ricard.
She seemed shocked.
Yeah, 'cause I was...
told her I was with her.
You know? What else was I going
to tell her?
It was the hardest one for me
'cause I really wanted
you, me and Genie.
Genie calls me back to
who I am in real life, you know?
I'm a pastor. My heart's already
wide open for people,
but in this game, I need, like,
a Ricard to pull me,
you know,
to the gamer side of things,
the strategic side of things.
SHAN:
But at the same time,
I am worried about Ricard.
Part of me feels like
I can't really trust him
completely with his word.
...and say, "You give me this
vote back for me to trust you."
That is ... up.
So the extra vote--
it's kind of become
a complicated little thing
between Shan and myself.
When Shan opened
the Beware Advantage
and lost her vote,
she gave me her extra vote
to vote out Genie.
Okay.
RICARD:
Then she got nervous
and asked for it back
right before Tribal.
Could you give me my advantage?
No, I'm not.
I just want insurance.
RICARD:
You really don't believe me?
You said
you'd give it back to me.
If you're saying
you're not going to, then...
I am going to give it
back to you tomorrow.
Which was really bothersome
to me.
But I could have opened
that damn idol, too.
-But I didn't.
-Okay. So then why didn't you?
You wanted all the power
in your hands so that you...
What did you risk?
I could have been voted out.
I risked my vote.
I had no guarantee
that you were voting with me
if I gave you that advantage.
Brad didn't want you around.
I was the one that pivoted
in that conversation and got you
in on that connection.
When JD wanted to blindside you,
I was the one
that was, like,
pulling you in on that.
When Genie wanted you out,
I was the one
that pulled you in on that.
RICARD: Ever since
Shan got the extra vote,
she's felt very attached to it,
and we're supposed to be a team.
She already got the hidden
immunity idol that was Genie's.
And so now she would have
two advantages in this game.
I do, because
I feel a little bit of, like,
something
because you said you would,
and then you held it.
If we're in it together,
it really doesn't matter,
but I'm not... like,
I'm not fighting you on it.
-Mm-hmm.
-I just don't see
why it matters.
Shan asked me again if she could
have the extra vote back.
For her to have an active idol,
an extra advantage,
plus her paranoia?
It's just too much.
The way you're approaching me...
Instead of being like,
"Oh, hey, can I have it?"
You literally just could have
come in and been like,
"Oh, you promised to give it
back. Can I have it back?"
-But if you... but if you...
-I shouldn't have to be on,
-like, some tight schedule of...
-If you would have offered it
last night, I would've been
like, "Oh, thank you."
Ricard's been my number one
since day one.
If you feel like you're with me,
you should feel safe, you know?
You know, you gave me your word
about something,
and then you went against it.
It doesn't sit right with me.
I'm just saying, I feel like
you don't trust me fully.
No, no, it's not
about me not trusting you.
It's just, I want to go into
the merge without me feeling
like, "Ricard gave me his word,
and then he didn't."
I don't want that in my mind.
I don't want that
in my mind at all.
Then put it out of your mind.
I'm going to when you give me
the advantage back.
-Then, fine.
-Okay, it's out of my mind.
I still think
it's questionable on your part.
SHAN:
Moving forward with Ricard,
you know, I...
I trust him... ish.
Next advantage we find,
next idol we find is yours.
Thank you for giving me
permission to have it.
Like with everything
in this game so far with Shan,
I'm just going
to drop it and move on.
But from here on out, but
I have to do what's best for me.
EVVIE:
I don't know.
Okay, everybody put some energy,
put some food energy into this.
Please let it be some sort
of sustenance.
-Food, food, food, food.
-Okay, Evvie, do the honors.
-All right, all right,
all right, all right.
-Me?
Okay, I'll do the honors.
(gasps)
(screaming)
-Ooh!
-Ah.
EVVIE:
Yes!
-(Liana screams)
-We did it!
XANDER: It sounds like
it's going to be a merge,
but everything right now is
set up perfect for that.
-We did it!
-We did it.
-BOTH: We did it. We did it.
-This is Evvie's little dance.
-We did it. We did it.
-This is what I'm talking about.
-Go, go, go, go.
-Go, go.
-Go.
XANDER:
We've gotten
to be a really close four,
and we're locked solid.
-Look at us now.
Look at us now.
-Yeah.
XANDER:
You get so excited,
thinking, "Maybe this could be
"my Survivor story,
"and that this ragtag group
of people could
totally shake up
the post-merge game."
Yase Four, established day five.
-LIANA: Yase Four.
-TIFFANY: Yup.
All right, let's go,
let's do it.
LIANA:
I think, amongst the women,
there's a really,
like, solid form of trust.
So much so that we're putting on
this kind of, like, facade
to keep Xander
in a certain place.
But in the back of my mind,
I'm always thinking,
Xander on my tribe is
still a huge threat.
He has all of these advantages
in the game.
LIANA:
But Xander's overconfident.
He feels so comfortable with me,
he doesn't see me as a threat.
And so, I'm chomping at the bit
to, like,
just flip the narrative.
DANNY: Bring all the stuff with
you, personal items? Sounds like
-a merge with this.
-(whooping, cheering)
-SYDNEY: Sounds good, but...
-ERIKA: I still don't
trust him. I'm excited,
but I still don't trust him.
-NASEER: Unify as...?
-DANNY: Unify as one?
I'm skeptical.
I don't know.
I feel like
nothing's come this easy so far.
I think a lot of people would be
jealous to be in our position,
having been the winning tribe,
but it comes with its own set
of difficulties.
We don't have
solidified alliances
because we've never gone
to Tribal Council.
DESHAWN:
Yes. I think
it might just make
the most sense
for everybody strategically
to just, like,
at least for the first couple
votes, just vote together.
Keeping this tribe Luvu Six
is damn near impossible.
Are there cracks?
The tribe is shattered.
Basically, Luvu Six is
dissipating. I'm just trying
to keep the pieces together
for one vote.
But if I can't,
we're going to be screwed.
♪ ♪
Time to bring you in
on another big twist.
So big, this is a two-part
episode, so no Tribal tonight.
Nobody going home.
All right, it's day 12.
The tribes already know we're
going to merge from tree mail.
But this is 41,
where they've already learned
that nothing is easy.
What they're about
to find out is
that even when you earn it,
nothing is guaranteed.
So here's what's going
to happen.
It's the biggest twist so far.
Here they come.
We're going to run a big
challenge, and when it's over,
a group are going to believe
they're safe.
But they're going to be forced
to send one player away,
which is always dangerous,
and in doing so,
they will unknowingly
give that player
a historic amount of power.
And the question' going to be,
what will the player do
with that power?
This one may ruffle
some feathers.
Come on in.
Getting your first look
at the new Ua tribe.
Genie voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, well, as you know
from tree mail,
we are entering the next stage
of the game.
Tribes are no longer.
You are now
in the individual portion
of Survivor.
Everybody drop your Buffs.
-(whooping)
-Yes! Oh, my God, yes!
-Ah.
-You are...
ALL:
Merged!
DESHAWN:
Cool.
Ah...
(all clamoring)
-Not exactly.
-LIANA: Oh!
-Damn it!
-Oh, God, he's killing me.
PROBST:
May be better to say
you're not merged.
In fact, for the moment, you are
without a Buff
and without a tribe.
Like every other thing
so far in this game,
you are going to earn your way
into the merge.
Here's how it's going to work.
We're going to draw
for two teams.
On my go, you're going
to dig up a massive boulder
and push it through
a series of obstacles,
retrieving keys along the way.
When you get to the end,
you'll climb
to the top of the tower,
use those keys
to unlock the Survivor
word puzzle.
First team to finish earns
their first proper meal
in 12 days.
Plus, you earn a Buff--
the merge Buff--
and you will not have
to participate
in the first
individual immunity challenge.
You'll be safe.
The losing team--
no proper meal, no Buff,
and you will have to participate
in that challenge
to be safe at Tribal.
And to be clear, everybody will
still vote at Tribal Council.
And there's one more layer
to this twist.
Two players will draw
gray rocks.
You will not participate
on either team.
You will not run
in the challenge.
Your fate will be decided
by the winning team.
A Survivor player's journey
often comes down to a
moment, and sometimes the
moment starts with luck of the
draw.
Let's draw.
Two players will draw
gray rocks.
You will not participate
on either team.
You will not run
in the challenge.
Your fate will be decided
by the winning team.
Let's draw.
Everybody reveal.
Who has the gray rocks?
Naseer has a gray,
Erika has a gray.
You two will not participate.
If you have yellow,
go to yellow.
If you have blue, go to blue.
If you have gray,
go in the middle on green.
Game just took another turn.
We've got Naseer and Erika
in the middle,
and we have two teams of five.
For yellow, we have
Xander, Heather, Liana,
Tiffany and Shan.
On the other team,
we have Danny, Ricard,
Sydney, Deshawn and Evvie.
Liana, where are we in the game?
This is another new twist.
You don't just waltz
into the merge.
You got to earn the merge.
Yeah, it's-it's really real,
Jeff. (laughs)
I'm super hungry right now,
and when Liana's hungry,
she's feisty,
so I want to win this.
All right, Naseer
and Erika will watch.
Everybody else, give you
a minute to strategize,
we'll get started.
Here we go for food,
Buff and immunity
at that first Tribal Council.
Big stakes.
Survivors ready.
Go!
(grunting)
Your first job is
to work together to dig up
a very big
and very heavy boulder.
You got this!
(sighs)
It looks like
there is a big
physical advantage for blue,
but that remains
to be seen right now.
(grunting)
These are big holes
you are digging
-to get a big boulder out.
-(grunting)
You're just looking
for that moment
where you can wedge the ball
out of the hole.
This gives new meaning
to one of my favorite phrases.
"You got to dig deep."
-(grunting)
-♪ ♪
Both teams got
to be getting very close now.
Got it. One, two, three, go.
PROBST:
Yellow now going to try to push.
Can they get it to move?
(grunting)
-It's close to moving.
-(muttering)
-Just a little shy.
-Go. Come on. Go!
Come on, guys. Keep digging.
Blue gonna give it
an official go now.
-SYDNEY: One. Two.
-EVVIE: Count it out.
Three. Oh, there you go.
-Go, go, go.
-Go.
And they are out of the hole.
-Good job, blue.
-♪ ♪
Blue is now in the lead,
pushing that Earth-like globe
-onto the course.
-DESHAWN: This way.
-SYDNEY: Go this way.
-And you can see the momentum
-kick in.
-Push!
-(grunting)
-Good job, y'all.
Right side.
Now blue
at their first key station.
-DESHAWN:
Step in the back, though.
-I got it.
You got to hold that ball
and get
somebody up on top of the ball.
-SYDNEY: Nice, dude.
-PROBST: They're putting
the biggest guy up on the ball.
Also,
probably the most athletic.
EVVIE:
You got this, Danny.
-Nice.
-Danny has the first key.
Got to get down.
You're on the move, blue.
EVVIE:
All right, we're good.
We're good.
Let's go, yellow! Keep going!
-Let's go, guys! Come on!
-ERIKA: Keep digging, yellow!
Keep digging!
PROBST:
We've got blue going
-for their second key.
-This side!
Yellow trying
to get some momentum.
-(grunting)
-Can they get it out
of that hole?
-(grunting)
-Ah, let's go...
(indistinct,
overlapping chatter)
PROBST:
Yeah!
That's how you do it!
-Keep digging!
-We're not letting it fall.
I'm not letting it fall!
-(grunting)
-PROBST: You're out!
You're in this.
Yellow is not giving up.
-Roll the ball! Roll the ball!
-They are in this challenge.
We've got blue going
for their second key.
-Nice.
-Doing good. Good job.
PROBST:
Yellow going for their first.
-(grunting)
-(indistinct chatter)
-Roll the ball.
-Sure enough here,
all ten players
in the game right now.
Nobody's giving up.
-NASEER: That's right, yellow!
-PROBST: You got it.
Keep moving, yellow.
Keep moving.
Danny with the second key
for blue.
-They've got a big lead.
-(indistinct chatter)
Closer to that meal,
that Buff and immunity.
Blue now got to get up
to that tower
using only the ball
and each other.
-I got it. I got it.
-NASEER: "Evie."
-Nicely done, Evie.
-Good job, Evvie.
Good job, Evvie.
-It's "Evvie"?
-Evvie.
-Nice one, Evvie!
-Good job, Evvie!
And here comes yellow.
Keep moving! Push!
You never know
when there is a word puzzle,
how long it will take
the other group.
Push that ball!
-Here goes Ricard!
-(grunting)
Look at that human ladder!
-Yeah, let's go.
-Danny, Deshawn and Ricard.
That is how you do it in this
challenge, but they are up.
Now it's a human ladder
to get to the top.
-Let's go.
-(grunting)
Sydney goes up
on Danny's shoulders.
(grunts)
Got it, got it, got it.
-(grunting)
-Got it. One, two, three. Go.
-Keep going! You're in it.
-Keep going...
PROBST:
Yellow, still fighting.
Exhausted but still in it.
Come on, yellow!
Keep moving! Get that ball back!
You got to get that second...
-Slow it down. Slow it down.
-This way?
-Catch, catch, catch.
-PROBST: There goes Deshawn.
-He's gonna give it a go.
-(grunting)
Holding on by his fingertips.
That'll do it.
-SYDNEY: You got this.
-Now Danny on his own,
gonna have to scale this wall.
-And he's got it.
-Yeah, Danny.
Wow. Made it look easy.
Puzzle, puzzle, puzzle.
PROBST: All right, on the mat.
Two people on the puzzle.
Got to unlock it.
Flip that center piece
and start sliding pieces.
Two different stories.
-One team trying
to solve the puzzle.
-Yeah.
The other team just trying
to get up here.
-More.
-You got it.
Tiffany, go, baby.
Yes. (grunts)
-Go, go, go, go!
-Tiff, come on!
Blue continuing to move
one piece at a time.
-Uh, tribe.
-Merge, merge, merge.
Merge, merge, merge.
Merge, merge.
Getting closer and closer.
Pull, pull!
Hold, Xander. Come on.
-Yellow has four people up.
-Come on, Xander.
-Let's go... We got it.
-PROBST: Look at that. No quit!
-That's it!
-Go, go, go, go, go.
Let's go! Start
that human ladder right now.
-Right here, right here!
-PROBST: Yellow, you are still
in this challenge.
Here goes Liana.
Can she pull herself up?
Very little strength left
in that body,
-but she is using all of it.
-TIFFANY: You got it, baby.
-Struggling.
-I got you, baby. I got you.
PROBST:
Holding on to anything.
Look at that effort!
Nice job.
-Nice, Liana.
-Nice work.
Keep put...
moving 'em all down.
Move 'em all down.
PROBST:
Blue's struggling now.
-Yes, yes, yes!
-(indistinct chatter)
-RICARD: Yeah, it all goes here.
-PROBST: Yellow now in this.
Here comes Heather.
She's gonna need a hand.
-Come on.
-You ready?
-(grunting)
-(indistinct shouting)
-SHAN: Come on, Heather.
-(Heather groans)
-Come on, Heather.
-We are not letting you go.
-You got this.
-Give her a push, Shan!
Come on, Heather!
-Come on, Heather!
-Pull!
-Go, go, go!
Look at that.
One of the most amazing displays
of teamwork
in the history of this game.
Here comes Shan.
Shan is up. Xander, get up here.
You could be back in this.
Xander gonna give it a run.
Let's go.
Time is ticking.
Hold me. Hold me. Shan, hold me.
-Nice!
-Come on. Come on.
-Xander's got it!
-(groans)
-Get on the puzzle. Let's go.
-(groaning)
Suddenly, we got a challenge.
-Wait, wait...
-No, A, A, A.
-No, A's first.
-PROBST:
Blue had the early lead.
But I think that lead is gone.
It would be a huge comeback if
yellow came back and won this.
(indistinct chatter)
Anything is possible
on Survivor.
-EVVIE: You got this, dude.
-PROBST: This could
come down to seconds
and a few pieces.
I know. This is gonna look
weird. Give me a second.
-You got it. You got it.
Suddenly blue is moving quickly.
Yes, you're so right.
You're totally right.
Wait. No, no, no, we want...
It's not...
We're not...
not going backwards.
Is it "Merge Feast"?
Now it's yellow
who's slowing down.
-Amazing, bro.
-You're right, Ric.
PROBST:
You could not ask for more
on day 12 of Survivor 41.
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Amazing, bro.
-Wait. Oh, that's good.
-Bring it down.
-Yes. Jeff?
-Jeff.
Blue thinks they have it.
Say it!
-ALL: Merge Feast!
-That's it!
-Yes!
-Blue wins the first meal
of the season.
Congrats, guys!
A tribe merge Buff and immunity
at that first
individual challenge.
And what a huge effort
by yellow to get back in this.
(indistinct chatter)
Danny, Evvie,
Ricard, Deshawn, Sydney,
boat's going to take you
to the sanctuary.
Beautiful spot where
you will have a proper meal,
plus tribe Buffs,
the merge Buff.
Ooh...
And you don't have to compete
in that first individual
immunity challenge.
You are safe
at that first Tribal Council.
Before you head out,
a very big decision to make.
You are going to choose either
Naseer or Erika to join you.
The person you choose
to join you--
for them, it will be
as if they won--
food, Buff and immunity.
A very big strategic decision
because that is a gift.
For the other person,
they'll be taken
to a separate island,
where they will live alone
for two days,
two nights, no proper meal,
no Buff, no immunity,
no company, no shelter.
So for very different reasons,
also a strategic decision,
so talk about it.
Big decision.
One person gets a gift,
one person gets sent away,
which is always dangerous.
All right, before you tell me,
what was the thought process
for your decision?
Paper, rock, scissors.
PROBST:
Really?
It's our tribemates, and,
you know, it's hard to choose,
-and, uh...
-So rock, paper, scissor?
Yup.
PROBST:
Okay.
So, blue, who is going
to join you for the Merge Feast?
Uh, Naseer.
-(whoops)
-PROBST: Naseer, come on over.
Guys. I love you guys.
-Sorry, E.
-It's okay.
PROBST:
All right, you six gonna have
a great afternoon together.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Boat'll take you
to the sanctuary.
Enjoy.
-DESHAWN: Good luck. You got it.
-Good luck, guys.
PROBST:
Xander, Liana, Tiffany,
Shan, Heather,
consolation prize?
You'll have a little bit of rice
waiting for you back at camp,
enough for the day.
You're heading to Luvu tribe.
This will be your merge home.
Grab your stuff, head out.
The game continues.
Enjoy, guys.
Have a good day.
-Thank you. We will.
-Sorry, Erika.
-We got you.
-I'll be okay. I'll be okay.
I'll be okay.
Erika,
how you feeling right now?
You're left behind.
Yeah, I mean, I had suspicions
that I was at the bottom.
Maybe this just proved it.
I honestly thought that
when the choice was
between Naseer and I, like,
I was dead in the water.
So maybe the rock, paper,
scissors was, you know,
like, a nice cover
to not hurt my feelings,
but I never expected
to join the feast.
Well, Erika,
there is no denying it.
Your game just took
a dramatic turn.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Boat will take you
to the island
where you will spend two days
and two nights alone.
Good luck.
ERIKA:
Hearing I was going to be alone
on an island
is honestly a nightmare.
My first 12 days
on Survivor is not
what I thought was going
to happen.
I didn't expect
to have moments where
I was perfectly safe
and feel so powerless.
I didn't expect to be exiled
for two days, but, like,
as long as I get it done
and I do it,
that's what matters.
EVVIE:
I'm a huge fan of Survivor,
and there has never
been anything like this.
Only the winners
of the challenge
officially make the merge
and get a Merge Feast.
Losing the challenge
and not getting the feast?
That's got to be heartbreaking,
absolutely heartbreaking.
-EVVIE: Oh, my God.
-(whooping)
EVVIE:
Winning this challenge is huge.
It means
I officially made the merge,
it means I have immunity for
the first vote after the merge,
and most importantly,
it means I get to eat.
-Who wants a beer?
-DANNY: I do.
(indistinct chatter)
EVVIE:
I've seen every season
of Survivor,
and I really, really,
really believe
that this is one
of the hardest ever. Like,
it cannot be overstated what
not having rice means. Like,
there are many days, where I ate
literally zero calories.
Zero calories.
Yo, real talk? We,
the last three days,
ate nothing.
Like, nothing nothing.
EVVIE:
Yeah.
It is probably the
toughest thing I've ever done.
-Yeah.
-NASEER: It's a great day
for me.
This is what I got.
This is, like...
I feel like my... the individual
immunity is around my neck
for the first challenge, so...
Smells really good,
and I love the color.
You guys think
Erika's gonna be okay?
-DESHAWN: I hope so.
-I hope so.
-DANNY: I really hope so.
-That is a rough punishment.
-Yeah...
-But she's, like,
super happy-go-lucky.
-Is she?
-You think she...?
-DESHAWN: She's gonna
make the best of it.
NASEER:
And also I have
a hidden immunity idol
in my pocket,
so I feel like I'm doing
really good in this game now.
(whoops, laughs)
First Tribal Council,
I'm not going home anymore.
SYDNEY (laughing):
Yeah.
Now I get to feast.
RICARD:
Do we...? Do you like Erika?
EVVIE:
Yeah, I was gonna ask.
-RICARD: Okay.
-DANNY: We hadn't really got
a chance to play the game,
so it's been,
like, true harmony
in the... in the tribe. Like...
I do feel bad for Erika
that she's out there
for two days alone, but
we didn't want
to send Naseer because
the real situation is,
a lot of the men were voted out.
But nobody really wanted to
explain why we chose Naseer, so,
first thing that popped
in my head
from old Survivor seasons was
paper, rock, scissors.
EVVIE:
Huh?
You got it right.
I'm still worried. (laughs)
We assumed
you would be afraid.
DANNY:
I thought it was pretty obvious
that the women were kind of
knocking the men out
on the other tribe.
So it was really,
really important for us
to keep the men's numbers up.
So we needed
to keep Naseer safe.
The truth is, a woman
definitely has to go home,
and I think
Erika makes 100% the most sense.
Okay.
Of the things that I absolutely
did not want to happen to me
on Survivor, number one
on the list was "Be alone
on a beach for one night,"
and it is happening times two.
Oh, yeah,
Jeff wasn't messing around.
I really don't get a lot.
Being alone
for that amount of time
almost seems scarier than
not being in the game
for two days.
What's in here? Okay.
Okay. We have some rice
on the menu.
This one looks promising.
Oh, it's water.
Okay.
It just felt so daunting.
I immediately had the fear
of like,
am I going to, like,
literally survive?
Am I going to be
able to stay alive?
I didn't come into Survivor
with a lot of outdoor skills.
And the person least equipped
to be outside is me.
But I've been used
to, like, things never coming
easy for me in life. Like,
growing up in Canada,
like, always looking different
than the other kids
and knowing, like, how
many challenges my parents had
in trying to, like,
give us a good life.
Coming from the Philippines
to Canada,
working so many jobs
to, like, keep us going.
I know that, like,
it probably hurts them that
they didn't have as much, like,
time with us, like, growing up
as they would have wanted to.
But I know that, like...
that everything they did, like,
set me up with, like, the skills
to be able
to, like, achieve
what I want to do.
I'm just so used to, like,
things not being handed to me,
but I just, like, always am able
to, like, somehow, like,
persevere and figure out,
like, how to get through it.
Oh, my God. Please stay.
Please stay lit.
It's been such a dream
to be on Survivor,
and I can't believe
that I'm here.
In many ways, me being
on Survivor is almost
like a love letter to my parents
to let them know that, um,
like, everything they did,
like, gave me what I need
to survive out here.
And I don't know.
I actually think that
if I can survive here,
survive, like,
double my Survivor nightmare,
I'm going to come back
into the game, like,
still looking like a lamb
but ready to play like a lion.
Wow.
Well, that sucked.
XANDER:
Because of that challenge,
I'm covered from head to toe
in bruises and bumps,
scrapes and dirt.
And I felt like I looked--
just completely disheveled,
downtrodden.
I haven't even made it
to the merge yet.
I mean, this is like
-a merge-atory.
-All right, can we get that?
XANDER:
I want to ensure
that I get there, so,
it's possible
that playing my idol now
or winning immunity
is the only thing that's going
to keep me in this game.
I knew you had it.
I wouldn't have shared it
with anybody.
You did the right thing.
I didn't play 'cause
I wanted you to have it.
-Well, thank you.
-Yeah. I...
TIFFANY:
Okay.
LIANA:
Shan immediately,
in front of Tiffany,
talks about the advantage.
I didn't plan on sharing this
with anybody.
That sucked because there was
no getting out of that pickle.
No...
I can...
The way my Knowledge Is Power
Advantage works-- I have
to have the knowledge
about where everything is.
I have to ask the correct person
the correct question.
And I only have one shot
to do it.
I can ask either
"Do you have an idol?"
or "Do you have an advantage?"
and they have to give it to me
if they do have it.
Mm-hmm.
I know.
SHAN: I am super excited to work
with Liana moving forward
because Liana and I really
bonded on the journey, and
I kind of just trust her
with everything.
You know, she's like,
"I've got your back,"
and I know...
I know I've got hers.
And that's how I...
I genuinely feel.
XANDER:
Oh, my God, what a sight.
Oh, my God.
Baruch Hashem.
We're eating.
-HEATHER:
I'm good. Let's share it.
-XANDER: Mmm-mmm.
-We'll take turns.
-HEATHER: I'm good.
TIFFANY:
This is delicious.
And the seashell's got
some salt on it,
-so it's gonna kick in.
-HEATHER: Mm-hmm.
-XANDER: Mmm.
-Savor every bite.
-I am.
Every single little grain.
TIFFANY: I'm kind of on the outs
in a weird way
'cause Liana went on a journey
with Shan, so they have
a little bit of a... connection.
Heather's sort of
connected to five people
who have already won.
And I'm sitting here like,
"What's happening?"
So I'm just going
with everybody at the moment.
All right, we're gonna rinse,
you get water.
-Okay.
-Is that fair?
You want to do that?
-Yeah, that's cool.
-All right, let's do it.
LIANA:
Tiff gets a moment with me
as we're walking down
to do shells,
and she's like, "Okay, well,
what's the advantage?"
I'm like, "Oh, my God."
Essentially, what I can do is,
I can steal someone's idol
or advantage
at Tribal Council, and they...
they have to give it to me.
I'm not kidding.
So we can take...?
Naseer's. We can take
whoever we want.
LIANA:
That was just nerve-racking
to tell Tiff
because she's to me like,
"I knew it.
"I knew you had it
the whole time.
"Don't worry. I wouldn't have
have told Evvie,
I wouldn't have told Xander."
Like, she has this,
like, intensity about her.
-Whoa.
LIANA:
She's playing so hard.
Yet she's this really funny,
you know, charismatic person
that everybody loves
to be around.
And so, that, to me, is kind
of like poison, and I'm like,
"Especially with you knowing
about this now,
"and how I've seen you operate,
you've just become
a major threat."
TIFFANY:
Liana is continuing to hold
this emotional tie
to wanting Xander out.
And she's gunning
for one of our own.
That's a problem,
and here's another problem.
She did tell me right away
what it was,
and it's some sort of advantage.
But all I could think was,
"We were a tight three
coming in here,
"and you already had something
to hide from us,
and now we're in a big group."
If she can do that
within the game like this,
she's gonna flip on us
in two seconds. So,
I'm not so sure I'm gonna have
her back like I did before.
Oh, my.
-Look.
-Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness. Hi!
Hi.
Hi! Oh, my gosh.
-I'm Sydney.
-Hi. I'm Liana.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Xander.
-I'm Danny.
-Hi, Sydney. Nice...
EVVIE: So going back to camp,
I was expecting it to be awkward
because we just had
a feast and the others
have just been sitting there,
but actually,
they were so excited to see
everyone here.
Everyone put on their best
merge-making-new-friends face.
-Okay, I'm Liana.
-Liana. Liana, okay.
-I'm from a suburb
of Chicago-- Evanston.
-Okay.
Thank you, man. Oh, I really
appreciate that. Aw.
When the red Buffers
came back home,
it was all fun and games.
We're having a great time
out here, we're getting
to know each other, but
in everybody's mind, we know
that it's not going
to last very long.
Yeah.
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Okay?
XANDER:
It's bad being the only guy
eligible to be voted out.
Everybody
could decide that,
you know what?
This is our best chance
to take out Xander.
However,
I do have the extra vote
and also an immunity idol.
So I'm not entirely powerless.
But she didn't tell me.
She didn't tell me.
I'm hoping that everybody
is of the mindset of...
Yeah.
I think...
DANNY:
The Luvu tribe--
we got fractures
all over the place,
but with Erika getting sent
to exile, it's kind of obvious
that she's at the bottom,
and I don't want her
to come back with a grievance
and automatically decide
that she wanted to flip
and try to get one of us out.
-Who?
-Erika.
-Oh, yeah.
-Right. So basically,
she's gonna take a spot away
from one of us.
Yes, exactly.
SYDNEY:
This is an absolute no-brainer.
Erika's a very smart person
and an incredibly
intelligent player.
And if she has some sort
of advantage,
that makes her very dangerous.
-EVVIE: We don't know what
she has on the island.
-Yeah.
And I think that will just make
everyone feel more comfortable.
-You know? Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
SHAN:
Ricard and I--
we're the only two from Ua.
So if people are pitching Erika,
I'm okay with all of that
and I'll rock with all of that.
But if she comes back
with an advantage,
it might not be that easy.
XANDER:
I think the Luvus want
to cannibalize each other first.
But it's just,
like, it's almost,
like, too good to be true.
-It sounds too good to be true.
-I don't know.
SHAN:
I was just really,
really nervous,
and the only person that really
seems reliable is Liana.
Liana and I really bonded on the
journey and the excursion, so,
I feel like I can trust her,
and then I do really like Danny
and Deshawn. More than any
other season that I think
I've ever watched on Survivor,
I think Season 41 has been
the most diverse and most,
like, inclusive
and representative
of America.
No, I...
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
But, like, I... I think it's...
-I think it's dope.
-I agree.
LIANA:
As people of color,
there is a shared experience.
You immediately have this bond.
You're like, "Oh, you're the
only one in your classroom
that looks like you? Me, too."
And so, you have this bond
and this connection
right off the bat. We do want
to uplift one another
in this game, and that would be
a really beautiful thing.
SHAN:
Right.
-Delicious.
-Guys, let's really do it.
-Let's do it. Let's do it.
DESHAWN:
Recently I made some new friends
and new allies
in Shan and Liana.
I'm going to be honest.
I'm a guy from San Bernardino.
I'm used to being around a lot
of African American people.
But I thought that I probably
wouldn't get a chance
to play with Black people
in this game.
And that's not the case.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
As long as it's not one of us.
This season, the beauty
of having a diverse cast is
that it kind of
busts your possibilities
wide open, you know?
And everybody is kind of
bringing something to the table.
It's like,
"Well, we got an arsenal here.
We would be foolish not
to work together."
(Liana laughs)
ERIKA:
I was sitting
in my little exile home,
and I see this boat pull up.
It looks
like Jeff is on the boat.
It made me think, like,
"Okay, I'm actually crazy."
Like, there's no way
Jeff is making house calls.
-What?
-Take me in. Let me see what...
Are you serious? Oh, my God.
Jeff doesn't just show up
to tribe camps for no reason.
And he certainly doesn't
show up to Exile.
-So you kept
the fire going all night?
-Yes.
Working on the fire
is what kept me sane.
I think that if I didn't have
this little fire
that I felt
like I was taking care of,
I probably would have just laid
in a ball and cried.
So let's talk about
the emotional part of that.
-Yeah.
-Because this game can take you
on some wild journeys.
-Yes.
-And when the decision was made,
however it was made,
the result was,
you were sent here alone.
What does that feel like
when it is really just you here
with your thoughts?
I feel like... I just feel like
I was left behind.
I feel like coming here and
having to spend two days alone
when the merge happened--
which is so important--
it feels like... like I have
so much catch-up to do.
Well, it doesn't have
to be that way,
because in sending you out here,
what they didn't know is
they gave you
tremendous power.
Oh, my God.
I was hoping for something.
This... is an hourglass.
The black sand at the bottom
of this hourglass represents
the time
that has already passed.
-This is the history of what
has happened in the game.
-Yeah.
If you want, you can leave
the game in its natural state,
and the events
that have happened happened,
-what is is,
that's our history.
-Yeah.
Or if you want,
you can go back in time
and change history.
You have the power
to reverse the outcome
of yesterday's merge challenge.
-Oh, my God.
-So those that have immunity
would have it stripped
from them.
They would have to compete,
one of the six of them
would be voted out.
You and the other five
would be safe
and guaranteed a spot
in the final 11.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna leave you with this.
If you want to do nothing,
then just leave everything
as it is.
But if you want to make history
by changing history...
Oh, my gosh. How much time
do I have to think about this?
Tomorrow morning
before you leave the beach,
you got to make your decision.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Game is always changing.
You've earned your spot
out here.
You're still in the game.
What you do with this decision
is up to you.
It's obviously
a big strategic decision.
-I'm going to leave you with it.
-Jeff.
Not only has Jeff created this
single game-changing decision.
(singsongy):
Little old me gets to make it!
The little girl from Canada
who's much smaller
than everyone else,
who everyone was okay
with sending to exile,
gets to make this decision? Oh,
my... God!
What makes it complicated
is, the six who are safe
are the majority
of my original tribe.
So this could burn bridges
with people
that I do have some type
of trust with.
No matter what I do,
I'm probably going to lay awake
for the next few nights,
wondering
if I did the right thing.
People are going to talk
about this one for a long time,
and it's a lot of pressure.
Whatever I do,
there are going to be people
who are going
to be upset with me.
I had the opportunity
to change the events of history.
-Wow.
-SHAN: Oh, my God.
XANDER:
That's a curveball.
EVVIE:
This is literally life
or death for me.
What decision did you make?
(roars)