♪ ♪
SHAN: Yo, we got
to freaking day ten!
-GENIE: Yay!
-SHAN: Yay! Did you think
we'd be here-- us three?
You know what I really hoped?
I-I'm serious.
I wanted you, and I wanted you.
-Sure.
-I felt that, too. I felt that.
It's-it's weird
how that happens, but I did.
I did honestly.
GENIE:
Tribal went really well.
I went with my instincts
to trust
that Shan and Ricard
were voting JD
because, the last Tribal,
I was on the wrong side
of the vote on a blindside.
And usually that means you're
on the bottom of the tribe.
But I was reassured
that's not the case, and now
I-I feel very, very solid
with the three of us.
Do you want me just
to go get water, and...?
Yeah.
GENIE:
So, two Tribals ago,
Brad left with an immunity idol
in his pocket.
"Congratulations.
You have found a three-way
shared immunity idol."
GENIE:
So now we're assuming
that the same
Beware Idol, the three-way idol,
was going to go back into play.
Right now, at this moment,
we got to fend for ourselves.
We-we are the fewest number
of people at any tribe.
We got three.
So we need every arsenal
and every tool we can have.
Ooh-hoo! What?!
(laughs)
I found an immunity idol?
Ricard! Shan!
SHAN:
What?
GENIE:
If it is what I think it is,
you lose your power to vote
until that idol can get
turned on, or until the merge.
We know Yase tribe
has found their idol,
but Luvu has not found theirs.
That is terrifying, especially
with only three of us left.
I have a feeling it's
the same thing that Brad had.
Okay, if we open it, do we think
that Luvu went and got the idol?
GENIE:
See, I don't think Luvu went
to look for the idol.
If they didn't get it,
this doesn't matter
-and we've lost our vote.
-Right, but then we get our...
GENIE:
No, we get our vote back,
don't we?
SHAN: But at the merge.
At the merge. Here's the thing.
Our vote is our voice,
and it's the most powerful thing
you have in the game.
So maybe I'm thinking
we don't touch it.
SHAN: And the truth is, I don't
want Genie to open it because
I don't want anyone having
any more potential power
in this game than me.
So I just said, "Let's...
let's just leave it here
for now and come back to it."
We'll leave it right there, and
we know where to come back.
Cool.
-Nobody betrays anybody
and grabs it.
-All right.
Nobody, please, take it.
I don't know what it is.
I... There's just something
I don't trust about her.
-She might have opened it.
-Yeah.
So, we... we could look
at the packaging really quick
-to see if it's been opened.
-We should go check that.
There's a part of me
that's like,
"Just kill it. Just kill it.
Nothing good can come from it."
And then, on the other hand,
I'm like,
"I've got this extra vote
in my back pocket."
So I'm thinking...
why not open it?
Maybe I'm gonna open it.
-Well, I'd rather
give you the vote.
-Yes.
And have you write her name
'cause I told her
-I'd never write her name down.
-Yes.
-It works?
-Sure.
But what's the argument
to Genie to let me open it?
SHAN:
It's like Pandora's box.
I don't know what
I'd be unleashing.
And yet, the Survivor player
in me can't help
but want to take a risk.
Let's do it now. Let's do it
now. Let's do it now.
RICARD:
She's, like, right there.
Okay, remember how it was tied
like a Christmas present.
See, it's a three-way.
Um, phrase... Um...
-"I didn't realize until now."
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Hey, come on.
-RICARD: Okay.
SHAN: It's the same exact
advantage that Brad had, so,
if nothing is said by the merge,
this becomes a souvenir.
Which... That's trash.
RICARD:
Now that Shan has opened
the Beware Advantage,
and she doesn't have a vote,
she has
to give me her extra vote.
It's just the only thing
that makes sense.
-If we don't need it,
you'll give it back, right?
-Yes.
RICARD:
Now, I've been trying to come up
with different scenarios
of how to navigate
Shan actually needing
to say the phrase
for the idol to be active.
And so, I'm going to tell Genie
that we want to say the phrase
out loud, maybe,
just to see
if Luvu has the idol or not.
But just out of curiosity,
I was like,
"Well, maybe, Shan--
maybe you say it,
just to see
if the Luvu person says it."
Even though it won't really
do anything, but...
Yeah.
That's some boss stuff
right there.
RICARD:
Right now, Shan and I together--
we are a solid duo
controlling the game.
And Genie--
she's a spare tire
that we're about
to just put
on the side of the road
when we don't need her anymore.
(laughs)
♪ ♪
SYDNEY: We haven't actually
eaten fish up until this point,
but I consider myself
to be a mermaid,
and I've always known that I
feel in my element in the water.
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey... ♪
Everyone's like, "Wow.
Like, women catching fish."
And I'm like, "Whatever."
SYDNEY: I never saw myself
as any different
as men, but it is cool
to get that accolade.
-Oh, no.
-I got to throw my-my...
my age-old idea out there.
DANNY:
You look at the other tribes.
The men are leaving the game,
and they're leaving the game
very quickly.
DANNY:
So I'm absolutely nervous, uh,
that the women will have
more numbers than us
at a switch or a merge.
DANNY:
I'm realizing that
Naseer's probably not somebody
that I want to play with,
specifically because he doesn't
want to throw the challenge.
But he's somebody
that's gonna be necessary
if I want
to move forward in this game.
-I agree. I agree.
-Yeah. I agree. I agree.
-(laughs)
-NASEER: I'm feeling great here.
It seems like my tribe is
including me
in many conversations.
Yeah.
So...
-So...
-NASEER: Danny and Deshawn
agreed before the challenge,
do not throw...
just throw away the challenge.
And now I am feeling great
because these guys want
to work with me.
-I'll bring some up.
-Let me know.
I'm like, "Yeah, that's amazing.
That's music to my song."
XANDER:
Yes.
EVVIE:
I would love to go to the end
with people that, like,
if they won, I wouldn't hate
myself. You know what I mean?
-Exactly.
-Yeah, and I think as long
-as you and me stay tight...
-Yeah.
...no matter what happens
to this tribe, we're good.
-Yeah? Yeah.
-Exactly.
EVVIE:
I think
Xander thinks of me
as his number one.
And the three women--
we know we're the three,
and Xander's on the outs,
so it's all
about making sure Xander
feels like he has all the power.
-Right?
-Yeah.
She has something going
with him,
-and it's beyond me.
-I know.
I think Evvie's alliance
with Xander
is a much tighter alliance
than she wants
to let on to me.
Yeah.
Okay. Thank you.
EVVIE:
That-- I don't think it's crazy.
XANDER:
Yeah, I know.
-Oh, it's in my bag.
-Oh, it's in your bag.
-But I just sleep on my bag.
-Yeah, I think it's fine.
He has an extra vote.
Yeah. Yeah.
-It says, "You have found
a hidden immunity idol."
-Okay.
But it doesn't activate
unless all three other players
at the same challenge
repeat the phrase.
And you can't vote
until it's activated.
So until the merge,
he's worthless.
Another way
to throw him under the bus.
Get him out.
Done.
Yeah.
Should we just tell Tiffany?
'Cause I'm, like,
sure of you, me, and Tiff.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-But I'm not sure of Liana.
I'm fine with that. I think
that would lock her in with us.
-Don't you?
-Yeah, yeah, I think so, too.
XANDER:
I don't have a vote.
I have my Beware Idol that
hasn't been activated yet.
And so I have no power.
I'm completely stuck.
I'm at the mercy
of my tribemates.
And I feel like Tiffany's
someone who is in the middle.
So I really want
to cement that trust.
-TIFFANY: Let me see
what a real one looks like.
-Yeah.
-TIFFANY: It's so exciting.
-Right?
-It's pretty freaking cool.
-I know.
Okay, where's the thing
that goes with it?
-XANDER: The letter?
-Yeah, right?
No? Or you don't have that?
I mean, I've got the...
the congratulations one.
TIFFANY:
He's being very, very giving.
And as he's showing me
this stuff, there's papers
coming out of his bag, and
there's other papers that say
the phrases thing
that you need to activate.
But what about the butterfly
and stuff like that?
-Didn't you say something
like "Crazy"?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
TIFFANY:
And he starts stumbling
and realizes that he's already
said one of the phrases
during the last challenge.
-(laughs)
-And Brad also said
one of those statements.
Now, Xander told me
he only found this today.
So I didn't find it this
morning. I just told... like...
-Wait. I'm so confused.
-Yeah.
So I was worried about you guys,
like, getting nervous...
Okay, okay, okay.
I lied a little bit.
But she works with kids
who are delinquents--
kids who have made mistakes.
It's her job to forgive them,
so I'm hoping
that she'll take pity on me,
and we'll work together.
I am used to being on 24-7.
It's what I do.
It's my job, so with Xander,
I'm on to him.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Luvu and Yase getting
your first look
at the new Ua tribe.
JD voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
This is the hottest spot
in all of Fiji,
if not the Earth.
It is day 11.
I am already drenched.
I cannot imagine
how you're doing.
I'm hot, I'm tired.
She's vegan.
-She's losing her mind.
She thinks everything's food.
-Yes.
Yes, I was, like, losing
my mind. I didn't realize it
until just now, but broccoli
are just small trees.
-(laughter)
-RICARD: We're a little rough.
I think,
you know, we're all
just trying our best.
-We have no rice.
-SHAN: No calories.
He was talking about ladybugs
being his dead relatives
-or something.
-XANDER: Actually, I said
I truly believe
that butterflies are
dead relatives saying hi.
-SHAN: Oh, my goodness.
-RICARD: So, you know...
We're all going crazy.
Well, you are... off.
(Shan laughs)
-All right.
-Jeff?
I am as confused
as a goat on... Astroturf.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
What is this?
NASEER:
I was looking early morning,
and all of a sudden, I saw
something right on a branch.
I'm like, "Whoa!"
I can see my daughter
right front of me
when I found that idol.
She created her own idols
and hid in our backyard.
Then she made me find
those idols on a daily basis.
It's amazing. But noth...
You know what?
I love this game.
This is the reason
Always something new,
and it's never easy.
You have to work hard to get it,
but that is why I'm here.
My daughter's going
to be so proud of her daddy
because
that training worked out.
This is for you, my love.
Raya, I love you.
Yeah. (laughs)
PROBST:
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first--
got to take 'em back.
-Thank you, Naseer.
-You're welcome. Thank you, sir.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna go up and over a net ramp,
release a key,
unlock a machete,
use that machete
to drop your sandbags.
You will then fire
your sandbags at two targets.
First two tribes
to finish win immunity,
safe from the vote.
You're also playing
for a reward.
(whooping)
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
-Yes, sir.
-SHAN: Wow.
-GENIE: All right.
Okay, all right.
PROBST:
First tribe to finish--
a giant tarp. I don't care
how many people you have,
it will keep you dry.
Second tribe to finish--
not as big. Still offers
a little protection and comfort.
-Man.
-PROBST: Losers--
Tribal Council, where somebody
will be the sixth person
voted out of this game,
and I'll keep your flint.
All right, Luvu,
you have three extra people.
You can sit out anybody.
Who's it gonna be?
Erika, Heather
and Deshawn gonna sit out.
Yase, you have one extra person.
Who are you gonna sit out?
Tiffany gonna take a spot on the
sit-out bench. Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize,
and we'll get started.
Let's do it!
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready.
-Go!
-TIFFANY: Go, Yase!
-Come on, Luvu!
First part of this, you got
to get all three people up
and over this net.
It's not easy.
No shortcuts,
you just got to work together.
-My back.
-Genie is on.
TIFFANY:
Good job, Xander! Let's go.
-PROBST:
Xander getting up there.
-Good job.
-ERIKA: Nice job, Danny.
-Luvu getting
through it quickly.
-(whooping)
-Danny's now up there.
You got to get everybody
on the other side.
-DESHAWN: Good job, Naseer.
-You're good, Luvu. One person.
-Good work, Naseer.
-You got it.
It's Naseer trying
to untangle the knots.
Here comes Xander, going hard.
There goes Ricard for Ua.
Waiting on Evvie.
That's a big jump.
-Let's go. You're good.
-TIFFANY: Good job, girl.
Liana now. You've got Liana,
Ricard and Naseer trying
to get that key to drop.
You have to untangle
all of the ropes.
Then that key will drop,
and you can unclip it.
SYDNEY:
Nice!
Naseer's very close.
He's got it. Release that key.
You're good.
Now unlock the machete.
Yes. Machete man.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Luvu in the lead!
-(cheering)
-Naseer has a lot of time.
You're looking
to take down two targets.
Naseer gonna fire.
Ooh. Just misses.
Take your time.
Get a feel for it.
Liana has the key for Yase.
-Yes, yes, there it is.
-Ricard has the key for Ua.
-Now unlock the machete.
-Go, go.
-There you go.
-One, two, three, four.
Liana, you're a rock star.
Go, hack that bad boy.
PROBST:
That's how you do it!
(overlapping chatter)
-Nice.
-PROBST: Ua's in it,
Yase's in it.
-You got it.
-Naseer looking
to hit that first target,
take advantage
of this time lead.
-Yeah! Yeah!
-And he does!
There's one for Luvu.
It's going
to be Ricard firing for Ua.
-Get the feel for it.
-You got this, Ricard.
-Oh.
-PROBST: Ricard just short.
-Go, go.
-Another learning curve
to figuring out
the slingshot,
but you'll get it quickly.
(cheering)
Xander knocks down
the first target for Yase.
It is now Yase with one
and Luvu with one,
and Ua in dead last again.
GENIE:
There we go. Hey, that's good.
-That was good, though.
-PROBST: Naseer for the win.
-Just misses.
-Oh, so close.
PROBST:
Here comes Danny in for Luvu.
Ricard trying to get immunity.
Oh, it hits the post.
Not enough.
Oh, my gosh.
-Oh!
-PROBST: Xander just misses. Oh!
-ALL: Oh!
-PROBST: Danny just clips
the bottom of the post.
Here's Xander.
Can he win it for Yase?
-There it is!
-(cheering)
Yase wins immunity!
-Yes!
-Yeah!
-Yeah, man.
-Oh, my God.
-Wow.
Let's go!
Take your time. It's all good.
Go! Go! Jump!
We're looking for one more.
Losers-- Tribal Council.
Oh, you were right there.
Naseer coming back in.
Come on, you got this.
You got this.
GENIE:
Put your body weight into it.
We got Ricard
and Naseer in a showdown.
Ricard misses by just an inch.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
Naseer for the win for Luvu.
-There it is!
-(cheering)
-Oh, no!
-Naseer does it for Luvu...
-DANNY: Yes!
-...sending Ua
back to Tribal Council,
where the tribe of three
will become
-a tribe of two.
-Good job, Ua.
-Good job, you guys.
-SYDNEY: That was so hard.
-Good job, both of you guys.
-Oh.
GENIE:
You all right? It was fun.
Yase, congratulations.
Immunity once again.
Come grab your giant tarp
and rope to assemble it.
Well earned.
Luvu, another immunity.
Thanks, Jeff.
Come grab your tarp.
All right,
before I send you on your way,
Yase, you're going to send
two people on a journey.
-Ooh.
-XANDER: Oh.
They will make a decision.
Pick somebody
from the losing tribe-- Ua.
Who are you going to send?
Anybody can go.
Nobody of the three has been
on a journey yet.
-Who are you gonna send?
-Shan.
-Really?
-Okay, Shan will be going
on the journey from Ua.
One more person's gonna go.
It can be
from Luvu,
or it can be from your tribe.
-I'm gonna go.
-PROBST: All right.
Liana gonna go for Yase.
So Liana and Shan will
take a journey together.
Yase, nobody going home.
You guys can head back to camp.
Liana will stay.
Luvu, once again, nobody going
home from your tribe.
Grab your stuff, head back
to camp, enjoy the night off.
Thanks, Jeff.
PROBST:
All right, Ua,
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be voted out.
I will continue
to hold onto your flint
as a punishment for losing.
Genie, Ricard,
head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
Shan, Liana,
you two are going
to take a journey together.
Head out, boat'll pick you up.
You'll both return back to
your camp before Tribal Council.
SHAN:
I'm concerned about Camp Ua.
You know, being away
for so long, I just know
they're gonna come up
with a plan to blindside me.
It's inevitable. They have to
talk about that reality, right?
But I'm also super excited
because Liana is somebody
that I've wanted to meet, so,
you know, hopefully,
it all comes together.
♪ ♪
SHAN:
I am super excited
because Liana is somebody
I've wanted to meet
and wanted to connect with
for a while.
And so, I want
to cultivate trust because
you cannot play this game
without trusting someone.
You can't trust anyone, and yet
you have to trust someone,
because nobody gets
to the end without trust.
-LIANA: So, how old are you?
-I'm 34.
-LIANA: No freaking way.
-Yes.
LIANA:
You look so young and kick-ass.
-SHAN: Oh, that's so sweet.
-That's awesome.
-I'm super psyched
that they chose us both to go.
-Okay,
they're gonna be thinking
we're gonna work together
-as two Black women.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-We have to be super careful.
-I know. Oh, I know.
Do you feel
under pressure tonight?
-But know I have the idol.
-Okay.
So, Xander has an extra vote,
-and he has the third...
the now... that immunity idol.
-Yeah.
SHAN:
I think it's an advantage
to be playing
with two women of color
because if I am here,
you know, going into the merge,
then I'll have another ally
on the other side.
LIANA:
So that's kind of what
the situation is, and so,
when we get back,
obviously, I'm not going to say
that I know anything about
the idol. I'm gonna play dumb.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-That's good. I think
that's good. Oh, my goodness.
But I'm definitely
gonna play down us.
Us. Yeah, all the way through,
even when we merge.
All the way,
Liana, I told you my game, okay?
-I know. I know. I...
-Okay, so...
-I will take you with me.
-If your name's out there,
I'll tell you. If your name's
out there, you'll tell me.
-Yes. Yes.
-We'll cross communicate, 100%.
-All the way, okay?
-Seriously.
Seriously. I'm... listen.
-Yes.
-If by any chance,
I am not here on day 12,
-Ricard cannot be trusted
because he's my number one.
-Okay.
Wow. This is really beautiful.
My mom would love this.
Oh my God. I'm so sorry.
Well, how old were you?
Um, just... I was...
I was thirty... two.
-Still. Still.
-So she was...
It was, like...
It was May 22.
So Mother's Day is that,
you know, May,
-and then she passed, so...
-I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God, I can't imagine
not having a mom.
-Oh. So many hugs in here.
-(crying)
SHAN:
When I look out at the ocean,
I think about my mom.
♪ ♪
When I was little,
she was my everything,
but she was battling
with the demons of addiction,
and because of that,
I was put in foster care.
I got mixed up
in the wrong crowd
and became affiliated
with a gang.
It was a really,
really dark time in my life.
I felt completely abandoned,
and I didn't even want
to live anymore.
I remember a girl at school
inviting me to church.
That was where
I found my higher power
and became a pastor.
My mom and I hadn't spoken
in years,
but the last five years
of her life we got really close
and really connected, and
I just miss her so much.
You're the first person
that, when I told that,
you're like, "Sorry." I think
people don't know what to say.
(crying):
No. Like, there's nothing
like your mom.
SHAN:
I've spent days
with Ricard and Genie,
and I don't think I've had
moments with them like that.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-SHAN: And then
I meet Liana, and
I have this moment with her
after, what, three hours
of taking a trek up a hill?
That tells you that connections
are so much bigger
than just, like, the time
you spend with someone.
Oh, boy.
Do what you need to do.
-I could risk it.
-You need something.
I need something, so I think I'm
going to lean that way probably.
Okay, I won't risk it.
I want you to have it.
-Okay?
-Okay. Okay.
SHAN:
I choose not to risk my vote.
One-- because
I need my vote
for tonight because of Tribal,
and two-- because
genuine trust is so rare
in this game.
I just wept on top
of the mountain with this girl.
I trust that that is something
that's going to be stuck
in her mind 'cause
I know it's stuck in mine.
-I'll see you on the other side.
-See you on the other side.
-The merge.
And I want Liana
to have something
in her pocket
going back to Yase.
-You got this? Good luck.
-Okay.
LIANA:
And it's not about
who you trust in this game.
It's about who trusts you.
From the moment my feet
hit the sand on this beach,
I've been playing
an individual game,
but I see something in Shan,
and it was mutual, so
my individual game changes
going into the merge.
I'm going to risk it.
Thank you, Shan!
Yes, this is what I need.
This is what I need.
Oh, my God.
This advantage is so valuable.
Essentially, how it works is
asking the right person
the right question means that
I can steal either an idol or
an advantage. I can literally
say the word and take
someone's idol at Tribal.
Like, that's insane.
I should hide it.
Shan said to me,
"I'm giving you 100% right now."
And now I have this advantage
where I needed it most.
XANDER:
As long as I keep
telling myself I'm not
that hungry,
I don't actually feel hunger.
LIANA:
Xander's absolutely not
someone I can trust,
but Knowledge Is Power gives me
everything I need
to potentially snuff his torch.
♪ ♪
She has not talked to me at all.
I don't know
if I'm being paranoid.
I feel like Shan is going
to vote me out tonight.
Shan getting chosen for the
journey hurt a little bit, but
me having this time to really
let this fake story
with Genie sink in--
it's really perfect.
My game plan is,
throw Shan under the bus,
make her sound awful,
and create a story for Genie
of why she needs to vote with me
to take out Shan,
when in reality, Shan and I
take out Genie.
Every move I've made,
she has taken credit for,
and is in a way more
powerful position
-than me.
-Oh, my God, the fire.
Let me check the fire.
Ricard is very strategic,
but he does kind of come off
a little bit
distrustful.
You would... you would be
willing to write down her name?
I'm willing to write down
her name 'cause it would...
Otherwise, it would be my name.
My game plan
coming into camp was,
I need Ricard
to talk to me to vote Shan out,
and sure enough, he did.
It has been a huge concern of
mine-- her and me in the game.
This is just an idea
I'm throwing out.
Yeah, I'd like to hear it.
If it was
the two of us together,
I feel like
it would be so unexpected
that we would be tight.
People would be like,
-"Oh, it was clear
Shan and him were tight."
-Right.
And we could be way more
stealth than her.
Ricard, that's what
I'm feeling right now.
If you think you can work better
with me from now on...
'Cause I'm definitely
at the bond right now.
-Oh, my God, yes.
-Yeah?
Come on, let's put some...
He thinks getting rid
of her might be the better idea,
and keeping me.
But I didn't tell him, "Well,
me and Shan-- we're voting you."
-Hello!
-How'd it go?
Can I just say...? (sighs)
Heading back to camp,
I'm so nervous
because I haven't been there
all afternoon, and so I know
they've been strategizing
about me,
so I know that I want
to tell them what's happened,
share everything that I can
with them about the journey.
-Want to sit out here
on the beach?
-GENIE: Yeah, yeah.
SHAN:
And then I want to start
pitching to them 'cause I know
the sun is going down,
and Tribal is coming.
So, Liana and I go
to this, like,
island, and we see this sign
that says, like,
"You've got
to make this journey, this trek
"all the way up
to the top of the hill.
And then you're going
to have to make a decision."
Right? So, basically,
um, I told her, I said,
"I value my vote in this game
-because we're going
to Tribal tonight."
-Yeah.
And I said, "You should risk
your vote and just know
"that I'm not
going to risk mine,
and you'll definitely
get the advantage."
Okay. So what was the advantage
they offered you?
-I don't know. They don't
tell you until you play.
-Oh.
And I just turned the big...
the big steering wheel
to the right
and protected my vote.
Wow.
I know you guys have been
strategizing
all afternoon, and I would
appreciate just a moment
-to pitch my...
-Well, I need
to pitch myself, too, so...
I need to pitch myself, too.
Can I go first? Is that cool?
-Can I talk to Shan first?
-RICARD: Sure.
SHAN:
I have an idol in my pocket
that's been activated,
but I'm feeling very nervous,
very anxious.
I am an option.
You know, it is very possible
that they could blindside me
and vote me out, so I need
my one-on-one with Genie
and my one-on-one with Ricard
'cause I don't know
if they're both with me.
I've got to figure that out.
What I want to do is
I want to stick with you.
I want to stick with you, too.
Okay. Um...
Did Ricard pitch me?
-He did pitch...
-As a blindside?
As a blindside, yes.
-Okay, okay.
-But I'm still...
-I'm still with you.
-We're locked in here?
-I-I promise you.
I promise you you're fine.
-Okay. Okay.
-On your faith and
whatever faith I still have...
-Okay.
-...I promise you I'm with you.
-Okay. Okay.
I trust Genie.
I believe Genie.
She's an honest player,
so when Genie tells me
that Ricard is coming after me,
there's a part of me
that's thinking I have to get
the extra vote back from Ricard
as, like, insurance.
I want him to know that if
he votes me out,
the extra vote goes
with me and so does the idol.
SHAN:
I don't want this
to set off any alarms,
but could you give me
my advantage that I got from JD,
just so that you keep me
in the game
so you know that we have
all the things come merge?
But then you have no reason
to keep me.
I'm keeping you, Ricard.
I gave it to you
because, you know,
we thought
I wouldn't have a vote
because I took the idol.
It sounds like you're trying to
get it so you can blindside me.
No, I'm not. I'm not.
I just want...
Okay, one-- to be honest--
one-- I want what I...
I-I... I did the legwork for
with JD.
That's what I want,
but it's ours.
I just want insurance so that,
like, you're-you're like,
"Shan has the idol,
Shan has the advantage.
"I'm not going to vote her out
because she's got these things,
and they work for us."
That's how I feel.
But there's no insurance
for you to keep me. Like, I...
There would literally be
no reason to keep me.
You said you would give it back.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-You really don't believe me?
-I just have a fear.
You're a master strategist.
I just have...
Then play the idol tonight.
Waste it for the merge for us?
If you don't believe me,
then play the idol.
-I'm not doing...
-So...
I am not voting you out.
Okay, so you're not gonna
give me back the advantage?
I feel like
this is a weird conversation
'cause this is literally
what I told you to tell JD.
I know. That's what...
You don't think I feel stupid
having this conversation
with you,
knowing that this is what...?
It doesn't seem
you're feeling stupid
-'cause you're still doing it.
-I do feel stupid, but I want...
I still want the advantage back
'cause I don't want...
-So you'll have two advantages.
-Yes.
You'll have the credit
for all the advantages.
You'll get the choice
between the two of us,
'cause she's going
to write down my name.
How do I know you're not
gonna blindside me?
'Cause I'm not.
So are you saying
you're not giving it back to me?
Is that what you're telling me?
-Are you threatening
to vote me out if I don't?
-No, I'm not.
-Did I say that?
I did not say that.
-Well, I don't...
-Well, I'm just trying to...
-I did not say that.
I just don't want
to do this back-and-forth.
You said
you'd give it back to me.
If you're saying
you're not going to, then...
I am going to give it
back to you tomorrow.
-I-I just got to trust you.
-Yes, you have to.
I... It's Survivor. You can't
be upset or be tripping with me
-just because I'm... I'm not...
-I'm not upset at all.
SHAN:
Ricard and I
work very well together,
but that moment he refused
to give back something
that rightfully belonged to me
was a hard moment for us.
And I could easily
vote his behind out.
I believe
that I can fully trust Genie
because Genie is
an extremely honest person,
and I-I love that about her, but
in this game, it's just
that that's a liability.
I have to make choices
for my own game,
so it does come down to,
do I bring the strategist,
or do I bring the loyalist?
♪ ♪
All right.
So, Genie,
you lose the challenge today,
and you have to go back to camp,
but Shan doesn't go with you.
This is a perfect Survivor storm
because
there's two of you, she's gone,
you two can talk.
What happened
between you and Ricard?
GENIE:
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
I mean, of course
I'm gonna do my best
to pitch to Ricard,
you know, why he should keep me.
And it's hard, because
these two have been a good pair
since the beginning,
and they are still tight,
but you have to think,
who do you want
to go into the merge with?
Do you want to go into the merge
with somebody else
that's, like,
you know, you know,
honest and-and can completely
be loyal to you,
or do you want to take somebody
to the merge
who can make friends
with every single person,
and maybe
they don't need you anymore
after a couple of days?
PROBST:
And, Ricard, while Shan's away,
this is a game.
You would be a fool
-to not listen to her pitch.
-RICARD: I mean, I feel like
I come up
with phenomenal strategy
on how to get people out,
on figuring out the blindsides,
on giving advice
on how to do something properly.
She's like the closer.
She figures out how to do it.
She does the talking.
She's such
an honest human being,
she's gonna tell me if she's
gonna vote for me, except today.
I'm trying to figure out
who's more beneficial
for me-- the honest person,
or the one that closes
what I have come up with?
It-It's really difficult
to figure out.
PROBST:
So, Shan, what are you thinking,
while you're doing
whatever you're doing,
about what
they're doing back at camp?
SHAN:
Yeah, I'm definitely...
Like, when they select me
to go onto the journey,
I was like, "Oh, shoot." Like,
you don't want
to be absent because
anything could happen
when you're not around.
So I just said to both of them
when I got back, "I-I want
to pitch to you why I think,
"Genie, you should vote with me,
and I want to pitch to Ricard
why I feel like, Ricard,
you should vote with me."
And you know, we-we all took
turns at doing that.
PROBST:
Genie, what's interesting
about that is
that Shan is saying
to both of you,
"I'm going to both pitch you,
then I'm going to pitch you
against the other person."
That... Exactly.
Shan's the master at that.
You know, I think
she's in the power position.
Well, I-I mean, they also
could be blindsiding me.
Like, they spent so much time
together this afternoon.
Like, it... I'm sure
Ricard pitched
really good reasons for why,
and Genie pitched really
good reasons for why, and, like,
I don't know. I don't know
that I'm completely
in the driver's seat tonight.
Tribal is a really
good indication
of how trustworthy
another person can be.
And I'll say at least to you,
we have been together
every single vote.
PROBST:
And, Shan, right now,
you don't know
if that's genuine
or a well-rehearsed script
that they both said, "Let's play
this thing. We have a history.
It's not going to work for us."
-You just don't know.
-(Genie laughs)
Yeah, Season 41--
like, you got
to be looking and reading
and watching, and you can't...
you can't rest for a minute.
You're always thinking.
There's no pause
in this... in this game, and...
And so, I'm listening to them,
and I'm like,
"Mm, I don't know."
Ricard, tonight's vote is unique
in that,
historically,
there is no invoice.
If the person's not in the jury,
they don't have a say
in the end.
So whoever goes home tonight,
unless the jury starts tonight,
they're of no consequence.
-There's no blood.
-RICARD: There is consequence
because the two people
that are left standing
are clearly experienced enough
already in this game
that they were able to navigate
getting rid
of their entire tribe.
The reality is, everybody else
that's been playing this game--
they are not at our caliber yet
because they haven't had
this experience.
They don't even know
who to trust,
they don't know
who's going to lie to them,
and they don't know
what to expect, and so,
whoever it leaves here is
going to be a massive target,
because everyone's going
to vote for us.
So where are we at?
I mean, we can vote anytime.
What's the...?
What's the blood pressure
right now?
-Oh.
-Where you at, Ricard? You calm?
What's happening inside?
I'm typically really calm,
but my heart is racing.
And all three of us are
genuinely concerned and scared,
which means we're all doing
a really good job.
Shan, what are the chances
that either a Shot in the Dark
or some kind of advantage comes
into play tonight?
You know, the Shot in the Dark
is this Hail Mary
kind of pass, right?
And you just really want
to save that
for a moment
when you're absolutely...
You know, you know you're at
the bottom, and there's just...
there's no way out
of this thing,
and-and you've got nothing left,
you've got no other cards
to pull out.
And that might be how some of us
are feeling tonight.
But I also think that the power
of the vote tonight is probably
more important than maybe
taking a Shot in the Dark
because advantages-- they come,
and they go, but the trust
is what carries you,
ultimately, to the end.
And so, that's what this vote is
about, for me, tonight is
the individual that I can trust
going with to the end.
All right, it is time to vote.
Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol
and they want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Genie.
Ricard. We're tied.
One vote-- Genie,
one vote-- Ricard,
one vote left.
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor 41...
Genie.
Want to bring me your torch?
Hey, seriously,
good luck, you guys.
-We love you.
-We love you, Genie.
Genie, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Bye, guys.
Wow.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
-Everybody drop your Buffs.
-(cheering, whooping)
-You are...
-ALL: Merged!
-Ah... not exactly.
-(overlapping chatter)
Damn it.
There has never been anything
-like this.
-Oh, my God.
DESHAWN:
It kind of busts
your possibilities wide open.
I had a feeling that this was
going to happen, and I...
I almost played
my Shot in the Dark.
But I feel like I did play
a pretty honest game,
and I should have listened
to my instinct
instead of trusting
other people. Man.
I actually kind of hope
it rains on them tonight,
'cause I know
nobody's gonna tend that fire.
(roars)