♪ ♪
LIANA:
Last night at Tribal Council,
the Xander vote
would have been genius.
I love Survivor,
and I want to make big moves.
And there's not many
opportunities that you get
to take out
big threats like that.
That's why it's-it's just
so hard to be here, because...
I'm sorry,
I'm getting emotional, but...
Um...
(crying): Like,
I came here to, like, play,
and because I come from such
a hardworking family, like,
I want to be a great player,
and it's just, like,
completely slipped through
my fingers last night, and...
But one of the things
my dad told me
coming out here
is that, you know,
"Change is the only thing
that's constant in this world."
So I'm never giving up
in this game.
There's always an opportunity
to flip the narrative.
♪ ♪
TIFFANY:
So I wake up this morning,
and I was not gonna get up yet,
but I was like, "Just get up.
Join the team."
(gasps)
"If you take this, it's yours
and you must do what it says."
TIFFANY:
Let me be clear,
I never would have
shared that with them
if I got it
without them in front of me.
However, I didn't have a choice.
"Congratulations.
You have found an advantage."
(both chuckle)
(gasps) Ooh.
"You will be taken
to another island
"where you must make a decision.
You will then return to camp.
"Failure to get on that boat
will result
in the loss of your vote
at your next Tribal Council."
-Oh, my God. I'm so happy.
-Oh, my God.
-Yeah.
-Good job, dude.
-Oh, my God.
-Good job.
It's my time
to go on an adventure.
I was meant to find it.
If I wasn't, it'd been
in somebody else's hands.
That's how I look at it.
So I'm taking it,
and I'm going with it.
Oh, my God.
-I can't believe
it was right in the fire.
-Yeah.
It was, like, literally.
I was right there,
and I just
wasn't paying attention,
and it was right in front
of my face, and...
like, that would have
just given me so much hope
to have that advantage.
Maybe that's
my million-dollar mistake.
JD:
"Don't say that
I gave that to him."
(laughter)
"Do you think I'm stupid?"
That's freakin' Reem.
I do Woo, like, all the time.
-GENIE: Oh, Woo?
-JD: I think that he's so funny.
"I bust out my arsenal,
which is my..."
-(makes whooshing noise)
"ninja stealth mode."
-(laughter)
"I'm cruising through the path."
(makes whooshing noise)
"Sonic the Hedgehog style.
There's no way
he's catching me."
(laughter)
BRAD:
I wake up this morning,
and I can hear
down on the beach,
it just sounds like
a beach party going on, man.
They're just laughing.
(laughter)
BRAD:
And I'm just laying
in my bamboo bed, and going,
"You know what,
kids will be kids.
"Just as well
start the day, man.
Chores need to be done."
When you're working on a ranch,
you don't do it
because of the money, right?
It's-it's a low return
on investment type of job.
Oh, it's just too wet.
You do it because
hard work pays off.
You got to go out and work hard.
You got to break a sweat.
And so, I think that translates
right over into Survivor.
♪ ♪
"Beware Advantage.
"If you take it, it's yours
and you must do what it says.
Otherwise, leave it."
"Tonight, a boat will arrive.
"You must sneak out of camp
and get on the boat.
"You will be taken
to another island
"where you must make a decision.
"Failure to get on the boat
will result
in the loss of your vote."
Got it. Sweet.
Game on, man. Game on.
Oh, I'm feeling so excited.
My heart's just
kind of missing beats,
and I'm just kind of all wired,
even though
I haven't eaten much.
The Beware Advantage adds
a whole new level to this game.
Everything comes at a cost,
but I'll tell you,
it's just,
I'm loving this game.
I'm loving all the twists
and all the turns
and all the danger.
High risk.
I just love high risk.
Wow.
Man, if you work,
you get rewarded.
And I guess
early bird gets the worm.
♪ ♪
SYDNEY: So, I'm, like, woken up
at, like, 3:00 in the morning,
and there's, like,
a man next to me.
And I'm like, "Who is this?"
He's like, "Naseer."
He's like, "We got to
get out Danny." (chuckles)
NASEER:
Okay...
SYDNEY:
"We got to get out Danny."
I'm like, "Well,
what about Deshawn?"
He's like,
"Deshawn will be so desperate,
he'll be crawling to us."
-(laughter)
-DESHAWN: Did he really?
Naseer, he said my name
on the first day,
so that was strike number one.
And then you want
to get out Danny.
Like, bro,
you have no strategy here.
You're just kind of
throwing stuff at the wall
and seeing what sticks.
All right...
And then he's like,
"Biggest blindside,
he's the biggest threat."
He's like, "Heather's a lunatic,
doesn't matter about her,
but it's like, we need to
actually play this game."
-I-I don't even
know where to start.
-ERIKA: Yeah.
NASEER: I feel like Sydney,
she's playing double agent game.
She talks to everyone,
and you-you can tell
from the vibe
that I feel like I'm in trouble.
I really feel like
he's ruining us.
-ERIKA: I know.
-Ruining.
But this is the only game
that you will never give up,
so I want to clear the air.
"English isn't
my first language."
-Yeah.
-NASEER: Yeah, so if anything...
Right.
So initially, we're like,
"God, we actually
cannot live without Naseer."
Like, he was so essential
to the tribe.
But at this point,
we can live our life
without Naseer,
because we actually think
that he can ruin
all of our games,
because he's so, so erratic.
After Naseer had his apology,
in plain sight,
I see a Survivor type package
sitting in the camp,
next to the fire.
♪ ♪
I wanted to play it cool,
but I didn't want to risk
Heather and Naseer getting it.
"Congratulations,
you have found an advantage,
"but it comes with great risk.
"Tonight, a boat will arrive.
You must sneak out of camp
and get on the boat."
After I read the clue,
I realized
that the top said "beware."
I'm scared.
There's no choice, like,
I have to get on this boat.
There's no option.
I'm getting on this boat
because I cannot lose my vote.
Like, that is the single most
important thing in this game.
That's why this says "beware."
This is a very dangerous
season of Survivor,
and I just put myself in
a very dangerous situation.
Damn. Nothing in this hole.
Ah.
Nothing.
I want everybody on the Internet
to shut up,
talking
"Idols are easy to find."
The idol is-is power
in this game.
Nothing.
I've been everywhere
on this island, you know?
And I still haven't found it!
And it's gonna drive me insane.
What am I missing?
But I do have one advantage.
I have an extra vote.
I didn't come here
for just one advantage.
I came here for them all.
I'm working so damn hard.
If it's not out there,
I'm gonna be so pissed off.
This idol is so hard to find.
Well, maybe it's hard to find
because somebody found it
in the easy place,
at the beginning of the game.
Ricard could have
the immunity idol.
He's sly. He's sneaky.
Out of everybody's
knowledge of the game,
he has the best, next to mine.
And...
Shan...
Shan's smart.
You know, she could be like,
"I don't want to tell JD."
So it wouldn't surprise me
that much if she had it.
Genie.
And she's also been
looking for the idol
so many times.
And then Brad never leaves
the dang shelter.
And some of us are like,
"Maybe it was at the shelter."
But I know I don't have it.
(chuckles)
SHAN:
Somebody's got to have the idol.
Is it you?
No. I don't think
anybody has it yet.
There's got to be an idol,
right?
No, doesn't got to be.
It's a new era.
It's a crazy feeling
around camp when you know
others are going out
looking for the idol,
but Genie and I
found it together
just 30 minutes earlier.
Ha-ha.
"Beware Advantage."
Oh, Genie.
GENIE:
Oh, my God, the moment when
I saw the joy on-on Brad's face,
I was like,
"I wish I had found it."
But that is the next best thing,
is that my closest ally
found it.
He said that.
(quietly): Okay.
BRAD:
He's got it. Xander's got it.
I truly believe that
butterflies are just dead
relatives saying hi.
-Wow.
-(laughter)
BRAD:
Xander said that exact phrase,
and so clearly he has one.
That's the other one.
They never said that.
And I didn't hear the one
about the goat and Astroturf.
So I assume the blue tribe
hasn't found theirs.
Oh. This is awesome.
So to have two Beware Advantages
is an amazing feeling.
It's great that
I have this powerless idol
that hopefully has potential,
but the "beware" part is I can't
vote at any Tribal Council
until the other two are found
and-and activated.
Down here,
there's that white log.
Up here is that white tree.
My gut says it's here.
BRAD:
And I feel worst for Shan,
because she is busting it
for this idol,
and I haven't told her yet,
and she's number one
with me and Genie.
So I want her to know that
I am loyal to her all the way.
I got a little extra something
to help us along the way.
You found the idol.
So, it's not mobilized yet.
SHAN:
Brad.
-This is for us now.
-(gasps) Oh, my God.
So Brad trusts me completely.
Because you only share
that kind of information
with your number one.
Okay, now, if you're ready...
-What? You found both?
-Number two.
-All right?
-Brad, when did you find these?
Hey, these things
just fall out of the sky.
What I need from you,
there's a boat coming tonight.
-Okay.
-I got to get on that boat
-and go to an island
to make a decision.
-Okay.
And just when I think it's over,
then he tells me
he also found
another secret advantage.
I don't know
what any of this means.
-Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
-Right?
-Come on. (laughs)
-Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, my...
I have to figure out
what I'm gonna do.
See, do I keep Brad in the game
because he's got all that power?
(thunder rumbling)
SHAN:
Oh, do you see that lightning?
RICARD:
Yep.
BRAD:
So, with this Beware Advantage,
I got to sneak out at night.
And I've got
to be able to provide
an appearance
that I'm still in camp,
because I don't know
how long I'm gonna be gone.
Man, I do not want
to get caught.
So I gather up the flippers,
and I gather up the oars
from the canoe, and I just build
this body in my bed.
And so, in the dark,
from a distance,
I think if anybody kind of
gets up and looks around,
they'll say, "Oh, yeah,
yeah, no Brad's sleeping.
I don't want to disturb him."
It's just like
Ferris Bueller's Day Off,
except without the snoring.
That's the only thing I needed,
and I'd have had it.
♪ ♪
This is scary.
TIFFANY:
(sighs) Oh, God. (chuckles)
-What the heck?
-I know, right?
-I'm Brad, by the way.
-Tiffany.
-Tiffany, nice to meet you.
-Sydney.
-Nice to finally meet you.
-Sydney. I know.
Nice to meet you.
I know, seriously.
Oh, my God.
We're the lucky ones.
"Clandestine meeting
with members of the opposition.
"It doesn't get
any better than this.
"You each have
a decision to make.
"You must choose
between two advantages.
A tarp tribe advantage
or a Steal a Vote."
The tarp is very useful
for the tribe
to just keep us out of the rain.
Keep things dry.
When you're wet,
you're miserable,
and so the tarp would be huge.
But I want the Steal a Vote.
That's what I want.
I want that in my pocket.
"But your decision
comes with risk.
"If all players choose tarp,
all players receive tarp.
"If all players choose
Steal a Vote,
"all players lose their next
vote at the next Tribal Council.
"But if there is
a split decision,
"all players who
choose tarp receive nothing.
All other players
receive a Steal a Vote."
BRAD:
If all three of us wrote
"Steal a Vote,"
we all lost
our vote at Tribal Council.
So that's
the worst-case scenario.
So just to be safe,
you'd write "a tarp"
and you'd be okay.
But when you split the vote,
i-if you can do one tarp
and two Steal a Votes,
then you both get Steal a Votes,
and she doesn't get a tarp.
"You may discuss as a group,
"but you will
make your decision in private.
"Check your tree mail
in the morning for your result.
"Act quickly.
The longer you are gone,
the more you risk being caught."
We didn't have time
for small talk
because we had
to get down to business.
Like, we had
to get back to camp.
-What are you thinking?
-TIFFANY: What do you think?
Let's just do something,
so that one of us has it,
-and it's out there.
-Right.
And then we can sort of
know that one of us have it.
-BRAD: So, you're down
to four players, right?
-We are.
So if you lose your vote,
all of a sudden two is majority.
-Right.
-You're definitely
choosing tarp.
-Um...
-I mean...
I mean, you can't risk
losing your vote.
SYDNEY:
You could?
What are you looking to do?
Tarp?
I'm erring
on the side of caution.
I think I'm gonna
choose the tarp.
If I'm gonna be straight up.
-Okay, so if you do tarp...
-I might just...
-Yeah.
-Then we get the Steal a Vote.
You guys both
want the Steal a Vote?
Whatever.
Just think about it.
At this point,
I do not trust Tiffany.
Dude, I don't even
know your last name.
I don't know where you're from.
She's playing too hard,
too quick.
Do you want to play it safe,
or do you want to play Survivor?
What do you want to do?
-SYDNEY: I...
-Or do you want to not
make a decision together
and just see what happens?
Roll the dice.
Um...
♪ ♪
It's kind of worth the risk,
uh, to get a Steal a Vote.
To go home with nothing
is kind of dangerous, too, so,
um, feel like, uh, got to,
got to play the game.
You don't win this game
by playing it safe.
You win the game
by taking risks.
Risks equal reward.
I'm gonna go with
play the Steal a Vote.
I just don't trust Tiffany.
I think she did Steal a Vote,
and I can't afford
to lose my vote,
so it's gonna be a tarp for me.
And I'll go back empty-handed.
Not so sure
I love Sydney's energy.
Me being me, I was like,
"Not gonna cause drama here."
I'm gonna make this
a win-win for me.
What's best for my game?
♪ ♪
There's no tarp.
I think I made
the right decision last night,
because although
I didn't get a Steal a Vote--
which would have been great--
I protected my vote
and maybe gained a little bit of
trust on two different tribes.
Found exactly
what I anticipated,
which was nothing, because
I knew that at least
one person got a Steal a Vote.
There it is.
And hopefully it's Brad.
"This advantage allows
you to steal a vote
from another player
at Tribal Council."
So I'm sitting with quite a few
Beware Advantages in my pocket.
The Steal a Vote,
plus the three-way
shared immunity idol.
So, man,
at the immunity challenge,
I'm hoping that blue has found
the immunity idol
because if they haven't,
that means I'm losing my vote
at every Tribal Council.
Cool.
Come on in.
Luvu and Ua are getting
your first look
at the new Yase tribe.
Voce voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
So, how are we feeling
seven days in?
Outside
of how difficult this is,
does anything else about this
game surprise you at this point?
-Yeah, we ain't got no rice.
-Yeah.
-You know...
-PROBST: Ricard...
-Oh, sorry, Brad.
-Oh, I'm sorry, Jeff.
You know, uh,
I was hoping
it was the salt water
that was making
my clothes baggy,
but the fact is, I'm just
turning into a little bit
of a twig
and just kind of a fuzzy top.
I feel like a broccoli, so...
(laughs)
Broccoli is, uh... grows little
bunches on, uh, small trees, so,
I feel like
a little broccoli tree, I guess.
Xander, does that surprise you
to have that kind
-of introspection?
-All you can do out here
is introspection.
I mean, all we got is time,
and I know I probably
sounded absolutely delirious
talking about
how I truly believe
that butterflies are
dead relatives saying hi.
Wow.
All right, should we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yup.
-First things first.
Got to take it back.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, one at
a time, you're going to swim out
and cross a rope bridge
over water.
When everybody gets to the end,
you'll dig up a sack of sandbags
and attempt to land those
sandbags on a series of targets.
First two tribes to finish win
immunity, safe from the vote.
In addition, you're playing
for reward. Want to know
-what you're playing for?
-Oh, yes.
-ERIKA: Yes.
-Please.
-Something you would take
for granted back home.
-Fruit.
-Oh.
-Okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
If you're feeling dehydrated,
lot of fluid.
You need a pick-me-up?
Natural sugars. First
to finish-- the large tray.
Second to finish--
also fruit, just less of it.
Losers-- Tribal Council,
and I will take your flint,
or in your case, keep your flint
as punishment. All right.
Luvu, you have two extra people.
Who are you going to sit out?
Heather and Erika.
Ua, you have one extra person.
Who's it gonna be?
-Genie.
-Genie gonna sit out.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
All right, here we go.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
-All right, you guys!
-(whooping)
It is Evvie in the water
for Yase,
Shan in the water for Ua,
-Deshawn in the water for Luvu.
-ERIKA: Yeah, Deshawn!
-Deshawn ripping
through the water.
-ERIKA: Yeah!
PROBST:
Deshawn is first to the ladder.
Shan right behind.
-Here comes Evvie.
-TIFFANY: Take your time, Evvie.
Now comes the hard part.
This is tricky.
You have a very narrow rope
to balance your feet on and only
four ropes to get you
from one end to the other.
NASEER:
Take your time. Take your time.
PROBST:
Deshawn doing a nice job,
-slow and steady.
-ERIKA: Good job, Deshawn!
Shan gaining on Deshawn
right now.
-Hey, Shan!
-Slow and steady.
(yells)
-Shan in the lead now.
-(Genie yells)
PROBST:
Got to get on that platform
and in the water.
Go, Ua!
GENIE:
Go, Ricard!
PROBST:
Deshawn getting closer.
Just got to get up
on that platform.
This is the tricky part
right here.
That'll do it.
Get in the water.
Go, Luvu.
Getting Naseer in the water.
Yeah, Naseer!
Evvie. You can see
seven days already
taken their toll
on how fast she's moving.
LIANA:
You got it, Ev.
-Jump, jump, jump, Evvie.
-Good job, Evvie.
PROBST:
Get in the water.
Go, Yase.
XANDER:
You got it, Liana.
Ricard quickly for Ua.
-SHAN: JD!
-PROBST: Naseer,
it is not pretty,
but it's working.
Yeah, Naseer! Come on, Luvu! Oh.
PROBST:
Naseer, you're good, jump in.
Go, Luvu!
Danny in the water for Luvu.
-Go, Ricard!
-Ricard's in. Go!
GENIE:
JD, you got it!
(indistinct cheering)
JD in the water for Ua.
Come on, JD!
PROBST:
Liana, you're good.
XANDER:
Go, Liana!
PROBST:
It's Tiffany
in the water for Yase.
Danny, doing a nice job,
almost at the platform.
-ERIKA: Yeah, Danny!
-PROBST: Danny, you're good.
ERIKA:
You got it!
PROBST:
Jump. It's Sydney,
the last tribe member
for Luvu in the water now.
-ERIKA: Yeah, that's my girl!
-PROBST: It's Tiffany
who struggled in the water
the last challenge
on the balance beam.
XANDER:
You got it, Tiffany!
PROBST:
Tiffany continues to fight.
JD is moving very fast.
-SHAN: Come on, JD!
-PROBST: Get in the water, JD.
Go, Brad!
-Sydney's there now.
-ERIKA: Yeah, Syd!
-ERIKA: Come on, Luvu.
-Tiffany almost drops
but hangs on.
-PROBST: Sydney's good.
-(whooping)
Sydney's got to get
to the mat now,
and Luvu can move on
to the next part of this course.
XANDER:
Go, Tiffany!
PROBST:
Look at that, Tiffany.
You did it.
Now get in the water.
Tiffany with a 3.5 for entry,
but it doesn't matter.
You did it.
-Brad, you're there.
-GENIE: That's right. Yes!
PROBST:
Here comes Xander for Yase.
ERIKA:
Come on, Luvu!
You're good! Go, Luvu!
Come on, guys. You got it.
You're so far ahead.
-PROBST:
Brad quickly there for Ua.
-RICARD: Come on.
-Come on. Come on.
Get on the mat.
-PROBST: Go, Ua!
Get over here!
It is a familiar story right
now, with Luvu and Ua battling
for first and second,
and Yase not even here.
You are digging
for one big sandbag.
Come on, guys!
Oh, yeah!
Come here, come here,
come here.
-Yeah.
-Pull, pull. Pull, pull, pull.
-(groans)
-Luvu has their bag.
-Yeah!
-PROBST: Empty it out.
You're looking
for five sandbags.
-Get on this mat! Go!
-PROBST: Here comes Yase,
still fighting, never quitting.
Dig, Yase. Let's go.
You're in this.
-ERIKA: Yes! Yes!
-PROBST: Luvu has it.
One bag at a time.
You've got to get
one on each
of the five targets.
Side to side. Side to side.
Ua still trying
to get that bag out.
They finally got it.
Yase has their bag.
Once again, Yase continues
to fight to stay in a challenge.
We have a challenge now.
All three tribes are in this.
First two to finish
win immunity and reward.
Losers go to Tribal Council.
Come on! Come on, Ua!
Don't panic out here.
Just find the touch.
-Come on.
-Just like that, one more time.
Tiffany lands
the first one for Yase.
It is Yase for the first time
in a challenge in the lead.
Come on! Come on, Ua!
Ricard is out.
Here comes JD.
Ugh.
JD trying to get some nice
style points.
Come on, JD!
-I got it.
-Oh.
SHAN:
Come on, JD! Come on!
-Deshawn is in now.
-Come on, Deshawn. You got it!
-(whooping)
-Deshawn lands one for Luvu.
-Go!
-Yes!
-Xander lands a second one
for Yase.
Look at this.
Yase in the lead.
-Come on now. Yeah!
-Yeah!
Xander lands another bag
for Yase.
Yase in the lead
with three bags.
-See, they're relaxing.
-There you go.
-Yeah!
-Luvu lands another bag.
There you go!
-(cheering)
-Deshawn with another bag.
We are tied three-three.
Come on, Brad. Yes! Yes! Yes!
Brad lands the first one for Ua.
-Yes! Yes!
-Brad hits a second.
Ua now has two.
-Yes!
-We are tied up--
three across the board.
-Good job, Brad!
-Let's go!
(cheering)
Deshawn lands one for Luvu.
♪ ♪
-Yes!
-Xander lands a fourth one.
Yase winless this season.
It would be a huge victory.
-Go for perfect.
-Oh, come on.
-Oh!
-Xander on and off.
Deshawn could win it right here.
-That's right!
-PROBST: There it is!
Luvu wins immunity!
-(cheering)
-We're looking for one more.
(whooping)
-Xander does it!
-Yeah!
Yase wins immunity and their
first challenge of the season,
sending Ua to Tribal Council
where somebody will be voted out
of Survivor 41.
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
What a challenge.
All right, Luvu,
another victory.
Tribe stays tight at six.
And Yase, your first victory.
Luvu, waiting
for you back at camp--
big platter of fruit
and no Tribal Council tonight.
Yase, waiting
for you back at camp--
a smaller tray of fruit,
along with your flint.
-You get it back.
-Thank you.
Yase, Luvu,
grab your stuff, head out.
-Enjoy the night off
and enjoy the fruit.
-Thanks, Jeff.
All right, Ua,
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be voted out.
Before you go,
I need your flint.
I know it's not easy to give up.
It's a penalty for losing.
Sorry for you.
Ua, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
♪ ♪
BRAD:
Challenge was
very disappointing.
Since Luvu
didn't say the phrase,
my idol is still worthless
at this point.
It is not activated.
It was just tough to land
those silly little sandbags.
So I have
the Steal a Vote advantage,
but I can't play it
even if I wanted to,
because I've lost my vote
with the immunity idol.
It's not activated.
I'm sorry, 'cause if I could've
just gotten one or two sandbags,
that would've made your life so
much easier on that challenge.
Yeah. Dude.
But JD, he always says
he can do the jump shots
and just keeps always
overselling and underperforming.
So my plan right now
is to get JD.
No matter what,
-us four go JD, no matter what.
-Yes.
Because even if
he smells it out,
the worst he can do
is roll his dice.
♪ ♪
SHAN:
I'll come down with you,
'cause I got to get my water,
and it's down there.
Or do you want to bring my water
when you come back, JD?
-I can.
-Thank you.
So I'm in camp, and JD says
he's got to go use the bathroom.
And so, after a while...
Oh, thanks, JD.
He comes back into camp,
and I look down at his waist.
JD:
First time, I thought...
And there's a piece of paper
sticking out of his waistline.
And I realized
he's got an advantage.
JD:
Damn it.
You're not coming clean.
You got caught.
That's not coming clean,
that's getting caught.
-I'm pissed.
-That's true.
Sorry.
All I can say is sorry.
-I can't really
do anything else.
-SHAN: No.
I was just so bothered
by the whole situation.
He's sloppy.
Honestly, a little bit of trust
was lost.
JD:
But now I know
I got to play better.
I now belong to you guys.
So just...
-take me further.
-(chuckles)
I'm not hurt,
I just can't trust him.
♪ ♪
We have to vote JD.
-Now, you mean that?
-I mean that with all my heart.
I think there are
pros and cons both ways.
-Yeah.
-If we keep JD,
he's a little sneaky snake,
but he seems really
indebted to us right now.
-He's sneaky,
but I-- and I don't...
and I don't trust him,
but I also don't trust Brad.
And Brad is also sneaky.
He's just a better worker--
harder worker--
and better in challenges.
Right now,
there are two big plans.
Voting out JD.
The other plan
is blindsiding Brad.
I, I-I-I...
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
RICARD:
But now Shan doesn't know
who she wants to vote for.
I'm gonna have to hope
Shan makes up her mind.
JD:
You know how people say
when things go bad, you know,
crap hit the fan?
Today, it was like
crap hit the fan,
and the fan was made of crap.
I want to play with y'all.
But then why didn't you tell me
about the advantage?
In Survivor,
you shouldn't tell people
about your advantages.
And to make matters worse,
I didn't tell you,
you found out.
So now it's even worse for me.
Yes, it is.
JD:
I'm worried that I lost trust
with Ricard and Shan,
and now they might
want to go for me.
I do apologize for that.
And I want to make it up to you.
I might even just
hand it to you.
Would you be willing
to hand it to me
to... for safekeep...
to-to hold?
Heck yeah.
I will hand it to you right now.
Okay.
JD:
This either
is a brilliant play by me
or one of the dumbest mistakes
in Survivor history.
You'll get it back when
you're not grounded anymore.
-(laughs)
-Yes, ma'am.
The best avenue for me,
since I'm not using it,
is to give it to her
as a form of trust.
I'm a ballsy player.
SHAN:
JD gives me the advantage,
and, in that moment,
I think, he is in my pocket.
And then I start thinking,
Brad has an idol.
Right now,
I'm the deciding factor
as to who goes home tonight,
and unfortunately
I get emotionally connected
to people in this game.
Every time I look at JD,
I want to vote with him.
Every time I look at Brad,
Somebody's gonna be
disappointed.
I remember
when I was five years old,
and I remember my mom and my dad
getting into a huge fight.
And I remember my mom
making me choose
if I wanted to live
with my dad or my mom.
And I remember choosing my mom.
My dad just started crying
in front of me.
(crying):
Like, I feel like
I let him down, you know?
Even at five.
And I still carry that
to this day.
So this situation half dances
on that, like a bit.
Like, just, like,
letting someone go
that feels like family,
and, like,
this is what makes
this game so difficult.
♪ ♪
Shan, Ricard had not even sat
down, and you had already...
started dropping your head.
SHAN:
Yeah, it's been a long day,
and we definitely didn't want
to vote someone off.
And so it's just sad.
PROBST:
So, JD, if there was
a Survivor newspaper,
which one of the five of you
is the face that represents Ua
that got their ass kicked
by Yase?
Oh, gosh.
Yase kicks Ua's ass. Yes.
That is what is on the headline,
and there's a really pretty
picture of me, you know?
And I thought, being the athlete
that I've been,
that I would be easily hitting
those sandbags up there.
But I mean,
I just couldn't get it done.
And that's on me.
Ricard, in order
to win this game
you have to survive
every single Tribal.
So what makes the most sense?
Having a tribe
that doesn't lose,
so you don't have
to go to as many Tribals.
Therein lies the dilemma.
Tribe strength
or my personal alliances.
You know, I'm kind of
starting to veer towards
my own personal alliance.
I'm not gonna make it very far,
once we hit the merge,
if I just have strong people
that don't actually like me.
I need to work with people
who I trust.
Wow. Genie,
Ricard is saying straight out
somebody in this tribe
has lied to him,
and he's not happy about it.
They're probably
getting his vote tonight.
He thinks he's got his alliance,
but I know I have mine, so...
Do you think that he thinks
you're the one that was lying?
Probably based on
the first Tribal.
I don't think
Ricard's ever really truly
trusted me since then.
-PROBST: What happened?
-But she spelled my name right
when she wrote it down.
PROBST:
Brad, it's really the one word
that comes up
all the time on Survivor--
trust.
BRAD:
Oh, man.
Jeff, the fact is,
you got to trust somebody,
because, in the end,
that's all you got.
-Yeah.
-BRAD: And so,
to build trust,
you say what you're gonna do
and then you do it.
JD:
Jeff, we're all
talking about trust,
and I feel like
somehow, someway,
I've lost a lot
of you guys's trust.
Where trust in this game
is like crystal, right?
And each one of you has your
own crystal, and it's precious.
It's not easily given away.
And I hope that, even though
I may have dropped your crystal,
that you don't drop mine.
In a game like Survivor,
relational stock
is hard to rebuild
once it's gone.
It's beautiful
to pick up crystals,
once they've been
broken and-and dashed.
It's even better when you,
when you don't dash them,
you know?
JD, you seemed to get down
the minute Shan said,
"Yeah, it's pretty hard
to put a crystal back together."
Yeah, it's heartbreaking,
but I think
writing down my name tonight,
like, look at my leg,
will be
like scratching a mosquito bite.
You know, and you may feel
a little relief now,
but in the long run
it's gonna get a lot worse.
PROBST:
So, Brad, what's the good
that could come from this vote
when you go back to camp,
the four of you?
Jeff, if you can
make it through this,
what don't kill
you makes you stronger.
And so, once we're walking back,
the morale
is gonna start going back up.
It's bittersweet,
but it's a healthy cycle.
PROBST:
JD, if you're not here
and this is the end,
what's it been like
for seven days for JD?
JD:
I've said it so many times,
my faith and my family
are my foundation, obviously,
but Survivor built me up.
I went through my life
really skinny and nerdy
and short and-and not cool,
and I was bullied a lot.
And, through all of that,
I would go home
and I could turn on the TV
and I would watch Survivor.
And I could live vicariously
through Ozzy and Malcolm.
All my heroes.
I wanted to be like them.
Why do you think
I have this hair?
You know, why do you think
I wear the necklace
and I, like,
I quote Woo so much?
And without Survivor,
I wouldn't be this guy
who-who is so confident
in himself.
And so, when I tell you that
Survivor made me who I am
and that I want to do that for
kids now, that's not a front.
I just wanted to play Survivor.
And I, and I, even if
it's cut short, I got to do it.
In just seven days
you've already impacted people
just like you were impacted,
of all ages, to not fear fear.
And that kind of enthusiasm
that you all have
is why it is so hard
to snuff a torch.
And with that,
it is time to vote.
Genie, you're up.
♪ ♪
This is a bigger
shot in the dark
than using
the Shot in the Dark die.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
♪ ♪
First vote, Brad.
JD.
One vote, Brad.
One vote, JD.
Brad. Two votes, Brad.
Fourth person voted out, Brad.
-That's three. That's enough.
-(groans)
Need to bring me your torch.
Wow. You got me.
♪ ♪
Brad, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
XANDER:
Really?
ERIKA:
Sydney's very reactive
and she's very impulsive.
Wow.
She made me feel terrible.
I was like, "You played me!"
DANNY:
Deshawn wants
to throw the challenge.
As a professional athlete,
this would be a sin.
So I left within my pocket
a Steal a Vote
and an immunity idol.
I made a multitude of mistakes.
In the end,
I think I probably put
too much trust in one person.
I just got wrapped up
in the fun of the game, I guess,
and didn't quite
slow down enough
to see some warning signs.
But I totally had the adventure
of a lifetime.
Back to the ranch,
where I can surround myself
with people I trust.
(roars)