(gasps)
Yes!
"You must say a secret phrase."
I truly believe that butterflies
are dead relatives saying hi.
Broccoli are just small trees.
I am as confused
as a goat on Astroturf.
Yeah.
XANDER:
Now all three idols have power.
Awesome.
LIANA:
"The Knowledge
Is Power Advantage."
This is so valuable.
-Jeff.
-Jeff, Jeff, Jeff.
Blue thinks they have it.
Say it.
-ALL: Merge Feast!
-That's it!
-(cheering)
-Blue wins!
You are going to choose either
Naseer or Erika to join you.
-Uh, Naseer.
-(whoops)
-PROBST: Naseer. Well, Erika,
there is no denying it.
Your game
just took a dramatic turn.
You will spend two days
and two nights alone.
Liana and I really bonded
on the journey, and so
I feel like I can trust her.
And then I do really
like Danny and Deshawn.
LIANA:
As people of color, we have
this bond and this connection
right off the bat.
This is an absolute no-brainer.
If she has some sort
of advantage,
that makes her very dangerous.
ERIKA:
I was sitting in my exile home,
and I see this boat pull up.
What?
This is an hourglass.
You have the power
to reverse the outcome
-of yesterday's merge challenge.
-Oh, my God.
If you want to make history
by changing history...
...smash the hourglass.
Jeff.
Oh... my...
God.
(insects chirping)
(thunder crashing)
(thunderclaps)
♪ ♪
ERIKA:
I came into this game
telling myself,
"Even the hardest day
on Survivor is still
a dream come true."
But last night was
the first time in the game
where I thought, like,
"Maybe I'm not going
to be able to pull it off."
But then I realized
I can survive on Exile by myself
and, like, feed myself
and take care of myself
in the rain.
Like, I just feel like I'm...
I'm, like, becoming,
like, the most authentic version
of myself.
And I feel like last night was
that first chapter
in this new book where I'm going
to realize the true
depths of my strengths,
and I'm going to learn
about who I am
in, like,
some new and profound ways.
And now I have this decision.
It allows me to, like,
hit a hard reset.
Whatever I do,
there are going to be people
who are going
to be upset with me.
It could set me up to be the one
on everybody's hit list,
but the reality is,
I have no idea what's ahead.
So I have to just trust
that whatever I do,
it's going to be
the best route for me.
PROBST:
Come on in.
All right,
we'll now bring in Erika,
returning from two days
and two nights living alone.
-EVVIE: Yay.
-DANNY: Yes, ma'am.
-Right here?
-Right here.
ERIKA:
Okay.
All right, so,
you're the big story because
just living alone in the middle
of the night in the jungle,
trying to make fire is
a big emotional event.
Oh, yeah, I, um...
There's a lot of me crying as
I'm trying to strike the flint.
Um, you know, I love everyone
here, but you can't help
but feel like the game is
moving forward without you.
And I knew I was going to come
back in two days, but, like,
you can't help but feel, like,
a little, like, left behind.
PROBST:
All right,
while you were out there,
you also had a very big decision
to make.
Arguably the biggest decision
in the game so far.
-Oh.
ERIKA: Yeah, I mean,
I had the opportunity
to go back in time and, uh,
change the events of history.
I had a special visitor come
and-and give me an hourglass,
and I had to decide if I wanted
to smash it or not.
-So, before you walk us
through your decision.
-Yeah.
So let me make clear
what's at stake here.
If Erika decided
to change history,
then what that means is
the six of you--
Evvie, Sydney, Naseer,
Ricard, Deshawn, Danny--
you would no longer
have immunity.
You would compete
in this immunity challenge.
One of the six of you
would be voted out tonight.
-God.
-Hmm.
-Erika, Heather, Tiffany,
Liana, Shan and Xander would be
safe. They would not compete.
-Wow.
-PROBST: Huge stakes.
What decision did you make?
Okay, this could make my game
or break my game,
but at least I'm playing for me.
I smashed the hourglass, and
I changed the course of history.
-Holy ....
-PROBST: What that means--
Evvie, Sydney, Naseer,
Ricard, Deshawn and Danny,
history has been changed.
Drop your Buffs.
-SHAN: Oh, my goodness.
-You are no longer guaranteed
a spot
in this new merged tribe.
(gasping)
PROBST:
Reactions, Deshawn.
How do you feel?
It's not the game I'm used to,
but as you said in the
beginning, this is Season 41,
and nothing's gonna be the same.
Um, and so,
maybe that is the new Survivor.
Maybe everybody who's watching
this now and who's here
should know this is what to
expect, so I'm ready to compete,
-but I just was
not expecting it.
-Mm-hmm.
-So, let's-let's get it, Jeff.
-PROBST: All right.
Here are the Buffs.
Take one,
pass 'em out
to the other five, head down
-to the end.
-Holy smokes...
PROBST:
Erika, Xander, Shan,
Liana, Tiffany
and Heather are safe.
They are guaranteed a spot
in the final 11.
That won't be the case
for everybody here.
Shall we get
to today's challenge?
For today's challenge,
you're going to use
your feet only.
On my go, you'll release a rope.
Blocks will drop into a basket.
You will then stack them
in a circle.
And put a flag in the middle.
♪ ♪
First to finish wins immunity,
the immunity necklace.
-You are safe with this.
-Okay.
Losers, Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the seventh person
voted out of this game.
You six that are safe,
take a spot down here.
The other six will draw for
spots, and we'll get started.
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready. Go.
First step is
to release the rope.
Everything's done
with your feet.
Evvie quickly has hers dropping.
Sydney has hers in there.
Yeah, you can use your hands
to get the rest of them in there
and get that rope out of the way
and then get to work.
You can only use your feet.
You want to make sure
you have a solid foundation
because you're building
three levels.
SHAN:
Good work, you guys.
-LIANA: Keep it up, guys.
-TIFFANY: You're doing great.
PROBST:
There's a lot on the line.
The game has just taken
a giant turn.
The game is constantly changing.
Adaptation is essential
on Survivor.
Sydney off to a fast start.
Evvie off to a good start.
Danny's got
a nice foundation going.
Ricard doing a nice job.
Deshawn with another piece.
Everybody doing a very good job
out of the gate.
-Everybody is in this.
-Doing great. Good job, guys.
-You got this.
-XANDER: Nice and slow.
PROBST:
In the early lead,
it is Sydney and Evvie
both with about the same amount
of progress.
But the further along
you get in this challenge,
-the more difficult it becomes.
-TIFFANY: Good job, you guys.
'Cause it's more likely that
you will knock another block off
while you're trying
to place one.
TIFFANY:
Let's go, Evvie.
PROBST:
Evvie now going on
to that third level.
-LIANA: Great job, E.
-TIFFANY: Good job, Evvie.
-Wow. Good job, Evvie.
-Good job, Evvie.
TIFFANY:
Good job, Sydney.
PROBST:
Sydney's on her third level.
Deshawn now moving on
to his third level.
It's Evvie, Sydney,
Deshawn and Ricard
all on the third level
right now.
-Come on.
-We got a challenge.
-Come on, Deshawn.
-We got four people
that are in it.
-Come on, Deshawn.
Here comes Naseer.
He's got his first block,
-but knocks one off.
-Evvie, you got this.
SHAN:
You got this, Ricard...
-ERIKA: Slow and steady, guys.
-PROBST: It is Sydney, Evvie,
-Deshawn and Ricard.
-HEATHER: Slow and steady.
-XANDER: You got it, Deshawn.
-SHAN: Slow and steady.
PROBST:
All four are in it side by side.
Come on, Ricard.
HEATHER:
Yeah, Deshawn.
PROBST:
One mistake could open the door.
(overlapping chatter)
Keep digging, keep fighting.
Evvie with another piece.
Sydney with another piece.
Evvie down to her last piece.
Sydney has two left.
-ERIKA: Nice work.
-HEATHER: Nice work.
HEATHER:
There she is. She's doing great.
Evvie with her last piece.
Now she's got to use both feet
-to get the flag.
-Hey, Evvie, slow, baby girl.
-Wow.
Sydney trying to stay in this.
It is Evvie and Sydney.
-Evvie now with the flag.
-Hardest part.
The hardest part.
Got to get it up and over
the three stacks
using both feet.
-Aah.
-And she knocks a block off.
-ERIKA: It's okay.
-PROBST: That's what
Sydney needed.
-HEATHER: It's okay.
-PROBST: Now Deshawn is in it.
-Ricard now has his last block.
-SHAN: Come on, Ricard!
-HEATHER: Come on, Ricard!
-ERIKA: Come on, Ricard!
-PROBST: It's now
Ricard going for the flag.
-Ooh!
Ricard could pull it out
right here.
It takes a lot of touch.
SHAN:
You need longer on the end.
HEATHER:
Oh.
ERIKA:
It's okay, Evvie.
PROBST:
It's now Sydney
trying to place her flag!
-TIFFANY: Oh, my God.
-LIANA: Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
Here goes Ricard with his flag.
-Can she get it?
-ERIKA: Oh, wow.
-Careful.
-Got to drop in that slot
without knocking anything over.
(grunting)
It is second by second. Ricard.
-I got it!
-Ricard has it!
Ricard, by seconds,
-wins immunity...
-ERIKA: Wow.
-...over Sydney.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Guaranteed a one-in-11
shot at this game.
Guaranteed a spot
-in the final 11.
-Yes! Phenomenal!
-Wow.
-PROBST:
That was an epic finish.
-ERIKA: Wow.
LIANA:
Good job, Syd.
Ricard, come on over.
SHAN:
Yes!
-Congrats. Congratulations.
-Good job, Ricard.
First individual
immunity challenge.
You are safe tonight
at Tribal Council,
cannot be voted out
of this game,
guaranteed a spot
in the final 11. Congrats.
-Take a spot back.
-(whooping)
-(indistinct chatter)
PROBST:
So here's what's going
to happen tonight at Tribal.
Everybody goes, everybody votes,
but the only five
who can receive votes are Evvie,
Sydney, Deshawn,
Naseer and Danny.
And now that we are in the
individual portion of the game,
I'm sure the Shot in the Dark
will become
an even more dangerous element.
So, starting tonight,
there are 12 scrolls.
Two of them are safe. Same odds.
One in six. All right, everybody
grab your stuff, head out.
-See you tonight at Tribal.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, Jeff.
ERIKA:
I smashed the hourglass
and flipped the game.
And there's no hiding.
I have to take ownership
for what I did.
But the days of me being that
little lamb on Luvu are over.
♪ ♪
-EVVIE: Good job, Ricard.
-SHAN: Good job.
-Congratulations.
-(indistinct chatter)
-I was so close, man. I know.
-That was heartbreaking.
-RICARD: Made me do that.
So, it was
a character-building experience.
-(laughter)
-EVVIE: Yeah.
LIANA:
Oh, my God. Thanks to Erika,
I'm safe tonight.
That's amazing. Also,
I still have
my Knowledge Is Power Advantage.
So at Tribal Council,
I can ask someone either,
"Do you have an idol?"
or "Do you have an advantage?"
And if they do have it,
they have to give it to me.
It's tricky 'cause
I have
to ask the correct person
the correct question, and I only
have one shot to do it.
But it's a lot of power,
and I can't wait to use it.
DANNY:
I busted my ass
on that challenge.
To learn that
that don't matter anymore
is, uh, really tough
for me to process.
DESHAWN: Danny, I don't want
to hear it, bro.
No, no, it ha...
No, it hasn't been that.
We drew rocks, we competed,
and there was a winner,
there was a loser.
And the prize was what?
Okay. I'm just asking.
DESHAWN:
No, this is the game now.
This is where you...
-He's flipping it, bro.
-Oh, no, no, I know. I was
just, like I said,
I'm not wired that way
-to, like, tip to before.
-I hear you. I hear you.
But now... now we got to rewire.
We have no choice.
DESHAWN:
Danny was upset. I get it.
But I'm like,
"What is fair, right?"
We came into this game
knowing that Jeff had some
tricks up his sleeve for 41.
And he said that it wasn't gonna
be like any other season, so,
fair or not,
that's how the chips fell,
and now we have to find a way
to respond to it.
Okay, so...
-BOTH: He does.
-So...
SHAN:
Yase strong.
-Right.
-Xander, Evvie and Tiff
-are really, really tight.
-Right.
-SHAN: No. No.
-SYDNEY: No.
Yeah.
SHAN:
So, is, is that, is that a plan?
-I'm down.
-I'm cool with it.
DESHAWN:
At this point,
there's five of us
that could be going home.
There's me, Danny and Sydney.
They're probably
my closest allies.
There's Naseer,
but he's one of my Luvu,
and I don't want to do that.
And then there's Evvie.
On the journey,
we talked about trying
to work together,
but at this point,
people are starting to see,
like, this girl's a threat.
And if they want to get her out,
I'm like, "Let's do it."
What you...? What...?
Mm-hmm.
Who is...?
LIANA:
Oh, my God.
I knew that eventually
I would have to take out Evvie,
but not so soon.
I feel really good
about moving away
from Yase and trading ties.
I really do feel closest
to Shan, Danny and Deshawn, but
Evvie's been really close
to me since day one,
and we've been through a lot,
so it's tough.
SHAN:
Liana, she's not 100 with you.
Oh, no, I-I understand, no.
-She glues Xander
and Tiffany together.
-Tiff.
A voting bloc, and she's also
persuasive and strategic.
Unfortunately, we both realize
-that there's going to be blood.
-Okay. Okay.
So you're-you're just
the first one to spill blood.
-I know.
-And then you just have to...
-I mean...
-And that's fine
-because we're still
the majority.
-But how do you feel?
...we have a different
perspective of the game,
different logic of the game.
When I want to strike,
she wants to play it cool.
So I feel way more connected to
you and how you think about it.
The problem is,
these two worlds cannot coexist,
and you have to choose one.
Evvie is going
to be devastated, but
I came out here
to make my own decisions
and hopefully win this game.
My heart's desire...
Honestly, I just...
-I have this vision of, like,
us four in the end.
-I know.
-(both laughing)
-LIANA: So this night
is kind of like
Liana coming into Liana
and-and being her own person
and kind of
putting on her big girl pants,
and I'm so excited.
(laughing)
Here's the situation right now.
Forever.
Yeah, we'll find out
if they are.
-It's the exact person.
-Guys, that was so close.
-Okay, listen.
-The exact...
-Wait. But can I just hug
you guys for a sec?
-Right?
-Hey, listen, do not...
-I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
-Okay. You promise?
-Yes, promise.
-Look. Listen. Careful.
-So close.
-Listen, listen, stop.
-You're my big sister,
all right?
-I know, but you need to...
-If you're out of this game,
-we're out of this game.
-Okay.
-TIFFANY: so just chill.
EVVIE:
This sucks. Literally, my back
is up against the wall.
But,
I mean...
tears of gratitude
that I have people
that are in my court still.
Because right away,
Xander says, "You're fine.
I'm playing the idol for you."
(sniffles)
Frankly, I don't know
that I would have done it
for him, so...
(sniffles)
It means the world
to me, you know?
So I'd say we take out one
of the super tight three.
EVVIE:
Yeah.
-XANDER: I think so.
-Yeah.
XANDER:
If we take out one
of her weapons...
-She'll have no choice.
-Exactly.
-I think Deshawn
should go out now.
-Deshawn, Deshawn.
Fine. That's my... fine.
EVVIE:
Deshawn and I went
on a journey together
early in this game and really
wanted to work together,
but I think
he had the best social game.
He's smart, he's building
a lot of relationships,
and that's really dangerous.
However,
there's been a complication.
Last night I learned that
Liana actually got an advantage
that she didn't tell me about.
-What?
-You got it.
Liana has a crazy advantage.
Before the votes are cast,
she can ask any person,
"Do you have an idol?" And you
would have to give it to her.
But it's only
if it's in your possession.
But, yeah, it's scary.
XANDER:
I was right about Liana.
I knew I couldn't trust her.
She's obviously holding back.
I mean,
I'm one of those sharks
that you can see my fin.
I'm up at the top of the water.
She's lurking down below.
TIFFANY:
No...
XANDER:
Liana's not Yase strong.
She's playing her own game,
and apparently,
Liana's got some kind
of advantage
where if she knows I have it
in my possession,
she can steal my idol.
That's a curveball, because
maybe she takes it before I can
even play it, and then
we're screwed, so we need
to figure something out.
(buzzing)
RICARD: We have such a brief
amount of time, I'm...
It's honestly hard for me
to process everything
-going through my mind.
-Yeah.
That's part of the reason why I
had to smash that thing, because
I have no idea,
like, where anybody is.
NASEER:
What'd she say?
She's thinking
we should go with Evvie.
Yeah.
-Exactly.
-So...
-Yeah.
-Uh-huh.
But, all right, so, like,
you've been only
honest with me,
and I want
to be honest with you, so, like,
Evvie's gonna be safe.
-I'm keeping her, you know?
-Got you. Yeah.
XANDER: It's going to be
a crazy Tribal. We've got
all these advantages
to keep track of.
I mean, my idol's
public information, so
I don't particularly care
who knows and who doesn't know.
However, Liana's got, by far,
one of the most powerful
advantages we've ever seen,
and that's something
that's unbeknownst
to most people at camp.
Here's the thing.
Liana has a Steal an Advantage.
She can take someone's idol.
-Oh, ....
-Is that crazy?
And she kept it from the Yases.
Got you.
XANDER:
This is gold for me because now
everyone's going
to know for a fact
that Liana is playing hard,
and that she's a big threat
out here.
And if I can create paranoia
in these people, that's great.
-Okay. What's up?
-All right?
Oh, my God.
Not only is Xander threatening
to play his idol for Evvie,
but also Tiffany told them about
my Knowledge Is Power Advantage.
So now
everybody knows
about this advantage,
and that could mess up
everything.
Which is Xander.
"The player cannot lie..."
SHAN: I don't think
her mind's working like that.
You bet your ass it is.
She is so smart.
This advantage is all
about asking
the right person
the right question.
So I have to make sure
that Xander has it
and hasn't given it to Evvie.
♪ ♪
EVVIE:
Yo.
Yeah.
-We have to protect you.
-Yeah.
Dude, I'm hearing my name.
-Don't worry about it.
-I'm really scared.
Yeah.
-100%.
-Okay.
-So we're good.
Okay.
Yeah, don't worry. It'll be
right on me the whole night.
-And then, when Jeff asks,
bingo bango.
-Okay.
EVVIE:
Liana-- she's shady as hell.
She's totally lying.
She wants to make sure
that Xander's
got the idol in his possession
so she can steal it from him.
He wants the moment, you know?
I-I trust him mostly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
EVVIE:
At this point my only
guarantee is Xander's idol.
But if Liana steals it,
I'm going home, so
this is literally life
or death for me tonight.
-They threw your name out,
-Who did?
Evvie. They want
to get majority of votes
on you, for Deshawn.
Yeah, right.
DESHAWN: Damn. It turns out that
I'm being targeted by Yase.
Now I'm in this very
vulnerable position
because we're all voting
for Evvie.
And if Xander plays his idol
for her,
I could be going home tonight.
SHAN:
Okay...
-Deshawn, calm down.
-DANNY: Listen, listen.
-Okay.
-The scramble that happens
right before Tribal--
it's-it's meant
to make you paranoid,
but you have to trust this.
-This is the core four.
-Okay, so then...
-Who's-who's... We're still...
-Evvie.
(buzzing)
SYDNEY:
Is anyone gunning for me?
XANDER:
I think you're fine.
-Do you feel worried?
-A li... Well,
-you're going to play
the idol for Evvie.
-Yeah, I am.
SYDNEY:
Right. Danny's gonna vote
for Evvie.
Shan is voting for Evvie,
Liana is voting for Evvie.
Ricard is definitely voting
for Evvie.
-XANDER: Really?
-SYDNEY: Yes.
If it goes my way...
I think part of my worry comes
from the fact
that I'm so self-obsessed
because I think, like,
"Oh, everyone's gonna
obviously want to gun
for me 'cause I'm me."
But then I'm like, "All right.
"Screw these people.
"I'll do what I have to do
to keep
"the votes off my back
and deal
with the repercussions later."
-LIANA:
Are you locked in with us?
-I'm locked in with you guys.
-Okay, listen to me.
-Okay.
Listen to me and just trust me
and believe me.
You will know before the votes
-what I've done.
-Okay.
And you'll feel safe,
and that's when you'll know
to vote Evvie, and it's fine.
-Okay.
-SHAN: Trust me when I say...
LIANA:
I can't wait to take the idol
from Xander just because
he underestimated me
for so long,
and I kind of had to, like,
fan his ego, and I hated it.
I don't like to be
underestimated, I'm not stupid,
and so tonight
I'm transforming into
that confident kind of
badass player that's willing
to make that move,
like a Sandra, like a Parv,
like these women I've,
you know, really looked up to.
So, tonight's game night,
and it's gonna be fireworks.
♪ ♪
If you've not yet been
to Tribal,
grab a torch,
dip it in and get fire.
Crazy that so many of you
have yet to even come here.
Wow.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council
because in this game, as you
know, fire represents your life,
and when your fire is gone,
so are you.
So let's just take this in--
all of you here together.
Crazy. Danny,
does it feel like what you
thought it would feel like?
DANNY:
I'll tell you this, Jeff.
I've played
in some pretty big arenas,
-and this is probably, uh,
top five automatically.
-Really?
-Absolutely.
-Wow. Give us insight
because you have a history and
a life that most people don't.
-So what's the context?
-Well... well, you walk in,
and you really don't know
what to expect,
and the people
that you're going against
are right here in your face,
and possibly getting you
to say things
that'll get you voted out.
PROBST:
Sydney, what is it like
with this many people
-on one beach, your beach?
-This has been, like,
honestly, kind of a miracle
because I was just
craving something different,
like, anything different
at that point.
So having all these new
personalities-- it's great.
I'm, like,
very much enjoying it.
PROBST:
So, Liana,
you guys get back to camp.
How fast did you feel
the pace pick up?
LIANA:
I'd say maybe, like,
five minutes or so, and
it's crazy 'cause I've watched
it through my TV,
but watching it happen live
in front of you,
you're like,
"What the hell?"
It's crazy. It was absolutely...
-It was undescribable.
-How do you
describe it, Tiffany? Because
this comes up a lot,
and players will say,
"You can't describe it,
but it's madness.
TIFFANY:
Um, I would say that madness
looks like 12 people who
have no idea who to trust,
want to believe that they trust
the people that they
came to know
through this experience,
but this is the part of the game
that I think is Survivor.
And you can draw a rock
and get put on a tribe
with four girls,
and you get nothing.
And then the other people
who go in-- they get everything,
and then it's taken away from
them. So, I mean, in my mind,
it's Season 41. Of course she's
coming back with something.
I just think we didn't think
it was the something
that she came back with.
SHAN:
And then also, Season 41
has come with a ton
of advantages,
including the Shot in the Dark.
So it's like,
even if you have the numbers,
you just don't know
what someone's carrying in...
with them in their arsenal,
and it can just turn the game
on its head
completely, so,
numbers only go so far.
It's-it's relationships,
and I think it's...
it's all those excursions
and journeys that
everybody's been on, you know?
-So...
-PROBST: Deshawn,
finally, somebody said it--
relationships.
It comes down to, "Who
do I think I can really trust
when everybody's telling me
I can trust them?"
DESHAWN:
Yeah, I mean,
I came into this game,
like, basing my gameplay
on the social dynamics
of things.
It just gets complicated when
you feel so secure in something,
and it gets flipped,
and now you're one
of five people who...
who can get chosen to go home.
I'm not complaining
about it, Jeff.
I made it this far, and
that's... that's dope for me.
That's really cool,
but I just wish
there was more, like, value
in what I brought to the game
in terms of my social abilities,
but that's all.
That's all I'm saying.
-Evvie, so, how are you feeling?
-Oh, my name is 100% out there.
Like, there are five people
that could be voted out tonight,
and four of them
were on the same tribe.
So I'm-I'm nervous,
but, luckily,
I got my jungle
little bro over here,
and, uh, I'm feeling like
I'm going to be okay tonight.
Wow. Ricard, that was
a barely disguised comment
that something's happening
that Xander's a part of.
RICARD:
Yeah, you know, we all know
about his little secrets.
Um... (laughs)
♪ ♪
RICARD:
Oh, there it is.
Yeah, I mean
it's no secret that I have
the hidden immunity idol.
There were some phrases
that were said
at challenges,
and they earn you this, which is
activated once
all three have been said.
And it's no secret, either.
So, yeah, it's honestly
a burden at this point,
so I'm happy to give it away.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Wow. Another big comment.
Liana, Xander's saying,
"I'm willing to not just use it.
I'm willing to get rid of it."
Obviously, idols change
everything in this game.
And one way
that you can show that you have
a really strong relationship
is by using your idol
to protect people that
you absolutely trust. And so,
as a Yase member, like,
that's something that, you know,
I think
we all hold dear to our heart--
-that we protect our own.
-EVVIE: And I think
kind of the interesting thing
about idols
this season, like, I knew
that Xander didn't have a vote
for a long time on Yase,
you know?
And I was never gonna let him go
because he didn't have a vote.
So this is, like, a relationship
that we built in the game, and
-that's how you play the game.
-Evvie, love you, girl.
Uh, but I'll just say,
she pretty much
told me everything that was
happening on the tribe, and
I knew that Xander had the idol
before I even met the guy.
And that was because of Evvie.
So, I get what she's saying,
but are you playing both sides
of the fence? Like, where does
your loyalty really lie?
PROBST:
Xander, did you know
Deshawn knew you had an idol?
I didn't know that.
It's an interesting point.
I just thought that I've known
Evvie the longest, so,
I figured that meant
that I could trust her the most.
Dude, and you can,
and you can, and I, like...
Clearly, I regret telling him
that, but the reality is,
you and me are in this together,
and we've been,
and I've been with you,
you know, this whole game.
LIANA:
And to that point, I think
Evvie and Xander's relationship
is super strong,
which is why, tonight,
I have an advantage
and I'd like to read it.
-Is that all right
with everyone?
-PROBST: Okay.
-Yes.
-LIANA: Okay.
So, um, I have the
Knowledge Is Power Advantage.
"Here's how it works.
"You're allowed
to ask one player
"either of the following
two questions.
"Do you have an advantage
or do you have an idol?
"If the answer is yes,
they must give you the advantage
"or idol, and it becomes yours.
"If the answer is no,
you receive nothing,
"and this advantage
becomes powerless.
"To be clear,
you can only ask one player
one question, one time.
That's it."
Um, so I just have one question
for one player.
Um, do you have an idol, Xander?
Ah.
♪ ♪
XANDER:
Right before we left for Tribal,
I gave my extra vote
and my idol to Tiffany.
(Evvie chuckles)
TIFFANY:
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-This way it looks like
I have an idol.
-Right.
XANDER:
I also have a fake idol
that I made a while ago,
and I'm glad I did
because Liana wants
to play her advantage
and wipe that grin
off my face.
Little does she know
I'm going to do it
right back to her.
-Thanks, Liana.
-LIANA: You're welcome, Evvie.
Why do you say thank you?
She's been telling me all day
we're good, and Xander says
he's gonna play an idol on me.
And she's trying
to steal it from him, so,
-thanks.
-Absolutely. This...
I mean, this game is cutthroat,
and you have
to do what you have to do.
So I hope you respect it.
-And that's the game.
-EVVIE: Sure thing.
Sure thing.
-Wow.
-Wow. (laughs)
-Evvie has Xander's idol.
-HEATHER: Oh, Evvie has it?
SHAN:
Evvie has Xander's idol.
Evvie is protected.
-I don't have an idol.
-Xander gave it to Evvie.
(laughter)
(Naseer chuckles softly)
Yo.
PROBST:
And now it begins.
Tribal just went very live.
(indistinct chatter)
SHAN:
Ricard, Heather.
(indistinct,
overlapping chatter)
Okay.
Yeah.
-EVVIE: I don't know.
-RICARD: Mm-hmm.
Okay.
No.
I have such a great seat.
-Look what you've caused, Erika.
-(Heather laughs)
-I know.
I can't believe
I'm actually here,
and there's actual
whispering happening around me,
and people have
whispered in my ear.
-It's like... I...
-HEATHER: It's crazy.
-ERIKA:
It's-it's hard to describe.
-HEATHER: Like, I have...
I-I know this sounds crazy,
but not eating at all,
being dehydrated
and all of this,
I can't even get
my words out right.
Like, this is all just...
(sighs)
-(Liana whispers)
-Yeah.
-SHAN: Okay? All right?
-LIANA: Yup.
-TIFFANY: All right.
Yup. We're good. We're done.
-We're done. We're done.
-PROBST: We're done, as in
-you want to vote?
-DESHAWN: No, sir.
Not at all.
So, Deshawn,
you're not ready to vote?
DESHAWN:
Um, it-it sucks to be
in this position, but I do just
want to give Xander props. Like,
that was a badass move, dude.
-Like, that was really dope.
-SHAN: That... that was bad...
-HEATHER: Mm-hmm.
-Unfortunately, for me,
it could expose me
tremendously tonight.
And if this is my night,
it's my night,
but you guys pulled that off,
so, good job.
-I appreciate you, man.
-Yeah.
-You're a good dude.
-TIFFANY: That's cool, Deshawn.
Sorry, one more question.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
SHAN:
Oh, my word.
-To me? Okay.
-DESHAWN: Yes.
Oh, man! (laughs)
But-but did...
EVVIE:
Yup. Okay.
Wait. How many do we have?
This...
Dude, dude.
It's... I'm-I'm aware
of what you were saying.
Okay.
-Naseer?
-Naseer, Naseer, wait.
-Done.
-They have one, two, three.
-Shh, shh, shh.
-Shh, shh.
-I think...
-Guys?
-Yes.
Okay, okay.
-Yeah.
-Okay, okay.
Shh, shh.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-SHAN: All right.
TIFFANY:
Okay.
-My God.
-SHAN: So, we're-we're good.
We are good.
We're good. We're good.
You guys good to vote?
-(laughs)
-DANNY: Please.
-DESHAWN: Yes.
-NASEER: Let's vote.
PROBST:
It is time to vote.
-Danny... you're up.
-Oh, me first.
First time for everything.
♪ ♪
(whispering):
Oh, that's Survivor
Tribal Council for you.
♪ ♪
(whispering):
"You made a risky decision
and it worked.
"You earned an extra vote.
"The last time
you can use this is when
there are six players left
in the game."
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
Okay, if anybody has
an advantage or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Jeff.
I'm just gonna play
my Shot in the Dark.
-You took your Shot in the Dark?
-Yeah.
-All right,
before you open it...
-Yeah.
...just to remind everybody,
Sydney has sacrificed her vote
in tonight's Tribal Council
for a one-in-six shot
at safety tonight.
Very low odds,
which means, clearly,
you think you are in danger.
Go ahead and open it.
First Shot in the Dark
ever played on Survivor.
♪ ♪
SYDNEY:
"Not safe."
All right, any votes cast
for Sydney will still count.
Jeff?
♪ ♪
Tiff, don't play it.
No, play it.
XANDER:
If they think
Ev was the one who had
the idol in her possession,
they wouldn't have voted for Ev.
EVVIE:
I could end up not
be on the jury at all
if they are tricking you.
You have to tell me
it's not mine.
All right, I'll read the votes.
♪ ♪
First vote-- Deshawn.
Evvie.
Sydney. One vote-- Deshawn, one
vote-- Evvie, one vote-- Sydney.
That's two votes-- Deshawn.
♪ ♪
Evvie. Two votes-- Evvie.
Sydney.
That's two votes-- Deshawn,
two votes-- Evvie,
two votes-- Sydney.
Deshawn. Three votes-- Deshawn.
Evvie.
That's three votes-- Evvie.
Sydney. We are tied--
Deshawn with three,
Evvie with three,
Sydney with three.
Evvie.
Four votes-- Evvie,
three votes-- Deshawn,
three votes-- Sydney.
♪ ♪
Sydney. We're tied again.
Evvie with four votes,
Sydney with four votes.
One vote left.
Seventh person voted
out of Survivor 41.
-Sydney.
-DESHAWN: I'm sorry, girl.
-Need to bring your torch.
-Syd, I'm sorry.
-TIFFANY: You guys.
-Oh, my God, Tiff.
-I told you.
-Yeah. That was close.
Sydney, I love you.
Sorry, girl.
Oh, my God, I was gonna die.
Sydney, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Good job, Syd.
-Love you, Syd.
-Bye, Syd.
PROBST:
Well, it was a journey,
but you all made the merge.
Here are your Buffs.
-Oh, man.
-(overlapping exclaiming)
(applause)
PROBST:
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Good call, man. Good call.
I want to get out
so many people,
-but I want to start with Evvie.
-Okay, I'm ready.
SHAN:
Everybody's just nuts.
It's a hot, steaming mess.
I do not know what the plan is.
-You think it's me?
-It could be.
The worst case scenario
happened.
Had I not played
the Shot in the Dark,
things would have gone
differently,
but it shows me
my instinct was right.
I'm, like, relieved,
I'm not on the jury
so I don't have to see
their faces ever again.
And I'm just glad I'm me
'cause what I have
outside of this game is
500 kajillion times better.
So that makes me feel good,
even if it's super immature.
(roars)