From day one,
the pace has been relentless.
They've survived
on very little food.
They've had to navigate
the most dangerous twist
we've ever put in the game.
They're on fumes,
but this is Survivor,
and every epic battle needs
that one final push.
This is the beginning of theirs.
Once again,
they're starting over--
new island, no food, no shelter.
There will be two immunity
challenges, two Tribal Councils,
one fire-making showdown,
and we have one last twist
that they will never see coming.
For the first time since the
summer of 2000-- 21 years ago--
we're gonna read the votes
and announce the winner
of Survivor
right here on location.
Then we're going to do
a Survivor after show
and keep everybody there
to talk about the season
while they're still
in that authentic raw state.
There they are,
the final five--
Deshawn, Xander, Erika,
Ricard and Heather.
Three of them will get
to the end and have a chance
to plead their case about why
they deserve the title
of Sole Survivor and the million
dollars that goes along with it.
This is the finale
of Survivor 41.
♪ ♪
DESHAWN:
This is my wildest dreams.
I can see myself winning
if I can just conquer
this last part of it.
XANDER:
This is here right now.
I just got to fight
to the bitter end.
HEATHER:
I have kept pulling myself up
and pulling myself up,
and I want to be the oldest
female to win Survivor.
RICARD:
I believe 100%
I could win this game.
ERIKA:
The game's gonna
get really intense.
It's going to be a lot
of scrambling.
of broken promises.
It's going to be a wild finish.
♪ ♪
XANDER:
Final five.
-Let's go.
-Final five.
XANDER:
Congratulations, guys.
Jeff throws us
another curveball,
and it's starting over
on a new beach
and getting
the bare minimum supplies.
Where are my pants?
XANDER:
We got to start over,
and, ooh, that's perfect
for me because
I don't need food,
I don't need sleep.
Yeah,
I'll eat my own adrenaline.
The other people out here--
I want them weak,
I want them starving.
They're gonna be
crumbling as I rise to the top.
RICARD:
There are different bugs
on this island
-than our old island.
-DESHAWN: Absolutely.
-Listen, Erika, we should talk.
-I-I...
-I'm sorry.
-No, I'm not ready to talk
to you right now.
-No?
-But you're welcome
for being here.
Oh. Bold statement,
and I love you, girl.
It was just Hail Mary
on my part. I had to do it.
-Had to do...
-I mean, I'm surprised
I was the target
of the Hail Mary.
DESHAWN:
I mean, Tribal was
another mess, man,
thanks to-to your boy.
I had to cause
some chaos tonight
so I decided
to blow up Erika's spot,
and that's exactly
what happened.
I'm saying it
in front of everybody
so you know it's the truth.
But Erika will not be taking you
to the end, Heather.
She told me at the water well.
Like,
"I can't bring Heather
to the end of the game
because if I do, she might
steal some of my votes."
ERIKA:
I've always just couldn't
understand why
-I couldn't 100% trust you,
and now I know.
-Mm-hmm.
Heather was a little bit
thrown off by that,
and Erika was pissed,
rightfully so.
But I mean, what can I do?
You guys are on the top,
I'm on the bottom,
and I'm trying to bring you down
to my level.
It's rough on the bottom, dude.
It's a rough road.
These people are shook.
And that-that was the goal
was to shake the table
a little bit because
it could maybe cause a rift in
y'all little foursome alliance.
And I think it might have.
-I was not expecting that.
-Yeah, not one bit.
That's why I'm, like,
I can't even talk to him.
I knew he says it's not
personal, but, like, it was.
-It was personal.
-It really was.
It was so stupid.
Danny went home, which was
completely my decision,
but I'm never
gonna trust Deshawn again. Ugh.
It just, like, drives me crazy
because I did so much work
to try
to protect him today,
and then he just, like,
pooped all over it.
-You're gonna be final four.
-Mm-hmm.
-And not him
because you made a good move.
-Mm-hmm.
But he wants to embarrass you.
ERIKA:
As long as I'm still in it,
I still got a shot.
What's important is how,
like, you bounce back.
-So, literally, he has to go.
Like, he...
-He just, like...
-Like, he can't be here.
-It just, like,
doesn't make any sense to me
when I'm, like,
I've literally tried to, like,
protect him so many times.
RICARD:
Deshawn thinks
he made some big move,
but all he was doing was
making it more impossible
for anybody to work with him
if he was the one
that stayed.
It was perfect.
-What?
-I know. It's...
-And now,
look who's on the bottom? Him.
-It's... I know.
RICARD:
I really want Deshawn
to continue to be the focus,
so first of all, I'm not,
and because I don't want Deshawn
in final four at all.
♪ ♪
All right.
Welcome to the Survivor
Final Five show
with your host Deshawn Radden.
Ricard, how does it feel to be
the last standing member of Ua?
Um, not that impressive
since I always knew I would be.
Ooh. Okay, so this guy--
he's a beast, and he knew it
from the beginning.
All right, Ricard,
I mean, listen.
We've watched all season long.
We think you're a great player.
I've been amplifying Ricard
as this huge target
the entire season for a reason,
for this very moment, actually.
And he has played a really good
game, and maybe these people
are smart enough to have seen
Ricard as a threat anyway,
so I didn't have
to do all of that.
We want to see you winning.
We're rooting for you.
Um, obviously, there's some
other players in the game
who probably
aren't rooting for you.
The guy is
good at these competitions,
and so, if he doesn't win
the next immunity challenge,
Ricard has to go.
So we're excited
to see where this goes.
Any last words for-for the show?
All right. We love you.
Good luck, buddy.
Oh, that was dope.
-How are you doing today?
-Fine.
So on the scale of one to ten,
how pissed are you at me?
ERIKA:
Thanks to Deshawn,
now Heather's, like,
so upset with me,
like, doesn't want
to talk to me.
But for me, it's reasonable
for everybody
to start thinking about who they
need to sit beside at the end.
So I'm surprised that she's so,
like, personally hurt by it, and
it sucks that,
like, she doesn't even want
to have a conversation
about it.
Just using, like, a forum
like, that to just, like,
try to make, like,
a fool out of me like that.
Like, that... that hurts.
For me, that, like, changes
-our relationship.
-That was not my intent.
I didn't mean
to make you feel that way.
-My thought process is,
I'm on the bottom.
-Right.
And I really did want
to keep you
'cause I really did think there
was, like, potential for us.
If you decide to send me home,
writing's on the wall
with that one.
If you decide
that I can be used,
whatever you want, I'm-I'm here.
And if you don't want any of it,
I understand that, too.
It is what it is.
-Like, I get it.
-ERIKA: Deshawn sunk his game.
I know that he's on the bottom.
He's trying to grasp at straws,
but he's just
throwing grenades and seeing
what you can break up,
and just, like,
blowing my game.
The crazy thing is,
I was also hoping
to, like, keep him around.
Now, like I don't see how
we're supposed to,
like, move forward here.
Oh, this looks interesting. Oh!
Oh. Oh. What?!
Oh, I'm down.
-Guys, we have tree mail.
-Tree mail!
-Oh.
-It's crazy,
-but there-there's one
for every person.
-RICARD: More chaos.
-Xander.
-DESHAWN: Chaos in an envelope.
Heather.
-HEATHER: Right.
-Oh.
-Let's go for it. All right.
-RICARD: Wow.
The clue says "Solve the phrase
to find the advantage.
"First you must unscramble
the words,
"then decipher the phrase.
"You cannot search
for the advantage
"until you have correctly solved
the entire phrase."
It's gonna be tough 'cause
we don't know this place.
I literally don't even know
where I'm supposed to pee here.
XANDER: Everybody's hard
at work figuring out
how to descramble these words,
because whoever gets
this advantage likely has a shot
of winning a million dollars.
RICARD:
In my head, I had started
unscrambling the words
while reading it.
I just love puzzles. Look,
I have won four
individual challenges. I love
this kind of stuff
'cause I'm great at puzzles.
Got it.
XANDER:
The final phrase is...
I'm thinking, they dance by the
ocean, they dance in the wind.
It's a million-dollar
egg hunt right now.
ERIKA:
All of a sudden, Xander gets it,
Ricard gets it, Deshawn gets it.
Like, in an instant,
I'm in last place.
Yeah.
RICARD:
Truly all that's going
through my mind is,
don't let Deshawn get it.
That is all I care about.
'Cause we don't know
what the advantage is.
It could be an idol,
it could be a twist
at Tribal Council. Yeah.
I feel like we all knew
we needed to beat Deshawn.
The goal here is just
to make sure
that Ricard doesn't find
this advantage.
Dancing trees, dancing trees.
ERIKA: Of course I'm the last
one to get the phrase.
"Your treasure hangs,
where the trees loved to dance."
Where are they dancing?
Oh, my gosh.
I hate doing scavenger hunts.
XANDER:
I love this.
It's a lot like
a cross country or track race.
Everybody's feeling pain
out there,
but when you look over
and you see the grimace
of your opponent, it fuels you.
All you have to do is push
a little bit harder than that.
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
"Congratulations!
In a season
"where you've had
to earn everything,
"you'll have a slight advantage
in today's immunity challenge.
It's not a lot, but it may
be all you need. Good luck."
I can't believe
I found the last advantage
in this crazy, crazy game.
My God, maybe this is,
like, the-the lucky break
I've been looking for.
Oh, my God.
All of the challenges have
been so closely matched,
so every second counts.
Even if I can have, like,
an inch of an advantage,
I'll take it.
Oh.
I found in this tree
with, like, weird branches.
I love that Deshawn's
still out there searching
for an advantage.
Damn treasure at?
What the hell?
Let him get tired?
ERIKA:
It weakens Deshawn going
into immunity today.
This is gonna drive me insane.
ERIKA:
And, also, like, there's no way
I'm gonna pass up
this opportunity
for a little sweet revenge.
Jeff, don't you know there's
trees everywhere on this island?
Come on, Jeff.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
-Hi, Jeff.
-She's still smiling on day 24.
Trying my best.
The final five. Come on,
that's got to feel good.
Starting over or not,
you are still in this game.
All right, ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yeah.
-For the third time, Ricard,
I got to take it back.
Thank you.
And Jeff, I have something.
Oh. Share.
This morning, I found
this envelope
that said "Final Advantage."
-Can I read what's in it?
-PROBST: Read it.
"Congratulations! In a season
you have had to earn everything,
"you will have
a slight advantage
"in today's immunity challenge.
It's not a lot, but it may be
all you need. Good luck."
Nice. Well done.
I'll explain that
after I explain the challenge.
So let's get
to today's challenge,
because once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to collect
a series of rope rungs,
and use them
to build a ladder.
You'll then maneuver a bag
of puzzle pieces
up a second ladder.
When you get to the top,
you'll use those pieces
to solve a 75-piece
Survivor puzzle.
First to finish wins immunity,
is guaranteed
a spot in the final four.
Losers, Tribal Council where
somebody's dream of winning
Survivor 41
will come to an end.
In addition, playing for reward.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Whoa.
-Yeah.
-ERIKA: Yeah.
-Steak.
-Ooh.
-PROBST: Steak, veggies,
bread and wine.
-Oh, my God.
-Wow.
-Ooh.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Big fuel to get through
these last few days.
All right, let's get
to your advantage. Erika,
you will start with four rungs
on each of the ladders
already completed.
-Okay.
-Wow.
-PROBST: Sound good?
-Great. Awesome.
All right, we'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
-Let's do it.
-Here we go!
All right, here we go
for a guaranteed spot
in the final four and a reward
that might help you get
to three.
Survivors ready.
Go!
First phase
of this challenge is,
you've got to collect all
of your rope rungs.
♪ ♪
Erika has a big head start
because
four of her rope rungs are
already off.
They're on the ladder.
♪ ♪
Everybody else has got
to get all seven,
so it's Erika
out in the early lead.
Erika has her three. She's off
to build her first ladder.
Ricard whacking at 'em.
Deshawn doing a nice job.
There goes Xander.
It is Heather in last,
a familiar spot,
but what is also familiar
is Heather never stops trying.
Erika with that big advantage of
having her first four rope rungs
already up there,
but here comes Ricard.
Now Xander.
♪ ♪
Heather's got all seven down.
Now she's got to collect them.
Deshawn working on his last two.
Once you build that, Erika,
get on up and start working
on your second ladder.
It's Ricard
with another rope rung,
Xander with another rope rung.
And another advantage for Erika.
The first four rungs
of her second ladder are
also already completed.
Here comes Deshawn,
and here comes Heather.
We got a challenge.
It is Erika all alone up here
on the second stage.
Xander has got to go back.
He is one rung short.
He left one hanging,
a potentially fatal mistake
on day 24 and final five.
Now Xander's got to really work
to get back in this.
Here comes Ricard.
He has won three
individual immunity challenges.
Love to win a fourth.
Erika is whipping through this.
She will get
to the puzzle first.
Question is,
will her advantage be enough?
It's Erika up top. She can start
working on that puzzle.
Xander made quick work of that
mistake. He's back in it now.
Here comes Deshawn.
Everybody moving.
Erika all alone working
on that puzzle.
Ricard trying to get up here.
Ricard's good.
Heather now reaching
the second stage.
That-away, Heather.
Represent.
Kids will be proud
watching Mom push through.
Deshawn is up.
There, he's got it.
Xander right on that last piece.
Xander has his.
It is a mighty big puzzle
so you want to get here
'cause you will be in it.
Heather has hers. Heather now
going to be in on the puzzle.
All five now working
on the puzzle.
It is Heather, Ricard, Erika,
Deshawn and Xander fighting to
stay in a million-dollar game.
You win this challenge,
you are guaranteed
a spot in the final four.
This is a huge challenge to win.
PROBST: Erika has been on fire
this entire challenge.
She earned an advantage
this morning.
She put that advantage
to quick work,
and she has been attacking
the puzzle.
Right next to her is Ricard
working equally fast,
trying to catch up.
Deshawn is fighting
to stay in this.
Xander taking a different
approach-- building
his puzzle vertically.
Heather has a lot of pieces
in the puzzle area,
-but very few
of them are together.
-Very few.
PROBST:
You got to stay focused
on your game
and hope
that somebody hits a roadblock
because it happens,
they get stuck.
Or there's one piece
in the wrong spot.
Erika with another piece.
She can see it coming together.
Xander's now
put his puzzle flat,
and now we can see his progress.
It's pretty good.
Everybody's in it right now,
except for Heather.
Ricard with another piece
and another piece
and another piece.
Erika with another piece.
The pace has picked up.
It's Erika and Ricard
side by side right now.
Erika's still in the lead, but
Ricard is making a go of it.
Erika with another piece, Ricard
trying to put another piece.
Erika is down
to a handful of pieces.
Erika down to two pieces left.
-For the win.
-Jeff, Jeff!
Erika wins individual immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final four.
Thanks, guys. Oh, my God,
if I didn't win this one,
I would have died. (laughs)
Erika, come on over.
Thanks, Jeff.
-Still a dream come true.
-Yeah?
What a day for you.
You start the morning
by earning an advantage.
Then you put that advantage
to the best use you can
by winning today's challenge.
You are guaranteed a spot
in the final four,
which means, at the very least,
you get a chance
to make fire to get to three.
This is a big spot to be in.
In addition,
you've won steak,
veggies, bread and wine
-back at camp... for two.
-Wow. Wow.
-Oh, my gosh,
-You have a big decision
because you are either
gonna choose somebody
who you are wining
and dining before
you send them to the jury,
hoping to buy a vote, or
you are fueling
your competition,
hoping to buy some loyalty.
Who is going to join you
for this meal?
I mean, we had a tough
Tribal Council,
so I have to pick Heather.
-PROBST: Heather.
-ERIKA: Yeah.
-PROBST: Come on over.
-Thank you.
Love you, Mama.
All right, afternoon meal
for you two.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations. You are safe
and guaranteed a spot
in the final four.
As for the rest of you,
after 24 days,
one of your dreams
of winning Survivor 41
will come to an end.
Grab your stuff.
Head back. See you tonight
at Tribal. Congrats.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Thank you.
XANDER: I was hoping
that I could win, but,
I mean, hey, I've got the idol
so I don't have to worry,
and I don't care if Erika
and Heather hate each other,
or if Deshawn and Erika
hate each other.
It doesn't matter
'cause Ricard's not immune,
he's an open target.
It's a no-brainer
that we're gonna try
and get
target numero uno out.
♪ ♪
Oh, my gosh.
This is, like, a real meal.
And listen,
I wanted to talk
to you about, like,
all the stuff
that went down yesterday.
When I saw how hurt you were,
that's, like,
what really hurt me,
because I feel like
our unlikely friendship
is, like,
one of the-the greatest gifts
that I got from being out here.
So, I would have been,
like, so upset
if, like, I messed that up.
What hurt me was
the way Deshawn
displayed it all to everybody.
Mm-hmm.
I-I just...
I'm really sorry for, like...
No. No harsh feelings with you.
-No. You didn't.
-If I, like,
-for hurting you or anything.
-You didn't.
But for him to do that to you
hurt me.
I didn't like anything
about Tribal last night.
And today,
I woke up broken, and...
...having lunch
with a good friend
really changed that around
for me.
I never thought that I'd have
someone that I could, like...
that I could trust.
-It makes me think how lonely
this game would be without you.
-Mm-hmm.
Cheers.
-Last two of us standing.
-To the two girls left.
-We did it.
-HEATHER: I didn't realize
I'd meet such good people
that I am looking forward
to staying friends with
when this game is over.
I guess people didn't see us
as strong,
because I'm the old lady and
you're the little, tiny girl.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm.
And we have just carried
each other through.
Of course, I'd like to see me
go to the end instead of her,
um, but we respect
each other's game.
-I'm in heaven.
-Oh, my gosh.
Heather, I... if we can get to
both of us pleading our case...
Here we are.
I-I think that, like,
if Ricard wasn't such a threat
I would love
to go to the end with him,
'cause I actually love him,
I actually trust him.
I know he had our backs.
But, truth,
I'd rather him go and win
than Deshawn win
and play into Deshawn's game.
We can't go with Deshawn.
And I'm pissed at Deshawn.
I am, too.
ERIKA:
It's almost poetic
how Heather and I have grown
from people
that were disregarded
to people who are now
calling the shots.
-Cheers.
-Love you.
-Ditto.
I don't mind
being a little tipsy for Tribal.
Tonight, Xander is safe
because he has an idol,
and tonight would be
the last opportunity
for Xander to play it.
Nice.
So, the chopping block
is between Ricard,
someone who I really respect,
but who I think
could beat me in the end,
versus Deshawn, who is someone
who really pissed me off.
What's your plan?
We're just writing down
each other's names?
See who wins?
Guess that's all we can do.
I have to write your name down,
after all that... (chuckles)
So I'm sorry.
Ricard's a big threat.
I've said it about 3,000 times.
I have no more saliva left
in my mouth
to speak about Ricard
and how big of a threat he is.
-Oh.
-We had a good time.
-I'm happy for y'all.
-We're at five.
There's no loyalty.
It's who can you beat
at the end,
and Ricard's
not one of those people.
And if they decide
to vote me out, shame on them,
because they're not gonna win
at the end.
-Okay, when this...
-Oh!
(Erika gasps)
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Well, we're voting
for each other.
You and Deshawn
are voting for each other?
-Right.
-Yeah. Um...
So, what are you...
-You can be honest with me.
-Yeah.
Am I going home?
Do you think?
I don't know. I mean,
I think it's pretty clear
-I hate Deshawn.
-Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
RICARD:
It floored me.
I'm reading Erika's face
and reading the fact
that she's saying
she's conflicted,
and she doesn't know
what she's gonna do--
which shouldn't be the case
at all.
You've been, like,
a badass ally,
but it's, like, I'm sure
you can appreciate it,
it's, like,
a rough decision for us.
Yeah.
What?
What are you talking about?
Deshawn tore her apart
at Tribal yesterday,
but she's saying
she's on the fence.
It makes me sick to my stomach.
I'm a day and a half away
from winning.
I don't want to leave this game.
I am not giving up.
I'm not at all.
I'm still gonna throw out
all the little things I can,
which I've been doing.
So, what do you think?
I love Deshawn,
but I think he's a liability.
But, you know,
you're a huge threat.
I think you'll win
if you go to the end.
But I feel like
Deshawn's gonna win this.
You can promise it by voting
him out tonight, Heather.
(both chuckle)
What's wrong with you?
I'm hearing you,
but it is complicated.
-I really could see it
going either way.
-Yeah.
I assume you will vote with me.
-And...
because he really, like,
screwed her over last night.
She's-she's angry at him. Yeah.
I'm sure you can understand
the dilemma I face.
One thousand percent.
In my head,
I know what I should do,
but it's also, like, hard,
'cause it's, like...
a trusted ally.
You wouldn't be fully to blame
to vote me out,
because of how
you feel like I did you,
but, at the end of the day,
you have a better chance
against me than him.
ERIKA:
Of course, it makes sense
to get rid of Ricard tonight.
He's, by far, the biggest threat
to win the game.
Deshawn is definitely not
as big of a threat to win,
but, after last Tribal Council,
I just can't trust Deshawn.
If I win
the last immunity challenge,
-I will bring you to the end.
-Okay.
And that's the truth.
If you win tomorrow,
who are you gonna take with you?
If you save me,
I told you this entire time
I was gonna take you.
I've never been able
to work with him.
He always just throws
unnecessary fireworks.
Someone like that doesn't really
deserve to go farther,
in my opinion.
Did you say...
did they say
they're voting Deshawn?
RICARD:
I think they are
kind of on the fence.
XANDER:
No matter what happens, man,
three more days,
and we get to see our families.
Am I still gonna get to visit
as Uncle Xander?
Two babies.
Two babies?
No way.
Oh, my God.
-Congratulations, man.
-Thanks.
Little boy.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
(sniffles)
So, I mean, he could already
be here, I don't know,
but I'm excited to find out.
I gave up a lot to be here--
which everybody does--
but I gave up, like, a life
moment, potentially, to be here.
Like, a huge one.
The first moment of
my baby's life to win this game.
I wanted to make it worth it
coming out here.
You did. I mean...
Yeah, I do. I think I did.
XANDER:
Ricard's an obvious vote.
He's the big threat here,
but we've developed this really
strong bond over the game,
and it does tug
at my heartstrings.
I-I really just hate to see him
in such pain.
-Like...
-Still a chance I'm staying.
Yeah.
I'm definitely debating,
you know, whether
I want to stick with my heart
and keep the guy who I love
around.
And if everybody's voting
for Ricard,
then I'm the only
one that can save him.
You look intense.
'Cause it's, like...
I could save you with the idol.
That would...
They would lose their minds.
-Can you imagine?
They'd be so shocked.
-I know.
I don't want to go home
with a souvenir,
so I'll probably play it anyway,
but there's a possibility
that I could
really change up the game
by playing it for Ricard.
Keep Ricard, because
he's someone that's loyal to me.
If anything,
that would make it look like
I'm the one
controlling the vote.
You would put another thing
on your resume.
(chuckles)
Using your idol on somebody.
The most important thing
to know is that, like,
you know,
I'm still undecided right now.
-Of course.
-Right, like,
I just got to figure out
what's best for my game, and...
Going into tonight's Tribal,
if I want to save him, I can,
and I think
it would make a big statement.
As long as you're not
changing your mind on me.
But do I want to make
that million-dollar gamble
that I would beat him
in a final Tribal?
It's hard to say.
♪ ♪
This is my showcase to the jury.
This is when
I finally send my message
that I'm the one who's
taking the reins in this game.
♪ ♪
All right. So, Deshawn,
last Tribal Council,
you said,
"Need to take out Ricard.
Keeps winning."
Today, Erika wins,
and Ricard's vulnerable.
So were you at camp going,
"We got to
take out Ricard,
'cause he's gonna keep winning"?
Um, I mean, so that was the
premise of last Tribal Council,
to kind of plant that seed.
So, I didn't have
to say a lot of that.
I think everybody here was kind
of on the same page with that,
and because
the seed was already planted.
Xander,
that feels like it's done,
according to Deshawn.
Uh, I don't know about that.
I can attest to the fact
that I was sitting
in the middle
of Deshawn and Ricard,
and it felt a lot like
high noon in the Wild West.
And, you know, draw.
I was like the tumbleweed
bouncing awkwardly
in the middle,
and they both know
they're on the chopping block
for different reasons,
so they were
gunning for each other.
So, Heather, Xander
describes it as high noon,
the Wild, Wild West.
-Were you open to hearing
both their stories?
-Oh, absolutely.
I'm open to listening
to everything.
I mean, the more information you
have, the more choices. Yeah.
PROBST:
How about you, Erika?
Yeah, we're at that point in
the game now where it's, like,
things that normally would be
a compliment in real life,
like, oh,
someone is a trusted ally,
could be, like,
a bad thing on Survivor.
And things that could be
a bad thing in real life,
like somebody cannot be trusted,
could be a good thing
on Survivor.
It's kind of like what's good
and bad get flipped around,
and any decision is a tough one.
PROBST:
So, Ricard,
you have been the topic,
quite a few times,
about he's gonna win
if he gets to the end,
and here you are now vulnerable.
All it takes is three
of these people to vote for you
and it's over.
Well...
I think I've played
a really good game.
It's hard, you know?
We get back to camp last night,
they are rattled.
She's almost in tears
from what he said at Tribal.
It's really hard.
And I just feel like...
To do so well in the game,
it's just...
I've been struggling
and nobody even knows it,
and it's just...
it's-it's really hard.
PROBST:
You've been struggling
with things in the game
that people don't know about?
Last year, my husband and I,
we had got pregnant again,
and I didn't know...
if it was gonna be okay and
everything was gonna be fine,
and Survivor
kept getting pushed back,
and COVID and everything.
And then I finally get the call.
And I don't know what to do,
'cause it's, like,
my dream to be here.
But my baby is due next week.
Like, I didn't want
to tell anyone,
'cause what would they
think of me?
Like, "Oh, you're leaving."
Like, my baby, literally,
could already be born right now,
and I don't know.
I've been really struggling.
And...
I'm still so proud of myself
that I made it this far.
And I did a really
damn good job.
Deshawn, is this hard for you?
Because you are similar
to Ricard
in that you're very honest
and open with your emotions.
And you will say
when you're hurting
or when you're frustrated.
And Ricard is having
that moment right now.
He's being very open.
"I don't like this.
It hurts my heart."
Yeah, I mean,
I definitely understand Ricard.
I think Ricard and I
have had a very tumultuous
"frenemy-ship,"
I guess you'd call it,
out here.
And he sees my heart,
I think, when we talk.
And I see his.
I know he's a good dude.
I can hear the hurt
in his voice,
and I feel bad,
but at the end of the day,
that's my friend,
and I wish him the best of luck.
PROBST:
Xander, if a group of people
have enough numbers,
and they want to get rid of you,
you can't stop 'em, unless you
have an idol or the necklace.
How do you reconcile
that in terms of,
"But that's the way it goes.
"We have the numbers.
You are going home,
and you can't stop it"?
Yeah, I mean, Ricard's fought
so hard this entire game,
and he's just been pegged
as this guy who's in charge,
and, you know,
choosing who's going home,
but Ricard and I talk
because we've grown so close
-over these days.
-Bromance.
It, yeah...
Th-There's a bit of a bromance.
It's kind of great.
I love it. (laughs)
And, yeah, it just...
it was really hard to know
that people have just
put him in this position
where he's got his back
against the wall,
and there's
nothing that he can do.
And I feel for him.
Can I just say one little
thing which is funny to me?
Everyone's saying,
"Ricard runs the show."
If I was running the show,
Deshawn would be gone,
and I would be in final four.
I think Deshawn's gonna get
more votes
than any of the three of them.
Now, Erika, it's Ricard
who's got the guns out,
saying, "I got nothing to lose."
The truth bombs.
Like, I-I don't blame him
for having the guns out,
but because perception
is so important
and because of the perception
that people have
when it comes to Ricard,
unfortunately, like, that's a-a
big consideration of the game.
PROBST:
So, Ricard, why don't you
write the last paragraph?
What has this experience been?
Because it sounds like you came
out here with a lot of emotion
that you had to keep bottled up,
and that you've learned things
about yourself and you're gonna
go home to be a different person
than when you came out here.
Yeah, um...
I just didn't think
I would do so well.
I did not think
that I was capable.
And I'm actually, like,
really, kick-ass at Survivor.
-(chuckles) Like...
I'm good at it.
-Yes. Yeah.
PROBST:
And, Ricard,
I can see the pride
you have in yourself.
And that's worthy,
and it's cool to witness,
because even you are finding
moments of vulnerability
where you want to share
a little more about who you are.
That's because of what
you've put yourself through.
That's because you did
decide to come out here.
Something in you said, "I need
this. I'm gonna be a dad.
"I'm gonna be a better
husband, as a result of this,
'cause I need it."
And here you are.
If you don't win,
it can still be a victory.
It may not be about
the million dollars.
It may be about this moment
right here
where you're feeling
okay enough...
...pat yourself on the back
a little bit.
RICARD:
It is weird, but today,
genuinely, I had a moment
of I, literally, can be
one of the Survivor greats,
one of the greatest players
in this game,
without being a winner.
And I actually do
fully believe I am.
Oh, some of our best players
will never win the game.
It's just the way it goes.
I appreciate your vulnerability.
And this is a rare chance
for me,
because usually I feel like
there's a blind side coming,
and that you're
putting on a show
and it's gonna be somebody else.
I don't feel that tonight.
Could be wrong, but...
Shall we get to the vote?
All right, it is time to vote.
Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody
has an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Yeah, Jeff.
Oh, oh, oh.
Today marks the 20th day
of me having it
and the last time I can play it.
I figured I'd do it some justice
since it saved me a couple times
and even saved a couple
of my friends along the way.
So I don't need to use it.
But I also don't need
a, uh, souvenir.
PROBST:
Playing this for yourself?
-Yeah.
-Thanks, Xander.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Xander will
not count. I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Deshawn.
Ricard. One vote-- Deshawn,
one vote-- Ricard.
Ricard. Two votes-- Ricard,
one vote-- Deshawn.
Fourteenth person voted out
and the seventh member
of our jury--
Ricard. That's three.
That's enough.
-Need to bring me your torch.
-Good job, Ricard.
-ERIKA: Bye, Ricard.
-HEATHER: Ricard.
-DESHAWN: Good game, dude.
-Good luck. Good game.
-Good luck.
(groans)
We love you, man.
Ricard, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
-Strong work, man. Take care.
-Bye, Ricard.
-Bye.
Bye, Ricard.
Dang, dang, dang.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
-Good night.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Thank you.
XANDER:
Thanks, Jeff.
I think this experience
was pretty kick-ass.
Like, I did a phenomenal job,
I made really good friends,
and I am not leaving with
any regrets, and I don't have
to walk out of this wishing I
had done something differently.
It's going
to be great watching this
with my husband and my two kids.
It really hasn't even sunk in
that I'm about
to have another baby
and the fact that
I'm just gonna be
a Survivor dad.
And that's just really,
really amazing and great.
DESHAWN:
Final four, dude.
-XANDER: Final four.
-ERIKA: One of them will win
the title of Sole Survivor.
XANDER:
Oh, my God, stop.
Whenever in our lives
are we gonna have a 25% chance
at a million dollars?
ERIKA:
Oh, my gosh.
Knowing that I'm in the top four
is, like, so surreal
'cause it's not necessarily,
like, a vote
that can take me out.
Wow, guys. Congrats.
-XANDER: Oh, my God.
-HEATHER: Seriously.
ERIKA:
At the very least, I know I can
compete in fire.
And I made fire
while I was on Exile.
So being
in the top three is, like,
so much within my grasp.
-Are y'all okay here?
-I'm fine wherever.
-Will...?
ERIKA:
But, honestly, like, I just want
to get a good night's sleep
so that whatever gets thrown
at me
tomorrow, I'm ready for it.
Yeah.
ERIKA:
Mm-hmm.
Good night, Final Four.
(wind rumbling)
-DESHAWN: Felt a few drops.
-ERIKA: Raining is, like,
-really not good.
-XANDER: Yeah.
It's sprinkling. I mean,
there's just this one cloud.
-(loud thunderclaps)
-(Erika gasps)
(rolling thunder)
XANDER:
It's pouring rain,
I'm soaking wet, I'm cold,
I'm hungry,
but, hey, I don't care.
I feel like a rock star, man.
Like, "Hello, Fiji!
Are you ready to rock?!
One, two,
one, two, three, four."
(crackling thunder)
XANDER:
Everyone else is suffering, and
the empathetic person in me
wants to feel for these people.
The gamer in me,
the true competitor,
is like, "If they're gonna
break, hell, yeah.
Bring it on.
Is this all you've got?"
(loud thunderclaps)
(wind howling)
(insects trilling)
-XANDER: Oh, man.
-Oh, it was so bad.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, well, we made it through.
-That was the worst,
the worst night.
-(Heather laughs)
-XANDER: We made it.
-Still shaking. Still shaking.
Yeah. Day twenty-four's sleep
was the hardest sleep.
Who would have thunk it?
Like, we were so close.
-HEATHER: That's true.
-Just sitting here
shivering all freaking night
with no shelter,
no tarp, just rain.
Maybe Mother Nature,
last night, was trying
to slap us across the face
and say, "Listen,
don't sleep, don't take your
foot off the gas, keep going."
Like, I'm literally
at the end of the race,
and I can see myself winning
if I can just
conquer this last part of it.
(knife tapping)
-You need to go long and slip.
-Yup.
DESHAWN:
But the problem is, I've tried
to make fire with flint.
I have failed miserably
every single time,
so I'm hoping I don't end up
at the fire-making challenge
because
it could be kind of embarrassing
if I can't make fire.
HEATHER:
Got it, got it,
DESHAWN:
But I can't
focus my attention on that.
I just need to win
the freaking challenge,
and that's it.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
-You again.
-I'm waiting for it.
-Hi.
-Oh. I didn't think
I'd see you today.
Yeah. Hi.
-Thanks, Heather.
I've gotten used to the "hi's."
-How are you?
-Oh.
-That never happens.
Are you gonna miss us
when it's over?
-Yes.
-ERIKA: Good.
PROBST:
Tell me about last night.
I know it rained where I was.
It rained where we were a lot.
We all got hit.
You couldn't not get hit,
and we, obviously,
didn't have a shelter or a tarp
so we were just kind of, like,
trying to stay warm,
and honestly,
it was okay 'cause we knew
it was the last two of nights,
-and it's just a part
of the experience.
-HEATHER: Yeah.
A little bit
of a badge of honor?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Definitely. Definitely.
All right, ready to get to your
final immunity challenge?
-Yeah.
-Yup.
-Let's do it.
First things first, Erika.
Take back the necklace.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
For the last time,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to navigate
across a curved walkway
while stacking blocks
on a wobbly platform.
First person
to stack all their blocks
and spell "Final 3"
is in the final three.
You will get a chance
to plead your case
to the jury about why you
deserve the title
of Sole Survivor
and the million dollars
that comes with it.
In addition, you have power.
You will decide
which person sits next to you
in that second spot
and who you force to make fire
for that third and final spot.
Big power, big decisions.
First, you got to win.
We'll draw for spots
and get it going.
-Here we go.
-ERIKA: Okay.
♪ ♪
Here we go.
Final immunity challenge
of the season, guarantees
you a spot in the final three,
the place you want to be.
Survivors ready.
Go.
Out of the gate,
you can move quickly
putting that first block.
You're gonna be spelling
"Final 3"
from the bottom to the top, but
the longer this challenge goes,
the pace will slow down
dramatically.
And right away, Deshawn gets
an idea of how this works.
Xander drops, too.
That's part of it.
You're trying to figure out
that balance of tension
on the rope
versus how fast your feet
are moving 'cause you want both.
You want to move quickly,
but you want to move
with some certainty that
you are keeping a balance point.
With every block you add,
obviously,
it gets much more difficult
'cause that stack starts
to grow,
and that balance becomes
really important.
You drop one, you drop them all.
So you could make a lot
of progress
and have one little slipup,
and you're back
to the beginning.
So a big decision in this
challenge is what do you favor?
Pace, where you're moving
a little faster, little riskier,
or do you slow it down
and hope somebody else drops,
and you try to get through
this entire challenge
without ever dropping?
Heather loses everything.
She's got to start over.
That means you got
to take all the blocks back,
grab the first one,
head back out.
Here comes Deshawn with his
third block. Deshawn is in it.
Here comes Xander heading back
with his fourth letter--
the end.
Erika ready to reach
for that fourth block.
She's got to keep an eye
on what she's built so far.
You got to be close enough
to reach it without tipping it.
Xander places the "N."
He has four.
Xander is now in the lead.
Here comes Erika
with her fourth letter.
It is possible to do this entire
challenge and never drop,
but it requires precision.
You cannot make a mistake.
Deshawn drops.
He's got to start again.
There comes Xander
with his fifth block.
Erika's still heading
back for her fifth block,
so Xander is increasing
his lead right now.
Xander now heading back
for his sixth and final block.
This is where
it gets very dangerous.
♪ ♪
He's got a lot of time.
He doesn't have to panic,
knowing he has a one-block lead.
And Erika drops, and that
opens the door for Xander
to control the entire pace
of this challenge right now.
A huge mistake by Erika.
She has to start over.
And now Heather drops.
She's got to start again.
The only person close right now
is Deshawn,
with only two letters.
This is Xander's challenge
to win,
but he's got to win it.
Xander now heading back out
with his sixth and final block.
You can see Heather's pace
moving faster now.
Erika trying to get back in it.
Everybody is hoping
that Xander drops
'cause that is their only shot.
Xander places the last letter.
He has spelled "Final 3."
Now he just has
to get back to the finish.
Erika moving quickly now.
Places her third block.
Deshawn coming back
with his fourth block.
Anything can happen
in this challenge.
You got to keep fighting
as if you got a shot.
Xander very slow, very steady.
It doesn't take much
with six blocks to lose it all.
This could be
a million-dollar challenge.
-(gasps) Oh, my God.
-Heather drops.
Got to start over.
It's Erika with four,
Deshawn with four,
Xander with all six, and he is
about two feet away from earning
a spot in the final three.
Got to have both feet
behind that tape.
Can he get
those last few steps?
Heather places
her second block.
Erika heading back
for her fifth.
Deshawn heading back
for his fifth.
Xander close to that pain.
He's got one foot
halfway over the line.
Very close.
The first foot is over.
Just got to get
that second foot over.
Half an inch back.
Xander does it!
Xander earns immunity!
He's got a guaranteed spot
in the final three.
After 25 days in Fiji,
Xander will have a shot
at pleading his case
-to the jury...
-Good job.
about why he deserves
the title
of Sole Survivor
and the million dollars
that goes along with it.
And he has power tonight
at Tribal.
Great performance. Wow.
Xander, come on over.
(sniffles)
What's the emotion right now?
It feels like I've been holding
my breath this entire game,
and I just got to take that
first breath of air, you know?
It's-it's like breathing.
Just, I...
Oh, man. I don't even know,
like... This is just
such an unreal moment.
You're putting the necklace
around me at final four,
and-and that's just, like,
the craziest sentence
I've ever said.
Like, way crazier
than the butterfly thing.
-(laughter)
-PROBST: Well, all right.
Now that the challenges
are done,
let's have this moment
because you're 20.
You were just a teenager
yesterday.
And not long before that,
you were the kid at home going,
"One day, when I'm old enough,
I'm going to be on Survivor."
And here you are, and now you
have a shot to win this game.
Can you still see that
little kid?
I mean, yeah,
I can see that little kid,
and he wasn't even the kid
who was like,
"I'm gonna be
on Survivor one day."
He was the kid who was like,
"I could never be on Survivor."
And I wish I could go back
in time and give him a big hug
and tell him,
things are going to be fine.
You know, if you work hard,
you can get it.
You got it.
You are guaranteed a spot.
-Yeah, bro, give me a hug.
-Yeah.
-DESHAWN: Yeah!
-Uh, I love it.
-Yeah.
Congratulations. I can feel
how big this is for you.
And it's fun to be a part of it.
You've accomplished the goal
almost all the way.
One thing left to do-- win.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council
where somebody will be safe, and
somebody will be making fire.
-Got it. Thank you.
-XANDER: Thanks, Jeff.
-ERIKA: Congratulations.
-HEATHER: You did good.
-(Xander whispers indistinctly)
ERIKA:
I'm really happy for Xander,
but at the same time,
it is a bit of a heartbreaker
for me because
I really, really wanted
to win this one
so I could control my fate.
But Xander won,
and I'm nervous
because he's been a bit
of a wild card.
So I really don't know
how this one's gonna go.
(birds squawking)
Thanks, guys.
-It's major, bro.
-Good job.
Congratulations, Xander.
XANDER:
Final immunity challenge.
I pulled it off.
From a game standpoint,
this means that I've gotten
to the final three
and that I've got my chance
at the million.
But on a much
more personal level,
having this necklace around me
is bigger than that.
I've always loved anything about
pushing myself in competition
because when I was growing up,
I was insecure.
I was chubby.
I was not proud of who I was,
but I wanted to change.
I wanted to be the version
of myself that I dreamed of.
So in ninth grade, I decided
that I would go out
for the cross country team.
At first, everybody saw me
as the chubby kid
who wanted to lose weight
on the team.
But after three races,
I had dropped two minutes
and knocked someone off
the top 50 board.
I went all the way
to the Nationals,
and we became the best team
in Florida history.
And I learned that through
hard work and discipline,
there's nothing you can't do.
So to have this necklace
around me means
that I got there,
that I'm that man
that I dreamed I could be.
We made the whole season in,
like, the hardest season
-of all time.
-ERIKA: I know.
-DESHAWN: Crazy.
Well, I don't want to be
the first one, but Xander,
I just wanted to talk
and see where your head's at
-so I can prepare my mind
for whatever is coming.
-No.
Yeah, it makes sense.
Let's do some individual talks.
HEATHER:
And I'll go next.
Tonight, Xander is 1,000%
in the final three.
And so now, the major topic is,
who are you gonna bring in,
and who's doing fire?
I've tried to make fire
early on, and I struggled a lot,
and so I'm hoping
and praying I don't have to
make this freaking fire.
I want to hear your pitch.
Like, you know,
why should I keep you around?
-Oh, thanks, dude. Um, okay.
-Yeah.
So, I would say that you stand
a really good chance of winning,
but I think that you kind of
would decrease your chances
just a bit
if you brought Erika to the end.
She would be
a tough person to beat.
This decision is
about perception.
I have the power
to show the jury
how I'm playing my game
and show them that
all my decisions
were calculated.
I'm a smart person,
and they need to know that.
I'm willing to make fire,
and if I can't,
I go home, and I go home happy.
I don't think so.
At the same time, intuition is
something that's powerful
and often overlooked, so,
whatever my heart rests on and
my head agrees with is something
that I want to go with.
If you think that it's better
to throw me in, I'll go in.
If you think
you want to take me,
I think there's, like, merit
to you taking me.
Okay. I think you can go back up
'cause I think
I've made my mind.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah, I'm taking you.
-You're take...?
Are you kidding? What?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Oh, my God. Really?
-Yeah, yeah, you're good.
ERIKA:
That was not
what I was expecting at all.
I thought I was 100% going
into fire with Deshawn,
so I was shocked.
But inside, I'm like, "Wait.
Do I suck? Am I beatable?
Like, why does he want
to take me?"
But if this means that
I get to the end
and at least plead my case,
then I'll take it.
You might want to practice
just in case.
-Like...
-Yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah.
-No, I'll respect
the-the process and practice.
-Yeah.
XANDER:
I think Erika has built
a good resume,
so, why would I give her
the opportunity to have
a flashy, fire-making move
at the end?
She's the only person here who
I know for sure can make fire
because she did it
so many times in Exile.
So I was saying
that I think you and Heather
are gonna face off.
-Okay. For sure.
-Yeah.
Yeah, but I-I told Erika
to also practice
just 'cause it's a huge decision
-and you know?
-DESHAWN: Okay.
DESHAWN:
Being in the fire-making
challenge
was the last thing
I wanted to do.
But all season long,
we've got ingrained in our head,
you're gonna have
to work for everything.
And so,
me having to earn this spot
at the final Tribal Council
is, like,
picture-perfect for this season.
So, give me a knife, give me
a flint and let me go to work.
Like, let me figure out
how the hell I'm gonna
pull this out, and I'm not
gonna stop until I do.
Because you never know
what Heather can pull out
of her pocket.
She may go out there
with a freaking piece of flint
and-and knife
and strike it one time,
and-and poof.
HEATHER:
I came into this game
as an absolute underdog,
the underdog of all underdogs.
But I worked hard to get here,
and my social game
has been really good.
Here we go.
And now I'm going
to earn my spot in the top three
by winning
this fire-making challenge.
It's happening. There you go.
XANDER:
You got it.
That was, like, six seconds.
Wow.
I'd love to see Heather
in the end because
she's gonna talk
about the exact same things
that Erika is gonna bring up,
because they worked together
this entire game.
So, to have her come out on top
would take out Deshawn.
It'll make Erika just look weak.
Yeah!
And if that happens,
I don't see how I couldn't win.
Oh.
I'm definitely frustrated.
I can get sparks with the flint
in-in the knife consistently.
Like, my spark game is crazy.
But there's no height
on my fire,
and it's really frustrating me
because it's like
me doing a six-inch fire is
not gonna get the job done.
All these sticks,
and nothing can...
Are you joking?
Is this a joke?
For me, this fire-making
challenge means the world.
I see the million dollars.
I can, like, almost reach out
and touch it,
but if I can't start a fire,
I'll never have the opportunity
to grab
what's rightfully mine,
so, it sucks.
It took me a long time on Exile.
A long time.
XANDER:
Oh, man. I thought since
she spent so much time on Exile
that she knew how to make fire.
What the hell?!
She can't make fire?
Oh, my God.
It's like, "What?"
Aw, man. I...
Oh!
She's just advertising the fact
that I could take her out
and make a big move.
Thank you.
Is this a ploy? Is she just
doing this to, like, tempt me?
I thought
everything was figured out,
but I cannot believe
she just showed me
that she can't make fire.
Always said, until she came up
and started practicing,
and she can't do it.
So, I can easily step down
and just do the fire
and get her out.
After a whole day
of solid decision-making
and feeling confident,
suddenly, I go back
to being that kid
who's not confident in himself
and so unsure of himself.
XANDER:
In this situation,
all you can do is stress.
I either live with the regret
of knowing
that I could have done more,
or I leave it all out there,
and it's possible
that I get sent home packing.
It's tricky,
but of course it's gonna be.
It's a million-dollar decision.
♪ ♪
So, Xander, are you aware,
as you're walking up,
that the jury is going
to be craning their necks
to see who has the individual
immunity necklace?
XANDER:
Yeah, of course.
I mean, from a strategic
point of view,
this means that I get to make
a make-or-break decision
that determines a lot
in this game.
So Deshawn,
what did you see go down?
'Cause now, everybody's got
to want to talk to him
and pitch their case.
What did you want
to have happen?
My ideal final three
would have been to sit next
to Xander and Heather
at the end.
So, my recommendation
to Xander was,
"Hey, throw Erika into fire,
and let the best man
or woman win."
Um, unfortunately, I didn't
win the necklace, so I have to
rock with whatever
he has planned tonight.
-How about you, Heather?
-Our conversation
was a little different.
It was,
"Throw me into fire-making
because I'm up
"for the challenge.
So no hard feelings.
Whatever you got to do,
I'm ready."
PROBST:
Xander, were you surprised
by any
of the three in terms of their
approach or their attitude?
Not really. I mean, they've got
their own biases in it,
and I wasn't paying
too much attention because
I've already been trying
to make my decision
before it even happened.
And a lot of that actually
stems from Deshawn over here.
His truth bomb
really told me a lot.
When he criticized Erika's game,
the jury seemed
to applaud and agree with him,
so,
that's something
that I took to note.
PROBST:
And so, Xander, you're saying,
"I'm looking and trying
to get perceptions
"of what I'm hearing,
and what I've been hearing
over the days,"
which is a very smart move
because
this is a game
of perceptions.
And the jury,
tomorrow night, is going
to take their perceptions
and put 'em
smack dab on top of you
with million-dollar votes.
That's why that position
you're in is powerful,
-but also risky.
-Exactly. So it seems
that the jury doesn't
respect Erika's game,
and they don't respect
Heather's game.
And I get it. They've played
very similar games.
But I feel like
Heather is someone
that they've...
pinned as this goat.
You know, this person
who's been dragged
to the end. They don't respect
how she's played.
But I don't think Heather's
a goat. I disagree completely.
I think that she's someone
who defies what people
pin her to the stereotype
of being the old, frail lady,
when she's actually so strong,
and she's got
this youthful vigor to her.
And I think that she might
prove people wrong,
that she's a badass.
PROBST:
Erika, one
of the toughest things
about being in the spot
Xander is in
is that the jury,
even unintentionally,
can give a signal
that might be true,
-might not be true.
-ERIKA: Oh, of course.
I think that even though
we can't talk to the jury, like,
there is still information
we can get from how they react.
But in the end like,
"Hey, you won. I respect
"whatever decision you make.
If you take me, you take me.
If not, I'll do my best
to make fire."
PROBST:
All right, so, Xander,
the question is,
who are you going
to take with you
to the final three
in that second spot,
and which other
two remaining players
will have to battle for fire?
♪ ♪
I'm taking Erika with me,
and Deshawn and Heather
are going to face off in fire.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
So we have our decision. Erika,
you're going to the final three.
ERIKA:
I respect the decision,
and what makes Survivor
so complicated is,
Xander is giving me good news,
but at the same time,
I'm like, "Oh, but then,
if he wants to bring me,
that's probably bad news
for how people perceive me."
But in the end, like,
I'm excited for tomorrow
to sit beside you
and to be able to plead my case.
Question left is,
who will be in that third spot?
-Good luck.
-PROBST: Will it be
Deshawn, or will it be Heather?
♪ ♪
All right, Deshawn, Heather,
I wish you both luck.
-All right.
-Take your spots.
Deshawn, you can
take the blue,
Heather, you can take yellow.
Okay.
PROBST:
You both have
the same exact supplies.
You have to make a fire
that burns long enough
and high enough to burn through
the rope and raise the flag.
(exhales)
Good luck, Mama H.
Are you both ready?
I think so.
This challenge is on.
Heather's going
right for the flame,
trying to get that husk to burn.
Deshawn is getting a big pile
of magnesium,
trying to use that to spark.
Deshawn has a little bit
of flame.
Trying to nurse it,
trying to get a stick to catch,
which would help.
Deshawn's got a flame going.
This is a key moment
for Deshawn
if he can keep that flame going
and get it to take hold.
Heather still trying
to get a flame.
Deshawn's flame is starting
to grow.
That's a good sign.
Deshawn is doing
a very nice job.
Heather continues to fight,
as she has for 25 days,
often in dead last,
but never giving up.
Deshawn's starting to burn
a little taller now.
He's got a time advantage
because Heather has yet
to get any flame.
Heather has a baby flame.
-(Shan gasps)
-Yeah.
PROBST:
She's now in it.
(Shan gasps)
PROBST: Heather now has got
a little something going.
Got two fires.
Heather, stick by stick,
is nurturing her flame.
Deshawn in danger
of losing his.
PROBST: Can he get it back?
Can he breathe life
back into that fire?
A fire paramedic.
♪ ♪
It might be out.
Deshawn has a lot of sticks.
PROBST: Heather's fire now
is burning very solid.
Deshawn looking,
searching through the rubble.
Is gonna have to start again
and get something going.
Now it's Deshawn
who feels the panic
as Heather once again,
close to being counted out
of a challenge,
and once again,
hanging in there.
(whispering):
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Heather's flame is
getting taller.
Deshawn has a flame again.
He's got to move quickly now
because Heather has
a legit fire.
Heather's flame is now
starting to hit the rope.
For the first time,
little by little,
burning off some of that rope.
Heather's got a great fire.
Deshawn is trying
to get back in this.
Heather is getting closer
and closer to the final three,
building a fire
her kids would be proud of.
Deshawn trying,
trying to get back.
You can see the fibers
of the rope burning,
little by little.
Deshawn is out of it right now,
and suddenly,
Heather's flame starts
to dissipate.
Oh.
Just like that, it is
several inches below the rope.
Now it's sparking up and down,
but it's not as consistent.
♪ ♪
Deshawn has a flame. Deshawn
trying to build something now.
Can he get back in it?
Did he learn anything
from his first fire?
Heather's back now with force.
That fire starting
to burn higher again,
starting
to burn that rope again.
Deshawn's is going higher.
Deshawn's back in this.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST:
His flame is now starting
to burn high enough that
it's getting close to that rope.
♪ ♪
Heather continues
to burn through that rope.
There can't be a lot left.
Now Deshawn is burning his rope.
Both players are burning their
rope, both fires are burning.
One of the best fire-making
showdowns we've ever seen.
That fire is right
on that rope right now,
burning, burning, burning
through the fibers.
-There it is!
-Let's go! Let's go!
-Out of nowhere, Deshawn.
-Oh, my God.
DESHAWN:
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
-Wow.
-(shrieking)
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
-And seconds later,
Heather's pops.
-SHAN: Oh, my goodness.
-Good job, Heather.
-Wow.
-Thank you.
-ERIKA: Good job, Heather.
-LIANA: Good job, Heather.
-DESHAWN: Love you.
-PROBST: Wow.
-Oh, my gosh.
EVVIE:
Wow. Best fire-making ever.
-Best fire-making ever.
-Ever, ever, ever.
-TIFFANY: Good job.
-EVVIE: Wow.
Best fire-making ever.
-Oh, my gosh,
my heart is racing.
-Holy cow.
-Wow.
-TIFFANY: That was amazing.
-HEATHER: Yeah.
I don't know where to start.
Deshawn, you never gave up.
-You won by seconds.
-DESHAWN: Yes.
-Hers popped right after yours.
-Yeah.
-It took every single thing
you had.
-I...
Like, I knew there was a reason
why I came out here
to play this game, and like,
I thought I was down,
but this is a moment, a lesson--
never freaking stop.
No matter what facet of life
you're in, don't stop, bro.
Like, mental health-wise
and, like, just getting
to the space
where I'm at right now, like,
there's moments in it,
a lot of times in my life,
where I just
don't believe in myself,
and now I feel a lot more
confident because of this, and
this is amazing, dawg.
Like, I'm speechless.
Like, I can't.
I'm speechless.
PROBST:
Heather, you didn't get
to the final three,
but that was an
admirable effort.
-Thank you.
-You lost by three seconds.
-It is over now.
-Yeah.
You will become the eighth
and final member of the jury.
-What is this experience?
-I got to this point,
and I'm proud of myself,
and I overcame a lot of fears.
Um, most people
don't know about,
um, I almost drowned when I was
younger, and I didn't get
in the water for 35 years.
And so, when these challenges
came up where I had
to run and jump off this,
you know, giant structure
into the water,
I was petrified,
but when I did it,
I feel like I grew another inch
that day.
So this pushed me
way beyond my comfort zone,
and I was proud
of how I've progressed,
and I'm thankful
for this journey.
-Yeah, it's been great.
-PROBST: All right, Heather.
I know. That-that thing.
-I got to go get it. All right.
-You got to go get it.
I got it.
Good luck, you guys.
It's been a blast.
-Thanks. Love you much.
-ERIKA: Love you, Mama.
-Thank you for this journey.
-Love you.
We'll see you
on the other side.
You got it, my friend.
You got it.
Heather, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Thank you.
-Love you. Love you.
-Bye, guys.
Okay, Deshawn, Erika, Xander,
you've gone as far
as you can go in the game.
You made it to the final three.
Now the power shifts over here.
These seven, plus Heather,
who will be
joining the jury,
will now hold the power
of the game.
Tomorrow night, they will decide
who wins the title
of Sole Survivor
and the million dollars
that goes along with it.
You have one more night
out here in Fiji.
It may rain, it may not.
-Try to enjoy it.
-Doesn't matter.
Try to get some sleep,
and I'll see you
back here tomorrow night
for the final
Tribal Council.
Congratulations.
-Grab your torches. Good night.
-ERIKA: Thanks, Jeff.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Thank you.
I was so close.
I'm sad to be going,
but I'm also so proud
that I've made it this far.
I got to see how all
of this works
and be a part of something
that I've loved for 20 years.
I hope I inspire some people
to try something new
and outside their comfort zone
because
the reward is so great.
It's so great,
it's indescribable.
Thanks for having me.
♪ ♪
DESHAWN:
Beautiful day.
ERIKA:
Our last sunrise.
-(chuckles)
-Arms out, you guys.
-(chuckles) Arms out.
-Soaking it up.
-We did it.
-DESHAWN: Yes. Yes.
-ERIKA: We did it.
XANDER:
Being in the final three
is just beautiful.
I'm so grateful.
There's no doubt
that this is the hardest season
of Survivor ever.
I think I've lost
like 20 or 30 pounds.
I... These used to be muscles.
This is... What is this?
But, despite the suffering,
I've loved every moment.
(excited chatter)
ERIKA:
Oh, my God.
(overlapping chatter)
-XANDER: Eggs.
-ERIKA: Oh, my God...
♪ ♪
XANDER:
My story has been
an underdog story.
I had to work my ass off.
I was on the bottom,
and I got myself here.
Congratulations. You found
a three-way shared immunity.
I found an idol.
I had an advantage.
I risked my vote.
I didn't have a vote
for a Tribal Council.
Pretty much all the way up
until the merge.
Xander wins individual immunity.
Huge effort.
I won two immunity challenges.
I got to choose
who goes to fire.
I made Jeff laugh.
I cried.
Every single checkpoint
on the Survivor bucket list
is checked.
Except for one-- it's winning
the million dollars
and the title of Sole Survivor.
To be able to grill bacon
on the last day...
If I win this game,
I would be
the youngest winner of all-time.
This is my chance to be
one of the greats,
so I've got to give every inch,
every fiber of my body
to make sure
that I can secure the win.
This is, like, the best
breakfast I've ever had.
I finally feel my stomach.
I know.
I feel, like, a bit more alive.
I played a hell of a game,
but I get underestimated
because of, like, how I look
and my size.
But inside, like, I know
that I'm a fierce competitor.
A lion that dressed like a lamb.
Now I have to be roaring.
It's time to show everyone
that I actually have teeth,
because I know I have
what it takes to win.
Erika wins individual immunity.
I won two challenges.
I flipped the game
when I broke the hourglass.
I'm playing for me.
And, behind the scenes,
I created the alliance
that dominated the endgame,
and I was always making sure
that the biggest threat to me
went home.
So, now is the time for
the little Filipino immigrant,
the Canadian citizen
to take off that lamb costume
and fight for the work
that I've done.
No matter what
gets thrown at me tonight,
I have everything it takes
to win.
DESHAWN:
I feel like I've grown
by being here,
so even though
tonight's not my night,
like, I feel good about
what I've been able to do.
So I'm happy.
I can't believe I've survived
one of the craziest seasons
of Survivor.
But I didn't only survive,
like, I thrived.
This is Survivor,
but I feel like a thriver.
-Yeah, no, I got you. I got you.
-You're-you're all good? Okay.
-Way to go, brother,
like, come on.
-Right. Right, right, look.
My social skills got me here.
This journey taught me
so much about myself,
and resilience, and confidence
and who I am as a person.
I didn't win immunity.
I didn't find advantages,
but I actually worked
my ass off to be here.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Deshawn got flame.
You are safe, my friend.
Oh, my God.
Winning the game
would be epic to me.
The money would literally
change my life,
so I got to keep my foot
on the gas.
I don't really get nervous.
I'm a little nervous. (chuckles)
There's no goats
in this final three.
Everybody has a chance
to win the million dollars.
This season has been a battle
from the very beginning.
It would be shameful
if it didn't end that way.
I'm excited for it,
and I'm ready to do
what I got to do.
Give me the belt.
I want to be the champ.
♪ ♪
All right, here we are.
The last day of Survivor 41.
Deshawn, Erika, Xander,
you did what you hope
to accomplish
when you dream
of playing this game:
put yourself
into a position to win.
This is the last phase.
The last stage of the game is
you got to claim your victory.
What's unique
about Survivor is,
a group of people
that you helped vote out
are the ones in control.
So, tonight,
they're going to interrogate you
because they're making
a million-dollar vote.
So they're gonna
ask you questions
at times may seem tough,
they may push
you around a little bit.
They're trying to get you
to stand up
and prove to them
why you deserve
the title of Sole Survivor
and the million dollars
that goes along with it.
So I'm gonna give everybody
a minute, compose themselves.
Jury will get ready
with their questions.
Final three,
you get ready to answer,
and then we will go.
♪ ♪
All right, it's time to get to
our final Tribal Council Q and A
from the jury.
Who wants to get us started?
Evvie, hand up.
I love it.
-If you don't mind.
-PROBST: Go for it.
All right, so I just want
to start by saying
huge congratulations
to all three of you.
I think we all can attest that
this is one of the toughest
seasons Survivor's ever had,
and the three of you are sitting
here at the very, very end.
So that's something that you
should be extremely proud of.
And given, you know,
the beautiful diversity
that brought this cast together,
this is just a beautiful
final three that reflects that.
However, the flip side of this
being a wonderful final three
is that each of you
is up against two people
that have a very good shot
of getting some votes tonight.
So, good luck,
keep making me proud,
it's all you.
Thanks for getting us started,
Evvie.
Danny, weigh in on this.
Where are you right now?
Yeah, so, most of the jury
knows now that I have a history
of-of being
a professional athlete,
so I tend to break things down,
especially complex games
and competitions,
into phases or quarters.
And Survivor's no different.
This game can be broken down
into pre-merge, post-merge,
final eight.
When you do that, you allow
yourself to have a game plan.
So I'd really like to hear you
explain your game plan
coming into the game
and how you adapted it
to get here.
Let's start with Xander.
So, going into this game,
I know a lot of fans
like to say they want
to play a Tony-style game,
or they want to play
a Spencer-style game.
I really wanted
to play a Xander-style game.
I wanted to do something
different and go with my gut,
take big risks,
and that's exactly what I did.
And going into quarter one,
I knew that
from my background in athletics,
in running cross-country
and track,
I know that team dynamic
is strong.
So, in Yase,
I wanted to be the workhorse
for the tribe.
I wanted to share advantages.
I wanted to say
that we could work together
and stay strong.
So that was quarter one,
was team dynamic.
And... (chuckles)
once I got into quarter two,
we were down in numbers.
Everybody knew I had an idol
because I had to say
the butterfly thing,
and a lot of people
knew about the extra vote.
I was the lone soldier,
so I market myself.
I say, "I'm a number.
You can use me. Please."
And once the big alliance
started crumbling,
the side that
I felt most comfortable with
was going with Ricard.
So, third quarter, final eight.
This was the phase of my game
that was keeping Ricard
as a shield.
He was the only person that
everybody was so vehement
about getting out instead of me,
But it was a gamble,
and had to turn on him
eventually,
even though I loved him,
because I had an idol,
and I knew I was safe
to get to the end.
DANNY:
Got you. Thanks-thanks, man.
NASEER:
And also, Xander,
you stepped forward
to get rice post-merge
for the entire tribe.
And also, the reward challenge,
you swapped the spot with Erika.
-XANDER: Yeah.
-I felt that-that was
your social aspect of the game.
In-in addition to that, uh,
one day, I was really thinking
about my family and everything.
Then you came and told me,
"If you need to hug it out,
brother, I'm there for you."
That was so kind.
You-you have very kind heart.
You are very social there.
I'm proud of you for that.
-(chuckles)
-Thank you, Naseer.
DANNY:
My buddy Deshawn,
your game plan
to get you to this point.
Yeah, so, um, coming into
Survivor, like, I'm a huge fan,
so I know that the foundation
of Survivor is the social game.
It doesn't matter
how many competitions you win,
it doesn't matter
how many advantages you find.
And so, first half,
first quarter of my game,
it was about
building those relationships.
So I talked to people
like Heather,
and we became
really, really close.
I talked to people like Erika.
We became close.
Naseer and I were like brothers,
by the end of the journey.
Um, so moving on to
the second quarter of the game
where we're talking
about post-merge,
like, I soon found out
that I was on the block--
which clued me in
that I was probably
a big threat in this game.
And so, it's amazing
that I'm sitting here,
but it's because
of those relationships
from the first half.
And I feel like
I played a pivotal role
in being the glue
of people to vote together.
You know, just keeping
that camaraderie alive,
always shutting down negativity,
for sure.
And, you know,
if we're gonna talk
about the last quarter
of the game,
that's what you call
social capital.
And that, in this game,
is invaluable.
So for me,
I know it's gonna be tough
-to get to the end,
and that's how I did it.
-DANNY: Thank you.
May I interject something
in regards to
keeping everybody together
-and camaraderie with Luvu?
-Mm-hmm.
That sounds nice.
-Yeah.
-Can you explain why
the first day of the merge...
DESHAWN:
Mm-hmm.
...your intention was
to pull all of us aside
and say how she needs to go,
Sydney should leave
so that Danny wouldn't know
what to do with his game,
that you didn't really have
a deep connection with Heather,
you were just trying
to be nice to her?
Um, basically, you threw
everyone under the bus.
So how does that really tie
into what you just said?
Um, so I really respect
your question a lot,
but I don't think
that everything
that you mentioned there
was true.
Um, what I can definitely say
is that I did see Erika
as a big threat
from the very beginning.
That's true.
Danny, actually, definitely
remember saying, like,
he hasn't had much of a game,
and he wanted to play the game
a little bit more slow.
But for me,
my truest intentions--
and I can only be honest here--
I never wanted
Danny out of the game.
I never actually wanted
Heather out of the game.
Did I want Erika
out of the game?
I kind of did.
So if those comments came out,
I 1,000% apologize for that.
And that's just the truth.
And then Er-Erika,
please. Uh...
ERIKA:
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I had a lot
of expectations
on how this season
was gonna go for me.
And I thought,
I'm gonna come in,
be a sweet lamb,
join the bottom
of the majority alliance,
vote with them
for the first vote
and then slowly start
to work my way up.
But the blessing
and the curse of Luvu
is we kept winning,
so we never had to vote.
And instead, we weren't voting
and eliminating people,
but we were starting
to see relationships shift.
And when it came
to Heather and I,
we became
the unlikely dynamic duo
that decided, you know,
"Let's go kick ass
at the merge."
And, of course,
I don't even go to the merge,
I go live alone on Exile,
and, socially,
I'm down and out of the game.
I come back,
I flip over the game,
and what I really noticed
was the opportunity
with the people
who were either on the bottom,
felt like they were on the outs.
So I started socially to
sow my seeds with those people
and build relationships
with them now,
so that I can reap this harvest
later in the game--
maybe unnoticed.
I think some people noticed.
I know Shan noticed,
and that's why I really wanted
to take out Shan.
And then I found myself
in the majority alliance
that dominated the late stage
of the game.
When I looked at
the final six, I knew,
no matter what
combination of final five,
I had set myself up
with enough potential allies
to know that I had a shot
to sit in the final three.
Yes, thank you.
Erika, you had
a very fantastic game.
-Thank you.
-I adore you.
I really trust you.
And what's unfortunate is,
you lacked that social game
with most of the jury,
and so they don't feel
the same way I do.
And I'm just like, "Oh,
I wish you could all see it."
-I know. I know. I know.
-You know, it's unfortunate.
But there is something to be
said about having a relationship
with everybody,
like Deshawn did,
because that also made it easier
for him to betray everybody.
So did you choose
to only have relationships
with certain individuals?
Can you just explain that?
This is a great discussion,
because for me,
what kind of drives me crazy
watching Survivor
is the perception that
having a strong social game
is feeling like you have
strong ties with everyone.
But I think that having a strong
command of the social game
is knowing where you stand and
what you're capable of doing.
So I knew I wanted
to be kind to everybody,
but I know that I do better
in one-on-one connections
and, like, smaller connections.
So I'm not the type of person
who's going to be best friends
with all of you, even though
I think it could happen.
Down the line,
hit me up on FaceTime.
And I think a big part
of my social game
is my relationship with Heather.
I think a lot of people saw
my relationship with Heather
as, like, I was the brains
of the operation,
or Heather was just,
like, an extra vote
that I dragged around.
But that was not true.
It was actually knowing, like,
how this duo
could work together,
even when there was a public
attempt to try to split us up--
otherwise known as a truth bomb.
It's wild to me that
we were a known pair
and we still were able
to make it into the top four--
which is so rare.
I wish I got
to know more people,
but I knew socially, like, what
I was capable of in this game,
and I played within that.
RICARD:
Well, thank you,
and I hope you're able
to prove your game to this jury.
TIFFANY:
I have a question for Xander.
What was your perception
of where you stood with Yase
going into the merge,
and how did that speak
to your overall social game?
Going into the merge,
I was gonna look like someone
who was maybe an Ozzy-type,
someone who'd be good
at challenges.
And those people,
they just don't make it far.
But we sang
in the rain together.
It was, it was cute.
(chuckles)
So I knew that, like, you know,
you guys would keep me around,
and I-I genuinely did
want to protect you guys.
It's just, at a certain point,
it was so detrimental to my game
that I had to adapt.
And, yeah, it hurt,
but there was nothing
I could do at that point.
-My hands were tied.
-LIANA: But, more specifically,
I wanted to ask,
was there a point in the game
where you had a good read,
in terms of social awareness,
where you use that
to your advantage
to make a move in the game?
Yeah, um, I would say...
(sucks teeth)
I would say
my social awareness, um...
LIANA:
Like, an example
of social awareness is:
"I knew about your advantage
the minute that you had it,
"but you assume
that I didn't know about it.
And I use that
to my advantage in the game."
So I'm asking, was there
ever a moment like that for you?
-And if not, that's cool, too.
-XANDER: Yeah.
Yeah, um, so,
during the Tiffany vote,
I was fed different stories.
Suddenly, it was Heather.
Suddenly, it was Naseer.
And so, that's how
I was able to figure out
I was likely getting duped
and that
I would have to play my idol.
-Thank you.
-So you were,
you were reading the room?
-XANDER: Yes. Yeah, yeah.
-Thank you.
EVVIE:
A question related to that.
An amazing thing for your game
was that you were able
to hold on to that idol
even though everyone
knew about it, post-merge.
Was that, you know, luck?
Or was that your social
game was good enough
that you actually knew
from people
that you didn't need
to play it each time?
I think it was
a mixture of both.
I wanted to play this game
a little paranoid,
because paranoid people are
always thinking of every option.
So when I went
into every Tribal Council,
I was nervous as hell.
You know, do I play it,
do I not play it?
But my relationship with
Ricard was strong enough
to the point where when
he said, "Play your idol,"
he meant that
people were voting for me.
But I knew that
with the chaos of Tribal,
people wouldn't have the unity
to take me out.
So a mix of both.
RICARD:
Xander,
we had a really solid
friendship, in my opinion.
I've never had this,
like, bromance
where I was like, "Oh, my God,
this is Uncle Xander.
He's gonna be meeting
my daughter. This is amazing."
Like, we were tight.
I can attempt
to get past the idea
of voting me out
in a strategic light,
but what doesn't make sense
to me is
you take out
the number one threat, me,
but the number two threat,
Erika's here.
And I know, at some point,
people are gonna ask you
about the fire-making decision
because...
Uh, it's all... it's crazy.
I'm not getting into that,
necessarily.
I'm just confused.
Were you always lying to me?
Was that a fake relationship?
I just don't understand,
because those two things
don't go together.
Our relationship
was completely real.
Like, I love people, and I love
to make these connections.
And our connection
was completely real,
but you would have won
against anyone, and...
So why did you keep her?
I was under the impression
that Erika wasn't
the biggest strategic threat
compared to me because
that was what Deshawn said
during his truth bomb,
and I felt like the jury
reacted positively to it.
And that could be
a fallacy in my game.
So I-I'm willing to admit that.
HEATHER:
I-I want to interject.
I said to Xander
on the last day,
"The only person
that's left here
"that could possibly
take your game away from you
is my friend Erika."
And you chose
to take her with you.
Explain why
this was benefiting your game,
taking her beside you.
I agree with you
in the sense that
she's someone
who's very strategic,
but I feel like
I've got an edge on her
because I've had
a more wholesale game.
So I didn't
give her the opportunity
to beat someone in fire,
'cause if she beats someone
in fire,
I think that would have tipped
the balance in her favor.
-So I didn't take that chance.
-TIFFANY: Okay.
-Hmm.
-That's a good answer.
-That makes sense.
Yeah.
So, my question's for you,
Deshawn.
DESHAWN:
Yeah.
I felt like you listed
a few different moves,
-which sound like
it's strategic...
-Yeah.
-...but it felt more
like temper tantrums.
-Mm. Mm-hmm.
-Like, there was
a lot of emotion involved.
And emotion
is not a bad thing, at all.
-It's very powerful.
-Yeah. Yeah.
But it felt like at every turn
where you had
an emotional breakdown,
I had to come to you and, like,
figure out how
I could talk to you
because I wanted
this four-way alliance,
you know, to work with,
you know,
myself, you,
and Liana and Danny.
DESHAWN:
Yeah.
SHAN:
And at every turn
when we had these conversations,
you relocked us in
with this social movement
that was really important to us,
that's happening
in the real world.
And we were all wanting
to bring home a win
for the Black community.
-Right?
-Yeah.
And I felt like that
hijacked me, emotionally,
a lot of the times,
because I was really locked in.
And that's, honestly,
where I was gonna put my game.
I would have come in fourth
for all three of you to take
one, two and three, you know?
-Mm-hmm.
-And I said that to you,
-time and time again.
-Mm-hmm.
It's really important
for my vote tonight
to know what happened.
Were you capitalizing
on a social movement back home
and using that to hijack me
and maybe the other people
in our alliance?
Or were you serious about that?
Uh, because that feels like,
to me, out of bounds.
I just want to make it
very, very clear, right now.
I don't even care
about how this...
Give me third.
I would never, ever
sell out my people for a game.
That was never my intentions,
ever.
And I just want to touch
on the point of, you know,
were the moves that happened
at Tribal emotional?
Not emotional, not emotional.
-Temper tantrums.
-DESHAWN: Temper tantrums.
-Sulking and pouting. Yeah.
-Right, right, right, yeah.
So I have to accept that
that's the way it was perceived.
But I wore my heart
on my sleeve, and so, if I felt
like people weren't listening,
that's the way I responded.
And I'm young.
I have to admit, I have a lot
to learn, so that's just that.
Um, it does hurt my heart
a little bit
that it would even be considered
that I would use
a social movement in this game.
Um, but I understand, from your
vantage point, how you feel.
You and I have
a very personal relationship.
I think of you as my sister.
And that's why I was so
emotional at Tribal Council.
Like, I was hurting, Shan.
It really, really hurt me
that Tribal Council
to have to vote you out,
and all I can do
is apologize for that.
It is something
I have to bear the weight of.
Like, I feel...
I would never have done that.
It was hard, Shan, so I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-Well, it's all forgiven
for sure.
And I... I'm super proud of you
for sitting there tonight,
and I think
that you're gonna make tons
of people proud, so...
-Thank you.
-Congratulations on final three.
Thank you.
-Any other questions?
-DANNY: Yeah, so,
I really just wanted to take
a chance to address Erika
for a second.
Um, from a competitor
and competitively-speaking, I
think you did absolutely amazing
in the individual immunity
challenges and the puzzles, and
intentionally
or unintentionally,
you allow people
to underestimate you, uh,
and not see what you were
really capable of doing.
Danny, coming through. I mean,
the reality is, I've spent,
like, almost ten years, like,
going into boardrooms,
people treat me like the intern,
but I'm really the one
who's running the meeting.
Again, I was never out
in front, but I was never quite
at the bottom, and at every
Tribal Council I went to,
I was on the right side
of the vote.
So I wasn't sure what the path
for me was going to be
to the end
when the game started,
but I knew if I got there,
I'd be a dark horse.
DANNY:
And I'll say that because
I envy you
because you played the game
that I really wanted
to play and...
-and tried to,
so congratulations to you.
-Danny.
-Yeah. Me, too.
-Me, too.
-(laughter)
Um, Xander, I have one question
for you.
Do you have an idol?
I'm totally...
-(laughter)
-Yes.
-DANNY:
You all played great games.
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
-Good job, everyone.
-SHAN: Really,
you did a good job.
-You all played great.
-Everyone did a good job,
seriously.
-DANNY: Very tough decision.
-RICARD: Good job, everyone.
PROBST:
All right, jury, nice job.
I'm going to give you a minute
now to think about your vote,
and when we come back,
for the last time,
we will vote.
Okay, after 26 intense days
of gameplay here in Fiji,
it is time for our jury
of eight to cast
their million-dollar votes
and decide
who wins season 41--
Deshawn, Erika or Xander?
For the last time,
it is time to vote.
Tiffany, you're up.
♪ ♪
NASEER:
I really respect this game.
You played a great game.
You did it.
♪ ♪
I felt that your game
was more intentional,
more risk-taking,
and good luck.
♪ ♪
I'll go get the votes.
All right, well,
the theme of this season
really did become
"Drop the four, keep the one."
First time we ever played 26
days forced a relentless pace,
and also, we introduced the most
dangerous twists we've ever
done.
So, let's add
a little history to it.
-(gasping)
-Oh, my God.
PROBST:
The only time
we have ever done this was
the last time we did it,
which was the summer of 2000,
when we read the votes
on location
-in season one...
-Oh, my God.
and announced Richard Hatch
as the first winner.
I think it's time
to do it again,
-21 years later.
-Oh.
-Wow.
HEATHER:
Oh.
PROBST:
We are going
to announce the winner
of Survivor 41 right now.
Are you ready?
I'm not joking.
-Wow.
-What?
-PROBST: All right.
These are votes for a winner.
Here we go.
First vote-- Erika.
♪ ♪
Deshawn.
One vote-- Erika,
one vote-- Deshawn.
♪ ♪
Erika.
Two votes-- Erika,
one vote-- Deshawn.
Erika. Three votes-- Erika,
♪ ♪
Erika.
Four votes-- Erika,
one vote-- Deshawn.
The winner of Survivor 41--
Erika.
-(applause and cheering)
-All the rest are yours,
as well.
-ERIKA: Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Our first
Canadian winner-- Erika.
Congratulations.
I'm good for the money,
but look, this is
an awkward moment, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-Like, we're right here.
There are usually... there are
thousands of people yelling.
Let's make
a little more history.
EVVIE:
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Let's do something
we've never done before.
What?
Let's keep shooting.
Let's bring it in.
-Let's bring in some pizza.
-Oh, my God.
-Let's bring in our champagne.
Oh, my God. What the...?
We're gonna do something
we've never done before.
We're gonna call it
the Survivor after show.
and we're going
to do that right now,
here,
in the most raw way possible.
-Let's move
our camera operators.
-(overlapping chatter)
We're gonna readjust
a couple of things,
starting with you coming over
and congratulating the three
that you just put
through the grill.
EVVIE:
Congratulations.
-I've wanted to do this for...
-(overlapping chatter)
almost from the beginning,
because this is as about as raw
as it can get.
Need it with a little fire.
Yeah,
let's light up the torches,
'cause we're gonna be here
for a while.
We're gonna move a few cameras.
Think of it
as, uh, the last night
of Survivor summer camp.
It's the Survivor 41
after show.
Give us two minutes,
and we'll be right back.
(overlapping chatter)
Let me get some champagne.
Oh, thank you so much.
-(indistinct chatter)
-No!
PROBST:
All right, so,
we've never done this before.
-The champagne is real.
-LIANA: What is happening?
Any time you need more pizza,
-you let me know.
-Touché.
-You're fine.
This is the... what would
normally be the reunion show.
Because, as much fun as it is
to be back
in Los Angeles and the lights
and the big crowd
and your family
and all that hoopla,
what it misses is the immediacy
and the truth.
So, let's just talk, and if you
want something else to drink,
we got... we got a team out here
to bring it to you.
-The champagne.
-Can I have some pizza, please?
-It's been a while.
-(overlapping chatter)
PROBST: And while
we're doing this, Erika,
I want to start with you.
And whatever you need,
-you just ask, we'll get it.
-Okay.
There was an interesting theme
that, in your career,
that you would go into a room,
and nobody would ever guess
that you were the one in charge.
-Yeah.
-That becomes a skill
in a game like Survivor,
where you were able,
even with your ego,
to say, "I don't have to have
them think I'm in charge.
I just need a path to the end."
How much of that going in
was something
you knew you could count on?
The way that I look, like,
really affects the way
that people treat me
outside of the game.
Like, whenever I go
to the airport by myself,
even though
I'm a frequent traveler,
people ask me
if I'm an unaccompanied minor,
and I have to go through all the
extra steps because I'm a kid.
So I knew that was something
that, like, I had up my sleeve.
And the other thing is,
like, yeah,
I had no ego
about how I was gonna play it.
I knew that, you know, if
it made more sense for Heather
to talk to someone,
she could do it.
I don't need to have
the full credit for anything.
And I knew that the path
to the end--
it didn't have to be pretty.
I think Tiffany
and I talked about it.
Didn't have to be pretty,
I just had to get here.
I didn't have to look
like the one in charge.
I just needed to have the chance
to plead my case.
One of the things they don't
know is that I visited you
when you were out alone
on that island.
I was the one that came
and delivered the twist
-that Danny adored so much.
-(laughter)
And I got to say,
when I saw you out there,
I asked you how it was,
and you said, "You know,
"the first night
was kind of tough.
"You know, I'm alone, it's wet,
"it's hard to live on an island,
but I kept striking the flint,
and I kept saying,
'I'm going to get fire.'"
Oh, my God, please stay lit.
PROBST:
What I saw when I saw you was
a different person
than the first half of the game.
You looked like
you belonged on that island.
ERIKA:
Oh, 100%. Like, being on Exile,
it felt like
the turning point in my game.
Like, two days before
I was on Exile,
I actually had a breakdown
by myself.
I was on the winning Luvu tribe.
You would think that everything
is great, and I was, like,
crying, thinking, "How am I
going to win this game?
I haven't even had
to vote for anyone."
Like, how am I supposed to have
the cred at the end of the game?
And then when I had to face my
greatest fear, to go one night
alone on Exile, and realizing
that I could do it?
Like, the rest of the game
was totally possible.
And I was looking at my fire
that took me
nearly two hours to build...
So maybe Xander should have
sent me into fire.
I don't think
I would have the hero moment.
Like, that's when I realized,
like,
"Survivor's going to be hard,
but as long
"as I keep going,
then I know I have
what it takes
to get to the end."
-All right, well done.
Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-To our first Canadian winner!
-To Erika!
-(cheering)
That's a lot of money
in Canada, so thank you.
-(overlapping chatter)
-PROBST: So, Xander,
I want to talk to you because
it's a very hard game to play.
You're very young
to get this deep.
And that was the theme
that the jury,
most of whom are older,
picked up on, is,
if there was something
you were missing,
it was a social awareness
to figure out
what is happening in the game
that you're not seeing.
So when you hear that,
what's your take on it?
Yeah, I mean, honestly,
I'm very appreciative
of this whole experience.
It's been, like, such a trip.
I did everything
that I wanted to do.
I accomplished so much.
And I didn't want it to be
something that was easy.
I didn't want it to be...
It wasn't about the win for me.
It was about
being able to come out here
and struggle
and get this experience.
And, yeah, I did so many things.
I made you laugh.
I won a challenge.
I found an idol.
I risked my vote.
I had an extra vote.
I made it to the final three.
And yeah, I mean, I'm so proud.
I knew going in
that no matter what happened,
I would be so proud of myself.
And not getting any votes--
as much as I knew
Erika was a threat, and I was
trying to underplay that,
I didn't see exactly how much
people respected her gameplay.
So, that was completely on me.
And now I get
to take this information,
and I get to grow from it,
and learn.
And I love
that I'm not, you know,
a complete person, that I do
have more things to work on.
PROBST:
And what's interesting
about your story is,
you said so clearly,
"I wasn't the kid
"that watched Survivor
and dreamed of being on.
"I was the kid who lamented
I would never be on,
because I didn't have
what it takes."
What did you learn that you can
connect back to that little kid
-to say, "I had it all along"?
-Yeah.
I mean, I wish
I could go back in time
and tell him
that the only limits that exist
in this world are the limits
you place on yourself.
Don't listen
to what anybody says,
because you can do anything,
if you just want it.
If you give it heart,
and you fight for what you want,
-then you can achieve it.
-Well, huge congratulations
to you,
-to get this deep in the game.
-Absolutely. Absolutely.
And Deshawn, the story
with you was being
temperamental, emotional,
reaction, whatever you want
to call it. Shan and Danny,
a lot of people brought it up.
Did that surprise you?
Um, I think it did surprise me.
I think
maybe I had a skewed perception
of myself outside of this.
And maybe Survivor just
brought out that side of me.
But in, like...
in the real world,
I didn't see myself as that.
But, like,
this is all documented,
everything's been recorded.
And you know,
when multiple people
are telling you something,
there must be truth to that.
So I'm really excited
for an opportunity
to, like, reflect and grow
from this experience.
Um, I thank you guys for being
willing to, like, educate me
on-on the person that I am,
and it's just like,
"No, you still got some room
to grow, man."
-So I'm-I'm excited to do that.
-PROBST: And I want to be clear.
I did not get the impression
that they thought
you were a disaster.
It was just one element
of your personality.
I found you, this entire time,
to be really likable, funny,
and you made it deep
into this game.
You got a vote!
I mean, getting any votes
-is an acknowledgment.
-Yeah.
And for me,
your turning point seemed to be
the fire-making challenge.
-When you were out of it...
-Yeah.
I mean, Heather was seconds away
from winning.
I was watching you.
You never once looked over.
-I don't know if you ever looked
at her flame.
-Mm-hmm.
You just kept trying
to resuscitate a dead fire.
-DESHAWN: Mm-hmm.
-And you did!
-(all voicing assent)
-I know it's just
making a little fire,
but it seemed
to represent a lot to you.
Yeah, no,
that was a major moment. I mean,
and at a certain point
in this game,
after a certain vote,
like, I was on the bottom.
And I had
the Do or Die thing happen,
and so, there was gonna be
sleek chances
of me making it to the end.
So, the fact
that I was able to come
into the fire-making challenge,
where it was, like,
my last opportunity
to do or die,
or, like, put up or shut up,
and you know,
I completed the task,
was amazing.
It's definitely something
I'm never gonna forget.
It definitely reminds me
to never quit,
never give up on myself and to
just keep-keep pushing forward.
So, I don't know
what the perception
might look like, but like,
I'm still so happy to be here,
and I'm so thankful
that I got this opportunity.
It was amazing.
And I'm gonna take these lessons
back with me
into the real world.
So, just thank you guys for
everything, so appreciate it.
-Ditto. Ditto.
-You rocked it, Deshawn.
-Your fire-making challenge.
-(overlapping chatter)
Thank you. Thank you, guys.
Does anybody need pizza
or champagne?
-I'll take anything.
-(overlapping chatter)
-PROBST: Yes.
Let's bring in...
let's bring in some more.
-Yeah.
-Let's get some refills in here.
Quick break.
We'll be right back.
PROBST:
Up next,
players share their reactions
to the Beware Advantage,
and Liana recounts
the Knowledge is Power Advantage
that backfired.
Plus later, your first look
at Survivor 42.
All right, we are back
with the Survivor 41 after show.
So let's talk
about some of the things
that made this season unique.
If we look at the big things,
it would be 26 days,
which I'm sure,
in the beginning, some of you
were like, "Oh, that doesn't
feel like a full season."
Is anybody feeling like
you did not get a full season?
-ALL: NO.
-Okay. Yeah.
Because we offset the 26 days
by trying to approximate
what a 39-day might feel like.
And the first thing
we did is said, "No food."
And then we put
these new twists in.
So, let's start
with the Beware Advantages.
Because I know
you found an idol,
Shan found one,
and Naseer found one.
When you first find
this new advantage,
and it says, on the outside,
"You better want this
if you open it,"
was there any hesitation
from you, Xander?
No. I mean, this is
my Survivor experience.
And I get to be the first person
to unfold this cloth
and figure out what the twist
is? I've-I've got to take that.
-How about you, Shan?
-There was, for sure,
hesitation.
Like, I left that joint
right where it was.
-Really?
-I actually had the information
about what it was beforehand,
because someone who thought
I was their number one shared
a lot of information with me.
And then they got voted out.
And then...
So I knew what was in it
-without having to open it.
-Uh-huh.
Um, so I definitely went back
and forth for a while.
But then, like, I was like,
"I just want it."
And then Genie found it
and told me that she found it.
Let's do it now! Let's do it
now! Let's do it now!
SHAN:
Ricard and I went
and looked at it,
and we convinced Genie
not to open it,
and then,
when no one was looking,
I kind of went and opened it.
-Wow.
-And so, I was just hoping
that Luvu would-would
find theirs, and they did.
PROBST:
Naseer, the phrases
were very funny,
so when you had to say it,
and you're not sure
that everyone knows
what's happening,
how do you figure out
how to do that?
NASEER:
So, first thing first.
Like, wow, I had
to memorize the phrases.
-So...
-(laughter)
-Which one was your phrase?
So, uh, "I'm as confused
as a goat on Astroturf."
-So I'm like...
-(laughter)
So I had... I had my cave.
I would sit
under-under a breadfruit tree.
There was a huge rock.
So I'd take a couple of coconuts
with me, go sit down,
and I'd start, you know,
repeating again and again,
trying to remember.
So, like, it took me
at least, like, 50 to 60 times.
-(laughter)
-Really?
-Yeah!
So, again, you know that English
is not my first language.
And I'm proud to say I learned
English watching Survivor.
-I love that.
-LIANA: Awesome. That's awesome.
So, to learn a new phrase
from Survivor-- it's even
more exciting, you know?
What a great phrase.
"I'm as confused as a goat
on Astroturf."
Let's get some refills in here.
EVVIE:
This is so crazy.
-All right, we're getting
a little more refreshments.
-Here we go, sir.
-Tiffany, while we do this...
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
-...question for you.
-Oh, no.
Does everybody know
about the night sneak?
Xander does not.
Did you know about it?
-Yeah, I know.
-Okay, he knows, now.
-PROBST: Okay.
So, when you do that,
what we like about
planning a night sneak...
I'm good right now. Yeah?
...is the, is the
Mission: Impossible of it all.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Which is,
you have to get out of camp.
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
-You're away from camp,
you have to get back to camp.
Which is the scariest part?
Is it leaving,
being gone or coming back?
He didn't know that I,
at that moment,
that I had got...
had gotten that advantage.
-And Liana and Evvie,
they knew I had to do it.
-(chuckles)
So, the most dangerous part
was coming back,
because it started to look like
it was gonna rain.
And that is the only time
that Xander would have woken up.
It was super stressful, but
it was really fun. It was fun.
Evvie, let's talk about one
of the big moves of the season
was Liana had
the knowledge is power.
(Tiffany chuckles)
She sure did, Jeff.
I need...
EVVIE:
Liana went on this journey,
and we thought that she gave
an advantage to Shan,
but it turned out that,
actually,
she received the
knowledge is power advantage.
And Shan kind of accidentally
revealed to Tiffany,
who then told me,
that Liana had an advantage.
So then Liana
felt compelled to tell me
she does have this advantage.
And Liana and I sat down,
and she showed me the paper
and I actually got to read
-exactly how
the advantage worked.
-Wow.
So it became clear, when my name
was on the chopping block,
that Liana
was no longer with us,
and Xander
had already been telling people,
"I'm gonna play my idol
for Evvie."
And so, when you're trying
to formulate a plan,
do you have to say,
"Hey, meet me by the tree,
I got an idea"?
Yeah, well, the amazing thing
about this Yase group is,
we had been working together for
so long that, pretty quickly,
I, like, flashed to Tiffany,
like, "We got to move the idol."
And she says to Xander,
"We got to move the idol!"
So we run into the woods,
Xander grabs his bag.
Really quickly, we shove
everything down Tiff's bra.
-(laughter)
-And Xander's putting
his fake idol
in his crotch,
right as Liana shows up.
LIANA: Guys...
EVVIE: Yeah.
LIANA:
We have to protect you.
-Yeah, no.
-Dude, I'm hearing my name.
-I'm really scared.
- Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
-Mm-hmm. 100%.
-Okay.
-Yeah, so...
And the timing could not
have been more perfect,
because she felt
that she walked in on him
putting the real idol
in his pants,
and it just worked out
perfect for us
that she really believed
that we still trusted her,
even though we really didn't,
and really saw
the writing on the wall.
And, uh, you know,
got to give it to Xander,
he acted the hell out of that.
-Yeah.
-(laughter)
Um, and, uh, to be honest,
uh, you know,
it was a really scary moment
for me,
'cause at the end of the day,
I still almost went home,
but to know that
we had this advantage,
we used our relationships,
our knowledge
that we were sharing
as a group,
to really thwart
the first time ever
that this advantage was played,
it was an amazing moment.
Xander, when you
watch a moment like that
as an audience member,
you forget you're watching
real people.
It kind of starts to feel like
a drama that you're watching.
But where's the heartbeat,
where's the adrenaline rush?
Because as Evvie described it,
Liana is seconds away
from showing up.
XANDER:
Yeah, I mean, it's such a rush
that you have
to formulate this plan
and figure out
exactly what to do,
based off of information
that I'm not even sure is true,
and I don't know who to trust,
but, you know, we're just
gonna go for it anyway.
And snap, she's here,
so we just got to do it.
So, I guess we've got a plan.
(laughs)
And, Liana,
when you're sitting at Tribal,
-and you're ready to make
this big move...
-(laughter)
...and flip the game
upside down,
walk me through
what you were feeling
and then how it felt when
you realized you'd been had.
Yeah, so,
it was a really big deal
that I even got the advantage
in the first place.
And when I got it,
I'm like, "Wow, like,
"the knowledge
is power advantage, like,
that sounds like my entire
experience being at Yase,"
because this whole time,
this guy is like,
I'm the only one that's not in
on, like, that he has an idol,
but I knew it the whole time.
So, like, this is great,
you know?
This is, like, the-the
perfect advantage for me,
it's the most powerful ever.
But I'd shown Evvie
the advantage already,
and I knew it was super risky
going in and playing it.
And so, I go to Shan,
I'm like, "Shan, like,
"I really think they,
like, moved it.
Like, I'm not so sure."
And I literally said...
I say this to her.
Something was off.
Like, my Spidey senses
were going,
but, um, this is a risky game,
I want to make this big move,
and, like,
I'm just gonna trust myself.
I just have one question
for one player.
Um...
Do you have an idol, Xander?
It blew up in my face, but also,
it was almost one of, like,
the proudest moments,
in terms of the game, for me,
in terms of
how I responded to it.
-PROBST: You did.
Handled it really well.
-OTHERS: Yeah. Yeah...
LIANA:
Yeah, that's what's so beautiful
about Survivor, for me,
and this experience is that,
you know, I-I fell on my face.
(bleep) Sorry.
(laughter)
I... I, like, face-planted,
for sure, but, like, honestly?
In my daily life, I say, like,
I'm-I'm really a pessimist
a lot of time and
don't really believe in myself.
And, like, I don't know how to
talk to these people after that,
'cause they saw me, like,
fall on my face.
And, like, what am I... like...
I'm, like, kind of worthless,
you know?
And there were kind of these
voices in my head of saying,
like, "It's okay to fail."
Like, "It's okay to fail."
And honestly, like, that was
the proudest moment for me,
'cause it could have gone
so different in my mind, like,
I don't even know
who this person is, right now,
that kind of just got back up
and is, like,
you know,
trying to pick up the pieces.
And so, it was just
really special for me
seeing the Liana
after that moment.
Do you think that's permanent?
I hope so, yeah,
I want it to be.
And that's, like,
that's the thing, like,
I think, leaving this game,
I am an entirely new person.
I feel like
I was kind of reborn.
You know, if I do fail, like,
just come back to this moment,
where, like, you know, like,
there's this voice in your head,
where you're like, "I did,
but you can get back up, Liana."
Like, and-and it doesn't matter
what anybody else thinks.
It's-it's about the voice
that's in your head that's like,
"It's okay. It is okay."
And there's...
As long as you're thinking
and you can get through it,
like, you can get through
anything.
And so, I was so proud,
the next morning,
just, like, talking to Evvie
and being like,
"Dude, like,
I know that was, like, horrible,
"but, like, that's the move
that I thought was best for me
at that time."
And just kind of, like,
owning that moment.
And honestly, like, that was
my proudest moment in this game.
PROBST:
And how ironic,
that "knowledge is power"
is what got you?
(laughter)
Can I get a slice of pizza,
by the way?
-(laughter)
-Would you like...
-PROBST: Yes.
Just a moment, we're gonna take
a break and we'll be right back.
Let me have a slice of that.
PROBST:
Up next, Evvie,
Ricard and Danny
share how their Survivor
experience changed their life.
All right, so we're here
in the jungles of Fiji.
We've just finished Survivor 41,
where Erika
was awarded a million dollars.
She hasn't got it yet.
I'm good for it.
(laughter)
PROBST:
So, I just want to kind of hit
on a couple of things.
Naseer, how do you explain
to somebody what it's like
to live with a group
of these people
in the real jungle in Fiji?
Jeff, being on Survivor
is my dream for ten years,
so I think I really enjoyed it
and-and appreciated every single
moment of this experience.
It is, and I would say,
it's one time--
How-how can I, uh...
-Once in a lifetime?
-Once in a lifetime experience.
There were no Survivor players
or castaways
utilized the island
the way I did.
Wow, you're getting
a lot of agreement.
-EVVIE: Absolutely.
-ERIKA: Mm-hmm.
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
DESHAWN:
Oh, my gosh.
NASEER:
Okay, food, please.
I'm like, "That's what I want."
Yes! (whoops)
I was so proud of myself
'cause of, like,
back home, 18 years, almost
18 year lived in Sri Lanka.
I-I felt like I'm-I'm back
to that age again, you know?
When I was seven years old,
wearing my slingshot, no shirt,
wearing a sarong, going around,
you know, hunting birds
and climbing coconut trees.
And I-I felt it, every single
moment and every single minute
-that I... when I was...
-Did you really?
Of course. Absolutely.
'Cause I achieved my dream.
Even though I did not win,
I'm so happy for Erika
and proud of her,
the way she played.
I'm here to inspire
kids that who
was growing up in "povertry."
-Uh, did I say the right way,
that way?
-Poverty.
-Poverty. Okay. Uh...
And also, kids that growing up
in small villages,
that they don't have
enough support or opportunities,
I want to
bring out this message:
Never give up on your dreams.
No matter what, or...
and where you live,
what type of culture you have,
you can wear your sarong
and still you can
achieve your dream.
-Beautiful. Love that.
-NASEER: Yeah.
And I-I did it,
and I'm-I'm proud of it.
-(laughs)
-PROBST: Congratulations.
Thank you.
Evvie, how do you
describe this experience?
(sighs) You know,
everyone told me, you know,
it's gonna be
a life-changing experience.
And I kind of came in thinking,
you know what, I...
I feel, of course,
that there's always, like,
growth in your life,
but that I entered this game
feeling, like,
pretty fully grown
and feeling...
feeling pretty confident
in who I am.
And I think
that's something I put out
is a lot of confidence
about who I am,
because I have had
growth in my life, you know?
But, for real, I never expected
to do anything in any challenge.
And the fact that I was able,
you know, in the course
of two days to,
like, feast a reward challenge
and win an immunity challenge,
like,
that was life-changing for me.
It really made me feel awesome.
And, like, it's really...
it is a life-changing
experience,
even if you are stubborn like me
and think that you can't grow,
you absolutely can,
and this-this place
makes it happen.
PROBST:
Uh, Ricard,
rawest moment for you?
Because even now, I can tell,
you're still working through
all of this vote-out thing.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm...
I'm-I'm struggling.
I-I had an image in my head
of what my journey
was going to be.
I thought I was going
to be winning today.
Like, genuinely,
I felt it in my whole heart.
But somehow,
even though the endpoint
was very disappointing for me--
and I'm working through it--
It was bigger,
and more beautiful and intense,
and I'm more proud of myself
than I thought was possible,
even though
I didn't achieve my goal.
Like, I did awesome.
Shan and I did awesome.
We were, like, a power couple
this whole damn time.
And, like, it's just...
it's amazing to me, like,
what I'm capable of.
DANNY:
I was about to say, I would
like to say something, too.
-Uh... (laughs)
-PROBST: Danny.
Just because, um, I think
I got a little-little bit
of something different out here
than possibly everybody else.
I came out here
thinking that I just,
I just wanted to compete,
try to find something
to compete at and win.
And, uh, I actually
came out here and found out
that I had a 25-year old demon
that I thought I was using
to propel me forward
in competitions and life.
And then, uh, all of a sudden,
found out that it was something
that I needed to release.
Have you shared
what that demon is?
Or maybe you don't want to.
-Is it personal?
-DANNY: Uh...
My dad passed when I was eight,
and we had this... I have
this history with car accidents.
And as an eight-year-old boy,
I didn't understand
how he couldn't stay alive.
Um, so, for my entire life,
I was upset,
and I was mad at everybody
who had their dad there.
Then I started to become
ashamed of myself
for thinking that way
for so long.
May 4th was the 25th anniversary
of him passing,
and we were all out here.
And, it was, it was hard.
But, um, they kept me laughing.
And I really had the opportunity
to sit back and think that
this has been holding me back,
not propelling me forward.
And I...
(chuckles) I let it go.
And, amazingly, I told Deshawn,
uh, I added my dad to the
"I want to make you proud" list
as I'm holding that-that thing.
And it gave me just enough
time to win that challenge.
PROBST:
Ricard drops.
-Xander drops at the same time.
-Oh, my God.
-Danny wins
his first individual immunity.
-DESHAWN: Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
DANNY:
And that's why I dropped
to my knees and-and shed tears,
'cause, I don't know,
I just felt something new.
I'm very grateful
for the experience.
I think I got everything
I needed out of here,
and I think
a lot of you helped me, uh,
get through some of that.
And I'm just happy and grateful.
Um...
Things are gonna change for me,
uh, when I get back, so...
PROBST:
Wow, thank you for sharing that.
Take a quick break,
we'll be right back.
Up next, your first look
at Survivor 42.
So, if you're just
tuning in, randomly,
-this is Survivor,
Survivor 41.
-(laughter)
We're doing our after show
in the jungles of Fiji.
I, also, just want
to answer the question,
if you're wondering,
where do you get pizza?
We make it.
Stu made this.
-Really good, right?
-Hell yeah.
-(overlapping agreement)
PROBST:
Have we missed anything?
Because this is really sort
of an impromptu conversation.
And the idea was to just share,
have a little champagne,
and, Evvie, yes?
I was just gonna say,
I think throughout the game,
there's a lot of talk about age,
and I think
I was super guilty of it,
you know,
sometimes, saying,
like, expressions like,
"Ah, these kids on my tribe."
You know,
I had the two 20-year-olds.
But when we look at, we had two
of the youngest people
to ever play,
and then we also had two older
women who were often targeted
as, like, weak,
and I was just...
listening to you say it,
I mean, I just think
we proved, like,
everyone can play this game.
And the two youngest kids were
sometimes the most mature,
brilliant people, saying the
most mature, brilliant thing,
and the two older women
were sometimes
the toughest people out here.
And I was just reflecting
that, like, if I was 20,
I could never look
like you guys,
and if I was, you know,
in my, you know, later days,
-I would never look
like you guys.
-Later days.
And, uh, I'm just really proud
of everyone out here.
And, like, in my confessionals,
-never said anything
about anyone's age!
-Ah.
You guys are all amazing.
Wait. Later Days wants
to say something.
-Uh, later age. 52, 52.
-I'm sorry.
-Yeah. Inside-- 28.
-Yes, 52.
-Absolutely.
-Outside-- 52.
-Thank you.
-Absolutely.
PROBST:
I got to say, having been here
every single day
of every single season,
the reason we're all
still out here
21 years in is because of this.
And what we do
at the end of a season,
that we never televise,
is we do this.
We don't sit down and talk,
but we bring in champagne,
and we bring in pizza,
and we bring in our crew,
because our crew never talks
to anybody,
because we don't want you
to develop relationships.
We want it to be about you,
and I'm looking at this group--
genuinely feel like
you reinvented the game.
And I wasn't the one
who came up with
"Drop the four, keep the one."
That was somebody else.
I took it, you adopted it,
you birthed it,
you dawned a new era.
And I just want to say,
personally, thank you,
because to Liana's point, to
Danny's point, Deshawn, Ricard,
all of you have shared
these really personal things.
And when we're watching at home,
and I watch
just like everyone else,
I get moved by your stories.
I get inspired by your stories,
I get entertained
by your stories,
and sometimes I learn
by your stories.
So, thank you for sharing.
And we're now going
to send you home.
We're going to stay here,
and bring in another group
of players
and shoot Survivor 42.
And I will give you
a little clue.
There are a few things from your
season that we're going to keep,
and we're going
to adjust a little bit,
kind of extend the experiment
and just see how they react.
All right, here's your first
sneak peek at Survivor 42.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
For our forty-second season,
the greatest social experiment
on television continues...
...as 18 new players take on
the most dangerous version
of Survivor ever seen.
(gasps)
MAN:
Being a firefighter prepares you
to you always expect
the unexpected, and
I'm excited about the challenge.
WOMAN:
I'm a smart businesswoman.
I have taken down
very smart businessmen.
MAN 2:
I have a world record
in pull-ups
with a hundred pounds
on my back.
But there's a million
world records,
but there's one Survivor.
PROBST:
How will they handle
risky Beware Advantages...
"You must say a secret phrase."
WOMAN 2:
"Potatoes have skin.
I have skin. Am I a potato?"
PROBST:
...crazy twists...
Ugh! There's always something.
PROBST:
...no food...
MAN 3:
I am starving.
PROBST:
...and a relentless pace
that will push them
to their limits.
WOMAN 3:
We have to earn everything.
WOMAN 4:
This game is so, so hard.
MAN 4:
What did I get myself into?
PROBST:
It's Survivor 42.
Premieres next spring.
All right, so on behalf
of everybody that's played,
this is it-- Survivor 41.
Survivor 42
will be on in the spring,
and we will see you then.
Good night, everyone.
-Good job.
-Fantastic.
Thank you, Jeff.
-Oh, come on.
-Ah, Jeff.
(overlapping chatter)
PROBST:
If you want to bid on props
from this season Of Survivor,
go to SurvivorAuctions.com.
Proceeds go
to Stand Up To Cancer.
And, what are you waiting for?
Apply to be on Survivor.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
♪ ♪
(roars)