♪ ♪
You want to dump
the rest of your water bottle
-so it's empty in there, too?
-Yeah.
Really?
BRAD: I'm awfully nervous
about JD right now.
I thought we had
a pretty good thing going,
but, at Tribal last night,
he was not consistent,
and he was not predictable.
That was a loose cannon
going off.
And then, when I saw
my name on the parchment,
my heart dropped,
because it's like,
"Oh, boy, this could be it."
BRAD:
So, I'm sitting in camp,
and I see Ricard and JD
head out to get water.
It doesn't take two people
to get water, you know?
And so you know
exactly what they're doing.
And my mind just
immediately goes,
"Dude, I can take
the beachfront,
and I can beat 'em to the water.
I know I can."
♪ ♪
And so I blaze down the beach,
come shooting over to the water.
And, uh, I kind of look around.
I'm like, here's a nice,
big old plump bush
just within ten feet
of the water hole, right?
And I just dive right in,
knowing I don't have
a lot of time.
So I dive right in there
and just kind of
get hunkered in there
as low as I can.
And I wait.
And sure enough,
here they come
right down the trail.
RICARD:
How you feeling?
I feel like...
I don't know if I could even
trust Brad at this point.
It's really scary
how-how quickly things flip.
I think he does think
you have the idols.
BRAD:
And so, they stop at the water,
and they're just talking away,
and I can hear
the word "he" a lot.
He, he, he.
Well, there's
three guys in camp.
Two guys are talking
about a "he." That's me.
-JD: Me?
-RICARD: Like, I...
No, yeah, I'm pretty sure
he feels strongly about that.
BRAD:
So, I'm a hunter,
and I know
in hunting game animals,
a lot of times
when you're close
you look at a game animal,
and they can feel that gaze.
They can feel that stare.
And so, I just
close my eyes and listen.
Last night, I felt really bad
about my position,
but, like, this morning
I feel better.
I feel a lot better.
BRAD:
JD has changed this morning.
He was so paranoid last night,
and now, all of a sudden,
he's relaxed this morning.
He's-he's calm.
It's, like, I think he must
have an idol in his pocket.
I know I kind of was, like,
being paranoid yesterday,
but there was no way
I was rolling that die.
BRAD:
They head off,
and so then I'm, like,
right back down the beach
fast as I can go,
because if I can
get back to camp
before they do...
no harm, no foul.
SHAN:
Brad is a little bit
unpredictable.
His wheels are turning,
and he is thinking.
I mean,
when he jetted out of camp
to go spy on them
at the well,
my Spidey senses were like,
"Oh, my goodness,
he could easily do that to me."
So, it's like,
can I trust you?
RICARD:
Yes.
Brad went over to the well
and was listening
to you and JD talk.
I didn't say anything bad.
I'm just trying
to make amends with JD
and make him feel calm.
Brad decided
to go up to Shan,
my closest ally,
and tell her
that he heard me
having a conversation,
which is dumb.
He's not good
at playing this game.
I want you to know that
that's what happened, because...
RICARD:
So, Brad's getting aggressive.
It's annoying, but he's actually
playing all of a sudden.
I don't want Brad at all.
I think he needs to go.
♪ ♪
(scraping)
This sucks.
ERIKA:
No, no, no.
It doesn't suck. You got it.
(chuckles) All right,
I'm-a scrape some more.
Sorry, guys.
DESHAWN:
I cannot start this fire
to save my life.
It is crazy.
The first time
I practiced at home,
it took me, my dad, my brother
about 13 hours to figure out
how to light a fire.
And ever since then,
I kind of got it,
but with a smaller knife.
Here, we have this
long-ass machete
that's, like, you can't even
get a grip on it, right?
And I'm just like,
"Dude, like, can I do anything?"
Well, if you need somebody
to beat in fire-making
-in the final four, it's me.
-(chuckles)
-Don't even. Don't even.
-I'm gonna be your guy.
(laughs)
NASEER:
I'm getting hungry now, guys.
May I try?
-DESHAWN: I'm gonna watch you.
-Thank you.
But at the same time,
I don't want to just jump in
and try to do things,
which is
I have been doing a lot.
That's what I want.
That's what I've been waiting
for a long, long time.
(exhales)
DESHAWN:
Oh, my gosh.
NASEER: Okay.
Guys, get some wood, please.
-We can't even
freakin' do fire, dude, like...
-I know. I know.
Like, this morning,
like, set it straight.
-(laughs)
-We can't do anything.
We are terrible out here.
SYDNEY:
It has become very clear
that Naseer
is absolutely essential
in the survival of this tribe.
Initially, we were trying
to learn as much as we could
from him,
so we could boot him.
But honestly, at this point,
I think I'm leaning towards
keeping Naseer,
especially as
we are getting to know him more.
Yes! (whoops)
I got it!
Yay!
♪ ♪
TIFFANY:
It's only day four,
and I'm completely exhausted.
I don't even understand
how I'm even upright.
So, I had a feeling that,
if it was gonna be 26 days,
it was gonna be hard-core.
And I was right.
We have no food--
not even a half a cup of rice.
So this is gonna be hell.
Plus, we lost
the first two challenges,
so we're in bad shape.
(sighs)
Maybe I should be
a little worried.
You think
Voce's been gone awhile?
-You want to go in a
different direction than me?
-Yeah.
Okay.
XANDER: So, Liana and I
are back at camp,
and everybody else is gone,
which is never a good feeling,
because you've got no idea
where they are.
Are they looking for idols?
Are they scheming?
We decide to split up,
but I'm not looking
for those guys.
I'm looking for an advantage.
I want it bad.
This season, you've got to throw
all you know about Survivor
out the window,
because
this is a new game
and I really got to make
sure that I'm prepared.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
Yes!
Oh, my God.
"Beware Advantage.
If you take it, it's yours,
and you must do what it says.
Otherwise, leave it."
(scoffs)
Damn.
Jeff's throwing
another twist our way.
It's an advantage, but it comes
with a twist, as we've seen so
many times, so far this season.
This could be something great,
or it could be something bad.
Man.
I mean, I've already taken
pretty big risks,
and the-the game's
only just begun.
So do I want to
take another one?
Screw it. I'm-I'm gonna open it.
No way.
"Congratulations.
You've found
a three-way shared immunity."
(laughs)
Wow, this is new.
"Each tribe beach has one.
"But in order
for your idol to have power,
"the other two idols
must also be found.
"Here's how you will know.
"At the next immunity challenge,
"you must say a secret phrase
in front of the other players.
"If another player
has found their idol,
"they will reply
with their secret phrase.
"Once all three phrases
have been said
"at the same immunity challenge,
"then all three idols
have power.
But until then, you cannot
vote at Tribal Council."
Holy ....
"This is why the advantage
says beware."
♪ ♪
Man, that's not good.
I'm gonna have to really
trust my alliance here.
Guys.
There are idols.
Luckily, I've got my two
closest allies--
Evvie and Voce--
and I feel like
they've got my back.
EVVIE:
"At the next immunity challenge,
you must say a secret phrase."
XANDER:
"Your phrase...
"'I truly believe
that butterflies
"are dead relatives saying hi.'
The other two phrases..."
What?
"But until then, you cannot
vote at any Tribal..."
Yeah. I don't have a vote.
So you don't have a vote
for any...?
I don't have a vote.
-Oh, you did get it? Yes.
-Yeah.
Thing is, like...
XANDER:
Yeah.
VOCE:
Holy hell.
Xander doesn't have a vote
right now,
which is kind of terrifying,
because that means there's
only four people voting.
Which means we might end up
two and two at the next vote.
Since you don't have a vote,
I really think
we could get Liana.
Like, Liana really trusts me,
I think.
-XANDER: So, if things go bad...
-EVVIE: Yeah.
-What's the plan?
-(exhales sharply)
XANDER:
I think that makes sense.
EVVIE: I think Liana is more
useful than...
-Yeah.
-Right?
There's this alliance
with me, Voce and Xander.
But the thing about Xander,
he found an idol
and he has an extra vote.
Right now he can't use it.
But still,
that's a lot of power.
VOCE:
Oh, damn, you're, like, loaded.
Yeah.
Clearly,
Xander's really dangerous.
So I want to go with the women.
It happens so much that
when a woman
is working with men,
at the end of the game,
the men get all the credit.
And I'm not
letting that happen to me.
And I also just feel most
comfortable with Liana and Tiff.
EVVIE:
Yeah, exactly.
LIANA: Do you think Xander's
really scrambling, though?
TIFFANY:
Yes.
-Yes.
-He-he keeps talking...
LIANA:
You know?
Oh, ... no. That is some ....
But we just need...
EVVIE:
I feel like I'm in a good spot.
I've built trust
with a lot of people,
but I won't be able
to maintain that trust
with every single person,
because, at some point, I'm
gonna have to put pen to paper
and say
where I really, actually am.
But for now
it's freaking awesome.
♪ ♪
All right,
Luvu getting your first look
at two new tribes.
Sara gone from Ua.
Abraham gone from Yase.
-(laughter and murmuring)
-Wow.
So how are you guys feeling
on day 50-- I mean, five...
-(laughter)
-...of Survivor?
Are you feeling it already?
-Yes.
-It's tough, Jeff. It's tough.
XANDER:
I mean, you know
how we're feeling.
You took away our flint,
and it rained last night, so...
we're exhausted.
No food, no sleep.
I mean, I woke up delusional,
thinking that I truly believe
that butterflies are
just dead relatives saying hi.
(chuckles)
-Wow.
-(laughter)
Everybody else
feeling all right?
Should we get to it?
-DANNY: Absolutely.
-LIANA: Let's do it.
All right, first things first.
Naseer, I'll take it back.
♪ ♪
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
one person from each tribe
is gonna swim out,
dive down and retrieve a key.
Then two other tribe members
will race across
a series of obstacles.
When all three are at the end,
the two remaining tribe members
will use that key to unlock
the pieces to the puzzle
they are trying to solve.
First tribe to finish...
-DANNY: Yes.
-XANDER: Oh, thank you, Jeff.
-(cheering, clapping)
-Yup.
-And the second tribe
to finish...
-TIFFANY: Thank God.
-PROBST: Win immunity,
safe from the vote.
-Oh.
In addition, you can tell
we are playing for reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yes.
-Oh, God.
First to finish,
a lot of fishing gear.
(excited chatter)
Second to finish, not as much
but still enough.
Yeah.
-Nice.
-Losers, no reward.
Tribal Council, where somebody
will be voted out of this game,
and, further penalty, I will
take your flint once again.
Luvu, you have one extra
person. Sitting somebody out.
Who's it gonna be?
-(quiet chatter)
-Yeah, I will.
Heather's gonna take
a spot on the sit-out bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
For immunity and rewards.
Survivors ready?
Go!
It is Sydney in the water
for Luvu,
Genie in the water for Ua,
and Xander in the water
for Yase.
This first leg
is a swimming leg only.
This is a race to
get that first advantage
by getting to the key first.
-RICARD: Come on, Genie!
-(cheering)
Xander picking up the pace.
It is Xander in the lead,
then Sydney, then Genie.
Xander gets there first.
Sydney goes down
looking for that key.
Xander can't get it
on the first try.
Sydney underwater
for a long time.
Wow. She's got it.
-Yes!
-Whatever, whatever.
Does Genie have it? No.
JD:
Take your breath. It's okay.
PROBST:
Xander has the key for Yase.
-Come on, dude!
-(cheering)
Go, blue!
It's Danny in the water
for Luvu.
Genie has the key now for Ua.
Go, Yase! Go!
It's Tiffany in the water now
for Yase.
Danny across the first obstacle.
Come on, Danny! (whoops)
-JD: Go! Come on, come on!
-Got to get to that mat.
Go, Ua!
-It is Brad in the water for Ua.
-VOCE: Tiffany.
-PROBST: Here comes Tiffany.
-VOCE: Come on, Tiffany.
JD:
Yeah, Brad!
Brad whipping across
that first leg.
Danny on that beam.
-(cheering)
-JD: Let's go, Brad!
PROBST:
We are very tight right now.
JD:
Let's go, Brad! Yeah!
Come on, Brad.
-HEATHER: That's it.
-DESHAWN: Good work! Good work!
PROBST:
Danny gets across.
Brad drops.
He's got to go back.
Tiffany gonna shinny across.
-Danny, get up that ladder.
-DANNY: Yes, sir!
Go, Luvu!
It's Naseer in the water
for Luvu.
Brad taking the conservative
but reliable approach.
JD:
Good job, Brad!
PROBST:
Tiffany falls off.
Brad is good.
There's Naseer,
whipping through this course.
-JD: Get up, Brad!
-PROBST: Brad,
got to get up there.
Go, Ua!
It's Shan in the water
for Ua.
-Now Tiffany and Naseer
on the balance beam.
-You can do it, Tiffany.
PROBST:
Here comes Shan.
It is Luvu down to their
last person in the water,
Naseer, who is inching
across the beam.
Here comes Shan
trying to catch Naseer.
-DESHAWN: There you go.
-DANNY: There you go, bro!
PROBST:
Tiffany drops again.
This is not looking good
for Yase.
Naseer is across.
Come on, Tiffany!
Yase has been a disaster
in challenges
this entire season.
Luvu, you're good.
Start working on the puzzle.
XANDER:
No, yes, yes, come on, fight.
Keep-keep going.
PROBST:
Shan is taking
the slower approach,
but it's working.
All right, so they're stacked.
Tiffany off again.
Shan is across.
XANDER:
Let's go!
PROBST:
Liana waiting for Yase.
Trying to get in this challenge.
-Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
-Yeah!
Erika's got one.
JD:
Come on, pull yourself up,
let's go.
You're good, Ua!
Start working on your puzzle.
It is Deshawn and Erika
on the puzzle for Luvu.
It is Ricard and JD
on the puzzle for Ua.
And it is Tiffany
past the halfway point.
Tiffany, let's go.
Every last bit of energy,
Tiffany! Get here!
VOCE: Come on!
EVVIE: Come on, Tiff!
(echoing):
You can do it! You can do it!
XANDER (echoing):
Tiffany, we're so close!
Tiff getting closer and closer.
You got this.
VOCE:
Come on. Believe in yourself.
You got it.
Let's go, Tiffany!
Tiffany is out of gas,
but she's across.
LIANA:
Yeah! Let's go!
And in the water.
-DANNY: Yeah, there we go.
-SYNDEY: Okay.
PROBST:
There's a piece by Deshawn.
Ua making progress.
Liana ready
to kick it into gear,
but first Tiffany's got
to get up the ladder.
VOCE:
That's right.
Go!
-(cheering)
-VOCE: Go, go, go.
You got this, Liana.
PROBST:
Deshawn and Erika for Luvu.
Ricard and JD for Ua.
-EVVIE: Come on, Liana!
-XANDER: You got this, Liana.
-Another big lead against Yase.
-VOCE: Come on, Liana.
DANNY:
Good job. Good job...
Good job. Good job.
Yes, yes, yes.
PROBST:
Another piece for Erika.
JD:
Something like...
Something.
PROBST:
Liana is making very fast work.
EVVIE:
There.
Wow. Liana sprints
across the balance beam.
She could put Yase back in this.
VOCE:
Come on, Liana. Get up.
PROBST:
You're good.
Go, puzzle solvers.
Voce and Evvie
now in this for Yase.
Big stakes.
Somebody going home tonight.
Does that go?
Ricard's not sure.
It is Luvu
with a bit of a lead over Ua,
but very close.
But Evvie and Voce
are making up time quickly.
-We're still in this.
-Yes. You got it, guys.
Don't give up.
Two tribes will win immunity.
Two tribes
will have fishing gear.
One tribe
will go to Tribal Council.
Another piece for Luvu.
There we go.
PROBST:
Voce with another piece.
Go. Good, good, good, good.
Let's go!
Ricard whipping pieces around.
Changing everything.
JD:
No, it's too small.
That's too small.
It has to be
one of the bigger ones.
That's too small.
PROBST:
Deshawn with another piece.
SYDNEY:
Deshawn!
PROBST:
Luvu getting very close
to winning
their second immunity challenge.
Luvu down
to their last two pieces.
(cheering)
Luvu wins immunity!
(cheering continues)
We're looking
for one more tribe.
It is Ua now in the lead
over Yase,
but Voce and Evvie
are fighting hard to stay in it.
Ricard trying
to get another piece.
Ua has been stuck
for a while,
and that door has opened
for Yase.
XANDER:
Green's struggling.
We're tied with green.
Keep going.
PROBST:
That door is open
if they can solve this puzzle.
You've got to get
some pieces going.
TIFFANY:
Stay focused. Stay focused.
We're good.
PROBST:
Ricard with another piece.
Suddenly,
Ua has some momentum.
TIFFANY:
No, no, no, no.
-(cheering)
-Another piece for Ua.
This is looking
like a familiar result.
There you go.
That's yes. That's yes.
With Yase in dead last again.
Ua on a roll.
One piece left.
-There it is.
-(cheering)
Ua wins immunity.
Safe from Tribal Council,
sending Yase
back to Tribal Council,
where another tribe member
will be voted out.
-You were so good.
-(whoops)
Luvu, congratulations
once again.
-Erika coming to get it.
-(clapping)
Your fishing gear will be
waiting for you back at camp.
Ua, also congratulations.
-Who wants it?
-(clapping)
Your fishing gear will be
waiting for you back at camp,
and you get your flint back,
as well.
Now, before I send you off,
another decision to make.
Luvu, as winners,
you have some power right now.
Two people
are going to leave here,
take a journey together
and then
make a private decision.
You're gonna decide who goes.
Choose one person from Yase,
the losing tribe.
That's your first choice.
-Evvie. Evvie.
-Evvie, Evvie. Evvie.
-PROBST: Evvie.
Evvie, you're gonna be
taking a journey.
Now, your second person can be
from Ua or from your own tribe.
What do you want to do?
I'm down to go.
I kind of want to go. Yeah.
-Deshawn.
-PROBST: Deshawn's
gonna volunteer to go.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Okay.
Bring in the boat.
Deshawn and Evvie
will take a journey together,
make a decision.
Hop on.
All right, y'all.
-All right, all right.
-ERIKA: Have fun.
(indistinct chatter)
You will return back to camp
before Tribal.
Head out.
♪ ♪
Ua, Luvu, enjoy the night off.
Swim out.
Head back to camp and celebrate.
All right, Yase,
Tribal Council again tonight.
Somebody will be
voted out of your tribe.
I'm gonna hold on
to your flint.
Penalty for losing.
Head out. See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
♪ ♪
TIFFANY: I'm so sorry.
I took some...
some time
getting across that beam.
My shorts
went all the way up here,
and it was scraping me,
and then I just lost balance,
and that was that.
I'm normally more athletic.
-I have no energy.
-I know.
TIFFANY: Losing the challenge
today sucked,
and I do feel like
it was a little bit on me.
Maybe I lost
a minute or two of time--
maybe three minutes--
but I still don't think it's
gonna affect my game that much.
Because even
though she's not here,
I'm sitting pretty
with Evvie and Liana.
Then we're voting out Xander.
So it really has to go very
wrong for me to go home tonight.
-And she's like...
"I'm gonna stop."
-It's like she was done.
And I was like,
"What are you doing? Move."
And she talked about, like,
scraping her legs. I don't care.
-It's immunity, like...
-Scrape your legs. Bleed.
-This is our life in the game.
-I know.
XANDER:
We just suffered
another devastating loss,
and Tiffany is someone
who is physically
bringing down this tribe.
The numbers
are certainly dwindling,
and you can't bank on
the traditional Survivor swap
or a merge coming.
We could be stuck
with this group,
and if it's
with the wrong people,
we're screwed.
-Nobody else said it.
-No one else said it?
-Damn it.
The other tribes can't
get their ... together enough
to find an idol?
-And Evvie's gone, which sucks.
-Yeah, I know.
VOCE:
We are basically
on life support right now.
We need to come up with a plan
that can keep this tribe
out of Tribal Council.
And right now that means
that Tiffany needs to go,
because Tiffany is a liability.
Liana, you're just going
down to the beach right there?
LIANA:
Yeah.
VOCE: I have an alliance
with Evvie and Xander,
but Xander lost his vote.
So now we need Liana.
LIANA:
Yeah, you're right.
-At some point, like...
-Yeah.
We're-we're just
gonna get obliterated.
I-I know.
And so it's, like,
what do we do at this point?
Yeah.
If we can talk to Evvie,
we can make something happen.
VOCE:
To get out Tiff?
LIANA:
Personally, after a loss
like that today?
-Yeah.
-I'm very open.
Voce's trying to get out
the weakest one,
Tiff, who didn't do that well
today in the challenge.
But what he doesn't know
is that me, Evvie and Tiffany,
we're gonna do
an all-girls thing
and blindside Xander.
He's playing
really, really hard,
and so that makes Xander
extremely dangerous.
TIFFANY:
Strength?
I can't believe this jerk
said my name.
I knew he was gonna
throw my name out.
Tiff.
TIFFANY:
Think about it for a minute.
Tiff, you heard him say
"butterfly" whatever.
He's trying to reach the
other players to get the idol.
-He's so dangerous.
-TIFFANY: You're right.
-That's why I...
-I'm not thinking straight,
because I...
-I had such a bad moment.
-It's okay. Give me a hug, mama.
(Tiffany chuckles)
LIANA: I really hope
that Evvie comes back soon.
We work really well together.
We're both very strategic.
We bounce ideas
off of each other.
And I'm gonna need help
with Tiffany.
She's all over the place.
I'm worried she's gonna
do something stupid.
♪ ♪
EVVIE: When I found out that
I was gonna be leaving my tribe,
right after
we lost the challenge,
to go on this journey,
my first thought was panic.
To be gone for hours
right before Tribal Council
is really, really scary.
I'm sorry for
bringing you here.
No, no.
No, man. No worries, man.
I mean, like...
I mean, I'm happy to be here
with you.
-Like...
-Okay.
-Let's chop it up.
-Yes. Yeah, right?
On the other hand,
it's very clear that Yase
is gonna be entering the swap
or the merge down in numbers.
So if I could have an ally
on Luvu,
which is gonna have
a lot of people,
that would be amazing for me.
I think Survivor
just put us on a blind date.
-DESHAWN: I think so.
I think so...
-(Evvie laughs)
♪ ♪
-Like...
-Yeah, a little bit.
A little bit.
-We're gonna be in the minority.
-Right.
EVVIE:
But I think
we can help each other.
-I think we should
help each other.
-You know?
(Deshawn exhales)
Ooh.
I'm serious.
I'm happy to do that.
-Awesome.
-Thank you so much.
-No problem, dude.
-I owe you something
in this game down the line.
No problem.
No, we'll just work together.
-That's it, you know?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
EVVIE: I know. No, seriously.
DESHAWN:
This trek up this mountain
was surreal, to say the least.
But my dad taught me the
three Ds when I was growing up.
And that's discipline,
determination and dedication
gets you the win
every single time.
DESHAWN'S DAD (echoing):
Remember them three Ds.
DESHAWN:
Just knowing all the stuff
that my parents sacrificed
for me in my life,
I don't know, I just feel, like,
a responsibility and pressure
to do well, you know?
When I was in school, I actually
wasn't really that smart.
I tell people,
"I'm not the smartest person,
but I work really hard,
and I have zero quit in me."
So I decided
to become a doctor,
which is something
that's really far-fetched.
You know, Black men are
the smallest demographic
when it comes to
practicing physicians.
So, um, all that said,
being here is surreal because
it's like, you fight so hard
to live your career dream,
-and then you get the experience
of a lifetime to come out here.
-We did it.
DESHAWN:
Look at this.
So I think my parents,
they're gonna be really proud.
Oh, man. Who do you think
is gonna go home tonight?
There's... It's like...
I'd say it's kind of
up in the air right now.
-Yeah.
-Like, basically I've heard
-Xander is the nicest kid
in the world.
-Wow.
-And we need him for challenges,
obviously.
-Yeah.
-But he came here.
-So, you know,
he might have an extra vote.
-Yeah, for sure.
So I think, honestly,
-I think it's p-probably
going that way.
-Probably gonna be Xander.
Which, everyone is gonna be
like, "You dummies.
-You need to win something."
-Right. "You need to win."
EVVIE:
I want Deshawn to know that
I'm someone he can work with,
and I want to try to give
him something to prove that.
But I don't really
want to give anything away
that matters too much to me.
Ready for me to solidify
our alliance even more?
Do you know anything about
how the idols work this season?
I don't have it.
But I know how they work,
and it's crazy.
-Okay. Tell me, please.
-Okay.
Basically,
on each of our beaches...
I'll reveal some things but
mostly other people's secrets.
That's basically my strategy.
So I think it's probably okay
to reveal some
of Xander's secrets,
'cause it probably
won't even matter tomorrow.
I know who has it on mine.
-Xander? Yeah, okay.
-Xander. That's the other reason
why Xander's in trouble
on our tribe.
-So be careful,
'cause it's a big risk.
-Yeah. No, I'm careful.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you for telling me that.
-Yeah, no, I got. I got you.
-You're-you're all good? Okay.
♪ ♪
All right.
"Risk your vote
or protect your vote."
EVVIE: My vote tonight
is extremely essential.
I've been gone from camp
all day,
and I need my vote tonight.
So I know, no matter what,
I'm gonna protect my vote.
And I also hope
that by protecting my vote,
I build some trust with Deshawn,
so that he could risk
his safely.
And I want to prove to him
that I do what I say,
and hopefully we are going
to be an alliance
moving forward in the game,
and that we can use
that extra vote together.
All right.
(birds squawking)
Yeah.
-LIANA: Evvie!
-VOCE: What's up?
...that thing is brutal.
Okay, let me fill you in.
And we did the decision thing.
It was...
XANDER:
Is it still "risk your vote"?
It was the exact same
that you said.
I was pretty confident
that he was gonna risk his,
so I protected mine.
So that's it.
I need to fill up my water
bottle if anyone wants to come.
-TIFFANY: I'm coming.
-Okay.
Coming back into camp,
I had no idea what to expect
because being away
from everyone else at camp,
you never know
what's going to happen.
-TIFFANY: Voce is scrambling.
-EVVIE: Yup.
EVVIE:
But whatever. It doesn't matter.
-Right?
-But wait a minute.
I know. I...
I... That's what I think. Right?
The only thing. We haven't...
We haven't won
-a freaking challenge anyway.
-Okay. Good. I'm down.
-Okay. And then we'll deal
with the fallout later. Okay.
-Yup.
EVVIE:
Us three girls are secretly
gonna blindside Xander.
He's vulnerable.
We could get that idol out,
we could get
that extra vote out
and have three women
in charge of this game.
And I just have to try
to make sure that the boys
believe that I'm with them.
VOCE:
Yeah.
-We've got to win. Yeah.
-I know.
So you guys are thinking Tiff?
I'm fine with that.
So Tiff? Okay.
And that protects me.
Hold on. It's-it's
whether or not he has the idol.
No, it's not. What keeps us here
today, tomorrow, no matter what?
-Just... just...
-The only way to protect me.
Listen.
If he has the idol,
the only way to protect me
is to put Voce's name down.
What does that tell you? I...
Listen, I know you want him out,
-but it has to be Voce.
-I know.
That's what I think.
There's a lot of things
going on right now
that I can't even
keep it all straight. Xander has
some sort of idol that he has to
come together with other people,
and I still am unclear if he has
one or doesn't have one.
Listen, he's savvy.
He might even be lying to Evvie,
unless I'm being one of those
stupid Survivor players,
which I really hope I'm not.
EVVIE:
Okay. Okay.
...butterflies in purple...
I read the note, dude.
I read the note.
It said that he had to say
"butterflies in purple"?
Yes. Yes. I read the note.
Because his idol doesn't work
yet, remember? His idol...
-Remember?
-Okay, because here's the thing.
EVVIE:
I don't think he has an idol.
Just in case, even...
'Cause...
EVVIE: Out of nowhere,
Tiff starts panicking.
She got a vote last time.
She knows
she might get a vote this time.
But I know for a fact that
Xander really can't do anything,
but Tiffany wants to vote Voce.
Liana, are you okay with it?
I know. I know you're not.
-I know you're...
I know you're...
-No.
EVVIE:
Now I'm having second thoughts
on who I really want
to work with in this game,
and the thing is,
Xander really, really,
really trusts me,
and that's huge.
Hmm. Yeah.
-LIANA: No.
-EVVIE: On this group of five,
I'm in the middle and will be
deciding who goes home tonight.
This is the craziest day
of my life, like, for real.
And no matter what happens,
Tribal's going to be insane.
(quietly):
The players are about
to walk in.
It could be a crazy Tribal.
It's either tribe strength
or alliance loyalty,
but somebody's going home.
♪ ♪
All right, so before
we get into it, I just want
to commend you guys because
you're vulnerable out here,
and you let us see you
at your best
and sometimes
your not best moments,
and that's what makes it
so compelling.
Starting with you, Tiffany,
because you had
a tough day in the challenge.
-I did.
-What is it like
just being vulnerable?
TIFFANY:
I'm not good at that.
I like to do my best.
I like to give 100%,
and I like to win.
But out here,
I've learned that
I can't be happy and social
and play this game on zero food
and no sleep.
And when it comes
to the challenge,
I think I can do it, but
I, at one moment, thought,
"I'm just gonna lay down
and I just hope nobody sees me."
And so, you want to give up,
but you can't.
-PROBST: Really,
the lesson is...
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
...Survivor will humble you.
Xander, you're a young guy,
you're physical,
you should be athletic,
but I'm sure
you've been humbled
out here already in five days.
XANDER:
Yeah, this is all raw,
this is all
real, and it's happening live,
you know?
I'm not sitting at home on
the couch watching and thinking,
"Oh, Xander's making
a great move."
No, I'm here, and
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Voce, how about for you?
Yeah, part of this experience
has been super humbling
because I'm used
to being in an environment
where you have to succeed.
In the operating room,
if you make a mistake
where you cut an artery,
that is devastating.
But one of the most
important things in surgery
is that you review your error
so that never happens again.
And we're, right now,
a tribe that's on life support,
and somehow we have got
to figure out where all
the bleeding is coming from,
because it's not stopping.
PROBST:
I have a question for you.
When we were talking
about Shot in the Dark,
and I said, "One in six,
roughly 17%,"
-and you said, "16 point..."
-16.66667.
PROBST:
Okay, did you know that already,
or were you doing that
in your head?
I knew the answers
to the fraction already.
Where does that come from?
As a kid, were you smart?
-What was your story?
-I actually was not smart
growing up as a kid.
My mother instilled in me
this mantra of,
"Whatever you do, work hard
and work to the best
of your ability."
She was a single mom
after my dad died.
She was raising me
and my sister.
She had to get up,
get us ready for school,
go to work, provide for us
as best as she could,
come home
and do it all over again.
And so it's all credit
to my mom for giving me that,
just that drive
where I want to succeed.
PROBST:
So, Liana, how do you
manage that
when you're at camp
going, "Well, we lost,
and we lost.
Therefore..." blank?
Yeah, you know,
like Voce was saying, like,
we're trying to find that
artery, where are we bleeding?
And everyone's version of where
we're bleeding is different.
That's what's so beautiful about
this game. We're a microcosm
of the real world, and we all
think about things differently.
But you just don't know
until you're up there voting
-what's going to happen.
-PROBST: So, Tiffany,
it would be very easy
for these four to say,
"Love you,
but you killed us today."
That had to go
through your head.
This is not
some shocking revelation.
Not at all. Not at all.
I absolutely
expected my tribe to think that.
But Survivor is not just
about challenges.
It's a social game,
and I'm really
banking on the fact tonight
that I've created bonds
and spoken to people enough
to know they're not going
to blame just me
on this one vote.
PROBST:
So, Evvie, Tiffany
is pitching the alliance portion
of this.
Give me the reason why
that makes sense in this game.
EVVIE:
Obviously, we'd want
this remaining
group of people
to win a challenge,
but we don't even know
that we're gonna be
in a challenge with this group
of people ever again.
You know, we could very well
swap tomorrow,
and then it would be
almost irrelevant
what everyone's individual
challenge strengths are,
and it would matter much more
what everyone's
individual relationships are.
On the other hand, if we do have
another challenge tomorrow,
none of us want to go down
to three people and enter,
you know, a merge
that far down in the numbers.
So it's really a balancing act
between those two things.
PROBST:
Xander, there's never a right
or wrong answer of,
should you be tribe strength
for challenges, or
loyalty strength for alliances?
It's just,
where is it going to go based
on the group of people?
XANDER:
I mean, you're totally right.
It's juggling chain saws,
whether you want to focus
on loyalty,
or is it someone who can help
get you further? I mean,
every person in this game
should be trying
to just get to the next day.
Because this game is
unpredictable,
and that's what makes it
so beautiful is that
you never know what's coming.
Like, there could be no swap.
This is truly
"drop the four, keep the one."
We should start fresh
and just consider
that, you know,
whatever gets us to the next day
is something
that's good enough.
All right, it is time to vote.
Voce, you're up.
♪ ♪
(quietly):
"Until three shared idols
have been found,
you cannot vote.
Return to your seat."
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
Anyone has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Tiffany.
Voce. One vote-- Tiffany,
one vote-- Voce.
Voce. Two votes-- Voce,
one vote-- Tiffany.
♪ ♪
Third person voted out
of Survivor 41--
Voce. That's three,
that's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Voce, the tribe has spoken.
Fail.
PROBST:
Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
-Good night.
-TIFFANY: Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Oh, my goodness.
I'm loving all the twists
and all the turns
and all the danger.
LIANA:
I was right there,
and I wasn't paying attention.
Maybe that's
my million-dollar mistake.
JD:
Ricard could have the idol,
you know. I still
haven't found it!
SYDNEY:
This is a very dangerous
season of Survivor.
I'm scared.
But I really am scared.
They got me good.
It's a big letdown
to be out this early
in the game.
I think I came into this game
with a mistrust of people,
and I instantly put my trust
in a couple of people
and didn't make sure
that my relationship-building
was going well
with the entire tribe,
and ultimately
that was my downfall.
No regrets. This was
an adventure of a lifetime.
(roars)