DESHAWN: You guys got messy,
again, for the second
-Tribal in a row.
-I've been...
Just do what we said
we were gonna do.
I don't understand it.
-And I was like, "Really."
-Heather, Heather,
-I love you to pieces.
-"Sit down and be quiet."
Heather, Heather, Heather,
I love you to pieces,
but right now
I just need a minute.
-Got it, but...
-What you did-- it was...
it was a little messy.
All right?
So I just need a minute.
Tribal Council was
absolutely a train wreck.
The plan was picture perfect,
but Heather stands up,
and she whispers
in a few different people's ear,
blows up the entire thing, and
then Shan says, "Vote Heather."
I didn't want to vote Heather,
so I said no,
and she jumped down my throat.
So now Shan is starting
to step on my toes.
You're starting to get in
the way of my million dollars,
so that started
to piss me off a lot.
Every time
that she has an opinion,
like, "Let's vote Heather,"
y'all sitting there looking
like y'all have nothing to say.
-Well... hold up.
-Why does nobody speak up?
SHAN:
It was like a whole
dramatic moment.
It just didn't have
to be all that.
Why am I bending backwards
for this dude?
He's more loyal
and more with them
than he is here, and that...
I don't understand that.
Everybody was like,
"Yes, let's vote Heather,"
except for Deshawn.
So we go back
to the original plan because
that's what Deshawn wanted.
Then he pouts, then he sulks.
That, to me, is immature, so
I just can't
with Deshawn anymore.
Shan is like a bulldozer
when it comes to her strategy.
I don't like to let people
tell me what to do in this game.
I came here to play,
and I'm not gonna
stop playing now
because Shan is telling
the group what to do.
It's just not gonna happen.
-I...
-This isn't your Survivor.
I'm gonna play it the way
I want to play it.
Like, I wish I would leave
this show because
I freaking made the decision
that you wanted me
to make, haphazardly.
-You didn't think about it.
-Yeah. I...
-And now look at you--
egg on your face. I'm done.
-Yeah.
EVVIE:
Coming back
from Tribal Council,
there were fireworks here
on our beach.
And that's fine with me because
things are gonna shake up
around here.
-ERIKA: Well, I was like...
-EVVIE: Chaos doesn't
help the people in power.
Chaos helps the bottom people.
So this cast is amazing for me.
♪ ♪
LIANA:
Oh, look at this beautiful sun.
ERIKA: These are the moments
we have to enjoy
-despite the craziness.
-LIANA: Yup.
It was not the way
things was supposed to go.
And I have to apologize to you
that I have to realize
I got to push through when
people don't communicate with me
the way I need them
to communicate.
So there is validity
to your points.
So I am...
I'm sorry that you don't
feel always heard by me.
That's something
that I want to work on,
even in this game.
I want you
to feel always heard.
It was a good talk
that Deshawn and I had.
I'm glad that we were able to
kind of repair that a bit, and
I don't want to seem like I'm
the one calling all the shots,
so, you know, I need to listen
to all the opinions, but also,
getting the way
I want the vote to go.
-Uh...
-And I can tell you,
Erika more so than Heather
'cause Erika's the mastermind.
-Um... yeah.
-I don't trust Erika
and Heather.
DESHAWN:
I was just trying
to smooth things over with Shan,
but yet again, she was just kind
of telling me what to do. Like,
she has very little tact.
I think that the group
of Ricard, Shan, Liana, Danny,
and I guess myself-- finicky--
I think the group
is already dissipating.
-...it's, like, back and forth.
We can communicate.
-Yes, yes.
-I don't...
-I know.
DESHAWN:
So right now I'm just trying
to play the middle.
I have to have conversations
with Evvie because
I feel like we can do
some damage together.
-And likewise.
-Yeah.
-Deal...
-How many is that?
-This will be 17.
Just want to tell you I'm not
upset with you or something.
Okay? It's a... That's...
Yesterday is gone.
Today is a new day.
I did not write your name.
Okay. And you throw my name
under the bus for sure.
Okay, that's fine.
Yeah, I know.
You don't believe...
-I did not write your name.
-XANDER: I know
for a fact
that Heather didn't vote
for Naseer
because it was me, but
I'm keeping my mouth shut.
It's great to stir up chaos
when you're on the bottom.
It's perfect that they're
fighting with each other.
-I was like,
"Something is wrong."
-Do I buy that? I don't.
I don't buy it.
What part don't you buy?
I don't buy anything
that you say now.
It doesn't matter.
Ask Evvie who she was told
to vote for.
Here, Evvie.
Can I ask you a question?
-Yes. Yes.
-When I asked you
on your shoulder,
knocked on your shoulder,
-I said "Who are you...?"
-Oh, yeah.
At Tribal, you said,
"Vote Naseer."
I-I didn't say, "Vote for him."
I said... You said, "Naseer."
HEATHER:
Last Tribal, I got caught
trying to scramble.
-Wow.
-HEATHER: Oh,
it totally backfired.
I ended up with a big old...
on my back.
So, yeah, yeah, I got... I got
a little lecture today.
-Got it.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
(groans)
What a lovely family.
NASEER:
Oh, that looks good.
-SHAN: Bon appétit.
-EVVIE: Amazing.
Uh, I'm so excited.
ERIKA:
So you lost, like, hearing
in your right side,
like, not when you were born.
It was, like,
-something that happened.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-So do you normally, like,
wear your hearing aids?
-No.
Because of my job,
there's so much
ambient noise,
it's really hard for me.
I don't really
wear it often, but...
Oh, I'm fully deaf in
my right ear, and I read lips.
-Wow.
RICARD:
Most people don't realize
I'm hard of hearing, but
since I was a kid, I've been
fully deaf in my right ear.
At times, that can be very
frustrating and very annoying.
It-it just made me scared
coming into the game.
(indistinct, muffled chatter)
EVVIE:
Where's the button?
(indistinct, muffled chatter)
Good-good for you. I'm okay.
But I'm really thriving.
(indistinct, muffled chatter)
That went in
and it'll be like, "Poof."
And then you want some, like,
rice to cool it down, too.
RICARD:
Reading body language
and reading lips--
I tune out everything else,
and I just see it all,
like, appearing in front of me.
This game is really testing me,
but I've really been blossoming.
I think I'm just kicking ass,
and it just makes me think
maybe I can be the first
hard-of-hearing winner.
And I'm in a really good spot
Day 17.
SHAN:
I felt like,
for the first time last night,
I just knocked out
-and was...
-DANNY: It went long.
-SHAN: Yeah.
-But, yeah, day 17.
-Right?
-EVVIE: Just think there...
SHAN:
Yeah.
ERIKA:
Like, are you serious?
You don't even see
that we're, like,
-right there?
-I guess they think
that, like, all the people
on the bottom are so scattered
that we could never
work together.
-LIANA: Yeah.
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh, yes.
-SHAN: Yes, yes, yes.
Not and, like, be low-key.
I don't trust Erika,
not with some...
-There's something off there.
-Right.
You think maybe we should be
voting either Shan or Ricard?
-Maybe.
-Like, could we do...?
Could we pull in Naseer
as a number and tell him
-we're voting Erika and Xander?
-LIANA: Yeah.
Xander's been a problem for me
for a really long time.
He continues to make it this far
with the idol in his pocket.
It just makes it
more apparent
how much of a threat
he is in this game and how much
he does need to go.
What if we did...
I think it's better.
Everyone's obsessed
with Xander
because he's got the idol, but
I want to get rid of Erika.
I feel like she's probably
one of the smarter players
in the game,
and I don't trust her.
Not even a little bit.
Come on in.
All right, let's get to today's
immunity challenge.
First things first, Evvie.
Take back the necklace.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to balance
on a very narrow perch
with your hands
holding onto a handle
behind your head.
If at any point,
a hand comes off the handle
or a foot comes off the perch...
you're out.
And to make it
a little more interesting,
today, we're going
to divide you into two groups.
-Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: So,
two people will win immunity,
be safe.
Both groups will go
to Tribal Council
-separately
and vote somebody out.
-EVVIE: Ah, man.
-(others murmuring)
-So two winners,
-two people going home.
-Oh, gosh.
In addition, playing for reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
-(whooping)
-XANDER: Let's see it.
PROBST:
The last person left standing
in the challenge not only earns
immunity for themselves,
but you earn chicken
and beef stew
-for your group...
-Oh, man.
to be enjoyed back at camp.
We're going to draw for spots
to see which group you're in,
and we'll get started.
Gonna be a good one.
(whooping)
♪ ♪
All right, everybody,
take your spots.
Get your feet up on the perch
and your hands
behind the handle.
Your feet are facing out.
(soft groans)
PROBST:
Everybody get comfortable.
-Ready?
-Heather's ready.
Is everybody ready?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yup.
Let's not waste any time.
This challenge is on.
Two groups.
It is Erika, Shan,
Ricard, Naseer and Heather
competing against each other.
In the other group,
we have Deshawn,
Evvie, Liana, Xander and Danny.
One person from each group
will be going home.
This is about pain management
'cause it's gonna hurt.
(wooden creaking)
I've watched people do this
over the years.
I know it's hurting already.
This is not a comfortable spot.
Everybody hurts
in this challenge.
You just keep fighting because
you never know when the person
next to you is going to drop.
-Jeff.
-PROBST: Evvie drops out.
You can take a spot
on the bench over here.
Evvie-- first out.
Ooh.
-(wooden creaking)
-PROBST: Shan literally
shaking, but still up there.
(Heather exhales sharply)
-Oh, God.
-PROBST: Heather drops.
Liana drops.
-Oh!
-Shan drops.
-EVVIE: You got it, Xander.
PROBST:
Shan is out, and just like that,
we're down to three in yellow.
It's Erika, Ricard and Naseer.
And we're three on blue--
Deshawn, Xander and Danny.
-Ooh.
-LIANA: You got it, Danny.
I'm not dropping.
-I'm not, either.
-(laughs)
Guys, I can stay two hours
if you want.
-Let's do it.
-NASEER: Let's do it.
SHAN:
You're looking great, guys.
HEATHER:
Good job, guys.
You're looking great, Naseer.
(rattling)
-PROBST: Danny suddenly drops.
-(groans)
He went
until he could not anymore.
We're down to two in blue.
It is Deshawn and Xander,
fighting for immunity, and it is
Erika, Ricard
and Naseer for yellow.
SHAN:
You got it, Ricard.
-You got it.
-(wooden creaking)
PROBST:
Ricard drops out
and into the sand.
-EVVIE: Good job, Ricard.
-DANNY: Yeah, Ricard. Good job.
-LIANA: Good job.
-PROBST: We're down
to a showdown
on yellow and blue.
It is a showdown
between Erika and Naseer,
and a showdown
between Deshawn and Xander.
The stew! The stew!
PROBST:
Immunity and stew on the line.
Bring it home, Naseer.
You got it.
-I promise you.
-PROBST:
You'll be a hero who is safe.
Best place to be in this game.
SHAN:
Hold on, Naseer.
I can't feel my right hand.
-Naseer, calm, maintain.
-Hold on.
-Calm down.
-PROBST:
Naseer really struggling.
-No, I'm not, Jeff.
-Naseer, get your hand
-on the back of that,
not the cap.
-I can't feel it.
Sorry. You got to move it,
or I'll call you out.
PROBST:
On the back of it.
Your hand, right hand.
-I can't feel it.
-PROBST: Naseer is out.
Don't drop.
-Erika wins individual immunity.
-(indistinct chatter)
Erika is safe tonight
at her Tribal Council.
She's now trying
to win chicken and beef Stew.
She can't do it.
ERIKA:
I'm sorry, guys, sorry.
-Keep grinding.
-Erika is safe, but we now know
that blue will have chicken
and beef stew.
Oh, hey, we got the stew, man.
-We got it.
-PROBST: The question is,
who will have
the immunity necklace
while they are enjoying it?
-We're feasting for sure.
-Yup.
-I'm sorry
I couldn't go on, guys.
-No, it's okay.
It's okay.
You hung up there as a girl.
-You did so good.
-PROBST: Deshawn fighting
through obvious pain,
but he is fighting through it.
ERIKA:
You're both looking good.
-Keep going.
-PROBST: Five feet to his left--
Xander.
PROBST:
Xander's body's starting
to shake a little bit,
starting to twitch.
Yeah.
(wooden creaking)
It's the last showdown--
Deshawn and Xander.
-For immunity.
-NASEER: Doing good, boys.
ERIKA:
Keep going, boys.
-Keep going.
-(wooden creaking)
-Come on, Deshawn.
-Keep going.
-Doing great.
PROBST:
Xander's fighting through it,
still twitching
but still strong.
When you win Survivor,
you can look back and say,
"I earned
-every minute in this game."
-(groans softly)
"Even challenges I didn't win,
I gave everything in the tank."
ERIKA:
Keep going. Keep going.
-LIANA: You got it, guys.
-You guys have
all you need to win. Keep going.
-PROBST:
You're at 33 minutes.
-SHAN: You got it.
You got it, Deshawn.
You've got it, Xander.
-ERIKA: Keep going, guys.
-SHAN: Looking great.
You guys are both
looking great up there.
PROBST:
That a way to fight, you guys.
-SHAN: Oh!
-PROBST: Deshawn drops out.
Xander wins individual immunity
and reward for his group.
What an effort. Take a break
-in the sand if you need it.
-Good job, guys.
Both guys trying
to find their bodies again.
(applause)
Huge effort.
-Man, if I can get
my arms around you.
-Oh, man.
-PROBST: Wow.
-(laughing): Oh, my gosh.
-LIANA: Wow.
Erika, come on over.
Oh, my gosh.
Dream come true.
Oh, my gosh. I've just dreamed
of this moment
-since I was a kid.
-Congratulations.
You fought hard. You've earned
individual immunity.
You are not going home tonight.
Head back to your group because
-somebody is going home.
-ERIKA: Thanks, Jeff.
Xander, come on over.
SHAN:
Xander.
-Good job, Xander.
-PROBST: I was gonna say,
"Did you dream
of this as a kid?"
But you kind of are
still a young man.
Yeah, I mean, oh, my God,
to have this moment.
And, like, this challenge
I've dreamed of so many nights.
Since it's aired,
-like, this is made for me.
-PROBST: Congrats.
Go ahead and head back, Xander.
Good job.
PROBST:
Heather, Naseer, Shan,
Ricard, one of you going home
tonight.
You know it won't be Erika.
You're gonna go now
to the old Ua camp.
Grab your stuff, head out.
We'll see you tonight
at Tribal Council.
You will go first
and vote somebody out.
And then go back
to our real camp?
Then you go back
to your real camp.
-RICARD: Okay.
-Okay, that's good.
Xander, Evvie, Liana,
Danny, Deshawn, you will go
to Tribal Council second.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
-Enjoy your well-earned reward.
-Thanks, Jeff.
LIANA:
The fact that Xander won today,
I mean, it's just, like,
so bad.
He knows he has power
on his neck,
and that's not good for my game.
Every single draw,
it's like I'm with Xander.
I'm like, what is going on
with this kid?
Like, can I get some space?"
EVVIE:
Oh, my God. This is so...
Look how much food this is
for the five of us.
It's also perfect 'cause
you always talk about stew.
-EVVIE: Yeah.
-XANDER: I know.
This is, like,
all I've been dreaming about.
I have been dreaming of stew.
And, aw, it hit the spot.
It does look good.
-Are you ready to dig in?
-It does.
XANDER:
I can't imagine a better day.
I have immunity.
I also have an idol, and
now that the numbers
are down to five,
this is a huge opportunity
for me
to take out the big dogs
on the top. Exactly what
I've wanted to, or...
(burps)
Still digesting that stew.
(laughs)
This is so ... good.
It's unbelievable.
EVVIE: Initially
just looking at the group,
I thought that for sure
I would be in trouble.
But the reality is,
Deshawn is really out
on the power group, so I think
for sure I have Deshawn, but
Xander-- he and I have
had a bumpy road,
especially the last couple days.
So if Deshawn is with me
and Xander's with me,
I should be fine.
I mean...
EVVIE:
Liana.
Yeah.
Liana's someone
who's almost a minion to Shan,
and that's so dangerous.
Not only that.
She has no trust in me.
She wants me gone. So,
Liana would be fantastic
for me to get rid of.
Yes.
DANNY:
It's a simple vote.
Evvie is going home tonight.
Fortunately,
the luck of the draw gave us
three people
that are in our alliance--
me, Deshawn and Liana.
With only five people,
we have the power,
uh, in this vote.
-This is the chance.
-I know.
For me tonight,
I'm definitely writing Evvie,
but my biggest worry is
Xander has an idol.
If he were to potentially
play it for Evvie,
that could be a huge problem.
I could go home tonight.
What are you thinking?
I want to hear the name
that you have.
Most threatening--
between Evvie and Deshawn.
XANDER:
Between Evvie and Deshawn?
-LIANA: Yeah.
-Everybody
wants Evvie out, though.
-She's not someone
we have to worry about.
-Okay.
I don't know.
The hesitancy is,
you do have your idol.
-Yeah.
-So...
I'm definitely... I'm... I'll
have you know I'm considering.
I woke up on the bottom.
Now I'm the prom king, and
everybody wants to take me aside
and give me advice in the game.
Like...
-You would do that?
-Well, I mean, not to you.
It's a little funny to me
that Liana feels
in a place to make demands.
She's got a big target
on her back,
and she knows it.
Liana has shown her cards,
and I'm ready to expose them.
XANDER:
They've got such
an interesting dynamic.
EVVIE:
Uh, on the other group-- I know,
I was thinking about that.
-Would be Naseer and, uh, Shan.
-Yeah, Shan.
-EVVIE: Right?
-XANDER: Both have idols.
-DESHAWN: Yeah.
-EVVIE: Yeah.
EVVIE:
And Shan and Ricard together.
XANDER: But Erika
and Heather are really close.
-EVVIE: Right.
XANDER:
And then that leaves Naseer,
and he's such a wild card.
SHAN:
Well, it sucks being back at Ua.
Man, our camp is much better.
-I hate it here.
-SHAN: I hate this camp.
Erika winning was a bad thing
for my game
because I did want her out.
-Heather, do you want
to go pick some limes? Okay.
-Yeah.
SHAN:
So maybe this is an opportunity
to get Heather out
because Heather is an ally
to Erika.
Well, I know Ricard and I
are a solid two,
and we've been working with you.
I mean,
it's three votes on Heather.
-Okay.
-And if we need to,
I have an extra vote
I can put on her.
Okay, and I don't want you
to waste your idol.
I don't want you
to waste yours, either.
That's what I'm saying.
Stick together.
NASEER:
I feel amazing.
Heather will be going home.
Plus, I have
an hidden immunity idol.
I have everything
that I want for tonight.
I'm like cool like cucumber
no matter
what situation is happening.
-Mom, I'm sorry.
-HEATHER: What?
Wow.
These two are my closest ally.
ERIKA:
There must be, like,
something else we can do.
Yeah, but you just have
one idol?
-Yeah.
-Would you play that
for Heather?
Yeah. No way.
-No?
-So I have to take care
-of myself, you know?
-Mm-hmm.
-Got it.
-ERIKA: Naseer seems confident
it's going to be an easy vote,
and Heather's going home.
It is a bit of a heartbreaker
for me because
it's no secret to anyone
that Heather and I are close.
I really am saying,
do what you need to do.
-There will be no hard feelings.
-Yeah.
-I'm ready to talk about that.
-I'm-I'm not voting for you.
Okay. I understand.
(stammers) I get it.
-Who? Naseer?
-Naseer. Yeah.
So I would love
to get rid of Naseer,
or I was hoping that, like,
maybe there's the chance
to vote out Shan.
The problem is, there's
so much power concentrated
with the people
who are here,
knowing that Naseer has an idol,
Shan has so many advantages.
It seems like
there's not a lot of options.
I really did want
to split up Shan and Liana,
but I'm hoping,
on the other side,
-they take out Liana.
-I hope they do.
-We were talking things out.
-Yeah?
I just feel like
you guys have been...
...with Shan and Ricard
and Liana.
I don't even feel
like I'm in it,
and I don't want to be in it,
because I want to play
my own endgame.
DESHAWN:
Whoa. Are you serious?
Xander's telling me Liana
tried to flip the vote on me,
but I don't know
if that's the truth.
But at the end of the day,
I'm gonna be at the top,
and that's not even me
trying to be funny.
It's just me being real.
Like, I've put myself
perfectly in the middle.
If there's a move
that you guys
want to make
that I could help you with,
I'm down to do that.
XANDER:
I'm willing to say
right here now...
Let's do it. Done?
-Yeah, let's make it tomorrow.
-Do it, please.
Evvie and I had made a deal
before we even knew that we were
splitting into this five,
and we said we were going
to protect each other.
-Okay. Okay.
-Yeah.
DESHAWN:
But if I take out Liana,
there are gonna be repercussions
from the power alliance,
and then that could put me
in a compromising position.
'Cause right now they think
we're still together.
DESHAWN:
This is where
the rubber hits the road.
I want to play my game
of Survivor,
and as long as Xander
doesn't play his idol,
I'm the one deciding
who goes home tonight.
I'm ready to work with you, and
if you say you want to do it,
-Yeah.
-...then I'm with you.
-I just want
to give you my thoughts.
-Oh, Evvie? Tonight?
-Yes. Yes.
When-when else will we have
the opportunity to get her out?
XANDER:
I was really convinced that
Danny and Deshawn were ready
to work with me, but Danny seems
kind of wishy-washy,
telling me
Evvie would be a better move.
Just think about it. I'm willing
to do whatever you want to do.
XANDER:
And that scares me because
they could work together to try
and blindside her
and pull some big move.
And I'm gonna have
to try and stop that.
So, maybe I should play
my idol for Evvie
because this Tribal is crucial
for the rest of my game.
SHAN: What do you think
is gonna happen
on the other side tonight?
We never know in this game
'cause Xander--
he has the idol.
He may play to Evvie.
-Yeah, we never know
-RICARD: We'll just see.
It doesn't even affect
our plan.
-SHAN: Yeah.
-Yeah.
Everyone has this huge target
for Heather,
and I'm baffled by it.
She has no advantages.
She has no idol,
and yet everyone's focusing
their attention on her.
And so, I have to focus
on an actual threat.
-They are going to vote you.
-Mm-hmm.
But they both have idols.
-Yeah. Yup.
-Okay, that's scary, but
I think
Naseer is the bigger threat,
and I need to make Naseer feel
so comfortable
-that he doesn't play his idol
tonight.
-Yes.
And I think
that really is a possibility.
-It needs to be that it's me
to make him feel good.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. I'm sorry.
-No, I'm... I agree.
RICARD:
If we make him feel really safe,
-he's gone.
-Mm-hmm.
HEATHER:
Oh, my God! This is epic.
Going into Tribal tonight, I
got to try to do the poker face
and just convince Naseer I'm sad
that I'm going home because
if Naseer plays his idol,
the votes are left on me.
If I need to get voted out,
I'm okay.
Like, I know
I'm at the very, very bottom.
Yeah.
HEATHER:
Ricard has come up
with this great plan,
and I'm hopeful everybody will
do their part to make it happen.
Those two are going
to be voting Naseer,
and we use the extra vote
on Naseer, but...
-Yeah, it's two-three.
-...we need to make sure
there's a Heather vote
out there.
And we need to make sure
there's enough of them
in case they do
try anything sneaky.
So then
we're all gonna vote who?
Naseer, and then he's gone.
Then we're fine.
I want to vote
Heather's ass out.
No! Heather makes no sense,
Shan.
Absolutely none.
She has nothing.
She has no alliance
except Erika.
She has no advantages.
Naseer has an idol.
-Because I don't trust
Heather and Erika.
-I don't care.
That doesn't make sense.
But can I have the extra vote
to do this?
Well, I'll cast the extra vote.
Will you?
I will cast the extra vote...
To take out Naseer?
I don't know. I-I just
don't know if I can trust Erika.
This is very, very risky because
I don't trust Erika and Heather.
I just get
the hibbity jibbities.
Like, I just don't get
the best vibe.
I just don't...
I just want to make sure
it's not gonna
turn on me or Ricard.
Well, it might, but...
SHAN: I feel like
Naseer is another number for me.
And so,
the easy move would be
to just cast all the votes
on Heather
and even maybe save
the extra vote
for a little bit further
down the road.
That is you making a decision.
That's not how
this game is supposed to go.
It's not what one person wants.
It... it is...
Uh, uh,
I don't know if that's...
I don't know
if I completely agree with that.
I feel like everybody's
doing that in their own way.
RICARD:
It's complicated with Shan.
I know she has my back.
But that doesn't
necessarily mean
she's gonna follow through
with the plan
because it has to be her way
all the time.
And it does not make sense
to get Heather out tonight.
If not, I will literally
kill you guys.
RICARD:
Naseer, to me,
is the biggest threat, but
I have the most high-maintenance
alliance ever.
If Shan is not willing
to budge on her stance,
then Heather could be bye-bye.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, so, Ricard,
after the challenge,
you guys were sent back to Ua.
-Which sucks.
-(laughter)
-It's just awful.
-PROBST: Do you even care
that you're there?
Does it just become about,
"What are we gonna do?
There's only five people,
-and Erika's safe"?
-RICARD: I mean,
Shan and myself have clearly
been together
since the very beginning,
and we've been very close
with Naseer,
and Erika is clearly safe.
And so, there seems
to be a more clear-cut choice.
PROBST:
Heather, does this ring true
that
you could be
a very easy vote tonight?
I am the easy vote tonight.
You know, I'm still hopeful
there's going to be a miracle,
and some idol is going
to just fall out of the sky.
Cue the idol.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
(laughs)
-Didn't work, did it?
-PROBST: What's the move?
If you feel
you're on the bottom,
do you just hold,
or do you try to make a move?
I-I... I don't have a-a person
that I could point to
at this point
because I don't have the goodies
to keep me safe.
I don't have the idol,
I don't have the extra vote.
-It's just me right now.
-ERIKA: I mean, it's not like
we laid down our swords.
Like, Heather and I are a pair.
We pitched to everyone.
"Like, we're two votes,
if you want to do something."
But the problem is,
everyone knows
where the advantages are.
And the advantages are not
with Heather and I.
So I think if you're not someone
with an advantage,
it actually creates, like,
all these obstacles for you.
Why does everybody know
what everybody has?
We know we had to activate--
it was a three-way activate.
NASEER:
Activate a three-way
shared idol, so,
I do have
an hidden immunity idol.
And we've worked hard
to get that power.
I don't want to give up
that power to save someone else
'cause maybe I may need
to use for myself.
PROBST:
Shan, often when people know
you have an idol,
you're worried
they're going to come for you
because they want you
to play it.
-Yeah.
-But it sounds like
this group has a different
maybe approach this season.
I-I mean, it-it seems
like there's an obvious
decision to make tonight,
because
Naseer, myself and Ricard
have been voting together.
But at the same time,
I feel just as much at risk.
You know, the only person
that's safe tonight is Erika.
Ricard, any time
there's a small group like this,
it is dangerous.
But every time
there's a dangerous situation,
for someone
there's opportunity.
What's complicated
with this particular season--
it's not very easy to say,
"Oh, this person has an idol.
Let's vote them out."
The reality is,
the three of us have
three advantages in this game.
And you're gonna make the same
argument to all of us saying,
"Oh, I can't say,
vote this person out
"'cause they have an idol
'cause you have an idol.
And I can't say that to you
'cause you have an advantage."
It's just a hard day, hard day.
It's a hard day for everybody.
Why is it hard for you, Naseer?
'Cause Heather and I--
we had a relationship.
Like, from the beginning,
it's like on a roller coaster.
But I approached her
'cause I'm still learning.
There's a lot to learn.
So, she's a great teacher,
and I really respect her
like mother.
But that person is about
to leave.
That is hard.
(groans)
It's okay.
PROBST:
What just came on?
What emotion just hit?
I'm here because I wanted
to do this for 20 years.
Right from the beginning,
I was going to start
at the bottom,
you know, because I'm older
and these disadvantages.
And I came out here, and
every day has gotten better,
and I've learned something else
about myself
and about other people.
And I'm proud
that I've made it this far.
Can't wait for my kids
to see this.
I really am proud of myself.
PROBST:
On that note,
it is time to vote.
Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
Sorry, Mama.
I'll go tally the votes.
All right,
if anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Heather.
Naseer. One vote-- Heather,
one vote-- Naseer.
Heather. Two votes-- Heather,
♪ ♪
Heather. Three votes-- Heather,
one vote-- Naseer.
Naseer.
That's two votes-- Naseer,
three votes-- Heather,
one vote left.
Naseer. We're tied.
Three votes-- Heather,
three votes-- Naseer.
♪ ♪
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna revote.
You can only vote
for Heather or Naseer.
Heather and Naseer, you can only
vote for each other,
so you won't vote.
Ricard, you're up.
Will you come grab this?
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
I'll read the votes.
♪ ♪
First vote-- Naseer.
Naseer.
-♪ ♪
-Ninth person voted out,
and the second member
of our jury--
Naseer. Naseer, you need
to bring your torch.
Good playing with you guys.
-Good playing with you, too.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for everything,
Naseer.
♪ ♪
Naseer, the tribe has spoken.
You can take your spot
on the jury next to Tiffany.
-Good job, guys. Bye.
-Good job, Naseer.
Thank you.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
We'll bring in the next group.
♪ ♪
Bye, guys.
Unfortunately, I was blindsided.
But did I enjoy
every single moment here?
Absolutely, 100%.
It was my dream
to be on Survivor
and to enjoy Survivor.
And I did it
every single moment I'm here.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Getting your first look
at what just happened--
Naseer voted out.
Wow.
-That's crazy.
-PROBST: Danny,
that's how real the game is,
how fast you can be out.
He was sitting in one of these
seats just a few minutes ago.
DANNY:
It's-it's very nerve-racking.
I think we all would have bet
that Naseer would have
played his idol
tonight and been safe,
but a lot of us don't
have protection here.
Xander's the only person
who's for sure not going home.
PROBST:
So, Xander, not only do you win
immunity for yourself,
but you win
chicken and beef stew.
-By the way, Jeff, you undersold
the hell out of it.
-Yeah. Oh, my God.
XANDER:
It was so good.
Hearty potatoes, warm broth
and carrots and onions,
and that was
-exactly what we got.
-PROBST: So, Deshawn,
you get back,
you have this nice reward,
which is great
because it's fuel.
But the bigger question is,
now what?
DESHAWN:
Yeah, I mean,
it's unfortunate because
there are four people here
who I wanted
to really work with
and who I feel
like I've developed
decent relationships with,
but there's nowhere to hide
in this Tribal Council.
Somebody has to go home,
and unfortunately
it's going to be somebody
who I actually wanted
to work with in this game, so...
PROBST:
So, Liana, you guys have had
some crazy
Tribals so far,
but this is different
'cause it's a small group.
Do you feel that?
Absolutely. I think, you know,
there's four of us
here on the chopping block.
25% chance of going home.
So, you know,
it becomes even more real.
Like, the game is as dangerous
as it's ever been.
And it's very real,
and my heart is beating so fast
in my chest right now
because of how real it is.
Xander, did you have
more power today
because you were safe, and
there's an odd number in five?
I mean, yeah. Certainly, people
are going to be kissing up
to the person
who does have the power.
And it's important to pay
attention to which people are
actually genuine and who I want
to go forward with.
PROBST:
Evvie, everybody's cagey.
-Nobody's really said anything.
-Right.
That seems true. (laughs)
I mean, I'm sure
there's a number of plans, but
I'm, like, 75% sure
that what I think is
gonna happen will happen.
Let's do that.
Let's just go around the horn.
Liana, how comfortable are you
that your plan is the one
that will happen tonight?
Pretty comfortable.
PROBST:
How about you, Deshawn?
I'm pretty comfortable.
-How about you, Xander?
-I'd say pretty comfortable.
PROBST:
How about you, Danny?
Before I walked up here
to Tribal,
I was pretty comfortable.
And then realization hit me once
I saw Naseer sitting up there
that you-you never really know,
and the reminder's sitting
right there in front of us.
Deshawn, everybody here must be
playing a very good game
because everybody's
pretty sure they're right.
If all of us here are saying
that we're pretty comfortable,
somebody lied
to somebody, so I think
we're gonna find out,
like, who's who in the zoo
when it comes
to who's telling the truth
and who's not, so we'll see.
PROBST:
Evvie, does that excite you
that you're playing
-with people
that are this good at it?
-EVVIE: Absolutely.
I mean, it's like you're
at the top of a roller coaster
and you, like, feel like
you're gonna die.
But, like, the fun part is
when at the end, you don't die.
I... you know, I've gotten
to the point where I, like,
looked Survivor death
in the face
and lived,
and it's freaking exhilarating.
You know?
But, uh, I really think
that the thing that I think's
gonna happen will happen.
-So, I just hope it happens.
-PROBST: So, Deshawn,
using Evvie's analogy,
we're up here
on the roller coaster then?
DESHAWN:
Absolutely.
We're all in this car,
this roller coaster car
together, and unfortunately,
in this scenario,
somebody's going to die.
On that note, it's time to vote.
Liana, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
PROBST:
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Liana.
Evvie.
Liana. That's two votes-- Liana.
♪ ♪
Evvie. We're tied.
Two votes-- Liana,
two votes-- Evvie,
one vote left.
Tenth person voted out, and
the third member of our jury...
-Damn.
-Evvie.
Damn.
All right. Good game, guys.
♪ ♪
Evvie, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Bye.
-Well played, guys.
Take care.
Damn.
Good one, guys.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
DESHAWN: As long as Ricard is
in the game, Shan is
the most powerful player.
RICARD:
Deshawn continues to lie.
It bothers me.
It annoys me.
SHAN:
Seeing Deshawn talk with Erika--
he's really sneaky.
Well, you know, they got me.
That's Survivor.
I honestly am not exactly sure
who flipped on me, but I was
living on borrowed time anyway.
You know, I did my best.
I'm incredibly proud of myself.
Like, I had an absolute blast.
I can't complain.
Survivor's the best game ever,
and I'm-I'm so happy
I was a part of it.
Any queer kids out there--
be yourself.
You're amazing.
Love yourself.
(roars)