LIANA:
Honey, I'm home.
DANNY:
Oh, my God.
-SHAN: Oh, my God.
-We were shocked.
-ALL: Oh!
-LIANA: Yeah.
DESHAWN: So, tonight
we had a double elimination.
So the outcome of Tribal was
exactly as I-I wanted it to be,
and Evvie went home.
Unfortunately, Xander and Evvie
were the only ones
that were shocked.
-Yeah, for real. For real.
-SHAN: Oh, my goodness. Okay.
Um, so, I know
Naseer was the one
that most folks wanted out,
and so I suggested for Shan
-to use her extra vote.
-SHAN: My extra vote.
LIANA:
Okay. Slam dunk.
Yeah, you just blind...
HEATHER: 'Cause he told me
he has two idols.
-That's crazy, man.
-Then he said that he had...
ERIKA:
Right now,
Shan is definitely, like,
the biggest threat to win.
The hardest thing with Shan is,
she has an idol,
and it's almost like
giving, like,
a baby a machine gun.
People are afraid to target her
because they know that
she could play the idol
at any second, and then
you could get hit
with a stray bullet and go home.
Yeah.
I... My preference would be
to get out Shan and keep Xander.
Because Xander has
no relationships.
Shan-- who knows
who she could pull in.
DESHAWN:
Erika wants to-to make
the move to take out Shan,
but there's just so many factors
that go along with that.
I know that I have this
really loyal alliance in Danny,
Liana and Shan behind me,
so I want to go ahead
and keep that strong,
but at the same time,
Shan and I have had
our differences, and
I'm smart enough to know
she can win this game.
So it might be time
to take out Shan.
Yeah.
SHAN:
Seeing Deshawn go off
and talk with Erika
makes me a little bit nervous.
My concern with Deshawn is that
he's really sneaky, you know,
and he's very charming, and
right now
I just don't feel like
I can trust Deshawn completely.
And so, seeing him walk off
with Erika makes me think
that they might be trying
to pull a blindside.
And so, I'm worried about that.
Honestly, like,
I think at this point,
like, you got to do
what's right for your game,
-and I got to do what's right
for my game.
-Yeah.
Like, that's... I feel like
that's where it's at.
I feel like everybody's
kind of scrambling, and...
But the thing is,
though, like...
-Yeah, I mean...
-I know Danny wants the four,
but, like...
we want to play our own game,
and we want to win the million
individually, but it's, like,
there's still this bigger
picture, and it's, like,
do you do it for the culture?
Do you do it for your...?
Like, in my case, like,
I'm swamped in debt.
-Yeah.
-Do I do it for my ability
to pay off my student loans,
or do I do it
for the bigger picture?
You know what I'm saying?
Well, a few years ago,
I was homeless, so I'm like...
-Exactly.
-"Do I do it for the culture,
-or I do it for a home?"
You know what I mean? So...
-Right.
Exactly right, and everybody
has, like, that story, right?
SHAN:
Deshawn comes to me, and
he reassures me that, you know,
he wants to, you know,
go final four
with me, Liana,
Danny and himself because,
you know, we really want
to give the Black community
back home something
to celebrate because we know
that 2020 was a hard year.
And so, whenever we refer to,
you know,
doing it for the culture,
that's what we're referencing.
And so, you know,
I wanted to do that, too.
I... you know...
But I've also made these all...
these other great connections
in that game
that-that... that go beyond
the color lines.
And so, it makes it really tough
at this point.
I don't think people will
understand how hard it is
until you... until you get here.
Like, you think
it's an advantage...
I wanted to do it
for the culture,
and then us all
duke it out, but...
I would love that.
I would love it, but I...
I don't... I don't know
if you really...
-At this point, you kind of...
-I-I... I-I don't...
I'm not... I'm not... I'm not
a liar. What I say I mean.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-You know, I just...
I need to know
that I can trust you,
that's all, and that's...
-It's hard right now.
-You can.
Last night when I spoke
to Erika, the plan was,
we were gonna try
to get Shan out of the game.
But then
I had some talks with her,
and I really do feel like,
coming into this game,
if there were gonna be
Black players here,
that I wanted to play with them.
But it gets tough because you
still want to win for yourself.
But there's, like,
that duality. Like...
Like...
Hold on for a second.
SHAN:
At some point before Tribal,
we're all gonna figure out
if we trust each other or not.
-Yeah.
-And the vote will tell.
-You know?
-Yeah.
The people before us did
so much for us to be here.
And the year
that we just had-- 2020 was...
It was rough, bro.
It was rough, and...
You get this opportunity,
the opportunity
you always wanted,
and...
you feel like the number one
person standing in your way
is your biggest supporter
and your biggest ally
and the biggest person
that you said, like,
you would never turn against
in this game because, like,
we don't get these
opportunities. Like,
this is the first time
we had an opportunity like this,
like, where we all could
just work together, and...
It's just hard 'cause I don't
want to turn my back on any
of the three of them,
but, like, I...
What am I going to do
for myself? What do I do?
Come on in.
♪ ♪
All right, let's get
to today's reward challenge.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna be attached
to a rope
that is woven through a series
of obstacles.
On my go, you will race through
those obstacles to the end
where you will solve
a Survivor star puzzle.
First person
to finish wins reward.
Want to know what
you're playing for?
-(all assent)
-Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Best reward of the season.
You'll be taken
to the Survivor sanctuary
where you will enjoy
pizza under the stars.
Really?
PROBST:
You will then spend
the night in a shelter
with blankets and pillows.
(laughs)
And return to camp
the next morning
fully rested, with a break
from the game and a full belly.
-Worth playing for?
-Absolutely.
-Yes, sir.
All right, we'll draw
for spots, we'll get started.
Let's do it!
♪ ♪
Here we go.
Survivors ready.
Go!
This first leg is just getting
to the obstacles.
So this is about swimming
or walking,
whatever you want to do.
It is Xander and Liana
in the lead.
Now you've got
to follow the rope.
Wherever that ring needs
to go to get through the rope,
that's where you need to go.
It looks so simple--
just follow the rope--
but it's not easy at all.
You can easily get confused,
tying yourself up in knots.
There goes Liana.
She's through.
Liana heading to that
second set of obstacles.
Ricard is through.
It's Liana and Ricard.
Erika now has made up
a ton of time.
-(shrieks)
-Heather's back in this.
Danny's in it.
Shan is in it.
There goes Xander.
Everybody's in it right now.
Keep digging, everybody.
It's now Ricard and Liana
at the very end, untying rope.
Xander struggling
to figure it out.
Ricard is through.
Go to the puzzle.
♪ ♪
Liana, you're through.
Get to your puzzle.
Here comes Deshawn.
He's in on the puzzle.
Here comes Danny. He's now
gonna be in on the puzzle.
Xander had the early lead,
but that's gone.
It is Deshawn, Ricard,
Danny, Liana,
and here comes Erika,
all on the puzzle.
Biggest reward
of the season on the line.
We have done this puzzle before.
It is not easy,
but it's very clear
when you have it right.
The pieces fit.
Xander's through.
Shan is through.
Heather's through.
Pizza under the stars,
a warm shelter,
blankets, pillows,
a break from the game.
Day 18.
Food in your belly is important
with an immunity challenge
coming up.
Deshawn with another piece.
It is now Deshawn in the lead.
Here comes Ricard,
not ready to give up.
Ricard fighting back now.
It's now Deshawn and Ricard
at about the same spot
on their puzzle.
Nobody else close right now.
It is now Ricard
picking up the pace.
It's now Ricard in the lead.
Ricard with another piece.
Ricard with one more piece,
if he's right.
That's the question--
is it right?
And it is!
Ricard wins biggest reward
of the season.
-SHAN: Good job.
-Wow.
All right, Ricard.
Nice job. Come over here.
Good job, Ricard. Good job.
PROBST:
Best reward of the season.
Choose one person to join you.
RICARD:
Um, so,
Shan has not had
a single reward,
and we've been together
this whole time.
Come on over, Shan.
Choose one more person.
Heather also has not had
a single reward
-this whole time.
-Me?
And she's been a trooper,
and last night sucked, so...
All right, Ricard,
one final person.
This is a strategic decision.
RICARD:
Um, one other person has been
very, very selfless,
has given up two opportunities
for reward
and gave us rice, so, Xander.
PROBST:
Xander, come on over.
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-ERIKA: It's okay. It's okay.
-Thank you.
No reason to apologize, bro.
All right, Ricard,
Shan, Heather, Xander,
you'll be taken to the Survivor
sanctuary for a nice evening.
Danny, Liana, Erika, Deshawn,
got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Everybody head back to camp.
Enjoy your evening.
Well deserved.
-Thank you. Thanks, Jeff.
-Thanks, Jeff.
DANNY:
So Ricard wins,
and I'm realizing
that he's playing the jury up
by picking other people
to go on the reward with him.
And in Survivor, you have
to knock the people out
who you think can beat you
in this game,
and he is slowly becoming one
of those guys
who we won't be able to stop
if we don't do it soon.
♪ ♪
DANNY:
So, me, Liana, Erika and Deshawn
are back at camp.
Hey, we got some burlap going
right now. Oh, there you go.
DANNY:
And
the other group is going
to eat pizza,
giving me the opportunity
to make a big move.
To see if something...
-Yeah.
And if it is, then, uh...
You want to go?
-Yeah, let's make money.
-All right.
Ooh.
-Wow. Okay.
-DANNY: I think with Ricard,
he's working with us, we've been
working strong in our alliance,
and now it's just come
to that point to where
he's become a very, very
big threat to win this game.
-But it's gonna be
difficult, bro.
-Hmm?
-What? To get...?
-To get him out
at this next vote's
gonna be difficult.
We would need five.
DESHAWN:
So I'm in an alliance with Shan,
but as long
as Ricard is in the game,
Shan is
the most powerful player.
So, we created this awesome plan
to take out Ricard
without letting Shan know.
And if Shan's upset,
you can be upset,
but what do you...?
Who do you have after that?
When he leaves,
you're going to come back to us
'cause you have no other agency.
If it works out, that's perfect,
but we need to talk
to, uh, Liana right now.
LIANA:
Uh-huh.
Somebody is gaining...
gaining a lot of steam.
-Mm-hmm.
-Who is that?
-Shan?
-No, no.
-Erika?
-Ricard?
-Yeah.
LIANA: Okay. Uh-huh.
I'm listening. Yeah.
Ideally, we do this plan,
but the thing is, like,
obviously Shan--
I don't know if she would be
able to be a part of this plan.
Yes.
I really do feel closest
to Shan, and so,
this is something I'm really
genuinely struggling with.
But at the same time, it's like,
I don't want anybody else
dictating my game.
I want to play my own game.
No, I know.
LIANA:
If I vote Ricard,
this move would
differentiate my gameplay
from Shan's and prove
that, you know,
I've made moves on the island.
You know,
Shan wasn't this ringleader.
You know, like,
I took out her main guy.
♪ ♪
-Ah.
-(Heather giggles)
Holy smokes.
This is great.
RICARD:
Getting to
the Survivor sanctuary
after winning the reward--
it was really awesome.
-Xander, you and I can
split veggie.
-All right.
RICARD:
It's like a shipwreck,
and it's beautiful
and really rustic.
Like, I love it.
It's very, very cool.
-Thank you for this.
-Thanks, Ricard.
Thank you for this gift.
-Thank you so much, Ricard.
-Oh.
RICARD:
Getting to do something kind
for Shan felt good.
Regardless of how our allyship
goes, how we vote together,
if we continue on together,
the reality is,
she has an idol, and she has
people who can back her up.
I don't have that.
I don't know how to do this
because I feel like
you're my best friend
on this island.
(Ricard laughs)
-You know, like,
what do we do here?
-Yeah.
You know, like...
-We'll figure it out.
RICARD:
We have not ever said
to each other we are final two.
And we have enough respect
and love for each other to say,
"Hey, we're gonna have
to fight it out one day."
My hesitation-- it's like
I think people like you more.
-I think...
...my hesitation is that,
like, I always feel like
a man will beat a woman
in the end.
And I feel like
this season'll be different.
It might, it might.
'Cause in 2021...
You know?
-It might. It might.
-Like, there are just...
there are a lot
of things there.
I don't want to talk
about it right now.
I don't want to talk about it.
I just...
I don't want to talk
about it, but I...
But...
It's not the time.
I know that my relationship
with Ricard is solid.
While I have
a lot of love for him,
this is still a game
for a million dollars, and I...
I want to win, and so, I have
to figure out what I'm gonna do.
(Shan hums)
What you singing over there?
Oh, sorry. Nothing.
Um, I was thinking.
Okay, so that's what I want
to talk to you about.
I don't trust Deshawn.
LIANA:
Mm-hmm.
But then I want
to do us four in the end.
Mm-hmm.
I had that moment
with you at the summit,
which was the biggest moment
for me in the game.
-Mm-hmm.
-Even now,
it, like, makes me emotional
just thinking about it.
LIANA:
I'm on board
with Danny and Deshawn,
but the thing
about this Ricard plan is,
without Shan knowing, so, I go
back to, you know, the summit.
(crying):
And... there's
nothing in this game more
precious to me than the moment
that me and Shan
were on the summit
on top of that gigantic hill,
just connecting over our moms
and our Blackness
and our womanhood.
And I was like, "You know what?
Like, I love you.
I love you, Shan."
And even if that means,
you know, it's idiotic of me
to sit next to you in the end,
I really don't care.
Okay.
...you know, wanting...
Hold on, people are coming.
Yeah.
But... it...
No, no, no, not tonight.
'Cause they want...
SHAN:
I just knew it.
You know, I just knew
they were up to that.
Which is fine.
They're playing their game.
They have to play that game.
But, you know, I don't want
Ricard leaving just yet.
That's not...
that's not my goal.
'Cause Deshawn's gonna play
the hell out of this game.
-So I think we need
to vote Deshawn tonight.
-Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Danny, Deshawn and Liana worked
up a blindside against you
last night because they want
to separate you from me
because they want us
to go to the end as a four.
So, the plan is,
you, me, Liana and Xander
are gonna vote out Deshawn.
Okay.
-They're gunning for you, kid.
-Okay.
Let me process it.
-You don't believe me?
-No, I'm not saying I don't.
Let me pro... I mean, that's
a lot of information to take in.
So who are the ones
voting against me?
Danny, Deshawn and Liana.
Okay.
-But, yeah, I'm fine.
-Are you gonna go
say something to them?
No. No.
-I need to think.
I need to... Like, I...
-I know. I know.
I'm a little... You know,
my hand's a little shaky.
I have you.
I got to say, I'm surprised
that you would tell me.
-That I would tell you?
-Not...
Like, I'm not surprised
as like a friendship.
But I'm surprised,
you know, like,
that you would tell me.
Well, I mean...
-We've been from the beginning.
-We're gonna have to...
I know, but we're gonna have to
fight each other at some point.
I know, I know, I know, but...
-not yet. (sniffles)
-Okay.
When I hear that Deshawn
wants me out, it scares me.
I'm going to work my hardest
to win immunity today,
-because if I don't win...
-DANNY: Gives you an advantage
if you get to the post first.
-Yeah.
-...they could get rid of me.
(indistinct chatter)
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yeah.
-First things first. Xander,
got to take it back.
Waited so long for you
to say that.
Aw. Erika,
got to take yours back.
Gosh. You're taking Xander
and I's friendship necklaces.
-(laughter)
-Oh, well,
glad they have another purpose.
Today, one will have...
-no purpose.
-ERIKA: Oh.
-SHAN: Oh, okay.
-HEATHER: All right.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
-Yes!
-Yeah!
-(whooping)
PROBST:
For today's challenge,
you're going
to stand on a narrow beam
while balancing a ball
on a disk.
At regular intervals,
you will move
to a more narrow part
of the beam
and move your hand
farther down the pole,
making it more difficult.
If at any point,
you fall off the beam
or your ball drops, you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
Losers, on the other hand,
Tribal Council where somebody
will be voted out
and join the jury.
Big stakes,
get bigger every day.
We'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
-Let's do it. All right.
-Do it.
All right, here we go. Everybody
put your ball on your disk.
Get it where you want it,
and then I'll count you down
to take your hand off.
Three,
two, one.
This challenge is on.
Very simple game on the surface.
Lot tougher than it looks.
Concentrating on lots of things.
Your feet on a narrow beam.
Your hands on your pole.
Balancing your ball
on your disk.
And just like that-- Liana.
Just a little bit of movement,
and she's out,
and we are down to seven.
You have one job right now--
keep your ball on your disk.
19 days into this game,
you don't want this
to be the downfall.
You lose this silly little
challenge, and you're out.
15 seconds left in this round.
And then we'll move down
a little farther on the beam.
Danny drops, will not make it
to the next round.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody put your hand
on your ball.
All right, everybody move down
to the next section of beam.
You're also going to move your
hand down farther on the pole.
Put your ball back up.
Here we go. Three, two,
one. This challenge is back on.
Erika drops,
can't get the transition.
Erika is out.
We are down to five.
We'll be here for ten minutes.
Heather's ball moving
all over that disk.
Can Heather get it back?
No, Heather's out.
We're down to four.
It is Ricard, Xander,
Shan and Deshawn.
Deshawn--
little bit of movement.
Xander locked in.
Ricard-- ball moving
for the first time.
Shan is locked in.
No sooner do I say that,
her ball starts to move.
Hang in there.
Shan continues to have
to navigate a moving ball.
Shan in trouble.
And once again, crazy save.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody put your hand
on your ball. You are all safe.
-Good job, guys.
-Really good job.
PROBST:
Now we move down
to the most narrow part
of the beam.
Your hands are in the same spot.
All right,
I'm gonna count you in.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
This challenge is back on.
Shan off balance.
Can she save it?
No, Shan is out.
We're down to three.
This is much more difficult.
You'll be in this spot
for ten minutes.
(birds chirping)
Other than a few birds chirping,
not a single sound.
Just Ricard, Xander and Deshawn
fighting for immunity.
How nice it would be
to go to Tribal tonight
with that necklace.
But you got to earn it.
You got to stay
in your own zone right now.
That's the trick
of this challenge.
You can't be distracted.
Don't worry about anybody else.
Deshawn-- ball moving a lot.
-(sighs)
-Deshawn finally drops.
And we are down to two.
And now, almost side by side,
we have a showdown.
Ricard and Xander-- both
have won individual immunity.
Now it's just full-on
who will outlast the other.
Ricard has been very solid,
Xander's been very solid.
And we've seen lots
of challenges
where players looked solid
and then dropped.
Ricard with a nice recovery.
Xander's ball moving
for the first time.
Xander drops.
-Wait. Did I win?
-PROBST: Ricard wins
individual immunity
for the second time.
(cheering, whooping)
Guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
Ricard, come on over.
Yeah.
For the second time this season,
individual immunity is yours.
You are safe tonight, guaranteed
a spot in the final seven
of Survivor 41.
As for the rest of you,
after 19 days,
one of you will be going home
tonight.
Won't be you.
Congratulations.
Grab your stuff. Head back to
camp. See you tonight at Tribal.
DANNY: Going into
the immunity challenge,
the worst case scenario would be
if Ricard wins.
But he somehow pulls it out,
and my heart drops.
You know, we lost our
opportunity to get Ricard out,
so it's back to square one
and try to figure out
what to do next.
-Good job, Ricard.
-Good job.
Good job, Ricard,
with your jewels.
-RICARD: Thank you.
-ERIKA: Good job.
Congrats, Ricard.
This was a tough one.
SHAN: Ricard wins, and I'm glad
because that means, like,
he's immune, he's safe,
so I don't really
have to go to bat for him.
SHAN:
I could get Deshawn out,
but because Ricard is safe,
I want to keep
the waters super calm.
-There you go.
-SHAN: Voting Erika
can be simple.
A lot of us want Erika out.
She's smart, she's sneaky.
And so, I'm actually okay with
letting it be Erika tonight.
SHAN:
I think that's what we do.
I think we put all of our votes
on Erika, but we don't
give Xander a name
so that he feels nervous
and he plays the idol.
-That's the safest thing?
-SHAN: That's the safest thing.
We just put all of our votes
on Erika. It's five of us.
Even if they have four,
it's five of us.
And we don't tell Xander
anything. I think
-Xander's gonna
keep his extra vote.
-DANNY: I think so, too.
But I think
he's gonna play his idol.
-Just don't talk to Xander.
-DANNY: Let's just do that.
RICARD: Shan is a very special
person to me.
But when she decides to get rid
of me with her four people,
I'm next. That was supposed
to be the case today.
I was supposed to be going home
today, tonight,
but I won the challenge.
-SHAN: Are you in?
-I'm in...
-LIANA: But hold on...
RICARD:
So I've decided
that today is the day
for Shan to go.
(squeaking)
XANDER:
I'm-I'm probably gonna play it.
RICARD:
It's a bummer
because I honestly think
it would be a waste,
but I have an idea.
Erika, me, you, you.
That's four.
HEATHER:
I like that plan.
-Yeah.
-Shan.
-I like this.
RICARD:
We have four votes
to get out Shan.
We only need one more, but
I don't feel like
there's anyone I can really
guarantee will be
this extra vote.
...that you had talked to Danny,
and you had all decided
to vote me out today.
And that, "They're switching
the entire vote
to you to get you out."
RICARD: Deshawn continues
to lie, and I don't respect it.
It bothers me, it annoys me,
but I still think
he's the best choice
moving forward today.
And he can go home tomorrow.
The only path forward
for me is with her gone.
...at this point, I'm
completely on board with you.
One thousand percent.
I'm having these moral dilemmas.
I want to kind of
protect the four.
I really wanted
to believe in Shan.
I really, truly did.
DESHAWN:
Shan snitched on me.
I mean, yes,
I was definitely trying
to take out Ricard.
She wasn't lying,
but at the same time,
it's like, now I know for sure
I can't trust you.
Like, you said,
my name to go home.
Now you've revealed my plans
that I didn't talk to you about,
so you can go.
Who? Okay.
So... it's not gonna be you.
Then...
Yeah.
ERIKA:
So the goal is to get out Shan.
But Shan has an idol,
and if Shan uses her idol,
that group can decide who gets
knocked out, and it could be me.
Danny and I were original Luvu.
Maybe
I can get Danny to vote
with us, too.
I wanted to talk,
and everybody's all
in different places, so...
Well, we know
who's not going home tonight.
-ERIKA: Ricard?
-Yup.
-And Xander.
-HEATHER: Yeah.
HEATHER:
Okay.
Would you move on any of them?
DANNY:
Yeah, Shan pissed me off today.
ERIKA:
What happened?
I don't want to blow up
the game, but, yeah, I would.
-Maybe we can work with that.
-Yeah.
ERIKA:
I'm thinking three people vote
for Shan,
three people vote for Liana.
If Shan doesn't play her idol,
we revote between Liana
and Shan, and Shan goes home.
If Shan plays her idol,
Liana goes home.
How would you feel
if we did three votes on Shan,
three votes on Liana,
and then
Liana and Shan vote wherever?
If Shan plays her idol,
Liana gets knocked out.
-HEATHER: Yeah.
-Okay.
That is a nice plan.
When you see Erika making
these moves,
you can see
that she needs to go.
DESHAWN:
I know it, but I think...
DANNY:
Throw my whole game over that?
The beautiful thing
about this setup right now...
DANNY:
It is very difficult
to split votes
to flush out idols.
One vote can change
the entire plan.
So in Tribal Council,
I do have a choice.
Me and Deshawn could choose
to keep Shan in the game,
or make a bigger move
of voting out Erika,
which I would rather do.
She is a dangerous player.
But Shan is the one
who broke my trust.
We put a lot into the four of us
making it to the final four,
and the fact that Shan is
willing to throw that away
because of some
19-day friendship with Ricard--
that just doesn't vibe with me.
(rolling thunder)
But
it's difficult for me
to make that decision.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, Xander,
what was it like back at camp
after the immunity challenge
today?
Because we're now down to it.
I mean,
there's not a lot of days left.
There will be seven players
left after tonight.
-I mean, you're asking
the wrong person because...
-(laughter)
for the last couple of days,
I've been the lone soldier.
Everybody knows
I've got an immunity idol,
and that could get me
through tonight's Tribal,
and hopefully I can be
on the right side of a vote.
You know, that'll just have to
wait and see till after Tribal.
Heather, where do you feel
you sit in the game right now?
I feel I'm at the bottom.
-You, too?
-Yeah.
I'm not making
the big decisions,
you know, but I'm okay
with that right now.
PROBST:
Erika, you start getting
down to these numbers.
Suddenly, people on the bottom
start to look up and go,
"We could make a move."
I would consider myself
in the bottom half for sure.
I think that maybe
there's something
that we can do
with the people at the bottom,
but I think
it's whether you're a part
of the planning,
or if the plan is told to you,
or sometimes
you don't get the plan at all.
PROBST:
Shan, that's interesting
because that can
backfire
if you're one of the ones
that are making the decisions
because suddenly
they start looking,
"Well, you know what? Why don't
we just make our own decision?"
SHAN:
I think anybody can be perceived
as at the bottom, anybody could
be perceived at the top.
It's all about the conversation
that you're having.
You know, like, you're always
one relationship away
from extending your life
in this game,
or getting your torch snuffed.
You only know
after a Tribal Council
who you can trust.
Bottom line, that's it.
PROBST:
Ricard, the new Survivor
is forcing you
to have relationships
with lots of people
because holding onto an
alliance-- very difficult to do.
RICARD:
Yeah, I mean,
Shan and I have this
really weird relationship.
We didn't just say, you know,
from the very beginning, "It's
the two of us till the end."
It's really just
who you can trust
for as long as you can trust.
-Shan, you're nodding.
-Um,
we are all liars here,
and when you're working with
someone, you've got to just say,
"What's the risk
with this liar?" Like,
what's the cost
to them working with me?
What's the benefit
to working with me? Um...
DESHAWN:
But lies can get messy.
Like, if you tell a lie,
then you have to cover that lie
with something else or something
else. At the same time,
when you find a good group
of people,
at least
you can tell the truth
to the people
that you're working with.
DANNY:
I will say this, Jeff. I know
who people feel like, uh,
they think are working together.
Um, but they could be wrong.
I'll just say that.
PROBST:
So, Erika, if you feel
you're on the bottom,
do you just hope that people
are gonna battle it out,
or do you try to make a move?
ERIKA:
You can't not try
to do something.
And I think for anyone,
the one pitch they have is,
their vote counts the same
as anybody else's vote.
So, what I can offer people
is a vote,
and see if we can get
something moving.
PROBST:
Shan, when Erika says,
"I got a piece of parchment.
Tell me what name
to write down,"
is that scary,
or is that an opportunity?
Absolutely both,
but if that individual has not
talked strategy
with you in that day,
then it becomes, like, scary.
Are you referring to Erika
in that situation?
I mean, I-I-I... maybe,
but I've-I've worked with Erika,
and she's a trustworthy person.
-So...
-ERIKA: Yeah, I mean, like,
we didn't get the chance
to talk today.
But Shan
and I have worked together.
We-we pulled off
the Naseer blindside
together, so there...
I-I hope
there's, like, some level
-of trust between us.
-For sure. Yeah.
PROBST:
Ricard, are there ever
conversations where they go,
"Look, there's still some people
on the bottom.
Let's just get them"?
RICARD:
Logically, you would think
that's how it is at camp,
but most of what's going on
is perception of oneself.
So, Erika feels very insecure
and on the bottom.
And then he has an idol,
which is so public
that now he feels
on the bottom, and, like...
It's just all our perception
of ourselves.
PROBST:
So, Liana, you guys
all have your own awareness
of yourself.
You have awareness
of everybody else.
And yet I'm guessing
tonight's gonna be a blindside.
What does that say about how
you have to play Survivor?
LIANA:
Yeah, Jeff. I'm a student,
and I've studied
very complex things,
and when I'm playing this game,
I feel like my mind is, like,
spinning around and around
and around and around.
And so, right now, everyone
thinks they have an idea
of what's going on,
but one of us is wrong,
and that's going
to show up tonight.
And so, that's why
this game is absolutely insane
and incredible and just chaotic
at the same time.
PROBST:
Great answers tonight, really.
41 seasons,
and I'm still learning
how this game works for you.
All right, it is time to vote.
Heather, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
Anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Erika.
Erika.
Shan. Two votes-- Erika,
one vote-- Shan.
♪ ♪
Liana.
Shan. Two votes-- Shan,
two votes-- Erika,
one vote-- Liana.
Liana. That's two votes-- Liana.
That's three votes-- Shan,
two votes-- Erika,
two votes-- Liana,
one vote left.
Liana. We're tied.
Liana with three votes,
Shan with three votes.
We're going to revote.
You can only vote for Shan
or Liana. Shan and Liana,
you won't vote. Ricard, you want
to come and grab this?
We always said
when the time was right,
we'd give each other
permission to do this.
So, so sorry.
I'll read the votes.
Shan.
Shan. That's three votes Shan.
11th person voted out and
the fourth member of our jury.
-Yeah.
-Shan.
-That was good.
-Good game, Shan.
-Good night. Well played.
-Great game, Shan.
-Good game, Shan.
(speaks indistinctly)
Ricard, you have my vote
for a million dollars.
Deshawn, you're a snake.
(laughs)
-Ooh.
-Ooh. Wow.
Don't do it, Jeff.
Don't do it.
-I take no joy in this.
-I know.
I played a good game,
and this was a dream come true.
I love you, babe.
-Shan?
-Mm-hmm.
The tribe has spoken.
-Good job, Shan.
-ERIKA: Good game, Shan.
-(overlapping chatter)
-PROBST: Time for you to go.
♪ ♪
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
LIANA:
If you're a snake, then
I'm gonna bite back,
and I hope you're gone tomorrow.
♪ ♪
ERIKA:
If I don't take the shot now,
I have no chance.
There is a twist
to today's challenge.
And it's a dangerous one.
XANDER:
This is too good to be true.
I am so proud of myself for
the way that I played this game.
I feel like I played a really
strong game, from Ua
all the way to the merge,
and there's no hard feelings,
but I left with an idol in my
pocket. That's the other thing.
I left
with an idol in my pocket.
Oh, my gosh.
But... this was a lot of fun.
(roars)