LIANA:
Mm-hmm.
At Tribal Council,
I was blindsided.
We had this plan for Shan, me,
Danny and Deshawn
for final four.
Um, but that exploded
in my face tonight.
How is it that we talked
about final four,
this trust, trust,
trust, trust, trust,
and I'm completely left out
of the vote tonight?
-DESHAWN: So...
-Somebody explain that to me.
-That's all I'm interested in.
-It... The thing is...
The thing is,
it wasn't our plan.
-Whose plan was it?
-This is Ricard's plan.
-Yeah.
DESHAWN:
We were in the minority.
DANNY:
They all turned on us.
And we kind of...
-They were going to vote...
-Yo.
-...by doing this. Now look-look
at what's over there.
-But...
XANDER: After all this fighting
and kicking and crawling
to try and get out
of the bottom,
I actually pulled off a move.
I was a part of the plan.
I took out Shan with Ricard,
and I'm left with an alliance?
What is this?
And furthermore, ... Xander
still has the ... idol.
-DANNY: I agree.
-(stammers) All for this?
-I agree.
-That's ... stupid.
-XANDER: Yeah.
-ERIKA: Yeah.
ERIKA:
It's true.
I'm just letting y'all know,
it's gonna get real.
XANDER:
All of a sudden, I'm in charge
with a group of people
that I actually trust
and that I can work with,
and we're saying final four?
Oh, my God,
this is too good to be true.
Yeah.
And I hear her.
I would be pissed, too.
My question to you now is,
why is it
that every time I do something,
it's on the front page
of the freaking newspaper,
and I did not come up
with the idea?
We blindsided Shan, which is
something that I was fully
on board with after she had
thrown my name out.
But before she leaves, she drops
a little... a little bomb
on the group,
and she says that I'm a snake.
Ricard, you have my vote
for a million dollars.
Deshawn, you're a snake.
DESHAWN:
So I was kind of pissed
at Ricard because it's like,
you were even more close
with Shan.
You were her number one ally.
And you backstabbed her
as well,
but she didn't call you a snake.
She said, "Ricard,
you get a million dollars,
"even though you were my ally
and you orchestrated this,
but, Deshawn, you voted
that way and you're a snake."
Like, huh?
RICARD:
From where I'm standing,
Shan and I--
we knew we were gunning
for each other.
-Mm.
-Like, we had such
a honest relationship
and conversation about that.
And I think the fact
that there was the plan
to get me out today--
I think she knows
that that is what rushed me
to get rid of her.
Because clearly,
everybody wanted us separate,
so it had to happen.
Like, that's the only way
for me to save my game.
Because if I did not
win immunity today,
-I would be gone.
-Yeah.
RICARD: As Shan left
after being voted out,
knowing that I planned it,
you know, participated in it,
she must know.
She said
I have her vote
for a million dollars,
and she called Deshawn a snake.
And so, he's taking a lot of
heat off of me, which is great.
DESHAWN:
And it's like I'm fighting
every day for my life
for things that I am not doing
in this game,
and it's freaking
irritating, dude.
Like, I voted out Shan
because she told me
that she was gunning for me.
That's it.
Now I'm the snake. Yeah.
So it's, like, congrats on
having that million-dollar vote.
Congrats on, like,
making the big move.
You're the top dog right now,
but at the end of the day,
I-I'm a snake, so now I got
to deal with being a snake.
RICARD:
Deshawn's game
is confusing to me.
He's very emotional
and blames a lot of people.
And so, in his eyes,
Shan's at fault
for calling him a snake
and ruining his game.
He can't take ownership
of the fact
that he's all over the place,
can't commit to any one person,
and doesn't really know
what direction to go
to have a good game.
It's coming off very, very
paranoid, and I think the...
I really think the thing that
can help you is to chill out.
If it sounded
like I was, like, coming at you
or ranting at you,
I actually was not angry at you.
I was trying to process, like,
why did she only call me a snake
when there was,
like, two other people
who also wrote her name down
that she was really close with?
You know,
it just didn't make sense,
so I was just trying
to process it.
A lot of things
happening at once,
but this is where I'm at
right now, so...
I thought
that if I came back to camp
and I basically exposed Ricard
for his move,
that the group would want
to take him out next.
The issue is, though,
that I guess I came off
a little bit accusatory,
and it just didn't end up
working out.
But thank you for that advice.
I'm, like, I'm Zen.
I'm back to Zen Deshawn.
You know what I'm saying?
It's tough because
if I could go back and redo
after the last Tribal Council,
I would probably just
go back and shut up.
It sounded like a good plan,
but if I can
change the hands of time,
I would probably
just not say anything.
Go in the shelter
and go to sleep.
-I know last night was a mess.
-Yes.
And, Liana, I-I would never
write your name down.
-I haven't thus far,
and I never would.
-I know.
-I appreciate that.
-If-if I can help you,
just let me know.
LIANA:
People are gonna lie
to you in this game.
I know that 100%,
but it hurts most
from the people
that you think you can trust.
I don't...
LIANA:
And Deshawn last night--
it was kind of like
I have this beautiful picture
of me and Shan,
and he just smashed it over
and over and over
with a mallet.
And so, last night
absolutely hurt.
Of course I want revenge.
Of course I want Deshawn out.
I mean,
I agree with what Shan said
last night.
Like, that was a snake move.
If you're a snake,
then I'm gonna bite back,
and I hope
you're gone tomorrow.
I'm absolutely open
to revenge right now.
(squawking)
Yum!
DANNY:
These last few days
have been kind of heavy.
Today marks 25 years
to the day of the passing
of my father.
He died in a car accident
when I was eight years old.
It's a very hard day,
and I always try
to keep myself really,
really busy, and,
here, I don't know. You just...
you just can't do it.
You can't hide from it.
Today's just a really,
really rough day for me.
-Mm-hmm.
-So, if I seem off,
it really ain't nothing
about the game.
It's the 25th anniversary
of my dad passing.
-Hmm.
-It's just like... I don't know.
My entire life, I think
I was angry at him.
You know, you want your dad
to be Superman.
You hear about other people
getting into accidents
and them surviving,
and you wonder why he didn't.
And then you're jealous and mad
every Father's Day, every...
every football game
where your dad's not there
that you see other kids
with their fathers and all this.
Every time I wanted to say...
I want to make my mom proud
or my family proud,
I was really
leaving him out of it.
I was really, really upset.
And being able to sit still here
has let me focus
and really understand, uh,
how I was thinking
and-and how I can change the way
that I think moving forward.
So today is more like, uh,
trying to get rid of the shame
that I feel
for being angry for so long
for something
that my father couldn't control.
From now on,
I'm gonna make sure I go visit
his grave as much as I should,
um,
talk to my mom about him more,
and just try to let him know
that I apologize
and I was wrong
and I'm a man now
and I understand that.
And I think, moving forward,
uh, my thoughts
and-and how I deal with stuff
back at home
will-will change greatly.
So I'm going to try
to move forward, uh, being happy
and try to live the rest of
my life of-of making him proud.
♪ ♪
It's day 21.
Seven players left in the game,
and today they're going to face
another very dangerous twist,
and it's going to force them
to make a big decision based
on where they think
they stand in the game,
because even choosing
to participate
in today's
immunity challenge comes
with potentially deadly risk.
Fun one to play along with.
Ask yourself,
what would you do?
Come on in!
Hi, Jeff.
Well, thanks for another
"good morning," Erika.
-Good morning.
-Wow. Heather, too.
All right, ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yeah.
-Let's do it.
-PROBST: First things first.
Ricard, got to take back
the necklace.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to use handles
to balance a ball
on a wooden cylinder.
At regular intervals, we'll add
more sections of cylinder,
making it more difficult
to balance.
If at any point your ball drops,
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
There is a twist
to today's challenge.
And it's a dangerous one.
(players groaning)
The first person to drop out
of this challenge will be forced
to participate in a new game
called Survivor Do or Die.
Here's how it works.
Tonight at Tribal Council,
that person
and only that person
will participate
in a potentially
deadly game of chance.
If you survive, you're safe
and you're in the six,
and we vote somebody out.
If you die, you're gone
and there is no vote.
No one can save you,
no idol can save you,
nothing can save you.
You either live or you die.
So you have a very big decision
to make right now.
You don't have to participate
in this challenge.
That's your choice.
If you don't, obviously
you can't win immunity.
But if you participate
and you're first out,
you could be gone...
without a vote.
I'm gonna give you two rocks.
It's going
to be a private decision.
Take one rock each.
Gray means,
"I'm going to sit out.
I think I'm good, and I don't
want to play Do or Die."
Red means, "I can't risk it.
I'm in trouble in this game,
and I have to participate."
All right, everybody,
take a look
-at your two rocks.
-(Heather groans)
Make sure you know
where gray is, red is.
Gray says, "I'm sitting
out of this challenge."
Red says, "I'm competing."
You're gonna show me one rock,
and that is your decision.
Is everybody ready?
-Mm-hmm.
-Palms out.
And everybody reveal.
All right,
so we have two gray rocks.
Heather is gonna sit out,
Liana's gonna sit out,
not risk Do or Die.
Erika, Ricard,
Deshawn, Xander and Danny
are going to participate.
One of those five
will be first out,
and you're the one
playing Do or Die
tonight at Tribal Council.
Sit-outs take a spot
on the bench.
-Everybody else,
we'll draw for spots.
-ERIKA: Wow.
And we'll get started.
Wow.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Here we go.
Everybody get ready
for the first stage
of this game.
You have three sections
of cylinder,
your ball in the middle.
Deep breath. Here we go.
I'm gonna count you in.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
And this challenge is on.
Everybody looks very good.
We'll go
in this section
for five minutes.
And just like that, Deshawn is
out, seconds into this.
And Deshawn will be playing
Do or Die tonight,
where a game of chance
will determine
whether he lives
to see another day
or whether final seven
is as far as he goes.
Wow. That drama was over quick--
not even three seconds.
And it's now Erika, Xander,
Ricard and Danny.
You go five minutes here,
and then we will add two more
sections of cylinder.
(insect buzzing)
All right, you can set it down.
You survived this round.
-Ooh.
-We add two more sections.
All right,
I'm gonna count you in.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody is up,
and everybody looking good.
Challenge is back on.
Five minutes
in this round, as well.
15 seconds left in this round.
♪ ♪
Five, four, three.
Erika drops. She's out. One.
Everybody else is safe.
Xander, Ricard
and Danny are safe.
ERIKA:
Good luck, guys.
PROBST:
Danny started to wobble
but made it.
Erika wobbled and did not.
Erika is now out,
no shot at immunity.
We'll move
into this final section
with only three players left--
Xander, Ricard and Danny.
Here we go.
The last two sections
have been added.
I'm gonna count you in.
Five, four, three,
two,
one.
Everybody is up cleanly.
Very nice job.
And we got a challenge
right now.
We go until we have a winner.
You're going to have
to really dig here
because this is going to go
until two people drop.
There is no relief.
There are no more sections
to add.
This is it.
We just go.
♪ ♪
Been in this round six minutes,
longer than any other round,
and it's the most difficult
of any round.
An impressive showing
of Xander, Ricard and Danny.
And here comes some wind.
Usually we love the wind
out here
in Fiji 'cause it feels nice.
But anything that moves
that ball even a little...
is an enemy.
Different strategies.
People changing grips.
♪ ♪
You're all three
looking really good.
Whatever strategy you are doing,
it is working
for you, so keep doing it.
Question is,
how long can you do this?
♪ ♪
Hang in there. Do not lapse.
Don't start to drift.
(insect buzzing)
♪ ♪
Ricard drops, Xander drops
at the same time.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-Danny wins his first
individual immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
-DESHAWN: Good job, buddy.
-PROBST: Clearly
a huge moment for Danny.
Wow. What a finish.
Two drops within a half a second
of each other.
-DESHAWN: Oh, my God.
-ERIKA: Wow.
Danny, come on over.
Yeah, Coach Danny.
First individual immunity win,
guarantees you a spot
in the final six.
You will not be voted out
tonight no matter what happens.
Well done. Congratulations.
Take your spot back over there.
-Good job.
-Congratulations.
-Congrats, Danny.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Appreciate it.
PROBST:
All right, so, tonight,
if Deshawn lives,
then we have a normal vote
and somebody goes home.
If Deshawn dies, then he's out
and there is no vote,
which means
you have to prepare
for Tribal Council
as though there might be a vote
because there could be.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp. See you tonight at Tribal.
-ERIKA: Thanks, Jeff.
-Thanks, Jeff.
ERIKA:
Congrats, seriously.
RICARD:
The person that was likely
going to be going home today--
Deshawn--
he'll be participating
in the Do or Die twist.
He either will go home
with no votes
or he will be safe
and cannot be voted on
by any of us who want
to send him home, and, uh,
I hope it's "die" for Deshawn.
(laughs)
-♪ ♪
-(indistinct chatter)
-HEATHER: Good job.
-LIANA: Good job.
You earned it.
DANNY:
Are you... you kind of excited?
You're-you're the first person
ever in Survivor history
to do this Do or Die.
-HEATHER: Yeah. Spin the wheel.
-DESHAWN: Yeah. Honestly,
when it first happened,
I was so mad,
but as the more
I thought about it, like,
-I'm-I'm content with this.
-XANDER: Yeah.
DESHAWN:
I feel like I could be safe,
but then also,
if I go out, y'all can
never say y'all voted me out...
Hey, it is what it is, man.
Damn. This could be
my last day on the island.
I went out of the challenge
first, and now
I have to play
the Do or Die twist,
where either I'm gonna win
immunity or I'm going home.
But I'm trying to keep positive
because after voting out Shan,
I had a huge target on my back.
So this way,
at least
I have a fighting chance.
Bro, I'm sorry.
Bro, I know.
30 seconds?
-Way to go, brother.
Like, come on, bro.
-Hey, hey, hey, look.
Listen, and this is no lie.
And I literally
just started saying,
-"I want to make my dad proud."
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna make him proud.
-Come on.
And that... that's why I cried
at-at the end, I swear to God.
Yeah, it's, uh...
Individual immunity against the
two dudes who is winning 'em.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Like, bro, that's major.
DANNY: I didn't think that
it would bring me this much joy
to win an individual immunity,
but being out here
on Survivor has made me realize
some of those negative emotions
that I had
around my father passing
and not being here
to take care of the family.
And this experience
helped me to let it go.
And I'm really
grateful for that, but now
we got Tribal Council coming up.
And if Deshawn wins
the Do or Die,
we'll be voting somebody out.
-DESHAWN: Yeah, he's got to go.
-DANNY: Yeah.
DESHAWN: 'Cause if you keep
him, he's gonna beat you
in the next competit...
Like, come on.
I got to... I got to talk to...
Yeah, I don't know how
you feel about it, but...
but the smart move is Ricard.
Do you feel like
you could do it today?
So, you're saying Ricard now.
-Yeah. Ricard?
Are you kidding me?
-Okay.
He's the only one
who's made a move.
-Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
-Like, a successful move.
-...and he's super likable.
-Yeah.
XANDER:
Deshawn was
the number one target,
and now
that he's possibly immune,
everybody's preparing
their backup plans.
Danny for sure wants
to vote out Ricard.
But Ricard's one of my own,
so I don't want to see him go,
because once Ricard's gone, I'm
the number one target around.
I'm the one
that people are talking about
as the guy who has a résumé
and the guy
who's good at challenges.
So they're going to get me out
if I get Ricard out.
I mean, like,
what's the alternative? Liana?
Yeah, which I don't think
makes sense.
XANDER:
It's true.
It's true. It's true.
Yeah, it would be a big move.
I'm acting as if I'm going along
with it, but
I trust Ricard way more
than I trust Liana.
I mean, Liana's lied to my face
more times than I can count.
So if Deshawn wins
the Do or Die,
my alliance of Ricard,
Erika and Heather
still has the majority.
And to break that up
would be a stupid move.
ERIKA:
I wanted to see, like,
-what you're thinking.
-XANDER: Yeah.
There's the plan where
it's, like, just vote out Liana.
And then there's another plan
that, like,
-do we take the clear shot
at Ricard today?
-Yeah.
...the only thing is,
he would beat all of us.
-He is really good at stuff.
-Yeah.
-He's, like, good at everything.
ERIKA: It's a tough choice.
Like, with Liana,
it makes sense to get rid of her
because she's someone who voted
for me the last Tribal Council
and who really doesn't have,
like, any allegiance to me
and will likely be sneaky.
But the problem
with keeping Ricard is,
he's by far the biggest threat
to win the game.
Really love him
and I really trust him.
It's just, like,
I'm scared that, like,
we won't get a chance again.
Like, I don't know.
-I know.
-I'm like
-so all over the place
and so unsure.
-Right.
ERIKA:
As much as I know I can
trust him, if I don't
take the shot now, Ricard could
run away with the game,
and I have no chance.
So my head is spinning
a little bit on this one.
(birds singing)
Your name's out there big-time.
I mean, you and I
are not going home
as long as Erika and Heather
stick with us.
Like, we're good.
-Okay, perfect,
perfect, perfect.
-Yeah.
XANDER:
Heather 100%,
-Erika...
-Erika's shady.
Erika's getting
a little squirmish.
So many voices
that are in her head
that she doesn't know if
it's going to cost her her game.
RICARD:
If Deshawn is safe tonight,
Danny, Deshawn and Liana
will be voting for me.
But it shouldn't really matter
because I have
a four-person alliance.
But Erika--
she's really, like,
unsure of what to do.
LIANA:
Okay.
Don't matter what you hear.
I 1,000% would never
write your name down.
-If I'm safe tonight,
it's not gonna happen.
-Thank you.
He's... he...
He's out...
He wants Ricard.
Everybody... everybody
with a brain
between their ears wants Ricard.
-Thank you.
-And I'm wishing you
all the best, thousand percent.
Thank you, thank you.
I am worried tonight
because with both Danny
and possibly Deshawn
being safe tonight,
I'm kind of like an easy vote.
So my only,
really, life in this game
right now is hoping
that people realize
Ricard is a much bigger threat.
If not, I might have
to play the Shot in the Dark,
but then I lose my vote.
Scared ..., honestly.
ERIKA:
Somehow I'm the swing vote,
and it's one
of those moves where
you're watching at home,
and you think,
"Oh, my God, it's so obvious.
You have to take the big threat
out of the game."
But, like,
when you're in the game,
you see how important it is
to have people you can trust.
-Either way. Either way.
-HEATHER: Either way?
ERIKA:
I'm rolling the dice
just like Deshawn is, and
whatever decision I make,
I just have to own it.
(insects chirping)
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, let's start
with today's immunity challenge.
Danny wins the necklace
for the first time.
You are safe tonight.
Today's challenge also came
with a twist
that if you were first out,
your fate would be determined
by a game of chance
in a new game
called Survivor Do or Die.
Deshawn, you were first out,
and in a few minutes
we're going to play Do or Die,
and that will determine
whether or not you live or die
and whether or not
we have a vote.
So before we get to that, Liana,
today's twist was all
about relationships.
If you didn't think you needed
immunity, you could sit out.
Yeah, Jeff,
I do not feel comfortable
in my-my relationships,
and I don't want
to give that impression at all.
The fact of the matter was,
in terms of Liana statistics
in individual immunity
challenges-- hasn't been so hot.
So that means in no way
that I'm comfortable tonight.
That was my argument, as well,
is the people
that I have outlasted in the
challenges were already gone.
And then, so it didn't
make sense for me
to stay there and risk that,
especially not knowing
what I'm risking.
PROBST:
And so, Xander,
there's always uncertainty,
but tonight
there truly is uncertainty.
We might not even
vote somebody out.
Deshawn might be
in the final six,
and we do vote somebody out.
We don't know.
I mean, you want to believe
that every Tribal is determined
simply by relationships.
But it's not only relationships
that you're worrying about now,
but about
this advantage
and this twist, and
I like that this season kind of
throws out all the expectations
we have of Survivor.
You know, now it's high-risk,
high-reward,
so you really have to gamble
a little bit.
PROBST:
Danny, how'd it feel for you
having certainty
with that necklace?
It felt pretty good, but, um,
Deshawn's my friend here.
The fact that he has no idea
what's gonna happen
with him tonight
is kind of crazy.
Um, we were trying
to figure out a plan,
and not really sure
we're gonna execute the plan.
But I'm more of the
"put your name on it," right?
If you're gonna put your plan
out there, go ahead and say that
you said it, and that's
what you wanted to do,
and you have
to face the consequences
-if it doesn't work out.
-PROBST: Erika, there's also
another factor tonight.
It's the last night
you can take
your Shot in the Dark.
One-in-six shot at safety.
ERIKA:
Yeah, I don't know what
the odds are for the Do or Die,
but if Deshawn,
like, doesn't die...
But I... I don't want you
-to, like, die die.
-Right, right.
ERIKA:
Um, and someone plays
the Shot in the Dark,
and someone else gets knocked
out, like, there's no certainty
for what's going
to happen tonight.
How's that feel?
Oh, it sucks.
Jeff, I-I have a love-hate
with this game.
Some days I love it,
some days I hate it.
Today I hate it.
That is a great answer to hear
because if-if the game
isn't doing that to you,
then it's not pushing you.
If this is the adventure
of a lifetime,
then you have to have that low
to have that high.
You have to have the anger
to feel the joy.
It's part of it.
So, Deshawn,
was it different for you because
you're the one that's going
to have to play Do or Die,
but you're still the one
hoping there is a vote,
-and you want it to go your way?
-Um, yeah, Jeff.
So if I can back it up
just a little bit
to my decision to actually play.
Um, after the Last Tribal
when Shan went home, um,
there was a bit of a discussion
between Ricard and I
just because, in this game,
morals and gameplay intersect,
and I felt very passionate
about the Shan vote
for a lot of different reasons,
and so I just wanted the truth.
And I think me confronting
Ricard made it seem like
I was some aggressive guy
that I'm not.
And I think that could have
put me in trouble.
So that's why I-I went ahead
and played.
PROBST:
Ricard, you obviously know
what Deshawn is referring to.
Do you want to elaborate?
Yeah, so...
there was a lot of talk
that I was the one who was going
to be voted out last time.
Um, I was told by Shan
that the plan was Deshawn's,
and so
we were going to try and flip
the vote and get Deshawn out.
And just to confirm, you said
that Shan told you that...
to vote me out, right?
She was the one that came up
with that plan?
Yes. And so our conversation
was him not fully knowing
if I was creating a lie
to divide them,
which I was not.
-Okay.
-And I stand by that.
I believe you.
PROBST:
And, Deshawn, for you,
why is it important?
When you talk
about your integrity,
what are you worried
about your integrity?
DESHAWN:
It's-it's hard, Jeff.
It's hard to put it into words.
I'm so passionate
about this game.
I'm passionate
about the decision
that we had to make
at the last Tribal,
and I don't know
what's gonna happen to me.
Um, but it's not even
about that.
You know, a lot of minority
players put in a lot of work
to diversify this cast.
And when I came into it,
I wanted to make sure
that I represented,
like, the Black community
as... as well as possible,
and so...
(cries softly)
And so it just hurt
to even have
to write her name down 'cause
that really is my sister,
but, like,
the gameplay and morals
intersected, and it was so hard.
(sighs)
You're all right, bro.
And it's hard, bro.
Like, it's really hard.
'Cause this is a game
that I love,
and I came here to play it.
But people don't understand
the extra baggage
that you bring into this game.
And it's a blessing
to have such a diverse cast,
but, like, I didn't think
this decision, this moment--
voting her out-- would be this
hard, so it's really tough.
(Deshawn sniffles)
I was just playing the game
with the information
that I was given,
and I had
to make that hard decision,
and it was the toughest thing
I've ever had to do.
So here I am.
(Deshawn sniffles)
PROBST:
Liana, do you feel that as well,
that you and Deshawn
and Shan and Danny
have this other thing
that really doesn't
have anything to do
with the gameplay,
but it has to do with
-where we are in the culture?
-LIANA: Absolutely.
Everywhere I go
as a Black woman,
I'm a Black woman first.
It doesn't matter that
I'm a student at Georgetown.
It doesn't matter
that I have this amazing
internship next summer.
When people look at me,
they see a Black woman,
and I take that with me
wherever I go.
And there is no question
that we're coming out of a year,
like 2020, where people are
just now becoming conscious
of the fact that being Black
actually means something.
It has this kind of currency
that can kill you,
literally kill you.
And doesn't mean that Black
death is like this new thing.
Like, Emmett Till happened
so many years ago,
and nobody really, like,
seemed to care then.
And now
it's become this thing, right?
And so, coming here
to play this is
about uplifting other Black
people and giving Black people
something to root for
besides everything else
that's out there
that's killing us.
And then, not only that.
How beautiful is it
that we're starting out
with a cast
with 50% POC, right?
There's another Black woman
right there that looks like me
who's also playing this game
with me.
Another piece of that is
that the fan base
that is watching this-- for them
to meet a Liana or a Shan
or a Danny or a Deshawn,
like, they get
to understand that Blackness
is not, you know, this monolith,
this one thing.
Like, we're all types of Black.
We're-we're Black
in different ways.
And to Deshawn's point,
it's, like,
we love this game, too.
We don't just want to have
this all-Black alliance and-and
throw strategy out the window.
Like, we want to play.
We want to, you know, like,
let's get Shan out
because she is a huge threat.
Like, we want to do both,
but how
do we do it at the same time?
And of course that's a factor
when we're playing this game.
Like, I'm Black wherever I go.
That's just it.
PROBST:
Danny,
it's a huge responsibility
inside a game that is
already impossible to play.
How are you managing with it?
Yeah, uh, I mean, it's a little
tough. I mean, like,
Liana said it perfectly,
and I understand Deshawn
and how he feels about it
because coming into the game,
it wasn't about
taking this, and
all Black people get to the end.
It was more about showing those
connections and that diversity.
And hopefully,
when people see that,
they'll be able to talk to each
other the same way that we are.
So, I just want to tell you that
I really appreciate
the explanation.
Uh, I think Shan and you
will be able
to have
a very in-depth conversation,
and-and maybe we all will, and
we can show that we'll be able
to kind of come
to understanding,
and move forward
from this, as well,
and I hope that's-that's
what happens from this.
PROBST:
Xander,
-what's the emotion?
-I mean,
I'm out here playing a game,
and-and then
you take it out, and you make it
this real-world thing,
and it's-it's so powerful.
I mean,
I don't represent a people.
I don't carry that burden
with me.
I don't think
about those kinds of things
because I-I have the privilege
of not having
to think about that.
So I have so much respect
for the people out here
who are representing people
and trying to show
that there are positive ways to
be represented in the culture.
And that's powerful.
That goes beyond this game.
Jeff, and I... and I just want
to say I think that's
really important because the
main thing in the outside world
is to show that we have allies.
We have people
that-that care about
what's happening to us,
how we feel,
and the justice
that we want, and,
Xander, you're a part of that.
Like, I really respect you
as a man.
Same thing with everybody else
sitting up here,
and I really feel like,
back in the real world
when all this is over,
if we call on this cast to be
allies for any type of cause,
I feel like we have a-a
good group to help push that.
PROBST:
Heather,
what's your perspective
on what's happening right here
as a reflection of our culture?
We're growing, we're learning.
I had no idea that this was
a conflict that was going on,
and it breaks my heart to know
that you are carrying this
with you,
and it's something
I don't understand.
I'm grateful
that you shared this because
it just shows me
I have a lot more... to learn
and more questions to ask.
-Um, I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
Thank you for your words.
I appreciate it.
(sniffles)
We're all learning.
We're all growing.
Thank you, Heather.
LIANA:
And can I also
just add something?
I think, also, you know,
something hard perhaps
for-for viewers back home is,
like, you know,
"I-I just want to watch
Survivor. Like, why is this...
"you know, all this, like,
kind of real-life elements
"kind of have to jump
into the game
when it's suddenly super
diverse?" To those people,
I understand, but, you know,
it just means that
we're human beings, and the game
is a little bit more complex,
and we're a microcosm
of the real world, too.
So, I'm sorry if some people
feel that way from,
you know,
this kind of moment, but
that's... I think
that's important to note, too.
PROBST:
Well, I would just offer,
I'm sure
lots of people watch Survivor
for lots of different reasons.
To me, it's about this.
What happens
when you put a group of people
and force them to live together
in a jungle,
a real jungle,
and rely on each other?
It's amazing,
and there's no doubt in my mind
this is a special group
for all the reasons
you're talking about.
It's beautiful of you to share
it, and I think it's going to be
powerful for a lot of people
to hear it.
Thank you, guys.
Everybody.
-Thank you guys for the support.
-Thank you.
(sighs):
All right.
No, don't do it.
-Let's just talk
some more, Jeff.
-(laughter)
PROBST:
Before we get to the vote,
we have to see
if there is a vote.
It's the looming suspense
of Survivor Do or Die.
Let me get it set up.
Lord, have mercy. I'm sweating.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
-Jeff.
-LIANA: Uh-oh.
All right, Deshawn. Come on up.
-Ooh.
-(laughing)
-DANNY: Oh, man.
-Oh, my God.
-All right.
-So let me lay it out
for you, okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-We have three
Do or Die boxes.
-Yes.
Inside one of these boxes
is a fire symbol.
That represents life.
That means you are safe,
guaranteed a spot
in the final six,
-and we vote somebody out.
-Okay.
Inside two of these boxes
is a skull symbol.
That represents death
in the game.
-Okay.
-And that means you are gone,
-and there is no vote.
-Okay.
-PROBST: Three boxes.
-Yes, sir.
Deshawn, choose one box.
Jeff, my heart is telling me
to choose this box,
-so I'm gonna choose this box.
-All right, this is yours.
-DESHAWN: Okay.
-All right.
Before we open your box,
I'm gonna open...
-What?
-...one of these.
DESHAWN:
Okay. Okay.
A skull.
So there is now one skull
and one flame.
-Yes.
-Do you want to keep the box
you have?
-Ugh.
-PROBST: Or...
-What the heck?
...do you want
to trade for this box?
Oh.
DESHAWN:
Jeff, I have to go with my gut.
Something was telling me
this box,
so I'm gonna keep this box
-for better or for worse.
-PROBST: All right.
If it is flame,
you're in the final six,
and we immediately go
into the vote.
If it is a skull, you're gone
and your game ends.
Let's reveal your box.
♪ ♪
-Oh, my God.
-Oh.
-PROBST: Deshawn got flame.
-Oh, my God.
-You are safe,
-my friend.
-Oh, my God.
No way.
-XANDER: Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, my God.
-(indistinct chatter)
-Welcome back.
-(laughing)
Welcome back.
PROBST:
Had you traded, Deshawn,
you would have
gotten the skull.
-LIANA: Wow.
-Go with your gut.
-Oh, my God.
ERIKA:
Oh, my gosh.
-Wow.
-PROBST: And now,
despite the celebration,
we are back into the game again.
It is time to vote.
Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
♪ This sucks. ♪
Oh, God.
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
All right,
if anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Ricard.
♪ ♪
Liana.
Ricard. Two votes-- Ricard.
♪ ♪
Liana. Tied again,
two votes each.
Ricard. That's three votes--
Ricard, two votes-- Liana.
Liana. We're tied again
at three votes each.
That's four votes-- Liana, three
votes-- Ricard, one vote left.
12th person voted out
and fifth member of our jury.
Liana, you need
to bring me your torch.
Good game, guys.
-Good job, Liana.
-ERIKA: Good job, Liana.
DESHAWN:
Good job, Li.
-(chuckles softly)
-Liana,
-the tribe has spoken.
-Thank you. Bye, y'all.
-Play hard.
-DANNY: Bye, Li.
-XANDER: Bye, Liana.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Me and Deshawn are on the
bottom. If there is an idol
on this island,
I hope I find it.
RICARD:
There was just something
about his vibe
that shifted.
That scares me.
...to keep you.
New plans are put on the table.
You and Erika-- that would be
a good final three.
We'll see who comes out on top.
All I can do is fight.
It was really cool
to be a part of that Tribal.
I'm just so happy to have been
a part of this season, and just,
like, so blessed to have been
able to play this game.
This was just
the best experience of my life,
and I've learned so much
about myself.
I didn't want to have
any regrets walking out,
and I feel like I played
as hard as I could.
So I'm-I'm happy with that.
I'm ready to eat. (laughs)
(roars)