(thunderclaps)
Oh, my God.
Dude, you saved my life.
-Yeah, of course.
-That was epic.
-XANDER: That was a big one.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-That was a-a splash, for sure.
-That was a splash.
XANDER: I played my cards right,
and I had
a stunning performance
that was a good enough bluff
to get Liana
to play her advantage.
I have the Knowledge is Power
Advantage.
So I just have one question.
Do you have an idol, Xander?
♪ ♪
Wow.
XANDER:
As much as I've been
playing a loyal game with Yase,
a lot of information has been
spilled at this Tribal.
I knew that Xander had the idol
before I even met the guy,
and that was because of Evvie.
I thought it was a secret
that everyone was gonna know,
and that's why I told him.
But I should have told no one.
I just figured,
it was, like,
you said it in public,
-so, like, eventually,
everyone was gonna know.
-Well...
-So I thought...
-XANDER: Things that
I wasn't aware of beforehand
and that maybe I shouldn't
put so much trust
into Evvie and Tiffany.
LIANA:
I played
the Knowledge is Power Advantage
tonight, and
I got played.
If "Survivor" was a verb,
like, Survivor happened to me.
But, also, I literally just
turned my back on my Yase tribe,
and I'm putting faith and trust
in completely new people.
And my relationship with Evvie
from this is fractured.
(thunder crackling)
You and I have really wanted
to work together.
-I know, from...
-And have been wanting
to work together.
-Absolutely.
-EVVIE: Just so lucky
to be here
'cause I was one vote away
from going home, but
the relationship with Liana is
definitely the biggest sad note.
Liana is the person out here
that I, like,
connected to 100% the most.
No, no, I-I appreciate it.
I really...
But I just want to say,
on a personal level,
-we're ....
-I know.
EVVIE:
I can't see how we could ever
get back to what we were.
It's pretty hard to think
that I could, like, really
trust her in the game again.
-(thunderclaps)
-Oh...
EVVIE:
I'm happy for you
-that you're still here,
and I'm sorry...
-Yeah.
-that it ended up, like,
that way.
-Yeah.
And-and I just wanted to let you
know, like, I'm not expecting us
to be back where we were.
You know what I mean?
Like, I totally
understand, like...
-Here's the thing, Evvie.
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Like, I know that things flip
all the time.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm really on a relationship
recovery tour because
the reality is I was
definitely playing too hard.
I can admit
when I make a mistake.
I am way on the low part
of the diamond's hierarchy here.
So as an anthropologist,
you might
see me,
the low-dominance individual,
cautiously approaching the group
of higher-ranking individuals
and testing the waters.
You know, see if I'm allowed in.
It's that horrible feeling of,
like, you're in high school, and
everyone's at the table,
and they don't want you
to come over,
but, like, what are you supposed
to do with your lunch tray?
Uh, it was so awkward.
-EVVIE: Right, right.
-And...
EVVIE:
Yeah.
What has happened
to poor little Yase?
-The little Yase turtles.
-Yes, that way.
-EVVIE: Good job!
-ALL: Yay!
We had such a cute
little story going
where we were just like
those little turtles.
Everyone counted us out, but
we just never gave up, and then
the four of us were
winning challenges together,
-and it was in a good place.
-(cheering)
But the reality is, Yase was
pulled in every direction,
and I think we're done.
Evvie had a final with you,
she had a final with him,
and she had a final
with me, so...
I'm really glad
it happened this early,
because now I'm going
to work with everyone.
EVVIE:
I'm open
to working with anyone.
Whoever needs me, I'm here.
Even though, last night, it
seemed like it was a Yase three,
I don't even think that exists
anymore 'cause we know,
so obviously,
we're all at the bottom.
You have to keep it
from Evvie and Tiff.
Let me know who,
and I'll write their name down.
TIFFANY:
I love Evvie. She's my girl...
At this point, I'm gonna use
whoever, whenever, however,
to get me as far as I can get.
I'm not here for Evvie.
I'm here for me.
LIANA:
Tiff is talking to everybody,
Yase is scrambling,
to put it quite simple.
Any little opportunity I can get
to make people
want to work with me,
that's gold.
I feel like very much
like a free agent, you know?
They tried.
The three Yases coming to me
after having voted for me
and then telling me
they want to work with me
in some capacity. No.
-It's so... it's so apparent.
-You think you're
playing with idiots,
-but we're not.
We see it. Like...
-Yeah.
DESHAWN:
I was like... I know.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm not a fool.
I will not be working with
any of the three of you.
I want to see you guys go
one by one by one.
♪ ♪
All right, it's been a while
since we've hidden an advantage
at a sit-out bench,
and we do this
not just
to keep the game unpredictable,
but also to remind players
that sometimes when you think
you're on the outside, you're
exactly where you want to be.
But it only works for the smart
player who is always looking
for opportunity.
We'll see.
Bring in the boats!
-Hello.
-Morning, Jeff.
Even getting here
is a challenge.
All right, let's get
to today's reward challenge.
-Ooh.
-For today's challenge,
you'll be randomly divided
into two teams of five.
One player will not participate
and will have no shot at reward.
On my go, you're gonna leap
off the top of a ramp,
dive down
and release puzzle pieces.
You'll put 'em in your boat.
Once you have
all your puzzle pieces
and all your players in
the boat, you'll pull yourself
to the finish, where two players
will use those puzzle pieces
to solve a pyramid puzzle.
First five to finish win reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-ALL: Yes.
-XANDER: Sure.
Grilled cheese back at camp.
Oh.
-Ooh.
-PROBST: Losers will smell
a grilled cheese back at camp
-being eaten by somebody else.
-All right.
Worth playing for?
-ALL: Yes.
-All right, we're gonna
draw for teams.
Here we go. We got two colors
and one not good color.
-(groaning)
-Won't be participating.
ERIKA:
I hate these bags.
-All right.
-I'm scared of these bags now.
I am, too. I'm so scared of 'em.
-I know.
-(laughs)
All right, everybody,
put your palms out,
-turn 'em over and reveal.
-Oh.
-If you are blue, go to blue.
-Oh, no way.
-No way.
PROBST:
If you are yellow, go to yellow.
-(laughing)
-If you're neither blue
nor yellow...
Once again,
Erika with the odd rock.
-Very... We're all sorry. Yeah.
-I hate these bags.
You're in the middle here.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: On the orange.
-I hate these bags.
-XANDER: Erika.
PROBST:
Wow. Erika,
once again, you drew the rock.
You will not participate.
You will be
on the sit-out bench.
Hold on, Jeff.
Uh, Erika's already
had her chance to draw
the, uh, gray rock, and...
Oh, you do not need to do this.
I think she's, you know, great
at puzzles, and she's probably
-hungry after Exile, so...
-Oh, my God.
-...I'll give up
my spot for her.
-PROBST: So, Xander,
you're saying you want
to give up your shot at food?
-XANDER: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Because you will not have it
if you take her spot.
XANDER:
That's right, yeah.
-Xander, swap spots with Erika.
-XANDER: Of course.
-Oh. Thank you.
-Interesting turn of events
-that I would not
have seen coming.
-(Erika laughs)
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
That's why I love this game.
All right, Xander opted to take
the sit-out,
gave up grilled cheese.
Here we go.
For reward. Survivors, ready.
Come on, Liana.
Black girl magic.
-Go! Liana's in first.
-Go, Liana! You got this!
-And Ricard's in first.
-SHAN: There you go, Liana.
(indistinct,
overlapping chatter)
-ERIKA: Let's go, Ricard!
-(clapping)
-DANNY: Yeah!
-Yeah!
-(cheering)
PROBST:
Big leap for both.
You got to dive down now
and release that first set
of puzzle pieces.
Liana has hers!
-Ricard has it for Blue!
-ERIKA: Yes, Ricard!
EVVIE:
Behind you! Behind you!
-DESHAWN: Behind you.
There you go.
-ERIKA: You got it, Ricard.
We're in this. Let's go.
-Go, yellow!
-Go, Liana!
PROBST:
It's Shan in the water.
TIFFANY:
Go ahead, Shan! Let's go, Shan!
NASEER:
Keep going. Great, great.
You're doing great!
DANNY:
There you go, Ricard!
-Go, Blue! It's now Danny...
-Go, Danny!
-in the water. Here goes Shan.
-TIFFANY: Yeah, Shan!
She's in, plugging the nose,
whatever it takes.
-TIFFANY: Yeah.
-HEATHER: Yeah, Shanny!
-PROBST: Shan releases
-the puzzle pieces.
-Whoa. Yup.
Danny in the water now for Blue!
Danny quickly releases
the second set of puzzle pieces
for Blue.
-Go, yellow! Heather for yellow!
-Go, go, go, go, go, go.
-Come on, Heather. You got this!
-Go, blue!
It's Deshawn in the water now.
-(indistinct shouting)
-No more puzzle pieces left.
Now it's just bodies.
You got to get to the boat.
SHAN:
Come on, Heather!
-Got it. Right here.
-Good job, Heather.
We got you, Heather.
Go, blue!
It's now Erika in the water.
Heather's got to get pulled up.
-Go, yellow! It's now
Tiffany in the water.
-Go.
Oh! Wow.
-Here goes Tiffany.
-(cheering)
Come on in. Right here,
right here, right here.
-Go, blue! Go, yellow!
-Here you go.
The final members of each team.
Naseer. Wow!
DANNY:
There we go! Yeah!
PROBST:
Naseer is going 100%.
You're good. Unclip.
Up, up, up, up. Yeah.
-I got it. Yeah.
-Okay.
-PROBST: Unclip!
-Got it.
-Go, go, go!
-PROBST: Yellow is unclipped.
-Working hard
for that grilled cheese.
-Go, go, go, go.
-PROBST: Now you're good.
-(overlapping chatter)
SHAN:
Go! Naseer, go!
-Need to get out.
-(grunting)
Get off and get your
puzzle pieces and get to work.
Two people on the puzzle.
Reward on the line.
It's gonna be Erika and Evvie.
-You're building
a pyramid puzzle.
-Yeah.
Wow, Evvie very quickly
is taking over this puzzle.
-Jeff! Jeff!
-Jeff, Jeff, Jeff, Jeff!
Unbelievable.
(cheering)
Blue wins reward!
Wow.
That's how you do it!
Evvie, you knew that puzzle.
I remember watching this on
Edge of Extinction.
I remember
that tribe sucking so bad.
And then they pulled out
this puzzle, and I was like,
"I can make that puzzle out of
beads in my house," and I did.
-And it paid off.
-PROBST: That is what
research and practice gets you.
Lesson to you future
Survivor players.
That's how you do it
right there.
All right, waiting for you
back at camp: grilled cheese.
Tiffany, Naseer,
Shan, Liana, Heather,
nothing for you.
Xander, you can come join them.
Everybody, swim out.
Enjoy your afternoon.
♪ ♪
I don't know if he looked,
but he didn't find it.
Missed opportunity.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God. Oh.
ERIKA:
For the last ten days,
all I've talked about is how
I wanted a sandwich with chips.
So when I see a pile of grilled
cheese sandwiches and a massive
bowl of chips, I was like,
"Maybe I manifested
this reward."
DESHAWN:
Let's eat everything.
-DANNY: Yeah.
-EVVIE: Yeah. Good job.
TIFFANY:
It was really insane.
Almost every single player
that was with me
on the last challenge
was with me once again.
We were not stacked,
and again we lost.
It was annoying as hell to me
because I haven't eaten.
I'm 47 years old.
Feed me already.
This looks so good. (laughs)
-It just seemed like...
-You guys okay?
Yeah.
SHAN:
This game is,
I feel like,
breaking me down sometimes.
I feel very frustrated
because I lost the merge feast,
and then we lost this reward.
Like, it definitely was
very emotional because
we all feel very, very hungry.
Come on, Liana, don't cry.
-Like, I might seriously cry.
-I just wanted to know
you weren't the only one.
It's hard.
-This is pretty.
-Like an old hangout.
Never been here before.
Oh, my God.
Look at this feast here.
-DANNY: Oh, man.
-EVVIE: That is so good.
-That's pretty damn good.
-I know. Ooh.
This is a better sandwich
than I was expecting.
The people with more calories
can obviously do
a little bit more, and that was
very frustrating for me.
You're showing us
that you're sad.
I know it. I'm sorry. Like...
I'm just really hungry, so...
-No, no.
-SHAN: But I just told
myself, "You know what?
Put food out of your mind
completely."
I'm here to win.
The cry gave me clarity.
It gave me perspective.
-I want Evvie to just go.
-LIANA: To disappear.
SHAN:
Evvie, to me, is probably
one of the biggest threats
in the game.
She's strategic,
she's a superfan.
Did you see her
with the puzzle today?
She's dangerous.
So the plan is
to really get in front of
some of the people
that I've aligned with and
tell them
that this is the direction
that the vote needs to go.
I want to get out
so many people,
-but I want to start with Evvie.
-Okay, I'm ready.
So, we were thinking
I would love to get out Evvie.
XANDER:
Part of the reason why I chose
the sit-out bench is because
I love being with the losers.
It leaves people
pretty emotional.
It leaves people pretty raw,
and I need allies.
I've got no one
to work with right now.
After everything
that's come out, like...
And she played you.
She was like,
"I got my little brother here."
And it, like, it really hurt
to realize that she'd,
like, just been
playing me like everybody else.
LIANA: Xander was someone
that I wanted out
from the very beginning,
and now he's somebody that
I'm considering
working with, and
I think, you know,
the best Survivor players
have had to do that.
So...
Wait. Catch.
We lost the reward challenge,
so what next?
Move on.
Find some different food.
If you stick there,
start crying, get emotional,
you're ruining your day.
Three papayas.
I can eat steak when I get home.
My daughter will make
grilled cheese.
Thank you so much.
Hey, this is so good.
(overlapping chatter)
RICARD:
What on earth is all that?
Papaya?
We have papaya.
Like, ripe papaya.
-We just ate papaya.
-LIANA: Yeah.
-RICARD: Where'd you find it?
-SHAN: Naseer found it.
I'm gonna try one bite.
Try one bite.
I want to try the papaya.
-Really?
-Really, son.
You just ate, and you just..
SHAN:
So we're the losers.
We haven't eaten
any grilled cheese.
And then Ricard comes in,
and he's like,
"Ooh, I just want
to try a little piece."
SHAN: I feel like
that was really selfish.
Like, we have not eaten,
and I don't care
if it's a freaking piece
of the inch of the...
like a centimeter, millimeter
of the papaya. Don't touch it.
I was so bothered when
he took a piece of the papaya.
Dude, you just ate a freaking
grilled cheese sandwich
and chips.
He's my number one, but,
honestly, those moments
really do change
and pivot the direction
of the game.
That's character.
Your belly is full.
You're at the height of...
You're feeling good,
and in that moment, you still
choose to, you know, take
from people on the bottom
who are losing.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
How good is the papaya?
RICARD: What's difficult
with these reward challenges
is there seems to be this divide
that I've never seen
as a fan from home,
of if you go on a reward,
you're expected not to eat
anything else that day.
And, you know, all the food
that comes from the island
is our tribe's food,
and I try a bite,
and I get snapped at
because I won a reward.
I don't like that.
RICARD:
Shan's had no food,
no merge feast, nothing, and
the game player in me
is really concerned
that she'll resent me for
getting everything in her eyes,
and so I'm hoping it doesn't
mess up our future alliance.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first.
Ricard, got to take it back.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna balance
on your toes
with a block of wood
wedged between your head
and the top of a frame.
The longer the challenge goes,
the more fatigued
your legs will become.
When they finally give out,
the block will drop,
and you're out of the challenge.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
Losers, Tribal Council
where somebody will be
voted out of this game.
So it's day 16.
Up until now, you've been living
on very little: hermit crabs,
small fish.
Who's sick of coconut?
So, two options for you today.
If any individual player
feels they're safe enough
in the game,
or doesn't feel they can win
this challenge, you can opt out
in exchange...
for a single portion of rice.
Doesn't seem like much,
but, Tiffany, out here...
-It's a lot. Yeah.
-HEATHER: It's a lot.
-PROBST: It's a lot.
Option two.
If, as a group,
you want to offer up
-multiple people to sit
out of this challenge...
-Hmm.
-...give up their shot
at immunity.
-HEATHER: Oh.
Enough rice...
-for everybody for three days.
-TIFFANY: Ooh.
How many is multiple?
Well, that's what
we're negotiating.
I'm the one putting up the item.
You need
to make the first offer.
-How many people do you need
to give up, Jeff?
-HANNAH: Yeah.
-Offer a number.
-What about two people?
-Three?
-I'll take seven.
-TIFFANY: Whoa.
-NASEER: Whoa.
-(Xander whistles)
-Are we negotiating or what?
-SHAN: All right,
I'll give you...
-HEATHER: Five.
-...five people.
-Done.
-HEATHER: Really?
-Any five?
PROBST:
Done at five. Fair deal.
SHAN: For all of us
to eat for three days?
-I'll step out.
-PROBST: Need four more.
Or else we're all playing.
I need to play.
-Here's Naseer.
-Wow. Thank you.
What's fascinating to me
about this
is that the stages
of the game are not clear.
Yes, you're in
the individual portion,
but you're still relying
on each other.
You're asking yourselves,
"Do I trust this group enough
that if I sacrificed,
they will not vote me out
tonight?"
Nobody?
If no one else is willing
to step up,
-then I want to compete.
-Yeah.
Jeff, what about four?
One more person steps up,
I'll step up
in the fourth place.
You got a deal.
Here's why I'll renegotiate.
Because I believe now,
watching you,
you are understanding
how dangerous this game is,
and you are petrified
to give it up.
This feels like
a great compromise.
There's our fourth.
We've got a deal.
Xander, Ricard, Shan and Naseer
are gonna sit out
of this challenge
in exchange for rice
for the entire group.
-Take a spot on the bench.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, guys.
-Thank you so much.
PROBST:
Question is: Is there enough
trust to make this work?
Let's get started.
All right, everybody,
get into position.
Put your blocks above your head,
wedge them in against the frame.
You can still hold on right now
until you get situated,
and once everybody's in there,
we're gonna start.
Everybody's in position,
and we're gonna let go.
This challenge is on.
Deshawn is out within seconds.
Erika's out. Two are down.
Tiffany, you're out,
and we are down to four.
That happens in this challenge.
-It's okay.
-PROBST: Just like that,
we are down to Liana, Danny,
Heather and Evvie.
You're gonna start
feeling it very quickly
in your legs.
(wood creaking)
It's another
pain threshold challenge.
The longest it has gone
is one hour, 22 minutes.
-Dang.
-Spencer.
Danny drops,
and we are down to three.
-Wow.
-PROBST: Liana,
Heather and Evvie.
(wood creaking)
Part of the early drops
certainly has to do
with the lack of calories
in your body over 16 days.
You simply don't have the fuel
to do things
that you could normally do.
PROBST:
Liana drops,
and we are down to two.
We are three minutes
into this challenge,
and already down to two players.
♪ ♪
This is it-- a showdown.
Neither one of you two offered
to sit out,
which tells me
you feel you need this.
You are fighting
for your security tonight
at Tribal Council.
(insects buzzing)
-(wood creaking)
-These are the kind of moments
you hope to find yourself in
when you sign up
for this adventure.
Come on, Mama H. I see you.
You got to dig right now.
And Evvie--
legs shaking on that beam.
Oh.
Heather drops.
Evvie wins individual immunity.
Cannot be voted out
at tonight's Tribal Council.
-ERIKA: Nice job, Evvie.
-Nice job, Evvie.
Wow. Shortest this challenge
has ever gone.
Barely four minutes.
TIFFANY:
Good job, Evvie.
-LIANA: Good job.
-Nice job, Evvie.
PROBST:
Evvie, come on over.
-Thanks, guys.
-Good job, Evvie. Nice job.
PROBST:
Right here.
So what's this feel like?
I know this is
something for you.
Just incredibly surreal.
Like, I never, ever,
ever thought I would win
individual immunity, so,
you know, pinch me or something.
I-I don't know.
-Doesn't feel real.
-It's real.
Okay, it's real. (chuckles)
-You are safe tonight.
-Thank you.
You're guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
You aren't going home tonight.
Somebody else is.
Good news is,
-before Tribal, you will eat.
-Yay.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-(clapping)
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
EVVIE:
In my real life,
I feel very blessed to have
a lot of support, you know?
But, like, out here,
I had really no support,
and I just did it,
and I am very positive
that I needed it today.
Sorry, guys.
Foiled you again.
♪ ♪
-Good job.
-Great job.
-Good job, Evvie.
-Good job, Evvie. Good job.
-Thank you.
LIANA: We had a whole plan set
on voting Evvie, and that was
gonna be how me and Xander
worked together
for the first time--
if Evvie lost.
TIFFANY:
Thank you for the rice, guys.
-Yeah.
-LIANA: But now, what I want
to see happen tonight is I want
to see Xander play his idol
unnecessarily, and then
-Tiff to go home.
-LIANA: Thank you for making
that good compromise,
'cause Jeff bought it at least.
-So, it would've sucked
if we didn't have any rice.
-Yeah.
And Tiff, right?
-It's the only, like, option.
-Yeah.
-LIANA: If those two things
happen, then Xander and Evvie
are now on the bottom, and
Xander doesn't have any power.
And there's two idols left
in the game,
being Naseer and Shan's.
SHAN:
Evvie has immunity.
-So is it easy?
-I think it's easy.
Between...
And Tiff.
Yeah.
-Even one play the idol?
-How do you feel about that?
-Yeah, th-that's fine.
-Fine.
-My goal is to flush
Xander's idol.
-Yeah.
Okay.
NASEER:
So we're gonna split the vote
to Tiffany and Xander.
But I'm hoping to hang on
my hidden immunity idol tonight
because I trust Shan and Ricard.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-That's it.
-All right.
NASEER:
So, I feel safe
because either way,
I have the numbers, plus,
I have the hidden immunity.
I'm not going home today.
Xander's more dangerous.
He's the only question mark
right now.
We don't know
what yellow's doing.
They're acting like
they're divided.
What I threw out was
let's split it
between Naseer and Tiff.
-I love it.
-Then nobody...
And here's the thing, dude.
Like, after tonight,
or the next vote, Naseer is
gonna know
he's on the chopping block.
Right now, he feels comfortable.
You guys, Xander is a threat.
-I'm telling you.
-They're both threats.
Xander's a bigger threat
than Naseer.
I don't think you know that.
And Xander and Tiffany and Evvie
working together is
a bigger threat.
I'm telling you.
We know what they have
in their pockets.
Xander has an extra vote
and the idol.
DESHAWN: I was quite pissed
at Shan because we even
utter Naseer's name,
and you shut it down.
That's not gonna work for me,
Miss Ma'am.
Like, you need to listen
to what I have to say.
Naseer is a number
in our pocket right now
to take care of everybody else
so we four get to the end.
Xander is not
a number in our pocket.
DESHAWN:
If we don't fix this,
then there's gonna
come a time where I'm like,
-"Shan's got to go."
-(squawking)
We got to communicate better
because I don't do well
when, like, people
tell me what to do,
and then there's no, like...
Like, you're not absorbing
my opinion, too, and...
-Help me understand, so...
-Okay.
-Tell me so I can learn,
'cause I don't know.
-Okay.
So tell me,
when did you feel like
I was not absorbing
your opinion?
-Okay, so when we were
on the beach, and I came up...
-Mm-hmm.
...just to say, like, possibly
it being Naseer, just possibly,
like, you... It was like, "No."
I need to know
that you're gonna actually
listen to my opinion, too.
-Hear you out?
-And that's all
I'm asking, please.
Okay. But I do want to hear you,
-and your voice does
matter to me.
-Mm.
So, like,
I will listen to you more.
I see the argument for Naseer,
but I-I want Naseer around,
specifically because
Naseer helps provide
for the camp, and to me, Naseer
is not that dangerous right now.
Naseer is loyal.
I can use that right now.
-I love you. I love you.
-I love you, too.
Deshawn has a moment
where he feels like
he hasn't been fully heard,
so I have to make sure
he feels fully heard as a man.
But my gameplay is social,
and so, I need to be the one
that's able to move the needle.
-Okay, so Xander has an idol,
so we want...
-Yeah.
-...to flush his idol tonight
and vote Tiffany.
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh, Xander's coming.
-So we're gonna
tell him that soon?
-Naseer.
-So, you... you'll tell Naseer?
All the while
making everyone feel heard
and feel like
their opinions matter.
Let's keep it simple: Naseer.
I think we just
concentrate our efforts
on Naseer tonight
'cause he's got the idol.
That's what I do as a pastor.
I take into consideration
all the information.
There's a lot of members.
They got a lot of thoughts
about this potluck,
this evangelistic idea,
this trip they want to take.
Then I got
to hear it all, and I've got
to convince them that still
my way is the best way.
So...
I know.
We shouldn't switch it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Heather. Heather.
XANDER: The first names
that I hear are Naseer
and Tiffany,
and now that it's Heather, it's
put my, uh, you know,
my betraydar on.
XANDER:
So right now,
I'm in debugging mode,
and I'm searching
through the code,
scouring for
that one stupid error
that's causing all my problems.
-Who do you think it is?
-I thought it was me.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
I think it's me.
I, Tiffany, do not know
what the plan is,
and that's not a good feeling.
I mean, I want to stay tonight
really badly,
and I don't know
how I'm gonna do it.
-You think it's me?
-It could be.
TIFFANY:
I am going into this Tribal
working with anybody
who wants to work with me,
including
crew and anybody else who might
want to come out and help me.
If I go rogue,
then it's gonna be a ... show.
I don't care who you are.
Join forces, jump on in.
If there's
a crab that wants to vote
tonight, it can come with me.
ERIKA:
Xander asked
-what the plan was.
-Uh-huh.
And then Shan said,
"Naseer and Heather."
Someone had said
that we're saying...
So what if he puts my name down
and they both play idols?
Then I'm ....
-No.
-Yeah.
Shan is, one,
definitely taken on the role
of telling everybody what to do.
-And I don't trust her.
-Who's the backup?
HEATHER:
You already told him me.
My name should never have been
-brought in th-- for this.
-It shouldn't,
but you're looking
at me like I was the only one.
It's not that I just
threw your name.
It was that other people
were saying your name, as well,
Heather. It wasn't just me.
But wouldn't it be nice to come
to me and say, "Hey, we're gonna
-do this"?
-Yeah, that was the plan.
That was the plan.
I just passed on what
I heard said. That's all it was.
HEATHER:
In Survivor, you're always
taught, "We never want
"to get back someone
that their name was said
because all ... hits the fan."
♪ ♪
SHAN:
I feel nervous going
into Tribal because
everybody's just nuts, it's
a hot steaming mess, and so,
there's a ton of things
that could go wrong tonight.
All the advantages are at play,
the Shot in the Dark
is at play.
You know,
the idols could come out.
Best laid plans never work out.
So right now, I need a prayer
maybe for Tribal Council.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, so food has been
a big issue the last few days.
Part of that is because
the new Survivor
is designed to see
how it will impact you
cognitively and physically,
and we're seeing that play out.
So, Shan, we get
to the immunity challenge.
You're the first person
to step up, willing to risk.
-Yeah.
-Was it because you're starving,
or were you doing that
-on behalf of the group?
-Yeah, I think my pastoral,
like, heart just kind of
came through, and I just
wanted us all to be able
to eat. I don't care
who gets the credit for it.
It took four of us to do it.
I just wanted us
to be able to eat.
Xander, the negotiation was
about to fall apart.
You open it back up again
and say,
"How about four,
and I'll be the one more?"
-Was a big move.
-XANDER: Yeah, I mean,
we really don't have anything,
and some people it's wearing
a lot thinner than others.
I wanted to prove to my tribe
that I was willing
to sacrifice immunity
so that the people
who haven't gotten as fortunate
with rock draws
-could eat something.
-PROBST: Naseer,
you stepped up, as well,
and gave up your shot.
When you say like,
"This is for the entire tribe,"
my heart is immediately...
I did not think even the cha...
about the challenge.
Even though I practiced
for that particular challenge,
since I have flat feet,
and I have chicken legs, too.
(laughing):
So...
I know I could have
won that challenge,
but still,
when it comes to tribe,
yes, I'd rather
take care of my tribe.
-Heather, you competed. Why?
-Because I am scared.
I'm not ready to go home, and
I feel like I'm on the bottom,
and I didn't feel secure,
and so,
I want to get there
and give it a shot.
PROBST:
Tiffany,
you didn't sit out today.
-Why?
-Also not comfortable
a hundred percent.
There are five Luvu left.
Then there's a whole nother
group, and then there's, like,
two or three people
that are not told anything.
That seems to be what happens.
People feel comfort
in numbers, but...
I don't know. This is Survivor,
so you got to rock the boat
a little bit.
PROBST:
Danny,
are you closer
to confident you're okay,
or closer to,
"I'm not sure I'm okay"?
DANNY:
Based on last Tribal Council,
not really sure.
Uh, things changed really,
really fast, and I think
we're just at the beginning
of this one, so we have no idea
what type of fireworks
-are about to get started.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
Shan, is that real that you guys
are sitting here going,
"I have no idea.
This may explode"?
Yeah, I'm just waiting
for a comment to drop
and someone to stand up
and start whispering.
Really? So you think this
group-- even though you look
fairly composed to me--
-under the water...
-SHAN: Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
-Give it a minute.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Evvie,
what am I missing?
-I mean, you're definitely
asking the wrong person, Jeff,
'cause literally,
not a single person told me
who to vote for today.
I mean, I know
that there's plans afoot, but
-no one told them to me, so...
-DANNY: Jeff? Jeff?
Let me help
paint the picture for you, okay?
-Thank you, Danny.
-DANNY: So, last Tribal,
there's a big theatrical moment
from Tiff, Evvie and Xander.
Next morning, all of a sudden,
they're going
to everybody saying,
"I'm ready to turn. I'm mad."
So now everybody's wondering,
is it still big theatrics,
are they really
disliking each other,
or are they really willing to go
against everybody else?
Because if you fall for it
twice, then it's your fault.
But the reality is, you saw me
literally begging Tiffany
to play the idol,
and Xander told her not to.
And the only reason
I'm still here
-is because Sydney played
her Shot in the Dark.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
-Mm-hmm. That's fair.
-Like, for real,
they were gonna let me die.
Honestly, we're one,
two, three individuals.
Like, that-that's the reality.
(laughs)
ERIKA:
Jeff, I think that,
because it's so hard here,
I feel like we're all
off-balance, we all met
just a few days ago.
And these three we thought
were together, but now
we don't know if they're
together. And I feel like,
even if you're here
and you have a plan for how
you're going to vote,
it's still like a leap of faith
because we don't actually know
who's with who.
PROBST:
All right, there anything that
needs to be said before we vote?
Feel like I have to ask
this group, 'cause you're all
-clearly... on edge.
-(laughter)
-Yeah.
-PROBST: All right.
It is... time... to... vote.
-Ricard, you're up.
-Oh.
-PROBST: Hang...
-HEATHER: What?
We don't get to talk?
DANNY:
Oh. (laughs)
-Oh, I thought we could talk.
-PROBST: Well...
Well, you can, but we just...
Okay.
You can do whatever you want,
but, Heather,
I couldn't have gone
any slower with
-"It is time to..."
-HEATHER: Okay. But-but
-can we kind of whisper
something right now?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-It's your tribe.
Yeah. All right.
Wait.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Wow. Once again,
-confused faces.
-HEATHER: Sorry.
-Just one second.
-Oh, my God.
Wow.
Yeah.
You know what?
Okay.
-Evvie, Evvie, come here.
-Come here.
-Please.
Yes.
-Heather's name.
-I'm fine with that.
-I'm so fine with that.
I don't get it.
-Okay.
SHAN:
What are we gonna do right now?
'Cause that was crazy.
-Yeah.
-SHAN: D, what do...?
-Come here.
-I'm cool. Let's do it.
-Come here. No, come...
-We don't need to talk.
-No, we should.
-D, let's talk.
-For real?
For real? Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Deshawn says, "Let's vote."
No. No, no, no, no, no.
-Shan.
-Okay. All right, so come
to... Okay, but, so then
come to the circle
and just talk to all...
-I'm not shut...
-You just did. You...
I'm telling you,
come to the circle.
-Then come to the circle.
-I told you I... We're...
-But I don't want to...
-We'll talk about it.
I don't... Deshawn's not down.
We'll talk about--
I'm doing it. Let's do it.
I love it.
Wow.
SHAN:
I'm saying, Jeff,
this is Season 41.
Drop the four, hit the one.
Ain't nobody ever seen
anything like this before.
-(laughter)
-Not only are we trying
to work a plan.
It's group therapy
at the same time.
-Mm.
-And it... and it honestly is
'cause I'm learning
how to talk to
different people the way
that they need to be heard.
All that stuff matters, so,
it is a different caliber
of game right now.
So is it time to vote?
-Yes.
-Please.
All right, Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Xander.
Xander. Two votes Xander.
Heather.
Heather. Two votes Xander,
two votes Heather.
Naseer.
Tiffany.
We're tied again.
Two votes Heather,
two votes Xander,
two votes Tiffany,
one vote Naseer.
That's three votes Tiffany.
Tiffany.
That's four votes Tiffany.
Eighth person voted out and
the first member of our jury.
Tiffany, that's five.
That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
-Love you, Tiff.
-Love you, guys.
SHAN:
Love you, Tiff.
-Love you, Tiff.
-Love you, Tiff. Thanks.
Tiffany, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks.
Time for you to go.
-Bye, Tiff.
-Good luck, guys.
-Love you.
Love you.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
XANDER:
It's perfect
that they're fighting
with each other.
-I will cast the extra vote.
-No!
It has to be her way
all the time.
Why am I bending backwards
for this dude?
She don't be making sense.
Shan is starting
to piss me off a lot.
EVVIE:
There were fireworks,
and things are gonna shake up
around here.
It was a...
such a terrible move.
There are three people
sitting with idols,
which is ridiculous
that I was voted out.
It's gonna bite them all.
They're playing a safe game,
and I just wasn't willing
to play the safe game.
But I'm so grateful
I got to play.
It was nothing you'd ever think
you were gonna experience,
and it's a once-in-a-lifetime,
so I can't really be that upset.
And I can't wait to be
the first member of the jury.
(roars)