♪ ♪
Oh.
GENIE:
Right now, I don't know
what to trust.
I don't know who to trust.
I had no idea this was coming.
I mean, the only person that
was more blindsided was Brad,
and he went home.
I thought we were voting JD.
-So-so now, now I know.
-JD: Hold up. Hold on.
I'm on the bottom of this.
Hold on. I know... I...
-Hold on.
-GENIE: Well, guess what.
You guys do your own food.
I'm-a do my own food.
And you guys work
as hard as you want,
and I'll work
as hard as I want for myself.
I've been, like,
feeding them, dude.
I've been, like, the mom.
I've been, like, in the kitchen.
I know nobody wants
to do that ....
Nobody wants
to tend to the fire.
If you don't want
to work with me,
I'm not taking care of you guys.
I'm not.
Genie, I'm gonna, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna squash this right now,
and I'm gonna
tell you something, okay?
And nobody else knows this,
but Brad had an advantage
that he didn't tell you about.
He got the, the Steal a Vote.
He only told me that.
I was Brad's number one.
Brad wasn't
taking you anywhere, boo.
-Wow.
-And he didn't...
He kept you
out of the loop on that.
That's crazy.
Bro, kudos to him. Played me.
I'm mad because
when Shan found out
that I was not telling her
about my extra vote,
she made me
feel terrible about it.
I, literally,
gave her my advantage.
And then for me
to find out that
she was actually withholding
information from me, as well.
I was like, "You played me."
I don't understand why I was
kind of raked over the coals,
in a way, for not telling
people about my advantage,
and then there's just
all this information
that I had no idea about.
SHAN:
Brad told me that
in confidence.
That's his stuff.
You won something.
Yeah, that's my stuff.
I'd like it back in my bag.
Oh, okay.
You can have it back.
You know, I think she gave me
the extra vote back
'cause she actually
does trust me.
And now that bad boy
is back in my bag.
But fool me once, shame on me.
And that's it.
That's the end of it.
You're not gonna fool me twice.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Luvu and Yase getting your
first look to the new Ua tribe.
Brad voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, let's get
to your first reward challenge.
-All right.
-SYDNEY: Oh, wow.
-(whoops)
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race out
with a ball,
toss it into an overhead track
and then catch it
on the other side.
Once all four players
are through,
you're gonna dig under a beam,
and then, one at a time,
attempt to land those balls
on a perch.
The first two tribes to finish
win reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
The winning tribe
will have a visitor
waiting for you back at camp.
-An expert at living
off the land in Fiji.
-(excited chatter)
They will teach you lessons you
can use the rest of this game.
The second tribe to finish...
-...one beautiful fish to share.
-Ooh.
-HEATHER: Wow.
-PROBST: Losers,
you're on your own.
Luvu, you're sitting
two people out.
Keeping in mind, whoever
sits out of this challenge
must participate
in the immunity challenge.
-Naseer and Erika.
-And Erika.
PROBST:
Naseer and Erika gonna sit out.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Let's do it!
All right, here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
-Come on, Xander. You got this.
PROBST:
It is Deshawn, Ricard and Xander
-taking it on first.
-(cheering)
Xander lands it down the track,
and he's moving fast.
Xander has it.
He's good.
-Deshawn is good.
-ERIKA: Nice. Nice. Nice.
-Good job.
-Good job. Yes.
Ricard is through.
Heather's working for Luvu.
-DESHAWN: Yes. Ah, damn.
-DANNY: Almost. Almost.
You got this, Shan.
There you go.
Wow, Shan, trying to catch it.
Can she get there?
-Yes!
-Nice job, Shan!
-Yes, go, go, go, go...
-XANDER: There you go.
There you go.
You got it. You got it...
PROBST:
Liana, wow!
Whipped through that course.
Nice job.
RICARD:
Yes, yes, go, go, go...
-PROBST: JD's got a shot.
-(grunts)
-But he stumbles. Can't do it.
JD's got to go back.
DANNY: They're not getting it.
There you go. We can.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Heather still working
for Luvu.
SHAN:
There it is! There it is!
You got this. You got this.
You got...
Turn around, turn around.
-Yes, yes, JD, go.
-RICARD: Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
JD is through. Go!
-It's Genie,
the last member for Ua.
-Come on, Genie. Come on, girl.
-Go, go. Yes, yes.
-XANDER: There you go, Tiff.
PROBST:
Here goes Tiffany.
Wow, she's got a shot.
-XANDER: Yes! Yes.
-And she's got it.
-(cheering)
-Go, Evvie!
-Go, go, go!
-Evvie's got a shot.
It's the first reward challenge
of the season.
-Yes!
-PROBST: That's how you do it!
-Start digging.
-XANDER: Let's go. (grunts)
PROBST:
Heather still working it
for Luvu.
-Oh, my God.
-SHAN: Hustle! Hustle!
-PROBST: Genie, she's on track.
-JD: Hustle, hustle, you got it!
And that is good.
Start digging.
SHAN:
Come on, guys. Dig.
DANNY:
To the right. To the right.
To the right. There you go.
Same throw.
PROBST:
Heather is in trouble right now.
-DESHAWN: Heather, yes!
-SYDNEY: Let's go, Heather!
PROBST:
She will never get to that one.
Heather has got
to get through this.
-(grunts)
-XANDER: Good job, Liana.
You're good, Yase. Go.
Okay.
Put 'em all in the basket.
PROBST:
You're good, Ua.
-It's gonna be Xander now.
-(indistinct chatter)
And JD.
-There it is!
-Yes.
JD with the first one for Ua.
It's Ua in the lead.
First and second place
on the line.
DANNY:
There's no quit over here.
-There you go. To the right...
-PROBST: Luvu nowhere close.
-DESHAWN: Come on, Heather.
Never quit, Heather. You got it.
-Straight up. There you go.
PROBST:
Heather struggling.
Will she have a shot?
Let's go, Heather.
Dive!
-Move! Move!
-(cheering)
-ERIKA: Oh. It's okay.
-Oh, ....
Just be prepared to catch it
when you come out, okay?
It's okay.
We got time. We love you.
-You're all right.
-You're fine. You're fine.
-DESHAWN: We love you, Heather.
-Sorry.
No. Stop.
PROBST:
Don't give up.
-Yes! Yes! Come on, Genie.
-Ricard lands his second for Ua.
It is Ua in the lead with two.
-(cheering)
-There you go.
Yase lands their first ball.
-Again.
-Same routine.
-Go, go, go, go, go!
-Let's go, Heather!
-DESHAWN: Yes, Heather! Yes!
Be ready to catch it.
Heather.
We want to see you do well,
Heather. Keep going.
-So sorry.
-No, you're fine.
-Heather.
-You're fine.
-(chanting): Heather! Heather!
-As soon as you throw it,
take off.
-Take off.
-Heather! You got it, Heather.
Come on.
You got to admire Heather
if for no other reason
than she has not given up.
She has not lost faith.
-Yeah!
-Ua with their third.
Genie lands a third for Ua.
-(cheering) Oh, my God!
-Genie wins it for Ua
with one toss.
We're looking for second place.
-(cheers)
-There's a second for Tiffany.
Oh.
-You got it.
-Got it.
-(whoops)
-Tiffany lands a third for Yase.
-There you go. One more.
-Come on. Come on.
-There is one ball left.
Oh, no!
-(cheering)
-There it is! Yase wins reward!
Giving Luvu their first loss
of the season.
Hey. Hey, it's not...
Hey, hey, Heather. Heather.
Heather. You all right?
-(crying): I'm so sorry.
-Listen, you don't have
to apologize to us.
-We win or lose together.
-It's fine.
This is a reward challenge.
-It's all right.
-(crying): I'm so sorry.
-No. We're gonna go fishing.
-You got to get out of that.
You got to get out of that.
-I know, but I let you down.
-You got to get out of that. No.
We-we all fail sometimes.
That's how it works, all right?
You can't win 'em all,
all right?
You didn't, you didn't quit.
We still, we still...
You know how hard you tried?
Don't cry. You tried hella hard.
Come on. Get up.
We hold our heads up, okay?
-We're Luvu. Let's stand up.
We got it.
-ERIKA: Mama, we love you.
-We love you, Mama.
-We got it. Come on.
-SHAN: You got it, Heather.
-(clapping)
-XANDER: Good job, Heather!
-We love you.
-LIANA: You got it.
-EVVIE: Good job, Heather.
-TIFFANY: Heather,
good job, baby.
-It's not easy.
-DANNY: You got nothing
to apologize about.
-You went out there
and gave it everything you got.
-We love you, Mama. We love you.
Right?
That's what I'm talking about.
-Good job, dude.
-It's all about not giving up.
That's what matters.
-Head up.
-LIANA: You never gave up.
That's what matters.
PROBST:
All right, Heather, a couple
of things happened out there.
-One, you struggled.
-(sniffles)
Two, you never gave up.
And three, when it was over,
everybody here
acknowledged your efforts.
So what are you
feeling right now?
(breathes sharply)
-ERIKA: It's okay.
-SYDNEY: It's okay.
I let myself down,
and I don't quit.
(sniffles)
And I feel like I let them down.
PROBST:
Danny, can you let yourself down
when you're trying to do
something you've never done
and have no expectation
to know how to do it?
Absolutely not. The only way
you can let yourself down
is if you don't give
100% effort, and she gave it.
And, Heather,
I just got to say, for me,
one of the reasons
I'm still here,
21 years later,
is because of moments like that.
I love the gameplay
of Survivor,
but I really like it
when somebody's vulnerable
and lets us watch
-and then is rewarded with love
from their competitors.
-Mm-hmm.
That's got to make you
feel a little better.
It does. It does.
All right, now let's get
to the victors.
-Ua, your reward is waiting
for you back at camp.
-(whoops)
I encourage you to soak up
as much as you can.
This guy is an expert.
Grab your stuff, head back,
enjoy.
-(clapping)
-Good job, guys.
-Good job.
Yase, one fish for the tribe.
Come grab it.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, he's so pretty, or she.
Luvu, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, Jeff.
HEATHER:
When you fail at something,
it hurts like hell
and you're embarrassed.
But with every failure,
you're told
it molds you into who you are.
And it sounds so cliché,
but it does.
At 52 years old,
I'm already coming out here
with a disadvantage,
but I didn't give up.
I just felt so proud of myself.
This personal victory
made me even stronger.
And that's why
I love Survivor.
♪ ♪
EVVIE:
Can't you just see it now?
It's like,
"Previously on Survivor...
Yase suffered a devastating
series of losses."
PROBST:
Yase has been a disaster
in challenges
this entire season.
"But with
the core remaining four,
they were on a winning streak."
PROBST:
There it is! Yase wins reward!
"Unstoppable."
"Challenge after challenge."
"And since Tiffany is
completely motivated by food..."
-(laughs)
-Clearly.
The tribe is doing so well
because I'm kicking some ass.
I mean...
Did you see
the last few challenges we had?
It's not just 'cause of me.
I was joking.
It was a group effort.
And in Survivor,
it's such a "me, me, me" game,
at the end of the day,
that the teamwork
often gets put aside.
XANDER:
Ah...
EVVIE:
Doesn't that look incredible?
TIFFANY:
God, that's a lot.
We've now learned
to work together.
And once you get a little bit
of momentum under you,
it just starts
to go the right way.
XANDER:
Wait, really?
See them? Oh, my God.
There's so many of them.
Where, where, where?
-Oh, my God.
-EVVIE: Oh, my God.
TIFFANY:
Hundreds of baby turtles.
-Look at them.
-See all these little guys
moving.
-TIFFANY: Look at them.
-EVVIE: Whoa.
-XANDER: They're so cute.
Dig deep, little guys.
-XANDER: Give 'em
Jeff motivation.
-EVVIE: Dig deep.
XANDER:
"You got to dig!"
EVVIE:
These are
the little Yase turtles.
-LIANA: So strong.
-EVVIE: Like, they're small,
but they're so strong, you know?
The Yase tribe,
everyone counted us out,
and it looked
like there was no way
for us to succeed in this game.
-Oh, it's scaring me.
Please don't hurt yourself.
-He's taking such a bad route.
-I don't like it.
-LIANA: No, no,
I don't like it, either.
EVVIE:
We just flopped our way
through every hurdle
that's come our way.
We've just never given up
and keep trying.
And those little turtles,
they were doing the same thing.
Come on, little guy. Get out
of the hole. You can do it.
-Yes, that way. Good job.
-Yay!
-(cheering)
-TIFFANY: Go, guy!
It doesn't even make sense
that a turtle that little
should be able to get
from wherever they hatched
to the ocean,
and yet they just never,
never gave up.
-Bye. Good luck.
-Bye.
And that's the story
of the Yase tribe, you know?
People counted us out,
but we're not out.
-TIFFANY: Oh, he's so cute.
-XANDER: Bye, little guy.
♪ ♪
GENIE:
Oh, God.
-Nathan! What are you doing?
-SHAN: Oh, my God.
JD:
That's not human, dude.
-Wow.
-SHAN: That's incredible.
JD:
Oh, my God, Nathan.
You're 25 feet high.
I love superheroes.
I'm a huge comic book fan.
And our local Fijian Nathan,
this dude just, like...
(makes whooshing noise)
Like Spider-Man or something.
That dude is superhuman.
What?
Bula.
-Bula!
-(laughs)
GENIE:
He flipped upside down.
It was like Cirque du Soleil
and the best stripper
you've ever seen.
-Oh, ho-ho-ho.
-JD: That's it.
We were floored.
-(gasps)
-What?
And you're gonna use the milk
of the coconut, the brown one.
-The brown one. Okay.
-For the fish. Oh, delicious.
SHAN:
And how do we catch these fish?
It's going for the low tide.
SHAN:
He is one with nature.
This man is, like,
one with the island.
He knows this land.
He's lived it.
His parents have lived it.
His grandparents have lived it.
I'm gonna show you how to,
like, in Fijian way,
we do, like, uh, kokoda.
GENIE:
All right, y'all, we're about
to eat three big old fish.
SHAN:
He had so much wisdom,
and I don't know that
Survivor's ever been so Survivor
until season 41.
We have to work very hard
for everything.
Best reward to win, hands down.
This is Gucci right here,
like, this is a pot of gold.
We struck gold with Nathan.
My body says, "Yes."
My body's like,
"Thank you, Nathan."
JD:
Beyond good.
RICARD:
The fish was amazing.
I'm happy, and what's funny is,
24 hours earlier,
I was being yelled at
by Genie.
Take care of my own fire,
and she's not
making us nothing anymore.
And so now I think,
"Oh, we don't need her."
Because we got to meet Nathan,
we don't feel discouraged
in our surroundings anymore.
SHAN:
Thank you.
-JD: Thank you.
-SHAN: God bless you.
JD:
Bye, Nathan.
You might be the coolest man
I've ever met in my life.
(Genie laughs)
♪ ♪
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. No, for sure. No, I'm...
ERIKA:
The challenge proved
that Luvu is not
an unbeatable tribe.
And I felt so bad for Heather.
The poor thing
struggled so much,
but to be honest,
I'm okay with losing.
To be here on day eight,
and to not have voted, like,
I don't even have a torch yet.
Part of me feels restless.
I know that I'm small,
that I'm a sweet person,
but I am actually
a lion dressed like a lamb.
As much as I wanted to keep
this, like, innocent act up,
like, I'm so ready to take off
my little lamb costume
and show my teeth a bit more.
Let's turn things up a notch
and get some people out.
♪ ♪
Sydney cannot
keep her emotions cool.
She's very reactive and she's,
like, very impulsive.
And I'm realizing,
like, that behavior
is what's going to sink
the ship as we move forward.
Seeing Sydney react
to not being able to make fire.
-Yeah.
-It, like, told me a lot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This girl is, like,
very emotional,
and she gets a bit nasty.
Yeah. You think?
I've always been
a little apprehensive of Erika.
Somebody who's that quiet all
the time is a little bit sus.
And I know
she's a really smart girl.
Her Survivor IQ is high
even though she tries
to make it seem like it's low.
-Yeah, I would do it. Yeah. Shh.
-Okay.
We have to keep this,
like, airtight,
because if, like,
anything gets to Sydney,
-then, like, you know how,
you know how she reacts.
-Yeah. Yeah, right.
If we take a shot and we miss,
-it's gonna be a mess.
-We can't. Yeah.
-We have to be able to get it.
-It's gonna be a mess.
The thing is,
I definitely trust Sydney
much more than I trust Erika.
Erika is sneaky, sneaky, sneaky.
Yeah. Yeah.
DESHAWN:
So I want to
just cut the head off the snake
before it gets too much
of a problem.
I don't want to give her
that opportunity
to play the slow beginning game
and then emerge
at the end and-and take me out.
Oh.
SYDNEY: It makes sense to hear
that Erika said my name.
I am like the threat
of threats.
Like, I'm savvy as hell.
I'm good looking.
I'm a physical threat.
Exactly.
SYDNEY:
Wow. Like, what is it about me?
I think they just hate me.
They love to hate me.
They hate me
'cause they ain't me.
(birds singing)
-Oh, no worries.
-(laughs)
Her thing is,
she wants to take out Sydney.
DESHAWN:
Yeah.
She is definitely going
to kill us, uh, come merge.
DESHAWN: I have this master plan
to get rid of Erika,
and she has zero idea
that she's going to be the vote
if we lose the challenge today.
Is it bad if we lose?
-Yes.
-Why?
Just think about it long-term.
We can win, and that's great.
We go into a merge
with Luvu six.
They're picking us off
one by one
'cause that's the easy vote.
We need to take control
of something, bro.
And if we don't make this move
now, we could be screwed,
but...
just throwing it out there.
DANNY:
Deshawn really, really wants
to throw the challenge
and get Erika out,
which makes sense to me, but
as a professional athlete,
this would be a sin.
But I want to compete
and I want to win.
Throwing the challenge--
that goes
against everything
that I've ever worked for.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yes.
-First things first.
I got to take back the idols.
-Thank you, Deshawn.
-Yes, sir.
-Thanks, Tiffany.
-You're welcome.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to race
through the water,
collecting three bags of logs
along the way.
You're going to then push
those logs through a tunnel,
releasing a key
at the other end.
You will use the key to release
three rings and attempt
to land those three rings
on a series of targets.
First two tribes
to finish win immunity,
will live to see day ten.
Losers-- Tribal Council
where somebody goes home,
and I'll take your flint.
Luvu, you have two extra people.
Who are you going to sit out?
Erika and Naseer sat out the
last one. They must participate.
-We'll do it.
-Not like pushing...
-Sydney and Heather,
take a spot
on the sit-out bench.
Everybody else,
get a minute to strategize,
and we'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready.
Go.
You got to move as a group.
You're getting
to that first bag of logs.
You got to untie them,
carry them
and move on to the next bag.
Xander crawling up quickly
for Yase.
You've got to stay together
as a group.
Ua has their bag.
They're in the water moving on.
-Luvu has their first bag.
-SYDNEY: Come on, Luvu.
PROBST:
Yase has their first bag.
-Go!
-PROBST: Luvu struggling
-to get to their second bag.
-DESHAWN: Go.
PROBST:
Ua moving together nicely.
They're to their bag.
Yase struggling in the water.
You've got
to get to your second station.
-Come on. Go, go, go.
-Go, go.
-Luvu has their second bag.
Ua has their second bag.
It is Ua and Luvu
side-by-side.
Yase in last place, a spot
they are way too familiar with
this season.
Erika back up for Luvu,
Shan back up for Ua.
Yase finally
has their second bag.
-SYDNEY: Good job, Erika!
-Come. Come on.
PROBST:
Luvu has their third bag.
-They're heading in.
-SYDNEY: Good job, Luvu!
PROBST:
Ua has their third bag!
DANNY:
So, me and Deshawn-- we decide
that we're going
to throw the challenge.
And I look back,
and I see Deshawn,
and he's moving slow
as snail's pace.
DESHAWN:
I am trying my hardest
to throw this challenge. Like,
I'm walking in the water.
Like, I'm, like,
-doggy-paddling.
-Go! Go!
DESHAWN:
Naseer is like, "Go!
Go!" And I'm like,
"Bro, I don't want
to go right now."
Go!
PROBST:
Day nine taking its toll.
-Nothing is easy on Survivor.
-(whooping)
Come on, Deshawn!
(grunts)
PROBST:
Yase finally has
their third bag.
Yeah.
-PROBST: Very heavy bags.
-Let's go.
-SYDNEY: Yes!
-Now you've got
to untie all the logs.
-Come on! Go!
-DESHAWN: So, I'm just trying
to, like, swim as slow
as possible, and I look back,
and freaking yellow
are still in the water.
And I'm just like, "Dude,
what can you guys do right?"
Like,
even when I'm trying
to throw the challenge,
you guys still can't win.
PROBST:
Evvie's swimming the wrong way.
"A" for effort.
Maybe a B-minus for direction.
DESHAWN:
So I get to the knots, right,
and this is like
the point where
I'm just desperate.
And I just start retying knots.
Like, literally, I'm just
sitting there tying, tying,
tying. I might have retied,
like, three or four
or more knots.
And I'm just like, "Damn.
I hope they don't see me."
-PROBST: Ua now working.
-Get to the box.
Here comes Yase.
Keep digging, Yase.
(grunting)
Luvu still working
on their logs,
like they're on a picnic,
taking a lot of time.
You got
to get all those logs out
before you can start pushing.
-All right, assembly line,
let's go.
-Luvu,
you're good.
Start the assembly line.
-Got you.
-One, two, three, go!
That's how you do it.
One, two, three. Go!
Got to get all these pieces
of wood out of this tunnel.
-Then you grab the key.
-One, two, three. Go!
Here comes Ricard.
-Let's go, Ua!
-SYDNEY: Come on!
Yase still in this.
You've been in last before.
You know what it's like,
and you know how to pull it out.
One, two, three! Go!
-(whooping)
-One, two, three. Go!
-Luvu getting closer
and closer to the end.
-Go!
-DANNY: I'm, like,
trying my hardest
-not to push these blocks.
-One, two, three. Go!
But Naseer is an animal
at this point.
He's just, "One, two."
(in slow motion):
Go!
(Danny laughs)
Like, goodness.
-One, two. Go!
-That's it, Luvu.
-You're good.
-SYDNEY: Yeah, you're good.
PROBST:
Ua getting closer but starting
to slow down,
and that's opening
the door for Yase to catch up.
You got it. Go, go, go.
PROBST:
It's now Xander
using his chest
to push 'em through.
Now Luvu is looking for a key.
There is one key
in one of those pieces of wood.
-There's blocks behind...
-DESHAWN: I'm hoping and praying
that I'll find this freaking key
in this block,
'cause I'm gonna toss this block
so far away.
-Come on.
-You got it?
-PROBST: They've got the key.
-Go, I got it.
Freaking Erika finds the key.
PROBST:
Unlock the rings.
-Ua-- one more log will do it.
-(grunts)
You're good, Ua.
One more for Yase.
-You're good, Yase. Let's go.
-DANNY: Go. Come on.
SYDNEY:
Let's go, Deshawn!
DESHAWN:
So I step up and do some rings.
I'm like, "Yes,
this is my prime opportunity
to freaking throw
the challenge."
-XANDER: Got it.
-TIFFANY: You got it.
PROBST:
Xander now has the key.
-You got it.
-Look at this.
Yase quickly found their key.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Here comes Shan.
She's got her key for Ua.
-You got it...
-Can I go?
PROBST:
Tiffany's up.
And Tiffany lands the first one.
-It is Yase now in the lead.
-Yes!
-Yeah.
-PROBST: JD sticks one for Ua.
Deshawn for Luvu.
-Just short.
-Come on, Liana.
-Gonna be Liana.
-Yes!
-Liana with her first toss.
-Yes, Liana.
Yase's one ring away
from winning this.
You got it, Liana,
just like you did
-the first time.
-Just short.
JD trying to tie it up.
-Just misses.
-GENIE: Come on, JD!
DANNY: Let me know
if you want to switch.
-Ah. Hold on.
-PROBST: Deshawn short again.
Going to take more than that.
PROBST:
Here comes Naseer.
DESHAWN:
So I'm trying to drag that part.
That didn't last long
because Naseer run up
at the freaking ring toss.
Like, really?
Of course Naseer would do this.
-Yes!
-Oh!
-PROBST:
Naseer snags one for Luvu.
-Ah! Go, Naseer!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
-PROBST: Luvu has one now.
-Oh!
Naseer with a second one
-for Luvu.
-Yes, Naseer, yes!
Luvu with two,
Yase with two.
-Naseer could win this.
-So close.
Just a little bit harder.
-Yes.
-PROBST: Naseer just got hot
and could win it
for Luvu right here.
-Oh!
-Just short.
-Xander could win it.
-DANNY: Take your time.
Take your time.
-There you go.
-Yes!
Xander does it for Yase!
We're looking for one more.
-Oh, my goodness.
-Yes!
It is now Ua and Luvu.
-Ua with one, Luvu with two.
-Ah.
Come on.
JD with his second.
We are tied. Here it is.
JD versus Naseer.
-On and off again.
-That was in and out.
-It's got to stick. JD.
On and off.
Naseer. On and off.
-Unbelievable.
-Don't look at it.
-Both guys so close.
Aah!
-(cheering)
-Naseer wins it for Luvu!
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Sending Ua
-to Tribal Council.
-I'm sorry, guys.
Sorry, guys.
DESHAWN: The win very much felt
like a loss to me.
Naseer was just the man
at that challenge.
He-he had his moment.
And I'm proud of him
because Naseer is a good guy.
He deserves the moment.
I just didn't want that moment
to be at that challenge.
Yase, congratulations.
-(whooping)
-Nice to have the big idol.
Yeah.
No Tribal, nobody going home.
Luvu, no Tribal Council,
tribe stays tight
-at six.
-Thanks, Jeff.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Yase, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Enjoy the night off.
Ua, head back to camp.
I'm gonna keep your flint.
See you tonight at Tribal.
SHAN:
Genie might be the one
on the outside,
but JD wants
to be the superstar.
He's so concerned about looking
like Allen Iverson. He's like,
"Money!" and it doesn't land.
We're like,
"There's no money there.
"You should have
shouted out 'Tribal!'
Because that's where
we ended up."
♪ ♪
(birds singing,
insect buzzing)
It's me, dude.
It's got to be me.
-I mean, the original...
-They blindsided me.
They didn't want to tell me
what was going on.
Shan was in on it.
Ricard is a mastermind.
This is what I'm thinking.
-I'm gonna throw that die.
-Yeah.
And if you can just
write down "Ricard."
The second go-to name
would be him.
That's-that's the only
game plan I have.
Are you 100% rolling your die?
I think so.
I don't want a souvenir.
I'm gonna play that.
It's like a Hail Mary.
I'm thinking about playing
the Shot in the Dark.
However, if you roll the die,
you cannot even vote.
So that is very risky.
I'm terrified tonight.
I would probably
be crying right now
if I didn't already lose
all of my liquids through sweat.
-I'm up against the wall.
-Yeah, I know.
I feel like
I'm in the same spot.
It could be either of us who...
-And I don't want
to roll my die, you know?
-Yeah.
-You know...
-That's a balls-to-the-wall
move.
I'm lying to Genie.
I had to convince her that
I'm so dedicated to her
so she doesn't roll her die.
If she rolls her die
and gets safety,
I could be going home.
My mindset is,
"Genie, Genie,
Genie, Genie, Genie.
I have to get rid of Genie."
I trust you, and
I trust Shan,
'cause we're a three.
But, like, Genie wants me
to put a vote on you.
I'm not doing that.
That's freaking stupid.
I need you and Shan.
Look at Miss Sneaky Genie.
(laughs)
-GENIE: That's the thing.
-Ricard?
-Yeah.
-No, Genie. I think we're...
-No?
-Okay.
I think you can trust...
Ricard more
than you could trust JD.
Bottom line-- Ricard's been
my number one since day one.
Now Genie wants to vote Ricard,
so now my work is
having her think
that JD is the target
to convince Genie not
to roll her dice
'cause we're voting out Genie.
I'm just afraid
I'm gonna get blindsided.
But all I can give you
is my word.
-Okay.
-And I'm-I'm trusting Ricard,
too.
-All right.
-But JD is not trustworthy.
He's not stable.
I'm also
deeply concerned that if Genie
doesn't feel comfortable,
Genie could team up with JD
because JD has the extra vote.
Then we could go to a tie,
or a blindside could
potentially be pulled off.
I've got to... I've got
to figure that out.
I've got to address that.
I'm gonna act paranoid.
I'm gonna say to him, "JD,
"I feel like
you're working with Genie.
"The only way I'm willing
to work with you
"is if you give me
your advantage
"and we vote Genie
because I feel like
you're gonna use that
against me with Genie."
What I'm trying
to get is that advantage.
It wouldn't matter if you had
that vote. It wouldn't matter.
I think you're working
a blindside with Genie on me.
Why?
I don't know.
I just get that feeling.
I promise you, that's not
what hap... what's happening.
For someone who plays so well,
plays so well--
she's a very good player--
she freaks out so easily.
-I don't... I...
-JR: Her name has not even
been in the mix.
You're not gonna play me, right?
I'm not playing you, Shan.
Shan,
you're getting a little, like...
You're not voting me tonight
that you're not gonna...
-I'm not.
-So you're not gonna
use your advantage?
-That'd be dumb if I used it.
-So can you leave it here?
I'm not... Like, what if
something pops off at Tribal,
-and I need to use it?
-I'm not... I'm not not...
I'm not... I'm taking you with
me, though, unless you're not
-taking me.
-I am.
So then why... so then...
You should always bring your
advantages to Tribal, though.
I don't want to be that dummy
who leaves their advantage
back at camp.
I came to contribute
to the evolution of the game,
not become one of the dummies
who ruins it.
You can get it tomorrow,
'cause we'll all still be here.
All I'm asking is
for a token of trust.
If that... if that will make you
trust me, I'll do it.
SHAN:
You know, again, like,
when I'm up to something
that I probably
shouldn't be doing,
I hum this song.
(humming)
JD:
You can kind of see in her eyes
that she's genuine
about actually thinking that
I'm gonna blindside her,
and me giving her that vote
showed her, "I trust you.
I'm giving you this."
Thank you...
for trusting me, trusting you.
JD:
I've done all
I can do to convince her
I'm with her,
and once I get that extra vote
back, it's not going anywhere.
I promise. This time for real.
(humming)
SHAN:
Number one-- how the heck
did that just happen?
Number two-- I feel like I have
some power in my pocket
that I didn't actually have
to go off to an island to get.
Number three-- I'm thinking,
"Oh, my goodness,
what if I just
"keep the extra vote
for myself and
vote out JD?"
It's in my back pocket.
That would be a big move to get
his extra vote for good.
I might never get
this opportunity again, but JD
has become family to me.
He's like a little brother,
and I love him.
There we go.
Ah, good job.
And I don't want
to be a villain,
but I-I do want
to be an assassin.
SHAN: With Genie,
you know, she's hurt.
We blindsided her with Brad.
I just feel
she doesn't really trust me.
So this is a hard vote. I feel
like tonight I'm holding
both of their lives in my hand.
And so, I go to my song
in my head.
(humming)
(humming continues)
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Wow, Genie.
Your face, your body language.
I'm exhausted. I... (sighs)
I'm-I'm playing from the bottom.
It's not a good day for me.
PROBST:
This is clearly a turning point
for this tribe.
I can feel it. I felt it
at the challenge when you lost.
So, Ricard, help the audience
understand what these moments
really feel like.
It's so weird,
going from audience member
to now being in this seat.
You know, you want
to pick off the people
that you hate when you're
watching them on the screen.
But with every vote out,
it genuinely hurts our feelings.
SHAN:
Yeah, we're bonding so that
we can survive the jungle.
Like, we're close,
we're farting on each other,
we're burping on each other,
and everybody does it.
-I don't care.
-I didn't do that.
SHAN:
Everybody lets a little gas go
at night.
-I hear it, okay, so...
-(laughing)
You know, and then it just
juxtaposes the reality of, like,
your life ends here, like,
this is the end of the road.
-So it's hard.
-PROBST: And, JD,
when you're watching at home,
it's easy.
You're sitting on your sofa,
bag of chips. You're like,
"I'd cut him, no problem.
Wouldn't have any emotion
at all."
Then you get out here--
to Shan's point-- not so easy.
JD:
Yeah. On the other hand,
leaning more on strategy,
what the viewer has
-that we don't all have
is information.
-There you go.
They know everything that's
going on-- who's lying to who--
and that's why I'm sitting
on the couch, being like,
"Malcolm,
what are you doing, bro?
-Like, they're coming for you."
-(Shan laughs)
PROBST:
So, Genie,
let's get back to you.
You walk in,
and the first thing you say is,
"I'm playing from the bottom."
I mean, the last Tribal, I was
just as blindsided as-as Brad.
So, you know you're on
the bottom of the tribe.
Because you didn't have
the information.
I didn't have the information,
and nobody wanted
to give it to me.
And-and... and I was
really thinking
we were gonna win
that immunity challenge
because we got a lot
of energy from that.
The fish and-and all these
things that we were taught
by the awesome Nathan. You know,
oh, my God, that guy is amazing.
And then this happens,
and now I'm scrambling.
I mean,
people are making me promises,
but how am I supposed
to really believe them?
-You know what I mean? Like...
-It's tough.
-Uh, yeah, it's freaking tough.
-So, Ricard,
with four people,
it's two-two or three-one.
And two-two would mean
that there are two pairs
that are locked in.
-Is that a possibility?
-I think it is a possibility.
I hope that's not the case.
I believe
that's not the case,
but anything is possible.
I don't believe it, Jeff.
It's gonna be three-one on me.
I think they're just trying
to appease me right now
or whatever, so I don't roll
this Shot in the Dark.
It's another new element
to the game
-that can cause a lot of havoc.
-Absolutely. Exactly.
This is the only thing I have
that-that I feel like I can take
-in my own hands.
-I respect that play.
Just keep in mind, when you use
your Shot in the Dark,
you lose your vote,
and that potentially
could be messing up somebody
who is willing
to work with you.
Just make sure
we all do what we said
we were going to do.
PROBST:
Wow.
That is a complicated statement
JD just said.
Does that change how you feel,
or would you reveal it
if it did?
I'll probably make that decision
when I'm in there.
JD, I can feel the tension.
-Yeah.
-Even though
I've seen you at Tribal
-enough, tonight is different.
-JD: Yeah.
I felt like
I had to do scrambling,
and I think Ricard felt like
he had to do some scrambling.
My name's been written down.
-Genie.
-Yeah, my name's been
written down, Genie.
You know, so... just as much
as I don't want to go home,
these three people don't want
-to go home, either.
-Nobody wants to go home.
So, Shan, what's the worst part
of going home?
Not getting to the place
in the game where you wanted to.
You know, as much
as we're all visualizing
sitting in the final three,
grabbing that check
from you, um,
17 people are just not going
to get that.
17 people are going
to be disappointed.
If you get there,
you've killed a lot of dreams,
and if you don't,
then you've killed your own.
JD:
And the worst part of going home
for me would be this idea
that I built up in my head,
growing up, that I was going to
be some amazing Survivor player.
And I'll-I'll be honest.
I have not played the game
that I imagined myself playing.
I checked off a lot of boxes,
but the list is so long,
there's so many boxes
that I still want to check.
And, JD, regardless, how long
you last, you don't really
know what this journey
is going to be about
-until you get some perspective.
-Yeah.
I'm just not ready
for the perspective yet.
I'm not ready
to see the perspective.
I need to... I need
to do some more stuff out here.
Then I'll reflect.
In other words, "Probst,
enough with the therapy."
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-PROBST: So, Genie,
we started with you.
Let's end with you.
If it's you tonight,
what will you miss?
I mean, I'm going to miss
everything about this, but...
I have to say, I think
I'm actually gonna...
I'm gonna miss these guys.
Oh, Genie.
Does the emotion surprise you?
GENIE:
I mean, not really.
It's just, you know, you...
We're just... we're just beaten
down to, like, our bare bones
and just the emotions.
It just comes out
at any time, so...
I mean,
a lot of it is exhaustion,
and a lot of it is because
I truly believe we bonded.
This game is hard, and we...
-It's not supposed to be easy.
-Oh.
'Cause nothing good ever is.
PROBST:
And with that,
it is time to vote.
Ricard, you're up.
♪ ♪
(whispers):
Sorry.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or hidden immunity idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time
to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
(sighs)
First vote-- Genie.
JD. We're tied.
One vote-- Genie, one vote-- JD.
JD. Two votes-- JD.
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor 41-- JD.
That's three. You need
to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
-I love you, JD.
-I love you.
-All right.
-It's all love.
♪ ♪
All right, Jeff.
-JD.
-Yeah.
The tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
-You rock.
-Go, JD.
(sighs)
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
GENIE: Right now,
at this moment, we got to fend
for ourselves, so sure enough,
I looked there, and I was like,
"What?!"
DANNY:
I'm absolutely nervous
that the women
will have more numbers than us.
Whatever.
TIFFANY:
With Xander-- I'm on Xan.
They played me, man.
Like, good on them. Like, damn.
That was a good blindside.
Shan got my extra vote,
but I was trying to play ballsy.
I was trying to play big.
I was trying to play
to win the game.
And to be out of the game
that I've dreamt of playing
my entire life sucks.
It sucks so bad. (grunts)
At least my hair looks cool.
(roars)