(thunder rumbling)
HAI:
I wish that Rocks was here
to make fire.
(Omar laughs)
HAI: We got split up
at today's challenge
into two teams, but our Tribal
went exactly the way
that I wanted it to again,
so I am extremely happy
that I got my main target out,
which was Rocksroy.
Yeah.
Please have sun tomorrow.
Please, please, please.
But I knew my biggest obstacle
in getting the Rocksroy vote
executed
was with getting
Mike's blessing.
Yeah.
It's all right.
We all voted for him.
He can't just get mad at you.
However,
thankfully, Mike being
a great ally, listened to me.
So I'm so happy
that Mike let me be the driver
for this one vote.
Mike, I know how hard
that was for you, so thank you.
MIKE:
I had no plans
on voting Rocksroy out.
I gave him my word,
and my word is my bond.
But Hai was so definitive that
everybody wanted Rocksroy out
because of his abrasiveness,
so, I voted Rocksroy.
It was unanimous.
But I was extremely upset
with myself
that I was letting Hai
play my game.
Listen.
-OMAR: Um...
-You got to be honest with me.
I-I was...
I didn't know it was coming.
I don't like if you felt, um,
-pressure to do that.
-Well...
OMAR: Mike says,
"I just want to know,
are you okay
with how everything transpired?"
And I'm like, "Hmm. Funny
you say that, Mr. Mikey boy.
"I am fine
with the way it transpired,
"'cause that's what I wanted,
but I do want you to be
a little bit leery of Mr. Hai."
-Yeah.
-You know, I...
But you're a good dude, and
don't worry about that. But...
-It's really bothering me.
-But-but what really bothers me
-is that you're bothered
by how it went down.
-Yeah.
OMAR:
Mikey no likey.
That lets me know that maybe
he's starting to not like how
Hai is running things.
Yeah.
So, over the next few days,
my plan is going to be
to bring Mike closer to me
and sever his relationship
with Hai, and
Hai has given me
enough ammunition to do that.
-Hello.
-Hey.
What's up, guys?
Don't mind if I come in?
-Yeah, come on, dude.
-Tell me news.
Who's here?
Good job, buddy.
DREA:
Tribal-- it was like
a very emotional thing
that has just happened,
and I ended up playing my idol,
and Maryanne played her idol.
But I'm still on Survivor, and
I have my Knowledge as Power,
I have my extra vote, so,
as long as I still have a leg
in the game,
I'm gonna play it
as hard as I can.
OMAR:
Yeah.
-And I was like, "Why?"
-He's so...
"Why would you do that?
Because if Drea plays her idol,
then Maryanne's out."
I'm, "But we can't lose
Maryanne."
-You need to a backup plan.
-He so doesn't understand
(bleep).
No, and he, like,
wouldn't listen to me.
It's like it was his plan
or no plan.
Jonathan was willing
to put Maryanne on the line.
He's not great at strategy.
I'm slowly not able
to rely on him
as much as I thought I was
in the beginning.
And if we seem like a pair,
and he's poor at strategy,
it looks like I'm in on that
poor strategy, which I'm not.
So, not
my favorite alliance member
to have anymore at this point.
LINDSAY:
So traditionally,
when two idols are played,
at least one is gonna
come back in,
and I think today's kind of
a good day to look
because everyone's cold
and miserable,
and like, "Oh, I'm looking
for firewood. Blah-de-blah."
It would be awesome
to have an idol.
That just helps me stay
a little bit further
in the game if I can.
Can't rely
on winning everything.
I haven't won anything yet.
So, I'm trying
to just look at places
that seem obvious,
like in roots and seeing
if I can see anything
in little crevices of trees.
And... I found
basically nothing.
I hope I find it at some poit
before somebody else does.
MARYANNE:
Oh, my gosh.
-We're having
a fire-making competition.
-Great.
What are you looking for, Hai?
I'll find it for you.
MARYANNE:
I'll see if I can get firewood.
-Like, you know, the-the...
the water well.
-Yeah.
MARYANNE: We're all looking
for dry firewood.
And so, I'm looking
at the trees,
looking for branches
to pick off.
Here we go. This is good.
And I see this tree,
like, right at the corner.
And I'm like,
"Oh, my goodness."
Oh, my gosh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You did not just...
No, no, no, no.
(gasps)
It's a freaking immunity idol.
Yes.
I just found
my second immunity idol, baby!
No. I was just trying to...
Oh, my gosh.
And do you see?
There is no stipulation,
no secret code,
no bunny rabbits or mailboxes.
Oh, my goodness. (gasps)
So this puts me in such a great
position. Because I have
an extra vote,
I now have this idol...
When playing my idol
at the previous Tribal,
I was so frustrated
'cause I knew that I was safe.
Being able to find an idol
literally the next day shows me
that the way that I'm playing
this game is both right
in the strategic sense,
and also in the moral sense.
Come on in.
Day 18.
Oh, man.
We're loving Survivor 42.
(thunder rumbling)
All right, how we doing?
Day 18.
I know it's not easy, but
are you feeling
that you're nearing the end,
that you can do this?
Playing the game, Jeff.
We're playing the game.
It's been a rough night,
but we're playing Survivor,
so it's all good.
Shall we get
to today's reward challenge?
-Yeah.
-PROBST: All right.
Well, you have had
some challenges this season
that have pushed you
to your limits.
Today is not one of those days.
Today's fun.
Yay!
PROBST:
All you have
to do today is maneuver
a sandbag
through a series of obstacles
and land it on a target.
First to finish wins the reward.
Want to know
-what you're playing for?
-Yeah.
-Hot pizza.
-Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
And cold beer,
and you will be warm
and protected
from the rain 'cause
you're going to the sanctuary...
-Oh.
-OMAR: Oh.
-PROBST: ...where you will have
blankets and pillows 'cause
-you're spending the night.
-OMAR: Oh, my gosh.
-DREA: Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Your first shot
at a truly decent night's sleep
as you head
through these last eight days
of Survivor 42.
-Worth playing for?
-Yes.
-OMAR: Yes.
PROBST:
All right, we're gonna draw
for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
Hot pizza, cold beer
at the sanctuary.
Day 18, Survivor 42.
The storm is coming.
Survivors ready.
(groaning)
Go!
First, you got to get to this
first over-under obstacle.
It's Jonathan and Lindsay.
Get up and over.
-(Jonathan grunts)
-Then go down.
Then come back up.
Here comes Hai, here comes Drea.
Jonathan in the early lead.
Got to untie your sandbags now.
It's a bunch
of little pesky knots.
-Maryanne's over. Omar's over.
-(grunting)
-(thunder rumbling)
-Keep digging, Romeo.
Let's go, Mike.
Fighting through it right now.
♪ ♪
Jonathan is through first.
One of the most miserable days
we've had out here.
You want the sanctuary tonight.
Pillows and blankets,
nice and warm.
Jonathan is first
over the balance beam.
Got to get to the platform.
You can start tossing sandbags.
-(thunder rumbling)
-Hai is on the balance beam.
Lindsay now on the balance beam.
Lindsay's across the beam.
Hai is across the beam.
It's now Jonathan tossing
his sandbag, and we've got
three people on the sandbags.
Everybody else working.
Drea's across.
You can start tossing sandbags.
♪ ♪
Hai on and off.
Lindsay just misses.
Somebody's gonna stick this, and
it's going to be over quickly.
-Oh!
-On and off for Jonathan.
Lots of people very close.
You got to get it to stick.
♪ ♪
-(screaming)
-Lindsay drops it!
-Lindsay wins reward.
-(grunting)
-Wow.
-Out of nowhere.
-Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Lindsay, come on over.
(whooping)
-Hey. Yeah, Lin!
-Well done.
-Thanks.
PROBST:
All right, so tonight,
boat's going to pick you up
from camp,
take you to the sanctuary.
Hot pizza, cold beer, blankets,
pillows, shelter from the rain,
and you will sleep there.
Choose one person to join you.
And before you choose,
walk me through.
Look at everybody right now.
-Everybody wants it.
-(thunderclap)
How do you make
this kind of a decision?
LINDSAY:
I mean, I had
to think about the people
who haven't gotten
a reward yet before.
And Omar's been with me
since day one,
and he hasn't gotten one reward,
so I have to take Omar.
-Yeah!
-Oh, thank you, Lindsay.
Yeah, bring one more.
Come on over.
PROBST: Didn't hesitate.
-Mike, you look surprised.
-He only had a PB and J.
And I've been talking
about splitting a pizza
with this man since I met him.
Thank you so much.
PROBST:
Okay, all right,
here's what's going to happen.
Lindsay, Omar, Mike, tonight,
boat's going to pick you up,
bring you to the sanctuary.
Maryanne, Romeo, Drea,
Hai, Jonathan,
got nothing for you.
Everybody,
grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Thank you.
LINDSAY: This is just
an awesome, badass reward
that I won, and
couldn't have come
at a better timing
'cause the weather couldn't
have been more miserable.
And I got to pick two people
that I really want
to discuss strategy with
and get close with, so it was
like a win-win.
MARYANNE: When you say
you want to play Survivor,
you're like, "Man, I want
to feel that feeling when
you get close to the end
and it starts to get hard."
But then you get to that place.
Like, we're at day 18.
The rain is miserable.
Literally, like,
I'm shivering so much
that, like,
it hurts to walk
because I just kept on tensig
my leg muscles. Like, that's
the type of pain that we're in.
ROMEO: This doesn't translate
when you're watching at home.
Like, "Oh,
it's just a little bit
of rain." Well, you try
sitting in wet clothes for 24
hours, starving, missing home.
That wind that comes when
you're wet, and it hits you like
a thousand knives.
I would kill
for a warm bed tonight.
LINDSAY:
Yeah.
ROMEO:
But Lindsay,
Mike and Omar get
to go on that reward
and sleep in a nice, warm bed
with pizza and beer.
And here we are, just dying.
HAI:
We had to fix the shelter.
We were all wet and cold,
but being out here
has taken me back to my roots.
I didn't have an easy childhood,
and as a result,
I've seen what it's like
to have nothing.
HAI:
I've seen what it's like
to be hungry and to be poor.
So, for me, I know
how much worse things can be.
HAI:
My family immigrated here
when I was three years old
as refugees from Vietnam.
Watching my parents sacrifice
everything that they have
to give me a better life
inspires me,
and I'll never forget
where I started.
(thunder cracks)
And I think being out here,
a lot of people forget there's
a finite ending for us in sight.
This misery is temporary.
We're so close
to the finish line.
That's what gets me
through another day.
But if you want to...
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
HAI:
I see Lindsay fragmenting
from Jonathan.
I had quite a little,
nice, quiet conversation
with her at the shelter
when everyone was
sitting around,
and she seems to be signaling
to me that she wants Jonathan
out next.
And guess what, Lindsay.
I'm open.
(thunder rumbling)
-OMAR: I'm so excited.
-MIKE: Look at this.
-Oh, my God. Pizza.
-(Omar gasps)
-Yeah.
-Oh, margherita.
Can I try some of that?
Margherita. Yes.
Can I please have a slice
of that?
I'm a New York,
Hoboken, Jersey kid.
We live on pizza.
I knew that I was gonna eat
until pizza was coming out
of my ears.
Oh, my God,
this pizza's so good.
WOMAN:
Hi, babe, I just want you
to know I love you,
-I miss you a lot.
-What's going on?
I wish I could be there in
person with you in Fiji, but...
-Who is this?
-I love you so much.
LINDSAY: And I start hearing,
like, voices
and mumbling, and I'm like,
"What's going on?" And then,
all of a sudden, I look up.
Oh, my God, that's me!
It's me and my dog!
Oh, my God,
these are our loved ones,
and we all just lost it.
-Oh, look.
That's me and my daughter.
-It's you!
-That's my daughter!
-Oh, my goodness!
-LINDSAY: Oh, my God!
That's my dad.
My God, that was me and
my daughter. That was Chelsea.
-(Lindsay shrieks)
-MIKE: Lindsay!
Look at you. Who's that?
-Tell me who that is!
-LINDSAY: Oh, my God!
-That's my parents.
-Look at you. Graduation.
-LINDSAY: Yeah.
High school graduation.
-MIKE: Look how cute
you were.
-Hey, Linds.
-Lindsay!
-(shrieks)
-OMAR: Oh, my gosh.
We are so proud of you.
Congratulations for making it
this far in the game. I wish
I could be there
in person with you,
but just know that we are
all there with you in spirit,
and we know
you're going to do your best.
-We love you so much.
-We love you so much,
and we miss you.
Oh, my God. They know
I made it this far.
They know you made it this far.
-This is so priceless.
-LINDSAY: This is amazing!
This is more than...
this is more than the pizza
for me, guys. I don't know.
-This is more than the pizza.
-Oh, my God.
OMAR:
It wasn't just food
for the stomach we needed.
We really needed food
for the soul, and you don't know
how much you need it
until you see it.
Oh, that's my girlfriend Sarah.
We were in Hawaii.
-MIKE: Oh. She is hot.
-LINDSAY: Ah!
-Oh, my God.
-SARAH: Hi, Omie. It's me
and Hashi. We just want to say
we miss you, and we love you,
and you're probably exhausted
at this point.
But I just wanted to tell you
I'm so, so proud of you
for even making it
onto the show.
Keep playing hard,
and we'll see you soon.
-Oh!
-Oh, my goodness.
So sweet!
Here we go, Mike.
That's me. Ches-Ches-Chelsea.
-Is that your Chelsea?
-Look at your hair.
Chelsea, yeah,
Chelsea's baptism.
-Me and Zach. Look at Zach.
-OMAR: Oh!
-LINDSAY: Oh!
That's Staci.
That's Staci, yeah.
-OMAR: Oh, there's Staci.
-LINDSAY: That's Staci?!
Hi, babe. I wish I could be
there rooting you on,
um, but unfortunately I can't.
I just want you to know
I love you,
I miss you a lot,
and I want you
to keep doing
what you're doing right now
and what you're best at,
and that's winning.
I love you.
-LINDSAY: Oh!
-Oh, my God. Thank you, guys.
-LINDSAY: You're so welcome.
-Thanks.
Thank you.
There's nothing that means
more to me than my family.
There's nothing
that means more to me.
Nothing.
-You gave me a great gift.
-Ah.
-Thank you.
-It's my pleasure.
-I'm so happy to do that.
-MIKE:
It was beautiful and, honestly,
it's-it's one
of the greatest gifts
that was ever given to me
by anybody,
and Lindsay did that for me.
(thunderclaps)
OMAR:
I'm so thankful
for this night with you two.
Honestly,
this is just so special.
MIKE:
I'm gonna be talking about this
till they put me in the ground.
Can I... can I share
-with you something?
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
I feel like the way
we got off on the game
was mostly related
to friendship.
-Yes.
-And I felt like, when it came
to the game, we weren't really
allowed to talk to each other.
-Yeah.
-Like, there was
a middle person.
-Hai. I hate it. Yeah.
-And always talking for us.
Can I tell you what his plan is
according to him to me?
-Go ahead.
-Hai came to me and said,
"Mike will do anything
I say in this game.
-He is my puppet at this game."
-(Lindsay gasps)
-Whoa.
-And so, that's why I was ever
afraid to talk bad about him
with you. Because I was like,
-"He says he has you
in his back pocket."
-MIKE: No. Listen.
I'm tired of him playing...
trying to play my game.
-Yup.
-I'm done. He's a liar.
OMAR:
Hai has never told me
that Mike was a puppet, but
hearing those words
just supercharged Mike,
and I'm like, "Mike, I would
never treat you that way."
(laughs)
You know how I know
you're telling the truth?
'Cause what you're saying
makes a lot of sense to me.
-Yeah.
-And I believe it.
OMAR:
It worked because
Mike looked me
dead in the eye, and he said,
"Your story makes sense."
And I was like,
"I know it makes sense.
You tell a good lie,
not a stupid lie."
You know what?
He thinks I'm stupid.
I'm not stupid. I'm just dumb
like a fox with him.
-Yeah.
-I listen to him.
You know
what I know about this game?
Anybody that raises a hand,
says they want
to run the show
gets their neck sliced,
and I'm letting him slice
his own neck, which he's doing.
Hai thinks
I'm totally with him,
I'm his puppet,
I'll do whatever he wants.
This is totally gameplay,
but he played me,
so this is personal
for me now, too.
I want to work with you,
so I want to tell you
that me, Hai and Drea
have an amulet
-that we can use together.
-OMAR: Oh, really?
-There's a three-parter?
-Yeah.
-MIKE: Oh, my God.
And we get an extra vote
if we collectively agree
to use it.
-Interesting.
-But if there's only
two of us left,
it is now a Steal a Vote.
And then if there's only one
of us left,
-it's a hidden immunity idol,
so they...
-Oh, my God.
There's three left?
LINDSAY:
My amulet is stronger
if Hai is gone,
but I'm conflicted
because Jonathan is
destroying my game
because he feels
like he has a lot of power,
and I don't like
being told what to do like that.
So it's the matter of
who wins immunity tomorrow.
-MIKE: Hai, he needs to go.
-He needs to go.
And he can't see it coming.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-Yeah.
-PROBST: First things first.
Boys, got to take 'em back.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Once again, individual immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna stand
on a narrow perch
while balancing
a ball on a wooden bow.
At regular intervals,
you'll move farther down,
making it more difficult.
If at any point you fall off
or your ball drops, you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where after 19 days,
somebody will be voted out
of Survivor 42.
Big stakes. We'll draw
for spots, we'll get it on.
-Let's do it.
-MIKE: Hey, let's do.
-(applause)
-(Maryanne whoops)
All right,
put your ball on your bow.
Try to find your center.
♪ ♪
All right, this challenge is on.
Out of the gate,
Hai is on the edge.
Can he get it back?
There you go. Now you've got it.
You'll stay here
a total of five minutes.
Then we'll move down
to the second section.
Mike in trouble.
Mike's gonna be first out
very quickly.
Hai struggling to stay in this.
Hai is out.
We're down to six,
but the six are looking solid.
Mike and Hai
both struggled out of the gate
to get a balance spot.
Romeo drops.
MARYANNE:
Oh, my gosh.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Jonathan now has a little
movement. He's got to recover.
Omar suddenly has movement.
Omar's out. We're down to four.
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
It is Maryanne, Lindsay,
Jonathan and Drea,
fighting for immunity
and a guaranteed spot
in the final seven.
♪ ♪
30 seconds left in this round.
Jonathan with a little movement.
Another nice adjustment.
Oh.
(breathing heavily)
PROBST:
15 seconds left in this round.
Hang in there.
Five, four,
three, two,
-one. You are all good.
You can grab your ball.
-MIKE: Great job, guys.
-Good job.
-Move down to the next section.
Ease your way into it.
♪ ♪
Here we go.
Everybody is good,
and this challenge is back on.
We're in the second section.
Shizzlesticks!
PROBST:
Maryanne drops.
It's much tougher to balance
on this beam right now.
It's a lot more narrow,
and we are now down to three.
Lindsay, Jonathan and Drea.
You'll be here ten minutes.
Jonathan with a nice recovery.
Drea calmly grabs her ball.
Drea's out, takes a seat.
We are down to two.
We have a showdown.
It is Lindsay and Jonathan.
Jonathan just gave me
the necklace back.
He would like to get it again.
Lindsay has not
had it this season.
Jonathan, a lot of movement,
but recovering nicely.
He's got a good rhythm going.
Lindsay, rock-solid.
Statue.
♪ ♪
One minute left in this round.
Jonathan's ball
is still moving a lot, though.
He's got to
get it back in control.
Lindsay very controlled.
She's just
got to keep it that way.
Another nice recovery
from Jonathan.
Little movement with Lindsay.
30 seconds left in this round.
DREA:
Oh.
Jonathan with a great recovery.
A little bit of movement
from Lindsay.
Now both balls are moving.
Lindsay trying to recover.
Jonathan trying to recover.
Five seconds left in this round.
Jonathan struggling to hang on.
Three, two, one.
You did it.
-Wow. Great job.
-(cheering, applause)
-Well done.
-MIKE: Wow.
PROBST:
Moving into
the most difficult section
of this challenge now--
the most narrow part
of the beam.
Very tough to balance here.
(laughter)
JONATHAN:
Oh, shoot, Jeff.
He has giant feet. Oh, no.
My feet are really big.
Find your footing,
and then we'll start again.
♪ ♪
All right,
we're on the most narrow part
of the beam now,
and this challenge is back on.
You will be here for 30 minutes,
if you can last that long.
Jonathan, once again familiar.
That ball is moving,
but nice recoveries.
Lindsay, a lot of movement.
♪ ♪
Jonathan in trouble,
and another nice save.
-That's gonna be it.
-OTHERS: Oh...
-(cheering)
-MIKE: Great job.
-PROBST: Jonathan out.
Lindsay wins
individual immunity.
Her second challenge win
in a row.
Lindsay, come on over.
-Yeah, Linds!
-(Maryanne whoops)
(applause)
Well done.
Thank you.
Second individual challenge win
but first individual immunity,
which means you are safe.
You are in the seven.
So, Tribal Council tonight.
After 19 difficult,
hard-earned days,
one of you, your dream
of winning Survivor 42
will fall short.
It will not be you.
You are safe.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See y'all tonight
at Tribal Council.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Nice job.
Thanks, Jeff.
Lindsay wins, and just
for Lindsay, I'm ecstatic,
but way more than that,
Hai did not win.
He thinks he's the king?
Well, guess what.
The king
will be dethroned tonight.
♪ ♪
-MIKE: Great job, Linds.
Great job.
-Congratulations.
Thank you.
-MIKE: Amazing.
-(whoops)
HAI:
I was so grateful
that Jonathan did not win
the immunity challenge,
because this guy kills it in
every challenge he competes in.
He either wins or gets second.
Hey, have I showed y'all
my monkey run?
-No.
-You want to see it?
-DREA: Yes.
HAI:
Right now, I have the numbers
to kind of sway the game
in the direction that I want to.
DREA:
Oh, my God, he does that!
(laughter)
HAI:
So for me, Jonathan being
vulnerable tonight might be
my only opportunity
to get him out of the game.
-Jonathan...
-We might not
get another chance.
Right. Exactly.
We might not get another chance
-until the end of the game.
-Okay.
I'm happy you're
on board with that,
-'cause I think
that's a solid idea.
-I am.
I am, but listen, it's gonna
bother me, but I don't have....
Mike...
Are you sure, man? Okay.
-I swear to you.
-Okay.
MIKE:
Hai's great idea is,
target Jonathan.
I'm gonna be Hai's puppet
for the next day.
I'll say, "Yes, yes, Hai.
I'm your puppet.
Whatever you want."
I want to make sure
you're comfortable.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
-I think this might be our
only opportunity.
-I know. I know.
And meanwhile,
his head's in the guillotine,
ready to be lopped off,
and rightfully so.
-Yes.
-MIKE: I'm not anybody's puppet.
I'm not playing
anybody else's game.
I'm playing my game.
I haven't lied
to anybody here yet.
Hai lied to me.
He lied to me about Rocks.
-He made me look bad to Rocks.
-Yeah.
You know how pissed off I was?
You're next.
He's playing us.
He's telling everybody
I'm his puppet,
I'll do whatever he says.
We're cutting the snake off
at its head tonight.
Does he have an idol?
-Absolutely not.
-Okay.
Hai's plan is to vote me out,
and I am very nervous.
Out of everybody here,
I would figure
that they would want
to kick me out first one
and get rid of me.
-We're cutting the head
off the snake.
-Yeah.
But Mike came and said,
"We need to get rid of Hai."
And if I can get him out first,
what a move.
I just see myself on...
Yeah.
DREA: After the last Tribal,
I realized that...
...I need to stop playing
the game with so much heart.
I'm definitely going
against Hai's alliance,
but if I get out Hai tonight,
my amulet becomes
a Steal a Vote with Lindsay.
(laughter)
So that's why he has to go.
MARYANNE:
I'm feeling as if, like,
tonight is the night
we make our move.
-I feel...
-Who do you want to get?
-Hai.
-Mm-hmm.
I agree.
Originally, I was wanting
Jonathan out,
but seems like
pretty much everybody
is on board to get Hai out,
except Hai.
-Get out.
-Yeah, so...
-Yeah.
-And Jonathan's
completely on board.
So right now
I don't want to rock the boa.
I'm gonna stick with the plan
and call it a day.
♪ ♪
All right, I'll be right back.
Hey.
HAI:
Every Tribal I go to,
I've made sure
I know who the target is,
and I can make the target
feel comfortable enough
that they do not take
a Shot in the Dark.
So I'm able to use
my fake idol play.
If I have to use it tonight,
I will.
Because I'm saying...
My strategy is tell him
that I will play my hidden
immunity idol for him,
and he will stay.
It's all B.S., but he bought it.
Really?
Uh...
-Really?
-So he's lying to me.
The worst lie I've ever heard.
-I know.
-But he is going home tonight.
And it's clear that
it's not gonna be difficult
to get Hai out at this point.
Everybody wants him out.
So, I mean, everything's
working out perfectly.
Um, but it's, like,
almost too perfect,
'cause then you start thinking,
like,
"Should I just work with Hai now
'cause nobody trusts him?"
-I love you, bud.
-Yeah.
So does that mean, in essenc,
that I should take Hai
and raise him
from his execution tonight?
Because he's loyal to me.
-The plan is still Jonathan,
obviously.
-Yeah, yeah.
-He's a big one, dude.
-Yes, he is.
He, like, wins or almost wins
every challenge.
OMAR:
Is the other option here to just
take Jonathan out of the picture
and vote Hai out next time?
Jonathan, my number one boy
from the Taku tribe,
he is still a liability
in this game.
If we don't
take Jonathan out tonight,
will he just win
every other immunity to the end?
Mm-hmm.
Romeo trusts me the most
out of everybody here,
and Maryanne's on my side, too.
I think Jonathan or Hai.
Yes.
OMAR:
And Lindsay is already primed
to not trust Jonathan.
If I had to choose right now,
I'd pick Jonathan.
-I feel like he's one immunity
away from slipping through.
-I agree.
Once again,
I'm in the middle,
and it doesn't take very much
to switch a vote right now.
The switch to Jonathan,
I actually think it might
be the better play here.
So the question is,
is it the time?
And that's what
you have to ask yourself
every time you go
to Tribal Council.
You know,
we're getting to the end.
There's only four more votes
before day 26, like...
You have to pick the right
person at the right time,
otherwise you'll be
the next person out.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, Lindsay,
let's start with you.
Back-to-back individual wins.
Reward and immunity.
With the reward,
was there any fallout,
given you could
only choose two people
and you brought Mike and Omar?
I don't think that there
was a fallout with anybody.
I tried to be as
diplomatic as possible
and kind of went with the people
who didn't have a reward yet.
PROBST:
Mike, what was the experience
like for you
in terms of strategy?
Because, in one way,
this could help me,
because I've got
two people I can talk to.
On the other side, there's
five people back in camp
that might
be plotting against us.
Well, I can't speak
to what happened at camp,
but at the reward,
honestly, no deep strategy.
I got to be honest,
we were just elated to be warm.
You know, as a firefighter,
we've been out
on sub-degree nights
where we fought fires and had
water drenched all over us.
And we're in icicles.
But I knew I was
going back to the firehouse.
I knew I'd get warm.
Here, there is no
end of the tunnel.
And that's the major difference.
-There's no place to go.
-Yeah.
And yet, Lindsay,
there is no shortage of people
who want to play this game
and have this experience.
Yeah, it's sick. We're all sick.
(laughter)
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity,
like, an amazing
life experience,
but included in that
is the worst days of your life.
You get really low lows
and then crazy highs.
It's like
everyone loves that rush
and is willing
to kind of take those risks
because you're just addicted.
All right,
so we know it's difficult,
but, Hai,
is it at all possible
that in the 42nd season
of Survivor,
three people would spend
an entire night together
and never talk about strategy?
It's possible,
but do I believe it?
Not necessarily.
This is an evolving game.
Alliances are fluid.
The perfect analogy is,
we're all long-distance runners
with blindfolds on.
-(chuckles)
-You don't know
who's in the front.
And that person
could very well trip up.
And you're just waiting for that
opportunity to overtake them.
PROBST:
So, Omar, are there times when
just keeping your same
pace is the right move?
I mean, there are times
where you have to coast.
It's very rare that you
can go from day one to day 26
and lead the whole way through
and not get your head
chopped off.
But in this game, every decision
you make is a choice.
I mean, I'm a vet
and I deal with patients.
And sometimes you don't know.
Do you take 'em to surgery
or do you manage them medically?
And the problem is, when you're
making a decision like that,
in that situation
is life and death,
or out here is life and death
in the game,
you don't know the outcome until
you've made your decision.
So you have to just go with it
and hope it was the right one
and not look back.
PROBST:
Mike, the other question is,
who do you take out
and when do you take them out?
Because there are
different reasons
you might take a player out
tonight instead of next Tribal.
MIKE:
Absolutely. It's all about
what your gut feeling is
at the time,
and I think
the players here are so good.
They're all setting
their own pace, and
they're getting ready
for their gut to tell 'em
when the right time is
to make that move.
It could be now,
it could be four days from now.
It could have been
three days ago.
We really don't know,
but we're gonna find out.
PROBST:
So, Maryanne, is there
just a constant dialogue
in your head?
"If it goes this way tonight,
then I get to seven.
"At seven,
then my move might be this,
"unless I smell something
happening tonight.
But I got to get to six
and then five."
Is that what
it sounds like inside?
The way that I see it, it's kind
of like Survivor Jenga, right?
Where it's like, "Okay,
I need to take a piece out,
"but that piece is going
to come back into play.
"But what happens if I take
a bottom piece too early?
"Will everything fall? Do I have
to then take that piece later?
"Or do I want to take that piece
"because I think someone else
wants that piece
"so I've stopped them
from having that piece
-so I can have that piece?"
-PROBST: Jonathan,
-did you track that?
-Yes.
So, Lindsay,
what is tonight's vote about?
I feel like tonight's vote
is about making
an even playing field,
trying to have everyone
feel comfortable
that they have a fair shot
to get to the end.
Wow, Jonathan. Lindsay said,
"To even the playing field."
Right. Yeah, it's something...
Uh, yeah, what she said was,
somebody is too powerful
in some way,
and, uh, she wants
to even the playing field,
so, um,
wrapping my head around
what that means... right now.
That's a great,
ambiguous answer.
It also depends on your
perspective of whatever facet
that they're the strongest in.
We have challenge beasts,
we have really
intelligent, strategic players.
We have players
that are incredibly social,
so it depends on what you value
and want in an ally,
and what you're scared of
the most in an adversary.
So there are eight
different perspectives here.
-♪ ♪
-PROBST: All right,
it is time to vote.
Lindsay, you're up.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Hai.
Jonathan.
Jonathan. Two votes-- Jonathan,
one vote-- Hai.
♪ ♪
Hai. We're tied.
Two votes-- Jonathan,
two votes-- Hai.
Hai. Three votes-- Hai.
Hai. Four votes-- Hai,
two votes-- Jonathan.
11th person voted out and
the fourth member of our jury.
Hai. That's five. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Well played, gang. (gasps)
Oh, my God, that was amazing.
(laughter)
That's how I wanted to go out.
Oh, my God. Brilliant,
-brilliant, brilliant.
-JONATHAN: Love you, Hai.
-Love you guys.
-MIKE: Love you, Hai brother.
-LINDSAY: Love you, Hai.
-Good luck to all of you.
-(Maryanne laughs)
-Wow.
Hai, the tribe has spoken.
Bye, guys.
-Bye, Hai.
-Bye.
HAI:
Wow.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Boom, boom, boom,
like dominoes.
Everybody's on board.
Screw them.
You can take either one out.
There is a twist
to today's challenge,
-and it's a dangerous one.
-DREA: I cannot. Ah!
I just got blindsided.
I honestly thought
I was going
to run away to the end
with the whole thing,
and I did not even suspect it.
It was stunning,
and I feel proud.
I don't have any regrets.
I came here to play the game,
and I played it very well
until the game outplayed me.
(roars)