"You can agree
to secretly work together
and each earn
an advantage in the process."
HAI:
I have to consider whether
or not I need to take them out,
because this thing
becomes more powerful.
OMAR:
"If both players choose to risk
their vote, then both players
lose their vote
at the next Tribal Council."
Go for the gusto,
and risk the vote.
Did I just do it?
Did I just find an idol?
It's the classic case
of the bunny rabbit
having dinner at the mailbox.
This potato has skin.
We have skin.
Are we just all potatoes?
There's such grace in the game
of soccer that it makes me cry.
MARYANNE:
Now all three idols have power.
I know that my head's
on the chopping block tonight.
I feel like my head is
also on the chopping block.
DANIEL:
Chanelle needs to go.
She did not have my back.
So why should I trust her
going forward?
CHANELLE:
Daniel has one arm.
He hasn't competed
in any challenges.
HAI:
Chanelle or Daniel.
The merge is coming up
any day now,
so tonight's Tribal Council
is monumental.
Daniel, the tribe has spoken.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
HAI:
What a vote.
LYDIA: I feel like that
was a pretty good blindside.
Chanelle, you really fought
for your life.
I am so impressed.
CHANELLE:
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness.
The saga of Chanelle
versus Daniel.
Guess who came out on top.
I did.
(laughs)
Just like I knew it.
Please.
-Chanelle came for his neck.
-(laughs)
Tribal was incredible,
but it was also very scary.
You know,
I threw a vote Mike's way--
just in case Daniel
played a Shot in the Dark.
I'm sorry that I had
to write your name down.
It was a game-time decision
where I...
I don't know what
the accomplishment was.
That's what I don't know.
Why my name?
Well, I was gonna tell you,
but you-you keep interrupting.
I just don't understand
the reason
why you would
write my name down.
So I thought that, uh,
you and Dan were teaming up...
-You think I believed
Dan's snow job?
-CHANELLE: Wait, wait. No. Wait.
MIKE:
Chanelle put my name down
for no reason other than
to save her own hide.
Expected? No. Surprise? No.
I gave you my word today.
I said, "I guarantee
you'll be here tonight,"
and you're here.
-I told you that.
-CHANELLE: I thought,
I thought you were playing
-some Jedi mind tricks.
-MIKE: No.
Let's-let's be unified...
We just, we...
MIKE:
I'm not mad.
It's gameplay. It's cool.
-Yeah. We got...
-MIKE: Listen, we're together
now. It's four of us.
-Either we stick together
or we're divided.
-CHANELLE: No, I know.
-HAI: We're strong.
-CHANELLE: No hard feelings.
-It's all fair
in love and Survivor.
-Yeah.
-Come on. G-Give me a bro hug.
-HAI: Yeah.
-Bro hug!
-I love you.
-Vati four.
MIKE:
I act like no big deal,
it's gameplay.
It's fine. No hard feelings.
Which is not true.
I will never trust Chanelle
ever again.
Please don't write
my name down again.
I-I won't. (laughs)
MIKE:
Hai and Lydia
I will take a bullet for.
Unfortunately, Chanelle,
I will step to the side,
because that's what
she did to me tonight.
Oh, my...
♪ ♪
In the produce aisle today,
we have...
limes.
Do you need help?
-ROCKSROY: No.
-Nice.
ROCKSROY: Ever since I came back
from my journey,
every time I turn around,
there's Tori bothering me,
trying to find out
what this journey entailed.
TORI:
Did you have fun at all?
-A Survivor experience?
-I did not have fun.
It is not fun.
TORI:
Rocksroy went to the summit,
and he must have found some
type of a clue or something.
Seriously...
No, I believe, I believe you.
I believe you when you say that.
I'm saying, do you know
exactly what it was?
That's what I'm confused about.
ROCKSROY:
Yeah, I know exactly
what it was.
Oh, but you're
just not telling me?
I'm not telling anybody.
I didn't tell,
I didn't tell Romeo
and I'm not telling Drea.
TORI:
Mm-hmm.
He won't give me
any information, and, like,
it doesn't make any sense
to me, and it's...
"Infuriating" is the best word
I could use to describe.
Just so you know, I wouldn't
have thought you were disloyal,
had you taken the advantage.
It's not a disloyalty.
-I don't know...
-But do you see
how that's a little sketchy?
It's clear he doesn't want
to work with me,
so I'm done with him.
Can you just respect
the fact that what I did
-was in the tribe's benefit?
-Sure.
But you don't believe me.
I'm predictable,
and it's good to have someone
that's predictable
a part of your alliance.
Tori is not predictable.
She's not someone that I want
to take far in this game.
If you don't trust me
saying that to you...
I trust
what you're saying is real.
I just want to know
the other information.
ROCKSROY:
So what do you think?
You think I have an advantage?
TORI:
But you're
leaving something out.
DREA:
It's never just, like,
calm with Tori.
Tori can't just, like, chill.
ROCKSROY:
Maybe I gave up something
so that all the four of us
-could move forward.
-Uh-huh.
ROCKSROY:
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
TORI:
I want to know what that is.
That sounds great.
ROCKSROY: But you keep asking,
and I'm not gonna tell.
DREA:
She continues to do things
that start chaos in camp.
That's a big con for me.
You know?
I would just like
to get her out,
but she always somehow slips by.
All right,
this is gonna be a fun day.
So, back in 41,
we did a historic merge twist
where one group
sent one player away,
not knowing
they would have the power to go
back in time and change history.
That player was Erika,
and she did seize the power,
and she changed history
and ended up winning the game.
But what's fun is, we shoot
our seasons back-to-back,
so the S-42 players
have not seen season 41,
which gives us the opportunity
to do the same thing,
only tweak it a bit
to see if we can change
their decision-making process.
So here are the three variables
we're gonna change.
First of all,
the food is from Applebee's.
That's big, that's emotional.
That's home.
That's hard to turn down.
Plus, we're gonna
tell them in advance
that the player
they choose to send away
will have the power
to change the game.
That's huge power.
And then finally--
here they come--
the winning five will determine:
do they want to send somebody
away and give them that power,
or do one of the five want to
give up everything they just won
and keep that power?
It's designed to test
if anybody at this point
in the game will choose power
over the instant gratification
of food
and perceived safety
in the game.
What would you do?
Here we go.
Come on in.
♪ ♪
Get your first look
at the new Vati tribe.
Daniel voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
Ooh.
PROBST:
All right,
shall we get to it?
Yeah.
You have entered
the next stage of the game...
...where tribes are no more
-and the game
has become individual.
-(gasping)
Everybody drop your Buffs.
(cheering)
LYDIA:
Oh, my God!
So, is this called the merge?
Not exactly.
(groaning)
PROBST:
In fact, you are not merged.
You will not be
officially merged
until after
the next Tribal Council.
(groaning)
Like everything else
in this game,
you are going to earn
your way into the merge.
-LINDSAY: Wow.
-PROBST: So right now,
you are without a Buff,
and you are without a tribe.
-What?
-PROBST: Let me explain
how it's gonna work.
We're gonna draw
for colored rocks
and divide into two teams.
On my go, you're gonna dig up
a massive boulder
and push it through
a series of obstacles,
collecting keys along the way.
When you get to the end, you'll
climb to the top of the tower
and use those keys to unlock
a 75-piece Survivor puzzle.
(exclaiming)
First team to finish
earns their Buff.
-MARYANNE: Wow. Oh, it's purple!
-The merge Buff.
You will also earn immunity
at the first Tribal Council,
which means
you don't have to compete
in that first
individual immunity challenge.
-You're safe.
-MARYANNE: Oh, my gosh...
PROBST:
You'll still vote,
but you can't be voted out.
You will also earn the biggest
food reward of the season.
-TORI: Come on, baby. Come on.
-PROBST: Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
It's good. It's big.
It's Applebee's.
(excited chatter)
TORI:
Oh, my God!
I love Applebee's.
-Oh, my gosh!
-Oh, my God!
We'll start
with some appetizers.
-No. (whimpering)
-Crunchy Onion Rings...
with honey barbecue sauce.
Oh...
Double Crunch Bone-In Wings.
Crispy on the outside,
tender on the inside.
Wings.
And do you want burgers?
You'll have
your choice of three burgers.
I'm a burger kind of guy.
-(exclaiming)
-MARYANNE: Oh, my goodness!
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: You got
the quesadilla burger.
-TORI: Come on.
-PROBST: You got
the whiskey bacon burger.
-LYDIA: Yes.
PROBST:
Or you got
the classic bacon burger.
MIKE:
Oh, my God.
For dessert...
-(gasps) Dessert?
-Hell yeah, dessert.
The Applebee's brownie.
-(exclaiming)
-Oh, I love brownies.
-Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: And the specialty drink
is the Shark Bowl.
-HAI: Yeah.
-Oh, baby.
-PROBST: Worth playing for?
-Yeah!
MIKE:
Hell yeah!
PROBST:
Losers, no Buff,
no immunity, no food.
-Holy crap.
-CHANELLE: Wow.
-MARYANNE: Aw.
PROBST:
And you will have to compete
in that first
individual immunity challenge
for safety
at the first Tribal Council.
(groaning)
There is one more twist.
-DREA: Obviously.
-Oh, God.
Two of you will
draw gray-colored rocks.
-MARYANNE: No.
-PROBST: You will not compete.
Your fate will be decided
by the winning five.
(groaning)
-PROBST: Shall we draw
for our teams?
-Yes.
With every hand that goes in
this bag, the game is changing.
Nothing is free
in the new era of Survivor.
All right.
Everybody, let's reveal.
♪ ♪
All right.
Everybody, let's reveal.
Oh, no.
PROBST:
If you are blue, head to blue.
If you are orange,
head to orange.
If you have gray,
you're in the middle.
You are not competing.
-Let's see our teams of five.
-(overlapping chatter)
All right, let's look
at what we have.
For orange,
it's gonna be Lydia,
Jonathan, Maryanne,
Hai and Tori.
Running for blue,
Drea, Mike, Romeo, Omar
and Chanelle.
And the two people
who drew gray--
Lindsay and Rocksroy--
you will not compete.
Your fate in this game
will be determined
by the winning five.
All right, you two are gonna
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give you
a minute to strategize,
and we will get on
to the biggest challenge
-of Survivor 42. Here we go.
-Yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
LYDIA:
Let's do it.
PROBST:
All right, here we go.
Biggest stakes of the season.
Survivors ready.
Go!
LYDIA:
Go.
PROBST:
First, you got to dig up
a massive boulder.
And I mean massive.
LYDIA:
Good.
TORI:
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
PROBST:
12 days into Survivor 42,
it's gonna take
everything you have
at this point in the game.
This boulder is heavy,
and it is deep in the sand.
PROBST: Jonathan gonna see
if they can get it out.
This would be a very fast move.
Jonathan putting
his shoulder into it.
Got a little bit of nudge,
but not enough.
-JONATHAN: Let's all try
pushing together, guys.
-Okay.
-JONATHAN:
Let's all try pushing together.
-Okay.
-One, two...
-PROBST: Orange gonna
give it a go again.
They've been moving fast.
And they've got momentum.
-Can they get it out?
-(grunting)
PROBST:
Yeah!
-Big early lead by orange!
-JONATHAN: Push fast. Push fast.
PROBST:
Now blue feels
momentum shifting.
Jonathan is leading his tribe.
Got to slow that ball down now.
TORI:
Orange, over here.
CHANELLE:
Go, go. Go.
Blue is now getting it
out of the sand.
-Everybody putting
their shoulder into it.
-CHANELLE: Go! Go!
PROBST:
That's how you do it
on Survivor!
You're in this.
-TORI: More, more, more, more.
-PROBST: It is Tori
up for orange,
trying to untie that key.
Blue trying to get
over that obstacle.
-MIKE: Up over the top.
-CHANELLE: Back it up,
back it up. Back it up.
PROBST:
She's got it.
(grunts)
PROBST:
Tori's down.
Slides on the butt.
That'll leave a mark.
MIKE:
One, two, three.
PROBST:
Here comes blue now.
Jonathan pushing
that ball again.
I-I am, too.
LYDIA:
Mm-hmm.
JONATHAN:
One, two...
-Push.
-TORI: Three.
PROBST:
Big push by orange!
Jonathan single-handedly
almost pushed that ball over.
Blue trying to stay in it.
Gonna be Romeo
trying to find the key.
(Lydia grunts)
PROBST:
Orange working
together very well.
(grunting)
PROBST:
Now you got to slow
that ball back down
-and bring it back.
But orange with a nice lead.
-LYDIA: Good!
Something Jonathan
has been used to.
-CHANELLE: We're not.
-PROBST: Romeo still
working on the key for blue.
Get ready, get ready.
This is it.
MIKE:
Come on down.
(overlapping chatter)
Blue's back on the move!
TORI:
Coming down.
Tori quickly gets down.
Orange out of the way.
Now you put it in its holder.
Jonathan, he's the ladder.
-Lifts Tori.
-(grunts)
-JONATHAN: Ready?
-(Lydia grunts)
PROBST:
Blue moving again.
No...
One by one, Jonathan
is getting everybody up.
Jonathan, watch out behind you.
Jonathan is up.
An amazing move by Jonathan.
-Wow.
-And you're good.
Start the human ladder.
Jonathan scampers to the top.
Another unbelievable display.
Jonathan gets Tori up.
Hai using his back.
There goes Maryanne. Jonathan
gonna just yank Maryanne up.
(grunting)
Here comes Lydia. She's up.
JONATHAN:
Let's go.
PROBST:
Hai gonna give it a running go.
JONATHAN:
Let's go.
Hai, he's got it.
You're good.
Two people on the puzzle.
-Let's go, mamas.
-PROBST: Great job by orange.
DREA:
Hold it, hold it.
You got it.
CHANELLE:
Get it, get it, Mike.
Get it, get it.
PROBST:
Romeo has the key.
Now you got to get down
and seat your ball right here.
-CHANELLE: Straight ahead.
-MIKE: Push, right,
straight ahead.
PROBST:
Gonna be Maryanne and Lydia
on the puzzle for orange.
It is a big puzzle.
Seventy-five pieces.
You got time, but you got
to keep moving.
Up here.
Mike gonna be first up on blue.
Scraping that body
against the ball.
-It's right here.
-Oh, nice.
PROBST: Maryanne and Lydia have
a big advantage right now,
but that is a big puzzle.
Good job, girls.
PROBST:
Mike bringing those
firefighter days into play.
Lift off. You go.
-One human after another.
-MIKE: Let's go.
-(grunting)
-PROBST: Mike pulling up
Chanelle now.
-Drea, a workhorse down there.
-ROMEO: Great job, Drea.
Now Drea's got to get up.
DREA:
Ah!
PROBST:
That is not easy to do.
-CHANELLE: You got this, Drea.
You got this.
-MIKE: You can do it.
You got this. You got this.
-Drea, you got it.
-CHANELLE: One more time, Drea.
-Let's go. It's time to eat...
-PROBST: Here goes Drea, again.
-(grunts)
PROBST:
Drea is literally scraping
her body against the ball
and goes down again.
-This is effort
on Day 12, Survivor 42.
-MIKE: Here.
-Pull my feet. By the feet.
-(Drea panting)
-PROBST: Mike, gonna try
-a different strategy.
-MIKE: By the feet.
-CHANELLE: Mike, let's-- Okay.
-(overlapping chatter)
PROBST:
Drea out of gas.
Beating up her body.
Good job, girls.
PROBST:
Lydia and Maryanne continue
to work side by side.
They've got
a big-time advantage,
and they're
working very well together.
-LYDIA: Yes.
-HAI: Nice.
PROBST:
Drea trying to get some wind.
-12 days into Survivor
makes this very, very tough.
-MIKE: Drea.
PROBST:
Drea literally gonna grab on
to the feet of Mike,
who's being held on to
by Omar and Chanelle,
who's being held on to by Romeo.
-Drea gets kicked in the face.
-ROMEO: You okay?
CHANELLE:
One more time, Drea.
OMAR:
Don't worry, Drea.
It's a huge puzzle.
MIKE:
All right, Romeo...
PROBST:
They're gonna change
their strategy.
-Romeo gonna have to
go back down now.
-MIKE: Where's Romeo?
Go down. Climb down on me.
Mike with a good idea,
which is to help Drea get up.
Maryanne,
while she's working on that,
why don't you flip the pieces
so you can see all of 'em?
No, that's all good.
We have time.
MIKE:
Use my body. Use my body.
PROBST:
Drea on Romeo's back.
CHANELLE:
Yes, Drea!
Climb, girl.
Everything in you, Drea.
-Yes!
-PROBST: Drea now
on Mike's back.
Drea's up.
Romeo now trying to get up.
Romeo's up. The strategy worked.
Blue is good.
Now Mike's the last one.
-I got it. I'm up. I'm up.
-Now you got another
ladder you got to build.
Right here.
You know you can do this.
I know.
Mike climbs on Omar.
Mike is up.
There you go. There you go.
-CHANELLE: You got it, Drea.
-MIKE: Pull.
-Drea's up.
-MIKE: Come here. I got you.
PROBST: Lydia and Maryanne
still working on the puzzle.
-They've got a long way to go.
-MARYANNE: Good.
PROBST:
Now, can Omar get up there?
Here we go.
Omar has Mike.
Can he pull him up?
That's how you dig,
right there!
MIKE:
All right, we're good. Go.
PROBST:
It is Chanelle and Omar
working quickly now.
It took them a long time to
get up here, but they're here.
DREA: Let's go, Chanelle.
Let's go, Omar.
Lydia and Maryanne continue
to work side by side.
-Piece by piece.
-LYDIA: Yeah.
Y'all are doing amazing,
but don't get comfortable.
Yeah.
Thank you for the reminder.
It really means a lot.
PROBST:
Lindsay and Rocksroy
down below,
no idea what
is happening up here.
Their fate will be in the hands
of the winning five.
PROBST:
Piece by piece,
orange getting closer and closer
to winning the biggest reward
of the season.
-TORI: Nice. Nice.
-PROBST: Tribe Buff, immunity
at the first Tribal Council,
and Applebee's on the line.
TORI:
Nice.
PROBST:
Shark Bowl, the brownie,
the burgers,
-the fixings, the fries.
-(overlapping chatter)
PROBST:
Chanelle, Omar struggling
to get back into this,
but it won't matter.
This one is over now.
It's just a matter
of these last few pieces.
Tori, Jonathan,
Hai, Lydia, Maryanne,
for the win.
-And they've got it.
-(cheering)
PROBST:
Biggest reward of the season.
And this challenge is over.
Wow.
-(excited chatter)
-Mwah.
PROBST:
The biggest challenge
of the season.
Everybody put in
a ton of effort,
but the victory went to
Maryanne, Jonathan,
Tori, Hai and Lydia.
So here's what you just earned:
your Buffs, immunity
at that first Tribal Council--
which means
you don't have to compete
in that first
individual immunity challenge--
plus Applebee's.
A very nice afternoon.
Here's a big decision you have
to make before you leave,
as a group.
Lindsay and Rocksroy,
you're gonna determine
their fate.
One of them is gonna join you.
-Oh, wow.
-And for them,
it is as though they won.
They get the Buff,
they get the immunity,
they get the food.
The other will be sent away
to another island and exiled
for two days and two nights,
where they will live alone
with no Buff, no immunity,
no food, no shelter,
no company, nothing.
And to complicate your decision
a little more,
the person you send away
will have the power
to change the game.
So the question
you have to decide,
do you want to send one
of these two away,
knowing they will be
in control of the power,
or do one of the five of you
want to give up everything
you just earned to be sure
you're in charge of the power?
You have two
big decisions to make.
Who do you bring
with you and who goes?
PROBST: Both Lindsay and
Rocksroy will have their game
altered dramatically
by the decision that is made.
Walk me through
the thought process
about who you want
to bring with you, Hai,
because it's a very big
strategic decision
to give this gift to a player.
HAI:
Jeff, it was simple.
One of them looks like
they really need to eat.
That was our reasoning
for the decision today.
I'm sorry, Rocksroy,
but we're bringing Lindsay.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
PROBST: Lindsay joins the five
that now becomes six.
Now, the next
equally big question.
You gonna send him away,
or are one of you
gonna take the spot?
We're sending him.
PROBST:
Okay. Rocksroy, you're gonna
be taken to another island
where you will
live alone for two days,
-two nights.
-TORI: You got it, Rocks.
For the winning six,
there are your Buffs.
Head out for a nice
afternoon of Applebee's.
MIKE:
Congrats, guys. Congrats.
Chanelle, Mike, Romeo,
Omar, Drea.
Normally,
I'd say I got nothing for you,
but after that effort, there
is a small consolation prize--
one serving of rice.
And you'll be heading
to the Vati beach.
That is gonna be
where everybody lives.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Get used to your new home,
and enjoy your rice.
Come on, guys.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
So, Rocksroy, what's the feeling
when they had a choice
between you and Lindsay,
but they still sent you away?
ROCKSROY:
Actually, I was
hoping it was Lindsay to go
when you said that the person
that's coming back
would have a little bit more
of an advantage in this game.
Yep, if there is a silver
lining, Rocksroy, it is that.
You will have power
to change the game.
And that's gonna be the question
as you sit out there.
What is the power,
and what will you do with it?
Everything
will be revealed in time.
For now, you got to head out.
Boat will pick you up,
take you to your new home.
See you soon, Jeff.
-PROBST: Good luck.
-All right, buddy.
They said they took Lindsay
because she needed food.
Uh, no, we all need food.
We're all hungry.
So I'm not sure
what the reasoning is.
Maybe Tori sent me out here
to weaken me even more.
But I'm not
disappointed about it
because in Survivor
this is what you want.
You want it to be hard,
because it shouldn't be so easy
just to get a million dollars.
♪ ♪
HAI (chanting): Applebee's,
Applebee's, Applebee's.
-(excited chatter)
-MARYANNE: French fries!
-LYDIA: Applebee's!
-French fries!
-LINDSAY: French fries!
Oh, my God.
The Applebee's was so sweet.
Oh, my gosh.
They bring out burgers,
and, oh, it was so good.
I'm gonna need to get one of
these again when I go home.
I wanted this one so bad.
So bad.
JONATHAN:
I haven't been
this happy in 12 days.
(laughter)
Even sweeter than the food,
the six of us got our Buffs,
and that automatically means
we're safe
in that first Tribal,
which is huge.
It was a win like no other.
-TORI: Oh, my God.
-LINDSAY: This was huge.
HAI:
Rocksroy has a huge power,
which is very ambiguous.
-Yeah, he did.
-JONATHAN: Like a whole lot.
-He, like, he was, like, warning
us almost, like, "Are you sure?"
-Mm-hmm.
I almost went to Exile,
because of this great power
that Jeff was talking about.
-Oh, my gosh.
-But I'm twice as big
as everybody out here.
And 12 days of not eating,
I'm starving.
So today
I'm eating like a king.
♪ ♪
Those wings are to die for.
They're perfect.
Back home,
my average meal is 18 eggs,
nine pieces of cheese and grits.
So I was in heaven.
I ate as much
as I possibly could.
Come on, man. Talk to me.
JONATHAN:
But I'm a bigger guy,
and I'm worried about that,
because that's
already a target on my back.
So I have got to lay low
as much as I can...
...and hope that
my social game is enough
to keep me around.
LINDSAY:
You're gonna love it.
MARYANNE:
Oh, my God.
Oh...
MARYANNE:
(gasps)
How am I gonna finish that?
LYDIA:
Dude...
Oh, my God.
I feel like
I went from zero to hero.
Like, not only
did we win Applebee's,
I'm the only person from Ika.
And not only that,
Rocksroy was the one
who was outcasted.
Like, it just, it couldn't
have been more perfect.
I was like the one person
on my tribe Rocksroy
would not have wanted
in the position of, like,
making the decision
if he went or not.
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
-I don't know.
Uh, you two
don't really get along?
No, it's very rare that
I don't get along with someone.
Oh, also he voted for me last
Tribal Council, as well. Yeah.
-Oh.
-They also, yeah,
tried to get me out
last Tribal Council, as well.
I am letting
all the secrets out.
I'm airing all my tribe's
dirty laundry. I don't care,
because my old Ika tribe
didn't want to work with me.
So we just don't get along.
So I didn't really want him here
because I wanted to enjoy this.
-OTHERS: Yeah.
-I'm trying to make myself
known as, like,
"Hey, you want a number? Like,
me, right here. Work with me."
And Rocksroy, he only cares
about the shelter and the fire.
So honestly, he's probably
loving being by himself.
-(laughter)
-TORI: I've been waiting
for the individual part.
And it was so scary, because
I almost didn't get here.
But now that I'm here,
I'm gonna do what I want to do
with other people, not Ika.
-Cheers to us, y'all.
-OTHERS: Cheers.
We'll always have Applebee's.
(laughter)
♪ ♪
CHANELLE: Literally, everything
that they're having today
was literally
what I was dreaming about.
-DREA: Really?
-What to expect this season.
Usually people will just get
to the merge and celebrate.
-We have to freakin' earn it.
-CHANELLE: Do you guys think
we're gonna have a merge feast?
-DREA: No.
-MIKE: The rice we're gonna have
is gonna be our merge feast.
Man, losing that challenge
hurt on a visceral level.
Like, I'm absolutely starving,
but I didn't come here to eat,
I came here to play and to win.
And so not having immunity
is probably the hardest part,
because the chances of me
going out just got higher.
It really sucks.
Do you want me to pour
the rest of the rice in, or no?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Uh-oh...
ROMEO:
We got a little bag of rice.
It could have been a bag
of cockroaches
or pieces of doo-doo,
and we would have been
celebrating.
MIKE:
That looks amazing.
ROMEO:
We have been starving.
I'm starting
to look like a skeleton.
So, sorry, America,
I look like crap.
I can't wait to know
what Rocksroy comes back with.
And he actually said to them,
"Are you sure you want to s...?"
DREA:
He kept on saying that.
You never know,
he might come back
and be able to say that
he can switch it to where
-they are not immune and we are.
-Ooh.
That's why he was like,
"You sure one of you guys
don't want to go?"
-That would be amazing.
DREA: Fortunately, Rocksroy's
a part of my alliance,
and if there's any way
he can change the game,
it would be
in my benefit as well.
However, I can't rely on that.
Did you guys
put clothes out there?
-MIKE: Where?
-OMAR: I put socks.
-ROMEO: Oh, I did.
DREA:
I know Mike has an idol,
because we both said the phrase
at the previous
immunity challenge.
So I'm hoping that Mike
wants to work with me.
Maybe.
I think that...
I mean two...
-Um...
-I'm with...
I'm with Romeo and Rocks.
All right, good.
Hai and Lydia are my alliance.
-Cool.
-Okay.
The one person on our team,
I'm just gonna tell you that...
-I won't say a word.
-Tori.
She literally tells
everyone's business on our team.
So...
But, uh...
-Yeah.
-MIKE: Drea's a smart player.
She knows where she's at,
and we both have the idol.
That was our bond.
We both feel
that we could protect
each other.
Am I feeling safe?
Absolutely not.
The war is about to begin,
and I'm not going home
with an idol in my pocket.
♪ ♪
Holy cow.
Oh, boy.
Well, I got a pot.
I got a machete.
Oh, what is this?
Some rice.
Jeff, thank you.
Let's get set up.
I'll start with fire.
♪ ♪
Damn it.
(sighs)
This is killing me that
I can't get this started.
I started with my fire.
Massive failure
on the first strike.
on the 50th strike.
Come on.
But I always tell my kids,
"Do it, get it done,
get it out of the way."
Don't rely
on someone else to do it.
Well, at this situation,
I can't rely
on anyone else to do it.
I got to do it.
Let's get this done.
Let's go.
You can do this.
♪ ♪
Rock and roll.
I tell myself all the time,
try it.
If you fail...
(scoffs)
...do it again.
Ooh, I've got something.
What is this?
Looks like some type of hammer.
Uh-oh.
I guess this may be
part of what my advantage is.
No information at all.
I'm gonna take it up to camp,
set it aside,
until I know exactly what
I need to do with this.
Jeff said I will have the power
to change the game.
So I'm not sure
what that means yet.
And now I'm here,
and I'm in this situation
where I have to earn it.
I'm dealt this card,
and I'm gonna deal with it.
There's a rule in firewood.
You think you have enough,
double it.
(whoops)
See? You got
a little point on it.
And then you can do this.
Let's do a twist.
(grunts)
There we go.
See? That's why you test it.
Oh, yeah.
Organic cordage. Nice.
Nice.
Being out here by myself
with no kids around,
no wife that's bored
and wants to nag me,
I saw it as an opportunity.
I'm getting to do
some things out here
that I've always wanted to do
and also learn new things
about myself.
Oh, yeah.
And that to me is wonderful.
Not to mention,
I'm in Fiji, man.
Oh.
Holy moly.
Jiminy Crickets, that's amazing.
Ah, this is truly beautiful.
Wow, I'm so lucky
to be here right now.
Wow, man.
I'm trying
to soak everything in,
take a mental picture of this,
because one of my biggest
challenges is just my vision.
I have, uh, keratoconus,
which is the coning
of your cornea.
I've had to have surgery
on both of my eyes for it,
and it could lead to blindness.
So this may be the last time,
at my age, that I'm able
to just see how beautiful
our planet is.
I mean, it's-it's-it's...
it's-it's emotional.
Wow.
Full moon off the horizon.
I was definitely meant
to be here.
Almost like
I'm getting a reward,
even though this
is not a reward, by the way,
by no stretch of the mindset.
This is not.
This is, this is work.
But it feels as if I'm getting
a little bit of reward because
of the beauty and how incredible
the Fijian islands are.
I think I'm just blessed
to be here.
It's just amazing.
I feel like
the luckiest person right now.
It's funny, I'm laughing
and crying at the same time,
but I feel like
the luckiest person.
It's crazy.
I was meant to be right here,
'cause I'm blessed to be.
Man. (sniffles)
♪ ♪
(squawks)
-MIKE: They're back.
-MARYANNE: Hey.
-New faces.
-(laughter)
-Nice to meet you, Hai.
-Pleasure, Omar.
-Omar. Nice to meet you.
-(overlapping greetings)
LYDIA:
Nice to meet you.
OMAR:
This is truly where
the party starts,
where the war begins.
From the outside,
you would think
that within this group of 12,
there would be four Vati people
sticking together,
four Ika people
and four Taku people
sticking together.
But at this point,
I'm one of the only people
that are vulnerable, so I'm not
closing any doors right now.
But make no mistake about it,
I will jump up
like a big shark from the ocean
and eat some of these people up
when the time is right.
I would like to think
we all made it to merge.
-HAI: We did.
-I'm not sure yet. I'm not sure.
-(overlapping chatter)
MIKE:
I'm not there.
LINDSAY:
Going into a merge,
the more relationships you have,
the more options you have.
So I really need to feel out
Drea and Hai about the amulet
we got on day one.
LINDSAY:
There's so many
possibilities for this amulet.
Do you work together,
or does greed take over?
I have no idea
how it's going to be used yet.
The first time I read it,
I was like, ....
-DREA: I know. Same.
-LINDSAY: I know.
-(Hai stammers)
Like, the first time
you read it,
it makes you think
you have to target each other.
So whoever needs my amulet...
-DREA: Same.
-LINDSAY: Same, yeah.
DREA:
The three together
steals a vote?
Is-is, no, a extra vote.
-HAI: Extra vote, Steal a Vote,
idol.
-Yeah.
HAI: Lindsay, Drea and I
are saying,
how about, instead of taking
each other out,
let's work together and use our
amulets to further our games.
-Yeah.
-If I hear y'all's name,
I will tell you.
-100%.
-Please do me the same courtesy.
But at the same time,
I'm nervous these ladies
are gonna come for me,
because they're
gonna want to grab power.
This game is
all about grabbing power.
I just need to figure out
who's gonna strike first.
Exactly. Knowing that, like...
-We just got to just lay low
and let things happen.
-Uh, yeah. Yeah.
These past 12 days,
I didn't have much power
in the game.
But now,
not only do I have safety,
but I have an immunity idol
which has been activated.
And I also have an extra vote.
Okay, don't worry.
I know. I'm gonna...
Don't worry.
-I feel like...
-I'm a, I'm a little person,
too.
I know. No, I know.
I know. I know.
My strategy is listening
to what they want as a plan.
I don't want to say my plan,
but if someone says their plan,
I can be like,
"That's a great idea."
And that puts them in
the spotlight rather than me.
What are your thoughts on Drea?
'Cause I know you guys
went to summit together.
Like, I like Drea.
Like, I just think, like,
Drea is gonna be
a problem in the future.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoa.
-(Maryanne laughs)
-Oh, my gosh.
-There's so much more to you
than just a bubbly personality.
-No.
Right now, I feel as if
I have just so many options
that I can work with,
which is great,
because in this game, you can't
go anywhere without allies.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Because it feels...
JONATHAN:
Mike and I both
have been through a lot
in our life,
and we can tell when
we look in each other's eyes.
And we bonded over that.
And that felt good.
Felt like I had somebody
caring about me,
and I appreciate that.
He's gonna be my buddy
for a long time out here.
Don't care what anybody thinks.
Be you.
-Yeah. That's good, though.
-Be you, and that's... and...
you are, you are you.
That's what I love about you.
Yeah.
MIKE:
Jonathan looks different,
he dresses different,
which I love.
There's a lot more to this guy
than probably people
are giving credit for,
just being a strong
muscular guy who's dominating.
I've been going through that
my whole life,
so I understand it hurts being
stigmatized as the big dummy.
That was our bond.
MIKE:
We're gonna go forward
looking out for each other,
and maybe for once
in Survivor history,
the people
that are physically stronger
win this thing for a change.
(laughs)
♪ ♪
-HAI: Look under here.
Look under here.
-LINDSAY: I see 'em. I see 'em.
-Right in that nook right there.
-JONATHAN: I see 'em.
CHANELLE:
Oh, I see 'em, too.
-(gasps)
-HAI: Oh. Are you all right?
-DREA: Are you all right?
Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Ah, there it is!
-HAI: Right-right there!
LYDIA:
Jonathan is a beast of a dude.
I like him a lot.
Obviously, he's amazing
to have around camp.
-Oh, my God. (whoops)
-HAI: Oh, my God.
HAI:
Thank goodness for Jonathan,
otherwise we would starve.
He is the biggest human
being I've ever seen in my life.
HAI: And he's also just
incredibly athletic.
-Oh! Oh, it's a stingray.
-Oh, my God.
-HAI: That was a valiant effort.
-DREA: Yeah.
-He, like, really
looks like a superhero.
-I know.
HAI:
This man is so intimidating,
but I'm not
going to oppose working with
someone I'm intimidated by.
Jonathan is someone I would
love to keep in the game
due to his sheer physicality--
just so I have a shield
in front of me.
(Jonathan laughs)
-CHANELLE: Yeah.
-DREA: Yeah, I love hearing
how people meet.
HAI: So, I was commuting
for work.
So I was, like, really lonely.
-Yeah.
-So I downloaded Tinder.
-And all of a sudden,
I receive a message.
And I was like,
"Who the hell is this?"
'Cause he had two blurry photos.
OMAR:
Yeah.
-And no bio.
-OMAR: Oh, that's sketch.
DREA:
That is sketch.
TORI:
I'm surprised you responded.
HAI:
Well, I didn't respond
at first, but he followed up.
ROMEO: Hai is part of
the LGBT community,
and I'm part of the
LGBT community, but I still
change myself a little bit to...
to fit in and be accepted.
And Hai doesn't care
about that stuff.
It's refreshing to meet
somebody that was the opposite--
somebody that's so
comfortable with themselves.
It feels good to be able to,
like, talk to somebody,
you know, that understands,
but...
...I grew up in
South Central L.A.
I come from an immigrant family.
It's not... it's not okay.
You know what I'm saying?
So I had to adapt, and pretend
and be somebody that I was not.
-Are you out
to your family at home?
-Most of them.
-Yeah?
-I mean, there's a huge part
of my family
back in El Salvador-- where
I'm from-- that don't know,
-that are gonna know watching.
-After this.
Which is terrifying.
HAI:
Do you think they'll accept you?
ROMEO:
I don't know.
My biggest fear
for people like us is, like,
being looked at differently.
You don't want to...
people to stop loving you
or seeing you the way that
they've seen you for so many...
-(exhales sharply) Sorry.
-You're-you're still
the same person.
Yeah. Let it out.
I know. I know you've been
holding it in.
ROMEO:
You can't hide on Survivor.
And my fear is
will people back home
that didn't know about me
look at me differently
when I go back home
and-and love me less
or-or not want to be around me?
That's my biggest fear
coming out here was, um...
...was disappointing people.
-You have lots of support here.
-Yeah.
-And I'm here for you,
and I don't want you
to feel as though
you need to, like, stay quiet,
just to fit in,
because we've had to do that.
Because I remember
how hard that was.
You should be the proud
gay man that you are out here.
ROMEO: Finally, as an adult, I
don't want to blend in anymore.
I'm living my truth out here
for the first time in my life,
and-and it's while
I'm playing Survivor.
It's crazy what this game
will do to you.
I didn't know how much
it would really affect me,
but I'm gonna leave here
like a different person,
for sure.
No, I-I appreciate it.
Like, I'll remember this
for a long time.
It feels like a huge weight has
been lifted from my shoulders.
That's something
that I will take with me...
...forever.
You guys excited for the next
phase of the game, or...
HAI:
Uh, yeah,
I love the individual phase.
-OMAR: Yeah.
-HAI: Yeah.
Just...
be, uh, wary of who you
give information to.
R... For you?
HAI:
Yeah, I've been at the bottom.
You've been at the bottom?
HAI:
They're gonna vote Lydia
and then me.
OMAR:
That's so interesting,
'cause on our hike, Chanelle
struck me as somebody who was,
-like, very honest and,
like, straightforward.
-No. Nope.
-OMAR: Really?
-She said, after the hike,
she lost her vote.
She lost it?
Yeah, that's so interesting.
-So I just want you to know...
-I'm happy you told me that
because I was trusting her
a little bit.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Chanelle lost her vote--
which means at the summit,
we both risked it,
and I won't have a vote
at the next Tribal Council.
It's so scary.
This is the most danger I've
felt in the whole game so far.
CHANELLE:
I just want to make sure, like,
you and I, we're-we're solid.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Like, the thing from
the summit still stands.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I thought from the summit
that Chanelle and I had a bond,
but she doesn't trust me enough
to tell me I won't have a vote,
and that's a problem.
This girl is sketchy.
I don't want to be around her.
I want her gone.
♪ ♪
I... So, I didn't date
anyone until I was 24, 25.
Eventually, we just
started dating...
-Good for you, man.
Nothing wrong with that.
-Um...
It is a long time.
That's a long time.
Yeah, but I think
the reason it's...
-Yeah.
-Good for you, man.
Good for you.
I literally vibe
with you so much.
-Oh, I know, I vibe with you.
-And, like, I feel...
-We're the youngins.
-Yes, we are. And we're...
-Youngins got to stick together.
-With the old grandma names.
Oh, my God.
Any good feelings
about anybody yet?
HAI:
I like you and Lindsay.
Yeah. I love Omar.
Love Mike.
-I-I feel really good
about Drea.
-Yeah.
You have Lydia?
Hey, that's perfect.
D-Do you remember what I told
about the first Tribal?
-No.
-I was willing
to go to rocks for her.
-Not to go home.
-Yes. Yes.
And I'm telling you, like,
man-to-man...
-Yeah.
-if I give you my word,
what I did for Lydia
I will do for you.
Everyone's
opening up and bonding,
and sharing our life stories
and cracking jokes.
Are you Buff-shaming me 'cause
I don't have a Buff?
-Oh. It's going to your head.
-Oh, my God, you're...
-You're Buff-shaming me.
-Oh!
HAI: Which is great, but now
I need to establish agency.
Whether it be through
my social skills,
wrangling people together,
I need to get my numbers
in order
and have
a clear path to the end.
-Lydia and I are together.
-DREA: Okay.
-For sure.
And Mike is a man of his word.
If Mike shakes your hand,
you're good.
-So he's taking you to the end.
-DREA: Mike is...
Mike is like Rocks.
Rocks is like Mike.
Rocksroy is solid.
-Okay. I knew that. I knew...
-And Jonathan, so yeah,
you, Lindsay and Omar
-are super tight?
-Yeah, super tight.
-Good.
-So just throwing numbers
out there.
You and Rocks.
-You, Lindsay, Omar.
-Mm.
Me, Lyds and Mike.
Would-would everyone
feel comfortable with that?
-JONATHAN: I'm-I'm down
with that.
-DREA: I'm good with this group.
HAI:
I'm a driver.
I can't take the back seat.
I need to establish the allies
that I need to protect.
And then I need to identify
the threats
that I need to eliminate.
I would also like
to share something,
if you're comfortable
about Chanelle.
So...
truthfully,
Chanelle was gonna be next.
She flip-flops, and
please be careful
what you share with her,
because she plays all sides.
DREA:
What's been going on
in our tribe?
Tori has been trying
to blindside everyone
since day one.
She's going to screw you over.
-Know what I mean?
-HAI: Right.
-JONATHAN: Mm.
-Be careful.
-HAI: Yeah.
Our next to go
would be Maryanne,
but she hasn't even done
anything to hurt our tribe.
-She was just the next to go.
-HAI: Right.
JONATHAN:
So here's the thing.
They're-they're immune.
HAI:
It's tricky. That's the issue.
-LYDIA: Yeah.
-JONATHAN: It seems
to be starting up very well,
as far as strategy.
So, Tori would be
one of the first gone.
Chanelle: gone.
I threw out Maryanne's name
cause I don't want them think
that we're super close.
And if I'm gonna throw
anybody's name out on my tribe
that I don't trust,
it would be Maryanne.
But here's the catch.
Tori and Maryanne are already
safe at the next Tribal.
And let me tell you,
that's bad news for Chanelle.
DREA: Dude, I'm, like,
we're nowhere near the end.
HAI:
It's impossible.
Me and Jonathan
went out there, and, like,
the net would not
catch anything.
-Hey.
-JONATHAN: We went, like,
neck-deep.
-What up? What up, what up?
-DREA: Neck-deep?
-You were neck-deep?
-We're up to, like, our...
We were up to, like, our necks.
CHANELLE:
There is an urgency out here,
because being in the majority
of the tribe is as simple as
you weren't
in the right conversation
at the right time, at the right
moment, with the right people.
HAI:
Well, we're gonna go crabbing.
DREA:
The tide is down.
CHANELLE:
I'm just gonna walk up
on this group and say "Hey."
Then they all get up and say,
"I'm gonna go spearfishing."
And so, I'm, like, trying
to find my place right now.
And, uh, I'm trying to find
who I trust.
-Ugh. That moment with Chanelle
was not good on me.
-No.
I felt like I was intruding
when I went over there,
-when you guys were all talking.
-Oh, no.
We briefly discussed, um,
Rocksroy, and just, like,
-trying to figure out,
like, what's going on there.
-Yeah.
-Of course...
-Are you guys trying to, like,
make a, like, a five?
-Oh. No. Oh, no, no, no.
It was none of that.
-Oh, no? Oh. Oh.
LYDIA:
No one trusts her.
And so, I'm playing dumb.
Like, I'm just, like,
"Like, no."
Like, I'm really just trying
to keep her
as comfortable as possible.
Have you heard any names
on the block yet?
Oh, no, no, no.
CHANELLE:
Yeah, um...
-Yeah.
-Our final three.
Yeah, for sure.
CHANELLE:
Lydia, I trusted,
but she just seems like
she's holding so much back.
I can see it. We talk,
she doesn't look me in my eyes.
She just seems like
she's out of it.
And it's, like, very...
makes me very uneasy.
I really don't trust anyone,
to be quite honest.
It's so scary,
because you don't know
who's made these
underlying side deals,
under-the-table deals.
Everything's lining up
with the eight that we have.
-Bro, I think it's solid.
-Yeah.
-JONATHAN: Are you
down with that, Omar?
-100%.
E-Except I don't know
if I have a vote or not.
-You don't know?
-Because of the summit.
HAI:
Chanelle screwed him.
-Yeah, Chanelle...
-OMAR: She lost her vote.
Are we together?
-Like, we're-we're tight, right?
-HAI: Yes.
-OMAR: Yeah.
I have an extra vote.
I have trusted my gut that I'm
aligned with the right people.
We need to stick to the eight.
So I wanted to tell them
about the extra vote,
because it could really build
connections with people.
We've caught Tori in so many
lies, and she does it so well.
We need to get her out.
OMAR:
But she's safe right now.
DREA:
We don't know what
Rocksroy brings home.
Oh. Unless immunity...
Unless Rocksroy changes it.
But everyone votes.
Either Chanelle or Tori,
'cause they're separated.
JONATHAN:
Yep.
This first vote is tricky,
because we've been subdivided
into two groups--
people who are safe
safe from the vote
and those that are
vulnerable to go home.
But fortunately, we have some
early low-hanging-fruit targets
for the first few Tribals.
-I'm telling you,
Chanelle is killer at Tribal.
-Yeah.
And she's coming right now.
-OMAR: Okay.
-HAI: Yeah.
OMAR:
We have to make Chanelle feel...
Yeah, 'cause the last time
she came, we split up, so...
-just talk.
-Yeah.
-HAI: Chanelle has proven
that she's not loyal to me,
since my very first Tribal.
And there's only one more person
on my hit list
that betrayed me--
and that's poor Chanelle.
We're talking about, like,
we all have good vibes.
And they all really like you.
DREA:
Yeah.
HAI:
DREA:
Yeah.
-JONATHAN: I'm gonna go check
that spot for spearfishing.
-HAI: Yeah, I'll come with you.
-I'm gonna go get the scuba
gear. You want to come with us?
-I actually want to enjoy
-the beach, too.
You want to enjoy it with me?
-OMAR: I'll enjoy the beach.
CHANELLE:
Yeah.
♪ ♪
(exhales)
Oh, gosh. Love that.
Pop, pop.
Don't want to drop a grain.
Spending time by myself,
away from the social aspect
of the game a bit.
Oh, I love it.
I've worked so hard
for two days, and...
I just want
to relax a little bit...
This is just
for a little bit of flavor.
...and not having
to think about the game.
♪ ♪
Let's go get 'em hot.
Get 'em hot. Get 'em hot.
Yippee ki-yay.
Time for some rice.
Oh, yeah, buddy.
Jeff!
-Hey!
-Rocksroy!
-Welcome to the pad, buddy.
-What's up?
Wow. You got a shelter.
Yeah, I built a shelter.
I had to rush everything,
but, you know.
This is impressive.
ROCKSROY:
Jeff's coming to visit me, okay?
So I was like, "Wow."
But at the same time,
I'm a little nervous,
'cause there's always some type
of twist and turn in this game.
I'm sorry, I may interrupt you
to take my rice off.
-(chuckles)
-I love it.
So, how are you feeling,
being out here?
I really wanted to experience
what it is to, like,
not only be on Survivor,
but a survivalist.
But I think having
this moment of zen, kind of,
I think it helps me.
So it's like a pause,
-and then the next stage
of the game.
-Exactly.
-So let's recap
where we are, all right?
-Mm-hmm.
Right now we have
the six that are safe.
They got the Buff.
They don't have to compete
-in the immunity challenge.
-Yeah.
You and the other five,
you will have to compete
in that immunity challenge.
One of you will win,
and one of the other five
will go home.
Doesn't have to be that way.
Huh?
Where's that hourglass?
(grunts) The one I've been
trying to figure out
-what the heck it's here for?
-Yeah.
I've been counting it out,
trying to see
if it's a real hour.
-This one.
-That one.
Yeah, set it between us.
So, the sand at the bottom
represents time that has passed.
-Correct.
-History.
Yes.
You can leave things
as they are.
-Right.
-Or you can go back in time...
...and change history,
by reversing the outcome
of the challenge.
They would lose their Buff,
they would lose their immunity.
You six would be safe,
and one of those six
would be voted out.
Whoa.
There are pros and cons
to doing it or not doing it.
I immediately think
of the con of doing it.
There's a huge target on me.
"Why did you do that to us?"
On the other hand,
I have Drea and Romeo
that's already in my alliance.
So those are people
you would be helping.
-And maybe they will
somewhat protect me for a while.
-Mm.
Because at least
I protected them.
It's a big decision.
If you decide to do nothing,
then just do nothing.
If you decide to change history,
at any time between
now and tomorrow morning,
when you return to the game,
find that mallet,
smash that glass.
That's your decision.
ROCKSROY:
This is the biggest moment
in the game so far.
And the decision lies with me.
Awesome.
Wow. Now it's time to play.
I am a honorable player,
but the five that
are currently vulnerable
lost, fair and square.
Hey, not everyone gets a trophy.
You lost--
better luck next time.
But if I leave it
and I don't smash it,
I'm gonna be vulnerable.
The six that are safe
right now--
would they look out for me
and not vote for me?
How much weight does
it carry for me going forward?
And then there's
the Tori factor.
That's the big factor.
Where does she stand?
Tori's a loose cannon,
and right now she's safe.
But with one swing of a hammer,
she's vulnerable.
It's tremendous power.
Ah, it's just a tough decision.
Do I smash the glass
or do I just walk away?
You know, the devil you do
or the devil don't.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Oh.
Let's bring in Rocksroy,
returning from two days
and two nights exiled alone.
(overlapping chatter, applause)
MIKE:
My man.
Right up here, Rocksroy.
All right, so first,
how are you?
Two days, two nights. Long time
to be alone on your own.
-Yeah.
-How'd it go?
It was tiring. Had to do
everything by yourself.
Blessed that there was no rain,
um, but it was tough.
It was real tough.
PROBST:
All right.
When you sent Rocksroy away,
you gave him
the power to change the game.
Rocksroy has the power to leave
things exactly as they are.
Whatever happened,
happened.
You six are safe,
you don't have to compete, or...
Rocksroy has the power
to go back in time
and change history
-by reversing the outcome
of the challenge.
-DREA: Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
Which means the six of you
would lose your Buff--
because you're not part
of the merge tribe--
and you six would have to
compete and fight for immunity.
You five and Rocksroy
would be safe
and would not have to compete.
-Huge stakes.
-LINDSAY: Oh, my God.
-MIKE: Rocksroy.
PROBST:
What decision did you make?
♪ ♪
So if I smash it,
six people get a do-over.
If I leave it on its side...
...nothing happens.
Sometimes everyone
deserves a do-over.
I went back
and I changed history.
-Oh, my God.
-(overlapping chatter)
-MIKE: Oh, Rocksroy.
So, in my thoughts,
they didn't get to eat.
-They didn't get to do anything.
-MIKE: Oh, my God.
These guys, they got to eat.
They got,
they got, they got
something in their belly.
They have some energy.
Go out there and do it.
All right, so, reactions.
Hai, you're smiling,
but I'm not sure you're happy.
-There are no free meals
this season.
-Yeah.
I know that.
I respect his choice.
We had a great meal.
You know, I felt good about
being safe, but it's time to...
-it's time to compete.
-PROBST: Tori,
you can hardly
look over this way.
TORI:
Keep in mind we sent you
not just to be exiled
for two days by yourself.
We sent you knowing
that you had power.
So I'm pretty pissed off that
that ended up happening,
because I actually was
doing that to maybe help you.
(laughs softly)
So, Tori, you're saying
that your decision
to not take the power yourself
and give it to Rocksroy
-was a gift to Rocksroy.
-(laughter)
Partially.
I mean, I really,
I know Rocksroy.
I got to live with him
for quite a few days,
and I feel like if he had
the choice between food
or gaining power in this game,
he was gonna choose power.
ROCKSROY: But what can I do?
Tori, you should know that
if I'm sent someplace,
I'm gonna stick with how I feel.
I'm gonna make a decision.
PROBST:
All right.
Lydia, Maryanne, Lindsay,
Tori, Hai, Jonathan,
drop your Buffs. You are
not part of the merge tribe.
One of you
won't even make the jury.
(groaning)
-Oh, my God.
-(overlapping chatter)
-PROBST: As for
the rest of you, Rocksroy,
-That is savage.
head over,
give everybody a Buff,
because you, Chanelle, Drea,
Romeo, Mike and Omar
are now in the merge tribe.
-(whoops)
PROBST:
Guaranteed a spot
in the final 11.
-Cannot be voted out tonight.
-Yes.
Go ahead and put your Buffs on.
Wow, it smells clean.
All right, let's get to it.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna pull
on a rope
while balancing a wobbly table
and stacking letter blocks.
If at any point
your stack drops,
you have to start over.
First person
to spell "immunity"...
...wins immunity.
This is what you're playing for.
-(oohing)
-(excited chatter)
LINDSAY:
That looks awesome.
MIKE:
That's sweet.
That's pretty badass.
-LINDSAY: That's badass.
-LYDIA: Badass.
TORI:
Very nice. Very nice.
Individual immunity
with this around your neck,
you are safe.
Cannot be voted out of the game.
Win today's challenge,
you are guaranteed
a spot in the final 11.
You'll definitely be
on the jury.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the seventh person
voted out
and will fall this short
of making the jury.
Big stakes.
We're gonna draw for spots.
We'll get started. Here we go.
You can sit here and watch.
♪ ♪
Here we go.
Biggest twist of the season.
Immunity on the line.
One will be safe.
The other five,
somebody going home tonight.
Survivors ready.
Go.
You've got to spell
"immunity" backwards,
from the bottom to the top.
MARYANNE:
I-M-M-U-N-I...
PROBST:
If your stack drops,
you got to start over.
Everybody racing out
with that first letter.
Six people, who, moments ago,
thought they were safe...
...now fighting to be safe.
Jonathan back first.
Has his second block.
He's heading back out.
Everybody else pretty even.
-Good job, everyone.
-PROBST: Couple of different
ways to play this.
You can be very slow
and steady...
...or, if you're behind,
-you may have to get
a little more aggressive.
-Whoa.
PROBST:
But as your stack grows,
that wobbly table
becomes much more important.
Oh, no.
Maryanne dropped...
Oh, Maryanne let everything go.
-(laughs)
-PROBST: I'm not sure why.
MARYANNE:
I dropped one.
I don't want to mess up.
It's easier just to start over.
All right, that makes sense.
Jonathan places
his second block.
Tori places hers.
They're even.
It is Tori and Jonathan
right now.
Here comes Maryanne--
still smiling.
(laughs)
PROBST:
Hai places his second block.
Here comes Lindsay
out with her second.
-Let's go, guys.
-Eight letters total.
-OMAR: Good work.
-Still a lot of challenge left.
Hai places his sixth block.
It is Hai in the lead
right now.
Then Jonathan, then Lindsay,
then Tori, then Lydia
and then Maryanne.
I-M-M-U-N.
PROBST:
Hai is now two blocks away from
winning individual immunity.
Now you're gonna see the
adrenaline start to kick in...
-Ah.
-as Hai gets closer and
closer to closing this out.
Tori trying to get out quickly
with her sixth,
as Hai reaches for his seventh.
Let's go, Hai.
You got this, buddy.
PROBST:
He has two left.
Lydia drops.
Lydia's got to start over.
It's still Hai in the lead.
He's coming out
with his seventh block.
Hai loses everything.
It is now Tori and Jonathan
in the lead, just like that.
Tori now overtaking Jonathan.
Tori places her seventh letter.
She has one left.
Jonathan coming out with his
seventh letter, still wobbling.
-Jonathan drops everything!
-(gasps, groans)
He's out.
It is now Tori in the lead.
Lindsay the only one
that can catch her right now.
Tori heading back for her eighth
and final letter.
Jonathan, frustration.
So close.
You got to keep fighting
because anybody could drop
at any time,
and suddenly,
you're in the lead.
DREA:
Take it easy, guys.
PROBST:
Lindsay places her seventh.
-She's heading back
for her eighth.
-Easy.
PROBST:
Tori slowly reaching
for that eighth.
You have to be very careful.
You don't want to drop here.
Lindsay has
slowly increased her pace,
but it's making a difference.
She is gaining on Tori.
Tori still in the lead.
You got to get all the way out.
Then you got to get
all the way back to win this.
PROBST:
Lindsay is on the platform.
Now she's got to reach
for that eighth block
as Tori reaches
to place her eighth block.
Lindsay has it.
She's heading back out.
-Aw.
-PROBST: Tori has
her final block
and a time advantage.
Lindsay will have
to make up time,
or Tori will have
to make a mistake.
-Aah!
-(gasps)
PROBST:
Lindsay drops everything.
One little hesitation
on that rope,
everything is gone.
Lydia places her sixth.
And... drops everything. Done.
It is now Tori and then
Maryanne, and that's it.
-(Tori groaning)
-PROBST: Maryanne
heading back out
with her seventh block.
Maryanne could be in the lead
if something happened
to Tori's stack.
-Ooh.
-Oh.
-(indistinct murmuring)
PROBST:
Tori with a lot of movement
on that stack,
but it's staying together.
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Tori is two steps away
from winning this challenge.
All she has to do is
get both feet on that platform
with all of her blocks
-intact.
-Oh.
PROBST:
Maryanne places
her seventh letter.
(Maryanne whimpering)
PROBST:
There's one.
Get it up there, girl.
-I'm just...
-DREA: Just do it.
Tori has it! Tori wins
individual immunity.
-Wow. Good job.
-PROBST: Will make
the final 11, cannot
-be voted out of the game,
-You got this.
-PROBST:
and the tears start to flow.
-JONATHAN: Good job.
Hey, you got this.
You got this.
Good job, everyone.
-Okay? Good job, everyone.
-ROCKSROY: Hey, fish.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
All right, Tori, get over here.
-(Maryanne whoops)
-Yeah, Tori! (whoops)
Oh, my God. Oh.
Pinch me. Pinch me.
I'm literally about to pass out.
First individual immunity
of the season.
Yeah!
You are safe, cannot be voted
out of this game.
-Oh, my God.
-You will make the final 11.
You will at least be
on the jury.
You're not going home tonight.
Maryanne, Lindsay,
Lydia, Hai, Jonathan,
one of the five of you
will be voted out.
Your dream will come to an end.
Everybody's voting tonight.
But you have one
of five choices.
-Won't be you. Congratulations.
Grab your stuff.
-Thank you.
-Head back to camp.
-MIKE: Yeah, great job, Tori.
PROBST:
See you tonight at Tribal.
LYDIA:
Tori and Chanelle were
in trouble,
and now they are both safe.
So it was basically worst-case
scenario for everybody.
And now we have to completely,
you know, 180
and have
to have a whole different plan,
and it is going to be,
like, every... just chaos.
OMAR: Congrats, Tori.
-MARYANNE: Yeah, first immunity
of the season!
-Thank you.
-MIKE: Tori!
-OMAR: Look at that necklace!
-(whooping)
-MIKE:
Nice. I want to pet it.
-(Maryanne laughs)
-Ooh! Ah!
-DREA: Welcome.
-Sweet. Where's the pool?
We haven't put it in yet, man.
We're waiting for you.
-Good to meet you, bro.
-Good to meet you.
I hear you're
the fire guy over here.
ROCKSROY:
I am safe for tonight.
I am safe for now.
Guys that-that
did the challenge,
you know, I feel for you.
I really...
-Yeah.
-I definitely did.
There's literally
no hard feelings from me.
ROCKSROY:
Because I've been away,
I'm gonna have to build
alliances pretty quickly.
Yeah, man, I'm gonna go see
if I can spear something.
Come on, man.
ROCKSROY: But I don't know
what's been happening
in the last two days.
I don't know what alliances
have been made. I have no clue.
Can you get me a boat?
I'll go back to that island
I was on for a couple more days.
Uh, like you, Rocksroy,
I'm-I'm a straight shooter.
I'm straight shooting.
I'm not just saying this 'cause
you're here. You can ask Drea.
She already put you
in this alliance.
-We got eight people.
-Okay.
I mean-I mean,
it would be stupid.
-He's gonna win everything.
-Yeah.
This is our chance. If we don't
do it now, we're dumb.
-ROCKSROY: Shut the front door.
-Yeah, bro.
-ROCKSROY: Oh, baby.
-Oh, my gosh.
-That's right.
-Aah.
ROCKSROY:
He's spitting.
You see, these guys are
doing the guy...
-(guttural groaning)
-I know. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Already.
I mean, did you not see it?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Get out of here.
I mean, Mike is so far up
Jonathan's ...
-it's disgusting.
-Yeah.
-He's a beast, man.
-TORI: Golden boy.
-Man after my own heart.
-TORI: Yeah. For sure.
He is. He's a man's man.
I love that.
-You know how I am.
-TORI: Yeah.
-ROMEO:
He sleeps next to him.
-TORI: Yeah.
ROMEO:
He... They wake up--
"Let's go see the sunset."
-Get out here.
-The energy.
Did someone give you food?
-Oh, my gosh.
-No, I'm just, like, honestly,
this is sort of...
-Yeah. They're...
-This is the second part
of Survivor.
-Yeah.
-And this is where
Romeo comes out.
-Oh, come on. Yes. Yes.
-You know... you know who I am.
-You know who I am.
-Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
ROMEO:
I was terrified
because I didn't have a Buff.
Now it's like
I have power again,
and I just feel like
a different person.
I'm power hungry,
I want control again, and
I want Jonathan gone.
Here's the thing. If it's not
him, it's gonna be you.
-I know. I know.
-They're not gonna vote
for one of the girls.
I know that physicality
is the merge boot. Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
MARYANNE: I really don't want
to vote for Jonathan,
but the thing is,
options are limited.
It's, like, my butt
is on the line, too,
and I'm talking
and I'm strategizing
and I'm scrambling, 'cause,
like, there's only five people
not safe for this Tribal--
Jonathan,
Hai, me, Lindsay and Lydia.
Jonathan is going to be
a very physical threat,
I think, going forward.
-He's terrible
with puzzles, though.
-Is he really?
And he's super helpful
-with having food.
-Which is fine, yeah.
-And, like, all of that.
-Mm-hmm.
-I mean, I'm-I'm open.
-Yeah. For sure.
-Yeah, me, too.
-But, like, Maryanne--
she's all over the place.
-Yes.
LINDSAY:
Like, she's going crazy
in her head,
so many different things,
and she's super strategic.
-Jonathan's not as strategic.
-Yeah.
-For sure.
Do you think she has anything
other than the Shot in the Dark?
-Yeah?
-(Lydia gasps)
LINDSAY: My biggest pitch
is Maryanne-- that she has
a lot of hidden ammo.
And I don't want to pitch Hai
because I want
to work with Hai.
Secondly, Hai told me that him
and Lydia were gonna go
for rocks for each other.
So the only option left
is Maryanne.
-Good chat.
-We can talk later. Yeah.
-Yeah.
LINDSAY:
I need people
to be more fearful
of the power that she has versus
a potential threat of me
or Jonathan,
'cause that's what it seems
like it's coming down to.
-No.
-No. Did it for you?
CHANELLE:
I see right through it.
Lindsay's put her pitch out
to protect herself and Jonathan.
He catches food,
and people are mesmerized
by the "golden boy"
kind of thing.
He's not golden to me.
Like, he could go on streak,
and that's always scary.
-Because, you know?
-CHANELLE: Yup.
CHANELLE:
Kind of seems like a no-brainer.
-Yeah, I'm definitely down
with that. Like, it's not...
-Mm-hmm.
You guys can do what you want,
'cause, like, I have no...
-I'm safe, and I have no vote.
-No, it's fine.
-So, ultimately, it's your game.
-Mm-hmm.
OMAR: My first instinct,
knowing that I'm safe
and I don't have a vote,
is to just shut the heck up
and not say anything.
Because why?
Why would I jeopardize
my position in the game?
But the more I thought about it,
I'm like, "This is terrible."
Omar, this is the time
that I need your help.
I know. That's why
I'm hustling for you.
-Help me.
-I am. I am.
JONATHAN:
I'm obviously
the biggest threat out here
when it comes to physical,
and if I were them,
I would vote me out.
But I'm gonna keep
fighting in this game
'till I'm dead.
I'm voting for Maryanne,
and, uh,
stick with me.
I promise, I'm loyal.
Well, if someone has to go,
then it's gonna be Maryanne.
Here's the problem, though.
The fact
that I have
to put my trust in people
that I met a day
and a half ago is very scary.
But we're supposed to be
an alliance of eight, and, uh,
I am confident in Omar
keeping people off my back.
Yes. Yes.
Um...
But I did speak to Lindsay,
and she was saying, like,
-Maryanne is, like,
a huge liability.
-Oh.
So, it's, like, it's really
what does your gut say--
-Jonathan versus Maryanne?
-(sighs)
It feels like you're swayed
Jonathan over Maryanne.
I just want to do majority.
There is eight of us that want
to all work together, but
there is just this point
where I'm, like, "I just
want to go with the numbers."
I don't want to be the one
on the bottom.
And I kind of feel like
we could be good.
We could be good,
but this game changes so fast,
so, actually, who knows?
I'm so worried. Like,
you can't prepare for anything.
Okay.
-Yeah.
-(laughs)
OMAR:
Lydia says to me,
"Like, I'm really torn."
And I'm like,
"This is opportunity."
Like, you're telling me
you don't know if you want
to stick with the eight.
And that's my opening to say,
"Sacrifice little Lydia."
Thing is, now I feel
it's between Lydia and Maryanne.
-Positive?
-And then I think
it's going to be something.
While it will be Jonathan
and not you.
I feel like you and Lindsay were
really on the Maryanne train,
-which I-I see, long-term.
-Mm-hmm.
But right now, it's too early,
and she's useful to us.
OMAR:
I'm trying to bring Taku
back together because,
at this point,
Maryanne has an extra vote
and a hidden immunity idol,
and I don't want either one
of those things
going out of the game
because I'm gonna need weapons,
I'm gonna need arsenal,
and I'm gonna need an army.
You were the primary at first,
but I'm trying
to shift it to Lydia.
-Why was I the primary?
-I don't know.
There's rumors
that you have an idol,
so I think
other tribes know about it.
-Okay, just be chill, okay?
I need you to be chill.
-Okay. Yup.
-Because if you blow it...
-It's gone.
I'm shifting things to Lydia.
Okay,
so I write down Lydia's name?
At Tribal, you need
to write down "Lydia."
And if I'm not successful...
That's fine.
My jaw just dropped.
I was like, "Why me?"
Like, I don't want to go out
before the merge.
I've worked so hard
to be here, and
I'm so terrified. All I want
to do is cry and scream.
But, like,
I know that in this game,
I have to go, and I have
to center myself,
and I have to stay calm.
I feel as if me playing my idol
right now--
it all comes down to Omar.
The plan is obvious.
We need to switch to Lydia.
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah.
Yeah?
OMAR:
In this game,
you take a little bit
of information, and that's
where you weave in your own lies
or your own truths
to prime them of the fact
that Lydia's maybe not
on their side, long-term.
But Lydia right now is Hai's
number-one ally in the game.
This is one of
the toughest jobs I've had
out here since I've started.
I didn't want
to upset the eight
-before it got to the point.
-Right. Right.
-So I didn't think
it was my place to say it yet.
-Right.
OMAR:
But Lydia is like,
"At some point
within the eight, we need
to go after the bigger players."
I think Jonathan--
it's too early for him, but now,
it's, like,
Maryanne's the only one,
-and she has an immunity idol.
-Yup.
If she plays that,
it's one of the eight.
So, Lydia is the choice here.
♪ ♪
But I want to make sure
all three of us are
-on board for the plan.
-MIKE: Hai,
if that's what you think,
I'm with you.
HAI:
Not an option at all.
Lydia and I have been day ones
out here, and I gave her
my word
that I would protect her.
So now I have to
scramble and get her
the numbers to stay.
Okay, and now I need to get
enough votes for Maryanne.
It's Jonathan and Maryanne.
Tonight's tricky.
There seems to be
a group who wants to target
the more physical players,
such as Jonathan.
which I don't like,
'cause I consider myself
one of the more physical
people here.
I want to win more
individual immunities, okay?
And I feel like
you would stand in my way.
HAI:
Which is why I need Maryanne
to go home tonight.
However, the issue is,
we know for a fact
that Maryanne has an idol.
Exactly, so we might be...
we might just slip by.
HAI:
In Survivor,
your relationships
take precedent,
and Lydia going home
will only hurt my game.
This game is wild.
Moments like these
are where good players
fold, and great players
prevail.
♪ ♪
Wow. Everybody here.
-First time.
-It's a good-looking bunch,
huh?
It really is. I was just kind of
taking everybody in, yeah.
-And we love you, Mr. Jeff.
-(laughter)
-PROBST: Mr. Jeff. Yeah,
I'm getting used to that.
-Yeah.
(laughter)
PROBST:
All right. Hai,
how do you feel about this?
Is this
-a defining vote tonight?
-It is a defining vote,
but things are a lot more fluid
this season.
Tribal lines are typically
with your starting tribe.
However, this season,
it's very fluid,
it's always moving,
and everyone's in conversation.
OMAR:
Everyone said,
"Let's go get firewood,"
but that firewood is empty.
LINDSAY:
I noticed that.
(laughter)
PROBST:
So Romeo, what do you base
trust on at this point
when you don't know
a lot of these people?
I don't know about them, but for
me, it's always a gut feeling.
How are they interacting
with me?
Do they want
to start a conversation?
Or are they just starting
a nonsense conversation
just to say
that they talked to me?
I can look at somebody
in the eye
and know if they're telling me
the truth or not.
Simple. That's just a gift
I've had since I was a child.
PROBST:
Drea, it's interesting.
Romeo gave
a very specific situation
of somebody coming up and just
starting a BS conversation.
-Right.
-Do you feel like
you can pick up those cues?
DREA:
I'm very good at that,
but maybe
someone didn't come
to talk to you
because they didn't feel
comfortable coming to talk
to you or something like that.
So, I see both sides.
PROBST:
Hai, that's a very
sophisticated approach.
You cannot just wait.
Sometimes you have to stick
your hand out and say,
"Want to talk?"
Yeah, it's the idea of,
are you a driver
or are you a passenger?
You know, for me, growing up,
I didn't have a lot
of confidence,
and I knew coming out here,
I didn't want to be
that version of myself.
I wanted to come out here
and play with confidence
because if you come out here
and you play a fearful game,
you're not gonna get anywhere.
PROBST:
Lydia, I really connected
-with which version
of yourself you want to show.
-Yeah.
When I was in high school,
we moved from Wichita, Kansas
to Seattle, Washington,
when I'm in the middle
of high school.
And I decided I'm going to put
a different version of myself
out in this new high school.
Have you had any of that
yourself
out here in terms
of what parts
of me am I gonna put out
and what parts am I gonna hide?
LYDIA:
Yeah. Growing up,
I-I faked a lot of confidence,
you know.
And leaving my hometown
and just, like,
gaining independence and just
accepting parts of myself
that I never even realized.
You know, it... the confidence
actually became real.
And in Survivor specifically,
you're going
to just play better
and you're gonna feel better
if you are just
your full authentic self.
PROBST:
Jonathan, one of the things
you have to do in this game is
hide your paranoia or your fear.
You know, the "never let 'em
see you sweat" thing.
Does paranoia get to you?
There's a point in the game
where you've done
all that you can do.
And whoever
gets kicked out of here,
I hope that they go,
"I did everything I could do.
"When I had the opportunity
to be on Survivor,
I left it here."
PROBST:
Omar, that would be
the best way to approach
every Tribal Council.
-Yeah.
-Can you do that?
Uh, my younger self would not
have been able to do that.
I think my older self--
now that I'm 30...
-(laughter)
-PROBST: Wow.
Let me just
take that statement in
-for a moment.
-Yeah. He don't know old, man.
-Oh, that hurt.
-OMAR: I would say now
that I've had some
life experience, you can just
look at it factually, and
you know that at some point,
somebody's gonna come for you.
So I feel like
I can just tell people, like,
I'm worried,
and not dwell on it.
PROBST:
Rocksroy,
-you came into this late.
-Yes.
PROBST:
Could you sense a direction
of why the vote
might be going the way
it's gonna go?
ROCKSROY:
Yeah, it's a tough one because
I'm coming in this
two days of not being here.
But one of the things I know
that I can rely on is
the bond that I've built
with my alliance.
And then there's a part of me,
also, that feels pretty bad
because it's, like, my decision
is ultimately is the reason why
one of these people
are going home tonight.
PROBST:
Maryanne, what do you
think the theme
of the vote is tonight?
MARYANNE:
Who can I continue
to work with and
who do I want to work with
for a long span of time?
PROBST:
Drea, you agree with that?
-No, I don't agree with that.
-Okay, that's fine.
'Cause tomorrow,
someone could be gunning for me,
and then I might have to depend
on someone else to save me.
So, yeah, it's always changing.
But you choose your vote
because you think
that person's going
to work with you.
But if they change their mind,
then of course,
you're not going
to work with them.
So then, I feel as if
we're on the same page,
different part of the line.
-Yeah?
-So you agree with me?
-And you agree with me?
-No, I agree that
this doesn't mean that
this could take you long-term.
-It's Survivor. Yeah.
-Exactly. We're on the same
page, I think.
Not really. Agree to disagree.
-And I respect that.
-PROBST: So Maryanne,
for all the charm,
do you worry talking too much
or debating too much
could be a reason
where the group just says,
"You know what?
"I just... I need
to get some sleep.
Let's just vote Maryanne out"?
Obviously,
I do worry about that.
But the thing about Survivor
is I can show
my true self, and, like,
that means not be subdued.
That means that, like,
if I have a weird thing
which I want to say,
I want to say it. Like,
I wanted people
to know me for who I am.
Like, everyone in this tribe
has great qualities,
and everyone
in this tribe has things
that they want to work on.
Some of these things
might be obvious
to everybody,
some of these things might be
less obvious to everybody.
Mine are obviously more obvious
to everyone, 'cause I'm just
like a "Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah." But, like,
I knew that coming into the...
What was your question?
(laughter)
(insect whirring)
-Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
-DREA: What is that?
MARYANNE:
It's, like, a beetle
or something.
-Or a rat.
-It's just a beetle.
-He's on me.
-Big-ass beetle.
-Look. He's right here.
-No! Aah! Ooh!
-TORI: Oh, my God.
-ROCKSROY: We're in
his neighborhood.
MARYANNE:
No, I know. It's all good.
It's all good. I'm fine with it.
Oh, you actually
do have one there.
-Yeah, he literally does.
It's there.
-Oh, that's cool.
-MARYANNE: Exactly.
-ROCKSROY: Just a beetle.
PROBST:
So Chanelle, are you
better off on Survivor
to try to quiet your quirks?
Or, as Maryanne is,
just embrace who you are?
CHANELLE:
That's what this game
is supposed
to bring out of you--
the fullest version
of yourself
where you are meeting
your highest potential.
And if you're not authentic,
people will
see right through that.
HAI:
Jeff, there are
12 realities here,
and each one of us have
a different perception
of every single other person.
So even if you think
someone's telling you the truth,
it could be a lie, so,
lies will be revealed tonight.
PROBST:
All right,
it is time to vote.
Omar, you're up.
♪ ♪
That worked.
This is the biggest risk
I've ever made in my life.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Jonathan.
Lindsay. One vote, Jonathan.
One vote, Lindsay.
Jonathan. Two votes, Jonathan,
Maryanne. Two votes, Jonathan.
One vote, Lindsay,
One vote, Maryanne.
Maryanne. We're tied.
Two votes, Maryanne.
Two votes, Jonathan.
One vote, Lindsay.
Lydia.
That's two votes, Maryanne,
two votes, Jonathan,
one vote, Lindsay,
one vote, Lydia.
Lydia. We're tied again.
Lydia: two votes,
Maryanne: two votes,
Jonathan: two votes,
Lindsay: one vote.
Lydia. That's three votes,
Lydia,
two votes, Maryanne,
two votes, Jonathan,
one vote, Lindsay.
Lydia. That's four votes,
Lydia, two votes, Maryanne,
two votes, Jonathan,
one vote, Lindsay.
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor 42:
Lydia. That's five. That's
enough. You need to bring me
your torch.
♪ ♪
Love you, Lyds.
Lydia, the tribe has spoken.
Time to go.
Good luck, guys.
-Bye, Lydia.
-(overlapping chatter)
(sighs)
-Congratulations. You are now...
-(whooping)
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: ...officially merged.
-Yeah!
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Thanks, Jeff.
HAI:
Someone is creating chaos.
I don't like that.
MIKE: They were like rats.
And when you turn on the lights,
and they scurry away.
Yeah.
I'm not closing any doors
right now.
DREA:
If they got to go,
they got to go. (laughs)
I got blindsided
and to be so close
to the merge--
it sucks, for sure, but as much
as I wanted to make it further,
I learned a lot about myself,
and I hope a lot of young girls
like me see that they can
do it just like I did,
and you don't have to get
to the end
to have a really
meaningful experience.
(roars)