ROMEO:
I just want to say
I have no hard feelings.
This is a game.
I'm glad I'm still here.
-Good job, Romeo.
-Thank you for keeping me,
and I still like all of you.
At Tribal,
three votes were thrown on me
just in case
Chanelle played an idol.
So, obviously, I was lied to.
All these people are fake.
I don't like any of 'em, so
I have
to put on a fake happy smile
and pretend
that it's all good.
"It's all good
if you voted for me."
You know, when in reality
I want to, like,
kick 'em in the face.
But that's not smart.
What?
What's up?
No, I have no idea
who that is.
-I thought so, baby. I-I got it.
-No, I voted for Chanelle.
-I-I know who it is. Thank you.
-Okay.
HAI:
I have not received
a single vote until this Tribal.
And then, all of a sudden,
I receive a hinky vote, which...
Whatever. It's fine.
But now I'm kind of,
like, upset about it,
and I have an inkling
that it came from Romeo.
He, you know, swore
that he's a God-fearing man,
he wouldn't write my name down,
and...
-ROMEO: Hai...
-...there it was.
So if you didn't vote for me,
who voted for me?
I don't know. It wasn't me.
I voted for Chanelle.
Even if this is my last vote,
I just want to see you squirm.
Does anyone want
to admit to my name?
Right. It-it was Romeo.
ROMEO:
Hai is the person who's
instigating everything on cam.
And people are too dumb
to realize it.
And so I threw a vote
his direction
because even though I knew
he wasn't going home,
I knew
that it would make him squir.
I wanted him to freak out,
and I was successful
because now people see
that this man is not all there,
and whoever is aligned
with him is... is... is dumb.
If I get voted off next, fine,
but I'm not getting voted out
without trying
and creating a little chaos.
You have to play this game, and
I'm-I'm going to play this game.
ROCKSROY:
Hey.
Okay. Okay, but...
-Well, you asked my opinion.
Can I finish?
-Yes. Go.
Not only
is he creating paranoia.
He can look me in the eye and
straight-up lie to me.
That's personal.
ROCKSROY:
I mean, yes,
Romeo is an easy gone,
but I'm nervous about me.
I've been busting my ass
out here, and it's not just me.
Jonathan is out there, you know,
first thing, "Let's go fishing."
Mike, same thing.
"Let's go get firewood,"
but no one cares.
Instead,
it's put a target on us.
So I need to do something.
The guys need
to stick together.
MIKE:
Say it, dude.
ROCKSROY:
We have more dudes
than women here.
And right now we have
the freaking numbers, guys.
I don't want to get taken out
and then, guess what,
-they're gonna start
picking off...
-Us one at a time.
-...buh-buh, buh-buh, buh-buh.
-Yup.
-You go first.
-You're going second.
-Second, yeah.
-Guess who's going third. Boom.
-Third.
-ROCKSROY:
I want to talk to Omar...
-MIKE: Yeah.
...and talk to Hai.
JONATHAN: Rocksroy wants
to make an alliance
with the five guys
so that we have
some pull in the game
because everybody's always
after the big guy in Survivor.
So I'm very interested.
-I'm in, bro. I'm serious.
Listen, I'm in.
-I'm in. I'm in.
-You know I'm in.
-Yup.
MIKE:
The guys are coming together,
'cause normally guys like me
and Jonathan are taken out,
so I would love
a male alliance.
I know sooner or later
we're gonna
cannibalize each other
and eat each other and leave
the-the dead bodies on the road.
I know that's gonna happen.
But the guys
that I'm with right now--
they deserve to go forward.
ROCKSROY: So, how many guys
are there right now?
-Every single Survivor,
the guys don't get together.
-Yeah, yeah.
-I'm not trying
to lead anything...
-Yeah.
...but if we stuck together...
OMAR: Rocksroy's like,
"Listen up, buddy.
"How many guys are there?
Hint, hint.
"Like, um, guys' alliance,
like, so obvious?
I don't know why nobody's
done this in 40 seasons."
I'm like,
"Are you insane, Rocksroy?
"You haven't talked to me
the whole time about game,
and you're going to come in hot
like that."
Like, that seems like a mistake.
Yup. Yup.
Yeah, yeah, I love it.
You're telling me that
I'm gonna have as equal
of a chance as Jonathan and Mike
at winning immunity
at the final five?
Like, are you insane?
HAI:
There seems to be
a boys' alliance brewing,
and I somehow became a part
of it.
And I don't know
where they got the idea
that I would vote
with all the boys.
Like, I'm not part
of the misogyny club here.
The way that Rocksroy talks
to people makes me upset.
He's very blunt,
he cuts people off.
He doesn't let you finish
your thoughts.
And you only talk strategy
with Rocksroy
when Rocksroy wants
to talk strategy.
And I hate it.
So he's quickly
making his way up the ranks
on my list
of people to vote out.
♪ ♪
All right, ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
-(all assent)
-First things first.
Tori, for the second time
in a row,
got to take it back.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to balance
on a triangular platform
in rough water
with your feet perched
on very narrow footholds.
At regular intervals,
we'll move higher,
making it more difficult.
If, at any point,
you touch the platform
or fall off... you're out.
Today, not just one person
will win immunity.
-Two people...
-Wow.
-Yes.
-...will win immunity.
-We are dividing you
into two teams of five.
-Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
PROBST:
One person from each team
will win immunity.
Both teams will go
to Tribal Council separately.
Both teams will vote
somebody out.
So two people
will have immunity.
Two people going home tonight.
In addition, the person
who lasts the longest
of the entire challenge earns
for their team
beef and veggie kebabs
-to take back to camp.
-Oh.
-Cook 'em up yourself.
-Whoa.
Plus, that team will go
to Tribal Council
last, which means you'll have
an additional advantage
of knowing who was voted out
-in the first Tribal Council.
-Wow.
-All right, we'll get started.
Here we go.
All right,
we have our two teams.
In blue-- Drea, Jonathan,
Tori, Lindsay and Maryanne.
Running orange,
we have Mike, Rocksroy,
Omar, Romeo and Hai.
The sea is very rough,
the wind is picking up.
This could be over very fast.
Your life in the game
hangs in the balance.
Here we go.
I'm gonna count you in.
Everybody get up off your butt.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
This challenge is on.
You're getting your balance.
-Everybody's good.
Maryanne is in.
-(yells)
-She's first out.
Rocksroy's out.
-(groans)
Omar's out. Mike's out.
Just like that, four are out.
We're down to Hai and Romeo
fighting for immunity
for orange.
Hang in there, Romeo!
Find that balance point.
It is a very rough day
on the water
-here in Fiji.
-I'm out.
Drea's out.
This is going so fast.
Tori's out.
Now it is Lindsay
and Jonathan
fighting for immunity for blue.
Not even a minute yet.
Unprecedented swells
and wind on an already
difficult challenge.
Romeo, you touched. You're out.
Hai, you're good,
but keep fighting.
Hai has immunity.
You want to stay in it now.
Remember,
the last person standing
also wins food.
Lindsay and Jonathan fighting
for immunity and food.
Keep fighting, Hai!
Lindsay, stay in it!
Jonathan hunched over.
You've been out there
only two minutes.
OMAR:
Good job, Hai!
Your life in the game is
on the line right now.
Keep fighting.
Lindsay With a nice recovery.
Hai with a nice recovery.
Jonathan with a nice recovery.
Lindsay with another nice save.
Great balance.
That's how you do it!
You want to make the final
eight, you win right here,
and you've done it.
Hai is already in eight.
Who will join him?
Hai is now fighting
for food for his team.
OMAR:
Hai, stay in it.
-(overlapping shouting)
-Hai,
-nice recovery!
-Yeah, Hai!
PROBST:
The wind continues to move
bodies and platforms
all over the place.
Very difficult to do
this challenge on a flat sea.
MARYANNE:
Whoa!
Lindsay can't do it.
Lindsay's out.
Now it's Jonathan
who has won immunity,
and we have a showdown--
Hai and Jonathan.
Hai's out. Jonathan wins
immunity and food for his team.
-(cheering)
-PROBST: Wow!
MIKE:
Great job, Hai.
Amazing effort by everybody in
a very difficult challenge.
All right, two winners.
Hai, come on over.
-(cheering)
-MIKE: Yeah, Hai!
-Come on, Hai.
-(whooping)
-MARYANNE: Yeah!
-ROCKSROY: My man.
And it looks good on you, bro.
You are safe, cannot
be voted out tonight.
Head back to orange.
-Yeah!
-Jonathan, come on over.
-(whooping)
-Yeah, Jonathan, swag, swag!
-MARYANNE: Oh, yeah!
-You've been waiting for this.
I've been waiting.
Come on, Mr. Jeff.
Yeah!
Jonathan also safe tonight
at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final eight.
Head back over. In addition...
-I'm proud of you.
-Jonathan earned
-for his team of five...
-Thank you.
kebabs waiting for you
back at camp, you can cook up
while you go back
to the old Taku camp,
where you will spend
the afternoon.
You will go
to Tribal Council first.
Then you'll go
to Tribal Council second,
and you will
have the advantage
of seeing what just happened.
Big night.
Two people going home.
-I'll see everybody
at Tribal Council.
-JONATHAN: Thank you.
MIKE:
Hai got the immunity necklac.
I don't have to even worry
about anything today.
I got me, Omar and Rocks,
and Romeo is out.
That's easy.
We got the numbers.
Four to one, we go home.
This is your camp, huh?
HAI:
This isn't that bad.
-It's kind of cute.
-Oh, it got old
-after a while.
-Huh?
OMAR:
I never thought I would
ever come back to Taku,
but here I am with Hai,
Rocksroy, Romeo and Mike.
-Wow.
-HAI: Wow. They really
separated our group
-so there's no discussion.
-MIKE: Yeah.
OMAR:
And what's interesting about
this configuration is,
Rocksroy boy,
you got your final five
of men.
But who's gonna be
the one out now?
HAI:
So we probably have about
-three to four hours. Yeah?
-MIKE: Yup.
-OMAR: Sure.
-Uh, food-wise,
-you want to take a look?
-Yeah, sure, let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
ROMEO:
This is my worst nightmare.
I mean, I never had anything
in common with Rocksroy,
even though we were aligned.
I have nothing in common
with Mike.
He's like a hundred years old.
And Hai-- we got into
an argument last night, so,
I'm going home.
There's no questions about it.
There's nothing really
that I can do.
Think it's kind of
a no-brainer, but...
Dude, nobody's
getting squirrely,
-so I think it's...
-Yeah.
ROCKSROY:
Fortunately,
I have three of the guys
that I brought together waiting
to go to Tribal right now.
Now, during the wait,
is where the dynamics come in.
You ask anybody that's been
with me since the beginning,
-what I say, I mean.
-I'm not voting
for you tonight, so...
And I'm not
voting for you tonight.
ROCKSROY:
I think, personally,
when it comes to guys,
guys are more rigid
in making a decision,
so I'm banking on that.
OMAR:
Going into tonight,
Romeo was a dead man walking,
but in the long term,
he's loyal to me right now,
whereas Rocksroy--
I feel like there's less room
to maneuver with him.
He's immovable, he's unshakable.
I'm trying to eliminate people
at this stage of the game that
I can't shape or mold
to what I want.
And so, they are coming
for you tonight.
I need to talk to Hai
to confirm the plan,
but I think
we should go for Rocks.
Hai will be the swing vote
tonight.
Yeah, but the problem is,
I don't trust him.
He wants me out.
I know you're feeling that way,
but you have to trust me.
So just be
as calm as possible.
ROMEO:
The irony is,
the person that I wanted to
vote out tonight is the persn
my Survivor life depends on
at tonight's Tribal Council.
It's terrifying.
I'm going to have to trust the
one person that I don't trust.
OMAR:
I know.
ROMEO:
Let's just say
I'm not too confident because
Hai is the sneakiest...
weasel that Survivor 42 has.
OMAR:
I feel like you might be
on the same page
-with me about Rocks.
-HAI: Yes.
-He's getting exceedingly
difficult to work with.
-Yes.
If we wanted to blindside Rocks,
-I would be with you
a thousand percent.
-Tonight?
-Here's the concern.
-Yeah.
-HAI: Mike still considers me
his number one.
-Right, right.
If we vote Rocks tonight,
and I don't tell Mike,
-I lose his trust forever.
-Right.
HAI:
Tonight's vote could be
very simple.
If I wanted
to make an emotional move,
I would take out Romeo.
But for me,
tonight's vote is not emotional.
It's strategic.
But I don't want
to make this move
without Mike's blessing
because I don't want
to lose Mike's trust.
Can I be candid with you?
MIKE:
Yeah. Course you could.
Here's my thought.
Obviously Romeo's
very untrustworthy.
I know he's coming after me,
but I'm not scared of Romeo.
Rocksroy, down the line,
is gonna be hard to navigate,
especially
as the numbers dwindle.
We can't take him out tonight.
-You don't want to?
-No, I'm not saying... No.
I do want to, but we can't,
because if we take him out,
it'll show that we're
not trustworthy,
that we would turn
on our alliance.
Voting Rocksroy
tarnishes what I say out here.
I'm a man of my word.
What happens if we do
vote Rocksroy out tonight?
Does the rest of our alliance
look at us and say,
"You're not trustworthy.
We could be next"?
That's what I think about,
and my word is big here.
Listen, they're gonna say,
"If they turned against Rocksroy
when they promised him,
they'll turn on me."
Here's the truth,
Rocksroy's not
a hard vote for me,
but I gave him my word already.
So Hai is putting me
in a bad position.
Hai is my number one here.
Me and Hai have been together
since day three.
So we got to figure out
what we're gonna do.
♪ ♪
(birds squawking)
JONATHAN:
Look at all the food.
LINDSAY:
Holy cow.
-Mmm. That's so good.
-TORI: Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, my God.
-And tomato.
LINDSAY:
I was so close
to beating Jonathan
at that immunity challenge.
But at least
we won a bunch of food,
which was super exciting.
And I'm happy with the way
we got divvied up,
because it's me
and two other Takus.
So we're in control of
who's going home tonight.
Drea has a hidden immunity idol,
so it kind of seems like Tori
might be the easy target here.
TORI:
I know.
Like, I, like, I think Romeo.
-LINDSAY: I mean,
after that whole scuffle.
-Yeah.
JONATHAN:
When we got split
into two different groups,
I realized this could be
really good for me.
From the beginning,
I've had to put any ego
that I've had behind me,
because the big guy
cannot come in guns a-blazin,
"This is how it's gonna be."
Because it puts an even
bigger target on your back.
So I've been waiting for
my moment to make a big move.
And now is that time.
-JONATHAN: So, listen.
-MARYANNE: Yeah.
We're gonna
get rid of this idol.
Okay? Not yours.
-Drea's. I was thinking that.
-Right.
-So, listen... So, keep...
-Okay. Yeah.
MARYANNE:
Yeah.
JONATHAN:
And we're gonna tell Drea
it's you.
If this works,
then we're golden.
This is how we have to do it.
MARYANNE: Jonathan is like,
"Look, we need to get Drea.
Drea has an idol.
She needs to go."
And I'm like,
"Okay, cool. I'm on board."
'Cause I've been on the outs
since the merge.
But then he says, "We're gona
have Drea vote for you."
And I'm like, "What the heck?"
-We can flush the idol.
But, like...
-JONATHAN: Okay.
We need to do it now.
Do you understand?
That is the plan.
Drea is going.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay?
MARYANNE:
Jonathan treats me
like a young little girl--
the child that needs to be led.
And that's so annoying,
because I'm not here
to be a sheep.
So I'm fine with targeting Drea,
but Jonathan's
really getting to me.
MARYANNE: Yeah, but he said
I can't tell you,
-so... he...
-Wait, he really did?
MARYANNE: You don't know this.
You don't...
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
-Yeah.
-But here's the thing,
I know Drea.
Drea has been wanting
to make a move on me.
I know, and I know she's
gonna get in their heads.
The only thing is,
if they're gonna follow.
After winning the first two
individual immunities,
my biggest fear is that it's
gonna be like a no-brainer.
Oh, Tori doesn't have an idol.
She doesn't have an advantage.
Let's just get her out now.
But somehow they're finally
willing to make a move
and to make it on Drea.
And as long as
they stick with the plan,
I still have hope in this game.
♪ ♪
We can either do Maryanne,
which I'm fine with...
DREA:
Do you want Maryanne out?
JONATHAN:
I think that it'd be good
to get rid of the idol.
I do, too.
Okay.
-DREA: You've got my word.
-Awesome. You got mine.
DREA: Getting split
into two tribes totally suck,
because none of these people
are really my close allies.
But then Jonathan said,
"It's Maryanne."
Instantly, I was like,
"Okay, awesome."
However, that's, like,
a red flag for me
when I hear that they're voting
out people who have idols.
'Cause I'm like,
"Uh... this girl has one, too."
(laughs)
JONATHAN:
So let me tell you,
-if you could just
hear me out, okay?
-Yeah. Mm.
JONATHAN:
We have an opportunity
to take out Drea.
Okay.
JONATHAN:
So, yeah,
three of us are voting Drea,
and she's voting Maryanne.
-Okay. Okay.
-This could be
a huge move for us,
because there's
only gonna be eight left,
and the Taku four
would still be here.
-And we have
an extra vote and an idol.
-Uh-huh. Right. Yes.
So we can make it
to the top four
if we play our cards right.
You down?
-So, we get rid of Drea...
-Mm-hmm.
-...to flush the idol out.
-Done.
LINDSAY:
But if she chooses to play i,
Maryanne would be out,
and we would lose
that extra vote and an idol.
♪ ♪
Let's think about that
for a second.
LINDSAY:
Jonathan is not very strategic.
But he's not thinking things
all the way through,
because if Drea plays her idol,
Maryanne's gone.
So how are we gonna keep
the Taku four?
And if he really
is trying to be Taku strong,
we need a contingency plan.
I can convince Drea
to vote Tori,
because they already
hate each other.
So me and Drea vote Tori,
and the three of you vote Drea.
JONATHAN:
So here's the thing.
Tori will tell Drea.
LINDSAY:
No.
-She could. (stammers)
-Why?
-Because Maryanne...
-She doesn't like Drea.
-She would not say it to Drea.
-Well, you don't, t-truly,
you don't know that.
I know more than you know that.
But that's... and that's...
I'm giving you... And that's why
I'm having you trust me.
Like, trust me
that the information
-that I've been getting...
-We're not supposed to trust
anybody out here.
Correct, but Tori knows
that she's been on the bottom.
I don't think
she would warn her,
'cause she knows that
she'd be the other option.
You're not listening to me.
Tori is not trustworthy.
LINDSAY:
Jonathan's impossible
to talk with,
and he's not understanding that
there's a lot more relationships
that he's not aware of.
It's not that I trust her,
I'm saying we need
a backup plan.
You're not listening.
You're getting really worked up,
and it's hard
to communicate with you
-when you, when you go
a million miles a minute.
-Sorry.
JONATHAN:
I don't think
she's gonna play her idol.
I think she's just
gonna go home.
LINDSAY:
Being the only man,
he feels like
a top dog right now,
and he's not listening to me.
LINDSAY:
Mm-hmm.
JONATHAN:
Most people that get immunit,
they relax
and they take it easy.
I think this is the best time
to go hard in the paint.
And if they listen to me,
we're going to the end.
LINDSAY:
If we get Tori out,
you have your idol,
Drea has her idol,
and we have more power.
JONATHAN:
I'm hyped that there's
a big move that's gonna be made,
and I get to orchestrate it.
I've been waiting
for this moment,
and I'm gonna love
every minute of it.
(thunder rumbling)
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right.
Before we get into
the dynamics of the vote,
I never want to take for granted
that you guys
are living in this.
-Yep.
-You're not going back
to a cozy cabin.
Put on some music,
crank up the fireplace.
You're going back to this.
Hai is shivering.
Your entire body is moving.
I have no body fat left.
-(laughter)
-Watching this on TV
is amazing,
but being
out here right now sucks.
OMAR:
But, Jeff,
when you get through it,
you learn that there's
part of in you that can
push further than you would have
ever been pushed in real life.
And while it sucks now,
the lifelong lesson
is greater
than the sucky moment.
So, Mike, you go back
to the old Taku camp,
and you only have five people.
It's a new dynamic again.
Well, here's the deal, Jeff.
You-you go to sleep at night
and, quite frankly,
you're not comfortable here.
So you wake up,
and what you do is,
you start going through
the different evolutions
of this game
that you want to play.
And you do it over
and over and over again.
You put everybody there,
you think about everybody,
what... who they are,
what they do.
Then you get out there
and you go to a challenge
and you realize all the things
that you calculated...
...gets thrown out the door.
And then we only have
maybe two to three hours
before we're back here,
voting on somebody.
And we have to do it now.
Right now, in the rain,
on Survivor.
PROBST:
Hai, that was a great summation
what a, what a day can be like.
You wake up with plan A,
and then you get plan B.
Yeah, especially on this season,
where luck and your destiny
are completely
out of your control sometimes.
You know, we all woke up
with an idea
of what we wanted to do
at this Tribal,
but everyone had to adapt
and be flexible.
So, Rocksroy, how fast is
the game shifting for you?
Uh, I think today
we were actually
a little bit more mellow, Jeff,
to be quite honest.
-PROBST: Really?
-ROCKSROY: Uh, we were...
-But we were...
-With only five people?
ROCKSROY:
With only five people.
We spent a lot of time
just eating coconuts,
not even really
trying to strategize
as much as you would think.
PROBST:
Do you think that's a little bit
like a game of chicken?
ROCKSROY:
It could be, or it could be that
some of us have an understanding
on what's gonna happen tonight.
PROBST:
Mike, there it is.
Everybody has to believe
they have an understanding,
because otherwise,
now with the Shot in the Dark,
everybody
could screw the game up.
So the lying has to be so good.
MIKE:
Yeah, and it's tough.
We don't know,
'cause he's right.
We didn't scatter today.
We just played it safe.
And then-- you're right,
it may be a game of chicken.
I only know what I'm gonna do.
PROBST:
So, Romeo,
if you had to categorize
or give a flavor
to this afternoon,
how would you label it?
ROMEO:
Well, I just
found it interesting,
you know,
that it's an all-male tribe.
And, like, everyone just did
the whole male thing, and...
"Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm. All right."
And then just went back
to talking about life.
It was very interesting.
Very different dynamic
with no women on this tribe.
PROBST:
So, Rocksroy,
when you hear Romeo say that,
all of you guys kind of did the
"What's up? What's up?"
-(laughter)
-Is that in your wheelhouse?
ROCKSROY:
As Romeo said, we kind
of acted like guys today.
We kind of, like,
dismissed that we really
had a big decision to make,
and we weren't gonna go off
and-and talk to each other.
But from what I saw today,
I didn't see anything
that changed my mind
to think that
what I came in thinking
tonight would be would change.
All right, then.
It is time to vote.
Rocksroy, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
All right.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Romeo.
Rocksroy.
That's two votes Rocksroy,
one vote Romeo.
♪ ♪
Ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury--
Rocksroy. That's three.
That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
ROCKSROY:
Way to go, guys.
HAI:
See you, Rocks.
♪ ♪
Rocksroy, the tribe has spoken.
-Thank you, Jeff.
-OMAR: Bye, Rocks.
-Good luck, guys.
-MIKE: Thanks, Rocks.
-HAI: Bye, Rocks.
Rocksroy, you can take a spot
on the jury next to Chanelle.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
We'll bring in the next group.
♪ ♪
-(laughs)
-(thunder rumbling)
♪ ♪
What?
MARYANNE:
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
So, getting your first look
at what just went down.
Rocksroy voted out,
second member of the jury.
There were some reactions
as you walked in.
Drea, is that
a surprising vote?
Yes, definitely to me.
PROBST:
So what does that tell you?
I don't know.
PROBST:
Lindsay, it's just a reminder
that the game is constantly
churning and turning over.
LINDSAY:
Yeah, it just threw us off guard
from what our plan was
for the five of us here,
because we kind of
all had an assumption
of where that five was going.
So I think it's
lingering a little longer.
PROBST:
So, Drea, what do you have to do
when you're forced to adapt
with this small of a group,
some of whom
you may have an alliance with,
some of whom you may not?
You have to go back
to the drawing board
and basically see, like,
where you fit in.
And now, as I look and I see
two people over there
that I really
did not think would be
over there so soon,
it changes your mindset.
From what?
Conservative to aggressive?
From trusting to not trusting?
I don't know yet.
PROBST:
And, Tori, that could be
good news or bad news,
depending on which side
of the vote
you were on
when you walked in.
Right. I actually, I see this
whole twist as good news,
because it, like,
frees people up.
And now, like, you get a chance
to work with people
that might not have
worked with you before
because there was
this bigger majority.
It's terrifying. Don't get me
wrong, it's terrifying,
'cause our odds are now
one-in-four of going home.
Like, that is terrifying.
And, Jeff,
Survivor players who are gret
need to look a step ahead.
Just because we're
isolated in the five
doesn't mean that
we're always going to be
isolated in the five.
So what's the best vote
moving forward,
in addition to what happened
at the previous Tribal?
Because we have
that information now.
So, Drea, the Rocksroy vote
could influence this vote.
DREA:
Yeah, definitely.
And I was so proud because,
you know, like,
we have four Black contestants
in Survivor.
And then it always
happens where, at one point,
the Black contestants get
booted out, boom, boom, boom.
And then it's exactly
what this is right now.
So, yeah, I'm pissed.
So, do you think
it's race-related?
I think it's just subconsciously
a little bit of that,
unfortunately, but...
I see now I have to play
the game a little harder now.
I can tell you right now
I'm playing my idol tonight
so that I can stay in this game.
I'm not gonna let that happen
to another one of us--
point-blank.
It's a reset for me.
This was a game changer.
Wow. Tori, this Tribal is alive.
People are changing their minds.
People are declaring,
"I'm gonna play an idol."
The rain is starting
to pick up even more.
Now we got a conversation going.
Yeah, I mean, I support Drea
wanting to play her idol
if she feels like
she's making a stand.
I don't think it's necessary,
but...
That's because
she's not in my shoes.
-But that's okay.
-TORI: No, I know,
but it doesn't change my vote,
so...
DREA:
I'm playing it
so I can stay in the game,
and then I'm gonna
strategically play the game
how it should be played.
PROBST:
And, Tori,
so far, you're the only one
not in this conversation.
Yeah.
PROBST:
Is that okay?
TORI: I've learned
to adapt and be flexible.
If I'm paranoid,
emotional, crazy,
people aren't gonna
trust me, so...
I can only do what I can do.
(laughs)
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
MARYANNE:
I cannot write her name down,
-and I'm so sorry.
-It's okay, it's very emotional.
MARYANNE:
No, no, I literally can't.
'Cause it's, like,
you know what, everyone can hear
what I'm saying. Okay,
I'll just say it out loud.
It's, like, look,
Chanelle goes out.
Okay, that's fine,
that's one thing.
Rocksroy goes out,
that's another person.
I write Drea's name out, that's
three Black people in a row.
Okay? And Survivor
isn't just about s-strategy--
it's not.
Survivor is also about
bringing the social world,
big, into a small thing.
If I write Drea's name
right now,
that means that I'm a part of
a perpetuating problem, so...
It's like the same thing
over and over again
-in this game, and it sucks.
-Again and again and again.
-I can't do it.
-DREA: I'm over it.
So, like, we can figure
something else out,
but I, morally,
cannot write her name down.
-That is my line.
-I'm playing my idol,
-so you have to figure
something else out.
-I hear you.
I knew it was coming for me,
so ... that.
Let's play.
JONATHAN:
I don't feel like this is right,
because y'all
-are coming at this
as like we're racist.
-Well, obviously my name...
-No one ever said that.
-(overlapping chatter)
-JONATHAN: Hold on.
Let me... Hold on...
-No one ever said that.
But obviously it was
gonna be me today, right?
-Was it going to be me today?
-JONATHAN: There's nothing...
It doesn't mean that that's
any... has anything to do
-with race, guys.
This is a game.
-No one ever said that.
-MARYANNE: But the thing is...
-JONATHAN: Yes, y'all are.
-DREA: No.
Y'all just said that.
Don't make it seem
like I'm being aggressive.
You are being aggressive.
-Let's calm down.
This is the game, guys.
-This is what always happens...
-JONATHAN: It has nothing
to do with race.
-MARYANNE: Jonathan,
but the thing is, yes,
it is a game,
but there are subconscious bias
that I might have
that you don't know,
because it is subconscious.
-And that plays a part
of the game as well, too.
-No, that's-that's saying
that I'm subconsciously racist,
and that's not true.
DREA:
We never said it was you.
We're saying how we feel.
Just because I'm saying
how I feel, at this moment,
does not mean that you can
make that your problem.
This is my situation, my issue.
I'm addressing it the way
I wanted to address it,
and the reason I wanted to play
was for representation--
because people like me
weren't represented.
That just is a fact.
A lot of times,
minorities get kicked off first
in this game.
And I was hoping that
it wouldn't be the cycle,
and it is, unfortunately.
You are not that person.
I love you.
I adore you.
I... We get along
and stuff like that.
This happens all the time,
where we speak
and then we get shut down
as if, like, we're calling
everyone racist, and I'm not.
PROBST:
Drea, just to make sure
I heard you right,
you're just saying,
"Right now, I'm stepping
"outside of the game
to stand up for something
"that means something to me.
"And within the game,
I have the power to do it,
'cause I have an idol."
DREA:
I came into this game
knowing...
(cries)
...I would have to think
about how I speak,
how I act.
And when we say representation,
it's because people like us
understand each other
and can help others
understand us, right?
So, like, if we go back,
and this is gonna get out
that maybe
they made it into,
like, a racial thing.
And then maybe they're like,
"Oh, well, I don't want that."
I could be there
tomorrow anyway, so...
MARYANNE:
And then, now,
let's say that
we get to the vote,
and both of us are still here,
and no idols are played.
Because I have an idol, too.
I bring it to every Tribal.
I don't think there's any votes
which are going to me tonight,
but I need to play this
so that people who are watching
will know that I didn't make it
another day because of race.
That it wouldn't be fair
if you could hold that,
-believing you wouldn't get
votes because of the topic.
-DREA: You wouldn't be able to.
I, a thousand percent, Jeff,
with a thousand percent
certainty, can tell you
that if both of us don't
play our idols tonight,
there will be someone watching
and saying they used race.
-Nothing is...
off-limits in Survivor...
-Off-limits.
And that's what I'm thinking.
Like, it just sucks.
Like, now it's gonna
become this.
-And it's like...
-LINDSAY: I never
took it that way.
I respect what
both of you are saying.
I respect
this whole conversation.
Like, I've never sat
in their shoes that way,
but I can empathize with them
for having to deal with that
day in and day out with things.
Like, it hurts me that they're
both getting so emotional
and that that vote
brought something
outside of the game into this.
And, Drea, I don't feel like
you were being aggressive.
I think it was absolutely fair
for you to say that.
And it's just, I'm sorry
that they're hurting for that.
MARYANNE:
Like, Jeff, coming to this game,
my biggest fear
wasn't going and, like, using
an advantage or idol correctly.
My biggest fear was that I would
see some sort of injustice
and I would sit down
and do nothing.
And, like, I'm not saying
that it's an injustice
for Chanelle and Rocksroy
to be voted out,
because, like,
I don't know the full story.
But if I let
that pattern continue,
that's an injustice for me and
my experience as a Black woman.
And especially coming on, like,
Survivor, where it's, like,
you know millions of people
will be watching,
it feels like I have to do it,
because who else will?
It's, like, so frustrating
how I have to then
incorporate that to
the way that I play the game.
Even talking to Omar previously,
there's never been a Muslim
person who has made the merge.
And that changes his gameplay--
maybe for the better,
maybe for the worse--
but that changes it.
And some people don't have
to experience that burden
when they go
and they enter the game.
Yes, we all technically have a
one-in-18 shot for the million,
but because we all come
with our burdens,
and we all come
with our privileges,
that one-in-18 might be bigger
or smaller for some people.
And that sucks.
-Wow. That was amazing.
-DREA: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
PROBST:
Jonathan,
how are you feeling now?
JONATHAN:
Um...
(sniffles)
I'm glad that it's cleared up
that it's not the tribe
that has
made them feel this way.
If I could, I would love
to let 'em know that I love 'em.
This isn't about me
hating you or anything.
hating any of you.
-'Cause you know
that I love all of you guys.
-I know that. I know that.
This is a moment
bigger than the game.
Yeah.
And seeing their emotion
is, like, hard for me
to just look past that
and be like,
"Okay, let's get back
to game mode."
I feel like that would minimize
their experience
that they're feeling to be like,
"Oh, hey, by the way,
can we talk?" I don't know.
That's why it just feels wrong.
Yeah, I hear you on that, too.
Yeah.
Is part of what
makes it hard to transition
is that we're now gonna
go through the formality
of walking up these stairs
and in private writing a name
down? Is that part of it?
-Yes.
-Because the other option is,
we can skip
that pomp and circumstance
and keep it here,
meaning it would be
talking about it.
So, would
they turn in their idols
and then we go from there?
Well, I mean,
that's their call, what they do.
Wow.
Good job, guys.
-Good job, y'all.
-MARYANNE: Thank you.
PROBST:
I can settle this quickly.
These are both
hidden immunity idols.
Drea's not going home.
Maryanne is not going home.
So, Lindsay,
what does that mean?
Because Jonathan is also safe.
Sounds like it's me or Tori.
And all I can hope for is that
they want to trust me and
want to go forward with me
and feel like
I'm gonna be a good player
to be alongside them.
Tori, that was
a long look back to me.
Well, I can feel
maybe you guys are
leaning more towards Lindsay.
Is that the vibe I'm getting?
-Yeah, I'm gonna vote for you.
Yeah.
-Is that the vibe I'm getting?
Well, actually
I'd like to know why.
Why would you like
to get rid of me?
'Cause you've been
gunning for me since Ika.
Not true, but okay.
You've lied to me.
Okay, yes.
I don't have as good of
a relationship with you.
Uh-huh. Than with her?
Right.
TORI:
Okay. What are your thoughts?
The game is still on, and
I don't want to vote you out,
but part of the game's that
I have to vote someone out,
and in this moment right now,
this is the best step for me.
Which sucks.
Well, I want to do this,
and I'm gonna go
play my Shot in the Dark.
And we can go from there.
Okay, so you formally
are telling me
that your votes
will be for Tori?
-JONATHAN: Right.
-LINDSAY: Yeah.
PROBST:
Okay. And, Tori, you're saying
you're gonna go play
your Shot in the Dark?
I got to do what I can
at this point. (scoffs)
That's totally fair.
Okay.
Very unusual Tribal Council.
Here's what it means.
It's Tori, unless she can get
the Shot in the Dark
that says you're safe.
In which case,
Lindsay, you're going home.
All right, Tori,
go up, drop your die,
try the Shot in the Dark.
♪ ♪
All right, Tori,
I'll take it from you.
So if this says you're safe,
you're safe,
Lindsay, you're going home.
♪ ♪
Tori, you are...
...not safe.
-Sorry, Tori.
-It's okay. I prayed about it.
-I knew God could
have made me safe,
-but my time's up.
-Bye, Tori. I'm sorry, Tori.
PROBST:
Need to bring me your torch.
-Bye, Tori.
-TORI: You played a wild game.
♪ ♪
-Tori, the tribe has spoken.
-No!
-Yes.
-(Tori groans)
-Time for you to go.
-Have fun, y'all.
-Love you so much.
-Bye.
-Bye, guys.
-See you, Tor.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
-Hope you can stay dry.
-Ugh.
God literally has shown up in
so many crazy ways in this game,
and I knew
that if it was my time to stay,
that I was going
to pick the right scroll,
and so I honestly am walking
away with a lot of peace,
a lot of gratefulness
because I can freaking do
a lot more
than I thought I could.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
OMAR: You have to pick the
right person at the right time.
Otherwise, you'll be
the next person out.
MIKE:
His head's in the guillotine,
ready to be lopped off.
Guess what, Lindsay. I'm open.
-(laughing)
-He has to go.
I am extremely,
extremely proud
of Drea and Maryanne.
Survivor sometimes can be tough
to understand
because it's playing games,
but it's serious
in terms of social interactions,
what baggage you come in with,
and what we're sharing together.
I am in immense gratitude
to have been able
to be a part
of Survivor 42, truly am.
(roars)