LINDSAY:
That was wild.
-MIKE: You can breathe.
-Oh, my God.
-I am so happy I'm here
with all of you.
-MARYANNE: Yeah.
I need to give everybody a hug.
Oh.
Nobody wanted to see you go.
Oh, my God, I'm so, so happy.
-Wow. How wild was that?
-MIKE: Hey, Lindsay...
That was the best Tribal Council
ever. Ever, ever, ever.
I couldn't believe that
I actually picked the right box.
That was awesome.
And then Drea pulls out
her advantage, which says
that she can ask anybody
one question--
if they have an advantage,
or they have an idol.
And they have to be honest
if they do,
and if they do,
they have to give it to her.
Mike, do you have an idol?
No.
I can verify
Mike is telling the truth.
Oh, my gosh!
Omar, you're the only person
I told the secret to, and I want
-everyone else to know that.
-(Hai gasps)
(laughs)
It was a such a great play.
So, she didn't get to use it.
The vote went to Drea.
She's out.
Now my amulet is now
a hidden immunity idol,
which I have to use at six.
So I plan
on using that tomorrow.
So, win, win, win.
Great day for me.
Dude, crazy lows, crazy highs.
-This game's insane.
-MARYANNE: Mm-hmm.
-LINDSAY: Drea took it awesome.
-She took it really well.
OMAR:
Tonight went
perfectly.
Like, I wanted to unleash
my evil laugh, like...
(laughs)
Because my plan
just worked out so well.
OMAR:
My relationship
with Mike right now
is right where I want it,
because he sees me
as his savior in the game.
Like, I saved his life
and saved his idol
and gave it back to him.
OMAR:
So my goal
in the next day is to pull
Jonathan and Mike apart,
make them distrust each other,
and know
that each other has to go next
so that when the time comes,
I can pick a side.
And, you know,
it'll be a clean swipe--
Mike or Jonathan out.
-No, I didn't see them.
-Oh, Omie.
(Omar laughs softly)
JONATHAN:
Hey.
MIKE:
We made a great move,
it worked out, but,
at the end of the day,
people want to get to the end,
and they're gonna look
for their best possible angle.
And I know that Omar's
afraid of me at the final
because I'm too likable.
I wouldn't want to take me
to the end at this point,
so I get it. I would try
and cut me loose, too.
So I have to do
what comes natural.
I have to cut Omar loose.
So...
So, it would be like...
-The merge started, yeah.
-Okay?
Mm-hmm.
MIKE:
Right now, I need to prove
to Maryanne that Omar
is not her pawn,
and he's working against her.
I'm setting the game plan
in motion.
I just got to nourish it,
and in this game,
you got to not go too fast,
not be down their throat,
let them
make their own decision,
but you give 'em a little nudge.
MARYANNE:
Mike is right.
At Tribal Council, what the jury
saw was Omar just go
from a caterpillar
to a butterfly.
This was someone who was sitting
in the background and, like,
boom, he's the reason
why Drea wa-was gone.
And I'm like, "There is no way
that I can beat him."
So I'm thinking,
being like, "Okay, there always
comes a time in this game
"when you have people
that you trust,
"but the people that you trust,
if you know they can beat you,
you have to do something."
Okay.
Oh.
MARYANNE:
I'm thinking right now
about, like, backstabbing one
of my alliance, and I'm, like,
this is honestly a hard decision
'cause I know Omar
and I love Omar
and I trust Omar,
and Omar's one of the people
who's grounded me
these past 22 days.
But if I don't make this move,
I'm not going to win,
and it's terrifying.
Yeah.
(Mike sighs)
Because...
MARYANNE:
Mm-hmm.
LINDSAY: My plan now is,
I want Jonathan gone.
I can't have him here
long enough
that he has another chance
to win another immunity.
His ability to win challenges
is a huge threat.
I don't want him
to keep winning challenges.
He's my main nemesis in that.
Like, if he's gone,
I will win them.
Mm-hmm.
"But I can't promise you yet."
She was very honest with me.
So she...
What was her word?
MIKE:
No, no. Come over.
We're talking about...
what's going on.
You know, we're just talking
-about with the vote last night.
-Oh, yeah.
JONATHAN:
At this point,
I don't trust Lindsay
and Omar anymore.
Omar thinks that I don't see it,
Lindsay thinks
that I don't see it, but
they're working together
very closely.
I know, right?
JONATHAN:
I'm not letting anyone see
that I'm upset
about what happened last night--
that Omar used a move that
made him go way, way higher
in the jury vote,
and I'm not letting Lindsay see
that I'm not happy
she's back, you know,
because the truth is,
they both have to go.
If I'm going to win this game,
I need to get them out.
-Final six.
-MIKE: Yeah.
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
JONATHAN:
Taku four has made it
to the final six,
and that's as far
as they're going to go.
We're not going to go
any further together. It's...
it's time to break up.
Come on in.
All right, ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
(all assent)
PROBST:
For today's challenge,
you're going to spin
to unspool a coil of rope.
You'll then make your way
through a series of obstacles
and collect a key.
You'll use that key
to unlock puzzle pieces
and use the pieces
to solve a block puzzle.
First to finish
wins reward. Want to know
what you're playing for?
-(all assent)
-Today, you're in charge.
You will have a choice.
You can choose sustenance--
grilled chicken and veggies--
or you can choose decadence--
chocolate cake and cookies,
which might be the sugar
that you crave.
-Ooh.
-You'll be in charge.
Worth playing for?
-Absolutely.
-Yes.
-PROBST: All right.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
-Let's do it, final six!
-(whooping)
-Yes.
Here we go. For reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
-You're spinning to unspool.
-Aah! (laughing)
-The faster you go,
the quicker you get there.
-Oh!
-(yells)
-But the dizzier.
Maryanne takes the first fall.
Still smiling.
Jonathan in the lead.
-And it's Lindsay and Mike.
-Aah! I can't see anything!
-Oh, my gosh.
-Maryanne is off the course.
(Maryanne exclaims)
Jonathan across the net.
There goes Lindsay.
There goes Maryanne.
Aah!
PROBST:
Lindsay tearing up those knees.
Man!
Now you got to get on the beam.
If you fall off,
you got to start again.
Maryanne's dizzy. Jonathan's
dizzy. He's coming back.
Here comes Romeo. Maryanne is
now trying to unspin
to reverse her dizziness.
Never seen anything like it.
Jonathan untying his key.
(gasps)
Lindsay trying
to stay on the beam
by using the rope to balance.
Mike drops.
He's got to go back.
Jonathan first across.
He's got the key.
Start unlocking those pieces.
Lindsay's good.
And Lindsay is across.
Start working on your puzzle.
Omar working on his key,
-Mike working on his key.
-MARYANNE: Ooh.
Omar has his key,
and you're across. You're good.
You're good, Romeo.
Mike's got a rhythm now.
Just get across. You're good.
You're good. Maryanne can
start working on her puzzle.
You're building a compass rose
piece by piece,
and you're studying as you go,
making sure it's right.
If you're right,
it's just a matter of time
before disappointment smacks you
in the face.
Sometimes it's fun
to just listen
to the sounds of the challenge.
(soft muttering)
This is hard.
PROBST:
Maryanne continues
to add pieces.
She was dead last to the puzzle,
and now she's down to a few
pieces left if she's right.
What am I doing wrong?
There's something wrong.
PROBST:
Now Omar with momentum.
It's now Omar in the lead,
Maryanne trying to catch Omar.
(gasps)
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
Omar with another piece.
♪ ♪
No, that's wrong.
-Jeff?
-PROBST: Omar thinks he has it.
-How confident are you?
-100%?
-Omar wins!
-LINDSAY: Nice!
-MIKE: Nice job, Omar.
-Great job!
-PROBST: Nice job!
-Oh, good job.
-MIKE: I had it, too.
I was right... I finally got
to the right track.
LINDSAY:
Nice.
Great job. I'm proud of you.
Good job.
Omar, come on over.
-Whew. (laughs)
-Whew. Good job, Omar.
-OMAR: Thank you.
-Nice job, Omie.
I never thought
I'd be next to you.
-Really?
-No.
-PROBST: You didn't think so?
-You surprise yourself out here.
-Yeah.
-You don't know what you're
capable of
until you have to do it.
-So...
-What surprised you about today?
Which part of this challenge?
I thought I was going
to blow through the puzzle,
but it was actually
really, really hard.
And my niece is afraid
to try anything new.
And I was terrified of
all the challenges, and I hope
she sees this,
and it inspires her
earlier in life
to take those risks.
-'Cause she's only eight.
-What's your...?
-What's your niece's name?
-Hannah.
Okay, so, Hannah, you're eight,
and there are millions
of other eight, nine,
ten-year-olds just like you.
Hear that message because
that is what Survivor is about.
-It is about pushing yourself
to your personal limit...
-Yeah.
and then seeing
if you got one more step.
That's what you've been doing
for 22 days. Today,
you did it.
You're in charge.
-You have a couple
of decisions to make.
-Okay.
You're going to decide,
do you want sustenance--
which is
grilled chicken and veggies--
or if you want chocolate cake
and cookies.
-Here's the additional twist.
-Yeah.
The invitation
with grilled chicken and veggies
includes two players.
-Okay.
-The invitation
with chocolate cake and cookies
includes three.
-Oh, man.
-So now you have
a very big dilemma.
OMAR:
You know,
we're all really out here
and really, really deprived,
so I think
I'm going to give
some more people...
And I'm really sorry
for the two I don't choose.
All right,
so you're going to take
chocolate cake and cookies,
and you're going to bring
three people with you,
which means
two will not participate
in this.
There's one person here
who's eaten nothing,
so I can't not pick Romeo.
-MIKE: Good job, Romeo.
-MARYANNE: Yeah!
-PROBST: Come on over, Romeo.
-MIKE: Yeah, Romeo.
The second person
I'm gonna pick is Maryanne.
She's been struggling, and
I think she could use a meal.
-PROBST: Come on over, Maryanne.
-Thank you.
PROBST:
One spot left,
so either Lindsay,
Mike or Jonathan is going
to join you,
and the other two will not.
For me, at this point, honestly,
it's really about who I think
would benefit from it the most,
and I want the other two
to eat all of our rice today.
So, Mike, come and eat
some chocolate cake.
-(applause)
-LINDSAY: Nice job, Mike.
-Thank.. thank you.
-Thank you, Omar.
-OMAR: You're welcome.
PROBST:
All right,
everybody heading back to camp.
You four are gonna have
a nice, decadent afternoon.
You two, got nothing for you.
-Thank you, Mr. Jeff.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-OMAR: Thank you.
-Nice job.
-Thank you.
To win a Survivor challenge?
It felt like I was
at the top of the world.
But the caveat is
which reward I picked.
You know, it changes the number
of people you bring with you.
So, for me, I thought
it would go a longer way
towards building relationships,
giving more people
some sustenance, and I hope
there's no backlash
to the decision I made.
-OMAR: Wow.
-ROMEO: Wow.
MIKE:
Omar, you take the first,
whatever you want, pal.
-OMAR: Holy cow.
-MARYANNE: Uh, cheers.
-ROMEO: Wait. Cheers.
-MIKE: Cheers.
-OMAR: Cheers.
-Cheers. Thank you, Omar.
-You're welcome.
-Oh, my God!
OMAR: Today's reward challenge
was exhilarating because
I just won a Survivor challenge,
which I never thought
I would ever do in my life.
ROMEO:
Come on.
MARYANNE:
Mm-hmm.
Romeo, I'm very happy for you.
-MARYANNE: Mm-hmm.
-Thank you for bringing me back
-from the dead.
-(laughter)
-OMAR: Well, you-you deserve it.
-Mm-hmm.
Everybody here deserves it.
I just feel bad for them.
I know how... gassed
Jonathan is,
and Lindsay chose me
for the other one.
But I was like
"I'm just trying to be fair."
At this point,
Mike and Jonathan are
two very open targets
that I want out of the game.
So leaving Jonathan behind
at camp was
maybe to deprive him
a little bit,
make him less energetic
for tomorrow's challenge
'cause I need to beat him.
No, I'm not bitter at all.
I understand the reason.
He's going to try
to get them comfortable.
-Mm-hmm.
-And then
blindside Mike is the plan.
That's what I'm thinking.
I didn't get
any confirmation on that,
but I assume
that would be the plan.
JONATHAN:
When Lindsay and I are
discussing the vote over rice,
we are obviously trying
to fool each other.
And right now
Mike and I are very tight, but
I don't think Lindsay really
wants to vote for Mike. No.
I think she would much rather
vote me out
because I'm a bigger threat
when it comes to challenges.
So I'm just trying
to get her comfortable,
and she's trying
to get me comfortable.
Hopefully, I'm doing
a better job than she's doing
because I know
that she's up to something.
-I'm gonna lay down.
-Okay.
-Take it easy.
Jonathan thinks
that Mike is going home.
That's great because
people actually
want Jonathan out first.
The only thing that's going
to be a real challenge is, like,
if Jonathan wins immunity,
Mike is abs...
is absolutely the target.
Hi!
So I need him
to feel comfortable
that it's Jonathan going home.
(insects buzzing)
-Am I safe?
-It has to be Jonathan,
is basically what needs
to happen.
Okay. Am I safe?
-I'm asking you straight up.
-I'm ask...
I'm telling you, if it's...
If Jonathan doesn't win,
you are safe.
MIKE:
Am I feeling safe?
Absolutely not.
I have to go with my gut.
My gut says
Omar is now gunning for me.
-You are the next biggest threat
after Jonathan.
-Okay.
That-that's how some people
feel. Me and Omar don't.
MIKE:
And Lindsay-- she's playing
the game with-with Omar.
I can't be 100%
positive, but I can't see
how they're not.
I'll let you know
if you need to use your idol,
-uh, tomorrow night.
-Okay.
MIKE:
In talking with Lindsay,
it clicked in my head.
Lindsay has an idol.
When Drea went out,
her-her amulet became
a full idol.
You... How long can
you-you... you can use...?
Okay.
So at this point, I have
to obviously protect myself.
So I think my best move now
is to tell Jonathan and Maryanne
that Lindsay has an idol and
make sure they're on my side.
Uh-uh.
Mm-hmm.
MIKE:
Anybody has to win this one
except for Lindsay
or Omar, of course, because
what if she says, "Let me keep
my alliance strong with Omar.
"I'll give him my idol,
and now we're both safe"?
That would be
a very, very big damper
on my plans.
-And so, if they take me out
first, guess who's next.
-Me.
-If they take you out first,
guess who's next.
-You.
-'Cause...
-Exactly.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
This vote is extremely huge
for me.
Maryanne has two votes,
so we need to work together.
And I'm thinking,
"I'll make a deal with you.
"If you save my life
"and help me get to five,
I have the idol
that'll help me and you
get to four."
The oldest and the youngest.
-The bookends.
MARYANNE:
So, Mike tells me that he wants
to play his idol
for me at the final five.
But I already have an idol.
And I'm here like,
"Are you kidding me?"
This means
that I'm double safe, so
I'm on for this plan for Omar.
Like, we have to get him out
as soon as we can,
and that means
at the next vote.
And even if he wins immunity,
we still have the votes.
Right. Who...?
Yeah, who do we go for then?
-This we have to talk about.
-Um...
Uh, Jonathan's on our side.
Then Lindsay? 'Cause, look...
No, Lindsay has immunity.
Lindsay has immunity?
-For final six?
-Yes. It's only good
till final six.
No.
MARYANNE:
So, Mike tells me
that Lindsay has some sort
of amulet,
which is a hidden immunity idol.
So that means that, like,
I'm out of the loop with her.
And, like, at this point,
my heart dropped
because I thought we were close.
But basically I'm just
like a sacrificial lamb to her.
So, I just have to keep on
holding into that hope
that my move that I've been
thinking about won't be ruined
and that I'll be able
to show people
that I'm a real contender
in this game,
not just a goat to be herded.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Still smiling.
Always.
PROBST:
Day 23 of the best,
worst experience of your life.
Yeah, it's true.
PROBST:
And you're still smiling.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-(all assent)
-First things first, Jonathan.
I got to take it back.
I'm coming back.
All right.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race over
a series of obstacles,
then across a bridge
containing puzzle steps.
You'll use those steps
to build a staircase.
You'll then maneuver a bag
of balls to the top
of a very tall tower.
Once there,
you'll use those balls
to finish a table maze.
First player
to land both their balls...
wins immunity, guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
-(Jonathan sighs)
-Losers, Tribal Council,
where, after 23 days, your dream
of winning this show
will come to an end,
and the only thing you will have
to do with the million dollars
is deciding who gets it.
Big, big stakes.
-Shall we do it? All right.
-Yeah!
-Absolutely.
-We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
-(whooping)
All right, here we go.
For a guaranteed spot
in the final five.
Survivors ready. Go!
First you're going
over these obstacles.
(grunting)
Doesn't matter how.
Just get over 'em.
Jonathan in the lead,
Lindsay on his tail.
There goes Mike.
Now you're untying the steps
you need
to build your staircase.
They're in batches of four.
Jonathan's out first
with his first four planks.
Everybody's getting
their planks together now.
We're tight early on.
Jonathan in a bit
of an early lead.
Here comes Romeo. Look at that!
Lindsay. Here comes Mike.
Now we got Omar.
-Let's go, Maryanne.
-(grunting)
They will go in one of the first
four spots on your staircase.
The question is,
which spots do they go in?
This is where
time is gained or lost.
And look at that.
Lindsay now in the lead.
She's getting
her next batch of pieces.
There goes Maryanne.
Omar's in on it.
Jonathan falling behind now.
He lost the lead.
There goes Mike.
Lindsay has her next four.
She's heading back.
Omar has his next four.
He's heading back.
Jonathan has his untied.
The next four pieces go
in the next four steps.
Jonathan is back.
Here comes Mike.
First you have to get
the pieces.
Then you have
to solve the puzzle.
He heads out.
Lindsay now heads out.
It's Omar and Lindsay
right now side by side.
Jonathan's done.
He's heading back.
Mike's good.
Omar, in the lead, continues.
He's back first.
Lindsay right behind.
Jonathan trying to get in on it.
It's day 23 of Survivor 42.
-Six players left.
-(Lindsay groans)
You got to step up,
or you go home.
Omar first to the top.
Lindsay right behind.
Now you have
to maneuver the balls
you need for the table maze
to get to the top of the tower.
Jonathan is stuck. Something is
not right. What is it?
You got to find the way it fits.
Mike is through. He's now
working on his table maze balls.
Lindsay working her way
to the top.
Omar working his way to the top.
Lindsay going to get
to the top first.
She's got her ring. She's up.
It's now Lindsay in the lead.
Jonathan on his last piece
of the staircase.
Jonathan's now up.
He's working on his.
It's Jonathan, Omar and Mike
trying to get to the top.
Lindsay's already there.
Romeo working on his staircase.
Maryanne
on her last four pieces.
Jonathan now up here.
Here comes Mike.
Here comes Omar.
We got four people
on the table maze.
This is where the challenge
will be won or lost, right here.
Everybody dead even
right now. You've got to land
the first ball,
the closest ball, first.
Lindsay very close.
But around the corner now.
Lindsay drops.
She's got to start again.
Mike drops.
-(Maryanne groaning)
-Keep working, Maryanne.
Jonathan has won
two individual immunities.
Lindsay has won one.
Omar and Mike have yet
to win individual immunity.
♪ ♪
Jonathan very close
to landing that first ball,
and he does. Jonathan now
in the lead with his first ball.
One ball left.
It's Lindsay very close
to landing her first ball.
And she has it.
Now it's Lindsay and Jonathan.
Mike has to start again.
Omar trying
to get something going.
Here comes Romeo.
He's gonna get in on it.
Jonathan working around
a tough part of this maze,
one of the toughest corners
to maneuver.
Lindsay right behind him.
They are side by side,
same spot in the maze.
Almost same spot where their
balls are, on opposite sides.
Both maneuvering the same corner
at the same time.
Lindsay drops. She's got
to go back. Jonathan makes it.
Jonathan has
one small section left.
The most difficult section
of the maze.
Jonathan very close
to winning it.
-Shoot, Jonathan. Idiot.
-PROBST: Jonathan drops.
Loses everything.
Romeo, no luck.
Mike trying
to get something going.
Here comes Maryanne.
Keep working, Maryanne.
Now Lindsay
in that three-quarter spot.
Jonathan right there with her.
Jonathan and Lindsay
once again
side by side in a challenge,
in a showdown
right now to win it.
Jonathan is around the corner
first,
and he navigated it safely.
There goes Lindsay.
She's navigated it.
Jonathan can sense it.
Lindsay on the edge, saves it.
Jonathan right on her tail.
Lindsay very close to winning.
It's in, and it's out.
Jonathan drops.
-And it's in! Lindsay does it!
-(screams) Oh, yeah!
Individual immunity.
-(exhales)
-PROBST: Safe tonight
at Tribal Council
-and guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
-Nice job, man.
PROBST:
Wow, what a challenge.
That was close.
Lindsay, come on over.
-Good job, Linds.
-(applause)
For the second time this season,
individual immunity is yours.
You are safe tonight,
cannot be voted out,
which means you have
a spot in the final five.
As for the rest of you,
a different story.
Somebody's dream
of winning Survivor 42
will be over.
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody gonna
head over to the jury.
It is also the last time the
Shot in the Dark can be used--
tonight's Tribal Council.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
-See you tonight at Tribal.
Congrats.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Jeff.
I didn't want Lindsay to win
because I know
that Lindsay has an idol
that's only good up till six.
That's tonight.
If she plays the idol,
Omar is now safe.
So I'm thinking plan B
got to come into effect.
♪ ♪
MARYANNE:
Congrats!
MIKE: Great job.
Another great job by Lindsay.
-Thank you.
-MIKE: Great job.
Thanks. That was a fun one.
I feel freaking awesome.
Came down to me and Jonathan
at the end once again.
Jonathan, how close were you
to landing the second one?
-JONATHAN: Very close.
-Aw.
But close in this game
means nothing.
-Bummer.
-Good job, Lindsay.
LINDSAY:
Jonathan is this
giant Goliath of a human.
And then you have me,
half his size and a female,
and I freaking won it.
I won that challenge.
Like, that's awesome.
Like, that's so cool.
MIKE:
Great job.
MARYANNE:
Oh, gosh.
JONATHAN: Lindsay winning
was the number one thing
I did not want to happen.
LINDSAY:
You want to taste some?
It really just tastes
like a cucumber.
JONATHAN:
Because now she can use
her idol to help Omar.
And if Omar doesn't go home,
then Mike and I
are the biggest targets.
So Mike and I
are gonna vote Romeo.
Just coconut is the only thing
that's been in here.
LINDSAY:
Jonathan thinks
that Mike is going home,
but all of us have been thinking
that if Jonathan loses,
he is leaving tonight.
So that is the plan
that I hope to just sink in.
-Jonathan needs to go.
-Okay.
-Jonathan's a huge liability
to stay.
-Exactly.
Like, the fact that
he didn't win today
-was, like...
-We have to take that opport...
-LINDSAY: We have to.
-Okay, yeah. So...
LINDSAY:
I don't see why
anyone would veer off from
this plan to vote Jonathan out.
Yes.
Like, that has to...
That's, like, a no-brainer.
ROMEO:
Jonathan has been a target
since early on.
I've been on the chopping block
every Tribal Council.
So it only makes sense
to get rid of him,
because then
the backup person would be who?
Most likely me.
...are 100% on Jonathan.
-So you need to be
on Jonathan, too.
-Okay. Okay.
We're heading into
Tribal Council in a few hours,
and right now the plan is set.
Jonathan's gonna go home,
and if there's a backup vote,
you know, have that be Mike.
It's definitely not me tonight?
No, definitely not you.
It's Mike going after Jonathan,
Jonathan going after Mike.
And if that's the case,
our plan is foolproof.
Mm-hmm.
This could be perfect.
Everybody is on board
to get rid of Jonathan tonight.
Yeah.
LINDSAY:
Tonight, if anything is crazy,
I do have my amulet,
which is a hidden immunity idol.
But I'd rather not play it,
because once somebody
plays an idol,
it usually goes right back out
for somebody to find.
And we don't want
to worry about an idol
being back in circulation
on the island.
-Yeah, okay.
-LINDSAY: Jonathan will be out
as planned,
and then me and Omar
have a nice
cruising out to final four
and make it to the end.
(exhales sharply)
MARYANNE:
Flame.
Right now, I'm feeling that
Omar can win this whole thing.
And that's not a feeling
that I want to have.
JONATHAN:
Flame on.
MARYANNE:
I feel dejected,
but I want to show that I'm here
to play my game,
and I'm here to win.
I have my extra vote.
I can go with
Omar and Lindsay's plan
and use my extra vote
the way they want me to,
or I can go with my plan
and use my extra vote
the way I want to.
So there's a chance
that this plan to take out Omar
-can still happen.
-Listen to me.
Okay.
This is our time to take a risk,
but a big move.
-Okay. Okay.
-This is what
you're going to do, okay?
You're going to tell Jonathan,
"Vote Omar."
Then...
-I know for a fact Jonathan
is voting Romeo with me.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
-And if you throw two votes
Romeo, and I vote Romeo,
there's nothing anybody can do.
Omar's next one. He has no,
he has no protection.
-It's me, you...
-But what if he wins tomorrow?
I want to vote for Omar.
I could use my idol
tonight, but
it's not gonna happen.
I need my idol tomorrow
to make sure that I get to four.
It's my life. My life's hanging
on the balance.
I'm putting my life
in your hands. Please.
MARYANNE:
I can't promise you right now.
I still need to think about it.
That's the thing.
MIKE:
Lindsay wins
the immunity challenge.
She doesn't need
her immunity idol.
I'm thinking Lindsay
gives Omar her immunity idol.
It would make them both safe.
So the easy thing is,
put four votes on Romeo.
Simple, except Maryanne
wants to play Survivor 18.0,
instead of 2.0.
And having my fate
in her hands
is scary.
-But you're not voting
for me, right?
-I'm not.
Okay.
-Okay.
Like, I gave you my word,
and I'm keeping my word.
-Okay.
-MARYANNE: Mike is just trying
to play it safe,
'cause people can feel
the final five.
And when people can feel it,
and they don't have
that necklace on their neck,
they get paranoid.
But I have my extra vote,
and my two votes
give me a lot of power tonight.
Nothing from this
conversation can leak.
-Nothing.
-I swear.
-We have six votes.
-Yes.
(gasps)
-Oh, my God.
-Used... And it has to be used
this Tribal.
So that means
that us four are five votes.
This is what we need to do.
Me, you, Jonathan, Mike
vote Omar,
because Omar will win.
I think I have Romeo on board,
but I still have
a lot of work to do.
-This is simple.
-Mm-hmm.
You two do Romeo.
Romeo and I do Omar.
-That is three.
-You do your two?
Yeah, I will do two on Omar.
-Okay, do we trust Romeo
to vote Omar?
-Okay.
I do. I've talked to him.
I literally trust him.
JONATHAN:
I'm not confident in Romeo
at all.
And he's been
very back and forth
throughout the whole game.
And if he votes me, then
I could go home.
So I think
it would be a dumb move
not to vote out Romeo.
MIKE:
So here's my question.
Is it best we just go along
with whatever they say
to all of us,
and we silently
throw our votes on Romeo?
Then we're all guaranteed
to be here tomorrow,
and then we get Omar
tomorrow night.
-And then, and then...
no, no, listen to me.
-Oh, my God.
MARYANNE:
Jonathan and Mike
are underestimating me.
I'm trying to play
a good move to take out Omar,
-and they're just
not getting it.
-Look.
If we all vote for Romeo,
Romeo is gone,
but then our way to the end
is more difficult.
This is a risk
that we have to take.
I'm going guns blazing to go
and make my move on Omar,
but I am getting frustrated
because I got to make moves
happen for me to get to the end.
And the only wrench in my plan,
if I don't get guys
who are literally, like,
a foot taller than me
to go and listen to me,
then my whole plan
is just gonna go up in smoke.
♪ ♪
(thunder rumbling)
PROBST:
All right.
Let's get into it. Wow.
I can feel intensity tonight.
You were all
looking at me like this.
(laughter)
Omar, is that just being eager,
or was it a crazy day?
Or are you anticipating
the rain? What is it?
I think it's
a little bit of the fact
that last Tribal Council
was outrageous.
And then we're also
dreading the rain that's coming
and wondering, is this Tribal
gonna be outrageous?
PROBST:
Well, I will say,
just since you've sat down,
the rain has
increased in intensity
-by about fourfold, right, Mike?
You can feel it.
-MIKE: Oh.
-Of course.
-PROBST: It's coming.
It matches the intensity
of the place.
Quite frankly, I'm at the point
now, this is past calculus.
There's nowhere to hide,
and there's only very few people
you can talk to.
PROBST:
Romeo, you get back to camp.
Lindsay has her second
individual immunity win.
You know she's not going home.
What was the feeling today?
I think the dynamic
is changing a little bit.
I think people are
starting to think about
who they might want to sit
next to in the final three,
as opposed to who they want
to vote off next.
So it's different thinking.
It's a different feel,
and I think people are thinking
more long-term
than short-term now.
PROBST:
Lindsay,
do you concur with that?
That maybe
the shift is happening?
Absolutely. He's-- was spot-on.
Uh, like, at this point,
you're kind of figuring out
what are my best odds
to feel the most comfortable
in the final three.
So then, Omar, what does that do
in terms of who is the threat?
Who do I need to get out?
OMAR:
I don't know if I agree
with either of them,
to be honest.
I think people have been
playing for the long-term game
since the beginning.
Some of the people there,
you know, they may have
been trustworthy allies,
but people didn't want
to go to the end with them.
And that's why they're there.
So I think
that that trend will continue.
It's just that
there's fewer people
and less room to hide now.
PROBST:
Maryanne,
where do you sit on that?
Is there a shift happening?
MARYANNE:
I feel as if it depends
on where your position
was in the tribe.
If you're someone
who's on the bottom,
you might be thinking, "No, I
have to think self-preservation,
self-preservation."
And when you finally feel
a little bit more wiggle room,
that's when you're like,
"Okay, now I can think
about the endgame."
Lindsay, how confident are you
about tonight's vote?
I-I feel confident
in tonight's vote
with the discussions
that I've had.
So it's really more so
if they feel equally
as confident
that I was being honest
with what my discussion was.
Mike, that's
a very honest answer
to actually say, "I'm good.
"I don't know if
the other people will trust me,
and if they don't,
it might not go my way."
I-I live my life on trust.
I trust who I put my, uh,
fate in their hands
and their fate in my hands.
I trust in who I believe in.
PROBST:
Omar, what'd you read
into Lindsay's answer?
I mean,
I think that answer is...
just sums up
the game of Survivor.
You never know if
what you say to other people
is gonna be taken with truth
or with a falsity.
If I'm telling you something,
and you don't believe me,
then you could
change everything up.
So I'm Survivor confident
in what's gonna happen tonight,
but every time you're Survivor
confident, you could be wrong.
So I'm open to that, too.
PROBST:
So, Jonathan, if you're right,
and the vote goes the way
you want it to go,
what impact will it have
when you guys get back to camp?
JONATHAN:
Like, if it works out,
nobody lies, and everything
is all hunky-dory,
then that'll be the first Tribal
where that's ever happened.
It's not that easy.
Something is happening where
somebody's being lied to.
There is gonna be people
that keep their trust,
and there are gonna be people
that lie.
Lindsay, do you agree with that?
I mean,
unless it's a clean sweep,
then, yeah, somebody else
will definitely be upset.
And usually, I don't think
there's been a clean sweep yet.
MARYANNE:
Mm-mm.
Not with the Shot in the Dark.
Why?
'Cause, like, you don't know
who's gonna play it.
This is the last time
we can play it.
And then, also,
there's idols in this game, too.
So then, after, if you're trying
to do a clean sweep, and then
that person who you're doing
a clean sweep for has an idol,
then you're up the river, too,
'cause that person chooses.
You can never do
a clean sweep anymore.
And, Omar, the tricky part
about that is,
when there's only
six people voting anyway,
if you start splitting votes,
it gets very scary.
Yeah, and, I mean, there's
definitely the possibility
of a hidden immunity idol
coming out,
so we have to be really careful
if we don't have one.
I don't have one,
so I'm extra nervous
when you call out for
"Does anyone have
an advantage to play?"
Because I could be on the
receiving end of a blindside.
All right, it is time to vote.
Lindsay, you're up.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Jonathan.
Romeo.
One vote Jonathan,
one vote Romeo.
Jonathan.
Two votes Jonathan,
one vote Romeo.
Romeo. Tied again.
Two votes Jonathan,
two votes Romeo.
♪ ♪
Omar.
That's two votes Jonathan,
two votes Romeo,
one vote Omar.
Omar.
Two votes Jonathan,
-two votes Romeo,
two votes Omar.
-(mouthing)
One vote left.
13th person voted out and
the sixth member of our jury...
Omar.
Wow. Good job.
-(laughs)
-MARYANNE: I'm sorry.
Good job, brother.
(chuckles)
Good job. I love you, brother.
-MARYANNE: Sorry, Omar.
-Love you, buddy.
-(chuckles)
(exhales sharply)
Good job. Good job.
That was wild.
-Omar, the tribe has spoken.
-(chuckles)
Good job.
(chuckles)
-Love you, Omar.
-Bye, Omar.
-Love you guys. See you soon.
-(clapping)
♪ ♪
Congratulations.
You've made it
to the final five,
and you'll be starting
over again at a new camp.
Grab your torches, head out.
Good night.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Next time, on the season finale
of Survivor...
JONATHAN:
It's gonna be a battle royale.
LINDSAY:
I ran around like a banshee.
I made a fake idol. See?
...won't be here tomorrow.
This challenge is on.
I'm fighting to the bitter end.
Maryanne got me.
She got me good.
And I knew playing with her
was like playing with fire,
and I should have
listened to my gut.
But I was Survivor confident,
and that is the worst thing
you can be.
But I still had a blast,
and this was the best experience
of my life.
(roars)