-(coughs)
-ROCKSROY: Yeah.
See how long it lasts.
That was very hard.
I don't want to do that again.
ROCKSROY:
I feel really terrible
about Zach going.
You know, it's just... (exhales)
ROMEO:
It was devastating
voting Zach out.
We were
hashtag, you know,
the skinny guys.
But the good part
about tonight's vote was
we made Tori comfortable,
and that's where
we need to keep her.
It'll be easier
when it's time for her to go.
TORI:
Obviously, thank you all.
ROCKSROY:
I told you
you didn't have anything
-to worry about.
-I know.
I have so much to celebrate,
yet there was part of me
that was actually sad
that it was Zach
that went home,
which, like,
that makes me want to cry.
'Cause that shows how hard
this is that I would
for a moment think, like,
"Dang it.
"Why isn't that me
that gets immediate comfort?
"And, you know,
I get to sleep on a real bed
and have food."
TORI:
And it's only three days in,
so I am kind of scared
for what's to come but, but...
I'm just really trying
to get myself back
to that mental space
of realizing
that I'm living
my dream come true,
and I don't want to change it
for anything.
DREA:
It's only going to get worse.
This is only day three.
I'll be asking you about stuff
-in my teeth all the time,
for sure.
-CHANELLE: Yeah.
But we haven't eaten anything,
-so there's nothing to check.
-Yeah.
There's got to be something.
Breadfruit, mango, something.
-Oh, look!
-Yeah. Ooh, oh, my God.
-Is it a crab?
-Can we eat those?
Ah, he's so ugly!
We found some hermit crabs,
and they were
way bigger than I've ever seen.
It startled me at first.
It looks like just a big bug.
(groans)
I didn't want to touch it,
to be honest.
I'm a city girl.
I'm still trying here.
CHANELLE:
He's got his claws out.
Oh, my gosh.
-(Jenny shrieks)
-Gonna chop my freaking hand.
I don't love the wilderness.
I don't like the jungle.
I don't like spiders
or mosquitoes.
You think
you're going somewhere,
but you're not, Mr. Krabs.
I thought
that there would be someone
who could be a provider.
And, uh, it looks like
I might have to be that person.
That looks like
a New Orleans boil, doesn't it?
JENNY:
Just need a little Old Bay.
Old Bay, give me some butter.
All right, guys,
dinner is served.
-MIKE: Can I eat the claw? Okay.
-CHANELLE: Yeah.
-Mm-hmm. Tell me what you think.
-Not bad.
-CHANELLE: Mmm.
It tastes good. Wow.
-JENNY: Yeah, they do.
-It almost tastes
like it has butter on it.
-It does, right?
(gasps) Yes.
MIKE:
It's amazing what no eating
will make you eat.
You got to do what you got
to do. I got to be honest.
It's good. You're not gonna
try it, brother?
-Nah, I'm okay.
-Come on, try it, dude.
-JENNY: Really?
-Y'all go for it.
Being a vegan
out here on the island...
is very tough.
So as my tribemates
were enjoying the crab
and having a good time,
I was happy for them,
but I'm struggling because
a part of me feels as though
I need to eat it
to sustain myself
and not be seen as a liability.
MIKE:
In about 24 days,
-I'm gonna be eating real food.
-Mm.
I'm eating burgers.
Sorry. Sorry, Hai. Sorry.
HAI:
Being in the elements
without food, starving--
it's tough, and it all just came
on top of me like
a ton of bricks at once.
CHANELLE:
It's a hard game, and I think
-everybody's gonna have
their moments.
-(Hai sniffles)
It's okay to have your moment.
-I would just like rice
and coconut.
-Mm-hmm.
HAI:
When Jeff said
there would be no rice,
I knew I would have
to make a conscious decision
whether or not
I would eat any fish
or crab or sea life
that we catch.
Get ready for an awkward hug.
Are you ready?
-Yeah.
-Okay. That's it.
-Thank you, buddy.
-Okay. (laughs)
-Oh! I love you, Hai.
-HAI: I came out here
to discover more
about myself...
beyond just winning the money.
As someone who loves animals,
I obviously want to stay true
to myself out here, but
I'm not gonna be able to sustain
myself on coconuts alone.
So any opportunity
that I have to strengthen myself
for the longevity of the game--
I need to take it.
I think the universe
will understand
in this one nuanced instance,
and eventually I'll be able
to forgive myself
for eating meat out here.
DANIEL:
There you go.
MIKE:
How is it? Good?
This is pretty good, yeah.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
CHANELLE:
Yeah!
How do you feel? Good?
♪ ♪
You said you feel like crap?
Just, like, overall.
Just in general.
♪ ♪
MARYANNE:
Yeah.
I'd move, too, if I were you.
(laughing)
JONATHAN:
You are swinging that thing
-like you're on a scary movie.
-(Maryanne and Lindsay laugh)
-Here's Maryanne!
-(laughter)
(whooping)
MARYA:
Maryanne is
on a hundred all the time.
There's no downtime
until we're sleeping.
Ready for this?
Hi. I'm Maryanne from Survivor,
and you're watching CBS.
♪ Doo-doo, doo-doo. ♪
-Oh, my God.
-(Lindsay laughs)
-Yeah.
-The energy she has is unreal.
-(indistinct chatter)
-I know.
-I'm crashing so hard.
(sings Survivor theme, laughs)
LINDSAY:
And she's a really sweet gir,
and I do enjoy her.
She's just very young, and she's
excited about lots of things.
(screams, laughs)
Who wants it?
Ooh.
LINDSAY:
But at the same time,
that's exhausting after a while.
Not everyone can be
that on the whole time,
so I think that does
start to kind of
rub people the wrong way.
OMAR:
Do you guys have a second?
I just want to share something
-with everybody,
like, I haven't yet.
-MARYANNE: Yeah.
OMAR:
Like, I am a Muslim.
I-I don't want to make it
a big deal,
but I just want everybody...
to let everybody know,
like, I'm gonna be doing prayer,
um, every so often.
-I'm not looking
for an immunity idol.
-(laughter)
I'll be on the beach.
Maybe at some point,
I can weave a palm frond
-to be, like, the mat.
-You don't need... Oh.
-Oh, yes, for the mat.
-Or... For the mat.
I can weave one for you, too.
Don't worry.
-Oh, yeah? That'd be awesome.
-Yeah, I'll weave one for you.
-Yeah, no problem.
-Thank you.
But I think, like,
if you guys have any questions
about, like, literally anything,
I don't mind answering that.
JONATHAN:
And, bro, if you ever have
any questions
about Christianity...
-OMAR:
Yeah, I think that's awesome.
-Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's awesome.
-I'm not really a great Jew.
-(laughter)
So you guys
-probably know more than I do.
-OMAR: You know?
Since 2001,
the world has changed a lot,
and the perception of Muslims--
we always have to worry
about what other people think
about us.
But I'm just a regular person
who happens
to have these beliefs,
and I wanted them to know
about me because you need
to be your most authentic,
genuine self
in this game and in life.
Because if you don't understand
where people come from
and why they do things,
you can't become accepting
of people outside
of your inner circle.
I love it so much.
-No problem.
-Thank you. This is beautiful.
OMAR:
Being a Muslim,
it's so important for me.
I've never taken a sip
of alcohol.
You know, I don't do drugs,
I don't eat any pork,
and I don't have sex
before marriage.
I am a 30-year-old virgin.
I don't want to be
a 40-year-old virgin,
but for me that is important.
And it's so nice to be
around people who are so strong
in their faith and are
so supportive of me in mine.
♪ ♪
(coughs)
Face full of smoke
right to the eye.
Get out of the smoke.
You're right in the...
-I'm, like, loving it 'cause...
-Oh.
...the flies are not on me.
Last night at Tribal, when I got
my extra vote, I was like...
♪ Ah! ♪
Having the extra vote
and the amulet
that I got on day one
with Hai and Lindsay--
it's freaking awesome, but
the game-playing never stops.
Sadly, if we do have
to go back,
-Tori's next.
-Exactly.
Right now, I have an alliance
with Rocks and Romeo.
Ah!
DREA:
But a potential
girls alliance could
open my options more.
And I know my extra vote
gives me leverage.
(laughs)
Straight up.
-We need to stay girls strong.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-That's a new thought for you?
-No, it's not, but, like...
-Okay.
-...we would have majority.
-Yes.
The only people
who had my back were you guys,
and I hope you can trust me.
And...
-Let's do this.
-Okay.
-Okay, let's do this.
-Yeah.
SWATI:
I love this possibility
of a girls alliance happenin,
but here's the thing.
Drea is really, really good
at pulling people in.
SWATI:
Yes.
She has so much sway
and influence.
And on top of that, she has
the extra vote advantage.
And to me, that's too much power
in this game.
-Oh...
-So, what's your opinion?
Like, I will follow you.
That's why I'm asking 'cause
I don't want it to be, like,
-because I'm talking...
-No, yeah.
Like, we're an alliance
so I want your opinion.
TORI:
I was maybe going to go home
in the last Tribal Council.
I had terror, I had doubt,
I had paranoia.
And now people want
to go after Drea.
The game is shifting, and so,
for me, it's just this huge sigh
of relief.
I see the way forward now,
and that's to get Drea out.
(branches snapping)
(squawking)
JENNY:
Look at all of that wood.
MIKE:
Yup, we're getting there.
The game I'm playing right nw
is: work hard around camp
and lay low.
But as I collect wood,
as I collect coconuts,
as I collect palms,
my eyes are everywhere,
looking around
for a hidden immunity idol.
But I got to tell you,
it's much harder than you see
sitting in your living room.
This is dense. It-It's really
like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
It's incredible.
I found the idol.
Oh, my God, you know,
it's a first.
I-I can't believe.
One of my bucket list items.
Something in me said,
"Don't leave it."
I came to this game saying,
"Go big or go home."
And I'm going big.
How bad could it be?
So my phrase is,
"There is such grace in the game
of soccer, it makes me cry."
I don't like soccer.
Matter of fact,
when I coach my football teams,
I told my kids
it wasn't even a sport.
But I will cry for soccer
in this instance. Never again.
Oh!
I found an idol,
but I lose my vote, so
there's a blessing
and there's a curse.
But no matter what,
I'm stuck with this,
so it's about adapting
to the situation.
Because of this, I need
to focus more on relationship.
It's the only way
I can survive without a vote.
♪ ♪
If you... if you watch me do it
the first time,
-then maybe that'll help. I...
-Sure.
-Unless you want
to keep doing it.
-No, no. It...
JONATHAN: Me and Omar--
man, we're so different
in almost every way.
But being different can help you
in this game.
-Thanks for that. (laughs)
-Hey, man,
-we got each other's back.
-Yeah. (laughs)
♪ ♪
LINDSAY:
I love their bro time.
(Lindsay laughs)
I can look in Omar's eyes,
and I see that he trusts me.
Ooh.
JONATHAN:
You like it?
Yeah. (laughs)
Jonathan is my meat shield,
and I'm his brain shield, so,
am I going to Jonathan and
saying "We ride or die, baby"?
Yeah. It's The Odd Couple.
This is also weird, but I had
never, um, peed standing up
until I was, like, 22.
-(laughter)
-What?
I got to digest this.
He's way more funny than I am,
and everything
that he's good at,
I'm not as good at
and vice versa.
Together we make, like,
the perfect human. (laughs)
-With you, I'm... I'm tight.
-Yeah. Me, too.
-With Lindsay, I'm tight.
-Yeah.
I need to get closer
to Maryanne and Marya.
We have me and Lindsay
who are very close
to how we think and
being super strong.
-Feel like a monkey. (hooting)
-(laughs)
Get the bug! Get the bug!
JONATHAN:
Then, I love Maryanne and
how much spunk she's got.
The only one that I'm not
connected with is Marya.
LINDSAY:
What's your story
of what you want
to get out of here
other than money?
(laughs)
Yeah, um, it's all
wrapped around my brother.
But when he passed, um...
LINDSAY:
Okay.
I just-- I felt...
He always used to tell me,
"You need to, like, loosen up
and, like, just do stuff.
Stop being..."
LINDSAY:
Did you kind of feel like
your brother's with you
-right now?
-I do.
JONATHAN:
Yeah. Couldn't imagine.
-How long ago did he go?
-March, um, 2020,
so COVID, yeah.
-MARYANNE: Oh, wow.
-LINDSAY: It was, like,
right in the beginning of COVID.
He was a nurse, right?
Did you say he was a nurse?
-Yeah, he was a nurse. Yeah.
-JONATHAN: Mm.
MARYA:
James was the first
health care worker to die
of COVID in the United States.
He was a nurse in New York
doing what he wanted,
which was helping people.
But I have not processed
his passing.
Like, we haven't had closure.
You know, I...
So, I got this little necklace.
And I got his face etched
on this side.
LINDSAY:
Oh, I didn't see the face side.
-And so my intent is
to bury this here.
-JONATHAN: Mm.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Mm-hmm.
That's so awesome.
-LINDSAY: I love that.
-So I have my own little...
-farewell.
-MARYANNE: Yeah.
-LINDSAY: Yeah. That's sweet.
MARYA:
Losing him-- it's indescribable.
I've been holding my breath
for a year
because my kids are home,
you know,
and I'm trying
to be the-the strong mom
that keeps it all together.
So being here on Survivor
is about closure.
And for me, that would be worh
more than a million dollar.
-Where was it?
-It was on the side
of the road.
What did it look like?
It's exactly what the idol
looks like you see on TV.
Coming into this season,
I swore to myself
that I would not tell anybody
if I found an idol.
But me not having a vote--
it changes everything.
So I decided to tell Jenny
because she's my strongest ally
out here right now.
My number one.
-I found it.
-Holy ..., man.
But it's not an immunity idol.
I also want to try and gain an
ally, somebody smart to help me,
and I think
Daniel is a no-brainer.
Okay.
Hey, there was a "Y"
in the road.
I said,
"Let me check the 'Y' out."
I remember the "Y."
When I found it, I buried
it quick 'cause I didn't want
to get caught,
and now I can't find it.
I can't lose an idol,
and what do I do?
I mean, I got...
I don't remember
even the phrase right now.
It can't get lost. No.
DANIEL:
Mike buried it
where two trails intersect.
And there's, like,
20 million trails here. I am
mortified at this gameplay.
-Uh-oh.
-That's what I'm trying...
Uh-oh.
DANIEL:
Mike has lost his vote.
That's a pretty,
pretty big deal, but
I have the mind for the numbers,
I think, between the two of us.
And so, I'm basically going
to help him
figure out how to play this.
-Yeah, great, but it's on me.
-This was a... this was...
-Come on.
-Jeff Probst had a good idea.
Sorry. Okay.
There's a lot
of moving parts in this idol,
but I might be the true winnr
because
I have all the knowledge without
any of the penalty right now.
Yes.
MIKE:
Daniel's got a great idea.
At the next immunity challenge,
I don't say the phrase,
so nobody knows I have the idol
except my alliance.
It's perfect.
-Wow,
-I think the two of us
together can figure out
the best way it helps us.
-Yeah.
-Maybe it'll help Mike, too.
-Right.
-But most importantly,
-help us.
-Us. Yeah.
He has lost his vote
until the merge.
Absolutely.
And there's only two ways
of accomplishing that.
One is to vote Mike out.
And the second is to convince
Mike to never say anything.
CHANELLE:
I love how aligned
me and Daniel are.
He's my number one
in this game,
and we both agreed, Mike's idol
is a massive liability.
And so the fact that he talks
to Daniel is great.
We can use that against him if
we have to go to Tribal Council.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
Taku, Vati, getting your
first look at the new Ika tribe.
OMAR:
Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: Zach voted out.
-What?
-Oh.
Maryanne, huge reaction.
I told my tribe, and I guess
I'll tell all of you.
Zack is like every type of white
guy that I have a crush on.
-So, there goes that.
-(laughter)
-Really?
-Yeah.
So a blossoming love affair
is over?
No, not on Survivor, though.
If we met, like,
on a tribe swap,
connected after,
and then after this is over...
PROBST:
So I just want
to take this moment,
Maryanne,
to show how beautiful this is.
In the midst
of a very difficult game,
you still had a little hope
for love.
You know, um, I have
an 100% rejection rate with
all the guys I've liked, so...
-PROBST: Aw.
-I was, like, you know, I focus
on the game now, but
a little part of me was like...
PROBST: Well, I will just say,
as somebody who loves love,
keep hope alive.
Just because
you've been rejected 100%,
it means
they aren't the right people.
That's all that means.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-(all voicing assent)
-All right, first things first.
Got to take back the idols.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
Thank you. Oh.
-(laughter)
-Oh, all right.
-Duly noted.
-(laughter)
Once again, immunity is
back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
one person will be your caller.
The rest of the tribe
will be blindfolded.
Using only verbal commands,
the caller will instruct
the blindfolded pairs
to collect three bags
of puzzle pieces.
Once you have all the bags,
the caller will then instruct
a still blindfolded pair
to solve the puzzle.
The first two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
In addition,
playing for a reward.
-Thank God.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
ALL:
Yes!
-Please, Jeff.
-First tribe to finish,
-a massive set of fishing gear.
-Wow.
(exclaiming)
Second tribe to finish,
a smaller but still
very effective and useful
-set of fishing gear.
-Nice.
PROBST: Last tribe to finish,
Tribal Council,
where somebody will be the third
person voted out of this game.
And in addition,
as a penalty for losing,
you'll sacrifice your flint.
Ika, I still have yours.
You are playing
to get yours back.
Vati, you have one extra person.
You're gonna sit somebody out.
-Who's it gonna be?
-Me, Jeff.
PROBST:
Daniel gonna sit this one out.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
-We'll get started. Here we go.
-MARYANNE: Yeah.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, we have our callers.
For Ika, Drea.
Vati, Lydia.
Taku, Jonathan.
Here we go,
for immunity and reward,
survivors ready.
-Go.
-DREA: Go straight. Tori.
-Tori. Tori...
-LYDIA: Hey, Mike, Mike, Mike...
PROBST:
Caller is the tough job...
Straight. Straight.
You're gonna hit a barrel.
-(overlapping chatter)
-...because they're responsible
for directing everybody.
Turn your body, Chanelle.
Which way?
-We got three callers...
-JONATHAN: Stop.
-Stop where you are.
-...trying to talk
over each other.
HAI:
Lydia, we cannot hear you.
I'm talking.
-The players are talking.
-Right. Right, right, right...
Straight ahead. Keep going.
-You're there. You're there.
-LYDIA: Yeah, go straight!
Keep going, keep going!
That's your key!
Don't go past that!
-Chanelle spinning for Vati.
-DREA: Stop, lean forward!
CHANELLE:
Jenny, keep up, keep up.
Keep up.
-PROBST: Omar slowly being spun
for Taku.
-DREA: Romeo, stop!
JONATHAN:
More left!
PROBST:
Jonathan, trying to get ahold
of his tribe
-by yelling.
-Hey, Lindsay!
PROBST:
Lindsay and Maryanne stuck.
-They don't know
where they're going.
-LYDIA: No, you're good!
PROBST:
You've got to get your puzzle
pieces and you got to get back.
Yes! Go under! Go under!
PROBST:
Vati is in the sawdust now.
-Mike untying.
-(overlapping shouting)
-Is this blue?
-Down, Tori!
ROMEO:
Down. Pull it down.
PROBST:
Ika's now through.
Now they've got
to find that post.
-I got it. Go.
-Stop. Okay.
You're there! Dig the hole!
Nothing is easy
when you're blindfolded.
Swati, reach to your left!
PROBST:
Tori's got the post for Ika now.
-DREA: Forward, Romeo!
-PROBST: Orange and blue,
holding hands
with the wrong tribe member.
Not sure where they're going.
Chanelle and Jenny
trying to find their way back.
Both of y'all bitches,
come here!
PROBST:
Vati back with the first bag.
And just like that,
Vati back with the second bag.
JONATHAN:
Go straight.
Lydia doing a great job
for Vati.
They are in the early lead.
Ika coming back
with their first bag.
It's Tori and Swati.
You're good.
Drea with a nice job.
JONATHAN:
Right here!
-Can you hear me?!
-OMAR: Yes.
Omar and Marya back
with the first bag for Taku.
JONATHAN:
Drop it there!
PROBST:
Rocksroy and Romeo
-working together.
-ROCKSROY: Go, go, go.
Keep going around.
Turn me around. Turn me around.
Hey, Lindsay! Straight ahead!
-Oh.
-Okay, we're almost there.
-Yeah, girl!
-ROCKSROY: Go.
PROBST:
Maryanne and Lindsay
untying the spool for Taku.
ROCKSROY:
Turn me around. Turn me around.
Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy.
Shimmy. Stop!
Go forward, Tori!
-LYDIA: Go to the other side!
-PROBST: Chanelle and Jenny
now are getting
all tangled in that rope.
You got to be
behind the hitching post.
And that's gonna be
a problem now for Vati.
They were doing a great job.
-Okay. Okay.
-Pull.
It's now Tori and Swati
now on the spool.
-Omar's untying.
-OMAR: Got it.
Rocksroy heading back
with a second bag.
Boys, stop on that.
Put it down. Stay there.
-Grab this.
-Now it's Lindsay and Maryanne
who are tied up.
-They're all tangled
in the rope.
-I went under.
PROBST:
Everybody getting tangled
except for Swati and Tori.
Hell yeah, baby.
Right here! Straight!
PROBST:
Taku heading back
with a second bag.
We are neck and neck.
It's gonna come down
to the spooling right now.
HAI:
You okay?
Who can manage their ropes
without getting all tangled?
Drop the puzzle pieces.
-Yeah, yeah.
-PROBST: Lindsay and Maryanne
have the bag for Taku.
They're heading back.
-JONATHAN: There you go. Hey.
-That's gonna leave a big mark.
-There you go. Let's go,
let's go, let's go.
-MARYANNE: You okay?
And another big obstacle.
-All right.
-Shizzlesticks.
-You got it?
-Yeah, let's go.
Tori and Swati
coming back with their bag.
Left, Tori!
JONATHAN:
Go underneath!
PROBST:
It's Taku and Ika right now.
Drop down! Drop down!
-PROBST: Vati is all tangled up.
-Lydia!
I can't see!
Still struggling to
figure out what is happening.
(overlapping shouting)
Now Taku heading back
with their third and final bag.
Ow!
PROBST:
Ika right behind them.
We got a challenge on day five
of Survivor 42.
I got it. I got it.
Jenny finally has found the bag.
Now she's got to get it untied.
They got to get back.
It is Vati now in dead last.
Taku has all three bags.
You can start heading out.
Everyone hold hands.
Ika's back. You're good.
DREA:
Yes, no hesitation.
Just roll with me, baby.
PROBST:
Jonathan leading Taku out.
Everybody holding hands.
Here comes Jenny and Chanelle.
Not giving up.
Go straight to the sawdust!
I got you.
Ika's going through,
Taku's going through,
while Vati is heading back.
You got to get
all your bags back,
then you got to come back out.
Follow me. Come on.
(groans)
A big hit.
-Rocksroy goes hard.
-(groaning)
He's gonna feel that one
for a few days.
PROBST:
Vati is back.
Now Lydia can
lead her tribe out.
Follow me.
Get in a line. Get in a line.
All right, we're here.
We're here.
-MARYANNE: What?
Omar, give me your hand.
Jonathan's still the caller.
Drea's still the caller.
-Vati quickly trying
to get back into this.
-Let's go, guys, let's go.
PROBST:
Huge comeback for Vati.
Got to get all the pieces out
on the table
and then solve it.
Immunity on the line.
-Somebody is going home tonight.
-LYDIA: Guys, everyone
get in a line.
PROBST:
Somebody's dream
of winning Survivor
is hours away from ending.
-MARYA: Take that one...
-JONATHAN: This is the center.
-I want you to drop it...
-PROBST: The only way to make
sure it's not you
is you got to win.
LYDIA:
No, here. Go here.
-Right here. Go right...
-(overlapping chatter)
Got all three tribes now
on the puzzle.
Different strategies about
how you lead at this point.
No, that's not the piece
you just put down. To your left.
Put those kind of to the side.
You just have to connect
with the two people
who are solving the puzzle.
This is about
communication styles.
Hey, no, no, no, no, no. Listen.
Don't freak out.
I'm-I'm good.
Jenny,
you have to place it there.
PROBST:
Jenny trying to place
another piece for Vati.
Yes, that goes right there.
That goes right there.
Now fit this other piece around.
Drea now looking
for that next level.
They've got
the outer edge built.
It's a pizza.
PROBST:
Taku's taking
a different strategy,
building from the bottom up.
Every piece matters
and every piece counts.
-Little bit more, little bit
more, little bit more. Yes!
-DREA: Yeah. No. Other...
-LYDIA: Keep it there.
-PROBST: Huge stakes.
You just don't want to be last.
DREA:
Fit that bitch in.
Move the one on top.
That's it...
Another piece for Ika.
Yes, okay, now...
PROBST:
Another piece for Taku.
LYDIA:
There, keep going. Keep going...
-Yes.
-(overlapping chatter)
This is gonna come down
to a few seconds.
-Right there.
-PROBST: All three tribes
are very close.
No, push that, and put that
middle piece in with the notch.
With the notch. Oh, my God.
You've got one piece left.
-In the middle.
Put it in the middle.
-Move straight.
PROBST:
Vati with one piece left.
Put it right there.
Put it right there. Yes.
-Jeff! Jeff!
-Vati thinks they have it.
They do!
-Yes! Yes!
-DREA: Put it in the middle.
Yeah, baby!
-We're looking for one more!
-TORI: Sorry.
PROBST:
Taku with two.
Ika down to two pieces.
-It's gonna be a race.
-ROCKSROY: We got it?
-DREA: We won.
-We won. That's it. That's it.
-JONATHAN: Come on, guys.
-PROBST: One piece left.
-DREA: That's it. To the right.
Put it there. Jeff!
JONATHAN:
Marya, can you grab that piece?
Yes, that's it. Yeah, right...
DREA: Right there.
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
-PROBST: Ika's done it!
-(cheering)
Ika wins immunity!
Safe from Tribal Council.
Sending Taku to Tribal Council,
where the third person
will be voted out of this game.
-(cheering continues)
-PROBST: Wow, that was a finish.
-(whooping)
-Yeah!
LINDSAY:
Oh, my God.
Vati, congratulations.
Immunity is yours.
Lydia, you put yourself in a
big-time role and you delivered.
Fishing gear will be waiting
for you back at camp.
No Tribal Council tonight.
-Ika.
-(applauding)
-(whoops)
-I know this feels good.
TORI:
Yes. Get it, get it, girl.
Get it, girl.
-PROBST: Drea gonna take it.
-Yes, ma'am.
Your fishing gear will be
waiting for you back at camp,
as well as your flint.
-You get that back.
-Thank you.
Ika, Vati, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Enjoy the night off.
Well done.
All right, Taku,
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be the third
person voted out of this game.
Before you go,
I'll take your flint.
(sighs)
Sorry for you.
All right, Taku,
grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
MARYANNE:
Tonight's Tribal,
it's like going on
the worst first date ever.
You show up
with the person you like,
and then, in the end, they leave
and you never see them again.
And hopefully,
after Tribal Council,
my heart isn't broken.
♪ ♪
JONATHAN: Do you think
I'm in trouble tonight?
OMAR:
Not at all.
'Cause to me it's not even
a question about you,
-because...
-And I got your back.
-If anybody mentions you...
-Yeah.
-Same. Same.
-...I'm gonna come tell you.
-I think we have two options.
-Yeah.
OMAR:
Marya or Maryanne.
I think, long-term,
-Maryanne's a bit less
trustworthy than Marya...
-Yes.
But in the short-term,
who's gonna help us more?
Man.
JONATHAN:
This is not an easy task.
Marya is so wise,
and she's a mom, you know?
She's got it more put together.
Maryanne's still getting
everything figured out,
but I love Maryanne,
like, I connect with her.
-We need to work
to make Marya feel safe.
-Yes.
She doesn't play
her Shot in the Dark.
-Right.
-And then make sure
that Maryanne
also doesn't play
her Shot in the Dark.
JONATHAN:
When you play
the Shot in the Dark correctl,
you get immunity.
So... whew.
You have to look at both of
these women in the eyes and go,
"I am not going
to vote you out."
I'm not voting for you.
-I know.
-Look at me. Look at me.
I'm serious.
No, I know. I know.
JONATHAN: No matter what,
we have to bold-faced lie.
And right now, one of those two
are gonna get
their hearts broken.
OMAR:
So, what's the story?
MARYA:
So, my gut is Maryanne.
LINDSAY:
That was what I was thinking.
Yeah, I don't know
if I can do that for 26 days.
-LINDSAY: Yes.
-MARYA: That's a little much.
Like, I know in my gut
it's gonna be
my name
that's written down by her.
So I know,
I'm-I'm sure she's thinking
it's either me or Marya, right?
-Right.
-Like, and that--
Like, it's period.
MARYA:
I believe she would vote me,
so I think that you guys
should tell her
-that's what you're doing.
-Yeah. Okay.
MARYA:
We all, on the surface,
seem to be
in sync
with who it should be, but...
I could be a huge fool.
Like, maybe they're
hiding something.
There is something more there.
So I'm bringing
my Shot in the Dark to Triba,
no question.
MARYANNE:
Dang it.
Dang. Five days,
and my name's gonna be put down.
Well, not-not by your people.
I know, not by... (sighs)
But, like, dang it, you know?
I'm terrified.
Plus, there's a chance
I have no power at all.
On day two, I risk my vote
to either A) get an extra vote,
or B) lose my vote
at this Tribal Council.
Mm-hmm.
And, like, that's, like,
my task for today.
Literally, my life
isn't even in my hand.
Dang it.
And they can just
kick me in the dirt.
So what do nervous people do?
They look for idols.
This is so nasty.
Do you think
sometimes her being emotional
can turn into paranoia
at the same time, or no?
MARYA:
I don't know.
I was looking around for
those flowers that you found,
but I couldn't see 'em.
LINDSAY: Okay, clearly
she's looking for an idol.
She cannot control herself.
Okay. No problem.
LINDSAY:
I feel like Maryanne does get
flustered under pressure.
Like, one of the things
that I look for in an alliane
is they don't panic and, like,
burn to the ground
and take me down with them.
-How do you feel?
-I think we're gonna need
four people to go forward
that are going to,
like, kill it
with social and hustle.
Yeah.
LINDSAY:
But I do think...
-Who?
-Marya.
Yeah.
OMAR: It would be so difficut
to see Marya go
when we've connected
so strongly,
because she's lost her brother,
and she's seeking closure
out here.
So my heart
is literally breaking,
because she may be
going home tonight.
Are you worried enough to, like,
play your Shot in the Dark?
I'm gonna go with my gut.
OMAR:
I actually trust her
more than Maryanne.
She's a ball of energy.
She's a wild card.
Maybe she can, um, have, like,
a great romance at Ponderosa.
(laughter)
But Maryanne
brings life to the camp,
and she has the hustle
that we need
to battle two other tribes.
Because now Taku's down
to four people, after tonigh.
Up until now,
we have been a family,
but the sun's gonna set
and someone's dream
is gonna get crushed.
♪ ♪
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch.
Approach the flame,
dip it in, and get fire.
This is part of
the ritual of Tribal Council,
because in this game,
fire represents your life,
and when your fire is gone,
so are you.
It's fun to say, not fun
when you think about it.
No. Not at all.
Mm-mm.
PROBST:
Omar, as much excitement
as I saw,
even on your face
when you walked in here,
this is where death happens.
Yeah, I mean,
as a fan of the show,
coming to Tribal Council,
it's unbelievable.
But on the other hand,
there's the horrible side
that we have to cut
a family member loose tonight.
And this truly is a family
after five days.
MARYA:
Absolutely.
I mean, we've shared
a lot together in five days.
Like, I know their stories.
PROBST:
Omar, that's really interesting
because the bookend
to coming out here
and feeling like
you can bond with people
is that now you feel
some level of moral obligation
to be a little more honest
than you might want to be.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: But you can't be
too honest.
Yeah, like, you don't want
to lie to their face,
but at the same it's like
Darwin's theory of evolution.
Like, there's a selection
pressure on us now,
especially with
the Shot in the Dark,
where everybody has to think
that they're safe,
but not everybody's
going to be safe.
Jonathan,
if it's a natural selection,
or if it's
survival of the fittest,
you're basically saying,
how do I make sure
I don't come back here?
By keeping the people
who are with me
strong enough to win challenges.
-That's really it.
-JONATHAN: Right.
Yeah, and, like,
strength in this game
comes in all different shapes
and forms.
You know,
physical strength is one thing,
mental strength is another.
Social game is another.
All connected is what you need.
-You can't just have one.
-I agree.
But, Lindsay,
what's interesting about that,
there are five people
who all believe
that you'll be stronger
after this vote.
LINDSAY:
That's the hard part,
because obviously it's only
going to end up being four.
It's trying to be
as level-headed as you can
to balance out your paranoia
with your trust of who you have
and hope it works out.
PROBST:
Maryanne, was there much talk
of Shot in the Dark?
I feel as if it's always
in the back of our heads,
you know, 'cause that now adds
another layer to the strategy.
So it's, like, do you now go
with Plan A, B, C, then D,
or Plan A Subsection A,
Plan B Subsection B?
And then, if two people use it,
then you have now
another subsection,
and then another, and another.
You just have so many things
that you're thinking about.
Like, "Oh, my G." It's, like,
so easy to just kind of go,
like... (ululating)
When just one little
measly thing,
which is, like, this tiny.
Wow. So, Maryanne,
let's say it's you.
That big smile, that big laugh,
full of emotion.
What's the reaction?
I think right now,
going to Tribal, is
when I just realized, "Oh,
I'm actually playing Survivor."
And it's like, I want
to do more and learn more
with my tribe members.
Like, don't send me to Zach.
I'm not ready. Please.
-(Maryanne laughs)
-PROBST: So love really is
on your mind right now, right?
(laughter)
Well, you brought it up
twice today.
It's like, being 23 and, like,
always single, it's like,
maybe there's something wrong
with you
because no one romantically
likes you, you know?
And it's like, it's something
which I've always
been working on, and
the thing is, like,
Zachary-- literally
picture perfect. And I'm like,
"Hey, God, is that you?" Like,
wow, is this like a two-for-one?
You win Survivor,
and then you also get a man?
And then it's like in the
reunion, Jeff's like, "Yeah,
Maryanne, so you started to
date Zach. How'd that work out?"
And I'm like, "Well, Jeff, thank
you for putting me on Season 42.
It's a whole big side."
But, like, you know,
it's like, even though the part
of the game is about winning,
you still think
about the little things, too.
Oh, I was just
getting comfortable.
Oh, you want me...?
I can go more. I-I love
-saying my piece.
-(laughter)
PROBST:
Okay, so Marya,
you talked about getting
to know everybody.
There's a perfect example.
She's been very open
about sharing
-how she's looking for love.
-(Maryanne laughs)
And yet, if the vote goes
the wrong way for her tonight,
it means, "Yeah, we like you
and we hope you find love,
but we don't want you
on the tribe."
MARYA:
Yeah, I mean,
it would be very hard.
However, part of my journey
here is to stop being the mom
and the caretaker,
'cause that's what I do.
I have to make sure
everybody else is taken care of,
and part of
what I want to accomplish here
is to put me first.
So, I need to put Marya first
for once.
PROBST:
So, Lindsay,
how do you vote out Marya
when she says, "Look,
I'm gonna take care of me.
I got some more journey I need"?
LINDSAY:
No matter who we vote out,
it's going
to be extremely difficult,
but you have to kind of balance
the personal relationships
that you gain
and then your game
and what you want for yourself.
And you want to make sure
one doesn't overlap the other.
JONATHAN:
Absolutely, there's a line.
It's like,
I love everybody,
but there's a game to be played.
I mean, it's that simple.
PROBST:
Wow.
It's that simple.
On that note,
it is time to vote.
Marya, you're up.
♪ ♪
(whispering):
Thank you, God.
Oh, my gosh. Yes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
MARYA:
Jeff?
I'm gonna play
my Shot in the Dark.
PROBST:
Great. I'll take it.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
Marya played
her Shot in the Dark,
which means she did not vote.
Taking a one-in-six shot
for safety in the game.
If this says you are safe,
then any votes cast
against you will not count.
If it says you're not safe,
then any votes cast
against you will still count.
I'll open the scroll.
♪ ♪
Marya, you are...
not safe.
Any votes cast against Marya
will still count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote--
Marya.
Marya. Two votes-- Marya.
Third person voted
out of Survivor 42--
Marya.
That's three. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Bye, girl.
Love you.
♪ ♪
(clears throat)
Marya, the tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
-Time for you to go.
-Hey, you guys, bring it home.
-Bye, Marya.
-LINDSAY: Love you.
-MARYANNE: Love you.
Love you.
♪ ♪
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
(gasps)
Yo, I got bait-and-switched.
MIKE:
The idol
is missing.
I almost stroked out
right there.
Hey, both tribes!
Never done this
in the history of Survivor.
My brother would tell me
that he's very proud of me,
and shake it off
and to keep living.
You know, take risks
and-and push myself
outside of my comfort zone.
I had a lot of fun playing
Survivor.
I got a lot in five days.
Survivor is like parenting.
It's super hard.
And yet I love it
in every possible way.
(roars)