♪ ♪
We need to talk
to Gabler real quick.
SAMI:
So at Tribal Council,
it was pretty straightforward.
Everybody wanted
to vote out Jeanine
because it was
the easy and simple vote.
But this is not
what I wanted to do.
I didn't have the numbers
to take
somebody else out,
but it's, like,
I'm ready to change this game
up. I'm ready to shake up
this game at this point,
and we got to start picking off
the people that are at the top.
Gabler. Here.
- Come talk
with me and Sami real quick.
- GABLER: Yeah.
SAMI:
Owen is the only person who was
left out of the vote again.
And so, I had to make sure
he knows I'm willing
to work with him going forward.
Here's what happened.
I was at the well
with Sami and James.
- I said, "If it's Jeanine,
just tell me. I'll do it."
- Yeah.
They said, "Nope. It's Ryan."
I am kind of pissed with
James because he lied to my face
minutes before Tribal,
told me to vote for Ryan.
If it's Jeanine, you can tell
me, and I won't say a word.
- JAMES: We're voting Ryan,
and it is what it is.
- Okay. Cool.
I was supposed to go with Owen,
but then James...
- OWEN: James insisted on coming.
- He insisted on coming.
- OWEN: And then...
- Because all day
he's been watching me.
He doesn't want me to tell Owen.
He wants
to leave Owen out of it.
OWEN:
Jeanine is not
who I wanted to see going home,
but I'm very grateful that
Gabler told me
at literally the last second
where the votes were going.
He lied to my face.
SAMI: I'm telling you, bro,
James is the only one
that didn't want you to know.
They wanted you to know,
but everybody
was too scared
to do it because...
Every... scared of this guy.
Who the...
does he think he is?
- GABLER: Bro, he's so arrogant.
- SAMI: Bro...
- He's not the... Godfather.
- They want to get...
OWEN:
James wanted me
left out of this vote,
and I'm just
freaking sick of it.
Like, you're not the Godfather,
dude. Like, it's...
He's driving me insane,
and it's time to get him out.
JAMES: Okay.
Owen's mad at me
for being left out of the vote.
When we got back,
I'm like, you know,
"What's up, Owen?"
He's like, "What?"
And I'm like,
"You want to talk?" "No."
Owen is not on my side.
I was like, "Owen."
He's like, "What?"
I'm like, "You want to talk?"
He's like, "No."
I'm just like...
Owen voted for me before,
so I don't trust him.
And at Tribal Council,
Jeff was saying,
"What's the social contract?"
The social contract is
if you break trust with James,
you go home.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Feast your eyes
on what awaits you.
[Owen chuckles]
- On day 17 of Survivor 43.
- [Cassidy whoops]
- Yes.
- [chuckles]
All right.
Day 17.
[whoops]
- PROBST: Shall we get into?
- Yes, sir.
First things first, Owen,
got to take back the necklace.
- I know you don't want me to.
- No, I don't.
- [clicks tongue] Thank you.
- Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna hold onto a handle,
clamping a ball
between a set of jaws.
If at any point
you lower that handle,
your ball will drop,
and you're out.
There is a twist
to today's challenge.
[Karla gasps]
PROBST:
Ten players.
We're gonna divide
into two teams of five,
which means one person from each
team will win immunity.
Oh, damn.
- NOELLE: Ooh.
- So there are
two immunity necklaces.
- Oh, damn.
- Ooh-la, baby.
PROBST:
Both groups will go
to Tribal Council separately
- and vote somebody out.
- Oh, man.
PROBST:
So two winners,
two people going home.
In addition,
the last person left standing
for the entire challenge earns
reward for their team of five.
- Want to know
what you're playing for?
- Yes, sir.
PROBST:
I think you're gonna like it.
It's a little
do-it-yourself PB and J.
- [gasping]
- [whoops]
Brah.
In addition,
you also get the advantage...
The winning five... of going
to Tribal Council last.
So you get to see what happens
at the first Tribal Council.
A lot going on
on day 17, Survivor 43.
We'll draw for teams
and we'll get started.
Let's do this.
♪ ♪
All right, we have our
two teams. Let's take a look.
On the red side,
we have Cassidy, Jesse,
Gabler, Ryan and Cody.
One of the five of you
will win immunity.
On the blue side,
we have Owen, Sami,
Noelle, Karla, James.
One of the five of you
will win immunity.
And one person's going to earn
reward in the form of PB and J
and going
to Tribal Council last.
All right, everybody put
your palms under your handle.
I'm gonna
count you in to lift up.
When you lift up,
you'll release the ball.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Everybody lift up.
This challenge is on.
♪ ♪
It doesn't look like much
until you're the one
holding the handle.
You have to keep
pressure on your handle
because that's what's
keeping the ball trapped.
Your hands cannot
come off of the bar.
Karla working with one bad hand,
trying to keep it together.
Little tiny injuries
can really impact a challenge.
♪ ♪
Jesse can't recover.
Jesse's out.
No shot at immunity.
Jesse on the bench.
We're down to four for Red.
Everybody from Blue still alive.
Noelle, her ball moves a little.
That's how fast it happens.
Cassidy.
Ball drops a little,
but she saves it.
Cassidy drops. She's out.
Red is down to three...
Gabler, Ryan and Cody.
Everybody
from Blue is still in it.
Noelle can't hang.
She's out.
Our first casualty from Blue.
Blue is now down to four...
Owen, Sami, Karla and James.
James, out of nowhere.
That's how it goes, James.
James frustrated.
You can't imagine
it could be this difficult.
One moment of letting
off tension on that handle.
That ball's ready to drop.
Gabler drops.
He's out.
We're down to two for Red.
- NOELLE: Let's go.
- PROBST: It is Ryan and Cody
with immunity on the line.
NOELLE:
I'll keep you guys updated.
PROBST:
It is Owen, Sami
and Karla for Blue.
Got to give Karla credit knowing
the pain that hand is in.
Karla, you're inspiring me right
now, broke finger and all, yo.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Owen, one little slip.
- And there it is. Owen's out.
- GABLER: Ryan, stay focused.
Stay focused, buddy...
We're down to two showdowns.
In Red, the showdown
is Ryan versus Cody.
In Blue,
it is Sami versus Karla.
NOELLE:
Stay focused. Stay focused.
Sami, Karla,
get us some PB and J.
Battle time. Here you go.
Day 17, Survivor 43,
this is what it's about.
Way to go, big boys.
Stay in there. Focus.
What about the big girls, huh?
- GABLER: You, too.
- OWEN: Yeah, Karla.
You got it, Karla.
JAMES:
Show 'em how it's done, Karla.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Been up there ten minutes.
JAMES:
Push through, Karla.
PROBST:
I know it feels like ten hours.
All you have to do
is outlast the other person.
- PROBST: Sami doesn't
even see it happening.
- Good job!
- [cheering]
- Karla wins! Stay alive, Karla!
- Stay in it!
- JAMES: Hang in there, Karla!
- PROBST: Sami dropped
and had no knowledge
- Wow.
The ball was even moving.
Karla has won immunity.
She's now
fighting for a reward as well,
between Ryan and Cody.
- GABLER: Hold still, guys.
- PROBST: It's a reminder,
on any given day,
anything can happen.
♪ ♪
Ryan with
a little bit of a slip.
Karla hunched over.
[Karla sighs]
PROBST:
Karla, you're out.
- Great effort by Karla.
- Yes.
- Peanut butter.
- OWEN: Hey, great work, Karla.
- PROBST: Hung in there
for a long time.
Immunity is yours.
This means that the reward
will be going to Red.
- Proud of you, boys.
- PROBST: Now
it's just a question
of who will have immunity
while they're
eating their PB and J.
- Rockin' Ryan and Cowboy Cody.
- [Ryan whoops]
Another battle.
Stay on fire, brah.
[whoops]
PROBST:
It is Ryan and Cody,
side by side.
Huge immunity on the line.
OWEN:
Dig deep, boys.
GABLER:
Amazing, gentlemen.
Ryan with another
little bit of movement.
Both digging, you can see it.
You can see the body.
You can see the intensity.
Ryan's ball moves a little more.
Cody is right where he started.
He has not had any slips.
If you lose your concentration
for a nanosecond,
that ball is on the move.
♪ ♪
Ryan drops. He's out.
- Cody wins
his first individual immunity.
- Yahoo! Yes!
- PROBST: Safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
- Ha. Right there, man.
- Along with Karla.
- CODY: Yeah, baby.
PROBST:
Has also earned PB and J
and will go to Tribal last.
Huge effort.
NOELLE:
Good job, boys.
PROBST:
Cody, come on over.
- Right here. Well done, brother.
- [exhales sharply]
Mahalos.
Cody, safe tonight
at Tribal Council,
cannot be
voted out of this game.
You will live to see day 18.
In addition,
you earned for the five
a little do-it-yourself
PB and J.
- And well done. Head back.
- Mahalos.
- Thank you, Cody.
- PROBST: Karla, come on over.
- Karla!
- Get that thing, yeah!
- Now, you feel the love?
- Yeah.
- Is it because people love you?
- CASSIDY: Good job, Karla.
Is it because
they appreciate the injury
- and that you're
fighting from pain? What is it?
- I... [laughs softly]
I mean, I-I think it's both.
I mean, I-I am capable of things
that I never
thought I'd be capable of.
I was ready to give up,
but the moment that I realized
that I could, I stayed
and I pushed through it.
Well done. The result is you are
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
You cannot be
voted out of this game.
- All right.
- All right. Head back.
Necklace looks so good on you.
- So good on you...
- PROBST: All right,
here's how it's gonna go.
The five who lost are gonna
go back to Vesi beach.
No rice,
no personal items, nothing.
That's where you're gonna figure
out who's going home tonight.
I'll see you
at Tribal Council first.
Gabler, Ryan,
Cassidy, Cody, Jesse,
you'll go back to your camp,
where you have at
least the luxury of a shelter,
and you'll go
to Tribal Council last.
Grab your stuff, head out.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Thanks, Jeff.
I was able to pull off a win.
And given the fact that I still
have stitches in my hand,
the odds are stacked against me.
So it just feels wonderful.
But it's also beyond
what I ever imagined
would happen to me.
And it's all
because of the power of
believing and trusting in me.
♪ ♪
This adventure could be yours.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
[whoops]
Ah.
[sighs]
RYAN:
PB and J!
Feels good.
♪ Peanut butter jelly time ♪
I finally won immunity.
Obviously,
it's a checklist for everybody.
That's-that's the biggest win
in a competition I've had
on the biggest stage
I've ever been on.
And it came with food.
- Cheers, y'all.
- Thank you, man.
- Cheers.
RYAN:
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Man. Nice job, team.
CODY:
This is so huge
for moving forward, man.
- CASSIDY: I know.
- CODY: Like...
- GABLER: Big time.
Once we got back to camp,
obviously our very first
priority is to break bread,
fill our tummies
with nutrients and good food.
Our bodies
are just eating this up.
I know.
GABLER:
But we're in groups of five,
and there's fewer places
to hide. So
once the food was gone,
the game is on.
Yeah.
That way, 'cause, you know,
obviously
I wouldn't tell her me.
So it has to be you.
It has to be you.
And you say me.
RYAN:
I've been trying to vote out
Cassidy for a very long time.
And I can't really trust her.
The first time I tried it, um,
trying to get Cass out,
it didn't really work for me.
But I think right now
is the best time to strike.
Yeah, that's
what you guys are thinking?
Karla, James, Cass.
RYAN:
Right now, the game plan
is to break up the Coco tribe.
I don't want to be told,
"Oh, you rode Coco's coattails."
I'd rather say,
"No, I broke up Coco
when Coco
was ready to break up."
I cracked that coconut open.
CASSIDY:
All right, so,
what are we thinking, folks?
- Ryan. Me, too.
- Yeah?
No, I...
Like, my thing is, like,
I don't have, like, a for-sure.
Like, I don't know
exactly what I'm doing.
I-I've obviously spent a lot
of really nice time with you.
My whole thing is, like,
I want to be here
- with people that I like.
- CASSIDY: Yeah.
- I want to have
conversations with everyone
- Yeah.
- before I, like, start
saying, "Yeah, let's do this."
- Okay.
I think if us three
stick together,
- then that means
we have the numbers.
- CODY: Yeah.
CASSIDY:
I'm definitely
worried about tonight.
I want to believe
Cody and Jesse,
and I think that
they are on my side,
but you never know.
If Ryan's trying
to make a big move right now,
um, yeah,
they could be coming after me.
I know that
if we voted Ryan out now
the other side would not be mad.
And plus,
I like it when everyone...
Yeah, I-I need to find people
that are willing to really
- work with me, because...
- Yeah.
- And we've already built trust.
CASSIDY:
This game never stops.
It is completely exhausting,
and so it takes a lot
to keep that fight alive.
But, I mean, I'm not gonna
let that fight go out in me.
Being on Survivor
is what I've dreamed about
since I was a little kid.
When it's really hard out here,
I draw strength
from my family and my brothers,
who are so proud of me
out here playing this game.
And I draw
strength from my sister,
who passed away
a couple years ago and...
[sniffles] grew up
watching the show with me.
I know that, like,
her spirit's with me.
And so, in moments like this,
when I'm feeling
really down and depleted
and kind of a little bit scared,
I always say a prayer
and I kiss my necklace.
It has my sister's ashes in it.
I'm out here for her,
to honor her,
and that's why
I don't give up in this game.
I am putting a lot of trust
in Cody and Jesse tonight
to vote Ryan out, but I've been
on the right side of the vote
for the entire game.
And everybody
who's come after me in this game
I've sent home successfully,
so I'm just hoping
that it's Ryan tonight.
KARLA: This is so surreal.
I'm really proud of myself.
Day-one Karla
would never believe this.
I won individual immunity.
And it just
feels wonderful to kind of...
to be able to wear this,
- [grunts]
- Because it guarantees
that I make
it to the final eight.
I'm a freaking badass.
- NOELLE: Welcome home.
- OWEN: Not a bad shelter.
KARLA:
Jeff tells us that we have
to go over to the Vesi camp.
So we're stuck at Vesi
until Tribal.
Great job, Karla.
- That was hard.
- Thank you.
NOELLE:
Great job, Karla.
[James chuckles]
KARLA:
James is a crucial part
of my alliance,
and I know
he wants to vote out Owen.
No, sorry. My-my thing is full.
Owen isn't really
part of my alliance.
So tonight, I'm voting for Owen.
But I do have to be careful,
because once you have to vote
one person out of five,
that's when it gets dangerous.
So you better be ready
and hope that you
can trust the group
that you are in.
So...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. For sure.
- SAMI: Oh, yeah.
NOELLE:
I think he's gonna go for James.
- A hundred percent.
- KARLA: Yeah.
And he's gonna
try to sway me and you.
So we-we need to talk to him
and make sure that
he's feeling comfortable,
- so he doesn't
play Shot in the Dark.
- SAMI: Yeah.
- That's the biggest thing.
So, you good with that plan?
KARLA:
Makes sense to me.
I mean... Simple.
Owen is gonna be going home,
and I think he knows
exactly what's about to happen.
And that's-that's a really...
...crappy place to be in,
I think.
So what are you thinking?
I feel like it is what it is.
OWEN:
So who are you voting for?
- Okay.
- I'm not trying to give you...
No. Like...
What am I supposed to do, James?
- I'm not...
- How else am I supposed to
prove that I can work with you?
- I did what you told me to do.
- So, so...
Two minutes before Tribal,
you told me to vote for Ryan.
- I... voted for Ryan, dude.
- Right.
So, so, let's-let'’s calm...
Like, I'm, I get...
Don't tell me to... calm down.
- I'm not telling you to... Bro.
- I did what you told me to do,
- and it
was the wrong thing to do.
- Hey. No, no, no.
- What am I supposed to believe?
- It was the right thing to do,
'cause that's
what we asked you to do.
OWEN:
Who does this guy think he is?
To me, he's implying
I am getting votes.
It's this
mafioso-style bullcrap.
- You know what
I'm saying? Like...
- Sure.
And I'm just, I'm tired of it,
and I'm nearing
my breaking point.
So there's
nine people on the vote,
and you're just mad at me?
You're the one I talked to
two minutes before Tribal.
Sami was there, too.
You... I said, "Tell me."
Sami was there, too, bro.
Like, so I'm saying...
You're the one who f...
Like, Sami and I were gonna go.
Who knows what he would
have told me if you hadn't
butted your way
into that conversation.
You're...
So everything is my fault?
- Yeah. In my brain.
- Okay.
- So, so, so...
- I asked you
what I'm supposed to do.
- So, so...
- I did what you told me.
Everything's my fault.
- Ah, get over yourself.
- Hey, man, like...
- Everything's my fault.
- KARLA: Is this for real?
- OWEN: Yeah.
- KARLA: What happened?
Yesterday at the well,
I asked him right before Tribal,
I said, "If it's Jeanine, tell
me. I will vote for Jeanine."
- And I told you Ryan.
- And he sold me Ryan.
And what did you do at the first
Tribal Council after the merge?
- Put my name down, right?
- Yeah.
What'd you do the next time?
Put my name down, right?
OWEN:
No, I put
Ryan's name down the next time.
You put my name down
the first time. Did you tell me
you put my name down
the first time you did it?
- No.
- What's worse?
- OWEN: No.
- What-what's worse?
- Like, on the scheme of things.
No, no, no.
- But you...
On the scheme of things,
what's worse?
Writing someone's name down
or telling them a vote?
- What?
- It's good.
JAMES: Owen is upset
at his predicament,
but also mad at me, even though
he wrote my name down
at two previous Tribal Councils.
The second the pressure hits,
you start cursing people out
and acting a little hissy fit.
I hate that stuff, yo.
I know.
Truth be told, I feel like
we should just go in there,
put the votes on Owen
and call it a day.
- Make it quick.
- Exactly.
I have no sympathy for the guy
and I have the numbers,
so he can go home.
♪ ♪
- We are at eight, right?
- We, yeah.
Who do we ride or die with?
'Cause if we can get
- the numbers on the next vote,
we're sitting... pretty.
- Yeah.
Tonight is extremely important.
We have this
five-five split Tribal Council,
and right now,
it's between Ryan and Cassidy.
We only have a say in, like,
these five people here.
But that's not to say that
these five people
don't have relationships back
at the other Tribal Council.
So even though
it's only us five,
it's gonna have a huge impact
on, like, our relationships
going forward.
And so, we have to
weigh that out.
Okay. So what are
the benefits of keeping
- Ryan?
- CODY: Ryan's a good shield.
- JESSE: Good shield.
- I think he's
kind of just a free agent
all the time.
JESSE:
If we take out Cass,
James and Karla
would not be happy, right?
- That's part of...
- Karla would definitely
not be happy.
They would not be happy.
If we get rid of Cassidy,
we potentially make, like,
James and Karla very angry.
They feel like she's
a part of their alliance,
and me and Cody have, you know,
voted with them twice now.
But on the other hand, she's
super social, super strategic.
So that's
a little bit concerning.
If we send Ryan home,
we're sending
a challenge beast home,
which is good for me,
but Ryan isn't
a strategic threat. And so
it's a tough one.
But also, here,
we have an advantage.
We have the advantage
of going to Tribal...
- after them.
- To know who, yeah.
JESSE:
So we will know
who's sitting there on the jury.
But we also
have to consider, like,
we're in the lucky position
of we get to see
who they send home.
And so that can
impact our decision, too.
If it is Owen, then maybe we'd
want to keep trust with James
and get rid of Ryan
and keep Cass.
You know what I'm saying?
If it's James,
maybe we just cut Cass,
because then
Karla's on her own completely.
I don't know how you feel.
I-I...
This is a huge vote.
- Yeah.
- This is a huge vote,
- because we got to get
our numbers lined up.
- Yeah.
CODY:
This is a super crucial vote.
'Cause at this point, I think,
you know, people are starting
to think
of their final three,
their final five, their final...
You know, it's getting
to that part of the game where
you got to decide who
your alliance is gonna be
and make it strong now because
this vote is about setting up
the final stages of this game.
So how do we
tell Gabler how this works?
- I think we just tell Gabler
how we're gonna do it.
- Yeah.
Just say, like...
I've always liked Gabler.
He's been a pretty straight
shooter this whole time,
and he's a free agent
that will be loyal.
And that's somebody
I want to pick up.
Deal.
- 100%. 100%, right here.
- Yeah?
GABLER: Deal.
Cody approached me and said,
"I think we can work together."
That's music to my ears, 'cause
I'm thinking the same thing.
I think I've
positioned myself pretty well
17 days in,
where people are approaching me,
and that is so crucial going
into this point in the game.
CODY:
I don't know what's gonna
happen between Ryan and Cass.
I haven't decided
where our vote's gonna go.
- I don't think Jesse has.
- GABLER: Okay.
- Uh, obviously we know where
Ryan and Cass' is going. Um...
- Okay.
I think it's gonna depend on
who's out in the other vote.
GABLER:
Yeah.
But I want to be 100%, like,
ride or... die, bro.
- Let's do it.
- Like, I want
all of us together, like...
CODY:
Now that Gabler
is a rock-solid pair with us,
myself, Gabler and Jesse are
driving the decision tonight.
I don't know if
it's gonna be Ryan or Cassidy,
but I think if tonight's
vote goes accordingly,
we're on the freaking Autobahn
to the million dollars.
♪ ♪
...plays a Shot in the Dark,
we have a backup plan.
- Oh.
- So...
- So he can't
play Shot in the Dark?
- Exactly.
- Makes sense.
- You good with that?
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- So just in case.
This whole time I've been
telling people, "Vote Owen out,"
but I am not gonna do that.
I've been wanting
to get James out of this game.
I mean, he has Cass and he
has Karla in his back pocket.
He's the one
that's kind of
running everything.
- So you're good with that?
Okay. Okay.
- Yeah. That's fine.
My plan is to make James
feel comfortable enough
to not play
his Knowledge Is Power.
Okay cool. That makes sense.
I woke up this morning
wanting to make a big move.
I have a Steal a Vote Advantage,
and I'm hoping
that I can pull off
a major blindside on James.
This is what we're doing.
Okay.
Yeah.
- This is perfect.
- Yeah.
- This is...
- But yeah, I trust you.
God bless her. I love that girl.
The plan is to use
Noelle's Steal a Vote
against me,
but to not vote against me.
And this is
to provide the smoke screen
so that James does not
use his Knowledge Is Power.
I know James is voting for me,
but Sami, Noelle and myself
will turn the tables
and vote out James.
Okay, so if me and you
aren't on the same vote tonight,
that's not what I want.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Same. Yeah, I know.
- That's what I'm saying.
'Cause obviously we know
who the-the two people who
are, you know, going to write
each other's name down.
- Yes.
- Obviously.
- What's-what's...
- What's the best deal here?
Yeah.
I think Owen is the easiest
option for us moving forward,
because James,
he's definitely with us.
- Does that make sense?
- 100%.
Owen and Noelle believe that
I'm ready to take out James,
but Karla's opinion
matters more to me
than anybody else's
does right now.
Karla doesn't
want Owen in the game,
and I want to work with Karla.
And as much as I love James,
it just makes the most sense
to get rid of him.
So I need to convince Karla
that this
is the right thing to do.
You got to listen to me,
you got to listen good.
KARLA:
What?
SAMI:
I think it could be James.
What's the reason?
You trust me or James more?
- Why?
- I know it sounds crazy.
It is crazy.
The plan is to vote Owen out,
but then, all of a sudden,
Sami's like,
"What about James?"
That just
doesn't sit well with me.
How bad would it be
if James was not here?
It's gonna be bad. We're
gonna go against a majority
that's gonna be like, "Why the
...did y'all vote James out?"
If the vote goes with James,
I don't think
it's gonna be that bad.
That's what
I'm trying to tell you.
Owen is expendable
because he has nothing.
And Owen and Noelle,
they don't have
the Steal a Vote anymore,
because she's
gonna use it tonight.
We will not have another time
where there's
not chaos going around.
KARLA:
Sami kind of makes sense.
James is a strategic player.
Everyone believes that
he's been calling all the shots.
However, James
is really valuable right now.
And why would I
get rid of one of my numbers?
If we go with Owen,
Owen's a simple vote,
in the sense that
he's already been on the bottom.
But I'm in
a decision-making position
because I'm safe tonight,
and I have Sami voting with me.
So I want to make
the decision that
works best for me,
but also works best
for the future
of the people that I say
I'm gonna work with.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right. So let's recap.
Karla, you win immunity.
- Yes. Thank you.
- PROBST: Congratulations.
But in addition,
as a penalty for losing,
you all got sent back to Vesi.
Owen, what was your reaction?
OWEN:
It's just like
an extra kick in the backside.
Like, not have rice,
have underripe papaya.
Cody's peed all over that camp.
Like, it's really just...
It was
a pretty crappy afternoon.
James, that's a fair response.
This game is punishing.
Jeff, I feel like
losing in this game,
like not eating in this game
and the frustration of
this game can get to everybody.
And I feel like
there was frustration
back at the beach,
and, you know,
that happens with this game.
PROBST:
Sami, are you aware
of what James is alluding to?
- Yeah, I'm aware
of what James is alluding to.
- [laughs]
SAMI:
Uh, in terms of frustrations.
PROBST:
What happened?
Um, Owen
went off to the water well,
and James followed him,
and then there was a little bit
of back and forth
going on when they came back.
I think that
the two of these guys,
they just have a lot of
mutual respect for each other...
...but they just
can't get along in the game.
We were able
to have civil conversations
throughout the rest of the day.
PROBST:
Owen, Sami's answer
sounded like a coach.
- Yeah. [laughs]
- He's got a couple
of high-priced players
that he wants to stay on
the team. He's like, "You know,
- there's just differences.
They work it out."
- [laughs]
So is this an argument
or just a discussion?
I was definitely upset, disappointed,
frustrated after being
left out of the vote last night,
when Jeanine went home.
I felt that
James had a big part in that.
He told me
to do a certain thing,
and that ended up
not being what happened.
So today I was just
airing some of my frustrations,
and I just ended up
kind of losing my cool a bit,
raising my voice
when I probably shouldn't have.
PROBST:
Okay, so wait. Now, hang on.
That sounds like there was
a little more to it
than just a conversation.
- No, there was yelling.
There was yelling.
- Yeah, there was...
I mean, I'm trying
to eat frickin' ripe papaya
without a machete,
and I'm chewing into it.
Then all of a sudden,
I hear these two yelling,
- coming back
from the water well.
- Yeah.
And James
throwing up his hands saying,
-"There's nothing I can do."
And Owen...
- [laughs]
NOELLE:
Owen basically kind of
giving him a little swear,
- like, "... off."
- Here's what happened, Jeff.
So, we're talking at the well.
I'm getting frustrated at James,
given
the Jeanine Tribal Council.
I'm saying, "What else
can I do to prove to you
"that I'm open for business?
You told me to vote for Ryan.
I voted for Ryan."
I asked you to vote for Ryan,
and that was a form of trust.
And you did that,
and you-you had my trust.
You're frustrated
because you feel like
you're in a bad spot
in this game,
and you were frustrated
and you let it out.
And I'm sorry you did that, but
don't act like it was my fault.
You were following me back
after I tried to end
- the conversation, and you
were trying to talk to me
- I was walking...
- All right, we're done.
- after I said,
"We're done talking."
Too much testosterone.
I'm done with it.
PROBST:
So I think
I understand what happened.
Tell me if I got this right.
Owen, you're frustrated because
James said vote Ryan, and you
did, but that wasn't the vote.
And James is saying,
"You want to earn my trust.
"You did. You voted Ryan.
It wasn't the vote,
but you were trustworthy to me."
- Is that right, James?
- JAMES: Correct.
And I feel like trust
is the key currency
in this social contract,
as you said,
that's Survivor right now.
Last Tribal's vote showed trust.
And I feel like
we'll leave this Tribal
with more trust moving forward.
PROBST:
Okay, so you're at Vesi beach.
You've only got five people.
You don't know what's happening
on the other beach,
but now you
have to get down to the vote.
So, Karla, what did you
feel was happening?
KARLA:
It's-it's hard in this game,
even for myself.
Like, I-I have
an immunity right now,
but I don't know if what people
are telling me
is the truth or is a lie.
I've learned today
that you really have
to trust in yourself first,
and go with that feeling,
and hopefully
you continue to move forward.
James, how much talk was there...
Or maybe none at all...
About how one advantage tonight
with only five people
could flip everything?
I think,
on the talk about advantages,
that one advantage can really
make a situation very simple
and shore up trust
and help everybody move forward.
PROBST:
That's interesting, Noelle.
That's a way of looking at it
as a positive thing.
The other side of an advantage
is, "Oh, if somebody has one,
they could disrupt my plan,"
which would be a negative thing.
It is really difficult to
find something of an advantage
or an idol and not tell anybody.
You have to kind of
use them in your favor,
and you have to be like,
"Listen,
"I'm putting this in
with our alliance.
"I'm using this with us.
I hope I can gain your trust.
Like, this isn't just for me.
This is for us."
That's what the basis
is for me moving forward
to make alliances stronger
the best that I can.
All right, it is...
Time to vote, right?
You have an advantage?
NOELLE:
I have an advantage, Jeff.
PROBST:
All right, read the advantage.
NOELLE:
All right.
"Congratulations. You made
a risky decision and it worked.
"This advantage
allows you to steal a vote
"from another player
at Tribal Council.
"The player whose vote
you steal will not vote.
Instead,
you will cast a second vote."
PROBST:
All right.
So, you have the opportunity
to take somebody's vote
and make it yours.
Whose vote
are you going to steal?
I'm stealing Owen's.
PROBST:
All right. Owen, you're nodding.
Well, I was on the journey
with Noelle and James,
ironically enough,
back on day four.
She felt she was
on the bottom at Vesi,
so we both extended
the olive branch and let her
take the advantage that day,
and, uh...
We'll see what happens.
All right, so you are
stealing Owen's vote.
Owen, you will not vote.
Noelle, when you go up,
you will vote twice.
Okay.
PROBST:
All right. James, you're up.
♪ ♪
[sighs] My gosh, bro.
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote, Owen.
James. One vote Owen,
one vote James.
♪ ♪
James. That's two votes James,
one vote Owen.
Oh, baby.
Ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury...
James.
That's three. That's enough.
You need to bring me a torch.
JAMES:
Woo-hoo. Good move, guys.
Like, for real, man.
Man.
I'll take that
as respect, though.
Yeah, that's a sign of respect.
[scoffs]
See how far y'all get now.
[laughs]
- Thank you, Jeff.
- PROBST: James,
- the tribe has spoken.
- Cool beans.
PROBST:
Take a seat on the jury.
♪ ♪
You can grab your torches,
head back to camp.
We'll bring in the next group.
Good night, Jeff.
I had a great time out here.
I played
the best game I could play.
I wouldn't trade this experience
for anything in the world.
I feel like people
thought that if I made it
past this vote,
they would have no other chance
to get me out,
but I wasn't a big fish to fry.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, let's start
with the obvious.
Big part of the advantage
is you get to come second
and see what the other five did.
You see James on the jury.
Jesse, surprised?
Or is it impossible
to know what was going on?
JESSE:
I'm a little bit shocked.
James seemed to have a lot
going for him in the game,
and I know he had an advantage...
Knowledge Is Power...
And there were some advantages
at play in the last Tribal,
so I thought
he might be able to, like,
make a move and didn't
expect to see him over there.
Ryan, are you
surprised by this result?
Uh, yeah, I wasn't
expecting him over there.
What's gonna happen
when you go back to camp?
RYAN:
For me, I'm gonna
want to talk to everybody
that was at the last Tribal,
the Tribal before us.
I really want
to see where everybody lies,
what really happened,
so I can understand
who's making moves,
who's shaking things up,
because there
were some alliances
that James was a part of
that is now really shattered
a little bit without him there.
All right,
so let's get into this five.
You had a different afternoon.
Cassidy, what was the vibe like?
CASSIDY:
For me, it was glorious.
I've been dreaming
about peanut butter and jelly
for, like, 12 or 13 days,
but, you know, the game
doesn't stop for anybody,
so you realize, "Bam, I'm right
back in the belly of the beast."
You know? And-and here we are
back in a small tribe dynamic.
And the monster tonight
is also hungry.
It wants two heads
for the price of one.
It wants everybody
front and center,
so it can pick and choose
who it wants to devour tonight.
You know? Except for Cody, who's
protected by the golden monkey.
- But...
- [laughter]
PROBST:
The golden monkey. I like it.
[Cassidy laughs]
PROBST:
So, Ryan, Cassidy
said it really well.
The fact that
there's only five people
means there has to be some
level of concern for everyone.
RYAN:
I would have to definitely
agree with that, Jeff.
And now when we hear
our name on that vote,
- it has a lot more ring to it.
- Oh, yeah.
It's a lot more dangerous,
'cause three Ryans
can mean I'm out.
So it's-it's a lot scarier.
I'm not ready for you
to come down here and say,
"Okay, I'm gonna
read the votes."
Cassidy, what's that like
when you see somebody
that you just talked to,
and then they walk down
the beach with somebody else?
What are you thinking?
What are the fears?
At this point, you're kind of
starting to get used to it
and knowing that
it's an inevitable evil,
but it is a little
nerve-wracking,
because they could be
talking to you,
and then going and laughing
about you to another person,
and be like, "Ha, ha,
they believe me about this."
So you just never know
what kind of conversations
people are having.
It's like,
you almost wish
you had a can that you could,
like, somehow I don't know,
string over there...
and listen
to their conversation.
I don't know. Maybe you could
get crafty, but it is tough.
It's nerve-wracking, always.
PROBST:
So, Cody, you're
in that great spot
where you have
no concern tonight
but you still
have a long-term plan,
so you still want
to influence the vote.
What's the perspective,
given this is the first time
you've had the necklace?
Oh, yeah. The reality of it is
is I'm the man of the hour,
and everybody
wants to talk to me,
wants to tell me their story.
And I'm kind of just going,
"Whew.
This is a heavy position,"
because to your point,
I've got
to look votes down the road
knowing that my vote...
In literally a 25% chance
of each one of these...
Is going to be heavy
as to who goes home tonight.
And, um, I wouldn't give
this necklace up for anything,
but it is certainly a different
way to view the game, um,
when you do have this on.
Ryan, is it clear that,
at least today,
that Cody
was central in everything
because he has a necklace, and
therefore he knows he's safe?
I noticed the conversation
with Cody took a bit longer
than the conversations
people had with me.
Of course, when you're
not being talked to as much,
you kind of worry a little bit,
but you do get your word in
with each person.
I know, me, personally,
I have 30 pounds
of giant clamshells in my bag,
so if I get voted out, I
get to take those home with me.
So, you know,
I've been lugging that around,
just in case I'm walking
out with my torch snuffed.
PROBST:
How about you, Cassidy?
Yeah, I mean, it's, like,
really tight numbers right now,
so if one thing goes wrong,
it can blow up the whole plan.
Whatever we do tonight
is going to have impacts
that will probably reverberate
throughout the rest of what
we see happen in this game.
All right, it is time to vote.
Ryan, you're up.
♪ ♪
I've been left out
from Coco from the beginning,
so I'm trying
to get the power back.
This is the final part
of my revenge plan,
and it's pretty poetic
because I know
you're coming after me again.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
♪ ♪
First vote, Cassidy.
Ryan.
One vote Ryan, one vote Cassidy.
♪ ♪
Ryan.
Two votes Ryan,
one vote Cassidy.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member
of our jury, Ryan.
- That's three. That's enough.
You need to bring your torch.
- All right.
We're gonna go hungry now.
[Ryan laughs]
You got to keep 'em fed.
It's your turn to fish.
Thanks, brother.
Ryan, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Yeah.
Sami... I can't
freaking trust the guy.
The speed of the game
has been absolutely relentless.
I'm feeling great
about where I'm at.
I, uh, just got blindsided.
Honestly, I'm not
even really disappointed.
I played as hard as I could.
I got to go fishing
like I wanted.
I thought I could
help people get farther
than they thought
I could help them get.
So I guess they saw me more as
a threat than a benefit to have.
But I'm definitely excited
to see how this game goes
and how they're gonna play.
[roars]