♪ ♪
CODY:
Tribal went well.
Jesse and I
decided to make a big move
and vote out Dwight.
Team Coco jumped on board.
Me, Jesse, Team Coco.
And then, to my surprise,
who I would have never thought,
Sami jumped on board, as well.
SAMI:
That went the way
it was supposed to.
It's tough to vote
somebody out of my own tribe.
- Obviously, but...
- Uh-huh.
- It worked out. And it's fun.
- Anyways.
- All right, bro, cool.
- It was an honor sitting by you.
- It was a lot of fun.
- I know. Let's do it again.
CODY:
Before Tribal,
it was pretty common knowledge
that James had gotten
the Knowledge
Is Power Advantage.
And everybody
was in a panic mode,
moving around
advantages and idols.
But when you
hand that thing over,
you got to hope and pray
that you
made the right decision.
SAMI:
At this point, if you never
want to talk to me again,
I get it. But I want you
to listen to me, at least,
- Yeah.
- For a little bit,
because this
is the second time in a row
- you had no idea
what was happening.
- Yeah.
And you guys have to understand,
I find out
Jesse and Cody are flipping.
Mm-hmm.
Dwight's going home, regardless.
JEANINE: Tribal ended up being
worst-case scenario for me
in every possible way.
I lost an ally in Dwight.
And before Tribal Council,
I had given
Dwight my idol to hold on to.
Okay.
It's not going anywhere?
I'll wash it off
before giving it back to you.
Oh, thank you.
I was on such a high, and then
everything slipped
through my fingers.
I was so shocked.
I blacked out
the moment where
he got his torch snuffed.
And I'm like,
"I'm a freaking idiot
and had my idol
go home in Dwight's crotch."
SAMI: I know.
I get how hard it will be
to listen to me at this point,
but nobody even wanted to, like,
consider working with you while
the idol was still in the game.
JEANINE:
This can't be real.
This can't be happening.
I have no numbers, no immunity
and no idea of how to even
start picking up the pieces.
SAMI:
Dwight had Jeanine's idol.
- He had Jeanine's idol.
- Yeah, so...
I didn't want it...
We didn't want it here.
He literally went home
with Jeanine's idol.
That's freaking amazing.
You all know
where Jeanine's idol was?
- KARLA: No, where?
- Where?
- Dwight's pocket.
- [gasping]
- KARLA: No.
- CASSIDY: So it turns out
Jeanine's idol got flushed
sort of on accident.
It's insane.
Like, the idol's gone.
So it was kind of perfect.
JESSE:
They were shuffling advantages,
because they were scared
of whatever you have.
- Yep.
The last thing I heard,
in the shuffle,
was that it went
into Dwight's pocket.
- He had it.
- And so...
- I'm telling you, he had it.
- Yeah.
Everybody's high-fiving
because Dwight went home
with an idol in his pocket. But
that idol is... in my pocket,
and nobody knows about it.
[laughs]
JESSE:
Before Tribal Council,
Dwight comes up to me,
he's panicked,
and so he drops the idol
in my pocket.
This is awesome.
I already have Cody's idol
that he gave me and he hasn't
asked for it back yet, so, like,
in a way,
I kind of have two idols here.
JAMES:
A idol may be back
in circulation now.
But here's the thing, though:
I can take it.
SAMI: Uh-huh.
Knowledge is power in this game,
and I know there's a Knowledge
Is Power floating around.
So I'm keeping the idol
to myself.
That way I can make big moves
that people aren't necessarily
seeing until it's too late.
♪ ♪
JEANINE: Yeah.
Then we can write our names,
like, just wherever.
I like that idea.
CASSIDY:
This is so cute. I'm excited.
- KARLA: Just like this?
- CASSIDY: Yeah.
- Perfect.
- Okay.
SAMI:
That looks really good.
Un poquito.
Un poquito?
Yeah.
His parents only speak Spanish.
- And so, like, I went
and I met them, and, like...
- [gasps] Oh.
- OWEN: Oh, that's tough.
- So, like,
they said, like, "I love you."
And that was, like,
the only words they could say.
- And, like, it was just
my first time meeting them.
- Aw.
- But, like, I just couldn't say
anything, so it's all weird.
- OWEN: Oh, that's hard.
- That is weird.
- Yeah.
I tried to teach myself
a little Korean
- in the middle of the pandemic.
- [laughs]
I was like,
"Maybe I should learn this."
'Cause I'm adopted.
I don't know
if y'all had heard that part...
- NOELLE: Oh. No.
- Yeah, I have white,
I have white parents, so...
- Oh.
- I didn't grow up with
a lot of Korean culture.
Kind of rejected it a bit,
but coming around.
It's nice.
So I was adopted
when I was four months old.
I was born in Korea.
Owen Knight is not
a particularly Korean name.
My parents are amazing.
I've had a wonderful,
wonderful life,
but I was not like most kids.
Being Asian
was what made me different
and I just wanted to fit in.
I wanted
to be a "regular kid" and just,
like, get the same haircut,
and it just, i-it was isolating.
And now this game
reminds me of my childhood.
Being left out of the vote
two Tribal Councils in a row,
it's hard to not blame myself
and wonder what's wrong with me.
Hopefully I'll hear if my name
comes up, but it's scary.
I was not on the bus yesterday,
and, like,
I just thought the numbers
- were going
the other direction, so...
- Yeah.
It feels like I'm running
around the playground
asking people to play with me
and no one wants to.
If making final Tribal
is getting into college,
right now, my transcript
is sorry.
I have a 1.7 GPA right now.
My extracurriculars
are in the toilet.
I've got no recommendations.
Nobody has anything good
to say about me right now.
So I just need
to take a breath and reset
and remind myself
I'm here to have fun
and that we are
all on our own personal journey.
I have hope that
there's room to maneuver
and that there are some people
who feel left out,
feel on the bottom,
and that we can start a little
uprising of sorts.
It's finally
just us bottom dwellers.
JEANINE:
I don't understand
how it flipped so quickly.
I guess Jesse and Cody were
threatened by Dwight and that...
...they saw the opportunity.
NOELLE: Cody and Jesse flipped,
and I was left in the dark.
And that's shame on me,
because people started
playing this game before I did,
and that's just
a kick in the ass.
I'm not ready
to go down without a fight.
Like, we still have us three.
We have Gabler.
- OWEN: We need two more.
- We need two more.
NOELLE:
Right now, it seems
like us three
and Gabler
are on the bottom, but
I don't believe the seven people
that voted last night
are seven strong,
and they're gonna be like,
"This is gonna
be the final seven."
I don't believe that.
That never works out.
KARLA:
How are you?
JAMES:
I feel pretty good.
Have you started feeling
anyone out or anything out yet?
JAMES:
Right now, we have seven
with that last vote.
That can take us pretty far.
Like, this makes me
extremely happy, is that we...
KARLA: I know.
[chuckles]
Coming out of Tribal Council,
the seven
that voted out Dwight
were me, James, Cassidy,
Karla, Cody, Sami and Ryan.
And we all seem to be
on the same page that, like,
this could be the seven,
right, that make it,
and then we sort of, like,
all guns blaze
and we'll just
turn on each other.
That would be awesome
if we could just, like,
skip to our Lou to the end of,
you know, the game.
- KARLA: What do we think...
- CASSIDY: What's next?
KARLA:
Yeah, what's next?
Does anybody have a preference?
So, I think Owen.
Owen is kind of a snake.
I don't think he really has,
like, a backbone.
He's not gonna ever
put his foot down.
He's always gonna
follow the numbers,
and that's dangerous
in this game.
I have strong opinions
about who should go.
I really want Owen out.
He voted for me
at two previous Tribal Councils.
He is not my friend
in this game, and
when you have an opportunity
to take someone out
that you really,
really don't trust,
you take that person out.
♪ ♪
KARLA: I had a dream...
This is gonna sound so stupid.
[chuckles softly]
I... My dreams are wild here.
Probst was there.
It was, like,
an eating competition,
but it was, like,
a lot of chicken.
It was, like, a lot of chicken.
But then Probst was like,
"I'm hungry."
And I was like, "Here,
you could have some of mine."
And then he decides
to make ramen. [laughs]
- Ramen, and that's his lunch.
- [laughter]
And he proceeds to, like,
get in the middle of all of us,
- kind of like crowd-surf.
- What?
And he's like,
"All right, selfie time."
You know, "Picture time."
And I'm like,
- "This is weirdest thing ever."
- RYAN: That is an awesome dream.
Yeah, you had a good dream, man.
That's great.
[laughter]
KARLA:
I'm really dreaming about food.
People are definitely
hungry right now.
People are starving, um...
We've been talking
about food just constantly.
I want to eat every... something
from every one on the menu.
Like an appetizer,
a regular entrée
and a dessert,
'cause I never do that.
RYAN:
I'm gonna order the pepperoni
stuffed crust, right?
I'm-a get two of those.
And then I'm gonna
pick up really good bur...
a few really good burritos.
And those are gonna
get wrapped with the pizza.
- CODY: Oh, God.
- Yeah.
I'm glad you're excited about
it. I don't know if I could
- do the pizza... the burrito
- JEANINE: I'm not on board
- wrapped in pizza.
- With the pizza burrito.
GABLER: You know,
I don't need to eat
to win this game.
I think that is a luxury.
But check this out, boys.
I had a muffin top
coming out here,
but the wolf pack is hungry.
Everybody is
physically depleted.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Ah, daddy-o.
Last night's Tribal,
I was on the wrong side
of the votes.
So today, I'm gonna spearfish,
trying to curry favor
with everybody,
but our biggest food provider,
bar none, is Ryan.
Uh, he loves to do it.
He's just, you know,
he's an absolute physical beast.
RYAN: I went from,
as a kid with cerebral palsy,
being told, "You can't walk.
"You're gonna
to be in a wheelchair,
and your mom's gonna have
to help you most of your life,"
to catching fish
in the Fijian waters.
♪ ♪
[whoops]
If I had given up
on trying to walk,
if I had given up
on being myself
and really caring about others,
I probably wouldn't be
as far as I am in this game
and I probably
wouldn't be on Survivor.
And being a provider...
That is 100%
part of my strategy.
Nobody else was catching fish
like I was.
So, I feel like Aquaman
out there with my little spear.
My family's gonna
be so proud of me.
Oh, heck yeah, dude.
You're like a superhero, dude.
I keep saying it.
I think I could
survive out here.
That's why I'm going out here
and getting you guys fish,
even though, you know, next vote
it could be me, you know?
You know, you-you acknowledge
you're a-a big guy,
physically intimidating,
a little bit, right?
RYAN:
I hope people
don't see me as a threat.
Well, I think you
made quite the impression.
RYAN:
Of course, they're
gonna see me as a threat
in the challenges,
but at the same time,
I showed I'm a hard worker.
I'm willing to spend my calories
to get everybody else food,
but not only that,
since I am part of the seven,
I can trust the alliance
that I have.
Feel good. Do you feel
good about the seven, Cody?
CODY:
Absolutely.
- Take the gloves off
and let's just throw punches.
- KARLA: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
SAMI: With this newfound seven
of Cody, Jesse,
myself, Karla,
James, Ryan and Cassidy,
where do I fall
Within that group?
- It's, like, the line
is, like, drawn, seven-four.
- Yeah. It really is.
It would be stupid to say,
"That's the seven to go with
and then we make final seven."
- I'm not here
to play for final seven.
- No.
- I'm here to play to win.
- Play to win.
SAMI:
I'm trying to set myself up
at 19 to win this game.
Not to make it to the end
and not get any respect.
That's not what I want to do.
I want to be in control
and make decisions
for the rest of this game.
It's seven to four.
I don't want to go
get rid of you,
you, Gabler and Noelle.
Where does that leave me?
I'm at the bottom of the seven.
I don't want to be there.
You're seventh on there, like...
No, no, I know.
SAMI:
I don't want to go that way.
- That's why
I'm talking to you guys.
- I know. I know, exactly...
At the end of the day,
we still have four with Gabler.
- Yeah.
- And then we have Noelle.
And then, at that point,
we're one off.
- JEANINE: We're one off.
- OWEN: One more.
- All we need is six.
OWEN:
Thank God.
I feel like my game
has a little bit of hope.
We just need one
other person to maybe try
to turn the tables and
take down
some of the big players
who are starting
to get big heads right now.
That group thinks that
one of the four of you guys
- will probably just go home.
- Yeah.
- It's probably me.
- That's not
the way the game should go.
- OWEN: No.
- That's not the way
I think the game should go.
- I agree. I agree.
SAMI:
I feel like the seven
is sitting pretty
on a sinking ship,
but I need to act like
I'm still with that group.
Otherwise, they're
gonna start to be suspicious.
We're at war,
and I'm with the right folks.
JAMES:
That was the point, man. So...
I know.
It's one less person
to worry about.
- And at the end of the day...
- And he's definitely a flipper.
And those are the people
that are dangerous.
SAMI:
On Survivor,
it's all about windows.
It's all about,
"When am I gonna make my move?"
And with a million freaking
dollars on the line,
this game
is only gonna get crazier.
The moves are only gonna
become shadier and
more cutthroat. This is where
good players survive
and great players thrive.
This adventure could be yours.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right.
- Shall we get to it?
- Yes, sir.
First things first, Gabler,
got to take back the necklace.
- Yes, sir.
- You're gonna
make me take it off.
Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
- [exhales sharply]
- PROBST: For today's challenge,
you're gonna
balance a ball on a pole.
At regular intervals,
you're gonna
add another section of pole,
making it more difficult.
If at any point
your ball drops...
...you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the eighth person
voted out of this game
and the first member
of our jury.
So it's day 16,
and even though
we're still in the early days
of this still evolving
new era of Survivor,
there are
already certain markers
that the smart player
has identified.
Today is another
one of those markers.
There's enough rice in here
for four days for every player...
A lot longer if you ration it.
The established price
for this rice in this new era
is five players.
Still less than half of you
must sit out of this challenge,
give up your shot at immunity,
in exchange
for rice for everybody.
So take a minute. Walk me
through your thought process.
JAMES:
Jeff, can we do four players?
PROBST:
No.
I'll be fully transparent
in my negotiating approach.
Today is the only day
it will cost you five players.
Tomorrow it will be
more expensive.
Nobody talking.
I'm hungry.
- So I-I can.
- I'm game.
- I don't mind.
- KARLA: I...
My finger's busted.
- And this
is a gripping challenge.
- SAMI: I mean...
I will-I will do it.
- JESSE: I'll sit out.
- PROBST: There's two.
- You'll sit out? I'll sit out.
- Yeah, my hand's...
PROBST:
There's three. There's four.
Yeah.
We need one more
to make this deal done.
Day 16. That is a lot of rice.
- Uno más. Taco Bell.
- PROBST: That'll wake you up.
- That will give you energy.
- CASSIDY: All right.
- I'll do it.
- PROBST: And there goes Cassidy.
We have our five.
- RYAN: Thank you, guys.
- PROBST: James, Sami, Jesse,
Cassidy, Karla
agreeing to sit out.
Sami, that
was a pretty fast agreement
for five players with
a million dollars on the line.
Where are we in the game
that this group
is volunteering to do it
with no certainty that it won't
be you that goes home tonight?
Yeah, it's crazy, 'cause, like,
when you come out here,
you know,
"I want to compete,"
you know, "I'm this big guy.
Let me compete. Let me do it."
But, like, once you
get further down the road,
the-the deterioration
starts to take a toll on you.
Like, we're all deteriorated.
We're beat up.
We're all just a little hungry.
And if it is us tonight,
it's us tonight,
but we're ready
to give up our spots
so we can all have a little
bit more food in our stomachs.
PROBST:
Five of you are sitting out.
That is a massive risk.
Maybe the tribe
will treat you respectfully
and not vote you out,
or maybe we'll have
a big blindside tonight.
Who knows? James, Sami,
Jesse, Cassidy, Karla,
you're on the bench.
- Thank you guys.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
PROBST:
Everybody else
will draw for spots.
We'll get started.
Here we go.
Day 16, Survivor 43.
All right, we have our sit-outs.
Leaves us with six people
competing for immunity.
Let's begin.
Grab your first pole.
Put your ball on there.
All you have to do
for this first section
is to have
your hand under the paint.
- So you're either under the
white or you're under the black.
- Oh.
PROBST:
Just make sure
I can see a little gap.
Perfect. Everybody's good.
All right.
Let's add one section of pole.
You have 30 seconds
to pull this off.
This is a live transition,
which means
if your ball drops while you're
adding another section of pole,
you're still out.
There's no freebie.
♪ ♪
All you have to do now is move
your hand under the new coupler,
the lowest coupler.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody looks good.
All you have to do
is keep your ball on your pole.
That's it.
Every five minutes, we'll
add another section of pole.
The more pole,
the more difficult.
♪ ♪
All right, we're
gonna add another section.
Now you're gonna
feel the difficulty kick in.
This part
was probably pretty easy.
So long
as I can see that coupler
and no part
of your hand is above it,
you're in good shape.
Start working your way there.
Ryan's good. Gabler's good.
Jeanine can't
make the transition.
And Noelle,
right on the heels of Jeanine.
Both women are out.
Cody, Ryan, Gabler and Owen
all survive the transition.
- Good try.
- Good job. Good job.
PROBST:
Wow. Just like that.
Four players left.
All right, we're gonna get ready
to add another section.
You have 30 seconds.
Remember, you can't put
your hand above where it is now.
You can't really look down.
For fear of
taking your eyes off the prize.
So you've got to figure out
how to maneuver
that pole into its slot.
15 seconds.
Gabler's pole
with a lot of bend,
but that ball
still sitting okay.
- Damn.
- PROBST: Nope. It won't hold.
Gabler's out.
We're down to three.
Five, four,
three, two, one...
You are all good.
Gabler will now join
the others on the bench.
No shot
at getting that necklace back.
We'll go five minutes
in this round.
All right, we're gonna get ready
to add another section.
So start making your move.
So these 30 seconds
are yours to use strategically.
Go early, or wait and hope
somebody drops and go late.
15 seconds left.
Ryan has made the transition.
Cody.
Seven seconds left.
Owen's got to get
his hand down under there.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody's done it again.
Cody took every
single second, wisely.
It is Cody, Ryan and Owen
now with a lot of pole.
My toes are asleep.
My left foot is on fire.
No!
PROBST:
Ryan drops.
Thought he had a strategy
using his forehead,
but it resulted in that pole
bending a little too much, and
we're down to a showdown now.
It will either be Cody
or Owen who wears
the immunity necklace.
Keep doing what you're doing.
I know you're getting tired.
I know you're on fire.
It's hot out here.
Your hands
might be getting numb.
Your body's stiff.
You're afraid to move.
All of those things are part
of the design of this challenge.
You have
to overcome it right now.
If your leg goes to sleep,
rely on the other one.
♪ ♪
All right, get ready
to add another section of pole.
Think through this.
And your time starts now.
You have 30 seconds
to add another piece of pole.
You just need to make
this transition successfully
to stay alive.
Cody goes first.
Owen reaches
for his section of pole.
Owen locks in.
- GABLER: Oh, my...
- Careful.
PROBST:
Cody drops,
can't make the transition.
- Owen wins individual immunity.
- Let's go! Oh, my God.
- PROBST: Safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
- GABLER: Amazing.
- OWEN: Oh, my God.
- PROBST: Guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
- Great effort
from both Cody and Owen.
- GABLER: Both you guys. Amazing.
PROBST:
Nice job up there.
GABLER:
Cowboy Cody and Big O, good job.
- PROBST: Wow,
that went a long time.
- OTHERS: Good job.
Great job, guys.
Owen, come on over.
[exhales] Yes, sir.
- [Sami whoops]
- [chuckles]
- PROBST: Well-earned.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- [applause]
- Holding that a long time.
- SAMI: Yes, sir.
Oh, my God. Is this real life?
PROBST:
"Is this real life?"
What does that mean?
Walk me through that,
because I hear that
- so often in this moment.
- OWEN: Yeah.
I mean, you're a little kid,
and you-you watch Colby,
you watch Terry Deitz,
you watch Kelly Wiglesworth.
You watch everyone
winning all these necklaces.
- You're going old school.
- Old school, baby.
That was me, nine years old,
watching this show,
and I want to do that one day.
- And you're showing you can.
- And I'm not... I can.
I'm not the biggest,
I'm not the strongest,
but I-I just did that.
It's insane.
All right, Owen,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
cannot be
voted out of this game.
As for the rest of you,
somebody going home tonight...
Eighth person voted out,
first member of our jury.
Grab your stuff, head back to
camp. See you tonight at Tribal.
- Congrats.
- Can I give you a hug, man?
- Yeah, of course. Congrats.
- Oh, my God. Thank you.
- Enjoy that necklace.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Oh, my God.
- GABLER: Animal.
Owen won immunity,
which puts me, Noelle
and Jeanine in the hot seat.
I think the majority alliance
smell blood.
I'm trying to find safe harbor,
because as long as
my name doesn't hit parchment,
I'm moving forward.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Yeah, baby.
Good job, Ryan.
GABLER:
Yeah, Ryan. Great job, Owen.
- Nice work, buddy.
- Thank you.
Winning today is just
such a huge sigh of relief.
I've voted incorrectly
the past two Tribal Councils.
And whether or not
the seven versus four
is the reality out here,
it's safe to say
I'm towards the bottom.
SAMI:
We're gonna eat, right?
- Yeah.
- GABLER: A cup of rice
for everybody.
- Let's get a good meal.
- NOELLE: Do the same cup,
and then, like...
OWEN:
At the immunity challenge,
Jeff was asking
for five to sit out,
and James turns
and looks at me, and he says,
"You're protected."
Like, spare me that crap.
I thought that
was pretty patronizing.
So that gave me a little
extra fire to-to win today.
But I know this is temporary.
I don't want to get too cocky.
I need to get my footing,
get a majority and find myself
on the right side
of the numbers.
I'm gonna go fish
in about 30 minutes to an hour.
I just need to talk to you guys
and get everything situated,
- so I'm not... Yeah.
- GABLER: Before you go out.
JAMES: So, just...
- That's why she didn't sit out.
- If she had something,
she would have sat out.
- GABLER: Yeah.
RYAN:
Owen won the immunity challenge.
Great for him,
and horrible for Jeanine.
Now that she doesn't
have her immunity idol,
Jeanine's gonna go home.
Yeah.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Yeah. I'm down.
So, uh...
- So we're all good.
- KARLA: Okay.
RYAN:
Jeanine's
the vote tonight because
she's definitely a smart mind,
a puzzle threat
and also a threat to slide
under the radar.
Right now, it's fine.
We'll get Jeanine out, 'cause
she's not part of anything,
- and she's really smart.
- If we can...
- And I-I agree.
- So... Awesome.
- Well, then
I'll keep a pulse over here
- And I...
- while you're out there.
- Yeah.
Just let me know
if you hear anything.
If anything changes.
I want an unanimous vote.
I just went and double-checked
it with everybody.
Took about ten, 15 minutes.
Now I can go out into the water
for two and a half hours,
because part of me
really wants to show them that
rice is nice,
but fish is a little bit better.
CODY:
I think Jeanine,
just because she is such
a free agent,
she's gonna align with somebody,
and it's gonna
bite us in the ass.
And everybody said they'd
like to keep the seven strong.
We made the bed. We just
got to sleep in it one night.
Last Tribal was really crazy.
People were running
around the beach
like Jean-Claude Van Damme.
We can simplify
this game to an extent.
Like, there can be
some simple votes.
But right now, we're cruising.
You know,
this alliance with seven,
I believe we're
running the game right now.
We have full control.
We're steering the boat.
I just want it
to look sick as hell.
Yeah, it's
got to be sick as hell.
Yeah, we are
definitely outdoing ourselves.
That is a work of art.
"Proposterous.
Live 2 Get Radical."
Who wouldn't want
to hang out with us?
[laughs]
SAMI:
This group of seven,
we're already talking about,
"Let's not mess up a good thing.
- We already did this."
- Oh, it's beautiful.
SAMI: But I want to screw up
this entire operation
to try to make a move
and try to kind of break away
and make this game my own.
It's gonna be... It's supposed
to be you. Ryan wants you.
It's not gonna be you tonight.
We got to get more people,
because then we turn it.
- They're down on numbers.
- Uh-huh.
SAMI:
We're good.
I'm telling you...
You also have to be careful,
because you got
to move more in silence
to make these bigger-scale
moves. But I think
getting out Ryan
would make the damage control,
with that group that
I just ditched, a lot easier.
He's not really
making tight bonds
with anybody,
except for the fish.
Ryan loves the fish,
and the fish love Ryan.
How do you feel about that?
I need to ask you
a serious question.
Okay.
What would you think
if we flipped it on to Ryan?
Because I know that
that's-that's in that seven,
and I don't want
to make it seem like
- I'm trying to
break off that already, right?
- Mm-hmm.
You know, at this point,
it's an individual game.
Ryan is a big threat.
Even though he's Coco, that
doesn't matter to me, you know?
You're serious
about that, right?
KARLA: I'm excited about
possibly blindsiding Ryan
because it's a great move,
it's a big move. We get a guy
out, we get a strong guy out,
but that might be questionable
for some of the people
in my alliance, in the seven.
We need to get Ryan out.
- I know you are.
- I'm-I'm rocking out
whatever you want to do.
KARLA:
I love the kid,
but he doesn't...
Where's he at right now?
He's fishing.
He's been gone for a few hours,
bro. Like, strategize,
right?
Like, we finally have rice.
I don't care about your fish.
Aah! Freaking spines.
They're in my pockets.
[groans]
- I'm with you. Yes.
- I'm with you.
I'm with you, too.
All right.
- All right, sounds good.
- Jesse!
Would we be down
to go with Ryan?
I-I mean, I'd be down.
I'd be down, bro.
I mean, he's...
I don't think
Cass likes him very much.
Like, I feel
like we could do damage.
- Yeah.
- And I know
Ryan has it out for me.
I mean, I don't want you to go.
- Yeah.
- So for my game,
I would say Ryan goes.
- I-I've wanted to get Ryan out
for a long time.
- Yeah.
- Well, he's been out
to get you for a long time.
- Yes.
JEANINE:
I know that
I'm on the chopping block,
but I'm not willing to bargain.
I'm not willing
to succumb to the majority.
Okay. Yeah. Done.
Hopefully he can catch
some nice, beautiful fish.
- Before he goes?
- JAMES: Yes.
JEANINE:
I need to secure
some sort of shift in the game.
There are enough people here
and enough voices that we could
work together and
we'll all just vote Ryan out.
If it's Jeanine, you can tell
me, and I won't say anymore.
- JAMES: We're voting Ryan,
and it is what it is.
- Okay. Cool.
- Just got to, you know...
- OWEN: Yeah.
JAMES:
This is a great time.
OWEN:
It seems like
everyone's on board.
So, were you still
thinking Ryan?
SAMI:
I think that could work.
I think it could be pulled off.
CODY:
To me, this is
a very obvious one.
JAMES:
But right now, it's like,
you take the numbers,
you use the numbers
that you have.
The only question, does Jeanine
have anything up her sleeve?
I'm just saying we made a plan.
- JAMES: Let's stick to it.
- I think she's scary.
I really think she's scary.
I agree with Cody.
So the more
I think about the vote,
the devil you know is better
than the devil you don't know.
And the thing about
sacrificing Ryan tonight,
Ryan's a vote with me,
as of right now,
and he has trusted me,
as of right now.
I don't know.
I want to make everybody
in our seven feel comfortable.
She's not a big threat.
I just feel like that's a vote
we could always do later.
I think we need to get out more
immediate threats right now.
Who are you wanting? You want
to take these, like, big...
- Just because you want them
to be, like, competitors?
- I don't.
I just don't...
Does it not frustrate you to see
the girls picked off one by one?
Mm-hmm.
There are people here that are
strong, yes, but also athletic.
- Like...
- But J-Jeanine may be athletic.
Just never mind.
It doesn't, it doesn't matter.
- I feel like this conversation
isn't getting anywhere.
- JAMES: No, it's cool.
CASSIDY:
I want to get
my revenge on Ryan.
He's burned me in the past
and tried to vote for me,
so he's proven that
I can't fully trust him. He also
is a threat in challenges.
21!
CODY:
All right, dude.
Wow.
CASSIDY:
And voting out a guy right now
would allow the women to gain
a little bit of momentum
and have a little bit stronger
of numbers going forward.
I'm tired
of seeing women go home.
I know that's
nobody's intention,
but it's frustrating to me.
We need to...
take control of this.
I know.
CASSIDY:
It seems like Ryan and Jeanine,
everyone could agree
on one or the other,
but I don't think
Ryan would have my back
more than Jeanine.
I am truly a ship
looking for safe harbor.
I just want to know what's
going on with the majority,
- so that I write
the right stuff.
- We-we still don't know, even.
CASSIDY:
Everyone seems scared
of being on
the wrong side of the votes.
If there's, like,
a unanimous decision on
one or the other, it's like,
maybe we should just go with it
instead of
trying to rock the boat.
They told me Ryan, too.
Is this actually... Is...
I don't know, Jeanine.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I might actually
have to trust James.
CASSIDY:
But I'm ready
to fight for my game,
so sometimes
you have to rock the boat.
Like, this is a cutthroat game.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, let's start
with a big topic.
Every season of Survivor
has a unique social contract
that is established,
designed, built
and executed by the players.
You all decide,
"Okay, here are the rules."
So, Gabler,
does this group have a sense
of what the established
social contract is?
GABLER:
I think so, Jeff.
It's been a relationship game,
and when you step
outside of that, especially
if you're starting to get
too aggressive with gameplay,
you kind of
get cracked into line.
So it has to be subtle.
And with every Tribal Council,
we learn a lot more
about those social constructs
and those borders and
where they're gonna be crossed.
Karla, do you agree
with Gabler's assessment?
I do agree that
there is some subtlety,
but at the same time, you can't
be subtle the entire time.
You know? Like,
how will people know
what moves you're making?
How will the jury
know who to vote for?
Ryan, does this
line up with the way
you're seeing the gameplay?
I think, this season,
we're comfortable enough to say,
"Hey, let's slow down, and
we'll get to playing the game."
But right now, a lot of people
are trying to step back
and enjoy what's around them
and enjoy the experience
they're having.
So, Owen,
that begs the question,
are people staying in line
because you all
actually share
the same philosophy?
Or is the player saying,
"I'm reading the room.
I need to just lay low"?
I think, truthfully,
it's more of the latter.
I don't think all of us are
out swimming for three hours
the way Ryan is, necessarily.
- [laughter]
But foolishly,
last Tribal Council,
I tried jumping
in front of Dwight
from getting run over
by the bus.
So now, at this point, I just,
I don't care if I'm in
the wayback seat of the bus.
I don't care
if I'm sitting anywhere.
Terrible seat,
gum under the seat, whatever,
I just want
to be on the bus this time.
SAMI:
But at the same time, the last
two people that went home
had no idea
they were going home.
And so, there's a lot of game
being played, a lot
of conversations being had.
Everybody that's sitting here
is playing this game.
Everybody's just playing
it a little bit differently.
Cassidy, do you like
the way this game is playing?
CASSIDY:
Yeah, I mean, for me,
my gameplay is
maybe a little bit more subtle,
but that doesn't mean that I'm
not making big moves, you know?
It's just about
keeping trust with the people
that I want to work with.
PROBST:
How about you, James?
Last Tribal,
there were a lot of lines
that may have been drawn,
but each day
a new line can be drawn,
and you're trying to make sure
that you're drawing the proper
line for you to move forward.
PROBST:
Jeanine, James just said it.
The thing that
really complicates
these Survivor societies
is that they're fluid.
So how do you play this game
knowing that what was
true yesterday,
or even this morning,
may not be true
right now, this evening?
JEANINE:
Yeah. Like we've all
been talking about,
there has been
a culture established,
but just as much as
it was easy for us to all
kind of opt into that culture,
it could change and shift.
And you have to understand
when that's happening
and go with the momentum there.
PROBST:
Gabler, what do you do
when you talk to two people,
and they say, "Plan A,"
and you talk to two more people,
and they go,
"No, no, we're doing plan B."
Oh, well, that's...
that was my day.
I mean, it's been
plan A, plan B,
plan A for sure, back to B.
It's bounced around
a little bit.
So, yeah, tonight's
gonna be interesting.
I think it's gonna
put a little bit more
into focus for tomorrow.
PROBST:
Cody, when you feel comfortable,
does that make you more nervous
that you're feeling comfortable?
I get more nervous
when I'm comfortable.
And, for example,
when we got back today,
I'm thinking,
we're starting the rice.
Get the pot on there, let's eat.
And I'm sitting by the firepit,
and I look around,
and there's nobody around.
I'm going, "What, do I have
to go herd cats out here?"
I thought we were
gonna smash some rice
- and then
go have our conversations.
- [chuckles]
I was trying to talk to people
quick, so I can go out and fish.
- So, we...
- He caught 22 fish today.
- 22 fish. 21 fish today.
- 21.
21?
That's a lot of fish.
RYAN:
I'm still not 100% comfortable.
I felt, you know,
I'm gonna try my luck
with the waters,
and if I bring back a bounty,
then they'll
keep me in the game.
Jeanine, were you
comfortable today?
No, I think it's pretty obvious.
There were lines
drawn at last Tribal,
and I was not
in the majority vote.
And so I'm-I'm definitely
not comfortable tonight.
So what did you do today?
Ryan went fishing.
JEANINE:
For me, it was really just about
trying to connect
with as many people as possible
and lean on the relationships
that I think I can out here.
But there's never any way
to tell if someone's
telling you the truth.
You really just
have to trust your gut.
CODY:
You know, this game,
I learned today, Jeff,
it's a game of centimeters,
or even less.
And those same centimeters
don't only carry over
into the challenges,
but they also carry into
the conversations that we have.
And just
misinterpreting one word,
- Wow.
- one body posture, can change
the whole outcome as well.
So I-I don't know
where I'm going with this,
at the end of the day,
but it's...
Well, I was tracking every
bit of it, and it scares me.
So, Sami, the vibe of the tribe
is pretty clear.
The group is saying, "Listen,
"we have agreed
to play a certain way.
"Make your moves quietly.
Be respectful of time.
He wants to fish,
let him do it."
And what I would be thinking
as a player is,
"What do I do
other than just trust?"
SAMI:
I feel like we're
all talking about trust,
and it's, like,
such a fishy word.
Like, it's
a whole bunch of nonsense.
It's a crock of crap at this
point, you know what I mean?
Like, these rules
are being curved.
They're being amended
all the time.
And I think it's gonna
continue to be that way.
I think that
it's gonna be a damn civil war.
The rules are gonna
be outright broken all around,
and it's gonna
be crazy chaos around here.
All right, it is time to vote.
Cody, you're up.
♪ ♪
You're a wonderful girl.
You need to start
embracing yourself
and being the leader
I know you can be.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote, Jeanine.
Ryan.
Jeanine.
We're tied. Two votes Ryan,
two votes Jeanine.
Jeanine.
That's three votes Jeanine,
two votes Ryan.
Jeanine.
Four votes Jeanine,
two votes Ryan.
Jeanine.
That's five votes Jeanine.
Eighth person voted out and
the first member of our jury,
Jeanine.
That's six. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
All love.
- All love. All love.
- Bye, Jeanine.
♪ ♪
Jeanine, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
- See you guys in the real world.
- Bye, Jeanine.
Bye, girl.
♪ ♪
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
If you break trust with James,
you go home.
I woke up this morning
wanting to make a big move.
There are
two immunity necklaces.
Two people going home.
SAMI:
I'm ready
to change this game up.
We're on the Autobahn
to the million dollars.
Dwight leaving with my idol
had a major impact on my game,
but I can't look back
on any of it and not smile.
I truly do feel
like I've learned
more about myself
these last 16 days.
And I've challenged
myself physically, mentally,
in every possible way.
I can't describe it
any more than gratitude
and contentment.
[roars]