He sure did. I would have
expected nothing less.
Love that kid,
but he was a loose cannon.
Tribal Council was,
uh, exciting.
Sami decided
to play his Shot in the Dark,
and he ended up going home.
- The tribe has spoken.
- Thank you, brother.
I am a tad
disappointed, though,
because the plan going in was
for Karla to vote for Cassidy
and end up
with some egg on her face,
but Karla realized
that voting for Cassidy
could leave her exposed,
so she decided
to flip her vote to Sami
when he blew things up
with his Shot in the Dark.
All you had to do
was vote the right way
and your ass
would still be here.
So, my goal moving forward is
to drive a wedge
between Cassidy and Karla
just to reinforce that idea
that Karla is dangerous,
she's astute
and she needs to go.
I'm so glad you made it.
I know. I think
I was a little worried
that, like, Cody
might throw a vote on me.
Mm-hmm.
Well, see, I-I... I think
Karla maybe would have
taken a shot at you.
That's what... that's what
Sami was trying to tell me.
- I don't know
if it's true or not, but...
- Oh.
She's trying to...
I think what she's trying to do
- is put the target
off of her onto me.
- Yes.
Wow.
From what I'm hearing,
Karla was actually
targeting me last night.
If that's the case,
I'm gonna be pretty pissed
because me and Karla have been
together since day one.
- So she was gonna vote me?
- Oh, yeah. That's what I heard.
- Wow.
- That's what Jesse was saying.
This game is
so tricky. Like,
I don't know
if Owen's telling the truth.
People are good liars out here,
but I think I would be
naive not to question it
and see, like,
if she really was targeting me.
I think that's... crazy
because, clearly, I've been
voting with you since day one.
That would be a pretty big move
to take out
your number-one ally.
But it wouldn't
make sense for me.
That would be stupid.
Oh, man. Cassidy was like,
"I think you were
coming for me."
And I was like, "What are you
talking about? No, I wasn't."
But I was.
And the truth is,
I would like for her to go home.
What are you thinking?
- Really? Is this...
is this real?
- Uh, yes. Cass.
I've never said your name, Cass.
- Ever.
- Okay.
I don't know what to tell you,
because that's the truth.
I cannot say, "Yeah,
I was about to vote you out,"
because she's the only one
that knows about my idol, but
I'm picking up that
she's not buying it.
So the only thing I could
think of at that moment was cry.
But if this has to become
a soap opera, I'm ready for it.
Let's make it
a telenovela tonight.
Your body language
is just telling me
that you want me to go home.
No. I just... I'm hurt
because I heard that
you were coming for me.
I'm hurt that you would...
Sorry.
I just feel like
I've been so loyal to you.
- That's why-that's why I'm hurt.
- And I saved...
I've saved you twice.
Ask Jesse.
He'll tell you.
I was, like, crying. Like,
"I can't believe
you think I'd write..."
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- I'm so stupid.
I need an Emmy after that
performance. Yeah, go talk
- to her. She's over there
by herself.
- She stretching?
Yeah. Just be like,
"I saw you and Karla talking."
I don't know.
Or, like, you seem...
Okay.
Cass is hearing things
about Karla targeting her,
and so Karla told her like,
"Check with Jesse. He'll verify
that, like,
I was voting with you."
I want the rift.
I want that pay-per-view match.
I want, like, you know, those
two to be targeting each other.
But... Yeah.
Karla's good.
She laid it on so thick
with the tears and everything,
trying to convince me
that she had been loyal
to me since day one.
But I feel like
the bridge between Karla's
pretty much been burned.
I want to get Karla out.
Like, Karla, I'm coming for you.
Come on in!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh. God.
- Yeah, I knew it. Oh!
- Yikes.
- Yes.
- Wow.
- Hi, Jeff.
- Good morning.
- Jeff.
- Ooh. Day 22.
Six players,
two from each original tribe.
I mean, come on.
Look at that.
All right, are you ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
Yes, sir.
For today's challenge,
we're gonna randomly divide
into two teams of three.
One player will be strapped
inside a giant ball.
They will guide their two
- blindfolded teammates...
- Wow.
Through a long, winding course
to a table maze,
where the player
still strapped inside the ball
will guide the still-blindfolded
teammates
as they race to solve that maze.
First team to finish
wins reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
The winning three will be taken
to the sanctuary,
where good things happen.
- Waiting for you...
iced coffee and iced tea.
- Ooh.
And you need something
to go along with that.
How about an array of pastries?
- Ah.
- Oh, nice.
- Donuts,
- croissants, muffins.
- Oh, my God.
- Ooh.
- Hell, yeah.
- Worth playing for?
- Yes.
- All right.
We're gonna draw for teams,
we'll get started.
Let's do it.
All right,
we have our two teams.
In blue, strapped
in the ball is Owen.
We've got Cody
and Karla blindfolded.
They will be pushing.
In Red, it is Cassidy
strapped in the ball
with Jesse
and Gabler blindfolded.
Here we go. For reward.
Survivors ready?
- Go.
- Go, go, go, go.
Who will get
through this first gate first?
- It's gonna be Blue.
- There we go.
A little less.
A little more, Karla.
Karla, more.
Keep going forward. Forward.
Now to the... to the right.
Cassidy upside down now
and running into Karla.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Rotate.
- Which way?
- You got to get through
that tiny little gateway.
Stop. Forward. Forward.
There goes Blue. Here comes Red.
- Owen is leading.
- Forward. Left, left, left.
Left. There you go. Beautiful.
Forward left.
A little more left.
- That's how you do it!
- Here we go. 12:00 o'clock.
12:00 o'clock. Doing great.
Okay, straight. We got to hurry.
Move forward. Okay.
It is Cassidy,
Jesse and Gabler behind.
You got to get through
another passageway now.
- Communication is key.
- Forward. Push, push, push.
- Forward.
Straight on. Straight on.
Straight on.
- Blue is through!
- Straight on, straight on,
straight on.
- Keep going straight.
- Owen now on
- to the big part of the course.
- Right. Now we're taking
a hard right. 3:00 o'clock.
Or more like 2:30.
There we go.
- Owen doing a nice job
of communicating...
- Good job, bro.
- To Cody and Karla
- Yup. Now we're gonna brake.
As he goes upside down,
- left and right, sideways.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God. Got to go, uh, to
the right. To the right, guys.
- Red is hung up.
- You guys both got
to get behind me!
Keep going...
No, no, wrong way, other way.
- Oh, this way.
- Got it?
Cassidy is now maneuvering
around that obstacle,
and they are through.
Pull it towards Cody.
- Over the sawdust?
- Yup. Uh, not quite.
You'll be there in, like,
four steps. Watch your feet.
Owen with a nice lead for Blue.
- Uh.
- There we go.
Now we're through the sawdust.
- To the right.
You got to get behind! Go!
Red once again struggling to
get through another passageway.
- Pull back?
- Pull back, pull back.
Now-now push forward
to your right, to your right.
Yes. Yeah. Yes, yes.
Red is back on the move.
- Keep going.
Here we go. Watch out, Cody.
Watch out, watch out.
- Are we at the-the base?
- We're at the gate.
Owen doing a nice job,
calm communicating.
- Now push it?
- Now push me over.
Got to get him up on that
platform and then you're good.
So we got to rotate
180 degrees around. Clockwise.
Now Owen needs to be able
to see that maze so he can tell
Cody and Karla what to do.
Nice job by Blue.
- Okay.
- Owen is straight up.
That's about as good
as it gets right there.
Down. You're at it.
This is the last part
of this challenge.
- Cody, pull up.
- Get that white ball
from one corner to the other.
Up. Cody, up.
Karla, stay where you are. Okay.
Stay there. Yes. Now forward.
Forward. A little to the left.
- Stay where you. A little
to the left, now forward.
- Here comes Red
trying to stay in it.
Towards Karla, hard.
- Beautiful.
- Owen has been calm
this entire challenge.
- One, two, three!
- Push up. Three.
- Push. Oh,
to the right a little.
- To the right.
Red is lined up.
They come straight in.
- Okay.
- Now Cassidy... can she see
from here is the question?
- Are we in there?
- All right.
Yeah. Yeah, we're good.
- All right, go, go, go!
- She's gonna do it
- sideways.
- Where are you?
- To the right, to the right.
Now Jesse and Gabler got to get
to the maze
and find their spots.
- Both down.
- Blue has had
a lot of time now
- to try to figure this out.
- Tell me...
I'll tell you when to go.
Okay, we're going...
We're going up now.
We're fine.
- We're going a different way.
- There you go, Gabler!
Look at that.
Jesse and Gabler are here.
- Okay. Yes. Now go up. Up.
- They're back in it.
- This challenge is on.
- Karla, down a bit.
All right, we're gonna make
a left turn
so we're gonna go down
and then...
Big reward on the line.
A visit to the sanctuary.
Right, right,
right, right, right!
- Right?
- Right. No, up, up, up, up.
Up, up. Yeah, good.
It is a scorching
hot day in Fiji.
- Okay, go to the left.
- Left.
This will be a nice break
- from the routine of camp now.
- To the left. Down.
Up now, Cody. There we go.
Blue with another nice move.
They are closing in
on a victory right here.
Down. Down to the left. Yes.
Here we go. Now up.
Karla, start lifting up.
Gently, gently, gently.
- Gently. A little more.
- Wow.
This is a nice touch
- if they can pull it off.
- A little more. And now.
- Up.
- They can't.
And that opens the door
for Red now, who is gaining.
Down to the left, left, left!
There we go, there we go.
Red is not far behind
- Blue right now.
- Lift, Cody.
Gently, gently.
- Up, Cody, up, Cody.
- Blue losing more ground.
Going backwards again.
The door is open and we are
at the same spot in the maze.
- Yes, yes. Here we go.
- Push. Go. Go, push.
Hell yes. Okay.
We're right there.
Blue has made it.
They're closer
than they have ever been.
Just got to get it to drop
for the win.
As soon as I say "up," you got
to go up, up, up, up, up, up!
- Red right there.
- Down, Cody.
Give it more juice.
- Hard, Karla. Hard, Karla.
No! Other way.
- No!
They miss the opportunity.
Can Red catch them?
Up, up, up, up, up, up!
So close!
Pull towards you, Karla.
Down and to the left.
In and out again!
Up, up, up, up now!
Yeah, no. Okay.
- Up, Cody. Up, Cody.
- Yes! There it is!
Yes!
- Yes. Oh, great job, y'all.
- Owen, Cody, Karla
win reward...
A trip to the sanctuary.
- Aah! Great job, y'all.
- Oh, my God! Great job.
- Great job y'all.
Oh, my God.
- Damn it.
- Elbows. Elbows.
- Oh, we were close.
All right, Owen, Cody, Karla,
you're gonna leave here,
go directly to the sanctuary.
An array of pastries
fill your body
and lift your spirits.
Grab your stuff, head out.
- Boat'll pick you up.
- Thank you.
- See y'all.
Enjoy the afternoon.
Well earned.
- Thanks, Jeff. Ooh!
- Thank you.
Gabler, Cassidy, Jesse,
got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Thank you.
The reward challenge
was awesome.
My hands and feet
were all strapped together,
but I was like, "Yeah, let's go!
Yeah!" Like, I was
so fired up,
and now I'm thrilled
to come back to the sanctuary,
talk to Cody and Karla
to take the pulse
of where their heads are at
going into this pivotal
final-six vote.
If you think you have what it
takes to come out here and play
this game, what are you waiting
on? Apply to be on Survivor.
I am sky-high right now.
Feels so good.
I'm going to the top
with you guys.
- Yeah. To the moon, baby.
- Here I come.
Watch out.
- Man, I don't even...
- To the moon, baby! To the top!
My body has not had
caffeine, and to just send it,
like, on coffee and sugar
is out of control.
Say hello to my little friend.
But I have to be careful.
We have six people left,
and money makes people
do funny things.
Probably even more
than the caffeine
running through my brain.
It's a very interesting time
in the game.
I mean, we are down to six.
- We are really getting
down to it.
- Yeah.
It's kind of wild just
since we all voted together
last night.
Yeah. Where those lines
kind of are then gonna fall.
I feel like I have
a big target on my back.
- That's how I feel, honest...
to be honest, to be
- Really?
Completely honest
with you, yeah.
I'm a threat.
I know I'm a freaking threat.
You know, I've won
two immunity challenges.
The rumor is that I have an idol
because I actually
do have an idol.
But I need people to believe
I don't have an idol.
I'll do anything
to keep that target off my back.
I feel like everyone
is speculating about me,
that I have something.
That's the hardest part
because I... don't.
And...
I feel like it's been ruining
my game since the merge.
- That sucks. Like, that sucks.
- That's a... It... Dude.
You got that target
on your back,
- and you can't even defend it.
- Cody,
it's been a target
every single vote.
Once again,
I fake-cried and kind of
played like
I don't know what to do,
I need a lifeline,
um, which is partly true.
I'm trying
to see what can stick.
If I can at least make it
through one more vote,
I think I'm set.
I can use my idol at the five.
Phew. I don't think
she has the idol.
- You don't think so?
- No.
I feel like she would have
played it by now if she did.
- I do, too.
- She was in some pretty,
like, bleak-looking spots.
Brah, if she didn't,
she is a way better...
- Nerves of steel.
- She's an even better player
than I thought. Yeah.
- She's very dangerous, and...
- Yeah, 100%.
We've been wanting
to get the girls broken up
- for a long time.
- Yeah.
And, like, to take this easy
shot, now's the time to do it.
And if Karla wins, then we've
got Cassidy we can get rid of.
- You know, I think we'll be...
- Yeah.
- I think we'll be all right.
- I do, too.
Cody wants the boys
to take out Karla or Cassidy,
which works great for me
because my goal is to get out
Karla at this next vote.
- I feel good.
We got a... we got a good plan.
- I do, too.
Keep the boys safe.
Karla is very dangerous
because she has
the potential to win this game,
and for either of us
to stand a chance,
Karla has to go.
This is so nice.
So I'm just so over losing.
I know. It sucks.
- Now we can do...
- One good thing is that we get
to eat the rest of the rice,
I guess.
You know, I found in Survivor,
every time
you get kicked in the gut,
there's some victory
that comes out of this thing.
The reward challenge today
was bittersweet.
Actually, it was bitter,
'cause we didn't get any sweet.
But this close
to the end, though,
there's very strong players
that need
to get out of the way in order
for me to win this game.
We could talk maybe about
getting to the final three,
and, you know, I'd like...
It'd be great if the three
of us could be down there.
- We all have
three very different stories.
- Right.
'Cause, you know, Cody may claim
that his story is your story.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
-"Like, I did that.
Well, no, I did that."
- And Karla will claim
that your story is her story.
- Yup.
I planted the seed of
get rid of Cody and Karla.
And you know what's awesome?
I don't think people
see the game I'm playing.
The best assassin doesn't
show up at the castle
with an ax saying,
"I'm here to kill the king."
He or she slips
into the kitchen,
puts a vial of poison
in the king's bowl and leaves.
We need to get him or Karla
on this next vote.
I think that's a great idea.
I'm hiding in plain sight.
I am wearing some
pretty impressive camo.
Maybe that's it.
Look at me now.
Right? I'm just, like,
frozen in the tree.
They just don't seem
to see me, which is fine.
I mean,
it's no doubt Cody or Karla.
- I sort of worry,
like, he has an idol.
- Got you.
Everyone's scared
he's gonna play the idol,
so I don't want to waste time
voting for him.
Well, I mean, nobody wants
to be next to Karla,
so Karla will be a safe bet.
But she also an idol, so...
- Probably or...
- She definitely does.
Okay. So she definitely does.
- Aha.
- Yeah.
So Karla may play hers tomorrow.
Cody can play his...
I mean, ideally,
we could flush an idol
and eliminate
one of those two big threats.
Cass saying
that Karla has an idol
just sort of reaffirms that,
like, Gabler is right.
Cody and Karla are
sort of threats
because they have these idols.
They have these guaranteed paths
into the final five.
You guys all sugar cracked out?
But I do trust Cody.
You know,
he's been keeping his idol
in my bag because he trusts me.
And I have Jeanine's old idol
which everybody thinks
walked out the door with Dwight.
So me and Cody are
in a good spot, whereas, like,
Karla is a huge threat,
which is awesome for me,
and not that great for her.
For sure.
So, who told you?
Cass told you she has one?
Interesting. 'Cause she was
like, "I don't have it."
- If she plays her idol tomorrow?
- Well, I think
I'd play mine if she plays hers.
Yeah.
Karla has an immunity idol.
It's absolutely preposterous.
She's lied to me this whole
game. She's been full of B.S.
And now I can smell it.
We cannot let her win.
- Anybody but Karla.
- Or I mean, Cass,
for that matter.
But one of us four guys need
to win the challenge. I just had
3,000 calories of Danish here.
So, that's gonna be huge
for tomorrow
on a huge challenge.
I'm like... Bzz!
Good, like, sharp right now.
- Good.
- Like, watch out.
Good. That's good.
I'm not feeling that.
That's right, buddy.
I'm gonna be, frigging,
a Tasmanian devil
as I always am in there, I'm
gonna be having a great time.
I hope so.
And I'm gonna give you guys
all a kiss right on the cheek.
That's right.
With six people left,
if I win tomorrow,
I'm in the final five
with an immunity idol.
Come on in.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Hi, Jeff.
- Ooh.
- Day 23 Survivor 43.
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first, Karla
and Owen, got to take it back.
Of course, of course.
- But you can win it back again.
- Yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Owen.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race through
a series of obstacles,
collecting a bag
of number tiles.
You'll use those numbers to open
a combination, releasing a key.
You'll then race up a cargo net
and use that key
to unlock your puzzle pieces.
It is then a race
to assemble a bat puzzle.
First person
to finish wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Biggest stakes of the season.
We'll draw for spots.
Here we go.
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
All right, here we go,
for immunity
and a guaranteed spot in the
final five, Survivors ready?
Go! First, you're up and over
a cargo net.
On day 23,
everybody is flying down this.
Karla takes a big hit.
But she's still in it.
Not the first time
Karla has suffered an injury
on a challenge.
You got
to attack this challenge.
You want to get to five.
Do not let somebody
take you out at six.
Cody's gonna get through first.
Owen right next to him.
There's Cassidy and Karla.
Gabler has his.
It's Jesse, the only person yet
to win an immunity challenge,
in dead last.
Cody gonna get
to his combination first.
Cassidy's out second.
There's Owen.
There's Karla.
Here comes Gabler.
Everybody gonna be in on it.
Now you have three number tiles.
They are pairs of numbers.
Each pair represents one number.
You're trying
to figure out the order.
Once you think
you have it, try it.
If it doesn't work, try again.
Jesse goes from dead last
to first. Jesse solves his.
He's through.
There's Owen. He solves his.
Gabler has his.
Jesse up the cargo net.
Use that key to unlock
your puzzle pieces, Jesse.
- Oh!
- Owen has lost his key.
He's got to go back.
He forgot it. Cody has his.
Cassidy has hers.
Cassidy's through.
Here comes Cody.
Now, it's everybody but Karla.
Karla's still working
on her combination.
Cassidy is up.
Cody's up.
Owen is up.
Jesse gonna start working
on the puzzle.
Cassidy right behind.
Gabler's got his first two,
both in the paint.
Owen, there you go. You're good.
Cody getting in on it.
Everybody starts solving. Karla
has her combination solved.
Here she comes.
Five of the six players
on the puzzle right now.
That's what you want on day 23.
Karla working her way up
the cargo net,
and she is still smiling.
That is what you want
from a Survivor player.
You're making a bat puzzle.
Just think about your puzzle
and how you're building it.
Survivor puzzles always look
so simple when they're finished,
but assembling them
is another thing entirely.
Our puzzle designers
know what they're doing.
They know how
to make puzzles complicated
even though they look simple.
There are probably lots of ways
you can build this puzzle
that's not right.
It is Cassidy in the lead
with Karla
and Jesse right on her tail
on one side while Cody,
Owen and Gabler trying
to catch up on the other.
Damn.
Cassidy with a bit
of a lead still,
but Karla has caught up.
She was last
to get to the puzzle,
but that's why we have puzzles.
- You know what's wild, Jeff?
- What?
Is that, like, your hands get...
At least my hands,
because of the nerves...
They're all shot, you know?
Like, it's just kind of,
like, they're so numb,
and it's, like,
kind of scary, so...
Karla's had hand issues
this whole game.
For real.
Cody figured it out.
Cody's now in it.
Cassidy down
to a few pieces left.
Karla down to a few pieces left.
They're side by side
fighting for immunity.
That is the race right now.
Cody's in it, as well.
Wow. Look-look at them.
They're cramping.
Hang in there, Karla.
Dude!
Karla really struggling.
Aah! I just twisted
my ankle so bad.
Her entire body
is shutting down,
and Cody is seizing
the opportunity.
We got a challenge. Karla,
you're gonna have to dig.
It is now Cassidy and Cody,
with Karla still in it
but faltering physically.
Hang in there, Karla.
- Thank you. Aah!
- Cassidy down
to three pieces left.
Cody down to five pieces left.
Cassidy down to two pieces.
It is Cassidy and Cody.
Karla is falling out.
Cassidy with another piece.
Can Cody catch her on the end?
He's racing.
Cassidy with her last piece.
- Got it.
- Cassidy thinks she has it.
Cassidy is wrong.
- Oh.
- This challenge is still on.
Something is not right.
Cody's still digging.
Karla now getting back in there.
Karla down to two pieces.
Cassidy now trying
to fix her puzzle.
Can Cody seize this opportunity?
This is coming down
to the last two pieces.
Cody down to a few pieces.
I'm done! I'm done! Jeff! Jeff!
Cassidy thinks she has it.
And this time Cassidy is right.
Individual immunity for Cassidy.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Wow. What a challenge.
Cody got his puzzle
just a couple
of seconds too late.
That was a close finish.
Huge effort by everybody.
- Good job, Cass.
- Ugh!
- Cassidy, come over.
Congratulations.
- Good job, Cass.
- Biggest win of the season
so far, day 23.
- Thank you so much.
- You get to wear this again.
Well earned.
- Thank you.
- You are safe.
- You are guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
- Yeah.
As for the rest of you,
after 23 days,
one of you will be voted out.
- That will not be you.
You are safe. Congrats.
- Thank you.
- Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
- Good job, Cass.
- See you tonight at Tribal.
- Thank you so much.
Well done, Cassidy.
- Thank you.
- You need help?
This immunity was
a tough one to lose
because my body literally
gave up on me,
and I couldn't do anything.
Now Cassidy's safe.
I know people are gunning
for me, but I have an idol,
and it's showtime, baby.
Ay, caramba.
- But I mean, it is...
- Two idols at play.
- Two idols.
- And then
we didn't get immunity.
There's six people, so there's
three people that we might
- Yeah.
- be able to shoot at.
If Cody and Karla were open,
- No, absolutely.
- That's a different story.
If they both play idols,
it could be me or you
or Jesse that goes.
It's pretty complicated
right now because
Cassie's got immunity,
Karla has an idol
and Cody has an idol.
Probably, they're gonna
play 'em tonight.
And at this point in the game,
there's no more
Shot in the Dark.
So, me, Owen or Jesse will...
will tap out.
Tonight is my biggest hurdle.
So you're saying
there's a chance?
So you're saying there's
a chance.
I have an idol.
- I have an idol.
- Okay.
- Do you want to go
to the final four with me?
- I do.
Here's how.
- Okay?
- Yes.
I'm gonna tell Cass
I'm playing my idol.
And then you, like,
just tell them,
"Like, hey,
I'm playing my idol." But...
Okay.
I love a threat.
If you don't vote our way, bro,
we could easily
just vote you out.
Exactly.
You are such
a brilliant man, Cody.
Wow. Like, this could work.
Let's not go after each other.
It's, let's work together
and threaten people that
we're gonna use our idols,
and, uh, then we keep our idols
and go to the five
with our idols
and guarantee our spots
in the four.
And so now Cody, Jesse, and I
ultimately can decide
who goes home...
Gabler or Owen.
So I have an idol, um, and, uh,
- Cody's playing his
and I'm playing mine.
- Okay.
You know, if you want to stay,
like, would you vote Owen?
- I would.
- 100%. To stay in the game?
When you put people at risk,
it's fascinating to see
how quickly people will turn
on their own alliance.
- If push comes to shove...
- You'd be willing to...
I'm willing
to write Gabler's name down.
Homeboy's gonna play it,
I'm gonna play it.
It's a scare tactic, and it's...
it's foolproof, too,
though, right? Like, if
we get a bad vibe,
we could still use our idols.
I'll use my idol,
Cody would use his idol.
You know,
and we'll just duke it out
at the five
without idols, right?
But as long
as this works out,
you'll see me at the final four.
Okay. Okay.
We're playing 'em.
She's gonna buy it.
And wham, we knock her
right out of this game.
Won't see it coming.
- Is-is...
- Love that, bro. Okay.
So we just... Uh, yeah, we just
can't let her get the drift
that us four guys are together.
I'm stretching the truth
to Kar...
You know what?
The hell with it.
I'm lying to Karla.
I am lying to her
so she doesn't
play her idol tonight
so that way I can blindside
the hell out of her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
"Genius" is the word
for this plan.
I've been out here for 23 days.
I'm a quick learner, and I've
learned very fast like a sponge.
And I'm out here as, you know,
Wild Thing, Killer Cody,
Cowboy Cody.
Call me whatever you want,
but the switch
has definitely turned.
And, um...
yeah, sometimes
I surprise even myself.
Karla.
The four amigos of Owen,
Gabler, Cody and Jesse
are all gonna vote Karla.
And she's gonna leave Tribal
with a walking stick
that I made her and an idol.
Jesse is on board.
I love that guy.
He's my roll dog.
Our trust
in our relationship
has gotten so, like, forged,
it's unbelievable.
Yeah.
You know, Cody's plan
is great for him,
but taking out Karla,
the biggest threat in the game,
would absolutely
boost his rsum.
We're at six now, and, like,
I can't be seen
as Cody's number two.
And they just see
that I've sort of,
like, made the same moves
as Cody,
who's a little bit louder.
It might be time
to just be openly cutthroat,
but then, at the same time,
I don't know.
There's a lot to think about.
Like, I-I love Cody,
and I think he would
take me to the end, but, like,
I have to wonder
if I can beat him.
I got two kids at home,
I got a wife.
And, like,
people are out here
and they're saying, like,
"This is, like, so much fun,
right? Like, this..."
"No matter what, like,
oh, we've already won."
You know, they want the million,
but, like, they seem like,
"Oh, this is all
about the experience."
For me, like, no, the experience
is great, but, like,
for me, like, I need to secure
my family's future and, like...
And I'll do anything to do that.
You know, I'll do anything.
So...
If I got to switch it up
and be more brutal, I will.
Yeah, it is.
Oh. Oh.
Yeah.
She's gonna play hers.
And we'll flush...
- So...
- That's... completely great.
Right now, I'm sort of in
the driver's seat of the idol.
Cody thinks
he has it, like, locked in.
Like, he doesn't
have it locked in.
Got him right
where we want 'em, Jesse.
- I can't believe that.
- I... I know.
I know.
Don't know how it went...
For Cody to be without an idol,
that is so beautiful, because
he's unprotected.
We don't know for sure
if Karla's gonna play her idol
or not yet.
So we're throwing
all our votes on Cody.
Actually, I do. I want
to see what yours looks like.
- Yeah, for sure. I'll get it.
- Okay.
I want to just lock it down
- so nothing gets screwed up.
- Cody.
Okay. Phew.
Okay.
Oh!
Yup.
There we are.
I didn't want to push back
because then
that will make him nervous.
So I had to hand off the idol.
And I almost made it. I was,
like, trying to... Aah!
Mm-hmm.
If I can't get the idol back,
the plan will change
just because
it's out of my control.
No.
And then Karla
has an idol, and...
Aah! It's just a mess.
This is worst-case scenario.
It's so unbelievable
that I can almost believe it.
- A lot scarier.
- Yeah, it is.
For some reason,
Jesse gave it back to Cody.
Oh, these are very different, actually.
My plan with Karla is
foolproof, 100% foolproof.
If Karla gets spooked
and plays her idol,
completely fine.
I'm still safe with my idol.
If both Cody and Karla
play their idols, myself,
Jesse or Gabler could go home
with just one vote.
The gloves are off now.
There's no more niceties.
It's a death match
to get to the end.
To know I'm gonna this crazy
Tribal tonight
with this protection on
is absolutely vital.
Tonight's blindside
will be the biggest
of the season for sure.
No doubt about it.
What could go wrong inSurvivor
at the final six?
I don't know. You know,
just a million different things.
So let's start with today.
We obviously know how it ended.
Cassidy has a necklace,
another individual immunity win.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
But it was not easy. Karla,
you were close to having
a real shot at winning,
and your entire body
just seized up.
How are you right now?
Um, I'm physically exhausted.
Um, I still feel tingly
all over my hands.
Um, tired.
Uh, my ankle hurts.
It's swollen.
We're out of rice.
We have a few coconuts.
And the heat.
So, it's been a long,
uh, afternoon.
The other big story
of that challenge was, Cody,
you lost by seconds.
Yeah, it's a real bummer.
Uh, you know, I don't know
another way to summarize it
for you, Jeff.
To be seconds away
from wearing that necklace
is a couple of seconds away
from coming here,
in just completely different
emotional state of mind.
Jesse, the other side
of this is that
now you have to go back to camp
and try to strategize
when there are only
five choices.
Yeah. I mean,
Cassidy's safe, and then,
two of them are also safe...
Uh, Karla and Cody... so...
Why are they also safe?
Uh, they've sort of,
kind of made it known
that they're gonna be
playing their idols tonight.
Karla, what was
the rationale to say, A,
"I have an idol," and B,
"I am playing it tonight"?
Yeah. Um, I feel like rumors
of me having an idol...
Well, clearly, they're true...
Have been making me a target,
and this is the only way
I can guarantee
my safety tonight.
Cody, what was
the rationale for you?
Was it simply fear that
"I didn't win
and I think I'm a target"?
Yeah. I'm gonna give myself a
shot to live to see another day.
Um, you know, it's either today
or tomorrow that I play it.
So, it's a pretty easy decision
for me, and, uh, I...
I don't see any reason
that I wouldn't go that route.
So, Owen, what do you
do when you take all this in
at camp and you think it's
either you, Jesse or Gabler?
You have to go
and make your pitch,
and you just hope
something sticks.
But it's really crappy knowing
that someone with a necklace,
two people with idols, it could
just take one vote to send one
of the three of us home,
and, you know,
that's a different pill to
swallow than getting voted out,
you know, seven to two
or something like that.
Like, it's tough.
Jesse, it's also
a bit of gambling.
If they have idols and
those idols are good until five,
they could wait, so
this could be a bluff, as well.
Yeah, I mean, it could be,
but I don't feel like
I'm in a position to sort of
call their bluff at this point.
Like, you know, we talk
about the social contract
that's been in place, and, like,
you have to really be like,
"All right, you know, like, tell
me which dance moves to make,
and I'll make them and, like,
we'll just go along." So...
Cody, that's a big move
if that's what you are doing.
Two people saying,
"We're the royalty,
"and we're gonna tell you
what the rules are.
"We're not going home,
and it's one of you three,
and we're gonna decide."
Is that how you looked at it?
Absolutely. I mean,
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't talk to Karla
about it. You know,
"Hey, who are we looking at?"
And, um, it could just be one
that decides the fate
of someone tonight. And, um...
as tragic as it sounds,
it's not me.
Karla, Cody was just
- really honest.
- Mm-hmm.
He said it's tragic,
but it won't be for me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you feel similar?
Yeah. I mean,
luckily I do have something
to protect me tonight.
So it is unfortunate, but I feel
confident and I hope that
folks that I spoke to today
feel confident.
How about you, Gabler?
How confident are you
that what you were told
is gonna happen tonight?
I-I think I'm pretty confident.
I think I'm gonna see tomorrow.
You know, 12 hours difference
in Survivor is a world
of difference.
And, you know, this afternoon
it was an apex predator buffet
and we were just kind of
serving up whatever they were
needing just to see if
we could sail to tomorrow.
Jesse, you were
nodding in agreement.
Yeah. You know, I'm not
trying to make too many
big moves, right? Like, I'm
just like, "You fill me in,
let me know what's going on."
And as vulnerable
as I felt today,
I hope that I landed
on the right move.
How about you, Owen?
You know, I was peddling
the book of Sandra today.
You know, anybody but me.
You know, I've been
in tough spots before
in this game and I'm not
gonna count myself out.
But I'd be lying if I said
I felt super-duper confident
in my chances, but
I'm not counting myself out
just quite yet.
Cody, how confident are you
that the vote is gonna go
the way you think it will?
Uh, I'll give it a niner.
I'm pretty confident.
I think, um,
you know, I'm the person that
people were wanting to talk to
and, um, they were giving me
the best pitch and, um,
uh, yeah, nine and a half,
actually, is where I'm at.
- Pretty good.
- Yeah. Pretty good. Yeah.
I think that's where
I'm at on this. 95%.
All right, it is time to vote.
Cody, you're up.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Give me a minute.
I think a couple of us took
a look at the social contract.
We decided
to call people's bluffs.
So I'm playing this for Owen.
- For Owen.
- Yep.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Owen
will not count.
- All right...
- I... will play mine.
Gonna play this for myself.
Okay.
This is also
a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast for Karla
will not count.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Owen.
Does not count.
Karla.
Cody.
One vote Cody.
Two votes Cody.
Thirteenth person
voted out of Survivor 43: Cody.
Three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Whew. Wow.
Good playing, y'all.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Cody, the tribe has spoken.
Time to go.
A hui hou and aloha.
- Aloha, bro.
- Holler, brother.
You have made it
to the final five,
but this game is far from over.
Tonight you will be taken
to a new beach
where you will start over.
Oh, my God.
This is the beginning
of the final push
to get to the end.
Oh, Jesse.
Dig in and hang on.
Grab your torches,
head back to your new camp.
Good night.
- Golly, Jeff.
- Thanks, Jeff.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Next time on the season finale
of Survivor...
Final five here.
This is where it gets real.
I'm not an idiot, Karla.
She's dumb as hell.
I am furious.
This will change my entire life.
You're playing for
a million dollars.
Heart is crushed.
It is freaking crushed.
I can't believe
this just happened.
My main man Jesse
completely backstabbed me,
and, um, it's a damn good play.
I can't fault him on that.
I should have known better.
I'm gonna continue
to have the time of my life.
I'll keep trucking,
I'm gonna keep smiling, but
...you, Jesse... you.