♪ ♪
CASSIDY:
So tonight, Lindsay went home.
It was originally me,
Karla, James and Lindsay.
We were all four gonna
vote together to get Geo out.
Okay, yeah.
But then Lindsay started,
you know, kind of spiraling out
and getting really paranoid.
CASSIDY:
We told Ryan and Geo
at the last minute,
and so we all voted for Lindsay.
I also got a vote,
which stung a little.
So at this point, I just
wanted to kind of clear the air
and figure out who voted for me.
I knew it was
either Geo or Ryan.
Does anybody want to talk?
Anybody have any questions?
Um, I guess, I just,
if whoever wrote my name down
wants to, like,
talk about that...
We can... I can walk
and talk with you, real quick.
- Okay.
- Just drum the beats,
to explain that part.
- Was that you?
- Um, no, it's wasn't me,
but I don't want the person
who wrote it down to be held...
So... I mean...
CASSIDY:
In this game, like, it's all
about choosing your battles.
And so, at that moment,
it was like,
"I just need to play nice."
But in the back of my mind,
I'm like, you know,
"I want to go after the people
who put my name down."
So, Ryan actually
came up with the idea that
if you are
giving her information,
we should put one vote on you
and the rest of the votes
on Lindsay.
- That's just how it went down,
to be honest.
- Okay. Yeah.
Geo is just, like,
clueless about the game.
It's like, are you kidding me?
Ryan and Geo think that
they have the numbers right now,
but the truth is
they're at the bottom.
I think they're still
gonna try to gun for me
if we do have
to go to another Tribal.
And you know what they say,
revenge is a dish
best served cold, so...
I'm just biding my time till
I can pay them back for that.
I didn't vote for you.
That was Lindsay.
- So Lindsay voted for me?
- I voted for Lindsay. Yeah.
What do you think,
Lindsay voted for herself?
No.
I put a vote on Cassidy,
just in case.
I don't think she-she likes me.
I don't think
she's gonna trust me now.
She's not gonna trust me later.
And that's fine,
'cause, you know,
at the end of the day,
I still have the numbers.
There isn't much that Cassidy
can do unless we hit a merge.
She's in the outs, completely.
I guess we'll just...
Yeah. [laughs]
Yeah, it's all about
getting comfortable.
Yeah, I know.
- These...
- [both laugh]
KARLA:
At this point,
we're gonna try to decide
whether Ryan or Geo go first.
I want their egos to be stroked
and their heads to be big,
because that's when
people make mistakes.
And I'll be watching
and I'll be waiting.
So let them.
♪ ♪
Basically, every time
we get some time alone,
we're looking
for the hidden immunity idol.
We're looking up in the trees.
We're looking for places
that we haven't been.
Just really trying anything,
because it's been
a lot of days looking.
I feel like
I've looked everywhere.
But as we're walking,
we see this tree,
and it's, like, lit up
in all of its Survivor glory,
just... ♪ singing. ♪
♪ ♪
All right, I'll go check.
As a Survivor fan, I know
to look in nooks and crannies.
I know to look
in any suspicious holes.
And so I poke in one hole,
and it's not there.
And then I look down
into the tree, and...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
[gasps] It's covered in ants.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Elie.
Come here.
I'm shell-shocked that I
have found the Beware Advantage.
I am so excited.
I'm also terrified, because
I know it's a Beware Advantage,
so I know that
it's gonna come at a cost.
[quietly]:
Oh, my God.
But...
Let's read it over here.
In that moment, I'm thinking,
"Do I trust my alliance?
Do I need my vote?"
So should I do it? Are you sure?
- Yeah. I am sure.
- Are you sure? Okay.
Right now,
the tribe dynamic for me
is that I feel secure in
my alliance with Elie and Sami.
Owen thinks
that he's in on an alliance
with Elie and I, but in my mind,
he is a really nervous player.
So there's a little bit
of a question mark there.
And then Gabler's
getting on everyone's nerves,
so he seems like the next to go.
The complication is, though,
that he still has a valid idol,
and we think
he doesn't know that it's valid.
[gasps]
- Do you think everyone
would give me their bead?
- Yeah.
You don't think anyone
would be suspicious?
Yeah.
Hey.
ELIE:
Perfect timing.
And as I'm saying, "We
shouldn't tell Owen right now,"
I look up, and there is Owen.
Nothing? Mm-hmm.
Okay, you want to talk about it?
We know that we're caught.
We've got no choice
but to share it with Owen.
Basically,
I have to collect a bead
- from each of you guys
to start the bracelet.
- Mm-hmm.
Reading over the note,
my first thought was like,
"I could mess some things up."
If I denied Jeanine my bead,
I could go with Sami and Gabler
and just get her out
the next time we lose.
And they wouldn't be
able to do anything about it,
because Jeanine has no vote.
But I have been thinking about
working with Elie and Jeanine,
because that gives me
more options moving forward.
Playing with someone
like Gabler,
it is a little concerning.
You never know what
you're gonna get with him,
so I'm gonna
give Jeanine my bead.
Why don't you just take 'em all?
- Oh, my God.
- Take 'em all.
- Can I hug you?
- Yeah, absolutely.
And I want to make sure
she knows that this is a symbol
of my trust
that I am handing to you.
...but we found
a Beware Advantage.
- Where at?
- In a tree.
SAMI: Elie ends up telling me
that Jeanine
found the Beware Advantage.
And I have to try to act happy
and pleasant about this,
but in my head,
I know I've been trying to plot
against Jeanine and Elie.
So Owen already knows,
'cause he walked up on us,
and I tried to hide the paper.
SAMI:
So at this point,
all of us know exactly
what Jeanine is doing,
except for Gabler...
Who, right now,
seems to have no idea
what's going on in this game.
GABLER:
Pregame warm-up.
Everybody's chilling out.
JEANINE:
If we're kind of taking a chill,
- I really want
to make a bracelet.
- GABLER: Go for it.
But I want to do, like,
I want to, I want to know
a little, have a little bit
from each of you.
- Aw.
- So I was hoping
that I could, like,
grab a couple beads from your
bags or something to make it.
ELIE:
Ah, that would be nice.
GABLER:
I've got beads
and cool stuff, too.
JEANINE:
Yeah? Oh, my God. Thank you.
ELIE:
Here's mine.
Do you like that one?
Yeah. Perfect. Thank you.
- That one?
- Yeah.
So at this point,
I'm feeling good.
I have four
of the five beads that I need...
Gabler's bead being
the last that I need to get.
Oh, my God.
[gasps]
You get two.
Ooh.
Gabler has
this entire pouch of beads
that he's been making bracelets
from for his daughters.
And he hands me two
that I'm like,
"Ah, those are useless."
They're just
two little green ones.
And I see, in his pouch,
the one that I need.
Can I take this chunky one?
Um, I was gonna hold
that bead for my daughter.
JEANINE:
Oh.
ELIE:
When Gabler says,
"I was saving that one
for my daughter."
I'm like, "Boom.
Over. We are screwed.
"Jeanine just lost her vote
until the merge,
"because there's
nothing in this world
that Gabler cares more about
than his daughters."
If it were me,
I would have been stunned,
but Jeanine handled it so well.
- Can I give you the green back?
- Yeah.
- This one just reminds me
of you. Thank you so much.
- Okay, well, then good.
- I'm the big yellow. Good. Done.
- Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
ELIE:
And Gabler melts like butter,
right in her hand,
squishy, soft butter,
and trades Jeanine.
And... we got it.
Thanks for entertaining
the artist in me. [chuckles]
SAMI:
Lo and behold, Jeanine
has a hidden immunity idol.
And so,
I want to let Gabler know.
I'm hoping that this
can make him trust me more,
and realize I'm trying
to play this game with him.
Listen, those beads
that we just gave Jeanine...
- Uh-huh.
- That gave her an idol.
Yeah.
No, we gave her a real idol.
She found the Advantage.
[gasps softly]
I didn't have time
to tell you, but...
- ...
- [laughs]
You swear?
SAMI:
Dude, I can't make this up
if I wanted to.
Now the game
has changed dramatically,
not in our favor.
Oh, my God.
Jeanine is now protected,
and Jeanine could
give her idol to Elie.
There's many ways
this could explode on us.
It went from being
a much simpler game
to a very complicated game
by me handing a bead
to my friend.
And that's-that's... that's...
She got me. She got me.
I'll say that. She got me.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Baka, Vesi, getting your first
look at the new Coco tribe.
Lindsay voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
[whistles]
All right. Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
All right, first things first,
I got to take back the idols.
Thank you, Cody.
Thank you, Elie.
♪ ♪
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
four tribe members
will be tied together.
On my go, you'll work together
to get through
a series of obstacles.
You'll then grab a bucket,
fill it with water,
make your way
over a giant teeter-totter...
...transferring whatever water's
left into another bucket.
You'll do this until you have
enough water to lower the gate.
When you reach the finish,
you will race
to roll balls up a ramp,
landing them
on a small platform.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
In addition,
you are playing for a reward.
- Want to know
what you're playing for?
- Yeah!
Maybe the most
valuable thing out here. Tarps.
- Yes, very good.
That's it, okay, that's it.
- [excited chatter, applause]
First tribe to finish,
large tarp.
This will keep you dry
and keep you in the shade,
which is another way
to think of a tarp.
Second tribe to finish, smaller
tarp, will get the job done.
The third tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers,
date with me tonight
at Tribal Council,
where somebody will be the fifth
person voted out of this game.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Coco, you are still playing
to get yours back.
- All right, sit-outs.
Coco, you have one extra person.
- KARLA: I'll sit out.
- Who you gonna sit out?
It's gonna be Karla.
- Me.
PROBST:
That was fast.
Baka, who's it gonna be?
Gabler gonna sit this one out.
All right, sit-outs,
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else,
give you minute to strategize.
We'll get it on.
♪ ♪
Here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready.
Go!
[cheering]
Stage one,
you have to work together
to find a path through the chaos
- of all
of these sticks tied together.
- [indistinct chatter]
All three of these
are exactly the same.
When the Survivor art department
makes something,
it is identical.
- You just got to figure out
how to get through it.
- Good job, Baka!
SAMI:
Okay.
[overlapping chatter]
- PROBST: Vesi and Baka,
side by side.
- Good, good, good.
PROBST:
Cody's through. Elie's through.
Here comes Owen.
There's Ryan for Coco.
You got to get everybody
through this.
- It is Vesi in the lead.
- Over.
- Good job. Let's go. Let's go.
- PROBST: There's Coco.
Over and under. Over and under.
- Baka's through.
- Go, go.
It is Vesi and Coco, then Baka.
- Yeah, we're tied together.
- PROBST: Now Coco through first.
You're good.
Now it's Coco in the lead,
then Vesi, then Baka.
You're gonna get water
and head
over that teeter-totter.
- Coco has theirs.
- KARLA: Take your time, y'all.
- PROBST: Ryan has the water,
heading up and over.
- Ready?
There goes Vesi.
They've got theirs.
KARLA:
Good job, Ryan. Good job.
- Coco, nice job!
Ryan holds on to lot of water.
- KARLA: Beautiful. Good job.
PROBST:
Here goes Vesi.
- Baka's right behind.
- KARLA: Good job, Ryan.
- Do it again.
- The whole pot.
You dump your water,
then you got to come back.
- Back, back, back.
- KARLA: Come on.
Come on, come on. Go back.
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Nice job by Vesi!
Great teamwork.
- Stay low.
- All right, move your weight.
PROBST:
Vesi up, dumping their water.
Baka heading
over with their water.
Slow down. Slow down.
- Here comes Coco again.
Will this be enough?
- Go, Coco!
PROBST:
Baka's taking
a really long time.
Here we go.
Coco drops their gate.
You're good, Coco.
Head over the gate.
Here goes Baka with
their first bucket of the water.
It is Coco now.
It's gonna be
Ryan rolling balls.
Here we go.
- Oh, so close.
- Hold it.
Vesi with another bucket.
Cody another. Nice job.
Four tribe members
really working together well.
That's gonna do it.
Vesi drops their gate.
You're good.
[indistinct chatter]
Here comes Baka.
- Nice. Good.
- GABLER: Good job, guys.
♪ ♪
- It is Ryan, off and on.
- [groans]
- Come on, Ryan.
- Come on, Dwight.
- PROBST: It's gonna
be Dwight for Vesi.
[indistinct chatter]
PROBST:
Baka drops their gate.
Here they come.
It is Ryan and Dwight.
- Now you're
rolling balls up a ramp.
- ELIE: Hey, you got this, Sami.
- Go, Sami.
- PROBST: Sami in now for Baka.
You're still in this, Baka.
All three tribes
yet to get on the board.
[indistinct chatter]
That ball
needs to come to a rest
- at the top of the platform.
- [groans]
- PROBST: Too much speed,
it goes off the back.
- CODY: You got it, Dwight.
- You got it, buddy.
- PROBST: Not enough,
it won't get there.
- This is all about
finding that feel.
- Yes. Okay.
PROBST: Ryan with a nice toss.
He's got one for Coco.
- One. That might do it.
That's one for Vesi.
- Come on, Dwight.
Come on, Dwight.
Everybody's starting
to get a feel.
- OWEN: There it is.
There it is.
- JEANINE: Nice. Yes.
- Yes, Sami. Yes...
- There it is. Sami lands
the first one for Baka.
- [cheering]
- We are tied. One each.
- All three tribes.
Three balls total.
- Get up.
- Stay up there.
- Dwight with a second.
Will it stay?
- [groans]
- PROBST: No. The slow roll.
There goes
Ryan with a nice toss.
Will it stick? It does.
It is Coco in the lead with two.
- There it is. There's the kid.
- Yes, yes, yes.
PROBST:
Sami drops the second,
but it won't stick.
[groans]
♪ ♪
- PROBST: Dwight lands
a second for Vesi.
- Nice, Dwight.
- All you, Dwight.
- PROBST: We are tied two-two.
It is Vesi with two,
Coco with two.
Ryan could win it
right here for Coco.
[groans]
PROBST:
No. On and off.
Dwight could win it right here.
Dwight. Will it stick?
- It does! Vesi wins immunity!
- [cheering]
We're looking for one more.
It is Sami and Ryan.
Immunity still on the line.
- Sami with number two.
- JEANINE: Yes, Sami. Yes.
PROBST:
Will it stay? Yes, it does.
- Baka with two.
- Yes, Sami!
One ball left for immunity.
Ryan now feeling the pressure.
Aim for the right side.
PROBST:
Ryan close,
but knocks all three balls off.
- Yes.
- Ah, Ryan.
Ryan knocks everything off
for Coco.
- I'm sorry, guys.
- PROBST: It is now
Baka in the lead with two.
Will that do it? Will it stay?
- And it does!
- [cheering]
Baka wins immunity!
- Yo, bro, it's good.
- PROBST: Sending Coco
back to Tribal Council,
where somebody will be the fifth
person voted out of Survivor 43.
- What a finish.
- Hey, but I don't
go to Chuck E. Cheese that much.
[laughter]
Vesi, another victory.
- Well-earned.
- [exclaims]
Nobody from your tribe
going home.
- Yeah, baby.
- Come grab your tarp.
- It'll keep you safe
from the rain and the sun.
- CODY: Yes, sir.
- Baka, nobody going
home from your tribe.
- [cheering]
- Thank you.
- Come grab your tarp.
ELIE:
I'll get it.
Well-earned.
All right,
before I send you on your way,
Vesi, choose one person
from Coco
to go on a journey.
They will return back to
camp in time for Tribal Council.
- Who's it gonna be?
- We're gonna go with Geo.
PROBST:
Geo, you're gonna
go on a journey.
Choose somebody
from Baka to join Geo.
Uh, we're gonna go with Jeanine.
- PROBST: Jeanine and Geo
gonna be on the journey.
- All right.
One person from the four of you.
Who's gonna go?
- Me.
- PROBST: It's gonna be Jesse.
- Jesse.
All right, grab your stuff,
head out. Boat will take you.
You will return back to camp
in time for Tribal Council.
Vesi, Baka, nice job. Nobody
going home. Enjoy the night off.
- Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
- Thank you.
Thanks, Jeff.
PROBST:
All right, Coco, you were
playing to earn your flint back.
I'll still keep it for now.
Sorry for you.
Tribal Council tonight,
Coco, where somebody will be
the fifth person
voted out of Survivor 43.
Grab your stuff, head out.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal.
Thank you, Jeff.
I think it's time
I let something out of the bag.
About the end of that challenge,
I was thinking,
"Should I win this?
"Should I really try 100%,
or should I knock
these two balls off?"
Kind of made that decision
to throw that
at the end of that challenge,
because I've been
trying to vote out Cassidy
for a very long time.
And I know that when
Jeff says, "Fifth person
going home, Survivor 43,"
it's gonna be Cassidy.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry. I was... I was
so close at the end of that.
- I know. That's okay.
- I mean...
- We did... we were...
- Team effort.
RYAN:
I throw this challenge
without anybody knowing,
'cause it looked
like I was really trying.
I looked upset,
but I was pretty happy.
I know they wanted to win,
and I know winning feels great,
numbers are great,
but now we can go to Tribal
and vote Cassidy out.
I'm good at acting, so
we tell Cassidy the vote's me,
because I did mess up.
As long as we keep Cassidy
in the mindset
that I'm going home tonight,
I feel like she won't
play her Shot in the Dark.
She's caught in our web.
She's not able to escape.
We got four spiders
all ready to eat her.
- ...to vote Ryan.
- Why would Ryan tell you
to say his own name?
Because he's comfortable.
'Cause they want
to blindside you.
It's a easy four-zero vote.
Take a deep breath.
We have three votes.
We're putting them on Geo.
And the reason why we put 'em on
Geo is he's the most comfortable
- he's ever going to be.
- What if he gets an advantage?
Like an idol that's only good
for one Tribal?
Yeah, with those "what ifs,"
if you feel comfortable
putting three on Ryan...
Pret... 100% sure I trust Karla.
Okay.
We were deciding
between Geo and Ryan.
I brought up voting out Ryan.
I think it would be a good move.
And I think it would
be less risk on my part.
Yeah.
CASSIDY:
If we target Ryan, most likely
I'll be safe tonight,
and Ryan will go home,
because I don't think
Geo would use
any advantage
that he had on Ryan,
'cause I don't think Geo worries
that Ryan's gonna be voted out.
Hi.
Oh, my God.
You're cutting down
that whole tree?
Yeah.
I'm frustrated.
I usually go to the gym
to get my frustration out.
Yeah.
What are you frustrated about?
It's just, like,
they're being nice,
but I guess they were really
frustrated with the challenge,
'cause we were...
Because the change.
James came back with a different
energy, after he talked to me.
Yeah.
I'd rather you vote me
and not be on the wrong side
of the vote, in case it is me,
so that you have
a chance to get further.
You know what I mean?
CASSIDY:
Ryan thinks he's come up with
this mastermind plan
to put the votes on him.
And he's trying to act so noble,
like, "The votes
are going towards me."
Like, "I don't want you to be
on the wrong side of the numbers
"going forward.
I want you to be good.
So, like, if you have
to vote me, you can."
And meanwhile,
this whole time I'm like,
"You're so full of B.S."
Okay. Oh, my God. Okay.
- Why? What was he saying?
- [chuckles]
He's like...
He's like, "I just felt
the energy totally change
"with them, while you
were at the water well.
I don't know.
I just have a feeling it's me."
He's like,
"If it's me, you know,
I don't want you to be on
the wrong side of the numbers."
[chuckles] It's funny because
Ryan's planning
this whole thing and, like,
using himself
as a decoy, and now
he's the actual vote.
JAMES:
My man. Good job.
If this plays out,
I'm gonna have some ink
on my Survivor résumé.
And that's what I want.
Right now, you're definitely
playing a believable story,
so just keep up whatever
level of acting you're doing.
RYAN:
I got you.
Hopefully this
follows me outside the game.
- They're like,
"You're pretty good." [chuckles]
- Stop.
[exhales] Nice.
♪ ♪
JESSE: On the journey,
me, Geo and Jeanine,
we're pulling up
to this beautiful little island
in the middle of the ocean.
And so I'm thinking,
"Oh, it's gonna be simple.
"We're gonna get
to walk up to this table.
"We're gonna
get to take our risk
and potentially get a reward."
And then we pass the island,
and we come up on this,
like, pontoon
that has this, like,
rinky-dink boat attached to it.
- Hands. [grunts]
- Okay. Thank you.
Yeah, of course. [whoops]
- [chuckles]
- We made it. [chuckles]
Nice to meet you.
Okay.
I feel like I invited
you guys to a really... party.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'm so sorry.
- [chuckles]
- No, this is great.
This is a boat party. [chuckles]
- Let's do it.
- JESSE: All right. Let's do it.
We read that we have to sort of
row our way to that
beautiful little island.
So I was, like,
not too excited about this.
♪ ♪
- JEANINE: We're making progress.
- JESSE: Sorry.
- [chuckles]
- GEO: Yeah, a little bit.
- JESSE: Somewhat, yeah.
GEO:
It's kind of weird for me,
because I thought I was gonna
get voted out last night.
I'm so sorry about that.
GEO:
I'm not being 100% honest
with Jesse and Jeanine.
I know I'm safe, and
I'm protected by my alliance...
- We're so close.
- GEO: ...but I kind
of lie a little bit
about being in the bottom,
so that way
they can try to help me.
JESSE:
How are you feeling
tonight, though?
GEO:
Um, I'm scared still.
Like, I am
the smallest guy in the group.
Maybe they can feel bad for me
and be like,
"Hey, you know what?
"You kind of need this
more than I do,
and let me not risk my vote."
So that way I can get whatever
advantage there was on there.
- [screams]
- Damn. Okay.
So I'm kind
of just milking the moment.
You want to get out?
- Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- Oh... [groans]
Just to see if somebody bites.
- I don't want to go
home with any regrets.
- JEANINE: Yeah.
- I'm gonna risk everything
I can to be able to stay.
- Yeah.
You're definitely risking?
But I'm definitely risking.
JEANINE: From the get-go,
Geo's kind of like,
"I'm on the outs.
I need this. I'm risking it."
And I'm not sure
if I buy this underdog story.
I wish that I could trust him,
and so now I'm racking my brain.
JESSE:
Geo, I mean, I think
he's taking a risk
because his back
is against the wall.
But Jeanine seems like she's,
you know, out here to play.
Like, she's got
scars on her chin already.
She's got scars on her knees.
For me, I really have
to think through
whether I'm gonna
risk it or not.
JESSE:
We had to make a decision
whether we were gonna
risk our vote
or not risk our vote.
If we risked our vote,
we had a chance at an advantage,
but if I risk my vote
and I lose it,
it's really dangerous
to be on a four-person tribe
and you don't have a say.
Yeah, I really need this,
so I have no choice.
♪ ♪
[whoops softly]
[sighs]
JESSE: Yeah.
So we all take a risk,
and now I have a 33% chance
to get the advantage.
Which is limited odds,
but I'm here on Survivor,
and I had to do it.
I came out here, you know,
to set an example for my kids...
To dream big and go for it.
And so, like,
I don't think there was
really a question of whether
I was gonna risk it or not.
This is a million-dollar game.
Dang.
All that lying I just
had to do for no reason.
But I think it's worth the risk,
because even
if I don't get anything,
we still have three votes.
So at least
I'll be able to be protected.
- All right, let's go.
- JEANINE: All right.
Let's go.
But if I do get an advantage,
that'll be crazy, huh?
[laughs]
♪ ♪
JESSE:
Coming back to camp,
you know, there's
no use in being dishonest.
There's no use in, like,
trying to pull one over on them.
They know
what I went out there to do.
CODY:
Jesse!
- Let me sit down.
- [Dwight laughs]
NOELLE:
Yeah, come sit down by the fire.
- We got it going.
- Yeah...
JESSE:
So I plan to just be honest
and see what happens.
I risked and they risked.
And so, one-in-third shot.
- Yeah.
- All righty.
JESSE:
I have this little shell
that was tied together,
and so I decided to open it
with the rest of the tribe,
because I'd rather them know
where the votes stand.
Aw.
It's all right.
- No big deal.
- NOELLE: No worries.
JESSE:
So I took a big swing,
and I got a big miss.
[laughs]: I lost my vote
at the next Tribal Council.
So I come back to camp
with a little shell,
which I know inside has my fate.
And it's crucial that
I know what's in there
before I tell my tribemates.
♪ ♪
So I peel aside at camp
to sneak a peek.
Okay.
Crap.
Crap, crap.
- Hello!
- [cheering]
- We literally just said,
you should be home soon.
- JEANINE: Obviously not what
I wanted to happen,
but, so far,
our tribe has been
very open and communicative
with these advantages, and
I want my tribe to feel like
they are
on the same page with me.
You guys...
...I risked it...
ELIE:
And?
Let's open it.
So I'm kind of playing a little
bit of a actor role here,
and I'm like,
"Oh, I'm so nervous to open it."
[gasps]
- No. [laughs]
- Ah...
Dang.
- That's okay.
- Don't you dare win?
SAMI: One of the things that
all of us here know now,
that Jeanine lost her vote
because she,
for whatever reason,
risked her vote in order
to try to gain another advantage
in the game, which something
else that we know
is that Jeanine has
a hidden immunity idol as well.
It's just a funky
and crazy way to play,
'cause as soon
as somebody senses
that you're playing the game
harder than anybody else,
nobody will mind
just getting rid of you,
'cause that's
one step closer to their dream.
♪ ♪
RYAN:
Stella!
- JAMES: Yeah!
- Geo, come home!
GEO:
Tonight is gonna be
pretty easy.
KARLA:
Welcome home.
GEO:
Me, Ryan, James and Karla
voting Cassidy out tonight.
Welcome back, my guy.
GEO:
I don't want Cassidy
to know that I risked my vote.
I know she's going home tonight,
but I still don't want her
to know what's going on.
It was just a floating platform
in the middle of the ocean.
We only had, like,
a few minutes,
- and because of the waves, it
was, like, all over the place.
- Yeah.
Yeah?
GEO:
My plan is to show my alliance
what is it that I got,
because I don't
want them to think
that I'm trying anything shady
or anything like that.
I'm so excited for you, Geo.
I'm, like, shaking.
- I haven't opened it yet.
- Oh, my God, okay.
Yeah.
KARLA: The beauty of having Geo
trust me is that
he was too excited
to share that
he risked his vote...
Even though he lied to the tribe
and said that he didn't.
- You're the first person
I showed, but...
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh. I got it?
- [gasps]
- I got it. I got it.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
This is what I came here for.
Like, I came to Survivor to get
an idol or to get an advantage.
I've never seen anybody use the
Knowledge Is Power successfully,
but it's a very powerful tool,
and I'm gonna save it
in my little bank, and I'm gonna
use it later, because
I'm not getting
voted out tonight.
- KARLA: All three
of you risked it?
- All of us risked.
KARLA:
You are set.
Discovering that Geo
has a Knowledge Is Power,
of course I was excited.
I was like,
"Shoot. Someone could
make a really big move."
But then I paused, and I said,
"Yeah, someone could
make a really big move on me."
Does he know
that I have an idol?
Has he been wondering, what,
"We can't find one on
the island. Does Karla have one?
Should I use this
against Karla tonight?"
I have to
do something about this.
So, Geo did risk it.
I think Geo's
the best move right now.
JAMES: I know it's scary,
but that's the game.
CASSIDY: I thought we had it
locked in, but my alliance
got spooked at the last minute.
They're like,
"Just trust me. Vote Geo,"
but I know I'm getting votes,
and if this Geo vote
doesn't work out,
then I-I know I'm going home.
JAMES:
We have to take this shot.
They're going after me.
We all know that.
If it was one of y'all's
name on the line,
you'd also have concerns
- that you would want to bring up
- Let me tell you...
- and assess all the options.
- KARLA: I know.
JAMES:
Me and Karla want to vote Geo.
Cassidy wants to vote Ryan.
She's just worried
that votes are coming her way.
Why are people so afraid?
- We have numbers.
Like, it's a numbers game.
- I know.
She is starting to freak out,
and this is...
I-I hope it's
not a Lindsay number two.
We're so close
to the freaking merge.
Me and Karla
are sitting there like, "Yo,
we've had the same exact talk
with Lindsay
at the same exact place."
She got paranoid and therefore
she got voted out.
And we thought
Cass was a cool customer,
but it's
the exact same situation.
It's very easy to say,
"Sorry, Cass, you can just go,"
but I also feel like
Geo does have an advantage,
and I'm like, "That's dangerous
to keep in the game."
So I had
to figure out the best move
for me and Karla moving forward.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, here's
my first question, Cassidy.
Can you feel momentum?
Like, if you're at a sporting
event and you feel it shift.
Or is momentum
merely a state of mind?
CASSIDY:
You know, I do
believe in momentum. I think
we had good momentum
coming into this game.
It shifted a little bit,
but that doesn't mean that
it can't change on a dime
and shift back into our favor,
and that's really
what I'm hoping for
after this Tribal Council.
Ryan, what's
your take on momentum?
Um, I would have to say
it's a group effort.
It's synergy,
a way to move together.
And we had it in
the beginning of this challenge,
but at the end of it,
as an individual,
I think I dropped the ball...
Quite literally,
with this challenge.
PROBST:
Let's talk about that
for a second,
because in a challenge
like today,
where there were
so many layers to it,
- Yeah.
- Is it fair to put the blame
on the person who
literally dropped the ball?
You know, I told them, "Hey, if
my name needs to go out there,
"you know, I'm ready for it,
as long as it keeps you guys
strong through the merge."
And I'll look back
over my shoulder, if it is me,
and I'll give them a smile.
I don't have any hate,
no animosity.
I just want to enjoy my time
in Fiji as best as I can.
Cassidy, how was
that information received?
CASSIDY:
I mean, it's interesting because
for somebody to come in and be
so like, "It's okay if it's me.
I just want
what's best for the tribe."
That's just not normally
the type of game that you see.
And, I mean,
I respect it if that's
the way that
he wants to play his game.
Um, I just don't know if I
would have done the same thing.
PROBST:
So, Ryan, is there
any concern that
putting the sword right here
and saying, "If you want me
to fall on it, I will,"
that they'll just push you?
Um, yeah, but I think
staying true to myself, like,
I've always been a giver,
and going out as a giver
isn't something I'm ashamed of.
PROBST:
So, Karla, is there
part of you just thinking,
"I'm sharpening my knife, right?
He's made it so easy.
- He's going to lie down for me."
- [laughs]
- Of course.
You just want it to be easy.
I think an easy, an easy vote
- doesn't complicate things,
especially at Tribal.
- Mm.
And I can't imagine how
Geo feels just coming back,
and, like, just
getting all this information.
So, yeah, like, part of me
just is ready with the knives.
Like, why not?
All right, Geo,
so you're not there
- for this
early discussion, where...
- [laughs]
I'm trying
to catch up right now.
- I'm like, "What's going on?"
- [laughter]
- Are you really?
- Yes.
PROBST:
So then, what are you
feeling right now?
- Are you solid or uneasy?
- Um...
I'm uneasy because I wasn't part
of many of these conversations
that probably happened
back in camp.
I just want to make sure I vote
at the right direction,
'cause if I'm voting against
all the votes, then all
the votes might be on me,
and I might be
the next person going home,
and I'm not trying
to go home tonight.
PROBST:
James, did you ask Geo
- what happened on the journey?
- We didn't have to ask Geo.
- Geo came and-and
just told us what happened.
- [laughs]
I mean, I feel like that's the
best way to move in this game,
because keeping
the information flowing
amongst each other,
especially when we're
going to be competing soon
in a merge.
So, Geo, how do you
use Tribal right now
to try to make sure you're okay?
You just said, "I don't
even know who to vote for."
Well, you're scaring the crap
out of me right now,
like, telling me all this stuff.
- Wait, you've watched
Survivor before, right?
- But... I know.
- [laughter]
- Yes.
This is not new.
But at this point,
it's critical for me to hear
everything and see everyone's
faces when they're talking,
'cause you don't know
who's telling the truth.
I really don't know what to do,
but I'm just gonna trust my gut
and hope that I can
be on the right side tonight.
PROBST:
Karla, is it possible
that Geo's telling the truth
and that he really doesn't know
what the four of you are
talking about and planning?
♪ ♪
Yes. Uh, sorry. I'm...
I'm listening to the answers
and internalizing it.
I just hope that if anyone
would have gone on a journey
and come straight to Tribal,
that they really trust
in their alliance,
because that's really, I think,
the way that
you will survive Tribal.
PROBST:
So, Ryan, as we
get ready for the vote,
if you're voted out tonight,
is your story gonna be,
"Hey, man, I put myself
in the money position.
I didn't deliver. They
voted me out, and that's fair."
I-I guess that's what
I'm gonna have to go home with.
I feel more of the fact
of keeping the people
that I care about as unified as
possible as I walk out the door.
PROBST:
So if people write your name
down, would you like them
- to put, like,
a little smiley face?
- [laughter]
I would like them to say
what they liked most about me
to that camera.
- That's how I would...
- PROBST: Okay.
I never know what the truth is,
but you've pitched it
pretty hard
that you're a kindhearted soul,
and you just want to play
the game with love,
whether that means
you're out tonight or
you're there at the final three.
It's just, uh,
kill 'em with kindness.
It's what's been in my blood
since the day I was born.
Cassidy, if you survive
and the vote goes the way
you want it to go,
how will the tribe be different?
CASSIDY:
Um, I think
we'll be more unified.
I think with each vote
in the right direction,
you can kind of trust
your allies
a little bit more each time.
And so I think
it'll only strengthen
my alliance,
going into the merge.
All right, it is time to vote.
Geo, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'm sure you're amazing,
but you have to go.
♪ ♪
You think you can play me,
but the truth is
I'm the one that
put the blanks in your gun.
I have the real bullets.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
If anyone has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote, Cassidy.
Cassidy.
Two votes Cassidy.
Geo.
That's two votes Cassidy,
one vote Geo.
Geo. That's two votes Cassidy,
two votes Geo,
one vote left.
♪ ♪
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor 43...
Geo.
That's three.
You need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Geo, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
- BYOB! Where's the party at?!
- Huh?
JEANINE:
The game is starting.
I am so excited.
CODY:
We're at Normandy here.
...about to hit the fan.
One final twist.
SAMI:
Somebody's dream
is going to end.
There's nowhere
to hide right now.
I'm scared to death
at what's coming next.
Wow. You can't trust
nobody around here. [chuckles]
I just got blindsided,
but it's part of the game.
It's Survivor.
I'm going home with
a little souvenir in my pocket,
and I'm happy
with the game that I played.
I might have played
a little too hard,
but that's fine,
because if you don't come
to Survivor and play hard,
then there's no point of coming
to Survivor. It's pointless.
[roars]