♪ ♪
JEANINE:
I'm still reeling from
what happened at Tribal tonight.
Elie, my number one ally,
ended up getting voted out,
and I was completely blindsided.
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor 43...
- Elie.
- Dang.
Y'all see what
trusting Gabler will get you?
- Ooh.
Right back at you.
JEANINE:
You never hope to be that person
that is left out of the vote.
And just that
initial feeling of, like,
"Oh, my God,
I am on the outside,
and people didn't tell me
this crucial information."
I-I understand.
I was literally
in your position.
I know. This is the same thing
that happened with Justine. I...
- NOELLE: It is,
but the good thing is...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...this has nothing to do
with you and your game.
- Okay. Okay.
If anything, I mean, how
I learned, it bettered my game.
- Yeah.
- I believe this will help you.
- And my advice,
like, how to handle it...
- Yeah. Yeah.
- ...like, how I handled it...
- Yeah, yeah.
Like, you act like it's okay.
- Yeah. Of course. Yeah.
- You don't... Yeah.
- Because... No, yeah.
- I'm not, I'm not upset.
I'm not.
- No, yeah, yeah...
- Yeah, exactly.
I just feel
really confused and alone,
but I feel like right now
I need to pretend like this
is the best thing for my game.
I am so good.
Like, I-I know
that this is gonna free me.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- It was already
putting a target on my back.
But this is gonna be
a blessing in disguise,
because it allows me
to just play my own game.
I don't want you to think
that I'm tied to Elie
in any way and that...
- We're good. 100%.
- Oh, 100%.
It's gonna free me
to play my own game.
This is great for your game, honestly.
- Yes.
- Everyone could see that
y'all two were inseparable.
JEANINE:
Everyone has told me I'm okay,
but I just want to cry.
[laughs]
Yeah.
♪ ♪
CASSIDY:
Ryan's just stomping on crabs.
That guy's got endless energy.
He does.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
OWEN:
I wanted
to utilize the Baka five
that we had
worked so hard to keep.
"Keep the five alive."
That's what we've
been saying for days.
But it turns out
Gabler is on the war path.
He is a loose cannon,
and after the fiasco
with the Elie situation,
it's a bull in a china shop.
Yeah.
- Not even trying to... Yeah.
- [chuckles]
Yeah. It's like, "Oh, we worked
so hard to keep five of us."
- [chuckles] I mean, like...
- He's just like, "Screw it."
[laughs]
It's like
we've invited the entire tribe
to come view the Grand Canyon
that is the crack
in the Baka alliance.
And Gabler definitely
raises some red flags
about keeping him in my alliance
for the long haul.
'Cause who knows
what he could do next?
I woke up this morning, I looked
at the sunrise, and I'm like,
"Ah."
Yeah, I mean, it's a...
She was just
a dangerous player, man.
It's a better day on the beach.
More peaceful day
on the beach, for sure.
That's important.
I just put my idol...
Now-now defunct, right?
So I just took it
and put it right back in here.
Last night I didn't
play my idol. I didn't have to.
And now it's expired.
On top of that,
the plan that I hatched,
that I wanted
to have happen, happened.
"Alli-Gabler" kind of came up
to the surface, came over there.
I didn't trust Elie.
We took her out.
Now I plan
to go underwater again
and just chill,
and then pop back up so
I'm not perceived as a threat.
But when the time is right,
I'm ready to strike.
- Hey, y'all.
- Hey, guys.
- Come down to the beach.
- Come to the beach.
We got a little
something-something.
- Oh, shoot. Let's do this.
- Okay.
Art project!
RYAN:
We got tree mail.
DWIGHT:
So we get tree mail.
We're all thinking, oh, there's
gonna be something, like,
something happy of like,
"Hooray, y'all made the merge.
Go paint
your tribe flag together."
Oh... [chuckles] Okay.
Absolutely not.
Yes.
- [gasping]
- Oh.
Oh.
- SAMI: What the hell?
- [overlapping chatter]
- KARLA: "You must divide"?
- DWIGHT: Six pairs.
KARLA:
We must divide?
- We choose?
- I guess so.
OWEN:
We're gonna be pairing up
for this immunity challenge.
So that, to me,
is tremendously awkward.
Uh...
How do we...?
- JEANINE: How do we do this?
- GABLER: Ah, geez.
That's awkward.
No one wants to say,
"Oh, I want to go with Ryan."
"Oh, I want to go with Cody."
No one wants to
officially make the decision
of even the methodology
of how we're choosing partners.
- That is not
what I was expecting at all.
- DWIGHT: Yeah.
I thought it'd be
a lot more peaceful.
Well, I mean,
at the end of the day...
- CODY: We don't know
what the challenge is.
- We don't know what it is.
- Yeah, we don't know what it is.
- [overlapping chatter]
We're just forced to break up
into pairs to compete for what?
Are we competing for a reward?
Are we competing for two of us
to win immunity?
Are we competing
against each other?
What's happening?
None of us know
what to do at this point.
[laughter]
- Really awkward.
- [overlapping chatter]
It just brings me
back to middle school.
Everyone feels self-conscious.
- This sucks.
- DWIGHT: This is awkward.
CASSIDY:
I don't know.
Sure.
I like that idea.
It was a really interesting
five-second social experiment
before all of us just said,
"Let's draw rocks." [chuckles]
RYAN:
I'm nervous.
All right.
- [gasping]
- All right.
Ooh!
RYAN:
Okay.
Here we go.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
All right, day 14.
Shall we get into it?
- Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Today in tree mail,
you received a note
telling you
to divide up into pairs.
How did that go, Karla?
Um, we painted two rocks
with the same color to equal 12.
- And so we pulled rocks.
- PROBST: All right.
I like it.
Let's divide into pairs.
Just starting down here,
get next to your partner,
so we can see who's with who.
Okay.
PROBST:
So we have Owen and Gabler,
Cody and Dwight,
Noelle and Sami,
Ryan and James,
Karla and Cassidy,
and Jesse and Jeanine.
How do you feel
about these pairs?
- Everybody basically happy?
- Yeah.
- I think we all feel good.
- SAMI: I'm happy.
All right,
for today's challenge,
we're doing
something a little different.
Today's challenge
will be run in three stages.
You got to make the cut
in order to make the next stage.
For the first stage,
you're gonna crawl
through a muddy, twisted net.
You'll then dig up planks
and race back to your mat.
The first four pairs
to plant their flag in their mat
move on to the next stage.
The last two pairs are out.
No shot at immunity.
For the second stage,
you're gonna race up
a cargo net and use those
planks to cross a rope bridge.
You got to get both players
and all three planks
to the other side,
then drop down the wall
and race to your mat.
The first two pairs to finish
move on to the final stage.
The last two pairs, they're out.
No shot at immunity.
For the final stage,
the pairs are over.
You're now four individuals
competing against each other.
You'll hold on to a handle
which is attached
to a bucket that contains
25% of your pregame weight.
And as your hands fatigue,
that bucket will lower.
When it finally drops
and smashes the tile...
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity.
Tonight
you'll be wearing this...
- [group oohing]
- ...at Tribal Council.
This means you are safe,
cannot be voted out.
- Guaranteed a spot
in the final 11.
- Wow.
PROBST:
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the seventh person
voted out of Survivor 43.
All right,
we're gonna draw for spots,
and I'll give you
a minute to strategize.
We'll get started.
Let's do it.
♪ ♪
Here we go.
First four pairs
move on to the next stage.
Survivors ready?
- Go!
- Let's go, Jesse!
- Good job, Owen!
It's gonna be Cassidy,
Ryan, Jesse, Cody...
- DWIGHT: You got it, bro.
- ...Owen and Sami
going through first.
NOELLE:
Here we go, Sami!
PROBST:
Your partner can't go
until you get through.
It is a twisted, muddy net.
It looks so easy
for those first five paces.
Roll!
[groans]
Cassidy's
gonna be first through.
- Go, Karla!
- Let's go, baby!
It is Cassidy and Karla
in the lead right now.
DWIGHT:
You're good.
Ryan's through. Go.
James is in. Sami's good.
- Go, Noelle.
- SAMI: You got it, Noelle.
PROBST:
Noelle now in the net.
♪ ♪
PROBST: There goes Karla
working through it.
RYAN: Yeah, keep rolling,
keep rolling, keep rolling.
I'll tell you when you're done.
James working that net.
Super aggressive
with how he's doing that.
James has a lot of energy now.
That is how you do it.
James is through. You're good.
- It is James and Ryan
in the lead.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Both of you are digging.
- Now it's Cody really trying
to get something going.
- DWIGHT: Yes!
Yes!
There you go, Cody.
Dwight's now in.
We're looking for four pairs.
You're good, Owen. Go, Gabler.
- CASSIDY: Keep rolling, Karla.
You're almost there!
- [grunts]
- Here comes Karla!
- Good job!
- PROBST: That's
how you do it, Karla.
- Let's go.
Let's go, Karla, Cassidy.
You're good.
Start digging.
- Ah.
- PROBST: Dwight working.
CODY:
Keep spinning, Dwight.
Keep spinning.
You got to spin, bro.
That's the only way
you're gonna get through there.
DWIGHT:
[grunts] Dang it.
PROBST:
Noelle is working.
- She is stuck.
- SAMI: Keep going, Noelle.
PROBST:
Noelle is taking
her leg off mid-challenge.
Amazing.
- Jeff!
James, Ryan, you're good.
We're looking
for three more pairs.
Get to the mat! Get to the mat!
PROBST:
There you go. Jesse.
You're good.
Jeanine now on the course.
She was
the last to get in there.
She's gonna
have to make up some time.
JESSE:
You got it, Jeanine. You got it.
Let's go. Let's go.
You're good. Start digging.
It is now Owen
and Gabler digging.
- CODY: You're good.
- PROBST: You're good.
Start digging.
Dwight and Cody, let's go.
- There it is, Karla.
- Help me, help me. Come on.
Karla and Cassidy have theirs.
Get back with the flag.
- Owen and Gabler have theirs.
- [grunting loudly]
- Gabler.
- You're good.
Karla, Cassidy have moved on.
[grunts]
You got to get all the way.
Three's three.
Owen and Gabler have moved on.
We're looking for one more.
- [panting]
- SAMI: Keep digging, Noelle.
Keep digging.
PROBST: Right now it looks like
it's going to be Dwight and Cody
because Jeanine
and Noelle are both stuck.
Cannot get out.
It looks so easy
to just crawl through,
- but it's not.
- We're almost there.
CODY:
Right here. [grunts]
PROBST: The fourth pair
that's gonna move on,
Cody and Dwight.
There it is.
[whimpers]
PROBST:
Cassidy, Karla,
James, Ryan, Dwight,
Cody, and Owen and Gabler
move on. Everybody else is out.
Help your tribemates get out.
NOELLE:
I'm so sorry, Sami.
SAMI:
Stop it. You're good.
[whimpers]
- JEANINE: Jesse... I'm so sorry.
- It's all good.
- No, no, it's all right.
- I'm so sorry.
PROBST:
They'll get you out, Noelle.
You are not alone.
That was a difficult challenge.
- We tried our best.
- It's all good.
That's all we can do.
BOTH:
PROBST:
I love seeing this.
On day 14,
in a million-dollar game,
everybody helping everyone.
GABLER:
We got you.
[laughing]:
Stop.
We're good. I didn't want
to hold on to no damn bucket.
GABLER:
Way to battle. Everybody.
- [clapping]
- Good job, Jeanine.
Yeah. Thank you, guys.
You look like a warrior.
- Good job, everyone.
- CASSIDY: Good job.
Sami, you were
the first to get in there,
and you were the first to say,
"I didn't want
to hang on to a bucket,"
basically implying, "I don't
care. I care about you."
- Yeah.
- I'm noticing this
more and more in this game,
that you are all obviously
fighting for a million dollars,
everybody here wants it, and yet
you still have the capacity
and the empathy to say,
"But we got to help Noelle."
We all went through that,
literally through the ringer.
And for Noelle to do it,
for the sake of giving me
a chance to compete
and to further myself
- in this game,
that's all it means to me.
- GABLER: Oh, yeah.
- SAMI: So that was,
that was warrior effort.
- [clapping]
OWEN:
Beast mode.
NOELLE:
It's tough because
if this was individual,
I-I wouldn't
be beating myself up as much.
But, I mean,
I'm doing it as a team.
I'm doing it with him.
Like, I want him to succeed.
- More than me.
- And that means the most to me.
That's all that matters to me.
- She got through it.
- I mean, these guys, they're
the ones giving me inspiration.
[crying]:
And it's... it just... it...
This is like the first time
I've been emotional out here.
- [laughs]
- I mean, that sucked.
- JEANINE: Incredible, Noelle.
- [clapping]
- Yeah.
- RYAN: You are inspiring.
All right. I love the love.
The game continues.
The four winning pairs, let's
reset and we'll keep going.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
So, I'm gonna remind you
what you're
gonna do in this stage.
You're gonna be taking
your planks up that cargo net.
When you get to the top,
there's a rope bridge.
You're gonna use
the three planks to cross it.
You got to get both your bodies
and all three planks
to the other side,
then you get to your mat,
because only
the first two pairs move on.
The last two pairs are out.
Sound good?
- Yeah.
- Yes, sir.
PROBST:
All right, here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
[grunting]
PROBST:
Moving up that net.
Okay.
PROBST:
Everybody's up top.
Now comes the teamwork.
Cassidy using her teeth.
Once you get those planks free,
you can start
across the rope bridge.
There's no time to waste here.
This is a sprint on day 14.
- It is Ryan and James
once again in the lead.
- [indistinct chatter]
Cody and Dwight
right on their tail.
Here's Cassidy and Karla
and Owen and Gabler.
Six men, two women.
Both the women working together.
It is now Dwight and Cody.
Great teamwork.
Doing it two at once.
Lower.
Ryan and James,
it's just balancing.
It's gonna be Dwight and Cody.
They're gonna get across first.
- But you got to get
all the planks.
- Give me the planks.
- CODY: Go ahead.
- PROBST: You're good with one.
There's two. You're good.
Get down the other side.
Cody and Dwight.
- Yeah, baby!
- Let's go!
They're moving on!
- [whoops] Yes!
- [cheers]
Good job, guys.
Hold on to that bucket, boys.
- Smooth, bro! Smooth!
- Dude.
Oh, my God, that was amazing.
PROBST:
We're looking for one more pair.
Keep digging! Let's go!
Right now!
- It's Cassidy and Karla.
- Give me your hand.
Give me your hand.
PROBST:
You got to get the planks.
Owen and Gabler.
There's James and Ryan.
- This is gonna be close!
- [cheering]
Oh! Karla falls!
That's it.
They've got to start over.
- Here.
- You got to get all the planks.
Who's gonna be there?
They dropped! They're out!
[shouting]
- [laughter]
- Owen and Gabler move on.
- What a finish.
- Gabler with the barrel roll.
With the barrel roll.
PROBST: Two pairs collapsed
at the last second.
Karla fell, and Ryan and James
have lost one of their planks.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Bro, bro, bro...
I didn't look at them, bro.
PROBST:
All right, losers, take
a spot on the sit-out bench.
For the final round,
it's gonna be Cody and Dwight
and Gabler and Owen.
All right, let's do this.
Take your spots.
So, everybody has 25% of their
body weight in their bucket.
The way the challenge works is,
when we start,
you put your hands on the bar,
palms down, knuckles up,
and you're gonna
pull back toward you.
That's gonna
release the mechanism
that is
holding the bucket right now.
When you hit the tile,
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
- guaranteed one in 11.
- [spits]
All right, everybody
put your hands on the bar.
When I tell you to,
pull it back towards your body,
and this challenge is on.
Three, two, one. Pull it back.
Everybody is good,
and this challenge is on.
All you have to do is
keep your bucket up in the air
longer than the other three
and this beautiful
immunity necklace is yours.
We've had men
win this challenge.
We've had women
This comes down
to pure endurance.
How badly do you want it?
Nothing is easy out here.
Just to get to this position,
you had to work.
This is a challenge where you're
going to reach a breaking point.
Fatigue takes
over your entire body.
Just slowly,
it starts to inch its way down
and it gets so far
that you can't recover.
Dwight's bucket dropping.
This is that moment, Dwight.
You feel it
slipping away, literally,
slipping through your hands.
[exhales heavily]
You've got to dig in that grip.
Your forearms are burning.
Your body's exhausted.
- Dwight drops.
- JEANINE: Great job, Dwight.
- PROBST: Dwight
is the first person out.
- Nice work, Dwight.
No shot at immunity.
We're down to three.
It is Gabler, Owen and Cody.
Holding 25%,
a quarter of your body weight.
[breathes deeply]
What are you
digging on right now, Gabler?
using for inspiration?
My uncle had heart surgery...
last week.
Heart team I know worked on him.
Sure he's doing fine.
How about you, Owen?
What do you draw on right now?
Wearing that necklace.
That's my, that's my dream
as a little kid, man.
Just want to win.
Give it everything I got.
PROBST:
How about you, Cody?
Jeff, I lost a wrestling match
my senior year of high school
to go to State.
I've regretted
that moment my entire life.
PROBST:
Wow.
And this is my opportunity
to redeem myself.
PROBST:
Three very personal stories,
all with the same purpose...
Give you what you need
to keep that bucket in the air.
This next minute's for Noelle.
She's inspired me
throughout this whole challenge.
I admire the minute-by-minute
fresh inspiration.
Been out here 23 minutes.
- [whoops]
- That is a long time
to be doing this.
- Great job.
- You're doing great.
I can do this all day.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
PROBST:
Gabler, for the first time,
his bucket dropping
and quickly pulls it back up.
There we go.
[exhales]
PROBST:
Little movement by Owen now.
OWEN:
Ah.
Owen trying to pull
his bucket back up again.
- Digging in.
- [exhales]
PROBST:
Digging.
Owen starting to drop again.
- Hovering in that 50% spot.
- [strains]
- Owen drops. Owen is out.
- RYAN: Good job, Owen.
- NOELLE: Great job, Owen.
- Good job, Owen!
- SAMI: Good job, Owen.
Owen, take a spot on the bench.
We're down to two.
It is now Gabler versus Cody
in a showdown.
Cody's got his head down.
Gabler locked in.
You're at 24 minutes.
- Damn.
- [clapping]
PROBST: The longest anybody
has gone in this challenge...
25 minutes.
- JAMES: Let's go! Let's go!
- KARLA: Ooh.
- CASSIDY: You're so close.
- JAMES: Let's go.
We will break the record, Cody.
Hang in there, buddy.
I've been married
for almost 25 years.
I'm at least going 25.
Minute by minute,
Gabler working it.
Let's do this next minute
for Lester Tenney.
He's a war hero, passed now.
Survived the Bataan Death March.
Went to a prison camp.
Five years in captivity.
Made it home.
Found out his family
was told he was dead.
His wife remarried.
He had to remake his life.
Lester was one of our patients.
We fixed him.
I got to know Lester
for six great years.
I could do this
all day for Lester.
A lot of heroes
served in our military.
We do this for fun.
They did this for real.
- Love you, Gabler.
- PROBST: Been up here
a long time.
- OWEN: Hell yeah, bro.
- [overlapping chatter]
25 minutes and counting.
Yes, sir.
- [cheering]
- PROBST: This challenge
has now lasted longer
- than it ever has
in any other season.
- SAMI: Attaboys.
PROBST:
It does not get any easier.
Hell yeah, bro.
Every minute earned.
♪ ♪
This one's for my dog,
my furry-faced son.
32 minutes
you've been up there now.
[cheering, clapping]
This next minute's for Idaho.
This next minute's for Alaska.
I got some Navy SEAL buddies
that I went to high school with,
and this minute is for you.
I know a small man.
He had the same name of these
Louisiana forest sprites...
- Oh.
- GABLER: Muzzy.
They call 'em "Muzzies."
And he, uh, was my roommate.
- 37 minutes. A new record.
- JAMES: Yeah!
- KARLA: Wow.
- And in the last five
of those minutes,
both of
your buckets have slowly...
...inched closer to the bottom.
Gabler immediately
notices his bucket.
There goes Cody
pulling his bucket back up.
- Let's go, Cody.
- Let's go, boys.
PROBST:
Both guys digging in now.
38 minutes.
Those forearms starting
to really ache.
- Dig, Cody.
- [cheering, clapping]
This is why you came here...
For this.
RYAN:
Keep it going. Keep it going.
Cody drops a little more.
[overlapping chatter]
Getting dangerously close
to being out of this challenge.
KARLA:
Oh, no. Oh, no.
[straining]
Cody drops.
- Gabler wins
individual immunity.
- [chatter, clapping]
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
- Nice job, Gabler.
- Good job, Gabler.
PROBST:
What an effort.
In a three-stage battle.
Gabler, come on over here.
Man, you're feeling it.
Dude, I could have gone...
I was going for 51.
All right, Gabler.
- This is incredible.
Is this happening?
- [Cassidy howls]
- PROBST: It's happening.
- GABLER: Don't wake me up.
Don't wake me up.
- Man, you look handsome.
- Congratulations.
You are caked in mud,
but you are wearing the only
thing that matters right now,
the individual
immunity necklace.
With this around your neck,
you are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
- GABLER: Thank you, Jeff.
- PROBST: As for the rest of you,
somebody's dream
of winning Survivor 43
will come to an end.
Tribal Council tonight. Somebody
the seventh person voted out.
You grab your stuff, head out.
I'll see you tonight at Tribal.
- Well-earned.
- Thank you. Thank you, Jeff.
I didn't know I could do that.
All I can say is,
if you even think for a second
that you want to do this, do it.
You'll find power in yourself.
This could be waiting for you,
right here. Do it.
♪ ♪
- JAMES: Congratulations.
- CASSIDY: Good job, man.
Thank you.
In that challenge,
I was so inspired
by the people I was channeling,
because I'm playing Survivor
for veterans who are suffering
from traumatic brain injuries,
who are suffering from PTSD.
The veteran community has been
very special to me all my life.
My dad served and my uncles.
So I have
a military family background.
And until recently,
PTSD was something that
just came from the battlefield.
But trauma is trauma.
PTSD rings true with me because
I work in the operating room.
I've been in thousands of cases.
However,
sometimes things go wrong,
and there's
a patient on the table,
somebody's grandfather,
somebody's, you know, son.
There are some cases
that were 17 years ago
that I carry with me today.
Veterans are
one percent of our population
that take care of our 99%.
So if I can give 100% for them,
then I'll be, then I'll be
very proud and happy about that.
Oh!
- Same here.
- Yeah.
SAMI:
At the last Tribal Council,
not even everybody
was eligible to be voted for.
Over half
of the players were safe,
while the other half
of us were not.
Now things get interesting.
Now things open up,
and we really see
who's going with who.
I haven't heard any names yet.
Yes, we do.
OWEN:
Yeah.
Socially...
JEANINE:
So...
[grunts]
Oh.
What the heck
is that in there, yo?
Oh, what? Oh...
- Sorry.
- SAMI: You're good, bro.
I guess we're
together with this.
Damn. [chuckles]
Does anybody want it, though,
first and foremost?
SAMI:
Hell no.
JAMES:
Exactly.
- So, this is the thing.
- Oh, shoot.
Like, I'm regretting
everything at this moment,
just because I definitely put
a potential target on my back.
I mean, at the end of the day,
everybody gets nervous.
You know? And then
all you need is one extra thing.
"James has this."
We all know about it.
The note says there's an
advantage hidden under camp.
I was gonna wait
until after Tribal, but...
it's Survivor.
...that.
Curiosity got the best of me.
And also everybody knew
where it was at.
It may not be there by the time
Tribal happens, so...
Or they can vote me out
and just take it.
So I figured,
let me just get it now.
So...
SAMI:
A bottle in the well.
NOELLE:
I'm just thinking,
"Okay, James has something."
I was deciding
who I wanted to vote for.
It was either Ryan or James
and what benefited my game.
And that's just 100%,
nail in the coffin,
I'm voting for James.
James has, like,
just got a major advantage
in the water well.
- Supposedly.
- Uh-huh.
Supposedly,
James found something.
What do you mean,
he found something?
I heard James got some kind of
an idol down at the water well.
Oh, really?
I guess it was
in the water well.
- And then...
- Mm.
I think James is the one
that saw it first.
They found it in the water well,
and I think James got it.
So...
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- So then five on James?
JESSE:
Right now
there's the easy route.
I could go
with the Vesi-Baka alliance,
and we can, you know,
split the votes between
James and Ryan,
and we could take out James.
That's the route that Noelle
has sort of charted for us.
What are you hearing?
I have a feeling that Noelle
is calling the shots.
JESSE:
I go to Karla.
I genuinely trust Karla
more than I trust Noelle
right now. Like...
We have, like,
so many similar experiences,
and she reminds me
so much of my family.
If we don't
get Noelle by surprise,
we're gonna be dead.
This could blow my game,
because I've been, like,
with Vesi, but, like,
- we have
to figure out something.
- Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
- 'Cause you're seeing
the same thing I'm seeing.
- Yeah, yeah, for sure.
JESSE:
You can sit here in this game
and you can watch somebody like
Noelle accumulate this power
and, like, be like,
"Oh, you know what?
"Now is not the right time.
I'll try and, like,
weaken her eventually."
Or you can make a move now.
She's gaming.
She's gaming so hard.
And so, I go to Cody,
and I'm asking him
what his thoughts are.
I've never been
a huge fan of Dwight's.
- He's always kind of
been kind of eerie to me.
- Mm-hmm.
He thinks, instead of Noelle,
we should go after Dwight.
- Dwight's also
very good at this game.
- Yeah.
He's done the puzzles.
He's done all kinds of good...
JESSE:
That's not
personally what I want,
but if I'm able
to take out Dwight
and weaken Noelle,
that's fine with me.
And it also gives Cody,
like, a sense of agency, right?
Like, you don't want
to strip people
of their agency in this game.
It's gonna be a tough one.
Yeah.
We're exploring the option
of making a move already now
and joining with Coco
against Dwight and Noelle.
But Noelle...
CODY:
This is a move
that's going to really
make things a little crazy.
Is it too soon?
It could be,
but no matter what,
Jesse and I are gonna
be on the same page.
I have the Knowledge Is Power Advantage,
meaning that I can
take someone's idol or advantage
if I know who they are
right before
the votes at Tribal Council.
Ooh.
Right now I'm glad
I have something in my pocket,
but it's the most nervous
I've been in the game.
This is tricky just because,
once I take someone's idol,
if I'm successful,
I have a huge target on my back.
Then, if I'm wrong,
I'm definitely going home.
I got Geo's
Knowledge Is Power right now.
But using the Knowledge Is
Power to gain trust is very key.
- I do have Knowledge Is Power.
- Okay.
JAMES:
This Knowledge
Is Power Advantage
is something that I can use
to say, "Hey, I have this.
Let's work together."
I trust you, and...
Yeah.
Knowledge Is Power.
- So...
- Knowledge Is Power, you can...
- Take an idol.
- Really?
Yes.
CODY:
Oh, crap.
James has a Knowledge Is Power.
I still have
my immunity bracelet.
I know James knows I have it.
It may be time to vote him out.
Because now he is the most
dangerous player out here.
So, if for some reason
he would take
my immunity bracelet tonight...
...I've given it
to Jesse because
I feel it's safer with him
than with me at this time.
We don't know what it is,
but it could be
another merge advantage,
- like we've seen
the past two seasons.
- Yeah.
It's probably
Knowledge Is Power, so...
- We're just... Yeah.
- We're trying to, like,
transfer everything around
to make sure James
will never guess who has what.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- We don't know
what the advantage is,
so we're really
preparing for it to be anything.
But, in the event
that it's Knowledge Is Power,
we already have a plan
set in place where,
to cover our butts,
we will do cross-tribe switches.
It feels scary
to hand over my idol
when that is the one piece
of power I have right now.
- Okay.
- Of course, you know, I'll
give it right back to you...
Oh, no, of course. No, yeah,
of course. I trust you.
But I think my idol
is safer in Dwight's hands
than it is in mine.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just in case
James decides to ask me
do I have
an idol or advantage...
Ooh. I like that.
...we decide that I'm gonna
give my advantage to Owen.
This is gonna be super quick.
- Yeah. Dwight filled me in.
- Yeah, perfect.
- Genius. All right.
Piece of cake.
- Thank you.
OWEN:
Noelle gave me
her Steal a Vote in case
James had found
Knowledge Is Power.
So we played
a little musical chairs,
a little shell game,
to try to cover it up.
And then, on top of all that,
we're trying to, like,
figure out who to vote out.
So there are a lot of things
that could go wrong tonight.
JESSE:
There's so much that's
scary about tonight's vote.
There's the easy route
where, you know,
I just stick with the plan,
and we take out James tonight.
The more risky route is that
me and Cody flip our votes,
and we take out Dwight tonight,
and we turn our back on Vesi,
and it's officially
Vesi no more. [laughs]
♪ ♪
In this game there's
this question of timing, right?
Like, you don't want to make
a big move too soon, but also,
like, you don't want
to play somebody else's game.
But now we're
in the stage of the game where,
like, legends are made
or you flame out.
So, like, it's big. This is
the big league, so I'm ready.
♪ ♪
All right.
So, today
the challenge was designed
to really illustrate
this idea of earning it
every single step of the way.
Karla, you've
been banged up a lot.
Did you feel
that was a representation
of how difficult it really is
just to survive
one day out here?
KARLA:
Uh, I mean, of course.
The first stage was the hardest,
and I feel like that was
our experience, at least for me,
- the first five days
were the hardest.
- Mm.
KARLA:
And then you get
to the second stage
and you're kind of like,
"I-I got the hang of this."
But I could see then
the third stage was like,
"Oh, no, you got to hold on,"
because you don't know
how long you have
until you're gone.
So, Jesse, y'all get
back to camp. What happens?
I think we're at this, like,
different stage of the game.
Earlier stage of the game,
we're going to Tribal
with six people.
It's, like,
almost like practice.
And now we're, like, in
the Colosseum, and we're like...
- There were
definitely talks happening.
- [laughter]
PROBST:
Dwight,
I have not heard any talk
about what I observed,
which was this sort of
Baka-Vesi versus Coco
or maybe helping each other.
It was talked about at one
of the challenges at the end.
Did that just fall out
once you all got together?
Yeah, you know,
we all have the same color Buff.
We're all representing ourselves
at this point in the game.
There's no more, like, indication
of Vesi, Baka, Coco here.
That was in the past.
Let's move forward
as individuals
and play our own games.
Noelle, what talk is there,
at this stage,
about advantages or idols
that could be in the game?
NOELLE:
Going into Tribal Council,
if you're not thinking
someone has something, then
it's probably you going home.
You have to always be on your
feet about that kind of stuff.
You don't want someone
going home on your alliance
because someone else
played an idol or an advantage.
You have to have plan A,
plan B, plan C
and plan D, just in case.
So, James,
this idea of plan A, plan B,
plan C, plan D,
does that go through
your head all the time?
I mean, you still have
to weigh each relationship
with what they're saying,
and does the actual actions,
uh, back up
what's being said at Tribal?
So advantages are great.
Idols are great.
At the same time, you have
to know when to use them.
You have to know,
if you have an idol,
know if you're in trouble.
To use certain advantages,
you have to have
certain knowledge.
So a lot of people
have played advantages
wrong and to their detriment.
So you can't sit back
and just be worried
about advantages 24/7.
You can drive yourself crazy.
What you can do
is find a group of people
that you build trust with,
that give you a logical plan,
and you kind of stick to it.
PROBST:
Cody, give us a surfing analogy.
You're gonna go
surfing for the day.
Where are we right now?
At this point,
we're trying to decide
if we're gonna go in the water,
or if we're just gonna stay
on the beach with the girls
and the beers
and the umbrellas hanging out.
You know, it's that decision
of, are you gonna jump in
and play this game
and really go for it?
Or maybe just hang out
a little bit longer
and, uh, let it come to you.
So it's a little bit like Jaws.
You know
there's a shark somewhere.
[laughter]
[imitates Jaws theme]
But we haven't seen it yet.
Yeah.
Jesse, how confident are you
that you're
going to be okay tonight?
Are we doing this on a scale
of one to ten again?
That was super funny.
[laughter]
Just generally speaking,
how confident are you
the vote
will go your way tonight?
I am sitting at a nine today.
- PROBST: Karla?
- I'd say nine.
PROBST:
Ryan, how confident are you?
I would say seven, eight.
All right. Cody?
- Eight.
- PROBST: How about you, James?
8.5.
PROBST:
How about you, Dwight?
- Seven.
- PROBST: How about you, Noelle?
- Eight.
- This is crazy, right?
We have a bunch of people who
are all very close to saying,
"Pretty sure I'm good to go,"
and yet one of you is
about to get your torch snuffed.
SAMI:
I'll be the voice of reason.
- I'm terrified.
- [laughter]
I don't know
what's gonna happen,
but at the end of the day
you got to play this game
not with your heart,
not with your mind.
You got to go with your gut.
If your gut's wrong,
your gut's wrong,
but you only get to come
out here and do this one time.
And so, if you act like you
have anything other than that,
you're not gonna play the game
the way that you ever wanted to.
Wow. Well said.
♪ ♪
All right, it is time to vote.
Noelle, you're up.
♪ ♪
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote, James.
Dwight. One vote James,
one vote Dwight.
Ryan.
One vote James,
one vote Dwight, one vote Ryan.
James.
That's two votes James.
Dwight. We're tied again.
Two votes James,
two votes Dwight, one vote Ryan.
Ryan.
That's two votes James,
two votes Dwight,
two votes Ryan.
Ryan.
That's three votes Ryan, two
votes James, two votes Dwight.
Dwight. We're tied again.
Three votes Ryan, three
votes Dwight, two votes James.
Dwight.
That's four votes Dwight,
three votes Ryan,
two votes James.
Dwight.
That's five votes Dwight,
three votes Ryan,
two votes James.
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor 43... Dwight.
- Yeah.
- That's six. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
♪ ♪
Good game, you guys.
- Good game, Dwight.
- DWIGHT: Love you all.
Dwight, the tribe has spoken.
Glad to hear that.
- Time for you to go.
- Thank you, guys.
- Bye, Dwight.
- Have a good one.
Be safe, man.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
JESSE:
This could be the seven
that skip to our Lou
to the end of the game.
That's not
the way the game should go.
We can start an uprising.
- Yeah.
- Sometimes
you have to rock the boat.
People were running around
like Jean-Claude Van Damme.
SAMI:
I'm trying to set myself up
to win this game.
Uh, well, I just
got blindsided pretty hard.
If the votes went the way
I think it is,
that means two people
on Vesi flipped on me.
Don't know who they are,
but that's gonna
be tough to swallow.
It's a lot of emotions
right now,
knowing that I was, like,
literally a day away
from making the jury.
That sucks.
At the same time,
I can't be disappointed
how I played at all.
Like, I was playing this game
hard from the beginning,
and I'm not mad.
I'm just accepting
what just happened.
[roars]