Tribal
could not have gone better
for me, in my...
in my opinion.
This may be dumb.
I wanted the idol flushed.
You are playing this
for yourself.
I'm playing that for myself.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
I wanted Brandon to stay.
Maddy.
That's one. That's all there is.
And Maddy got voted out
by a single vote from Brandon.
As a Survivor fan, congratulations
for being
the first person to nail it.
We had two Shots in the Dark--
myself and Jaime.
I was in survival mode,
and that's why
I played the Shot in the Dark.
But in reality,
I knew I was safe,
and I didn't want
any of the heat on me.
So I played my Shot in the Dark,
really as more
of a play of strategy
so that I didn't have to vote,
which means that
no one knew where my lines were.
I have my extra vote
right there in my bag
if y'all want
to dig through it and find it.
At Tribal, I banked by vote,
and this is my extra vote.
So I'm gonna be able to use this
to my advantage.
This gives me a ton of power--
more power than
anybody else has, at this point,
'cause Brandon used idol,
so it's gone. [chuckles]
So I'm the powerful one now.
And obviously,
only one person here voted.
- Yeah.
- And that was you.
Yeah. That was just, like,
the last
majority consensus I heard.
So it wasn't anything personal.
I thought that that's
where the vote was going.
Tonight's Tribal
was an absolute barn burner.
It went about
as poorly as it could
possibly have gone for me.
So, I was in survival mode,
and that's what
I thought was going on.
There was majority consensus
that Brandon would go home,
but what it looks like
is I'm the only guy left here
that actually voted against him.
It was shocking.
I'm not gonna lie.
I thought...
I genuinely thought that I was
turning that idol in
for no reason.
The question
really is whether I can
repair my relationship
with Brandon.
If I can do that, I think
I'm sitting pretty again.
I just wanted a couple answers,
that's all.
So, no, I feel like I got 'em.
I'm happy
'cause I'm still here,
but I was
very surprised by Kane.
The fact that, you know,
he put the second vote on me
is kind of, you know,
eye-opening.
I get it. This is
the game we all signed up for.
But, I mean, it's cool.
I'm trying to act cool, calm
and collected back at camp.
I'm good.
I don't want to portray
that I'm mad or upset
or anything like that,
when in reality, like, yeah,
I'm... I take that to heart.
I don't trust Kane at all.
I just want, like, a little pup.
And I want it to have, like,
all pink stuff, and, like...
Even if it's a boy dog,
and just be the cutest thing.
Uh...
Why? You have a dog?
What kind of dog is it?
It's a
Maltese-cairn terrier mix.
- Oh, that's very cute.
- Oh, I love Maltese.
Yeah, so like Toto
from Wizard of Oz.
Aw...
And she's your personal dog?
- Whatever.
- So who kept it?
Aw...
Was it mutual?
Um, it was sort of.
She broke up with me.
Oh, that's hard. I'm sorry.
Coming into this game,
I was in
a very vulnerable state.
I recently
got out of a relationship
that meant the world
to me, and...
...I wanted to be able
to put that behind,
but you bring it in to the game.
And then kicking things off
on the journey,
I lost my vote
for the next
two Tribal Councils.
Like, I don't think this game
could have gone
any worse for me.
Even though the Matt stock
is at an all-time low
in this game, I found
an incredible connection
with Frannie.
I really like Frannie.
I really,
really like Frannie.
Wah.
Oh, yeah!
That went right into my hand.
Yes.
It feels more like fishing.
- Now, I'm changing the metaphor,
- Yeah.
but you're a little fishy,
and I've got my big long rod.
I don't usually make a habit
of talking about
my big long rod, but...
She is really cute.
She's got a really funny laugh.
The snorts--
I actually just... it...
you know, makes my heart gush.
I'm so glad that you're here.
Me too.
I would 100%
ask Frannie out,
and I think she likes me, too.
And we trust
each other completely.
Uh...
Which is, like, really bad.
I love Matt.
He's so much fun to have around.
And the fact that
Matt trusts me, and that
I'm the only person
who he's telling about this
is a really good sign.
But I'm worried that
other people on the tribes
might see Matt and I as a pair.
- Do you think?
- I don't know.
Heidi.
Here's the thing...
- It's only been four days. Yeah.
- Stop freaking me out.
The thought of distancing
myself from Matt
is a little upsetting.
That's so hard
'cause I want to keep,
like, talking to you,
but I feel like we should
- try to not talk, the two of us,
the rest of the day.
- Yeah, no, I agree.
Yeah, yeah, I agree.
I will say, I feel like
Matt goes where you go, so...
So, I told him
that he and I should
probably spend less time
together the rest of today.
It's so hard,
because Matt and I
just can't stop talking.
I think we just
gravitate towards each other.
We're just, like,
two big, dorky magnets
that can't be pulled apart.
Oh, me, too.
Me, too. Like Ernest.
Are you serious?
Like, what are they doing?
It's just digging their holes
deeper. This could be
a real liability for Frannie,
being so close to Matt.
Ooh!
- I know.
- Yeah. What else?
Wait, what am I doing?
I'm, like...
Some clean material.
As much as we're
trying to gel as a tribe
and, you know,
bond with each other,
I think there's
some underlying tension
that we haven't
really talked about.
That birdcage is kind of just
in the back of everyone's mind.
We all think there's
an advantage or an idol
or something in there.
I'm not gonna
sugarcoat it anymore.
Let's just talk about the key.
We want to find the key.
Let's go get the key.
I'm bored.
Like, I for real
just want to have fun.
Let's get the key.
You try to be coy, but
I was a little nervous about it,
because, you know, there are
people that you're working with
and then
that means that there are people
that you're not working with.
So a group hunt means
it's a free-for-all.
What happens if it ends up
in the hands of someone
you're not working with?
Okay, let's do it. Let's go.
I'll take the tree.
You guys go somewhere else.
Please, Yam Yam.
Don't try that ...
Oh, my God. That birdcage
is driving me crazy.
What it is, I don't know yet,
but I'm gonna get it.
I need to get this key because
I don't feel like
I click well with them.
I don't.
And so, I didn't just, like,
go on the ground.
I start digging.
And I was climbing.
Honestly, like, that
was just a dream in itself.
Like, I'm on Survivor
climbing a tree.
Like, you know how many times
I've thought about that?
So it was amazing, but as
I'm digging, I feel something.
Oh... Oh, my God.
- You need help?
- There's a snake in the tree.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Wait, we need, we need help.
Yeah, it's not...
After the last Tribal Council,
I'm worried because
I am the only person
who voted against Brandon
that's still in this game.
So we know that
the idol got flushed
and we know that, historically,
that means idols come back in.
So I'm going out there,
I'm doing my rounds,
picking up a little firewood,
but I'm looking for it,
just to see.
You never know in this game.
He's been taking
a lot of walks by himself.
Yeah.
Well, then, I mean, if he's
looking, then I want to look.
- I'm just gonna
be honest about it.
- Yeah.
Since Brandon played the idol,
there's another idol
to be found,
and Kane is definitely looking
for the idol the most.
Ooh!
Matthew!
- Yeah?!
- I got a crab.
Oh!
Let's see.
- Where is it?
- It's in here.
- In there?
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah. It's a big guy.
Incredible.
Good job.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
I'm always doing something.
And when I'm doing something,
I'm also
doing something else. And that
something else is looking
for advantages and idols.
You know "phone, wallet, keys"?
I'm going "bamboo,
palm leaves, idols"
every time I leave the house.
Right now,
the house is a shelter.
Is he just looking
for bamboo maybe?
I let him run himself down,
but I feel like
maybe I shouldn't.
We do not have
to keep up with him.
There's no way in hell
any of us are gonna
be able to, like,
go, go, go, go, go, like that.
- So don't feel, like...
Really, let's take breaks.
- Yeah.
I'm the chief laziness czar.
-"Stop that! Lie down!"
-"Be more lazy."
I don't know the best way
to find an idol,
but I know the worst way,
and that's not looking.
And I am not doing that.
All right, let's go, dude.
Where's, um, Danny?
Oh, I guess palm fronds.
It's the key to that birdcage,
and I'm really excited to
find out what's inside of it.
I can't wait to tell everyone.
Oh, wait. No, I'm not.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
I thought about this moment
in Survivor, for many, many
years, many, many times.
And let me tell
anyone who wants to listen,
it's just as good
as you think it feels.
Okay, I'm gonna go, Carolyn.
- Is it big?
- It's right up there.
Aah! Oh, my God. Okay.
So I went like this,
and I was clearing stuff.
Yeah.
People got
scared off by that snake,
and I just keep telling myself,
like, "Don't give up.
"I can do this.
I got this."
And it reminded me
exactly of the time
where my son
swallowed his tooth.
So I dug through
his poop for three days
until I found that tooth.
But I was persistent.
I made sure that
I was gonna get that tooth.
I said,
like, "I am not letting my son
not have a tooth under
his pillow for the tooth fairy."
And I know that, like,
I'm gonna do anything
to get this key.
I'm getting this key.
Before I came out here,
that's what my son told me.
He's like,
"Mom, don't be too silly,
don't get voted out,
and find something like this."
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm keeping
this to myself.
Like, I'm not telling anybody.
There's no way.
Oh, I just
got to compose myself. Okay.
It was the snake.
The snake got me, like...
Any luck, Carolyn?
No. I'm just, like...
- There wasn't nothing, nothing,
nothing over there? Nothing?
- Snakes.
- Nothing?
I haven't even
looked at the birdcage
in the past two days. I don't
even know if it's still there.
- Yeah.
- I think
the scariest part
- is gonna be opening the cage.
- Yeah, exactly.
I come up on this birdcage,
I'm incredibly nervous.
I'm like,
"Did I pick the right time?"
And yeah, constant fear.
I had that feeling
of looking over my shoulder,
uh, somebody's gonna roll up,
and it would ruin everything. But...
scared money don't make
no money.
This is an old-school hidden
immunity idol
found in a new-school way.
It's great,
and it doesn't end there.
This little cool amulet.
It's a coin.
"You have also found
a silver coin
"that has absolutely no power.
What you do with it
is totally up to you."
Do you want to check
the birdcage real quick?
Yeah. Let's go...
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
- Hmm. Looks the same.
- Looks the same.
Okay.
Yeah.
But for real,
- none of you guys
found anything?
- For real.
I thought that we would
have found something.
I'm surprised that none of us
found it. We looked everywhere.
- Yeah.
Unless someone's
being sneaky, sneaky.
No, for real.
I'm gonna have
to be sneaky with this.
But it's hard.
It's very, very, very
hard for me. And a-again,
I don't-- This is the game
where, like, deception,
and, like...
So I have to be better
at, like, playing Survivor.
All right, water well?
Let's do this thing.
Am I terrified to go
to that cage and...
Yes, I am.
I was questioning myself.
"Should I do it now?
Should I not do it now?
Should I do it?"
Like, I was
battling in my head.
"Don't, don't, don't, don't."
"Do, do, do."
And then I just
started, like, "Do."
I'm so, so scared,
but I'm on a mission.
I'm getting whatever
the heck is in that bag.
I was so panicked
that they were
gonna come back any second.
Finally, I reached
into that cage,
and I grabbed that bag,
and I put it in my pants,
shoved it down and I ran.
I felt like I couldn't breathe
because I was so overwhelmed.
And then I thought...
"Oh, my gosh!"
Oh, my God.
The cage is open.
And I'm the only one
who's been away from them.
And it's gone.
It's a tribe of five,
and I'm the only one who...
No.
I need to get this bag back.
And I ran back,
and I can hear them coming.
I can hear them coming.
I know.
And I, like, am shaking.
And I put that bag back,
I took that lock...
...and I got away.
And now I have an idol.
This is
the hidden immunity idol.
And these are just
some beads of nothing,
and they have no power.
So I don't know
what I'm gonna do with it,
but it makes me happy.
But, like, look,
I mean, like, that is open.
Like, that was not
open like that, right?
It's even not heavy...
It was, yeah.
- You see how, like, the...
- Yeah.
If-if there
was something in there,
it would be weighted down.
Someone's gotten it.
I don't know.
Now I'm getting nervous.
Yeah.
The little pouch
that's in the birdcage
looks like the drawstrings
have been opened.
Did someone get the advantage
and then hang up the bag,
lock the lock, and, you know,
it looks like
nothing's been touched?
I think the key's been gotten.
- I think so, too.
- Mm-hmm.
It's been messed with.
And right then and there,
I'm like,
"This is the time that someone's
gonna be
trying to be deceptive."
But I don't know
if it's one of us.
I know about body language
and deceptive behaviors
from all the books I read about,
like FBI interrogation
and-and knowing, like, how to
figure out if someone's lying
and reading body language.
So I instantly
start analyzing the people.
I don't have it.
Like, I'm going crazy.
Sarah looks concerned
that someone
has something
that she doesn't have.
Yam Yam looks distraught.
He has been
looking for this forever.
You can go look at her bag.
You could do my bag search.
Like, I'm not kidding.
Okay.
And then Helen,
arms crossed,
holding her body posture
a little bit,
and that tells me she's
not telling the truth
about something.
I don't know if she has the key,
but I know she knows
something that I don't.
- Everybody take their stuff out.
- Yeah.
So we all go back
to camp, the four of us, and
we all get our bags
to go through them.
- Mud dress.
- My bra.
- My pants.
- Belt.
- Nothing else. Yeah.
- There's nothing else.
When everybody starts showing
that they have nothing
in their bag, what I'm
looking for is nervousness.
And I saw, like,
a nervousness from Sarah.
- Sand.
- She started breathing
a little hard. She was,
like, touching her chest.
Like, if I had boobs,
I would put the idol
in my boobs, you know?
- I think she has it.
- My biggest
suspect is Jam. Jam.
He was looking the most,
wanted it the most.
He's sneaky.
Carolyn is gonna freak out
when she finds out
that someone has it.
Like, do you remember
it being open like that?
- Oh, my...
- And, like, on...
And look at the bottom.
Like, there's nothing in there.
Oh! I didn't even
know how to react.
And I felt just, like...
- It was meant to not look like
- Yeah.
someone took anything,
like someone tried
to make it look like
there was nothing taken.
But it very obviously
has been taken.
Yes, in an ideal world,
I would have
put the fake thing back
in there, but no, I didn't.
And they...
they knew it was gone.
That's crazy.
I have the idol,
but I'm so scared
that they might think it's me.
So what are people saying?
- Someone has to have it.
- Some... Yes.
In my gut, I say, like, "No,
they don't think I have it."
But then I get paranoid.
Come on in.
- Good morning.
Tika, Soka, getting your first
look at the new Ratu tribe.
Maddy voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
- Yeah!
- Yes!
First things first.
Heidi, I hate to...
You've got the saber
so nicely tucked in there.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race
up and over an obstacle
to a pile of large sandbags.
You're gonna empty the sandbags
until you find a bag
containing a ball.
Once you have the ball,
you'll lift
a heavy ladder, climb it,
then use a rope
to raise a bridge.
Everybody will then
race across the bridge
to the finish...
...where one tribe member
must maneuver that ball
to the top of a snake maze.
The first two tribes
to complete the challenge
win immunity.
That means you won't
be going home tonight.
In addition,
you're playing for reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
Something good.
It will change your life.
Second tribe to finish--
not as big, but it'll still
get the job done.
Third tribe to finish--
otherwise known known
as the losers--
Tribal Council tonight
where somebody will be
the third person voted out
and as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint. Ratu,
your plan to get yours back.
All right, Soka,
you have one extra person.
Gonna sit somebody out.
Who's it gonna be?
I'll do it again.
Claire gonna sit out again.
Is that a volunteer
or is that a tribe decision?
- Both?
- Huh.
Okay, Claire will take a spot
on the sit-out bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute a strategize,
we'll get it on!
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
- Go!
- Go, Soka!
First, you got to
get up and over
and get to your sandbags.
That's the first phase.
Wow. Danny,
that is how you do it.
All right, go, go, go, go.
Come on, Yam Yam!
You're good.
- Tika, you're good.
- Go, go!
Go, Carson!
Gonna be Brandon for Ratu,
- Let's go!
Danny for Soka, Carson for Tika.
You're looking for a colored bag
with a ball in it.
You don't have it,
it's not there.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Danny got it
for Soka.
Untie those knots.
Soka! Soka!
It is Soka,
once again, in the lead.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's throw the ladder up.
- One, two, three.
- Yeah.
Let's go, go, go, go!
Go, Heidi, go.
One person goes up.
It's gonna be Heidi.
Throw that rope down.
Throw that rope hard.
Okay.
- Yes!
- Come on, Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Tika now has their ball,
with Helen on the knot.
Nice, Helen. You got this.
- Come on, Heidi!
- I'm going!
Brace yourself, brace yourself!
Heidi heads across.
Pull that ladder. You're good.
Ratu still looking
for their ball,
with Helen on the knot for Tika.
Go, go, go, go! Go. Go.
One, two, three, go.
Soka, once again,
in a commanding lead
in a challenge.
It's Jaime looking
for that ball.
They've got it.
Ratu, start untying your knots.
Go! One!
- Two, three! Go!
- He got it! He got it!
He got it!
Gonna be Helen going across.
Whoa!
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
You're good, Tika. Let's go!
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
Ratu has their knots undone.
- Go!
- Here comes Tika.
You're good. Slide down.
Soka's through. It's gonna be
Josh on the snake maze.
Down, down, down, down, down!
You got it! You got it! Go!
- Go. Jaime, go!
- It's Jaime across.
- You're good!
- You're good! You're good!
- Here comes Ratu.
Dead last,
a familiar spot for Ratu.
Lauren working the knots
for Ratu.
Let's go, Josh.
It's gonna be Josh
on the last phase
of this challenge.
Go, go, go, go, go!
It's gonna be Sarah for Tika.
Let's go, Sarah!
Bring it home, you got this.
Lauren getting those last knots
undone for Ratu.
- Go! Go! Go!
- There you go.
- It's Matthew through!
- There you go, Matthew.
Don't rush, because
they're gonna mess up,
- and we'll have the lead.
- It's now Matthew in it.
We've got
all three tribes in it.
That's what you want.
This challenge is on.
Josh dropped.
That's gonna happen.
Definitely a learning curve
on this part of the challenge.
Takes a lot of touch.
You got to be right.
- Sarah.
- Tiny movements.
You got this.
Matthew making
fast work of this.
Matthew has almost caught Sarah
very quickly.
- Josh drops again.
- Hey, buddy,
- take a breath, reset.
- You got this.
Matthew really
figuring this out.
Yeah.
You're doing amazing, Sarah.
Sarah doing a nice job.
- Sarah two thirds
of the way through.
- Yeah!
Matthew's at the two-third mark.
Easy, Matthew.
- You got this.
- Ratu would love
a victory.
And a nice save by Matthew.
Josh drops again.
- Oh.
- Sarah with a nice save.
Good save. Good save, Sarah.
But she can't pull it off.
- It's okay.
Sarah loses all her progress.
It is now Matthew
in the lead for Ratu.
Matthew has not dropped yet.
There you go, Matt.
Come on, Matthew.
Matthew inching
closer and closer.
Closer.
He's as close as you can get.
A win for Ratu!
Ratu has it!
Ratu wins immunity!
We are looking for one more.
It's gonna be Tika or Soka.
Slow and steady,
slow and steady.
Sarah a little bit
behind for Tika.
Slow and steady.
- Josh with a nice save.
- You got it. Yeah!
Sarah now hoping
for a mistake by Josh.
You've got this, Sarah.
You're good. You're good.
But Josh back on the move.
Steady hands.
Just keep going. You're fine.
Josh getting very close
to the win for Soka.
- You got this, Sarah.
- And Sarah
- on his tail,
- You're doing super well.
not far behind.
Put it safe
in that pocket, Josh.
Remember to breathe. Josh.
Will Josh drop or can he close
the deal right here for Soka?
- Slow, slow, slow.
- Josh so close.
Nice job, Sarah. You have this.
Two inches away.
- Can he do it?
- Take a deep breath, Josh.
- Yes!
- You got it!
Soka wins immunity,
safe from Tribal Council,
sending Tika to Tribal Council,
where somebody will be the
third person out of Survivor 44.
All right.
Ratu, congratulations.
Sword is yours.
Nobody going home from Ratu.
Josh, nice job.
Nobody going home from Soka.
So, I got to ask, Matthew.
You took to that very fast.
You put yourself in that role.
Where does
that decision come from?
Because this is
a win it or lose it spot.
I asked my tribe to trust in me,
and I went
against the doctor's orders
and took my arm out of my sling
because I knew I could do this.
I built one of these
in my backyard,
and I practiced
on this many, many times.
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
So you built a replica?
Out of plywood, yeah.
I've been preparing
for this for a while.
Well, it paid off. Nice job.
That is dedication.
- In addition,
you've earned back your flint.
- Yes!
- Bring that this way.
- Yeah.
Ratu, Soka, your fishing gear
will be waiting for you
back at camp.
Enjoy the night off.
Nobody going home
from your tribe.
Grab your stuff. Head out.
All right, Tika,
Tribal Council tonight
where somebody will be the third
person voted out of Survivor 44.
And you know what's coming
as a penalty for losing.
Sorry for you.
Take your flint.
Thanks, Sarah.
All right,
grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
Losing today's challenge sucked.
There was just so much like,
"We got this!" I felt so good.
And then it was, like,
crumbling down,
and I'm scared
that I might be a target
because I just haven't felt good
on this tribe.
So I'm having a battle
of whether or not
I want to play this idol.
Pray for everybody.
How are we supposed to beat
a guy who has one of these built
- in his backyard, you know?
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, that's ridiculous.
- That's...
- Yeah.
I mean, like,
there's really no... Yeah.
It feels terrible to lose.
It made sense
'cause Matthew had practiced,
and if you practice
these things,
you could probably do way better
than the average person.
And I kind of relate to that
because to prepare
for Survivor,
I realized that so many
of the puzzles are repeated,
and I can use that to
my advantage, and so, I would
read a design and print them
on my home 3D printer.
And I practiced a ton
of past Survivor puzzles.
And nobody needs
to know that because,
like, that would just
put a target on me.
We have until sundown.
I would estimate, like,
maybe three hours? I'm not sure.
And I'm also studying
to be a rocket scientist.
I did do two work semesters
with NASA, so I have a lot
of problem-solving abilities.
So I'm gonna go try to find...
Like, just right around here,
- I'm gonna try
to find some little sticks.
- Okay.
But I don't want people to know
about rocket science because
I don't want them to think
that I am a little bit
more intelligent than they are.
So out here,
I'm focusing on my social gut.
Do I know where I'm going to go?
Not really.
But part of my gameplay
is to make people feel
like I'm with them.
Cease. Yeah, no, me too.
First, we can match just,
like, who we'd want to keep.
- Right.
- Yam Yam's strength
is really helpful, so...
It's so important,
and that might
keep us more sustained.
Um, Carolyn is... She's, like,
- hard to, like,
keeping her control.
- Yeah.
Carolyn has so much emotion,
and she's so unfiltered
that it's hard to sometimes,
like, work with someone
who's always going to be saying
the truth about something.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Sarah, Carson and I are really
on the same page, so,
I think the plan for tonight,
if I can trust my gut,
and the people that
I've surrounded myself with,
is to vote Carolyn out.
Um... What?
She's out. She's...
We're all on the same page.
- Right? Okay, so...
- Yeah.
I've lost my vote for one
Tribal Council on the journey,
but I don't want anyone
to know I don't have a vote.
So, right now, there are
five people, only four votes.
And I know that I need
to lock in three people with me.
So, ideally,
Helen, Carson and Yam Yam
all vote Carolyn.
We obviously know,
like, we're together,
- so, we just got to, like...
- Yeah.
...because we know...
So, the plan
that everybody's
throwing out there was Carolyn,
and I went with it. I said, "Of
course we're gonna target her."
But Carolyn and I have
a connection because
I really gel with her energy.
Here's my plan. If we don't get
Carson in with us...
Well, then we're screwed.
Carolyn and I--
we're old, crazy people,
but we're here to play.
Who you want to vote off?
- Anyone but me or you,
and I'm serious.
- Me too.
So, my preference would be...
All right,
we're in the same person.
Let's do a letter...
a letter with the hands
and then put the letter up.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
Yeah. H.
That was my H.
I want to get rid of Helen
because she's super intelligent.
She's constantly
working scenarios out.
And if we get rid of Helen,
and Sarah doesn't have Helen,
the only thing Sarah has is us.
We can't... we can't get...
Like, um, I think,
like, we have to stick together.
I want to...
I want to be... Yeah.
- Like, I want to be
a part of your life. Like...
- Yeah. Oh.
Yup. Okay.
So, but we got to be careful.
So...
Here-here... here's...
Here. You...
It's okay.
When Carson got to Carolyn,
she was, like,
all over the place.
No, it's fine. I'll go with...
She's like a mix
of Goofy and Cher.
Oh, we're done.
- Are you kidding me?
- Okay.
What do you mean, am I gonna
change this? To what-- me?
Oh, no. We believe you. Yeah.
I am not.
I swear on everything.
I'm the same. Everything.
Carson is, like,
this smart...
Like, I'm smart, too.
But, like, he's just, like...
He has it good with everybody.
So I'm trying
to think in my head like,
"What is the benefit for you
to go with me and Yam Yam?"
- I...
- I feel like, you're way tight
with them, so I'm like,
-"Why..."
- I have to put on that facade.
But, like,
this is what I'm talking about.
I'm scared that
Carson's lying.
Like, what's in it for him?
It's... it's something
that has crossed my mind.
So immediately, I worried, like,
"Is it gonna be me?"
And then I thought like,
"I have this idol.
I don't want to use it
if I don't have to,
but I don't want to go home."
I'm so scared.
Oh, my God.
Carolyn, you know,
is getting nervous,
- but I just talked with her.
- Mm-hmm.
- Exactly.
- So it's just
really nerve-racking.
I'm really liking playing
both sides, because for me,
I have a lot
of different elements
and layers to who I am.
And so, at one side,
I have the calm, collected side,
and that's more
of Helen and Sarah.
I'm just really excited
that we're working together
in secret.
- Give me a hug.
- Yes.
And I also have
the chaotic, crazy side,
and that's, like,
Yam Yam and Carolyn.
Wouldn't the easy vote
for you be me?
Exactly, but have you ever seen
an easy vote happen
in Survivor?
I'm just like...
That's why I'm so scared.
Helen and Sarah are
voting for Carolyn,
and Carolyn and Yam Yam
want to out Helen.
And so I'm kind of, like,
split. Like, I have one
personality leaning this way
and one personality
leaning the other way.
And so, it's kind of like
having an angel on one side,
a devil on the other,
and they are constantly at war.
Usually the angel wins,
but sometimes
the devil can come out.
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
dip it in the fire
and get flame.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council,
because in this game,
fire represents your life,
and when your fire is gone,
sadly, so are you.
That's gonna be the case
for one of you tonight.
So let's get into it, Yam Yam.
What did you notice happening
when you all got back to camp
after the challenge?
Was it calm
or could you feel some tension?
There was tension, definitely.
As soon as somebody walked
into the camp, and we're like,
"Where were you?"
You know? Like,
- we are wearing today,
like, radars.
- Ugh!
Like...
"There's somebody coming."
"Now somebody's
walking." You know?
Helen, what do you think
is the fear
where people want to say no?
The fear is that
if I'm talking to Sarah
or I'm talking to Carolyn,
I think I know what's going on.
But when they talk
behind my back,
they also think
they know what's going on.
So, what if that's the reality
and I'm just living
in my own delusion?
That would be called
a blindside,
and that would be Survivor.
It would be Survivor, Jeff.
So, Helen, one of
the big decisions you have
to make in the early part
of the game is
"are we going based
on tribe strength...
- Mm-hmm.
-"or am I gonna let my personal
alliance dictate my vote?"
I think that's at the back
of everyone's minds.
Like, when you think about it,
at the end of this Tribal,
we're gonna have
four tribe members.
If we want to make it to
the merge with enough people
to work with,
to actually succeed post-merge,
we need to be strong
and start winning challenges.
I think it's, like,
how you measure strength.
Being with people
that you trust--
I think that matters
so much in this game.
Carson, how do you define
tribe strength?
Yeah, it's, like,
super concerning
because Bruce was
our strongest tribe member.
And so, like,
if I just vote someone out
based off of strategy,
we might not be able
to win challenges.
We also have
to consider alliances,
and, like,
who am I working with?
But, like, it could be just
deception, and you don't know.
And that's what's so complicated
because, like,
you know, you come all
into this game, and, like,
and everyone thinks I'm a
teenager and that I'm, like, 15.
And so, like, for me, I know
- Oh.
- I try my best to figure out
like, and-and have that filter,
but I'm not perfect at it.
Carolyn, while Carson
was talking, you exhaled,
or had this exasperated feeling.
What's going on?
I don't want to cry.
I'm just scared.
I mean, Carolyn is like this
all the time, in a good way.
Even, like, opening
a green papaya
and finding out it's ripe--
like, she gets emotional.
You know,
and this is what makes her cool.
I'm just grateful.
I'm grateful that I'm here.
I'm grateful
for a papaya that's ripe.
So it's just...
it's those little moments
that... that have...
They've just meant so much,
and I've told them that.
You know?
Who's grateful?
So there's a little bit
of past tense in your language.
- So, you wishing, "I have..."
- No, I want to stay.
Like, I'm staying.
And what it comes down to
for me is, like, who is...
who's working with me?
Who's talking
about this with me?
Who's strategizing with me?
So, Yam Yam, is this
ultimately a good thing, that
"We'll lose somebody tonight,
but I think
we'll be a better four"?
Well, if they lose me,
it's their loss, not...
But it's a good thing because
we need to know
where this family stands.
Are we, like,
siblings that get along
or siblings that are not gonna
talk to each other?
Let's see what happens.
All right, it is
time to vote.
Carolyn, you're up.
Ah.
Oh, my God. Why are there
so many pieces up here?
Like, just put one.
Oh, my...
This is like a horror movie
over here,
like a haunted house, and...
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Carolyn.
Helen. One vote Carolyn,
one vote Helen.
Helen. Two votes Helen,
one vote Carolyn.
Third person voted out
of Survivor 44: Helen.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Got me, guys.
Good luck.
Bye, Helen.
Helen, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Thank you.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
I am up against
the darkest evil.
I want to be a hero to people.
Next time on Survivor...
I never intended
to play an honest game.
Those two--
they're a huge liability.
I'm Peter Pan
running through the woods.
I've dreamed of being
on this show for so long,
and to be
the third person voted out
is not how
I wanted this to end.
I feel like I'm second-guessing
every connection that I made,
but, you know, it's a game,
so I respect the move.
Every single person played
their part very, very well.
I had no idea they were
protecting their own game.
So, kudos to them.
They did a great job.