♪ ♪
I'm happy to see everybody.
- Yeah, let me... Yeah.
- Here.
Bring it.
Going into Tribal,
I thought
I was not gonna make it.
Like, I thought,
this is it for me, you know?
There were only
five of us voting,
and it's either Matt or me
because Ratu is all together.
Then Heidi has this advantage
that she can control that vote.
I'm going to take Lauren's vote,
and I want Lauren
to vote for Yam Yam.
YAM YAM: Luckily, her
advantage didn't change the vote,
and Matt went home.
Matt, the tribe has spoken.
And I'm still here.
Thank you. Yeah.
I know.
YAM YAM:
As of right now, I've been
at every Tribal Council
except two of them,
and I've survived all of them.
I guess I'm that cat
with nine lives, you know?
CAROLYN: It would
have been hard either way.
I would have cried. If I were
you, I would have cried.
- FRANNIE: Yeah.
- That's how I felt at Tribal.
- YAM YAM: It was a very emotional Tribal.
- Yeah.
Worst possible outcome happened
at Tribal Council.
Matt, my best friend out here
and my closest ally
in this game, got voted out.
And...
now that he's gone,
I feel like I've been marooned
with nothing all over again.
Oh, I know.
FRANNIE:
I feel like Matt felt like
home to me here.
[crying]:
And to watch him at Tribal,
and see...
how... scared he was,
and how alone he felt
and to watch him go
and to know that
that's now how I'm feeling...
It was so hard.
That's exactly...
I know.
We have to, so...
Yeah.
BRANDON:
We voted Matt out because
we know that him and Frannie
are very close, and
that was something
we wanted to break apart.
We wanted to take another person
away from Soka
so that we could have control
of the numbers
in our-in our own way.
- HEIDI: Here is the thing.
- YAM YAM: Mm-hmm.
- I wasn't gonna steal yours.
- Mm-hmm.
I wasn't gonna steal Matt's.
- So, my only thing was,
how can I not ruffle feathers
- too much with Ratu?
- Yeah.
And it was clear
from everything they said,
they were going for Matty.
Sitting there
at the Tribal Council, I knew
I had my advantage, and I knew
I couldn't change the outcome
of what was happening.
So, I tried
to use it the best way
without making
too many enemies, and
I could use Yam Yam's number.
So I had to really try
to gain some trust with him.
In my head, I was like,
"I'm gonna steal Lauren's
'cause she has two."
- Mm-hmm.
- If their plan is something different,
- she can use her second one.
- A second. A second.
HEIDI: Right now,
there's three Tika, three Soka,
but there's four Ratu
with a lot of currency.
We all know
that Lauren has an extra vote,
and there's a rumor
that Jaime has an idol.
Kane is very strategic
and very smart,
and Brandon
is a physical threat.
So, they are very strong.
I think us, the misfits, -Yeah.
Have to come up with
a plan to survive, -Yeah.
Because they're gonna start
picking us one by one.
- YAM YAM: Yeah.
- HEIDI: So I'm gonna need to pair up
with you, Carolyn, -Mm-hmm.
You know, Carson, -Mm-hmm.
- In some capacity.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Tonight,
I really for sure thought
I was going home,
but now the game is changing,
and the Tika three...
Carolyn, Carson
and I... are in the middle.
Everybody wants our votes.
CARSON: I know.
Yeah.
There's definitely a war
between Soka and Ratu.
Tika members
are the Three Stooges.
Nobody thinks
we're the strategists here.
we're the power players.
- Totally. Me too. Exactly.
- Okay.
- And keep them against each other.
- Mm-hmm.
That's exactly
what we need to do.
At this point, Soka
and Ratu are underestimating
the Tika Three.
They're continuing to battle
against each other, and
that puts Tika
in a very powerful position.
Oh, geez.
Feel like I was definitely
on the outs
when I first got here, but now,
we're in that good
middle position, and
I'm gonna keep trying
to just be underestimated
and looked at like I am
just the turkey of the tribe.
- Figure it out, yeah.
- You know?
KANE: Right now, my
Ratu members are strong,
and seems like
we have a good relationship
with the Tika Three.
So, this game is just
wide open for us now.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Um, yeah.
You know,
my slogan coming out here was,
"Don't get cocky, kid,"
because that's when
bad things happen.
But it's really hard right now.
It is our game to lose.
If it is not a Ratu member
who wins this game,
we messed that up.
Ooh. Those look good. Dang!
Thank you so much, Carolyn.
This is really good.
- Yeah, for real.
- CAROLYN: Yeah, team effort, for real.
- DANNY: Are they dead?
- CAROLYN: Yeah.
They've been boiling
for a while.
CAROLYN:
Those are good. Those are, like,
- bright red, though, right?
- HEIDI: Yeah, they look good.
FRANNIE: Yeah. The lemon is...
CAROLYN: But, like,
you got to have the lemon.
- HEIDI: I agree.
- CAROLYN: You have to.
HEIDI:
You make them even better.
[retching]
Is he okay? Was he throwing up?
CARSON:
This morning, I wake up, and
my stomach is just churning,
and I just have to throw up,
like, in the bushes.
It's, like, the reward
of the peanut butter-jellies
yesterday came with a curse,
and I just get sick.
I feel bad 'cause I'm, like,
I feel like people think...
No, they all know. Everyone
knows this is not like you
to, like, be over here saying
that you're not feeling well.
Don't even...
Everyone loves you,
and they're worried about you.
This isn't like you, so just
chill. You're good, Carson.
CARSON:
Coming out onSurvivor, I knew
there was going to be,
like, terrible days, but
this is definitely a low for me,
[voice breaking]: And I'm just
trying to push through.
JAIME:
Okay, so we got some tree mail.
[all cheering, exclaiming]
Let's see what it says. Okay.
"Today there
is only one necklace..."
Oh.
- FRANNIE: Oh.
- Wow.
It sounds like we are, yeah.
Heidi, how do you feel
about us as a pair?
- I'm... I love it.
- Okay.
- Let's do it. I have no idea what it is.
- Yeah, yeah.
FRANNIE: So we get a tree
mail that says that there's going
to be some sort
of an immunity challenge today.
But before leaving camp,
we have to divide into pairs.
I don't mind.
I just feel horrible
for whoever is paired with me.
CAROLYN: I'll be with
Carson. I'll carry him on my back.
HEIDI: You okay with that?
Yes, abso... I'm with Carson.
FRANNIE: Where things
get tricky is, we don't know
if these pairs
are duos that will
compete together,
or that will compete
against each other.
LAUREN: It's us four right here.
It's us four. We got to pick,
so I really don't care.
I just know I'm gonna be the
weaker link, so...
I am so worried because
my energy is low.
I haven't been eating.
So I know nobody
is going to want
to work with me.
- And that means we're together, Danny.
- DANNY: Yeah.
LAUREN: So I feel great going
into the challenge with Danny.
He may not feel as great going
into the challenge with me.
- All right, you good with that?
- 100%.
- All right, cool.
- Yeah.
- Good.
DANNY: I wind up getting stuck
with Lauren. Yesterday,
I was saying, "Hey, man,
let's-let's vote out Lauren."
You know, that's the beauty of
Survivor, man. You guys are...
You're gunning for each other
one moment, next moment,
you're brothers and sisters
in arms, but
I mean, I'm still saying
let's vote out Lauren.
Come on in.
♪ ♪
Day 15.
Eight people gone
from this game.
You are all still here.
All right, let's get
to today's immunity challenge.
First things first.
Got to take back the necklaces.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity is back
up for grabs.
All right,
this morning in tree mail,
you were instructed
to divide into pairs.
- Kane, how did that go?
- So when I first saw.
"Divide into pairs,"
I had a little bit of, like,
immediate anxiety, like,
I was back in high school,
and it was just gonna be
a scramble for desk buddies.
But I think everyone kind...
We were all in a group.
Everyone just kind of
took a second,
made eyes,
and we split into groups, so...
The-the big variable was Carson
'cause he's not
feeling well today.
- Carson, what's going on with you?
- Well,
I was sleeping,
and then all of a sudden, like,
throughout the night,
I just woke up
and had to go and go in
the bushes and throw up, and,
um, and so I did that
about eight more times.
I don't know
where that came from.
It was one of the worst nights
I've ever had in my life.
And so, this morning, there was
a lot of talk about, like,
"Well, who's gonna be
with Carson?"
Um, and so, it was just
really amazing to see
everyone around me.
They were pretty much all
willing to be a pair with me.
And so, that was a really,
like, heartwarming feeling.
All right,
so let's get into pairs.
Let me see what happened.
[laughing]
LAUREN: I'll scoot down.
PROBST:
So we've got Kane and Brandon,
Frannie and Yam Yam,
Carolyn with Carson,
Danny and Lauren,
and Heidi and Jaime.
All right, let's get
to today's challenge.
Today's challenge
is gonna move quickly.
It's gonna run in three stages.
Players will be eliminated
in each stage.
So, in order
to make the next stage,
you got to make the cut.
Here's how it works.
For the first stage,
you're gonna crawl,
one person at a time,
through a twisted, muddy net.
Then dig up planks,
race back to your mat.
First four pairs
to get back to their mat
and plant their flag
move on to the next round.
The last pair is out. That's it.
No shot at immunity.
For the next stage,
you'll race up a cargo net
and use those planks
to cross a rope bridge.
You got to get both players
and all three planks
to the other side.
Then you slide
down the wall, race to your mat.
The first two pairs
to finish move on
to the final round.
The last two pairs... you're out.
No shot at immunity.
For the final round,
pairs are gone.
It will now be four individuals.
You will use your arms
to brace against two walls
while your feet are perched
on narrow footholds.
It's painful.
When you drop, you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final nine.
Losers... Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the ninth person
voted out
and the second member
of our jury.
All right, let's draw for spots.
Get it on.
Here we go.
Stage one... for immunity.
Four pairs will move on.
The last pair is out.
Survivors ready?
Go! Gonna be Carolyn,
Yam Yam, Kane, Jaime
and Danny.
Danny whipping through it.
- LAUREN: Good job, Danny.
- But now you hit the twist.
Push, push, push.
You got it, girl.
- Breathe.
- BRANDON: Keep going, Kane.
LAUREN: You've got this, Danny.
FRANNIE: You got it, Yam
Yam. You've got it. Stay calm.
- This is tougher than it looks.
- [Carolyn screams]
Oh, my God!
Carolyn, you're doing great.
[yelling]
PROBST: You've got to
get through the twisted net.
Ow!
And it will stay twisted
for the next person.
- Yeah, uh-huh, that's the right way.
- [Carolyn yells]
Carson trying to help. Doesn't
even have a voice to yell.
[Carolyn yells]
- CARSON: Good job, Carolyn.
- [yelling]
HEIDI:
You got to keep rolling, baby.
LAUREN: Keep it up, Danny.
Danny is really fighting it.
Danny is making his way.
Danny's gonna be
first through. Get to the mat.
- You're good. Go, Lauren.
- Let's go, baby. - [Lauren yells]
PROBST: It is Danny
through. Here comes Lauren.
FRANNIE: Good, Yam Yam. Yes.
Yam Yam doing a nice job.
He knew how to get through this.
He twisted his body.
You're good, Frannie. Go.
- [whooping]
- PROBST: Kane is through.
- Brandon's now on.
- [whooping]
PROBST: Jaime's stuck.
It looks so simple.
"I'll just whip through that."
No.
- You got to work.
- You got it, girl.
- PROBST: Carolyn is all knotted up.
- [yelling]
She's been in the same spot.
You got to twist
to get through this.
Oh, my God.
You got it, Carolyn.
Don't worry about it.
[Carolyn yells]
Frannie's through.
- Go. Start digging.
- There you go. You're through.
- You're through. You're through.
- Brandon is through.
- You're good. Start digging.
- Thank you.
- [whooping]
- Yes.
You're looking for planks.
HEIDI: Don't stop. Don't stop.
PROBST:
Jaime's fighting, twisting.
Oh, my God.
- Jaime is finally through.
- HEIDI: Yes, yes.
Go, Heidi.
- It's now Heidi working.
- You got it, Heidi.
DANNY: You got it.
Come on. You're right there.
- Look at that, Lauren. That's how you do it.
- Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go, girl.
Let's go. Let's go.
- You're good. Start digging.
- CAROLYN: Oh, my God.
We've got three pairs
that are looking very good.
We're looking for one more.
[yelling]
PROBST: Carolyn has been in
dead last this entire challenge.
- She cannot figure it out.
- CARSON: Carolyn, um,
I think they were using the rope
and then,
twisting their body with it.
What?
There you go, Heidi, yes.
Heidi is through.
You're good. Start digging.
You got to get your planks back
and plant your flag.
[whooping]
- Kane and Brandon have theirs.
- Thank you.
- Plant that flag. You're good.
- [whooping] - Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about,
baby. Good job.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Brandon and Kane are moving on.
We're looking
for three more pairs.
[Carolyn yells]
- CARSON: You got this.
- [Carolyn screams]
PROBST: Lauren and Danny
make quick work of their planks.
You're good. You're moving on.
Looking for two more.
There it is.
Frannie and Yam Yam
have their planks.
We're looking
for the final pair.
[Carolyn screaming]
Carolyn not giving up,
but she is a long way
from getting out.
FRANNIE:
Carolyn, you never stop.
DANNY: Keep rolling, Carolyn.
Gator roll, gator roll!
- PROBST: That's it, Carolyn. Keep going.
- Ow!
Can she get out before Heidi
and Jaime get their planks?
- That's the question.
- You got it.
- YAM YAM: No. One more.
- HEIDI: Say when. Yes!
Look at that.
That's a Survivor right there.
- YAM YAM: You're amazing.
- You never give up on Survivor.
JAIME: So proud of you.
PROBST: Carson gonna
go for it even though he's sick.
Got it?
PROBST: Heidi and
Jaime have their planks.
- Got it.
- Get back and plant that flag.
There's our fourth pair
moving on. It's gonna be
Danny, Lauren,
Yam Yam, Frannie, Brandon, Kane
- and Heidi, Jaime.
- One at a time.
The last pair... Carolyn
and Carson... will not move on.
No shot at immunity.
PROBST:
All right, we are moving on.
I'm gonna tell you one more time
'cause I know it's day 15.
You run up.
When you get up there,
untie your planks.
You got to get all three planks
and your bodies
to the other side.
If anybody drops or
a plank falls, you start over.
Two pairs will move on
to the final round.
Survivors ready?
Go!
This challenge is back on.
You got to get up that cargo net
as fast as possible.
It's Danny and Lauren,
Kane and Brandon.
Here goes Frannie and Yam Yam.
Heidi and Jaime are up.
Now you're untying your planks.
This is gonna come down
to this right here.
This is where this challenge
is won or lost.
It is Kane and Brandon,
Yam Yam and Frannie,
Danny and Lauren already
on the rope bridge.
Heidi and Jaime are last
to get their planks free.
Now it comes down
to plank management.
HEIDI: That's it... far.
Put it far. Put it far.
PROBST:
How close are your planks?
How far are your steps?
It's Kane and Brandon
in the lead.
Here goes Yam Yam and Frannie.
PROBST: Danny and
Lauren working side by side.
They've got
a different strategy.
They're going sideways.
Kane and Brandon
going straight on.
Here comes Jaime and Heidi.
PROBST: You got to keep moving,
ladies. Let's go!
Day 15... Tribal Council tonight.
Kane and Brandon
looking very good.
Danny and Lauren
Kane and Brandon are across.
Get that last plank.
You're good.
Go down, get to your mat.
Kane and Brandon,
you're moving on.
- Boom!
- Ah! Let's go!
Let's go, dude.
We're looking for one more pair.
Danny and Lauren, you're good.
- Drop. Don't need the planks.
- Go.
PROBST: Danny and Lauren
are moving on. There we go.
Yeah!
PROBST: Our final four will be
Lauren, Danny, Brandon and Kane.
Good job, guys.
Out of this...
Yam Yam and Frannie,
- Heidi and Jaime.
- Good job, baby.
And we'll get it set up
for this final round.
You're no longer pairs.
You're now gonna be individuals.
Who once was your partner
is now your competitor.
It's the adventure of a
lifetime, and it could be yours.
Apply to be on Survivor.
Good luck.
Made it to the final stage.
Now somebody's gonna win it.
Everybody move up
into that first position.
You can use the footholds
to get up there.
You're going
to the highest part.
It's been a fast transition
from stage one
to stage two to stage three.
You're still breathing heavy
from everything you've been
doing, and now, you've got
to take all that energy...
get super focused.
All right, here we go.
This challenge is on.
This is about pain,
absolute pain tolerance.
It is going to hurt.
Every time you move down,
that foothold gets more narrow.
Puts more pressure on your foot.
Then you start relying a
little more on your upper body.
At a certain point, you go numb.
One minute left in this round.
So just start thinking how
you're gonna transition down,
because you're gonna be moving
down that wall,
using your arms to brace you
while your feet find
their new settling point
on that next lower perch.
It's a live transition,
which means
if you slip and you drop,
you're out.
♪ ♪
All right, it's time to move
to the next narrow perch
for your feet.
You can't grab the outside
of the frame,
but use your body
how you need to
and get your feet on there
and get settled again.
Everybody is good.
Great transition.
- Everybody's still alive.
- [whooping]
[whooping]
PROBST: It's already hurting.
Danny, Lauren,
Brandon and Kane
on day 15,
fighting for immunity.
[Frannie laughs]
PROBST: Everybody's
still looking really good.
Whatever you're doing,
whatever you're thinking about,
it's working.
This is not easy just because
it's only stage two.
Stage one was hard.
Stage three is gonna be a lot
more difficult.
All right, everybody, start
- making your move.
- HEIDI: Slow and steady.
PROBST: Down to the third stage
- of this challenge.
- JAIME: Nice and easy.
FRANNIE: You got it.
PROBST:
This is a live transition.
- If you fall, you are out.
- JAIME: Perfect.
- YAM YAM: Good job. Good job.
- HEIDI: Slow and steady.
- FRANNIE: You got it.
- PROBST: Kane trying to get
that foot down.
FRANNIE:
Keep breathing, everybody.
- HEIDI: Great job.
- YAM YAM: Look amazing, everybody.
Everybody's good. Nice job.
- Yes!
- [whooping]
PROBST: Successful
transition to stage three.
FRANNIE:
Y'all got it. Keep breathing.
HEIDI: Stay strong.
[wooden creaking]
PROBST:
Kane can't do it anymore.
- CARSON: Good job, Kane.
- PROBST: You can see the pain.
He just gave out.
Huge effort.
We are down to three.
It is Danny,
- Lauren and Brandon.
- [overlapping chatter]
Kane, when you can,
wobble over to the bench.
Nothing about that feels good.
- CAROLYN: Love your hair like that.
- Good job.
PROBST:
Brandon's former partner is out.
Like so many
endurance challenges,
this will end
when somebody just drops.
It'll probably be sudden.
FRANNIE: Y'all got it.
PROBST: Brandon drops. He can't
- take it anymore.
- Good job, Brandon.
And we are down to two.
We got a showdown,
- and they're side by side.
- FRANNIE: Good job, Brandon.
PROBST: Danny and
Lauren were former partners
that relied on each other
to get to this spot.
And just like in the game,
you now got
to outlast the other.
One of you is gonna wear that
necklace tonight.
Don't lose your focus.
Channel whatever you need to.
Jeff?
Danny.
[passes wind squeakily]
[laughter]
PROBST: That was nice.
Well timed.
[laughing]
So glad I'm not up there.
[laughs]
It is Danny and Lauren
in a three-stage,
single-day challenge.
And it shows in their bodies,
in their faces,
in their expressions.
Covered in mud, exhausted.
But with that necklace, boy,
will you sleep well tonight.
All right, we're gonna make
our move to that final stage.
Before you move,
let me remind you,
it is a live transition.
That foothold is so narrow
that it's barely enough
for your foot
to get any kind of an edge.
- HEIDI: You guys are looking great.
- [whooping]
PROBST: It could be over fast.
You might only need
to be up there ten seconds,
so lock into it.
Your time starts now.
Start making your move.
- YAM YAM: Take your time.
- PROBST: This is it.
You've got to successfully
make the transition.
HEIDI: You got to make it.
PROBST: There goes Lauren.
- There goes Danny.
- CARSON: You got it.
- PROBST: You're both doing great.
- YAM YAM: Good job, good job.
You've both done it.
You're good.
- [cheering, whooping]
- We're into
the final stage
of this challenge.
Now you got to dig.
You've really got to dig.
- This hurts.
- YAM YAM: Don't think about the pain.
There's nowhere for your foot.
That is a sliver of wood.
Keep fighting. Keep fighting.
- YAM YAM: Keep it. You got it.
- PROBST: Whatever it takes.
What are you trying to prove
- to yourself?
- YAM YAM: Keep going.
PROBST: What do you
want your kids to see?
- HEIDI: You're so strong.
- YAM YAM: Yes.
- PROBST: Danny drops.
- [Lauren yelling]
Lauren wins individual immunity.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
- Unbelievable performance.
Once again, Survivorsurprises.
You freaking did it.
HEIDI: That was amazing.
That was freaking awesome.
My kids are gonna be so proud.
My kids at school
and my own kids.
Like, that was freaking awesome.
- Lauren, come over here.
- [whooping]
Wow. Right here.
- Unbelievable performance.
- Unbelievable.
- PROBST: You surprised yourself?
- LAUREN: Yes. That's...
Um, I never thought
I would win any immunity, so,
it's so cool. Like,
this is, like,
a bucket list item,
and it's the coolest thing ever.
- Lauren, you are safe.
- I want Jeff to give me a hug.
I'll give you a hug. Well, both.
Let me put this on.
Now I'll give you a hug.
- All the mud... you can take it off, Jeff.
- I'll take it all.
I love being a part
of these moments.
- Yay!
- Where are you going?
- I want...
- I don't know. I don't know what to do.
I'm like, "Aah!"
- I don't know. I'm excited.
- PROBST: Lauren, guaranteed
a spot in the final nine.
You'll live to see day 16.
You are not going home.
As for the rest of you,
after 15 days, somebody will be
the ninth person
voted out of Survivor44,
become the second member
of our jury.
Grab your stuff, head out. See
you tonight at Tribal Council.
- Congrats. - Thank you.
- YAM YAM: Good job.
DANNY: I probably
would have been gunning
for Lauren if she didn't win,
but she took the whole thing,
beat my ass.
So, I have to change my plans,
and the logical decision is
we need to take someone
from Ratu out.
They're running away
with the game right now.
If somebody doesn't make
a move now,
this game's gonna play you,
and you got to play the game.
- CARSON: Great job, Lauren.
- CAROLYN: Good job, girl.
DANNY: Yeah, the boys are gonna
be proud of you, Lauren.
[indistinct, quiet chatter]
HEIDI: It's like brown spots
around every single one of us.
- BRANDON: I got so many cuts on my body now.
- Oh, man, my...
My body's stinging
from this all getting
in my little cuts that I got.
YAM YAM: We get back to camp
muddy as hell, and everybody's,
like, trying
to do a little small talk, but
everybody's, like,
giving eyes to each other.
Like, "Well,
who are we gonna vote for?"
Nobody's looking at me.
I'm worried again.
Oh, my God. Here we go again.
Another Tribal Council
with no immunity.
BRANDON: Ratu right
now... we have the numbers.
Me, Jaime, Lauren,
Kane and Carson.
We are strong right now,
and we are kind of
dictating the way
this game is being played.
So...
- Yup.
- BRANDON: I like that, yeah.
We decide that we want to put
Frannie, so we're just trying
to check all of our boxes.
- No.
- No, we're not.
Looking right at you.
No, we're not going for you.
Okay.
BRANDON: Carolyn and
Yam Yam are definitely numbers
to help us, and I feel like.
Carolyn is gonna go wherever
Yam Yam goes.
And right, now Yam Yam,
I would hope, feels some sort
of allegiance to us
since we've kept him
in this game.
What are you...
what are you thinking?
I am down with whatever name
you guys tell me, you know?
DANNY: Okay.
Yeah. I'm... I'm cool...
I'm cool with that.
BRANDON:
I feel like everybody's kind of
all-in on Frannie.
She's very intelligent.
She's a very strong
physical player.
So, it would just make sense
to get her out of the game, and
that's just another threat that
we don't have to worry about.
- This is our only shot.
- Yeah.
Like, we have
to go hard or go home.
Yeah, that's what I feel
right now. And now I'm gonna...
So, it has to be the three of us
with the three of Tika.
Ratu's plan is to convince
everyone to vote Frannie.
I thought about it.
I considered it,
but this is the time for me
to try to make my own plan
because we have three Soka
and three Tika.
Six is better than their four.
If we stick together
with numbers,
then we have the power
to vote someone else.
I know you like Brandon, but
- he's probably the most dangerous.
- No, no, no. I'm... No.
- I knew it.
- So...
Okay. Yam Yam is the biggest
person that we need to convince.
We are going to try it because
if we're gonna go out
this game, we're gonna
go out swinging,
but it has to be a blindside.
This is a fake one.
You have to understand this.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
If the three of you,
with Carson,
and the three of us,
there's six of us.
We can take one of them out.
We will be stupid
not doing that now.
Who...?
YAM YAM:
Ratu's trying to stay in power.
Soka is trying to survive.
And Tika... we're in the middle,
so everybody wants our votes.
Do we want to win
or do we want to be goats?
Yam Yam,
what do you think about it?
I need to talk to Carson
before we go to Tribal
because what's gonna
dictate the vote is what we do.
We don't need to make a move
that's gonna ruin our games.
- Okay. Heidi's coming.
- Heidi. Okay. Well, that's fine.
YAM YAM: Come, come.
CARSON: No, come on, Heidi.
We're trying to... I-I think...
You feel solid
about this at all?
CARSON:
It's a pretty smart power play.
Taking out a Ratu
would make sense because then
it would even the playing field.
But I also have to think about,
we don't want to make enemies.
- We're just...
- I'm, like, worried.
We're-we're worried.
We want this to work.
But we just want to make sure
it's going to before we risk...
Mm-hmm.
I hope it helps us
- in some capacity.
- Okay. - Yeah.
Apparently,
Danny's the one with the idol.
- CARSON: Yes.
- I didn't know this before.
- Otherwise, I would have told you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. Right, right, right.
Yeah. Yeah.
To convince me to work with her,
Heidi told me
that Danny has an idol,
but I'm playing everybody,
I'm playing all sides,
I'm playing all options.
So, five of us vote Frannie.
YAM YAM: And I'm thinking
about approaching Ratu
and telling them
that Danny has an idol,
and he's gonna play it
for Frannie.
After this, I'm gonna be
stronger with you guys.
YAM YAM: My game plan
tonight is to get through this vote
with all my alliance, and for us
to have options tomorrow.
DANNY: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It is you right now,
but, no, we're-we're good.
- Okay.
- Okay?
So we're gonna
make a big, big move.
We'll take out Brandon tonight.
Okay? Everybody's...
Everybody's voting...
everybody's gonna be voting you.
Mm-hmm.
- You have it?
- Yeah.
Danny, you're gonna make me cry.
I love this idea
of Danny playing an idol on me,
and I really want to believe
that that will happen.
But this whole
Brandon plan falls apart
if just one person
doesn't believe
that this six is going to work,
then it's completely shot.
Okay. No Carolyn?
- I'm open to it, okay?
- Yeah.
- You wanted to include Yam Yam in the vote?
- No.
Let's keep it small.
Four people.
- Okay.
- That way, it won't leak.
Okay, but I think Yam Yam knows
the plan. Just letting you know.
Yes. Sorry.
Oh. Who-who was it? Heidi?
Yeah, but, like...
But Danny, that means that you
just need to play it tonight.
I'm gonna go...
I'm gonna go talk to Yam Yam.
I'm gonna... I can monitor him.
Like, literally, a security
guard. I'm not joking. Um...
I don't think he'll tell them.
Ugh!
My fear is that Yam Yam
tells Ratu about my plan
to take out Brandon and then
they switch to vote to me.
He's a strategic
and smart player, and
that is the monkey wrench
in this situation.
If I go through with the plan,
I'm playing my idol
for Frannie, or maybe
to be safe,
I use it to protect myself.
If I could also trust
the Tika tribe is voting
with us
and keep the idol in my bag...
There's a lot to take in.
So, at Tribal Council,
I'm definitely gonna
have my ears wide open
because at this point
in the game,
it's purely being adaptable,
and I'm ready to be adaptable.
♪ ♪
All right.
Let's start with where
the game is right now. Kane,
the big, obvious difference
is now you have a jury.
Yeah, with our
handsome jury member.
And it brings another layer
to the game because, I think,
you have
to be playing different,
and you have to be
playing visible so that
people can see
what you're doing.
So I think
there's a lot of people here
who are going to start
skyrocketing their game.
Heidi, what's different
about the games for you?
Ay. The difference is everyone
is vulnerable except Lauren.
And I think before,
it was, like,
six and six or five and six.
So now, the pool is bigger.
So, don't write "Heidi"
on the paper today. Not yet.
That happens at the end.
So I'm just hoping...
I'm just hoping I'm on
- the right side of the vote.
- PROBST: Carolyn,
it's one thing to say "Be on
the right side of the vote."
The question is
what does that really mean?
Is it the vote tonight, or is it
a set-up vote
for the next Tribal?
CAROLYN:
And that's the thing. I mean,
I think of Lauren and Danny,
and they started out as enemies.
And now look at them.
They work together as partners.
So everything yesterday
means nothing today.
Nothing ever is certain.
PROBST: So, Yam Yam,
what is the key to Survivor?
Knowing that it could change,
who you're partnered with could
change, who you need to be in
an alliance with could change?
Well, the key to Survivoris,
know what's going on,
you know, be aware
of what's happening
behind the scenes,
and there's people that we like
that we don't need here.
There's people
that we don't like
that we can keep here, you know?
I like all of these,
I like all of these people, so,
I'm okay
with keeping all of them.
Heidi, from, like, zero to ten,
how much adrenaline
and anxiety was there today?
For me, ten.
From the moment we finished
the immunity challenge,
I was at a ten,
and I'm still at a ten.
Some people may feel more
comfortable than others, but
most of us are probably
at a ten right now.
Jaime, how you feeling
right now?
You always seem positive,
but Heidi said she's at a ten.
- Where are you?
- Yes, I'm at a ten at all times.
I just wear it well, so, that...
I mean, I don't wear it well.
- [laughter]
- Oh!
- YAM YAM: I think you do.
- JAIME: This is my ten face.
It's like you have to be
on your toes at all times, and
that's what's so fun about it.
But it's like if you blink
your eye, something changes.
PROBST: Brandon, is that
because you just don't know
where your relationships
might end?
Like, tonight might be the night
when I find out,
oh, Iwas the one on the bottom?
BRANDON: Yeah. I mean, you
can have a million conversations,
but it's always scary
not knowing, you know,
am I on the right side
or am I on the wrong side?
Am I the target
or is somebody else the target?
Like, am I being told
the right thing
or am I just being lied
straight to my face
so I feel comfortable
with what's going on?
PROBST: So, Lauren,
when a vote is happening,
how do you make sure
that part of that vote
is your decision so that
you're not just a floater?
I think really, for tonight,
I can say that
it may be a majority vote,
you know, but I'm still thinking
about my game
and thinking about it long-term.
PROBST: Danny, a
majority vote is fine so long
as it's the vote you want
- to have happen.
- Yeah. Being in, uh... on the wrong side
of the majority, uh, in a vote
is never a good thing.
There's something to be said,
though, about being on
the wrong side of the majority,
and then making a comeback,
and that's something
that people in the jury
kind of respect, as well.
So when you're out
in this game,
that's just an opportunity.
PROBST: Kane,
regardless how a vote goes,
is there always
an opportunity for somebody
to make that
part of their résumé?
I am always trying to make sure
that I am moving with intention
and that I have an intention
for this vote.
So, maybe that intention
is to make a flashy move.
Maybe that intention is
to build trust
with some of my new friends.
So, for me,
that's what the commodity
of every single vote is.
PROBST:
Frannie, Kane basically said,
you could have
ten different intentions.
Yeah, because we're all,
like, you know, arrows
pointing in slightly
different directions,
and we're gonna intersect
tonight, but tomorrow,
we're spread off.
And so, every Tribal is about
trying to intersect
as many points as you can,
but you have to figure out
what direction
everybody's going in if you want
- to be on the right page.
- Heidi, you're nodding.
HEIDI:
Yes. At this interception point,
some of us will find it,
some of us will not.
But the interception point today
will be key,
and I think
it will speak very loud
about each of our games
at the moment.
PROBST: All right, it is
time to vote. Kane, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
I got something for you, Jeff.
- Gonna play this for Frannie.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
This is a hidden immunity idol.
It's being played for Frannie.
Any votes for Frannie
will not count.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Frannie.
Does not count.
Frannie. Does not count.
Brandon.
Two votes, Brandon.
Ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury:
Brandon.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Oh.
Brandon, the tribe has spoken.
- HEIDI: Good job, Brandon.
- JAIME: Love you, Brandon.
- Good job, Brandon.
- BRANDON: Well played, well played.
[quietly]: Oh, my God.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
- Good night, Jeff.
- PROBST: Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
KANE: As soon as the move was
made, I wasn't heartbroken.
I wasn't betrayed.
I was woken up.
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
DANNY: The shy part
of the game is over.
CARSON: The Three
Stooges are running this game.
- It's crazy.
- CAROLYN: I want to vote out Danny.
I'm sick of him.
YAM YAM: You write my name down,
you're dead.
Clearly, Danny had the idol.
It was a great move.
I can't knock him for it.
And I'm not leaving here
with any regrets.
I left no stone unturned.
I did everything
that I felt that I could
to make myself proceed further
in this game,
and I played as hard as I could
and tried to,
you know, swing as many
relationships as I could.
But in the end,
you know, it'sSurvivor.
Sometimes you get caught.
They were going for the big fish
and tonight they got him.
[roars]