♪ ♪
[Carolyn vocalizing]
[holds high-pitched note]
Oh, my gosh.
I'm gonna
go back home with, like,
so many accents of English.
"What would you like?"
And I said, "A 'beg.'"
"A what?" "A 'beg.'"
"What are you asking for?"
"A 'beg.'"
And it was like they didn't
even know what I was saying.
- It's "bag."
- CAROLYN: Bag.
Huh? That's how I say it.
- "Beg."
- YAM YAM: Bag.
- How do you say it?
- Bag.
- [laughing]
- CAROLYN: Huh?
You say it like a goat.
Like, "Baag."
[laughter]
I say it normal, I thought.
"Beg."
Bag.
JOSH: I'm feeling on
top of the world right now
because, last night,
we didn't go to Tribal Council.
If I would have gone to Tribal,
I definitely thought
I was going home.
This buys me a new opportunity
to move forward
and a new beginning.
But for now
I'm stuck on an island
with Carolyn and Yam Yam,
who are both
very ridiculous and chaotic,
and I am ready
to get off this island.
Are you ready to get rid of me?
Mm-hmm.
[laughs] Don't say that.
Bye, Felicia.
JAIME: Oh, my God!
- [squeals]
- FRANNIE: What?
- Do the honors, Danny.
- Can I get a, uh...?
- [others imitating drumroll]
- Can I have a trumpet?
- [imitates trumpet]
- [laughs]
"The game is about to change.
Drop your Buffs.
- You have ten minutes to collect your things."
- [screams]
"A boat is waiting
to take you to your new home."
[all screaming]
MATT: Yes!
[all howling]
JOSH:
"The game is about to change."
- CAROLYN: [whoops] Oh, my gosh.
- JOSH: "Drop your Buffs."
"You have ten minutes
to collect your things.
A boat is waiting
to take you to your new home."
[all screaming]
- BRANDON: Wow.
- [Lauren exclaims]
BRANDON:
"The game is about to change.
"Drop your Buffs.
Your fellow castaways
will be joining you soon."
They're joining us here.
Freaking drop the Buffs!
[cheering]
I feel so naked.
LAUREN: I know! I know!
I might start sweeping.
I'm just so excited.
- LAUREN: I know.
- [laughter]
BRANDON: We got to clean
up. We got company coming.
CARSON: I am so excited.
Just the idea
that the game is changing up,
and I'm not
just kind of in this calm
peacefulness anymore
kind of excites me.
And I'm like... [gasps]
Chaos is about to ensue,
and I can
kind of capitalize on it.
BRANDON: It doesn't say
anything about being merged.
CARSON:
It doesn't say "the merge."
So we're not at the merge yet,
we're just all on one beach.
'Cause my idol said, "Your idol
doesn't have any power once
everyone's on the same beach."
That's when it stop having
power, so it no longer
has power today.
Knowing that everyone
was gonna be on the beach,
I disclosed
that I do have an idol.
If I have this idol,
and it's pretty much powerless,
what's the point
of me hiding it?
As for other advantages...
I'm just gonna say that...
CARSON: Lauren has openly
admitted to having an extra vote.
In addition to that,
Matthew revealed to me
that Jaime
had found another idol.
- Oh, my God.
- MATTHEW: What is it?
CARSON: So I believe that Jaime
does have an idol
that she's keeping very secret.
Plant lady and plant daddy.
Give it up, give it up...
CARSON: And who knows
if anyone else has found
an idol on Tika or Soka?
[Danny exclaims]
CARSON:
And so it's kind of concerning
'cause there's
a lot of things to navigate,
considering
there are potentially
a lot of idols at play.
Y'all, y'all, there's a boat.
- ♪ ♪
- [all cheering]
[whooping]
LAUREN: Hello!
Welcome!
- Jaime!
- [cheering]
Hi!
JAIME: Excitement on
one to ten is a 20 right now
because I've met
more people than anyone here.
So I'm the most valuable
player... the MVP...
Because I have more information
than literally anyone.
I know what's going on at Ratu.
I know what's going on on Soka.
And if anybody doesn't see that,
then they are blind.
[excited chatter]
I'm so happy to meet you.
MATT: I've had so many.
"Aah!" thoughts today.
- Like, this is a very anxiety-inducing day for me.
- Yeah. It's nerve-racking.
The game is moving forward.
I get to make new friends.
I get to play this game
a little harder.
But I'm nervous
because I have no idea
what's going on
in the other tribes.
I have no idea
who their targets are.
We're not merged yet.
There's a lot of new people
that I have to meet.
I have no idea where
I stand in their plan.
MATT: Cool.
I'm a lot better now.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm so happy to be around people
and not
just Carolyn and Yam Yam.
Okay.
JOSH: Seeing Soka again,
I am ecstatic.
Thank you, Survivorgods.
[chuckles]
- On the first night.
- Mm-hmm.
You-you do?
From Soka? Yes, I do.
I'm trying to figure out
what I'm gonna do
with this lie
that I told Carolyn and Yam Yam,
that I have a-a real
immunity idol from Soka,
when I don't... it's fake.
I told Brandon
that I do have the cage idol,
just in case he was wondering.
And then
I can dissipate that later,
but I don't know
what I'm gonna do with...
About that information yet.
Oh.
You used it already. Oh, okay.
JOSH: I've already told
Jaime that I don't have it,
'cause she was asking.
So I have
a variety of information
and situations going on
that I need to figure out
and align my story correctly.
I'm thinking Josh has something.
JAIME: I think he 100% does.
I straight-up asked him.
I'm like,
"You have an idol or what?"
And he was like,
"Oh, well, I had to use it,
but I made a fake one."
Like, 100%. That's a lie.
He has the idol.
Not that I have any, like,
fact-checking confirmation,
but, like, I know.
FRANNIE:
My head is kind of spinning
in terms of what Josh has
or doesn't have,
or what he's trying to do.
We should put the target on him.
- JAIME: Yes.
- I want it to be Josh.
He's dangerous socially.
The fact that Josh is still here
concerns and alarms me,
because Josh really
survived by the skin of
his teeth when he left Soka.
And Josh may or may not have
a real idol at this point,
and that makes me nervous.
♪ ♪
HEIDI: Uh, what-what...
who else went home?
- So it was...
- FRANNIE: So, what happened with Sarah?
JOSH: And I played an
immunity idol to save myself.
And now I'm here.
Right, Yam Yam?
- HEIDI: And Sarah, too.
- [laughter]
YAM YAM: Josh is
holding his grudge too hard.
Like, every time
we talk about Tribal, like,
"The betrayal."
Dude,
we were on the opposite sides.
There's no betrayal here.
You betray me, I betray you.
What's the freaking problem?
What I'm afraid is
that Josh's perception of me
is gonna affect
other people's perception.
Oh, no, they don't hate you.
I don't hate you.
YAM YAM: I think Josh is
definitely going back to his tribe.
So I'm basically here by myself
'cause Carson left me
five days ago
and Carolyn
left me out of the Sarah vote.
So I don't know if Carolyn
wants to still work with me.
So now I have
so much work to do here.
I have so many
conversations I need to have.
I need to have serious
conversations about game.
Yeah.
I mean, it sounds crazy,
but the plan
legitimately is to get Josh out.
We wanted
to get rid of Josh at Soka,
but Josh swapped tribes,
and we thought, "Oh, he's done."
And then, again,
he has dodged a Tribal Council
and made it to this merge.
So the man
definitely has nine lives.
Yeah. Right.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Of course.
- But...
Uh-huh.
This. Oh, interesting.
Like...
Level one. Yeah.
I see. I see.
JAIME: That's on my list, to grow
a pomegranate tree in Arizona.
They grow really well.
CARSON:
If you grow a pomegranate tree,
- I'm moving to Arizona.
- Yes.
- I will. I swear...
- [laughter]
[distorted, indistinct chatter]
CAROLYN:
It's a weird feeling right now,
'cause it's like,
I want to be in,
but you can't force that.
You can't.
- You know the-the standard, like, bread crumbs?
- BRANDON: Yeah.
DANNY:
She hates that so much. Like...
- Oh, my God.
- [distorted laughter, chatter]
CAROLYN: So many
people, it's overwhelming.
It's day one all over again.
...the whole time. And sweat
was just going in there.
I was like, "Oh, this is gross."
I like sweating.
[tapping]
FRANNIE: Just always?
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
Like, I don't like the initial,
like, "Hello."
I struggle with it.
Being out here,
playing this game
- where you have to, like, lie and betray people.
- JAIME: Yeah.
Like, "Oh, I'm gonna open up
to you and tell you my life."
If I'm not being real,
it just seems, like,
forced and phony.
But I've trusted my gut,
trusted my heart this far.
So I'm like, "I can do it."
I have to just
keep following this.
I can't wait
to talk with Carson.
Like, I trust Yam Yam a hu...
eh, 90... 4%.
But, like, Carson,
it's like 99.9.
I have no idea, but I hope that
we can pick up
exactly where we left off.
♪ ♪
Like, you're the person
I trust 100%.
CARSON: Yeah, me too, 'cause
I really do trust you 100%.
CAROLYN: I feel like
you're already, like, in.
I don't feel like
I'm in anything here.
- So, I...
- I'm just being honest.
Right, but I think with Yam Yam,
you and him
need to, like, reconnect.
Carolyn and Yam Yam and myself
formed the Three Stooges
at Tika.
And now,
even though Yam Yam and Carolyn
don't really have
a great position in this game,
I could still work with them,
and I feel like with those two
we can kind of act like
a force without anyone knowing.
I think us three, let's,
you know, let's stick together.
Like, I trust y'all.
I want to...
- Like, I love y'all.
- Yeah.
CARSON: I think we just
need to play it a little down-low,
because if we're
identified as a threesome...
Three Stooges... [chuckles]
Then people
will try to take us out.
I feel like
the best move for me,
sit back and let the big
power forces go at each other
and then come in,
scoop up
the people at the bottom,
and form my own alliance.
And that excites me,
'cause then I can
take control when I need it.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[both chuckle]
[both laugh]
- Boo.
- [laughs]
[laughs]
Right now
Frannie is still my number one
and she's still
the only person who knows
that I do not have a vote
in the next Tribal Council.
And I plan
on keeping it that way.
[chuckles]
But we got to stop
hanging out so much.
Like, if everyone knows
how close we are,
that's really bad for our game.
Okay.
MATT: That said, it's hard
to leave each other alone.
Like, we have developed
such a relationship
of trust and support.
I think that's
gonna be a delicate line
for us to walk
in the next few days.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Take it in.
You want
to live to see another day?
Here's the obstacle
in front of you.
♪ ♪
So yesterday in tree mail,
you receive a note saying,
"Drop your Buffs."
It marks the end of
the tribe stage of the game,
but you don't have
your new Buffs
because you're not yet in the
individual stage of the game.
You got to earn that. That's
what's gonna happen today.
You're gonna earn
your way into the next stage.
Shall we get
to today's challenge?
- DANNY: Let's do it.
- First things first,
- got to take back the tribal idols.
- [clapping]
- Thank you. Thank you.
- CARSON: Mm-hmm.
PROBST:
Tribal immunity is no more.
But we're not yet in
the individual part of the game,
- so we don't have individual immunity either.
- [groans]
Here's how it's gonna work.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna be
randomly divided
into two teams of six.
On my go, you're gonna
dig up a massive boulder,
push it through
a series of obstacles,
collecting a key along the way.
You'll then work
together to get everybody
to the top of a tall tower,
where you will use that key
to unlock the pieces
to a large tree puzzle.
♪ ♪
The first team to finish
wins immunity.
You'll get your Buff and
you will also get a merge meal,
- your first proper food in 13 days.
- Oh, man.
PROBST: You'll be safe
tonight at Tribal Council.
You'll still vote,
but you can't be voted for.
- That's nice.
- The losing six,
no Buff, no food, no immunity.
One of the six losers
will be the seventh person
voted out of Survivor 44.
- All right. Make sense?
- Yes, sir.
All right,
we're gonna draw for teams.
- YAM YAM: Oh, my God.
- We'll get started.
- CAROLYN: Oh, my God.
- Okay, here we go.
Take one. Don't look.
Let me share in the surprise.
Danny, this
really is a turning point.
The people you end up
with right here will have a hand
in whether or not
you have immunity and live
to see another day or whether
you go to Tribal Council.
This game is certainly
a lot of skill, but, uh,
I don't think anybody would say
it doesn't have some luck to it.
All right.
Moment of truth.
Everybody put your palms out.
[exhales]
And reveal.
If you are orange,
head to orange.
If you're purple,
head to purple.
Let's see what we have.
Looks like
a pretty even division.
YAM YAM: Yes, we got this, guys.
All right, for purple,
it's gonna be Matt,
Frannie, Carson, Carolyn,
Jaime, Brandon.
All right. On orange, we have
Heidi, Danny, Lauren, Yam Yam,
Josh and Kane.
I'm gonna
give you a minute to strategize.
- We'll get started. Here we go.
- [whooping, clapping]
Here we go.
For immunity,
for a Buff, for a merge meal.
Here we go. Survivors ready?
Go!
First thing you got to do
is dig up a very heavy boulder.
JAIME: You got this, guys...
PROBST:
Everybody wants to make it
- to see another day.
- [grunting]
People are hungry.
You want that certainty.
You want to earn that Buff
right now.
- [indistinct chatter]
- DANNY: Everybody.
Everybody. Everybody...
Here goes orange.
They're gonna go for it.
Do they have enough?
GROUP: One, two, three.
PROBST: That ball is
moving, and it's out of the hole.
It's orange in the early lead.
HEIDI: Yes.
Now you've got another obstacle.
Here comes purple.
Purple's now out of the hole.
LAUREN: One, two, three, go.
PROBST:
They're gonna run into orange.
Up and over.
Now you got to work together
again to get that heavy ball
- up and over this obstacle.
- [grunting]
Everybody working.
That ball is heavy.
[Carolyn groans]
Purple trying again.
Everybody pushing.
[Carolyn cries out]
Purple starting
to lose that ball.
[grunting]
Can they get
control of it again?
They do. Is it enough? It is.
It's now purple in the lead.
- Orange now working to stay in it.
- [straining]
There goes their ball.
It's up and over.
Who's gonna get
to the center section first?
It's gonna be purple.
Go, go.
- PROBST: Orange now has to wait.
- Ow!
PROBST:
Orange slamming into purple.
- Carolyn gets taken out.
- One, two, three.
- [Carolyn screams]
- YAM YAM: Get ready.
PROBST: Purple in the lead.
Orange right behind.
YAM YAM: They have momentum.
PROBST: Here comes orange.
And that ball's
gonna run into somebody.
Carolyn again
in the line of fire.
Here goes purple.
- Once again, you got to grunt that over.
- [grunting]
They're going off.
They're going to the right.
Purple is up and over.
JOSH: Get it up. [Grunts]
PROBST: Orange struggling.
Somebody's got to go up now
and untie that key.
Go around, someone go around.
Orange is over now.
- There goes their ball.
- HEIDI: Go, Danny.
PROBST: Frannie
untying that key for purple.
Who's going up for orange?
It's gonna be Danny.
Frannie has it.
- JAIME: Everyone on the mat.
- PROBST: You got to get down off that ball.
That's a big jump. You're good.
Now Jaime
untying knots for purple.
Danny retrieving
the key for orange.
Danny has the key for orange.
He's down.
Now it's Josh on the knots.
You got to whip through it.
Tear up those knots.
You're good.
Start up the wall.
- Frannie. Look at that.
- JAIME: Nice, Frannie. Damn.
PROBST:
Attacked the wall with no help.
- Here goes Matt.
- [grunts]
PROBST: He's doing the same
thing. Carolyn gonna give it a go.
Three for three. Yes!
Here comes orange.
Danny going straight up.
- He's got it.
- MATT: You got it, Carolyn.
- You got it, Carolyn.
- Yes...
PROBST: Everybody
full-out on this right now.
Here comes Heidi.
Here comes Yam Yam.
He slides down.
Lauren gonna give it a go.
- DANNY: Go, go, go. Grab that.
- She's getting a boost from Kane.
FRANNIE: Yes, Jaime, yes.
PROBST: Jaime tries.
Gonna have to try again.
This is full tilt boogie
on Survivor 44.
YAM YAM:
I got it, I got it, I got it.
PROBST: Yam Yam. He's got it.
Jaime slides down again.
- Jaime struggling.
- LAUREN: Come on, Yam Yam.
- It is now orange in the lead.
- Your leg. Your leg.
- PROBST: You got to get everybody up and over.
- KANE: Come on, buddy.
- Here comes Kane.
- KANE: Yes.
With an assistant
from Danny and Josh.
It is now purple.
Trying to get Jaime up.
She has struggled.
Carolyn giving her a hand.
Once everybody's over,
you can move on to the puzzle.
You're good, orange. Go!
- Go, go, go, guys.
- PROBST: Orange now in the lead.
- FRANNIE: I got you. I got you. You're so strong, Jaime.
- PROBST: Jaime holding on.
- Stay holding on, Jaime.
- Keep holding, keep holding.
KANE: Let's go, girls.
- You guys got this.
- Look at the pieces.
- Help, help, help.
- There you go.
- You got it. You got it.
- You got it. Come on.
Jaime, after a lot of effort,
is up.
Here comes Carson.
CAROLYN: Yes! Carson's up.
- Yes!
- PROBST: Brandon's waiting. Brandon helped
with everybody else.
Now Brandon's got to get up.
Yeah.
- He makes it look easy.
- Yeah! - Yeah, Brandon! Yes!
- Yes! Yeah!
- You're good, purple. Go!
PROBST: It's gonna be
Lauren and Heidi for orange,
Matt and Carson for purple.
Yes, that's it.
FRANNIE: There you go, Carson.
PROBST: Pressure position
- for Matt, Carson, Lauren and Heidi.
- JOSH: Come on, guys.
- You got this.
- FRANNIE: Yes, Carson! Yes!
Carson off
to a fast start for purple.
- JOSH: Keep going. You're doing great.
- You got it, ladies.
PROBST: You want to get to
day 14, it's happening right now.
You want that Buff,
you want that food,
- you want that security...
- BRANDON: Let's go, Carson.
- ...tonight at Tribal Council.
- We got this.
PROBST: Without it, somebody's
dream is coming to an end
- in just a few hours.
- Let's go, Carson.
- Yes!
- PROBST: Carson with another piece.
Carson is whipping
through this challenge.
Think. Come on.
PROBST: Orange struggling,
purple thriving.
You want to make the individual
part of the game. As of right
now, you don't have a Buff.
You're in limbo land right now.
- Another piece by Carson.
- Yes!
PROBST: Wow.
This looks like one that
orange cannot come back from.
It is a runaway victory
for purple in the making.
Carson with another piece.
Down to two pieces left
for purple.
An absolute blowout
with another piece.
[indistinct chatter]
BRANDON: Let's go, Carson.
PROBST: Carson
with the last piece for purple.
- Yes. Yes. Yes!
- There it is.
Purple wins immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
All will make the next stage
in this game.
What a challenge.
You were neck-and-neck
until the end.
And it was over.
Good job.
Purple, a lot
of emotion down here.
What's going on, Jaime?
There's a lot of tears.
I just didn't want
to let my team down,
especially with the wall.
I'm so grateful
that they were there to catch me
when I fell and to help me up
all the way. [Crying]
Carson, I'll give these to you.
You won that.
- Yeah. Yeah...
- Take those Buffs, put them on.
You have earned your way into
the next stage of this game.
Nice job, everybody safe,
food coming for you.
For the other six,
one of you will be
the seventh person voted out.
Grab your stuff, head out. See
you tonight at Tribal Council.
CARSON:
I am just, like, beyond ecstatic
because
all my hard work paid off.
I have a 3D print
of this puzzle in my house,
and put it together
probably a thousand times.
I think it's a lesson that
you should always be prepared.
And now I've made the merge.
It's definitely one
of the best days of my life.
If you want this, you got
to apply to be on Survivor.
I wonder what they're eating.
YAM YAM: So I come back
to the camp with the six losers,
me being one of them.
First thing I think is like,
"Oh, my God, I'm in trouble."
And being one
of only six targets,
I have no meal,
no Buff, no hope.
What am I gonna do?
What's your plan then, Yam?
I have no idea 'cause
it's one of them, I think.
- So, who are you thinking?
- Josh. It is what it is.
It's always been me against him.
Josh hasn't been talking to me
since we got to this beach.
Who else am I gonna say?
It's obvious we don't get along.
I'm gonna do whatever they...
whatever they come back and say.
- Yeah.
- I mean, if they come back and say, "Josh,"
I'm in, so... I mean, I would...
If I was you,
I would be less worried
about talking to me and Kane.
YAM YAM: Danny did not
react too well to the idea.
He wanted to wait
for the six winners.
I just opened my mouth
when I shouldn't have.
I should have waited.
And here I go with
my biggest Survivormistake
to date... saying a name.
I made a mistake.
I swallow my words.
Do you guys have a name?
- I don't have a name.
- Me neither.
- Yam Yam.
- I just have a personal thing, you know?
'Cause he was
against your number?
Yeah.
I'm down. He's not a number
for me, so, yeah.
He's not a number for anybody.
- All right.
- Yeah.
JOSH: Right now,
I don't have an idol
so I want to get the target
on Yam Yam
because Yam Yam and I don't have
a great history,
I don't trust him.
You know, he voted for me, so,
I want to get him out
immediately.
I just have a personal vendetta
against him, so, that's why
I'm just like,
"Ugh! I can't trust him again."
- Hey, I'm down.
- Me too.
We have to survive today.
- You and I have to survive today.
- I know.
I've heard that he does.
- Me too.
- Yeah.
- Wh-Which makes me wonder.
HEIDI: Right now,
the vote may be Yam Yam, but
in all honesty, for my game,
I think Josh going home is...
is the right thing.
He survived Soka,
he survived Tika,
even though he was going to be
the next voted out.
But if he has an idol,
there may be a plan B, which
could be Yam Yam, or maybe
it could change by tonight.
[all whooping]
- My God.
- [screaming] - Here we go.
We made it to the merge feast!
- ALL: Cheers!
- [whooping] - Congratulations.
The stakes were really high
for the challenge.
We were playing for immunity,
and we were getting
the merge feast.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, let's freaking eat.
- Let's go!
- Yeah.
JAIME: And we did it.
We hadn't eaten in 13 days.
If you count worms
and some papaya,
then great, but this was
a true full-blown meal.
- Wine?
- CAROLYN: Wine!
[laughing]: Let's go, let's go.
JAIME: The wand has been busy.
Win the challenge.
Bling! Get your Buff back.
Bling! Win immunity?
Ring, ring, ring! [Laughs]
It's all happening.
So who do you guys view...
...as the biggest threat out
of those six that are up there?
MATT: I think Josh
is a pretty big threat
- for sure, yeah.
- FRANNIE: He is a very
- adept social player.
- MATT: Yeah.
If he has an idol,
he's playing it tonight.
So there has to be a vote
on someone else.
BRANDON: A lot of
people want to vote for Josh.
The only issue is
he told me that he has an idol.
I mean, he's told other people
that he doesn't have an idol,
so in the case
that he does have an idol,
we need to have a plan B.
- So who would be plan B then?
- [rolling thunder]
Does anyone feel close to Kane?
I wasclose with him,
but I just...
You know how you can just tell
when somebody looks at you?
'Cause the way
he looks at me sometimes,
I'm like, "I just know that..."
- Something else is going on there.
- I'm so serious, though.
Kane voted for me
at the first Tribal,
and he's tried to,
you know, apologize
to me and stuff like that.
But I forgive,
but I don't forget, and I know
that he's somebody who is gonna
come for me again.
It's just a matter of when.
We also need to be careful
about who we tell.
'Cause we don't want Josh
to play his idol,
- you know?
- MATT: Right.
- He doesn't have one. He does not have one.
- Yeah.
CAROLYN: He showed me
the one he got from the journey.
He used that already.
Then he tried to say
that he had another idol,
so he whipped it out.
And then Yam Yam goes,
"You took that
from tree mail this morning."
- Yeah.
- CAROLYN: Now, knowing that information, does anybody
here think
he actually has an idol?
No.
FRANNIE:
So I think we have to plan
- just in case as if he does.
- Yeah. Right.
CAROLYN:
The people at the merge feast
are all worried about an idol,
and I know
Josh does not have an idol.
I tell them the story
of the fake idol.
I tell them how he stole it
from tree mail,
and they still
wouldn't believe me.
Maybe Josh leaves fake,
takes real,
but leaves the paper
that says "This is a real
hidden immunity idol."
What the ...?!
They still are questioning it.
I'm done.
You guys, I cannot believe
we're here right now.
[laughs]
- [whooping] - [rolling thunder]
- FRANNIE: This is the most.
- Survivorthing you can do.
- CARSON: Yeah.
♪ ♪
- DANNY: How was it?
- YAM YAM: Hey. - Good.
DANNY: What did you guys have?
- It was a charcuterie board.
- DANNY: Oh, my God.
- Ah.
- [indistinct chatter]
JAIME: All right.
JAIME: At the merge meal, we...
all came up with the vote
tonight being Josh.
So,
it sounds like
we have an easy Tribal Council.
However,
that's not always the case,
Knowing the game of Survivor.
Tell us, did any names come up,
any of our names?
- Is everyone... gone?
- Yes.
JAIME: So right now, we
are pretty unanimous on.
- Josh being the biggest threat.
- Okay.
But the only thing is, I don't
know if any of you guys know
if he has an idol.
Because Josh might have an idol,
people threw Kane's name
as a plan B so, we have a couple
of votes going on Kane.
But hopefully,
our number-one plan works.
...while we were eating.
Okay.
JOSH:
My first thought was, "Okay",
Yam Yam's the vote,"
but Frannie came to me
and said, "It seems that Kane
was the primary vote
that they were going for."
And I said, "Fine, I'm fine
with that. That's great."
So this puts in my mind,
then, I need
to squash everything
with Yam Yam
and make this work.
Instead of everyone
separating you and me.
Ah.
JOSH: It makes sense for us
both to put Kane's name down
because we know each other,
we don't really know Kane.
And I think I can save
my personal vendetta
against Yam Yam for another day.
I just want to look into
your face and... We're good.
I thought
you were gonna kiss me.
I was like,
"Not here. I'm married."
Can we do
the double-crossing hand?
Girl.
YAM YAM: Josh, the person
I'm trying to take out, he said,
Kane as a vote,
which is a great idea.
You know, but I like Kane.
I don't want
to write Kane's name down.
I want to write Josh's name down
and look at him and say,
"Bye, baby." You know?
I want that gratification.
Are you gonna play your idol?
I probably have to. I mean, yes.
Give it to me.
Why would I give... Girl...
- 'Cause we're making friends.
- Girl, no.
YAM YAM:
But it's better Kane than me.
So, do I have any hope
of working with Josh?
I'm not gonna rule it out,
but it's gonna
be my last option.
Yeah.
BRANDON: Part of me hopes
that Josh does go home,
but then, part of me hopes
that he doesn't, and then,
Kane goes home 'cause I really
don't trust Kane.
- He's played...
- He freaks out anyway.
BRANDON: But what could go wrong
with this plan is
that Kane somehow finds out
that he's a name.
That's the scary part.
You know, we all
seem so on the same page,
but it only takes one person
to go tell the wrong person
some information,
and everything could change.
How are you feeling?
Well, like, a little bit
nervous because my...
Like, my ass is
technically on the line.
But, like, did you hear anything
at the picnic or anything?
Soka was pitching you.
But everyone ended up
going to Josh.
I'm just worried Josh is, like,
gonna play an idol.
Then I don't know
what will happen.
I disclosed Kane's name
being brought up because
I legitimately feel like
I connect with Kane.
On Ratu, Kane and I bonded
because he's a nerd
and I'm a nerd, and
I kind of did want
to work with him.
Okay.
My name is swirling.
That's a concerning thing.
I don't want my name out there
just so Josh doesn't play
his idol.
Yam Yam seems like a perfectly
fine name to get out there.
I don't understand why
we had to mix my name into it.
I'm going for Yam.
So I'm trying to get people
to vote Yam Yam instead of Josh
because if Josh plays an idol,
whoever he votes for goes,
and I certainly don't want it
to be me.
But Josh wanted Yam Yam.
Yeah.
KANE: Yam Yam is
a more chaotic player,
so let's just get rid
of Yam Yam so that
I'm still safe because I don't
know who all is gunning for me.
I don't know these people.
So thank God I talked to Carson.
Yeah, that was a bad move,
Carson.
- Why...?
- I did... He-he...
- I know he is su... I think...
- First,
he asked me. He's like,
"Did my name come to mind?"
- I'm so sorry.
- This is gonna shake things up a lot.
So, I think Josh has
a real idol, which is scary.
KANE:
Will you vote for Yam tonight?
Yeah, Yam Yam goes home.
- Yeah, I can do that. I'll do that for sure.
- Yeah.
MATT: Kane wants
to switch the vote to Yam Yam,
and as of this moment,
I am interested
in having a very large majority
because I do not have a vote,
and I think that Yam Yam
is a pretty easy vote
for most of the people
still in this game.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I think so, too.
MATT: Yam Yam doesn't
have super strong relationships
with almost anyone
in this game right now.
MATT: But even back in Soka,
we were trying to get rid of Josh,
because nobody trusted him.
And if he escapes
at tonight's Tribal Council,
he is like Superman, you know,
bullets bouncing off his chest.
If Josh has an idol,
he's playing it tonight.
It's all a gamble.
You know, you have to make
these calculated risks.
- I don't know what is going on here.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, like, my eyes are gonna
jump out of my... face.
[Lauren laughs]
MATT: There are so
many variables in this game.
Everyone on the same beach
is honestly overwhelming.
Yam Yam's nervous,
Kane's nervous.
I don't know
what's about to happen.
I'm getting confused.
I-I have no...
Legit, things have changed.
I... No idea.
MATT: There's so many people,
there's so many personalities,
there's so many different bonds.
The matrix of relationships is
exponentially more complex
in a group of 12.
So, my mind is spinning.
So far, we have been playing
Survivor.
Now we're playingSurvivor
with a capital S.
♪ ♪
All right.
Carson, before we get into
the nitty-gritty
of tonight's Tribal,
what's the biggest difference
having so many people living
together? Even looking tonight,
we haven't had a Tribal
with everybody here until now.
Yeah. I feel like
on your individual tribes,
you're able to kind of
keep track of what's going on.
But when we're all on one beach,
it's chaotic.
You can't keep track
of what anyone's saying.
So you almost have to rely
on the people you trust more
because you don't know
what conversations they've had
and what they could be
saying about you.
PROBST: Kane, how
did you approach today?
Because there's so many
different things happening.
You have
everybody living together,
but you also have only half
of the people
that are in trouble tonight
- and could be voted out.
- KANE: Carson put it right.
We need to operate from a place
of belief and trust.
So I met some of these folks
one day ago,
so I don't really know
what they're all about.
And I met some
of these people 13 days ago,
and I still don't really know
what they're all about.
So, uh, I think that it's
really about the information
that comes back to me,
whether it's true,
whether it's false, if it's
from the people that I trust,
that is my truth tonight.
PROBST: Yam Yam, how do you
feel given that Tika got so small...
You, Josh, and Carolyn...
So you don't have a lot
of numbers coming into this?
YAM YAM: We're coming
into this tribe at a disadvantage,
and me and my big mouth
might be an even easier target.
- So...
- PROBST: Is that real?
Do you feel like you talk
too much or say the wrong thing?
It's a thing that happens
in my normal life, you know?
I just can't hold it in.
I can see the faces when I speak
more than I have to speak,
but I just can't stop. You know,
I mean, it keeps coming out.
Now I can't stop, either.
You keep looking at me.
I think you want more.
You want more? I don't know.
[laughter]
PROBST: Josh, you're
a part of this Tika three.
Yeah, so, I come
from a little bit of a unique
kind of background because
I did have a tribe before Soka
that I started
establishing relationships
and conversations with
in the beginning.
And then, when we came back
together, that allowed me
the opportunity to reconnect,
so for me, it was a benefit.
Brandon, how much talk was there
amongst the group
about who might have idols?
Speculation,
stories heard on journeys?
Yes, there was absolutely a lot
of talk about idols.
You know, who might have them,
who might not have them, are...
Is it a fake idol?
Is it a real idol?
Like, there was a lot
of talk about idols today.
PROBST: So, Carolyn,
what do you do when
you're cross-checking
all of that in your head
- to keep it straight?
- There has been so much
information going around,
the fear of idols,
all of this speculation
about fake idols,
and the cage, and we just...
Getting together,
especially at the feast,
and hearing
so many different stories,
it's so much information.
I'm used to talking
to two other people.
This is insanity.
PROBST: So, Heidi, is the
concern always that I'm being
told to vote this way,
but what might be happening is
I'm the only one
that's gonna vote that way,
and I'm not in on the vote?
HEIDI: Yeah, it's very scary.
It's like I'm driving the car.
I pick one person,
they tell me a story A
and plan A.
I drop them, I pick up
person B. They tell me story B
and plan B. And then it's like,
"Okay, A or B?"
I pick up C,
and they-they have plan C.
So it was
all over the place today.
Yam Yam, when you're watching
Survivorat home,
- you have all the information.
- Yeah.
But when
you're sitting here tonight,
and you don't have
all the information,
it really is
a terrifying thought.
Every player is worried
at Tribal because they don't
- have all the information.
- YAM YAM: There hasn't been
a Tribal Council I haven't
been worried, like, for real.
I'm really scared right now,
and I think
the six of us
are feeling the same thing.
Like, none of us are sure.
Can we go back to the beach
and not do this tonight?
- You know what I'm saying?
- [laughter]
And just, like, keep this and
we vote two people next Tribal?
Like, I will not eat for two
weeks if you let that happen.
[laughter]
Matt, it is a rare opportunity
to try to utilize
a little leverage
and get just a little bit
of a foothold
ahead of these other six
who don't have
the same leverage.
MATT: But at the same
time, it's overwhelming.
I-I think we all feel that
the game has turned a corner.
You know, like, in our tribes,
we're kind of going down
the bunny slopes,
and then, we've turned a corner,
and suddenly,
it's double black diamond,
and we're flying down.
And then, a confetti cannon
goes... [whooshing]
And there's a picture
that you have to put together
with all the little pieces
as you're going down the hill.
And then, you have to vote
based on this picture.
That's kind of what it feels
like for me tonight, Jeff.
I'm, like,
hanging on for dear life.
I have made some conversations,
some connections, but, like,
genuinely, I don't know.
All right, it is time to vote.
Jaime, you're up.
[sighs heavily]
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote...
Yam Yam.
Josh.
Kane.
Yam Yam. Two votes, Yam Yam.
Josh. We're tied.
Two votes Josh,
two votes Yam Yam,
one vote Kane.
♪ ♪
Yam Yam. Three votes, Yam Yam.
Josh.
We're tied again.
Three votes Josh,
three votes Yam Yam,
one vote Kane.
Josh. That's four votes Josh,
three votes Yam Yam.
Josh. Five votes, Josh.
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor44...
Josh. That's six, that's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Josh, the tribe has spoken.
- Time for you to go.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye. - Hey, bro.
- Bye, Josh. Love you.
- Josh.
- FRANNIE: Bye, Josh.
♪ ♪
- Congratulations. You have made the merge.
- Yay!
- FRANNIE: It's official.
- PROBST: Put on your Buffs.
[screaming, cheering]
YAM YAM: Oh, my God!
- Yes!
- PROBST: All right, grab your torches.
- Head back to camp. The game continues.
- HEIDI: Thank you.
- Good night. - Jeff.
- Stay out of trouble.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
KANE: This is like
I'm inDungeons & Dragons.
There's magical items in play.
Ha, ha!
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
MATT: I can't describe
how important she is.
LAUREN:
That duo cannot go any further.
There's a twist.
Yes!
I love it.
You will have no say
- in who goes home.
- [Yam Yam groans]
I'm devastated. I'm sad. This is
something I really wanted.
I wanted to make it
to the merge.
I was one vote away
from making the jury
and I fell short,
so I'm bummed out.
It sucks because the people
I thought I could trust,
I couldn't, really.
So, I guess they thought
I was a threat.
But I did everything I could
in my power.
[roars]