♪ ♪
But I wouldn't want to be left,
like, hanging, you know?
Well, from my perspective,
I didn't know where you were at
anymore, and I felt like
- you and her would strategize together.
- Gosh, I just, like...
- and then just tell me the plan.
- Mm-hmm.
Just, like,
put yourself in my shoes.
CAROLYN: I never felt
comfortable with her here.
No, I know you didn't,
and you wanted her out
since day one.
Tribal was crazy.
Like, oh, my God.
Like, it did not go
as I expected at all.
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor44...
Sarah.
Need to bring me your torch.
YAM YAM:
I was so surprised it happened.
Like, if you saw my jaw
dropping to the floor,
it looked likeRoger Rabbit
scene where the coyote
drops his jaw to the table.
Oh, my God.
I'm happy I survived the vote,
but I'm not happy
that I didn't know
how it was gonna go, you know?
Does that feel good in the game?
YAM YAM:
I understand. I understand.
CAROLYN: What am I gonna do...
Keep, like,
being shushed and, like,
be the third turd of, like...
- For what? Yeah, I was.
- You were never the third.
YAM YAM: The most dangerous
player right now is Carolyn.
She played everybody here.
I assumed, like,
we were playing together,
but she left me behind.
It sucks. Like, this sucks.
It-it sucks, too.
It doesn't have to suck.
What? I don't even...
I can't even...
I really can't process that.
JOSH:
Tribal Council was a whirlwind.
Yam Yam tried
to vote me out, so,
I'm glad I trusted my intuition
and my gut
and used my idol
and trusted Carolyn.
I swear.
- Cause...
- I was... I felt like if I would have told you...
CAROLYN: Yam Yam's mad that
he was left out of the vote,
but when everything
was going well
and in his favor...
"Aah!" [babbling]
But the second it goes wrong,
he's boo-hooing.
Well, whatever.
Sarah's gone. I don't care.
I want to play this game,
and I want to win, so,
moving forward,
who do I go with?
Yes, my heart says, Yam Yam.
That's my... That's Yam Yam.
But I know, though, I got to do
what's best for my game,
which would... [sputters]
...probably be Josh.
Aah!
♪ ♪
- Oh.
- You're fine. You're fine.
I'm in lot of pain.
On day two,
I dislocated my shoulder.
- [gasp]
- [screams]
[grunts]
MATTHEW: Now it's day ten,
and I'm still dealing
with an immense amount of pain.
Every day that
you stay out here,
you impress me so much.
I know how hard
you play this game.
You're an absolute gladiator.
You're a certified legend.
Okay?
And I'm glad I'm stuck
on this beach with you.
MATTHEW:
It's forcing me to be adaptable,
but at the same time, like,
it dulls my spirit
to not be able to move.
Do you feel like it just
keeps getting worse every day?
MATTHEW: Last night
was definitely the worst night
- that I've had.
- Mm-hmm.
And, like,
it's emotional because...
just...
I've literally been, like,
training to be here
for, like, years.
Mm-hmm.
So, it's just...
It's more
than just, like, the pain.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
You need a hug.
I don't know if it would hurt.
Yeah, I'll take a hug.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Carson adds an interesting mix
to the tribe.
He has come on, and he's the guy
that I feel like
I can emotionally open up to.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I appreciate your concern.
You have a big heart
for a little guy.
- Thank you.
- [laughs]
CARSON: I've only been
with Ratu for four days,
and I'm in the exact position
I wanted to be at.
I've really developed
the relationships
that I've wanted to build.
- Right.
- So I was happy when you got to this beach.
- Oh.
- Because I felt that I was a target here, as well.
Yeah.
Everyone in this tribe is
just sharing so much information
with me, and it gives me
a lot of power.
I know. Me too. Me too.
I've been trying
to keep my cool, but, like,
I got to ask this guy,
like, what's...
- Oh, my gosh. Yes.
- Like, are we...
KANE: I know that
Carson is a nerd, and
I'm also a nerd, and I know that
nerds work together, you know?
- I love Lord of the Rings so much.
- Oh, are you serious?
How did you feel when, like,
the sword and shield out here?
It's like this season
- was made for us, man.
- It really was.
KANE:
It's like Geek Squad out here.
It's, like, nerds know
to stick together, you know?
Like, we've all been
through wedgies and whatever,
you know?
I also understand, like, you
know, I am the new person, so...
Yeah. No, I know. Right.
But I think
that once rubber hits the road,
I don't think it would be you.
I think we need
- to protect the young guns out here.
- Yes.
I know, really.
CARSON: I think at this point,
they don't really see me
as this strategic mastermind,
but really, what I'm doing
is putting myself in a position
where I am getting closer
with some of the Ratu members
than they are with each other.
Once someone actually
understands what I'm doing,
they'll be gone. [Laughs]
DANNY: 30 breaths.
You're gonna fill up your belly
as much as you possibly can.
No pause
in between ventilations.
[Danny breathes rapidly]
I practice Brazilian jujitsu.
It's my passion. Like, I'm-I'm
absolutely in love with it, and
I realized in the last couple
of years
that I've been breathing wrong
the whole time.
Not breathing in my...
my belly and my diaphragm.
So once I started
to, like, tap into that,
you can actually open up
your mind and
see more clearly.
After 30 breaths,
you're gonna do that exhale.
[exhales]
And hold.
It's all about the love
and energy.
And it sounds silly, I know,
and it is silly.
We're a bunch of silly gooses
out here, but it-it works.
I don't know
if there's some sort
of chemical release
or something, but
when I closed my eyes, I was...
I was dancing bachata
with my wife and daughter.
My daughter's
four months tomorrow,
and every night,
I think about her, and
every little cry I have,
any-any little emotionality
I have,
I'm missing my, uh,
my little girl.
Uh, when I hold her,
it's gonna be... oh.
It's gonna...
it's gonna be nice.
Want to fill up the belly.
Fill it up
with all that loved one's
energy. You're channeling it.
We're storing it in
for later when we need it.
JAIME:
I feel like I really was meant
to be on the Soka tribe, and
if I had my choice, this is
the tribe I would have picked,
not only because
they're strong, but because
it's the high vibe tribe.
Everybody here meditates.
It's not me having
to teach how to meditate.
It's, like, us going deeper
and gaining that mindset
that we need
to work well together
as a tribe.
Obviously, like, somebody coming
in new, it's like, "Okay",
"she's the easy vote," which is,
like, nerve-wracking.
- Yeah. For sure.
- And, like, unfortunate.
But if you're looking to go
into the merge even stronger,
I'm really valuable.
I know everything
that's going on at Ratu, so,
it's like, "Hello."
I have so much more information
than anybody playing this game.
You're doing exactly
what you need
- to be doing right now.
- [laughs]
Um, I'm not gonna, like,
commit to anything.
- I'm a noodler.
- Yes.
I prefer slow deliberation.
JAIME: We are all
running a marathon right now,
and Matt is learning to crawl.
I am the most valuable person
that anybody could
ever interact with,
and for a player to not
jump on that is mind-blowing.
Well, I can't make sense
of what type of game Matt plays
'cause, like,
it doesn't seem very
strategically strong -Yeah.
Unless he's, like,
hiding everything.
I think he's just
really affable,
and...
that's, like,
his biggest strength.
I don't think that
Jaime has quite caught on
to the fact that Matt and I
are really close.
And that's a good thing because
I don't want to be in a position
where somebody wants
to make a move against Matt,
but doesn't feel like
they can tell me.
It's good to have a friend
in the game.
Someone totally
honest, completely, -Yeah.
- Who has my back no matter what.
- Yeah. Yes.
MATT: At the end of the day,
Survivoris a game
about relationships.
And right now,
my blind spot is Frannie,
'cause I really like her a lot.
Um...
- Just to, like, take a big, deep breath.
- Let's hug.
- Yeah.
- All right. Ready?
[both exhale and inhale deeply]
MATT: And I think
we also...
I don't know. [Laughs]
I feel like
there's a little, like, uh,
you know, a spark between us.
- Okay.
FRANNIE: I don't
nothave a crush on Matt.
When this game is over,
Matt and I are gonna go out
for Ethiopian food together,
and whatever happens happens.
Oh.
Matt's somebody
I would date in real life,
and if it comes to that,
after this game is over, then...
I would be pleased as punch.
[laughs]
[laughing]: Yeah, I know.
- Oh.
- What part of my face is red?
- The whole thing?
- It's kind of blushing.
[laughing]: No.
No!
Yeah, I'm good.
No, no, I'm fine.
But, I mean, it's a game,
so, I'm-I'm...
I'm fine. I'm still here.
YAM YAM: I'm trying
to make amends with Josh.
I understand why he's mad,
but, dude,
you did the same thing to me...
You lied to me.
But he's like,
"You're the one's wrong,
and I don't trust you,
and you're the one dishonest."
Dude, great move. Applaud.
Move on. If you don't want
to work with me, it's fine.
But what's up
with the bitch face, you know?
Well...
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I was going with the group.
Nothing personal.
JOSH: Yam Yam, I think,
felt like he was in a position
of power this whole time,
and now he's not.
So, he's very somber, very sad,
walking around like
someone killed his dog,
and feeling like
he's going to be next.
JOSH: But the truth
is, I don't feel safe either
because yesterday
I played my immunity idol,
so now I'm vulnerable.
So, to make sure that.
Yam Yam and Carolyn don't get
together and try to vote me out,
last night, I made up a lie,
saying that I'd had another idol
that I received at Soka
from the birdcage.
JOSH: I showed him the
piece of paper that I received
on the journey, and then today,
I made a fake immunity idol
with some beads from tree mail
that I weaved into a bracelet.
That makes me...
- I do, yeah. Yeah.
- Awesome.
YAM YAM: So Josh is telling
me he has a second idol now.
He didn't show me,
but if it's true,
next Tribal Council,
it's either Carolyn or me.
And I know
Josh doesn't trust me, so,
next vote, it means I'm out.
It sucks, you know, because
Josh and I are not
that different.
Did you ever come out
to your mom?
- I've never come out.
- You never told her?
You just... It was just...
It was what it was?
I... Like, the thing is,
like, coworkers of my mom, like,
they always told her like, "Oh,
he's gay, he's gay, he's gay."
And she was like, "I'm gonna
wait for him to tell me."
And blah, blah, blah.
So I never, like,
put myself out there.
Like, it wasn't a thing
of me being afraid I was gay.
Was me... a thing of me
not finding myself attractive.
And many, many years after that,
that's when I met my husband.
And my husband
is my first boyfriend.
Then we got married
a year after.
Right.
Um, sophomore year of college.
I couldn't come out in high
school 'cause kids were mean.
- Yeah, it was...
- You know, I wasn't ready.
So I moved away from my hometown
because I knew I was different.
And then I was like,
"You know what?
- I can't live a lie anymore."
- Mm-hmm.
So I told her, and she was like,
"Are you sure?"
Said, "Yeah, Mom."
Like, that whole day was,
like, awkward.
She was crying all the time.
And the next day,
she came around.
She was like,
"This doesn't change anything.
Thank you for coming out.
That means so much to me."
She was good.
I love her.
Yam Yam and Idid bond.
We were talking
about how I came out
versus how he came out
and how that was
kind of hard for us.
So we've talked about
a lot more deeper things
than Carolyn and I.
But I have to be smart.
I'm in a position of power,
and I haven't decided yet
who I want to keep around.
But I need Yam Yam
to feel comfortable.
I mean, I think at this point,
I have your trust?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- And I think I can trust you.
I think so. Yeah.
YAM YAM: I hope
he's telling the truth
because Josh
has all the control.
So, we have a challenge
coming up.
Best case scenario, we win.
If not, I'm willing
to vote out Carolyn.
Aah!
♪ ♪
Come on in!
- Good morning.
Good morning.
PROBST: Ratu and
Soka getting your first look
at the new Tika tribe.
Sarah voted out
the last Tribal Council.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
- [all voicing assent]
- PROBST: First things first.
Got to take back the idols.
Thank you, Brandon.
- My liege.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you'll be tied together.
On my go, you're gonna race
through a series of obstacles
to a bucket.
You'll fill that bucket
with water
and make your way over
a hinged platform,
transporting the water until
you have enough to lower a gate.
Once you reach the finish,
two tribe members
will work together
to maneuver balls
through a table maze.
The first two tribes
to land all three balls
win immunity.
In addition, you are playing
for power in this game
in the form of control.
Once again,
the winning tribe will decide
which three players
go on a journey.
There is a lot at stake
- in this challenge.
- Okay.
The last tribe to finish...
Tribal Council, where somebody
will be the sixth person
voted out of Survivor44.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Tika, you are trying
to earn yours back today.
Let's get to sit-outs.
Ratu, you have two extra people.
Who's gonna sit out?
Matthew sitting out again.
And Lauren gonna sit out.
Soka, two sit-outs.
- Are you okay with that?
- Jaime, Frannie.
PROBST: Jaime and
Frannie gonna sit out for Soka.
Sit-outs, take a spot
on the bench, everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize,
and we'll get going. Here we go.
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward,
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, you got
to get through this obstacle.
The key is how well
you can maneuver together.
- Under the stick, under the stick.
- BOTH: Got it.
There you go, Soka!
Over this top one.
PROBST: Ratu's going up top.
- So is Tika.
- Over more.
We're gonna go under this stick.
PROBST: That was Soka.
Everybody took
the high path this time.
PROBST:
Yam Yam is out first for Tika.
There's Carolyn.
- Sorry.
- No. You're fine. You're fine.
PROBST: Everybody's
got to get through it.
- Tika through first.
- FRANNIE: There you go, Soka!
Now you're going
to the over-unders.
Over one, under the next.
Soka's through. Ratu is through.
- Here we go.
- [indistinct shouting]
Come on, Ratu!
PROBST: You got to go
over and under together
because
you are tethered together.
JOSH: You ready?
PROBST:
Everybody's slowing down now.
- That under is tough.
- HEIDI: Yup. We're good.
- You got to get low.
- Here we go.
- PROBST: You're good, Tika.
- Yeah. Yeah.
PROBST:
Get the water bucket undone.
- Ratu is through.
- LAUREN: Y'all still got it, Ratu!
PROBST: Soka last to the bucket.
Once your bucket's free,
fill it with water.
Key to this part
of the challenge
- is transporting the water.
- All right, let's go.
Now you've got
to go over this hinge platform.
There goes Tika.
Ratu heading out.
Danny dips in.
Soka's heading out.
There's the transition.
How much water can you save?
MATTHEW: Oh, they're
spilling all over the place, guys.
LAUREN AND FRANNIE:
Slow and steady.
PROBST: Ratu does a nice job.
Tika with a nice job.
Go back, go back, go back.
Two good buckets full of water
from Tika and Ratu.
There's Soka.
Danny pours the water.
Everybody did a nice job
on that first round.
Here comes Ratu. Wow.
No water lost at all by Brandon.
- Well done.
- MATTHEW: Good job, you guys.
PROBST: Here comes Tika.
- FRANNIE: Nice and easy!
- LAUREN: You got it. You got it.
FRANNIE: Nice, Danny! Nice!
PROBST: Matt takes a big fall,
but Danny holds on
to that water.
Yeah, you got it, you got it.
Dump any time.
[Lauren screams] - PROBST:
And that's enough for Ratu.
- They are through.
- Right here, right here!
PROBST: Is that enough for Soka?
- JAIME: Yes!
- Yes. Is it enough for Tika?
Yes! Everybody's through
with two buckets.
[indistinct shouting]
We are very even right now.
You take it off,
you take it off.
- HEIDI: Go, go, go!
- It's Ratu on the maze first.
Then Soka. Tika's there.
We're about as even
as you can be in this challenge.
Tip the other way.
PROBST:
It is Yam Yam and Josh for Tika.
- It is Danny and Matt for Soka.
- HEIDI: Come on, Danny.
PROBST: It is Carson
and Brandon for Ratu.
You have immunity and power.
You decide
who goes on that journey.
Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow.
Uh, that's a dead end.
Slow and steady.
Nice job by Soka,
making a lot of progress.
Tika drops.
That's okay. They're learning.
Keep going.
Danny and Matt.
Critical point right here.
They can see the end.
Very fast...
with this first ball.
HEIDI: Breathe.
PROBST: Can they land it
without dropping it off the back end?
That's the risk now.
And they do.
Soka has their first.
- Yes, Soka!
- Beautiful! Do it again!
Too much.
PROBST: Yam Yam and
josh have to start again for Tika.
This would tie it.
And they do.
- Yes! - Yes.
- Ratu has one. We're tied.
It is one-one,
Ratu and Soka. It is now Tika.
They drop.
- FRANNIE: You got it, Soka.
- JAIME: There you go, Soka.
- See you.
- FRANNIE: You got it.
PROBST: There goes Soka again.
Getting near that finish.
- Ratu is right there, as well.
- It's almost... [mutters]
PROBST: Ratu getting
very close to the end.
Ratu's at the same spot.
Soka loses theirs.
CARSON: Hold yours up a little.
PROBST: And they in and out.
- LAUREN: Yes!
- That's it! Ratu has it!
Ratu in the lead with two!
- DANNY: One-two, Ratu.
- PROBST: Tika...
closer than they've ever been.
-[Josh murmurs] -YAM
YAM: Balance it. Balance it.
[exclaims] - PROBST:
And they drop their first.
Tika's in and out with one.
Danny and Matt near the finish.
Do they have
the touch this time?
And they do.
We are tied, two-two.
- Yes! Yes! That's beautiful!
- Relax, relax.
- We got it.
- PROBST: Ratu with two.
It is Ratu with two,
Soka with two,
Tika with one.
Tika has to start over.
Ratu and Soka...
Thanks, Mom.
PROBST: ...going
for their third to win it.
About at the same spot.
Danny and Matt
as close as they've been
with that third ball.
- HEIDI: Take all the time you need.
- They could win it right here.
Here comes Ratu
right on their tail.
For the win.
Can they save it?
They are on the edge
of disaster.
HEIDI: Bring it back.
PROBST: And they bring it back.
Ratu is right there.
Ratu pulls it out!
Ratu wins immunity.
We're looking for one more!
It could be over right here
for Soka
if they can close it out.
And they do!
Soka wins immunity, sending Tika
back to Tribal Council
where Carolyn, Josh or Yam Yam
will be the sixth person
voted out of Survivor44.
ALL: Soka! Soka! Soka!
Jeff, I always wondered
if the matches were as close
- as on TV, and...
- They were.
PROBST: They are.
- It was seconds.
- Yeah, everyone out here.
Ratu, the sword is yours.
Immunity for Soka as well.
All right, now,
you have power, Ratu.
You're gonna decide which three
players... one from your tribe,
one from Soka, one from Tika...
Are gonna go
on a journey together.
I'm gonna be going on a journey.
Let's talk about Soka.
We like Danny.
We pick Danny to go.
- PROBST: All right, Danny going on a journey.
- All right.
All right,
you got one last decision.
You have Yam Yam,
Josh and Carolyn.
Who you gonna pick to join
as the third player?
We're sending Carolyn.
PROBST: All right, it's gonna
be Brandon, Danny and Carolyn.
Head out.
Boat will take you out.
Carolyn, you will return
in time for Tribal Council.
- [indistinct chatter] - Have fun.
- FRANNIE: You got it, Danny boy.
- Have fun. - Okay.
- Yeah.
PROBST:
Soka, Ratu, no Tribal Council,
nobody going home. Grab
your stuff, head back to camp.
But Matthew, just given that
you've sat out two challenges,
and it's clear
you have an injury,
I'd like medical to take a look
at that and just get an update.
- So you can stick around.
- Okay.
PROBST:
Okay, grab your stuff, head out.
- Enjoy the night off.
- Jeff!
Well earned.
All right, Yam Yam and Josh,
Carolyn will return
in time for Tribal Council.
Somebody will be
the sixth person voted out.
As a penalty for losing,
I'll hold on to your flint.
You'll have another chance
to earn it
at your next immunity challenge.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at Tribal.
YAM YAM: I don't think
people understand how hard it is
to be only three of us
at Tribal Council.
I don't think
Survivorgets harder than this.
Especially me being out
of the last vote.
Like, what power do I have?
I have nothing.
I don't want to work
with Josh or Carolyn,
but it's like, "Hello.
We cannot vote the coconut
palm tree out, you know?"
WILL: So I just thought
we'd have a look
at your shoulder again
because I know
you've been struggling,
haven't you?
MATTHEW: Yeah, I have been.
Like, the pain
has been really bad.
- Mm.
- And it's just...
It's so weak
that I can't even, like...
I feel like gravity's gonna pull
it out of the socket.
And, uh... and I'm just,
like, really worried
because, you know,
I'm only eating, like,
a couple hundred calories a day,
and I just don't know,
like, how well my body can heal
under the conditions
that I'm in.
PROBST: Will, can you explain
why is he feeling so much pain?
- 'Cause it's clear he's hurting.
- Yeah.
What happens when you pop your
shoulder out, Matt is the...
the soft tissue that holds
the shoulder in place...
That can get torn.
And if it's a small tear,
then the pain
is usually quite short-lived.
- But you're in a lot of pain, and this is nine days on.
- Yeah.
I got to say,
I'm very impressed.
You got injured
playing the game.
You fought through it,
you tried to hide it.
Sometimes you had the sling on.
Other times,
you didn't have the sling on.
When challenges came up
that you could have sat out
to try to preserve
your own health,
you fought for your tribe,
and I've watched you
lift a very heavy box.
I watched you slap at the keys.
So what is it? Is it just drive?
- 'Cause I know we've been advising you not to.
- It...
It's painful, but I'm not one
to give up on something
that I want so badly.
Doctor told me that
I probably tore something
in my shoulder, and...
I want to be out here.
This is a dream of mine,
but I wake up in so much pain.
Just got a lot weighing
on my mind, 'cause I got
to figure out what I should do.
- We were right there with them.
- We were.
- Sorry, dude.
- No, it's okay.
Good effort, though.
The immunity challenge
was rough.
Tika lost, and now
we're going to Tribal Council.
Fortunately,
it seems like Yam Yam really
believes that I do have an idol,
which I'm using
and banking on because
that lie is the only thing
that I have going forward.
So I'd like
to save my idol if I can.
Obviously,
I'm using two in a row.
That's your...
that's your decision.
We obviously were on different
sides of last Tribal Council.
I want you to understand...
I understand.
Oh, yeah, I understand it.
...how it went down.
But I just want to make sure
it doesn't happen again further.
- It's not gonna happen again.
- 'Cause we're working together.
Because here's the thing.
- Carolyn is playing both me and you.
- Right.
She is not as unaware
as it looks she is.
She proved it
with the Sarah vote.
And she made you use your idol
when you needed me to.
Do you think
that was a mistake or a...
a fluke or whatever it's called?
She's thinking.
If Josh has an idol,
I have to save my own ass.
So,
I'm throwing Carolyn
under the bus, the train,
the airplane, the submarine,
going back and forth.
[trilling]
Hoping I come out alive,
you know?
Like, I can't trust her.
Like, she's too emotional.
And what
you're saying makes sense.
- She's the ticking time bomb.
- Yes.
So, when Carolyn comes back,
let's see what she tells you that
she has, -Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- And let's see what she tells me.
- Okay.
And then see what kind of game
she's playing.
While Carolyn and Yam Yam want
to work with me,
Carolyn went on a journey,
and who knows what
she might come back with?
She could lose her vote, she
could have a Knowledge Is Power.
She could have
an immunity idol. Who knows?
But it could change everything.
All right,
I'm gonna shake on it.
- Let's shake it. I'm for real.
- Oh.
- We're in this. All right.
- For real. Okay.
JOSH: Perfect.
BRANDON: I was happy
to be going on the journey
because I figured
something could come of it,
but at the same time, I'm
immediately thinking, you know,
"what am I gonna say
when I get back?"
Because there's been
so many journeys that have been
taking place already,
and they're gonna be looking
for me to come back
with some sort of advantage.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- All right.
DANNY: It's you guys'
first journey, right?
- CAROLYN: First journey.
- DANNY: Oh, dude.
Hopefully, it doesn't suck.
- [Danny laughs]
- BRANDON: I know.
[Carolyn screams]
There's a sign here.
Oh, we got another sign.
All right.
- Oh, yeah.
- What's this?
Shut up.
- CAROLYN: Is this serious?
- Ooh!
- Ooh, boy!
- [Carolyn shrieks]
DANNY: And nobody
is gonna believe this,
- But I don't care right now.
- BRANDON: Nah, nah, nah.
BRANDON: We all were like,
"There's some catch.
There's no way this is real."
But sure enough, it was.
- Boom. Yeah, let's go in.
- Go in?
I don't eat meat,
but I do on Survivor.
Even though I was super,
super nervous
because we're going to Tribal,
it kind of felt good.
I was like, "I am starving."
This is an opportunity,
me coming from a tribe
of three people, where I'm
gonna get to know these guys,
maybe gain more allies
and just feel better
in the game.
What's going over at Tika?
'Cause that's the real question
I'd like y'all to answer.
DANNY:
Yeah, what's going on there?
How do you think it's gonna
go down tonight for you?
I'm worried!
I'm sorry to yell at you.
No, no, please do. I would...
I would feel the same way
if I was you.
It's a tough spot for you.
I'm worried
because Josh came back
with an idol from the journey
- that he could only use up to the merge...
- Oh, actually...
- until... We used it.
- ...that means Jaime has one.
- BRANDON: And so does Carson.
- And Carson.
This right now is a disadvantage
unless, like,
we get to the merge
- and we, like, work together, and then...
- Ah, for real.
DANNY: I couldn't have been
more grateful for this journey.
Between the food,
the information,
I don't know what tasted better.
I also got some time
with Brandon.
We hit it off 100%.
We were thinking
the exact same thing.
- I've been wanting to work with you.
- Yeah, absolutely.
So, I'm happ...
That's why I was like,
"I want to make sure
Danny goes on it."
So, I'll give you my word
right now,
we get to the merge, I'll get me
and whoever else I'm with.
- And vice versa.
- Am I in on this, or am I still...
- Absolutely.
- Here's the thing, though.
- I said, hope... - Okay, yeah.
- I've been wanting to work...
CAROLYN: I was excited
to go on the journey
and just experience
the whole experience.
So I'm gonna get to
talk to Brandon, I'm gonna
get to talk to Danny.
Like, this is great.
But the conversation immediately
just becomes... those two.
DANNY: I'll tell you
right now, the beauty of
you and I getting
to link up right now...
- People like us very rarely win.
- I know.
And what do you mean
"people like us"?
[mutters] People who are looked
at as more physical threats.
DANNY: Our enemies
are gonna be everybody
who's intimidated by us
and our physicality.
That was exactly why
I wanted to meet you.
- Yeah, well, I'm glad you guys worked it out.
- Yeah.
- I hope...
- I hope you make it through tonight.
CAROLYN: They don't even care.
It's like I'm not even there.
It didn't even matter.
I wanted
to work with you anyway.
- I wanted to work with you, too.
- And I want
to ask about your tattoos
because I love 'em.
Yeah, man. I love Achilles,
so I got...
- Oh, it's Achilles?
- Yeah, it's Achilles.
- Is there no one else?
- Yeah.
- DANNY: Is there no one else?
- Exactly.
CAROLYN: So they're bro-ing.
Meanwhile, I'm just here.
Me and you, maybe Josh...
That's money
in the bank right there.
So we meet up in the merge,
you give me a name.
- Yeah.
- And we take out whoever.
- Good luck, guys.
- I'm so surprised.
CAROLYN: What the hell?!
I'm already gone to them.
Well, who would you want
to take out, Carolyn?
BRANDON: Yeah, who would
you want to take out, Carolyn?
I'm not gonna tell you guys
because
uh, what I need is allies.
I don't need...
I'm not trying to, like,
go in and target people.
- I need people that I can trust.
- BRANDON: Honestly,
- like, I don't mean this in a mean way.
- Say it.
I feel like you'd be somebody
to keep around because
you haven't proven yourself
to do very well on challenges.
- [laughs]
- So I'm just being honest.
- I love that. I love that.
- You know, I'm being honest.
I couldn't believe it.
People might look at me
and underestimate me
and think I'm just goofing
around out here,
but I'm playing.
I found an immunity idol,
planted a fake immunity idol.
I've planned
a successful blindside.
So they better watch out for me
at the merge
because I will make the merge.
Yes!
This adventure could be yours.
Apply to be on Survivor.
Here she comes.
JOSH: Wow.
How was it?
Really good.
This journey
has big-time affected
the way I'm gonna vote today
because I don't want anything
to do
with Danny
and the muscle bro thing.
And Josh is a part of that.
So I almost jumped off that boat
into Yam Yam's arms.
[mouthing]
JOSH: So you didn't walk up,
like, a mountain or anything?
No. It just said,
"Today, no advantages,
no risking your vote."
And then, it was, like,
a big spread of food.
JOSH:
I'm cutting up a papaya then.
CAROLYN: Cut one up.
[mouthing]
YAM YAM: As soon
as Carolyn gets back to camp,
she's mouthing,
"Everything's okay."
"Everything's cool,
we're fine, don't worry,"
every time
he has his back at her.
I'm like, this is the Carolyn
I know, you know? She came back.
Hey, Carolyn. How you doing?
I've been missing you.
CAROLYN: I was having
lunch with two people
who were so obsessed
with each other
and how
they are such big threats.
- They bro'd out?
- Yeah.
And then they just sat
and talked about how
you're a good guy
and that you're really smart,
and if you make it,
we can team up at merge.
JOSH: Carolyn came back upset
about what Danny
and Brandon were talking about,
about, like a meat brigade,
basically.
And they made it seem like
I'm a part of it, which I'm not.
But now, that's gonna put
another target on my back.
So they basically,
like, were like,
"Yam Yam's dead in the water."
So, they-they basically...
I mean, I have my idol,
so I amfine, so...
- Yeah. [Laughs]
- Yeah.
CAROLYN:
You have another idol, too?
I do...
- that I'm playing tonight.
- CAROLYN: Okay.
JOSH: So...
CAROLYN: Did you see
it, Yam Yam... his idol?
JOSH: No.
JOSH: They're not.
I wouldn't lie.
It's not.
YAM YAM: Mm-hmm.
CAROLYN: So he takes
out the exact same note
that he showed me two days ago
that he used on the last Tribal.
What, does he not think
I read it the last time?
I'm not stupid.
Can you not destroy it for me?
- I didn't do anything.
- Come on.
- It came apart.
- You're...
YAM YAM: Josh is
sketchy, sketchy, sketchy.
I mean, he pulls out
this freaking fake idol.
[laughing]
The beads were fake.
This idol is so fake.
Whatever. I need to, like...
I'm gonna fill my water.
YAM YAM: Does that mean
I'm working with Carolyn?
I don't know. Does that mean
I'm working with Josh?
I don't know.
I still have to figure it out.
I know. I'm nervous about that.
Carolyn may or may not have
an advantage or immunity idol,
which makes me nervous for sure.
But I still want her out
because now she feels like
that I'm in an alliance
with bros, trying to get
all the girls out or something.
Let's get her out.
But to do this,
I need Yam Yam on my side.
Yes, I have
my fake immunity idol,
but Yam Yam's
kind of onto me, so,
I feel vulnerable,
I'm frustrated, I'm scared.
But adversity is my middle name.
I was born with something called
Guillain-Barré syndrome.
I had weak kidneys.
They didn't think I was
going to make it past age five.
Miraculously, I did.
But at age nine,
I had a kidney transplant.
Because of that,
I've been on immunosuppressant
medications all my life.
And from that, when I turned 25,
I was diagnosed
with cancer of the stomach,
and they also found signs
of B-cell lymphoma.
So I had to have
a total stomach removal
my first year of medical school.
I still graduated
at the top of my class,
and I'm a successful
physician now.
So I take negative situations
and turn them
into positive outcomes.
So now, I just need to step up
and do that again.
YAM YAM: Josh wants
to get rid of Carolyn bad.
But with that fake idol,
I don't know if I can trust him.
That's the thing.
Like, I don't know if
we're working together or not.
So maybe
I should go with Carolyn.
Listen.
I'm here.
Like, I know I love you.
...you can't trust me, and you
want to turn your back on it.
But I'm sorry.
I don't want to go
with his bros alliance.
I made sure to let Yam Yam know,
"I am so sorry that I ever
strayed away from you, and,
like, I will never, ever, ever,
do that again. Please. Please."
But because
I left him out of that vote,
he just does not trust me.
Are you...? Dude, just stop.
Just... Don't... don't...
I don't have the stupid idol.
The truth is, I do have an idol,
but I don't want to use it.
Like, it's too early.
But Yam Yam's just freaking out.
So,
how do I build back the trust
with Yam Yam?
It's just something
I'm gonna have to just hope
and take that risk
that he want...
like, he's with me.
Take it. Yes!
YAM YAM: But she's worried
that I don't trust her anymore,
and I kind of don't.
YAM YAM: At this point,
I think I have the trust
of both of them.
I'm happy I'm back on top,
but I'm not sure
what's best for me in the end.
So this is a huge vote,
and whatever I do,
I hope it doesn't bite me
in the ass, you know?
[engine rumbling]
Is that Jeff?
Jeff's here.
- That's Jeff. What happened?
- No freaking way.
We're sitting at camp,
waiting to go to Tribal,
and all of a sudden,
Jeff arrives in a boat,
and I was like,
"What's going on?"
- Welcome to Tika! - Ah!
- Ah!
All right. First of all,
I have a question.
Before I got here,
what was happening in terms
of heart rate?
Because you all look very calm
for three people
who are ready to go to Tribal.
- We're not.
Outside, we are. Inside, I am...
- We're playing it cool.
- My pulse is through the roof.
I'm so anxious.
In the back of my mind,
I was like,
"Well, I'm done. This is it."
- All right. So curious why I'm here?
- JOSH: Yes.
No. Matthew left the game?
Matthew is no longer
in the game...
- YAM YAM: No way. That sucks.
- Due to his shoulder.
PROBST:
The pain became too much.
- He couldn't take it anymore.
- YAM YAM: No. No.
And he wisely opted
to take care of himself
- long term.
- YAM YAM: No way.
Matthew had to leave the game
because of his shoulder injury.
That sucks. Like,
he wanted to be here, and
he pushed through all that pain
and all those days
of that injury.
The fact that the game can
change so fast... that's scary.
That sucks. If you want
to go out with your...
You know, have your moment.
Hey, Survivoris not easy.
And Matthew is
a really good example of that.
Hurts himself on day two,
and nine days later,
is over. So,
Matthew's, bad news
is your good fortune.
That means
there is no Tribal Council.
- YAM YAM: Stop it.
- But I'm sorry that he went home.
You're not going home.
Carolyn, you're not going home.
Yam Yam, you're not going home.
JOSH: I know Matt really
wanted to be in this game.
This is everyone's
dream come true.
But him going home
allows me to be safe,
and it starts over my game,
because five minutes ago, I'm
thinking they might vote me out.
So, this is a new beginning.
PROBST:
Well, this is a great example
of the absolutely
unpredictable nature of Survivor
because this could completely
change the direction of the game
because you're all three
still here.
- That was not supposed to be the case.
- No.
One of you was supposed to be
going home in a couple of hours.
You're not.
So what was supposed to happen
is now not going to happen.
And the question is
what will happen instead?
- [laughs]
- All right, have a good night.
Thank you, Jeff.
- So scared. [Groans]
- Good night.
Carolyn, why do you think
this is such a bad thing? Girl!
'Cause...
- [Carolyn laughs] - It's obviously... but...
- Ah!
CAROLYN: I thought I
would be more excited
not gonna Tribal,
but it's kind of the opposite
because I wanted
to get Josh out.
So I'm frustrated,
I'm annoyed, I'm pissed off.
[Carolyn groans]
I don't want nothing
to do with you, Josh.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org.
- "Drop your Buffs."
- Oh, my God.
CARSON:
We're all on the same beach, and
I am so excited!
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
CAROLYN: So many people.
What the ...?!
Betrayal.
MATT: My mind is spinning.
Now we're playingSurvivor
with a capital "S."
I came out here for the journey,
and in a lot of ways,
I achieved a lot of goals.
Was the journey
a little bit short? Absolutely.
But I feel like
I'm leaving the game
a much stronger person,
and I know I have the skills
to get wherever I want to go.
The only regret that I have is
I shouldn't have
climbed that rock. [Laughs]
[roars]