♪ ♪
- So happy to be home
on our beach.
- YAM YAM: Can I give you a hug?
Yes.
CARSON:
I did like Helen.
I just didn't trust her.
Pulling off a blindside
my first vote at Tribal
was so terrifying,
but, like, so exciting, too.
Helen, the tribe has spoken.
CARSON:
Seeing Helen leave
was very relieving.
She didn't have any idea.
I mean, I was kind of, like,
in my seat, like, "Aah!"
What happened today...
No shots fired.
- You know what I'm saying?
- SARAH: Yeah.
- YAM YAM: And it was, like,
nothing against Sarah.
- Right.
CARSON:
Tonight, I tapped into
my chaotic, crazy side.
I loved working
with Yam Yam and Carolyn,
but I realize that I need
to smooth things over with Sarah
because I don't want to be
in a situation where she feels
like I'm
the strategic mastermind.
I know everyone thought
me and Helen were, like, BFFs,
but, like, it's really okay.
Everyone is all,
"Sarah, it's not against you.
I hope you're okay."
It's all nice
for our little kumbaya vibes,
but I don't believe it
for a second.
CARSON:
Let me know how you're feeling,
because I know
that I went behind your back,
and I actually do
see me working with you
more than anyone else.
Obviously, right now,
your word carries, like,
slightly less weight,
but I understand.
Carson is the most dangerous
player right now by a landslide.
Everyone trusts him.
He's the cute little nerd.
I mean, out of the three of
them, I trust him the most, so
I think that just
speaks to how dangerous he is.
I was gonna, I was gonna...
I was dying.
I totally put my full trust
in Carson and Yam Yam,
and, like, we pulled it through.
[laughs]
I made it another day,
and I still have my idol.
- Yo, we did it. We did it.
- I know. I know.
[exclaims softly]
I'm playing Survivor.
Mm-hmm.
I'm doing good.
[laughs]
And with two different shoes.
♪ ♪
KANE:♪ O Canada ♪
♪ Our home and sacred land ♪
♪ We see thee rise ♪
♪ The True North
strong and free ♪
♪ O Canada ♪
♪ We stand on... ♪
It's like the national anthem
part right at the end,
when you, like,
sing it for the people.
♪ We stand on guard ♪
♪ For thee! ♪
[cheering]
The Ratu tribe is
laughing, we're
winning challenges.
Morale is up.
I got myself a sword
from that last challenge.
I feel right at home here
on an island with a sword.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
I'm all
things fantasy.
Like, I'm all things RPG.
I play Dungeons Dragons.
I've been a Dungeon Master
for four years now.
I love the hero's story.
Five knights just up against
everything that you can
throw at them... darkest evils.
And good always conquers.
And that's what
I'm hoping happens out here.
I want to be
a hero to people.
BRANDON:
It's crazy to think, six days,
think of everything we've eaten.
- LAUREN: Right.
- Short list, so...
- JAIME: I know...
- [laughing]
Look, we gonna...
I'm coming back with some fish.
Yes, sir.
KANE:
You a fisherman?
I'm an everything.
[laughing]
Jack of all trades.
I never shy away
from anything difficult.
I feel like that-that
helps mold who you are.
It breeds character.
It's going down.
I feel like a lot of the things
worth doing
in life are gonna be
very hard to-to accomplish.
But your growth begins at
the edge of your comfort zone.
I played for the Seattle
Seahawks from 2015 to 2018.
And as an athlete,
people think that's
all you know is football.
You kind of get put into a box.
But there's so much more to me
than just being an athlete.
I do consider myself
a Renaissance man.
I'm a pilot.
I play piano. I play the drums.
I do magic tricks.
I love to snowboard.
I'm gonna have
my scuba diving license.
I cook like a madman.
I kind of
do a little bit of everything.
Yes, sir.
LAUREN:
Good job. Wow.
BRANDON:
I learned that from my parents
forcing me to never quit,
whether I liked it
or whether I didn't like it.
JAIME:
Nice.
[whoops]
Oh, my God, it's so good.
BRANDON: In this game,
you have to be willing
to take risks and take chances.
With no risk, there's no reward.
♪ ♪
MATT: Uh-huh.
After this, can we
go on a road trip together?
Yeah, I would love it.
I would love to go
on a road trip together.
Okay. Okay.
[laughing]
I want that, too.
Am I missing something?
That the two of them
are just so, like...
I'm like, man, my heart is warm
because they're
making a great friendship,
and my heart is warm because
it just takes it to the target.
- [Claire laughing]
- Man, double heart warm.
CLAIRE: Matt and Frannie
go off alone all the time
and they're, like,
two nerdy people
who just like to nerd out.
- Whatever.
- Tallyho!
[laughs]
CLAIRE:
They can giggle
about Star Wars,
they can giggle about
being nerds in high school,
but it's a huge liability
for four other people
in the tribe to be looking
and saying, "Oh, yeah,
those two... they're a duo."
Step by step,
with these four right here.
It's very obvious that
Matty and Frannie are a duo.
It is a beautiful thing.
I want to keep as little eyes
on me as possible because
I have a hidden immunity idol.
Not too long ago,
I find this key.
Run on over to that birdcage,
open it.
"Congratulations, you have
found a hidden immunity idol."
I not only get
a hidden immunity idol,
but I get this
silver coin that has
no power that looks like
a hidden immunity idol.
And I've already
cultivated a plan.
I had a note that said
this silver coin has no power.
I wrapped up that fake idol
in the letter that says,
"Congratulations, you have
found a hidden immunity idol."
I got the fake idol prepared.
Now I just got to get it
in the birdcage.
I'm incredibly nervous.
I don't want to get caught
going back to the birdcage.
There's just brush about to,
like, waist level.
People from camp
get an easy view on me.
♪ ♪
JOSH:
Yeah.
- Hey!
- [excited chatter]
Breadfruit.
JOSH: Breadfruit.
DANNY:
I'm Peter Pan
running through the woods
and got over there,
popped it open,
threw it in,
locked it back up nice,
looking like
nothing's been touched in there.
Who should we have
try to find it?
I don't know yet. [laughs]
I took the key, I wrapped it
in a nice green bow.
I think it looks pretty good.
This is better
than the fake idol.
I've now re-hid the key
that I found.
Hopefully, the opposition
takes the bait.
That way,
any rumors, any kind of
shadow of a doubt
that maybe Danny has it...
That's the end of it.
All right. Who do you guys
got your bets on?
YAM YAM:
When I wake up from this
two-minute nap,
I'm gonna go get wood.
CAROLYN:
I'm getting so tired, too.
You've been snoring
like a monster at night, too.
- YAM YAM: Me?
- Oh, my... Yes.
[snoring]
CAROLYNN:
It sucks.
- [laughing]
- It's horrible, and I just
get so pissed at you.
And then, you'll get up and...
from the fire, and be like...
If I see that you're smiling, I
get really mad 'cause I'm, like,
you don't
have to deal with this.
YAM YAM:
Nobody have ever said anything
about my snoring.
I know I snore.
My husband tells me.
Like, he's super annoyed
I snore.
But for some reason,
I thought I wasn't snoring here.
People get voted off
because of snoring.
I don't want to get voted off
I would never vote you out
because you snore.
[laughing]
SARAH:
I love it when
the tribe's getting along.
I think it does
feel good to laugh,
which is, honestly,
so healthy out here.
Yes! Baywatch, baby!
Yes! You look stunning.
But I am laughing slightly less
hard than everyone else because
I have a lot more weighing on me
than the three of them.
CARSON:
I just want us to go far and not
have to worry about
going to Tribal anymore.
I sure hope that, too,
but I feel like
- odds are, in the next three...
- Yes, three.
We're going at least once.
Our team is so weak.
In order to win,
we need it to be
some challenge that
perfectly caters
to sweet little Tika's skills.
And I am clearly at the bottom
of a very small group,
so unless a miracle happens,
I'm the one that's gonna go.
Ay-ay-ay.
We were all scrambling,
looking for some sort of key
to open the lock for the cage.
I don't know yet.
I'm going crazy with ideas.
I sat in front of the cage.
I'm running out of ideas.
And are you just
sitting here pondering?
You're just sitting here,
staring at it?
It's, like,
what-what are we missing?
I haven't found it,
so I don't have it yet, but
hopefully it comes to me
before someone else finds it.
You should be
reaching your hands
into each one
of these guys, bro.
Do snakes, like, live in there?
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Like... Or-or rats.
DANNY:
Group search parties?
Dude, this is perfect,
but it turns out
they're not good lookers.
Like, you don't just look
at a tree and go,
"Check, that tree's done."
No, dude, get in there.
No. No. [groans]
DANNY:
The key, I put
in the most obvious spot.
This is baffling to me.
Come on.
Move some leaves around.
This is Survivor.
You've watched the show.
DANNY:
No. You?
No.
MATT: This is the key that
everyone has been looking for.
This is the key that has been
taunting us the entire time.
Danny goes off.
I'm feeling like
I'm in the clear.
Come to Papa.
"Congratulations. You have found
a hidden immunity idol."
Yes. Let's go.
My heart starts pounding.
The hidden immunity idol
right here.
Mwah. This is power.
I need this.
Everything in this game
has gone wrong for me so far.
You sneaky little snake, you.
You sneaky little snake.
Phew. All right, now it's time
to tell everybody I...
I saw Matt putting something
in his pocket.
Yeah, yeah.
What'd you put in your pocket?
I... I swear
I didn't find anything.
I swear I didn't find anything.
- Okay. I don't believe you.
- [Matt laughs]
I-I, like, swear it.
Okay, so...
Okay.
MATT:
I'm, like, being outed
in front of Josh by Danny.
Oh, no. Heart sink.
Like, this clean idol that was,
like, my hope in this game,
and it's just been
bathed in mud.
The jig is up, at this point.
My hand is forced.
[Matt laughs]
Okay. All right.
JOSH:
Matt showed me that
he had an immunity idol.
Let's go. Let's go.
JOSH: So that's great for me
and his relationship.
Um, so because of that,
things have changed.
Now that
he has an immunity idol,
Matt and Frannie
are no longer easy targets, so,
it's a good and bad thing.
Yes. We have an immunity idol.
Yes. Okay. That's good.
- We've got it. We're in good...
- Really good. Yeah. Yeah.
FRANNIE:
The good news is
that Matt has an idol.
The bad news is that
the worst people know about it.
Danny knows about it.
And Josh knows about it.
I would have loved
if this idol was something
just between Matt and I, but
that throws a wrench
into things.
I'm-I'm telling you
because I-I got you.
I feel really confident,
me and you.
The epicenter
of this mission was
get people off my tail.
Now everybody has
a false perception
that Matt found the idol,
which works out
splendidly for me.
I don't have to worry
about people being on my case
about having the idol.
[chortling]
So, as of now, everything's
looking really good.
JAIME: I found a big one.
- I'm gonna eat it raw.
- MATTHEW: You are?
Is that the only way
to eat it, right?
That's not. I mean, I... Yeah.
Is everybody gonna eat a worm
or am I the only one?
If you eat that raw worm,
I'll eat a raw worm.
- What's the worst
that can happen?
- MATTHEW: Not much.
That's 70% protein right there.
- It is.
- [Lauren gasping]
- Oh.
- LAUREN: Oh, my God!
- Yes!
- [laughing]
LAUREN:
Me and Jaime
are not exactly the same.
She's definitely
on a high at all times,
which kind of
boosts the morale for us.
This thing is still
moving in its water,
- flipping and flopping.
- Ugh.
- JAIME: It will die
as soon
as it hits your stomach acid.
Well, I don't have any acid.
I don't have anything inside me.
You come out here to the islands
of Fiji, like,
you got to try new things.
The biggest thing for me was
to show my kids and my students
that you can
take on any challenge,
and you can overcome it.
- Three, two, one.
- Two, one.
Aah!
Ah.
[laughing]
I ate an earthworm!
Lots of protein. It's delicious.
I knew I would love this
experience so much because
I love being outside, I love
being creative with things.
We have our very first
house plant.
LAUREN [laughing]:
That's so cute.
JAIME:
I was born for Survivor,
hands down, 1,000%.
I love it.
I have so much energy here.
This is the life.
- I love this tree.
- I know. Me too.
- Check out those roots,
like, crawling up and around.
- Yeah.
I totally connect with Matthew.
We both love plants
and being in nature.
This is our element.
We are
the plant lady
and the plant daddy.
We are always hunting
for firewood, coconuts, worms.
I love hunting for worms.
- Where?
- That looks like mud.
- That looks like mud to me.
- Okay.
Like, I love being with my pets,
but also just, like, randomly...
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
Oh, my... [laughs]
JAIME:
This is so exciting.
[quiet shriek]
I can scream so loud, but I feel
like I... I can't be too loud.
Oh, my God.
[whispering]: Okay. No one's
even close. No one's even close.
JAIME:
We all know,
at the first Tribal Council,
Brandon used his birdcage idol.
Typically, another one
is placed in the game.
So, it's real.
- Plant lady and plant daddy.
- Oh.
Give it up,
give it up, give it up.
Gimme five, man.
JAIME:
I'm digging for worms
and I find the idol.
I couldn't have written
this better. It's perfect.
MATTHEW:
This is perfect.
Jaime thinks that she has
the hidden immunity idol,
but the real truth is
is that I have it.
Oh!
Oh, my God. This is awesome.
This is awesome.
I found it two days ago,
and that gave me
the opportunity to make
a fake hidden immunity idol.
It didn't have to be grandiose,
didn't have to be crazy.
It just had
to be somewhat believable.
MATTHEW: I like being sneaky.
I don't get to do that
in my day-to-day life.
So why not explore
every option out here?
I never intended
to play an honest game.
That's not how I wanted
to outwit, outlast and outplay.
So I will pull any trick
out of my bag to win.
MATTHEW:
I am happy to be plant daddy
to her plant mommy, plant lady,
whatever she wants to be.
That's fine.
I'm in the power position now.
I gave Jaime a fake idol,
and I did that
to one, gain trust, but if that
trust isn't gonna get there,
then I can turn it on her
and put a target on her back.
Instead of talking about
what you would do
if you were out here,
just get out here.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
You look good. Formation.
- We're feeling good.
- Warriors.
Ratu and Soka
getting your first look
at the new Tika tribe.
Helen voted out
the last Tribal Council.
Oh, wow.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
- [all voicing assent]
- PROBST: All right.
Look at that enthusiasm.
First thing first.
Got to take back the idols.
- Yay.
- Thank you for the sword.
- Thank you for the shield.
- Absolutely.
Wow.
Sword's been through something.
Doesn't quite fit anymore.
Feel a little mini sword action.
There we go.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna dive into the ocean
and swim to a large cube.
Working together,
you're gonna roll that cube
to two large poles,
collecting keys along the way.
Once you have your keys,
you'll dig under a log...
♪ ♪
...and unlock
your puzzle platform
where you will stack
four colored blocks,
making sure there are no
repeating colors
on any side.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
In addition,
you're playing for reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
[all voicing assent]
First tribe to finish...
Large Survivor tool kit.
[whooping and cheering]
- And a huge platter of fruit.
- Yo.
- Yes!
Oh, my God.
Second tribe to finish...
Smaller tool kit, smaller fruit.
- Oh.
- PROBST: Last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers...
- Oh, my God.
- PROBST: Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the fourth person voted out,
and as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Tika, you are fighting
to earn yours back.
- We'll get it.
- All right, Soka,
you have two extra
tribe members.
Who are you gonna sit out of
this challenge?
Do you think you'd be better
at getting up on that thing?
PROBST: Big question.
Will Claire compete?
Okay, whatever. Yeah.
Let's make it three.
PROBST:
Claire and Heidi gonna sit out.
So, Claire,
just to mark this down,
you have yet to compete in an
immunity challenge this season.
Yeah.
- And you're all right with that?
- Yeah.
As long as we get
to the next immunity challenge,
maybe I'll compete then.
I want our best shot,
and I really trust these people,
So it sounds like, "We make
the best decision for the tribe.
My ego's not involved."
All right.
Ratu, one extra tribe member.
- Who are you gonna
sit out of this challenge?
- Me.
PROBST:
All right.
Lauren gonna sit out,
Claire and Heidi gonna sit out.
Everybody else, give you a
minute to strategize. Get it on!
- Let's go!
- [whooping]
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward,
Survivors ready?
Go!
[indistinct shouting]
PROBST:
First you got to get
to that big cube
and then you have to roll it
until it is under
that first pole.
LAUREN:
Let's go, Ratu!
PROBST:
All three tribes get
to their cube at the same time.
Once you're under your pole,
send one person up.
Ratu is gonna get there first.
Matthew heading up.
Matthew does not have
a good position.
Now he's flicking at it.
PROBST: Tika's now
underneath their pole.
Soka now underneath their pole.
Matthew's got the first set
of keys for Ratu.
Let's go! Let's go!
- Got it.
- PROBST: Danny has the keys.
- Soka, you're good.
- Yes, Danny!
PROBST:
Carolyn has her keys for Tika.
- You got it!
- Go, go, go.
PROBST: Ratu still in the lead.
Immunity on the line.
- Let's go, let's go!
- Soka!
PROBST:
We've now got a bit of
a roadblock with Soka and Tika.
Each have their own lane,
but Tika is out of sorts.
Now they're gonna have
to spend more time getting back.
In the meantime, Matthew has
the second set of keys for Ratu.
LAUREN:
You guys are doing great!
Guys are doing great.
PROBST:
Danny has
the second set of keys.
- Soka, you're good.
- Yeah, Danny!
- Do it!
- PROBST: There goes Carolyn
back up for Tika.
- Go!
- Let's go!
- PROBST: Start digging now.
All four people got
to get under.
- PROBST: Here comes Soka.
- CLAIRE: Yeah, Soka!
- You're crushing it!
Good teamwork!
- It is Carolyn now
flicking the key for Tika.
Yam Yam already heading up.
PROBST: You're good!
- Matt, you're in the middle.
- Now Soka digging.
LAUREN: Go, go, go! Yes!
- Great digging!
- LAUREN: Yes!
- Push, push, push, push, push!
- Push! Push!
- PROBST: You're good, Tika.
- Go.
- It is Tika in dead last.
- Oh!
- No!
Got to get under that log,
which means
you're gonna have
to move a lot of sand.
Once you think
that hole is deep enough,
you can send somebody under.
PROBST: It's gonna be Danny
trying to get through first.
- Is that hole deep enough?
- CLAIRE: Push, push, push!
Soka just pushing him through!
And it works.
Danny's through.
- Now Danny can dig
on the other side.
- CLAIRE: Yeah, Danny!
Soka undefeated in
immunity challenges this season.
- Yeah, yeah, go!
- Come on, come on, come on.
Looking
to keep that streak intact.
Go!
PROBST: Here goes Ratu.
- Hell, yeah!
- There you go. There you go.
- [overlapping chatter]
- PROBST: Jaime's through.
There goes Matthew.
Carson is through for Tika.
CLAIRE: Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go, guys!
- You're good, Soka.
One person unlocks.
CLAIRE:
Go, Soka!
LAUREN:
You got it! Y'all got it!
Keep going!
Brandon's through!
One person now.
LAUREN: Let's go, Jaime!
- Go, go, go! Yeah!
Y'all got this. Y'all got this.
That's Yam Yam. He's through.
- PROBST: You're good, Soka.
- CLAIRE: Great work, team.
Now you got to get all
four cubes up here
and then two people
will work the puzzle.
- I got it.
- PROBST: Jaime has it.
They're good! Start moving
your boxes up here, Ratu.
PROBST: Carson has it.
Get that rope off there.
You're good.
You got it, Carson!
You got it!
PROBST:
It is Frannie and Matt for Soka.
Matthew and Kane for Ratu.
PROBST:
Yam Yam doing
his own play-by-play.
♪ ♪
You are looking
to build the tower
four blocks tall with no
repeating colors on any column.
We have done versions of this
puzzle for years on Survivor.
- Has anybody studied this?
- Oh, it's all in.
These are the puzzles
you are sure
you can solve
when you're at home.
- There's two reds, two reds.
- There's two reds on this side.
PROBST:
But you get out here,
and they are
so much more difficult.
Okay.
PROBST:
Carolyn and Sarah
watching Yam Yam and Carson,
knowing "Our fate in the game
is in their hands."
[loud gasp]
- We're good over here.
- PROBST: Kane and Matthew
with another approach.
- [overlapping chatter]
- PROBST: Matt super excited
this time.
PROBST:
One of these versions
is gonna be right.
- Yes.
- PROBST: If you have it,
you will know it.
- Yes! Yes!
- They think they do.
- Yes!
- Ratu has it!
Ratu wins immunity!
- Yes!
- We're looking for one more.
Yes!
Now the shield is up for grabs.
- Hurry up.
- PROBST: Who will solve it?
Will it be Matt and Frannie
or Yam Yam and Carson?
Wait.
They need to be next to...
Matthew now literally just gonna
go over and study the puzzle.
Here goes Yam Yam and Carson.
Never seen this before.
- Now it's just copycat.
- Oh, my God.
Carson thinks he knows,
Matt and Frannie think...
- One sec.
- PROBST: No, Carson's
gonna go back. Nope. Yup.
[laughing]
Carson and Yam Yam...
They think they have it.
Matt running back
for another look for Soka.
This could come down
to the last few moves.
- Go, go, go!
- PROBST: Who gets it
- and gets to their mat first?
- Guys, we believe in you guys.
Is this is for Tika?
They think they have it.
Carson feels good.
They're gonna go back.
There's one side, two sides,
- three and four. Tika has it.
- [cheering]
Tika wins immunity,
sending Soka to Tribal Council
for the first time this season.
Wow, what a finish.
Ratu, congratulations.
- [cheering, whooping]
- Yay!
Sword is yours.
- [laughing]
- Yeah! [whooping]
- I don't know if I...
As a Survivor knight?
I don't know. Take the sword.
No Tribal Council tonight.
Nobody going home.
Waiting for you back at camp...
A massive Survivor tool kit
and a fresh platter of fruit.
- Well earned. Congratulations.
- [whooping]
- Tika. Carolyn is so excited.
- Yeah!
You are safe at Tribal Council.
In addition, you have
earned your flint back.
YAM YAM:
Thank you, Jeff.
PROBST:
Nobody going home
from your tribe.
- Oh, my God.
- Waiting for you back in camp...
Small tool kit,
small platter of fruit.
Tika, Ratu,
grab your stuff, head out.
- Enjoy the night off.
- YAM YAM: Thank you, Jeff!
PROBST:
Nice job.
Soka, Tribal Council tonight,
where the first person
from your tribe, fourth person
out of the game,
will be heading home.
And as a penalty for losing,
you know what's coming.
Got to take your flint.
Sorry for you.
All right, Soka,
grab your stuff, head out. See
you tonight at Tribal Council.
MATT: For the first time,
this tribe has
to go to Tribal Council.
And that sucks
because on day two,
I lost my vote.
If it comes down to it
and I feel like I'm at risk,
I will play this idol for myself
because I want
to stay in the game,
and with Frannie,
as long as I possibly can.
♪ ♪
Does anybody here feel as though
they could have done better?
- No.
- So...
- You stepped up.
- It's also, like, the hardest...
- DANNY: No one didn't give 110%?
FRANNIE: Just give me, like,
three minutes.
- I'm gonna...
- HEIDI: By yourself?
- FRANNIE: Yeah, yeah.
- HEIDI: Okay, you got it.
JOSH: Go.
CLAIRE:
Do what you need to do.
- JOSH: Yeah, go...
Yeah, release everything.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Heidi and Frannie
are both athletic.
- Exactly. Okay.
- So, listen, I loved...
And, like,
- You do.
- And, you know, it sucks
for Claire. She hasn't...
- She hasn't played anything.
- Yeah.
DANNY:
How do we get to the merge
without losing again?
It sounded very simple.
Who hasn't done any challenges
and who doesn't seem
like they're gonna be useful
in challenges?
It's in your gut.
Claire's the weakest.
Yeah. It was just part
of the game.
- Right?
- We're good.
DANNY:
The plan would be
vote Claire out,
tell Claire it's Matt,
'cause Matt doesn't
have a vote right now.
I think Claire...
She's been sitting out a lot.
FRANNIE:
Yeah. It also feels kind of
to get dirty and exhausted
every challenge, and then,
Claire walks back clean and...
JOSH:
Claire is an easy vote.
However, originally,
it was supposed to be Matt
or Frannie to go home.
But it's not in my best interest
to go against the tribe at this
point in time 'cause it's gonna
put a bigger target on my back.
So, I don't want to rock
the boat. Yeah, Claire can go.
But if we can get everyone else
on board with this,
then you can save your idol
so you don't have to use it.
Yeah.
We do need
to put our heads together,
whether we do
the slightly easier thing,
which is just taking Matt out.
If he truly doesn't have a vote,
he cannot Shot in the Dark.
You see what I'm saying?
So I think...
FRANNIE:
Claire thinks
that Matt is the person
that we're voting off,
but Danny and Josh
are firmly against Claire.
And Claire is somebody that I
want to work with strategically.
I don't want to just vote out
Claire, and then be,
you know, up a creek without
a paddle after she's gone.
So I want to keep
her and Matt in this game.
I think that
Matt is predictable
and very malleable
to whatever you or I see.
Yeah.
I actually do feel like,
for this first vote,
Josh is better because Josh,
I think, is just
so unpredictable.
I don't feel like I have
an open relationship with Josh.
I think that
Josh is pretty cagey.
In my perfect world,
I would love Claire, Heidi and I
to vote together
to get Josh out of this game.
Danny and Josh both told me
that it was you.
CLAIRE: I am fuming,
baffled, insulted
that Josh and Danny think
that they are smart enough
to pull one over on me.
Like, are you kidding me?
Danny, I actually
am now thinking,
he doesn't have brains
in his head,
so he's not a threat to me.
But I do not trust Josh
as far as I can throw him.
Now that I know he's gunning
for me, I want him gone.
- We need...
- We need Heidi.
- We need Heidi...
- with you two...
To vote Josh.
- CLAIRE: We need... Heidi.
- We need Heidi.
DANNY: Yeah.
- All he takes is three,
by the way.
- DANNY: Yeah.
MATT:
Heidi is the linchpin in it.
- That's our first step.
- MATT: Yeah.
'Cause if Heidi will flip,
it's easy.
My life in this game is
going to be 100% in your hands.
- Frannie is locked in.
Frannie will vote for Josh.
- Okay.
And they're gonna pull you in
and try to get me.
- I...
- I have to think
about this so much. Like...
- Think about what?
- Uh, like...
The decision
you're making is me or...
- Yeah, and I will tell you.
- So, you're thinking...
If-if... if I cannot convince,
I don't think it's on me only.
CLAIRE:
I am so nervous about my life
in the game right now.
I am hanging on by a thread.
It's going to be
a game-time decision
whether or not I play
my Shot in the Dark tonight.
It's really coming down
to how good I feel about Heidi.
HEIDI: It's very hard
because it seems like
everyone wants Josh out,
except Danny, but I feel
like Danny is probably
my number one.
This game is about necessity.
We don't need Claire now.
I understand, logically,
the strength argument, but...
Yeah.
But I'm still undecided.
- Yeah.
- DANNY: So...
FRANNIE:
I won't go against you, either.
HEIDI:
I'm trying to decide
what's best for my game.
My relationship
with Josh is not that great.
He hasn't quite talked
that much strategy with me.
- I love you. Can I have a hug?
- Aw.
HEIDI:
Claire and I are
a little bit more aligned, but
with Claire, we may not be able
to win more challenges,
so, yeah, I'm conflicted.
No matter what,
it's gonna be heartbreaking.
But in here, it's cutthroat,
and I'm in it to win it,
and I'm in it for me,
I'm in it for my family,
not for them.
♪ ♪
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
dip it in the fire
and get flame.
This is part of the ritual
of Tribal Council
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
When the fire is gone,
so are you.
Frannie, you're smiling.
Is it because
the ritual of even saying that
heightens the feeling
of being here?
Oh, yeah. It all felt imaginary
as we were walking in.
And then you hear those words,
your magic words,
and we know that we're here,
and we're playing.
Josh, for all of the
Tribal Council "ooh" and "ah,"
it's that gargoyle.
That's Tribal.
"I'm coming." For somebody.
Did you feel that back at camp?
JOSH:
You know, Jeff,
when we got back today,
the tension was on. You could
tell Tribal was looming.
You know, people were starting
to scramble and go off
on their own
and start talking strategy.
So, this was
a completely different feeling
that we weren't used to.
Claire, what's the smile for?
Today was not the first day
they were playing.
I just don't want to lie and say
that this is the first time
we've ever decided
to look towards each other
and think about it, right?
It's become clear to me
that people have already
been thinking about it
for a while.
PROBST:
Frannie, do you understand
what Claire's talking about
when she says, "Come on,
people have been
playing the game"?
Yeah. We can all
pretend, you know,
for the past however many days
that we've been
a big, happy family but
none of us forgets
for a second why we're here
and what we're here to do.
And so,
people have been talking,
but it's like
a sick merry-go-round, you know?
Every name is gonna be said
at some point.
You just don't want it
to land on yours.
PROBST:
And Heidi, did it
really feel like
it could be anybody
or did it feel like,
"No, there are certain names
that keep coming up"?
HEIDI:
I think it could be anybody.
And I think we would be foolish
not to look through
all the options to see what's
best for each of our games.
PROBST:
So that's
the big question, Matt.
What's best for everybody's game
is to never come back to Tribal.
But what's best for somebody's
individual game could be, "Well,
"we do have
to get rid of somebody,
and this is
who I want to get rid of."
I know for myself,
I have played through
so many scenarios.
Like, "Can I trust this person,
can I trust that person?"
That is the balance
that we are all walking.
Claire, you've sat out
of every immunity challenge,
and the tribe always concurs
that this is a tribe decision.
But is there any concern
that that tribe decision
may actually
just be fingers going,
"You don't even contribute
at the challenges anyway"?
There's a ton of concern
for me because,
to be completely honest,
you know, I love this game.
I came to play everything,
but every single time,
swallowed my pride, put down
that urge to try and test myself
and fight and play with you all
because I was putting the team
before myself.
And so I sat out.
But in the moment,
I trusted you all.
So it stinks to hear that people
are valuing tribe strength when
they didn't even give me a
chance to show what I'm made of.
PROBST:
Danny, you were nodding.
DANNY:
Yeah, I definitely think
our concerns are accurate.
And, you know, conversations
were had about that.
CLAIRE:
But I think it's just
easy to say, you know,
"Those people who step up,
put their neck on the line
are doing it."
But is brute force strength
really what tribe strength is?
What is tribe strength
other than
trusting each other
and working together
and not doing things
that could harm
Soka making it further
in the game?
PROBST:
Heidi, it's a pretty
compelling argument.
I agree 100% with what she said.
Yeah, absolutely.
What is strength?
Is it really just being
the strongest, the best swimmer?
- Maybe, maybe not.
- FRANNIE: To Claire,
I just want to say I'm confident
that you would have
crushed any challenge
you would have been in.
So this is
a lot more complicated than
"Claire's on the chopping block
because Claire
sat out of challenges."
You can't think quite
so myopically in this game
about this one vote.
We all kind of need
to zoom out of it and realize
that this is a longer game
than just tonight.
PROBST:
So, Matt, what's the criteria
at your first vote
when there's only six people?
Survivor is a game of trust,
and so,
not so much, like,
challenges or whatever.
It's all about trust.
Claire, you still
look concerned.
CLAIRE:
Yeah, I don't feel good at all.
I mean, uh, I'm just
gonna be brazen.
Like, have you...
have you thought at all more?
Are you still at the place
you were before?
- I think so.
- Okay.
That sounded coded, but it...
you know what it means?
I think I know what it means.
Heidi's, like,
- figuring it out, but...
- PROBST: Heidi, this is
- a tough time
to be figuring it out.
- Absolutely.
And in all honesty,
this is our dream.
All of us dreamt to be here.
Unfortunately, it's gonna be
the last day for someone,
so one of the dreams
is coming to an end.
All right, it is time to vote.
Claire, you're up.
♪ ♪
[sighs heavily]
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Yeah, Jeff,
I did the Shot of the Dark.
Thank you.
So, Claire played her
Shot in the Dark, which means
there is no vote in here
from Claire.
You have a one-in-six shot.
If it says you're safe,
then any votes
cast against you will not count.
It says you're not safe,
any votes cast against you
will count.
Claire, you are...
not safe.
Any votes cast against you
will still count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Claire.
Claire.
Two votes, Claire.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor 44: Claire.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Claire, the tribe has spoken.
- Time for you to go.
- Thank you.
- Love you, Claire.
- Thanks, Claire.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Broaden your attention
to your surroundings.
HEIDI:
I don't think he sees it coming.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
YAM YAM:
who put that X in there?
MATTHEW:
Information
in this game is power.
This can change the game.
CARSON:
This is so crazy.
- FRANNIE: Oh, my God.
- HEIDI: What?
I got outplayed.
I got eliminated.
So I'm so sad.
But this experience
has been everything.
I'm the biggest fan.
It's been my dream forever.
And I've been so afraid
to come out here
because of this exact situation.
But I'm glad
that I took the chance.
It was an amazing experience.
I just wish I got to see more.
[roars]