♪ ♪
FRANNIE:
Broaden your attention to...
your surroundings
and slowly...
start to focus on the breath
and just really tune
into that breath.
JOSH: Last night,
Claire was voted out.
Claire, the tribe has spoken.
JOSH: So I'm feeling
great because I feel like I am
close with Matt and Frannie.
As we start to wrap up here...
JOSH: I'm also close
with Danny and Heidi.
...take one last big
cleansing breath in.
JOSH: So now I'm
in the perfect position
where I'm in the middle between
two different,
opposing alliances
that both trust me,
and that makes me feel good.
Yeah.
FRANNIE:
Are you comfortable voting Josh?
- No, that's what we're doing.
- That's the plan.
- FRANNIE: Okay.
HEIDI:
I think Josh seems to think
he's playing everyone,
but all four of us are united
at the moment.
We are trying
to blindside Josh now,
and I don't think
he sees it coming.
♪ ♪
What?
YAM YAM: What?
SARAH: This morning
we walk by the birdcage
and see that there have been
two red sticks kind of woven
into the birdcage with an "X."
Does that mean it's empty?
And we go like,
"What? Is this still alive?"
Like, we were, like,
giving up on the fact
that there was something
in there,
but who put that "X" in there?
I think it's one of us.
Just, like, having fun?
CAROLYN: So we all are
thinking different things.
It could... it could be
one of us who planted it,
but the truth is, it was me.
[laughs]
Why an "X"?
Like, that makes no sense
for anything.
I found the idol,
but inside that bag,
there was also this fake idol.
So I knew I need
to do something with it.
And my brain kept saying,
like, "'X.'"
"Like, 'X' marks
the spot of a treasure.
Now go look for this
similar 'X' somewhere else."
So yesterday
I just found red sticks,
made two Xs,
and then I waited
for it to get dark.
[snoring]
And then I put one on the cage,
came back to camp, and I just
stuffed the fake idol in a log
and put the other "X"
right underneath it.
I'm worried
that it looks so fake.
But part of me thinks
it's not as
unbelievable because
there are so many twists.
There are, like...
Why is a birdcage
in the middle of a jungle?
"Look for the, like..."
So I-I don't feel like
this is too far off left field
to have an "X."
[sighs]
YAM YAM: That got everybody
paranoid again.
An "X." Where's the "X"?
What do you think?
YAM YAM: I don't know
'cause I was looking at red stuff,
and there's nothing red
around here.
But there may be something red
at the challenge. I don't know.
SARAH: We're all sitting
around the campfire just thinking
what the "X" is,
where the "X" is,
what the "X" might mean,
when suddenly
I spot
these two matching red sticks
sitting underneath
our bench log.
So I immediately start digging
where I see the "X,"
just kind of, like, casually
wringing my hands
through the sand,
and I'm feeling nothing.
CARSON: You want me to
open... y'all want me to open
- some coconut water for us? Okay.
- Yeah, you open it.
SARAH: And then I look down,
and in a little crevice there is
a piece of cloth wrapped up
with a pretty purple bow.
And I grab it with my underwear
without anyone seeing.
I know I'm at the bottom,
so finding this means
I have life in this game,
I am moving forward,
and I know
none of them have the idol,
and I will make it past tonight.
CAROLYN: I don't know
who took it, but all of a sudden,
I see the fake idol is gone.
So my plan worked.
Somebody has a fake idol,
and they don't know
that it's a fake idol.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
Oh, my gosh.
- Looks like a slingshot.
- Mm-hmm.
Good times.
Whoa.
PROBST: Tika, Ratu,
getting your first look
at the new Soka tribe.
Claire voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right, let's get
to today's reward challenge.
For today's challenge,
one player at a time is going
to climb up the ladder,
across the cargo net
to the top of the tower
where you will launch
the sandbags
at a series of targets.
Each player on your tribe
must hit at least one target.
First two tribes to get
all five targets win reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
ALL: Yes.
- PROBST: Tarps.
- [whooping, cheering]
First tribe to finish...
A large tarp.
Second tribe to finish...
Smaller but just as effective.
In addition,
at the end of this challenge,
one player from each tribe
is going to go on a journey.
The winning tribe will decide
who goes from each tribe.
That's important because
journeys can change the game.
So having even a little power
in who you send to go on that
journey is power worth having.
Ratu, Soka, you have one extra
person. Gonna sit somebody out.
- Cool.
- Who's it going to be?
- Me.
- Frannie gonna sit it out.
- I'll sit out.
- Kane going to sit out.
Sit-outs, take a spot
on the bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
Get it on! Let's do it!
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
For reward. Survivors ready?
Go! First you got to get
- everybody to the mat.
- Yeah, Soka!
- Then one person goes up.
- Go, go!
- FRANNIE: Yeah, Danny! Attaboy!
- MATT: Okay, go!
- Okay, go!
- [whooping]
SARAH: Carson, you got it.
- PROBST: Danny's up first, then Carson.
- LAUREN: Go, Brandon.
Here comes Brandon.
FRANNIE:
You got it, Danny. You got it.
- You got it, Carson!
- PROBST: Now you got
to start the learning curve
of a giant slingshot.
Brandon launches.
Just misses!
KANE:
You got to untangle, buddy.
Got sandbags in the air.
- There's a hit for green!
- FRANNIE: Yeah! Yeah, Danny!
PROBST: Danny hits for
Soka, and he heads back down.
FRANNIE: Oh, be careful, though.
PROBST: Carson in
here. There's a hit for Tika.
Carson's going to head down.
- Go, go, go.
- PROBST: Here comes Heidi.
Here goes Brandon again.
Will that do it?
Yes, it does! Brandon connects.
We are tied one each.
Here goes Heidi
with a big launch.
There it is for Heidi!
That's the second one for Soka.
Here comes Josh.
It is Lauren up top for Ratu.
Here goes Carolyn for Tika.
And that's not going to do it.
- Ah!
- PROBST: There goes Josh for Soka.
And he's got it.
Soka now with three.
- Go!
- Here comes Matt.
Aah!
PROBST:
Carolyn continues to struggle.
- YAM YAM: Don't give up. Don't give up!
- I'm not!
PROBST: Lauren connects.
She's got it for Ratu!
- Aah!
- PROBST: Carolyn has got to connect.
Get somebody else up here.
That will not do it.
- HEIDI: He got it.
- There goes Matt.
- [cheering]
- And he's got it for Soka!
That is four for Soka.
Everybody has gone for Soka.
Now they're going
to send somebody back up.
- Go!
- PROBST: It's going to be Danny coming back up.
Yeah, Danny! [Whooping]
- Aah!
- PROBST: And another poor toss from Carolyn.
- FRANNIE: I like it.
- PROBST: Danny launches.
- [cheering]
- PROBST: Oh, yes!
Danny launches
and wins it for Soka.
Soka's won reward.
We're looking for one more.
YAM YAM:
Pull! Pull! Keep pulling!
- Aah! Aah!
- Keep pulling! Keep pulling!
PROBST: Carolyn trying
to get maximum velocity.
- And she's done it! Carolyn hits for Tika.
- [cheering]
We are tied two-two.
Here goes Jaime.
That looks good.
And it is. Jaime hits for Ratu.
It is Ratu with three,
Tika with two.
Here goes Sarah.
Sarah all the way off.
- CARSON: Nice, Sarah...
- PROBST: Just misses.
Here comes Matthew.
Took his arm out of the sling,
but still holding it
as if there's a sling there.
Will he be able
to even pull it back?
- [cheering]
- Matthew, with his first shot,
hits it. That is four for Ratu,
two for Tika.
There goes Sarah,
trying to keep Tika in it.
- CARSON: Nice!
- PROBST: Sarah connects for Tika.
It's four-three.
She's got to get down quickly.
Tika trying to stay in this.
Here comes Yam Yam.
Brandon for Ratu.
Is this the one?
- Yes, it is!
- [cheering]
Ratu wins reward.
All right, Soka, nice victory.
Large tarp waiting
for you back at camp.
Ratu, nice victory.
Smaller tarp
waiting for you back at camp.
Now to the other part
of this reward.
Soka, you're in charge
of the three people that are
going to go on a journey.
Heidi, who's it going to be
from Soka that's going to go
- on this journey?
- It's going to be Josh.
PROBST:
Who's going to go from Tika?
We decided to be Carson.
PROBST: All right, who's
going to go from Ratu
to join Josh and Carson?
We decided that we're going
to send Jaime to the trek.
PROBST: All right, Jaime,
Carson and Josh,
grab your stuff,
head out this way.
Boat's gonna pick you up.
- SARAH: We'll miss you.
- Thank you.
All right, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
JAIME:
I'm so excited to get chosen.
I literally
was sitting there like,
"Jaime, Jaime, Jaime, Jaime."
Bling! It happened.
I have a magic wand.
And so, when I go, "Ding,"
things happen.
And I wanted to go
on the journey
because this is a huge
opportunity to get an advantage.
JAIME: I am really, really
pumped to go on the journey.
I want
the entire Survivorexperience.
JOSH: We're here, guys.
Yay! We made it!
I see that Josh and Carson
are also chosen,
and I'm super excited because
I kind of had my eyes on them
during challenges as people
that I could possibly
work with in the future.
So, the fact
that they were chosen was just
beautiful for me.
- You guys, we're here!
- I know!
This is the coolest thing ever.
JOSH: All right, let's
see what's going on here.
- Ooh. - Yay.
- Yay.
- You guys ready to do this?
- Yes! Let's do it.
All right, here we go.
CARSON: Being on this
journey is kind of the pinnacle
of mySurvivor experience.
JAIME: So amazing.
I haven't really gotten to find
a idol or an advantage
or a clue.
So, finally, I'm able
to get something of value.
But I will not risk,
because when
there's only four people left,
if I lose my vote, I lose a lot
of leverage in my tribe.
Okay.
- See you at merge.
- Do it.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye-bye.
What is this?
Ah!
"Congratulations.
You have an immunity idol."
Immunity idol. [Laughs]
I'm just so happy.
This is amazing. Okay.
[gasps]
"Oh, one more thing.
You will not be returning..."
What?!
JAIME: "Oh, one more thing.
You will not be returning
to your tribe."
[gasps]
Oh, my gosh.
Okay. Well, at least
I have immunity.
Let's see what tribe
I'm going to.
I'm going
to have to switch tribes.
I was in a great position
at Soka.
Now I'm going to a tribe
that I have to start all over.
This has changed
the game completely.
The game just changed.
Even though
I'm going to a new tribe,
I have a second immunity idol.
Can you believe two idols
coming into the game?
Who would have known?
I can't wait
to see everyone's faces today.
I'm just kind of nervous.
This is so crazy.
I'm not on Tika, like, the tribe
that's been losing
the whole time.
But then, also,
my emotions change
from excitement
to anxiety because I'm gonna be
at the bottom of a new tribe.
♪ ♪
Oh, he's coming home.
- YAM YAM: Ooh!
- Ah!
SARAH: Carson!
Is that him?
That's Joshua.
What?!
When I see Josh, my heart sank.
Like, I had no breath in me.
Like, I was like... [gasps]
It means all this
relationship I've been building
with Carson is no more.
Welcome to Tika!
- You're gonna love it here.
- Hey.
JOSH:
I pull up to the Tika camp,
and they greet me
with open arms,
but the truth is,
I'm walking into
a lion's den, you know?
Like, I'm a lamb
and they're all lions
and they're ready to pounce.
All right,
so, we see this scroll.
It basically says, "You are now
a part of a new tribe."
"Reach in..."
CAROLYN: Oh!
So I unwrapped it,
and it was your buff.
So here I am.
SARAH: Wait. Are you a surgeon?
No. No, no, no, no.
I am a physical trainer.
I'm not telling anybody
that I am a surgeon.
I just want people to think
that, you know,
I'm a happy-go-lucky,
uh, jock that likes to work out
and, you know,
isn't really strategic
or "smart," as you will,
because
that could blow up my game.
So, after college I wanted
to go to med school, right?
But I couldn't
really pass the MCAT,
so I moved away
from Pittsburgh to Atlanta
in 2020, and, um, I got
into personal training, well,
because I like working out.
SARAH: We thought
we'd heard at the snake puzzle
that Josh wanted to take
on the puzzle because
he had to have steady hands with
his job or something like that.
And so I immediately asked him,
"Oh, are you a surgeon?"
And then he says that
he's a physical trainer, which,
we're like, "How steady do
your hands have to be for that?"
His timeline...
Let's add this up.
Unless
he graduated college late...
YAM YAM:
He's a year or younger than me.
SARAH:
I know, he's 34. So he said,
"Right after college,
I took two years
"trying to get into med school.
"It didn't work.
That was in 2020."
That timeline is...
Yeah.
I love strong people, and I love
strength, and I love everything.
I hate your lying to me.
Josh makes me very nervous.
So, if it comes down
to voting him off,
I'm down with it.
Like, I would be the first one
writing his name down.
- Carson's over here.
- What?
- Why is it Carson?
- Oh, my gosh. - Carson's here?
MATTHEW: Young man!
I guess we have a story
to hear from you.
- We haven't officially met. Brandon.
- Brandon.
BRANDON: I'm taken back.
I'm thinking, "Is he here
for a couple hours?
Is this permanent?"
What is he going to tell us?
Is he gonna tell us the truth?
CARSON: And I go to, like,
this, like, platform,
and it says, "Switch tribes."
I was like, "That's not really
a congratulations."
[laughter]
Picking up a new buff
and realizing
I'm gonna be on Ratu...
I'm kind of nervous.
So I really want
to paint a perception
of Tika being led by Yam Yam
and downplay
how strategic I am
so that they're going to see me
as a number
that they can pull in.
When I saw that I was switching,
I was actually
very excited because
I was pretty sure I was next.
You know, Carolyn and Yam Yam...
I kind of saw them as a pair.
- Yeah.
- We were thinking that Yam Yam was running the show.
LAUREN:
Running the show over there.
Well, he kind of is.
I think... I think so.
MATTHEW:
My heart sank when I found out
that Carson was going
to be our new tribe member
because I had put so much
legwork into getting Jaime
to my alliance.
Now I have to put
in some groundwork
with Carson
because information in this game
is power,
and I am ready to load him up
on some powerful information.
I just wanted to, like,
build some trust with you
- and give you some knowledge.
- Yeah.
Like, Brandon played the idol
on the first night,
and he already opened
the birdcage.
- What?
- Yeah.
That's crazy.
And after the idol was played,
it goes back into rotation.
Yeah.
MATTHEW: I think me and Carson
have the ability
to have a good connection,
and so I planted a seed
by telling him that Jaime had
a hidden immunity idol,
which is fake,
but he doesn't know that.
So... you're...
I know, earlier, you shared
that Jaime had an idol,
so I definitely trust you.
MATTHEW: That information helped
build that bridge of trust
with Carson,
and that is a very satisfying
and reassuring feeling
to have because
I need personal numbers
to go far in this game.
- FRANNIE: Oh, my God.
- HEIDI: What?!
- Oh, my God. It's Jaime.
- Oh, Jaime's coming... - What?
JAIME: This is a huge
opportunity, coming over to Soka
and starting fresh.
I came, I saw, I conquered.
I did what I needed to do
at Ratu,
and now my plan is
to do it here.
Hi, family!
Well, welcome to our home!
JAIME: I'm super nervous.
I don't know what to expect.
But I have two idols,
so coming into a new tribe,
that is a lot of power.
- So I am the new Josh.
- [laughter] - New Josh.
I'm Jaime,
but I am the new member
- of Soka tribe officially.
- Wow. Cool. Welcome.
- MATT: Okay.
- Welcome.
JAIME: Yes. So happy to be here.
FRANNIE:
My first impression of Jaime
is that she's really open and
kind and friendly with everyone.
But the bad news is
that the one person
that we really didn't trust
is the person
who she swapped out with.
So that gives us
an easy position
to just vote Jaime out
right away.
The only thing
that throws a real wrench is
if Jaime has
a hidden immunity idol.
- MATT: I don't know.
- Can she prevent us from voting her out?
What if she found the idol
and brought it here?
FRANNIE: Danny, if you're...
- If that's your... If you're willing, I'll watch.
- Sure.
DANNY: I think that
if Jaime has nothing,
and we can vote her out,
if we went to Tribal,
it would be a clear-cut vote.
But the fact that Jaime might
have something is a problem.
So I took the liberty
of going through her bag
to see
if there's anything there.
You certainly feel very low
going
through a person's goods, but
we're on Survivor, and
the rules of normal,
ethical actions
don't apply here,
at least not in my book.
And we're reading my book.
I gave it
a fairly diligent search.
Like, I just bent everything.
Well, definitely...
She definitely
doesn't have an idol.
MATT:
I'm not convinced that Jaime
doesn't have some sort
of advantage.
And even if she does,
everyone is so committed
to staying Soka strong
that Jaime has
pretty much no shot
in the next few days.
♪ ♪
Good morning.
Oh, Ratu coming strong
with the sword.
Ah!
PROBST: That is a battle cry.
- SARAH: Yes.
- PROBST: You got the new Ratu tribe.
They're letting you know,
"Here we are."
All right.
Shall we get
to your first immunity challenge
as new tribes?
- [all assenting]
- All right.
First things first.
Got to take back
the sword, Lauren.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to dive
into the ocean,
one person at a time,
climb to the top
of a tall tower,
then leap off it
while grabbing a key.
You'll then cross
a floating balance beam
and race to the finish.
Then the next person goes.
Once all four players are
at the end,
two players will use the keys
to unlock your pieces
and solve a manta ray puzzle.
First two tribes
to finish win immunity,
safe from Tribal Council.
Losers... Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the fifth person voted out.
In addition,
as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Soka, you are
working to get yours back.
All right, sit-outs.
Soka, you have one extra person.
Who you gonna sit out?
Jaime's going
to sit this one out.
Ratu, same thing.
Who's going to sit out?
- I will.
- Matthew's going to sit out.
All right, Jaime, Matthew,
take a spot
on the sit-out benches.
Everybody else,
we'll give you a minute
to strategize. Let's get it on.
Let's do it!
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors, ready?
- Go!
- [overlapping shouting]
PROBST:
It's Josh in the water for Tika.
JAIME: Attaboy, Danny!
- PROBST: Danny for Soka.
- JAIME: Yeah, you got it.
PROBST: Brandon for Ratu.
Josh gets up that ladder
quickly.
Now you got to leap.
Josh has his!
Danny has one. Brandon has one.
Now comes the tricky part...
The balance beam.
Josh doesn't hesitate.
Danny's on it.
Here goes Brandon.
- MATTHEW: Yeah, Brandon. You got this!
- PROBST: Brandon's good!
- [whooping]
- Come on, Brandon!
Danny drops. You got to go back
to the start, Danny.
- SARAH: Yeah, Josh!
- Josh is good for Tika.
Brandon's back. You're good.
Go, Ratu!
- Carson has a key!
- MATTHEW: Yeah!
PROBST: Thataway, Danny.
Danny's across the balance beam.
Here comes Josh.
You're good! Go!
Sarah going to go for a key.
- Sarah's got one.
- CAROLYN: Go, Sarah!
PROBST:
Carson across the balance beam.
Danny's back for Soka.
You're good, Soka.
- Here goes Matt.
- HEIDI: Yeah, Matt, you got it.
PROBST:
Matt jumps and has his key.
FRANNIE: Yes, Matt!
- PROBST: Carson back.
- All right, let's go.
- Go, Ratu! Here goes Lauren.
- BRANDON: Let's go, Lauren!
- Come on, Lauren!
- PROBST: That's a big jump.
If you've never done it,
it can be scary.
Come on! Come on!
PROBST: Lauren taking time.
There she goes.
- Oh!
- PROBST: She misses it and does a big belly flop.
She is not going to go back,
which means
somebody else will have
to do the entire run.
Sarah's... Go!
Tika, you're good.
Yam Yam jumps.
Yam Yam has the key.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- PROBST: Here comes Matt for Soka.
You're good, Soka.
Here goes Heidi.
She's got a key.
Yes, Heidi!
- There you go.
- JAIME: Yes!
All right, you're good.
One of you two got to go.
One of you two.
Brandon now has to swim back out
to get another key
to recover for Lauren.
It is a big setback for Ratu.
Heidi's across the balance beam.
- Here goes Yam Yam.
- CAROLYN: You got it, Yam Yam!
PROBST:
Brandon's got a long swim now.
Heidi's back. You're good, Soka.
Here goes Frannie.
She's got a key easily.
Frannie!
PROBST: Here goes
Brandon, gathering his energy.
MATTHEW:
You got it, Brandon! Good job.
PROBST: He's got the key.
Now he's got to swim it back.
Ratu is still in there.
- Aah! - Yes!
- And Yam Yam drops.
- Hustle back!
- Big setback for Tika.
That opens the door for Ratu.
We are looking for two tribes.
Frannie made that beam
look easy.
Yam Yam's got to start over.
It is Yam Yam and Brandon
side by side.
- Brandon has caught Yam Yam now.
- MATTHEW: Good job, Brandon!
- Good job.
- PROBST: You're good, Soka.
Two people on the puzzle.
Yes. Brandon's across the beam.
- It is now Tika dead last.
- SARAH: Keep going, Yam Yam!
PROBST: Yam Yam on that beam.
You got it, Yam Yam!
PROBST: It is Heidi and
Matt doing the puzzle for Soka,
with a big time advantage.
Brandon still working to get up.
Exhausted.
Go, Ratu! Here goes Kane.
Kane has a key.
Carolyn waiting on Yam Yam
to get to the end of the course.
Yam Yam, you're close.
CARSON: Nice. You're
almost there, buddy. Yes!
PROBST: Yam Yam's
across. You're good.
- Nice belly flop.
- LAUREN: Yes!
PROBST:
Kane drops. He's got to go back.
You're good, Tika. Go, Carolyn.
YAM YAM: Go, Carolyn!
PROBST: Carolyn has
her key. That's half of it.
MATTHEW: Do it, Kane.
PROBST:
Kane trying it again. Punched.
Carolyn could catch Kane
and put Tika back in this
because Kane is going
to drop again.
YAM YAM: Go, Carolyn!
Heidi and Matt with a big
time advantage for Soka.
Carolyn step by step.
Carolyn can put Tika back
in the lead right here.
Carolyn has it easily.
And it is Tika back
in the lead now as Kane
feels the pressure of that beam.
Let's go, Kane, get across.
PROBST: Get it in here, Carolyn,
before you can start working.
Let's go. You're good, Tika. Go!
It's going to be Sarah and Josh
on the puzzle for Tika.
Kane is almost there.
BRANDON:
Let's go, Kane, let's go.
- Yes!
- Nice, Kane! Let's go!
Here comes Kane for Ratu.
Now they're going to get a shot
at the puzzle.
You're good! Go, Ratu!
Now Ratu on the puzzle.
Going to be Carson and Lauren.
It would be a gigantic comeback
for Ratu,
- given their setbacks.
- HEIDI: This one goes here.
- And then a side piece might...
- Soka looking very good
in a commanding lead right now,
with Ratu and Tika vying
for second place.
Josh joining a new tribe,
trying to make
a good first impression.
Carson also on a new tribe,
trying to make
a good first impression.
It's all over for Soka.
They've got the victory.
You've got it, Heidi and Matt.
PROBST: Down to
their last couple of pieces.
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- There it is for Soka!
Soka wins immunity.
Nobody going home.
- Jaime heads over.
- [cheering]
Now the race is on.
We are very close.
Too close to call right now.
- This one.
- PROBST: Ratu's made up a lot of time.
- KANE: Good job, Lauren!
- PROBST: They got a shot!
Josh with another for Tika.
Another piece
by Lauren for Ratu.
- Come on, guys. Come on.
- We are neck and neck,
side by side.
Next to the tail.
To the left. To the left. There.
CAROLYN: You got it! You
got it! You guys are so close!
We are within one or two pieces.
Carson with another for Ratu.
- There's one for Tika.
- CAROLYN: You got it! You got it! You got it!
- PROBST: And another for Tika!
- Oh.
PROBST: We are neck and neck,
coming down
to the last few pieces.
- BRANDON: Yup. There you go.
- Six pieces for Tika.
KANE:
Come on, guys. Come on, guys.
- CAROLYN: Over there, Josh. Josh.
- There's another for Ratu.
And another.
Ratu down to two pieces.
Tika falling out of it.
BRANDON: Come here, Lauren!
Come here, Lauren! Come here!
There it is! Ratu pulls off
a huge comeback,
sending Tika to Tribal Council.
That was an epic finish.
Wow.
Soka, huge victory.
Nice job. Immunity is yours.
Nobody going home.
- DANNY: Look what your mama did.
- Yes!
Soka, in addition,
you've earned back your flint.
- Thank you. - Yes.
- Yeah.
Ratu, great example of why you
never give up in a challenge.
I know you want that, Lauren.
All right, Ratu, Soka,
no Tribal Council.
Nobody going home. Swim on out.
Enjoy the night off.
Wow. I give that an 11.
[Lauren laughs]
PROBST:
Tika, Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be the fifth
person voted out of Survivor 44,
and as a penalty for losing,
gonna take your flint.
Sorry for you.
All right, Tika, swim out.
See you tonight at Tribal.
JOSH: Heading back to
camp, I still don't feel 100%
with this group.
I just met them yesterday,
and I do have an immunity idol,
and having that in my
back pocket will be beneficial.
But I'm nervous.
This is the biggest moment
of Survivorfor me.
If you think you have what it
takes to come out here and play
this game, what are you waiting
on? Apply to be on Survivor.
YAM YAM:
Watching them do that puzzle
and not making any progress...
[groans] - JOSH: I'm
gonna take a dip in the pool.
YAM YAM: But I'm
thinking, game on, you know?
It's either me or you, baby.
And it's not going to be me.
We need to keep
three of us strong.
SARAH:
Yeah. He goes first... Josh.
YAM YAM: I think
it's in our best interest
to make the merge
with four Tikas,
but Josh is not Tika, so...
we need to vote out Josh.
So don't get offended by that.
It's all good, man.
It's not like the first time
you've ever said that.
- And that's what we're doing.
- CAROLYN: Yeah.
I'm always the decoy vote.
"Here, Carolyn.
"Here's your plan.
"Here's how you're going
to stay safe another day.
"You're gonna vote with us,
and we're going to go
and we'll vote out Josh."
CAROLYN: "But we got
to make Josh feel comfortable,
so you just keep
doing your thing."
I'm done with that. I'm done.
I understand completely
why you're scared,
but, like...
- we want to play with you.
- YAM YAM: Yeah.
- We do.
- Right.
SARAH: Yeah.
- I-I want that for us.
- YAM YAM: Yeah.
And I-I hope
I can trust you guys tonight.
- SARAH: Yeah.
- YAM YAM: Yeah.
SARAH: My main goal is
to make Josh feel comfortable
that we're voting out Carolyn,
but if he has an idol,
he's probably going to play it.
In that case, I would
immediately play my idol,
but I want to see Josh go home,
I don't want him
to play an idol,
and that would be
a magical happy ending.
I don't feel like that.
They're acting like...
- I know that that's not true.
- Right.
I can't really trust
Yam Yam and Sarah.
They've been together
for eight-plus days,
and I'm just coming in new.
I was in a good position
with Soka.
So my goal now is
to get back to Soka and
continue on to merge.
- Sound good?
- Yeah. Yeah.
JOSH: Carolyn is on the outs.
They don't really mesh well
with her.
So I'm dropping seeds
in Carolyn's head
that Yam Yam and Sarah
are trying to vote you out.
Yeah. Yeah.
JOSH: I need her to trust me
so that we can get Sarah out
because she is a big threat.
CAROLYN: Want to
see what it look... [gasps]
JOSH:
Carolyn can be voted out later,
and I don't think Yam Yam
and Carolyn really get along,
so I think
it's my best option
at this point.
- Let's do this. Okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
CAROLYN: I'm shocked
because I have an immunity idol,
and Josh also has a hidden
immunity idol, and he wants
to play his idol on me.
But I just know I'm gonna lose
Yam Yam's trust.
But, like,
they don't do a great job
of making me feel
like I'm in with them.
So why would I have any loyalty
to them is how I feel right now.
YAM YAM:
We are telling him it's you.
You feel good?
SARAH:
Yeah, we have to be solid.
CAROLYN: I did not
come out here to be told
what every plan was.
Like, that's not going
to get me anywhere.
I'm trying to weigh this out.
Do I let Josh play this idol
for me,
and then Josh goes home, or
do I tell Josh, "Hey,
play that idol on yourself."
"Me and you vote Sarah,
and she is gone"?
I'm battling in my head.
"Be logical, don't be emotional.
"You don't need to be
in control right now," versus.
"No, stand up
and do something for yourself."
I'm doing what I am confident
in my heart, in my gut is
the best for me.
♪ ♪
PROBST: All right, let's
start with the obvious.
Josh, did you consider
when you went on the journey
that "maybe I won't come back"?
Honestly,
I was completely shocked.
Um, I went from
a really good position at Soka
to the bottom
of the barrel here.
So I'm extremely nervous
at this Tribal Council.
PROBST:
So, Sarah, this could be simple.
"We just vote out Josh.
We don't even know him.
We don't owe him anything."
Right, but then
he's got four BFFs
on the other tribe right now,
and come merge time,
that could be valuable
if we were
to move forward with him.
PROBST:
Yam Yam, how about for you?
Yeah, he's like
the new kid in the classroom.
You know?
Like, maybe I had a friend
in the classroom that we were
really good friends with,
but I don't want
to be her friend anymore.
Um, and I want... that's...
Well,
what are you trying to say?
- Are you...?
- YAM YAM: Like, the new kid
- in the classroom...
- But the new kid
in the classroom isn't a her.
YAM YAM: No, no, no, I'm
just saying it, like, as an idea.
I'm not saying
that Yam Yam is saying,
"Bye, Felicia." You know?
- I'm just saying.
- Who's Felicia?
[laughter]
PROBST: So, Carolyn,
your face right now.
- I'm Felicia.
- PROBST: Oh, you'reFelicia?
And you think
he's talking about you?
I think he made a slip
that he regrets making.
- When he said "her"?
- Yeah.
YAM YAM: It's normal
for this to happen with us.
I say some things
that I'm thinking
they're going to sound all cute
and funny, and I-I...
I hit the wall
and I offended her again.
- You know?
- Sarah, you were nodding.
SARAH: Yes. There is
occasional misunderstanding,
I would say, in the words
that Yam Yam uses
and how Carolyn perceives them.
I disagree.
I think that that was a slip
that you didn't want to make.
[laughs]
I disagree to your disagreement.
- Okay.
- This is great news for me. I like chaos.
I'm just doing what I can just
to not have the focus on me,
but on their previous issues.
CAROLYN: Yeah, he can
pick up on this. In a game
where you're supposed
to hide, like,
fighting,
or if you're not getting along,
we don't care,
we put it out there.
JOSH: But even with
that, maybe this whole thing
was just a charade, you know,
just to knock me off my game.
And yet you have
to find somebody to trust in.
Yeah,
and there are certain people
that I feel like I can trust
and others that I can't trust.
Sarah, we're only nine days in.
Is it even possible
to trust anybody?
All you have is
what you're telling people
and hoping that they trust it
and they go in on the plan.
PROBST: Carolyn, I'm
sensing some uneasiness.
[laughs]
You pull your eye... Your-your
eyes go back in your head.
It's so hard. It's so hard.
PROBST: And so what's your pitch
as to why you should stay?
I've been
with this tribe a lot longer.
They-they know me.
We have those connections.
Um, he is the new guy.
Yam Yam,
that's a legitimate pitch.
"I'm loyal, I'm here,
- "I wear purple."
- YAM YAM: Yeah.
That has a lot of value,
what she's saying.
But like Sarah said,
the connections that Josh has
on the other tribe of people
that I want to know and meet
are very powerful.
Yeah. Well, who's left?
- Felicia.
- [laughter]
So it, like...
Is this all an act?
Like, I don't know.
PROBST: So, Josh,
as we get ready to vote,
do you feel that you've said
everything you need to say?
I think I've said everything
I need to say.
I've had my conversations
that I need to have,
and the information
that was said back and forth,
I think, is pretty honest
and open and ready to go.
Is everybody ready to vote?
YAM YAM:
Is there any other questions?
- [laughs]
- CAROLYN: Oh.
Just, yeah,
put me out of my misery.
[Sarah laughs]
You sure?
All right, it is
time to vote. Josh, you're up.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Jeff? [Laughs]
I don't want
to take any chances,
so I'm going
to play my hidden immunity idol.
For myself.
Okay. Thank you.
This isa hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast
for Josh will not count.
All right, I'll read the votes.
♪ ♪
First vote... Josh.
Does not count.
- Josh.
- JOSH: Wow.
- Does not count.
- Wow. Knew it.
Sarah. One vote... Sarah.
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor 44...
...Sarah. Need
to bring me your torch.
Sarah, the tribe has spoken.
- Time for you to go.
- SARAH: Thank you.
Pick up your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
MATTHEW: I've literally been
training to be here
for, like, eight years,
but I wake up in so much pain.
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
FRANNIE: She doesn't know
that Matt and I are really close.
CARSON:
Everyone is sharing with me,
and it gives me a lot of power.
CAROLYN: Those two... oh!
Dude, what's up
with the bitch face?
I kept trying to tell myself not
to worry and held onto the idol.
I didn't think he was going to
vote for me, and it was stupid.
It's miserable going home
with the idol in your pocket.
I join a special club
of sad, sad people
because I had the ticket to keep
going, and I didn't use it.
I got played.
[roars]