♪ ♪
DANNY: Just got back
from Tribal Council, and, uh,
contrary to what usually happens
in this game, everything went
exactly to plan.
All the votes went on Frannie.
I played the idol for her.
- I'm gonna play this for Frannie.
- Okay.
DANNY: And we got Brandon out.
Brandon.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
DANNY: To play an idol is,
you know,
it's on everybody'sSurvivor
bucket list,
and for it to go as planned...
It's a good feeling.
Was that not the most
boss move ever? Like, iconic.
- Really good move.
- Oh, my God.
DANNY: Everybody was
afraid of the former Ratu tribe
just bulldozering
their way through, so,
the game plan was
to weaken Ratu.
Just wanted to even everything
out, you know, so...
And now it's three Tika,
three Soka,
three, uh... three Ratu.
We're all
on an even playing field,
so it worked perfectly.
Deep in my soul, I kept saying,
"We need to split the vote.
- We need to split the vote," and we did not.
- DANNY: I know.
- No one wanted to listen, so...
- DANNY: That's exactly... Yeah.
...whatever.
I did not see
that vote coming tonight. My boy
was blindsided.
It is not a great feeling
to have to lose one
of our Ratu members.
That means
that our numbers are dwindling.
JAIME: Every single
person did want to do a split.
- KANE: Every...
- Mm-hmm.
- And it was Brandon that was saying no.
- LAUREN: Yeah.
- Well, lesson learned.
- Yep.
LAUREN: We should have split the
votes, but we didn't, but lucky for me,
I still feel like
I'm in the majority.
We have the members of Ratu,
in addition to
the Tika members, so hopefully
those bonds can stay strong
so that I can have numbers
going into the next Tribal.
It's like, yeah, we...
YAM YAM: Tribal just went
exactly as I expected it to go.
Ratu still thinks
I'm working with them
'cause I voted
with them against Frannie.
But in reality, I knew all along
Danny was going
to play the idol to protect her.
So, big target goes out,
no blood in my hands.
I'm good with both sides.
This is a good night for me.
I'm a little James Bond,
you know. Double-O Zero.
What is it? 0-0-7?
What? Stop it. No, no, no.
Look at this.
Josh, Matt, Brandon
all wrote my name down,
all have been gone
one after the other.
You put Yam Yam's name down,
and you think
you can get away with it...
That's not happening, you know?
[birds chirping]
I know.
Yeah, you feel kind of
in control.
Yeah.
KANE: To be honest,
as soon as Brandon was removed
from this game,
I wasn't, like, heartbroken.
I wasn't betrayed.
I was woken up.
The idea is that there
are idols back on this beach.
So I put my business pants on,
and I'm going to work now.
In Dungeons & Dragons,
everybody plays on the same side
against a common enemy.
So, the common enemy in Survivor
is the big threat.
And Danny is growing
into a big threat.
He's made a big move,
and I know that Danny's going
to keep trying
to make these big moves
and keep his foot on the gas
until somebody rips him
out of the car.
DANNY: I could have let
Frannie go and kept the idol
and played a defensive game,
but this game is not won
playing a comfortable game.
You got to go outside
your comfort zone. I'm really
uncomfortable now...
I don't have my idol anymore.
And I guarantee
making such a big move
put a target on my back,
so I would like
to find another one.
Dan, you are good
at finding firewood, my friend.
I do my best.
I'm trying
to be somewhat subtle,
but at the end of the day,
I don't really care.
The shy part
of looking for idols...
That part of the game is over.
Yeah.
JAIME: I need to find the idol,
well, because I want two idols.
Can you believe that?
I still have my idol.
[laughing]:
How do I still have my idol?
I'm so happy,
I still have my idol.
How do I still have my idol?
Oh, my God.
LAUREN: Everyone is
searching at this point.
It is no secret.
Everyone's out looking.
LAUREN: Every single person.
DANNY: Finding an idol...
It's a game of chance,
but this is one
of those games of chance
that you can
put the odds in your favor
with effort.
So, ultimately,
my goal is to outwork them,
and I intend to do that.
HEIDI: Oh, my God.
This is the best moment yet.
I just found
a hidden immunity idol.
I hope no one saw me because
this could be
a double-edged sword
'cause now I have power.
People are gonna
come for me 'cause
they're gonna try to flush it.
So my plan is
to not tell anybody,
but this is real, and I'm
extremely excited.
This is like a bucket list item,
and I'm extremely happy.
♪ ♪
YAM YAM: Is there a game
we could play? Like Veo, Veo?
Veo, Veois, like,
you say a letter
and then everybody has
to guess what it is.
Like I Spy,
but you get a letter?
Yeah, it's called Veo, Veo,
like, in Spanish.
- So, I Spy. You start, Frannie.
- FRANNIE: I'll start?
- YAM YAM: Frannie.
- No.
No.
YAM YAM:
After 16 days of being here,
it's good we have, like,
an off day, you know?
Does it really work to talk,
talk, talk, talk, talk, talk,
talk, talk, talk, talk,
talk game?
At what point
you're going to chill? Never?
Keep going.
FRANNIE: No.
- LAUREN: Firewood.
- FRANNIE: Yes.
- LAUREN: Yay!
- Firewood. - Yes.
That was fast.
Okay. "S."
- [laughs] Ass?
- YAM YAM: Ass.
- What's the letter?
- "S."
[laughter]
Why are you guys
making fun of me?
Your face. She goes like, "Ass."
- We need some speech therapy.
- [laughter]
"Ass."
I don't know why
I'm doing it like that... "ass."
Today we had time
to just connect with each other.
That's my favorite part
of the game.
When we're not
playing at up. We just
got real.
Some of you guys have obviously
heard my story, but
I just celebrated 13 years sober
right before coming out here.
- LAUREN: Yeah.
- HEIDI: Congratulations.
- That's awesome.
- CAROLYN: Thank you. And
I think it's hard for people
to understand, too.
Like, people who come from
seemingly, like, "normal..."
- Mm-hmm.
- ...childhoods and normal upbringings,
like, you can get addicted.
Like, you know, it doesn't,
like... It doesn't discriminate.
I'm an open book
in real life and here.
And my addiction... it's a part
of my story,
and it-it no longer is something
that I'm ashamed of.
It's just a part of me
and made me who I am today.
The preoccupation that, like,
comes with, like, okay,
"Well, I-I...
well, I got to have
- "my drink first, or I got to..."
- JAIME: Yeah.
Oh, there's so much involved
in that
that is so exhausting.
I messed up.
I made a lot of mistakes,
but it's like
that wasn't me, but
I didn't know, like, who I was.
And so getting sober
and going to treatment...
I started to like my life.
Then I met my fiancé in...
at an AA meeting.
- And...
- Someone who's also recovering.
Yeah, and it's literally been
like, poof ever since.
[crying]: Yeah,
I'm proud as hell of myself.
I never thought I would have,
you know, a family
and this wonderful son
and, like...
everything. I look at my house,
and I decorate for Halloween...
[sniffles]
and it looks creepy as ...,
but it's everything
that I wanted.
It's like... [sniffles]
...I have everything
that I need.
What, like, we're both grateful
for is that, like,
our son never has to see, like,
- us addicted.
- HEIDI: Yeah.
CAROLYN: Like, he sees
the recovery side of things.
- And, like, I can get up on a Sunday.
- HEIDI: Yes.
CAROLYN: We can go to church.
We can do whatever, and it's
like we're not struggling
to get up and get out of bed.
We feel better,
and I can just be present.
FRANNIE: I love
Carolyn. She's so herself.
She's the kind of person
that I want to be around
because that's something
that I'm trying to work on.
Right? Being more myself
and being okay
being, like, weird or out there.
And looking at Carolyn,
I'm like,
"Man, I can learn a lot
from her."
Who here has felt like
the weird kid before?
- Yeah. - I think all of us.
- All of us.
Doesn't matter
where you come from.
Doesn't matter, like,
how cute you are with makeup.
- Right.
- Like, we all had those moments.
It's crazy how each day
I'm getting my footing more.
When I came here, they all said,
"I don't know
if we can work with her."
How are my teeth?
CAROLYN: And so now
people aren't suspecting anything.
They think I'm confused.
Itches. Itches.
I can't. I can't.
- [Frannie laughs]
- I got to put this down.
I've had to work past that,
like, insecurity,
and I'm not caring so much
about, like,
how people look at me or how...
'cause I can't control that.
And part of it, too, like,
I want people to think
that I really don't know
what I'm doing.
Am I having fun? Of course I am.
- That's scary.
- [Frannie whooping]
CAROLYN: But I want them
to think that
I would rather be having fun
than actually strategizing.
But I'm here to play,
and I don't care. I'm not
holding anything back. I'm not.
I promised my son I wouldn't.
[birds singing]
CARSON:
This morning, when I woke up,
I felt more tired than I was
when I went to bed last night.
I mean, the last couple of days
in terms of how I'm feeling
have been a roller coaster, but
at least I don't feel like
I'm gonna throw up all the time.
- Are you feeling okay?
- CARSON: Oh, yeah, like,
I think, like,
my stomach doesn't hurt at all
right now, but, like,
my energy levels are so low.
CAROLYN: Oh, yum.
- Carson?
- HEIDI: Have you had BM?
CAROLYN:
You want, like, the last sip?
FRANNIE: Yeah, the
coconut water, I feel like, has,
like, electrolytes and sugars.
CARSON: We are really hungry.
I know, for myself,
I haven't eaten
in literally days, and so I have
nothing in my body.
Should we try
to get 'em crispier?
- Ooh, yeah.
- Yeah, way thinner
so we can't
even taste what this is
- 'cause I'm sick of it.
- Yeah.
CARSON: We just kind of find
unripe papaya and, like,
cook it and just
char it. It's pretty gross.
And we don't have
that many coconuts.
So we're really
literally starving.
But I signed up for this, I knew
I was going to be miserable.
It is what it is. It's Survivor.
[singsongy]:
We've got tree mail!
- [whooping]
- LAUREN: All right.
- CAROLYN: Awesome.
- LAUREN: Va-va-voom.
- HEIDI: Ready?
- CARSON: All right.
[Heidi sighs]
"This challenge
is relatively painless
unless you're craving rice..." Oh, gosh.
- HEIDI: Oh.
CARSON: "...because
you will feel the sting
when you negotiate the price."
LAUREN: This morning
the tree mail mentioned
that we can negotiate for rice.
So,
as we've seen
in past Survivorseasons,
we have to have enough people
willing to give up their shot
at winning immunity
to get that rice.
YAM YAM: Do we have
people that want to sit out?
I haven't even really been able
to compete in an immunity,
- so I want to.
- HEIDI: Yeah.
But I'm also really hungry.
If I see it and I'm like,
"I don't think
I'm gonna be good at that,"
- I'm fine with, like...
- HEIDI: Yeah, we can check it
after we see it just to see.
DANNY: There's some
nonsense idea out there
that people are going to not do
an immunity challenge for rice.
It's embarrassing
every time I hear it.
I don't even want
to be standing there with them
when it's brought up 'cause we
came out here to playSurvivor.
You can go 30 days
without eating.
- CARSON: And I'll see the challenge. It's...
- I'm hungry,
- but I'm not sitting out.
- KANE: Yeah.
DANNY: Let's call a
spade a spade right now.
We're three, three and three.
- Yeah.
- DANNY: Everybody's
relatively even,
so let's just play the game.
FRANNIE: At this point,
there's three members
of each of the original
three tribes.
And Tika has kind of
been floating in the middle,
it feels.
Because of that,
I don't know for sure
that Tika is with us,
so that's not a sacrifice
that I'm willing to make.
DANNY:
Let's be the season that says,
- "We're players."
- CAROLYN: Yeah.
Let's-let's be that season.
- So...
- FRANNIE: Yeah.
CARSON:
People on this tribe are so
gung ho
about not giving up their spot.
So we'll see what will happen,
but, like,
I'm hungry. [Laughs]
[thunder cracking]
Come on in.
♪ ♪
Now it's Survivor.
Now you know you're here.
Decent bit of rain,
some people already shivering.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
First things first.
Lauren, got to take back
the necklace. I know.
- You can win it back.
- [laughs softly]
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
going to stand on a small block
while balancing a ball
on an overhanging piece of wood.
If at any point, the ball drops,
but you fall off the block,
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final eight.
Losers, Tribal Council
where somebody
will be the tenth person
voted out
and the third member
of our jury.
All right, so this morning
you got tree mail
telling you, you would have
the opportunity
to sit out of this challenge
and give up
your shot at immunity in
exchange for rice for the tribe.
Have you discussed this?
Are you interested
in negotiating for rice?
We have discussed it,
but I would love to hear now,
you know, due to the conditions
and everything,
to see if anyone have changed
their mind.
I'll sit out
if anybody else wants to.
- I'll sit out. I'll sit out.
- So there's two people.
- Anybody else?
- Please.
- LAUREN: Anybody else?
- PROBST: So, we got Carson and Lauren.
I want four. Four people's the
number. You're halfway there.
Kane, let's talk about this
because the idea
of this negotiation
is really simple.
Will people give up the most
important thing in the game,
your shot at immunity,
in order for the tribe
to have rice?
Because the easy thing is
to say,
"We won't vote the four
of you out."
Yeah, it's about the balance.
It's about the balance
of reliance
and competition, and I think
that if the vote had gone
how I thought
it would have at last Tribal,
I would have been more willing
to step forward.
But I'm not certain
that four people will be.
I-I won't vote for the sit-outs.
You will not?
- Sure.
- PROBST: Okay.
I won't either. I mean,
I'm a part of that, but I won't.
I won't.
Okay, so Danny's saying,
"I won't vote if you sit out."
- Carolyn, did you just say that?
- Me, I won't.
Yeah, scout's honor.
I'll make three.
- Kane's at three.
- CAROLYN: So we're just one person.
PROBST: We're one person away.
Nobody else?
PROBST: Well, the rain is not
going to let up,
so we might as well get on
to this challenge
so you can get back
to your shelter.
And aren't you glad
you have that tarp?
- All right...
- Are you thinking about it?
- What?
- Wait.
- Please.
- Are you doing it, Jaime?
Don't do it
if you're hesitating. Play.
It's just too...
it's-it's too much to risk
right now in the game.
- Should I do it?
- You want to sit out?
I'll do it. I'll do the fourth.
Okay. So we have Carson, Heidi,
Kane and Lauren. Wow.
I never saw that negotiation
coming to a close like this.
Sit-outs, take a spot over here.
Let's take a look
at those willing to sacrifice.
For the community,
almost half the tribe is gonna
give up their shot
at certainty tonight in exchange
for a large bag of rice will...
- Give it your all.
- ...be waiting for you
back at camp, nice and dry.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started. Here we go.
All right,
everybody take your spots.
You can only have one foot
on that block,
which means your second foot
will be on top of your first.
Get ahold of the handles.
Wedge that ball up there,
and we will go.
All right, everybody looks good.
This challenge is on.
Five people competing,
four sat out for rice.
It's Frannie, Jaime,
Yam Yam, Danny and Carolyn.
This is already
- a very difficult challenge...
- Oh, my God.
...to do when it's dry,
let alone with the rain
making that ball wet.
Oh, my God.
You're balancing
on a small block,
knowing you can't let that
second foot touch the block,
- or you're out.
- Oh, my God.
PROBST:
There'll be no grace period.
Carolyn trying to hang in there.
That balance
on the block is tough.
[screams]
Carolyn is the first out.
- LAUREN: Good job, Carolyn.
- HEIDI: Great job, Carolyn.
- CAROLYN: Oh!
- It's okay.
- PROBST: She would not sit out.
- CAROLYN: I tried.
Jaime is out. We're down
to three just like that.
LAUREN: It's okay, Jaime.
PROBST: We are down to Frannie,
Yam Yam and Danny.
You're doing a great job.
This is a difficult challenge.
You saw how fast it can be over.
Jaime had one little slip,
and the ball was gone.
♪ ♪
Like every challenge,
keep reminding yourself
what you're doing.
♪ ♪
- It requires total concentration.
- [rolling thunder]
Tiny little muscles
are keeping you up there,
trying to stabilize you.
Yam Yam drops.
Yam Yam's out.
Be mindful of Danny
- as you get down. - Good job, Yam.
- Good job, Yam Yam.
We have a showdown.
It is Frannie and Danny.
Frannie's been
in a showdown before.
She won it the last time.
Can Frannie do it again,
or will Danny pull it out
this time?
You've been up there
a grand total of five minutes.
That's how tough
this challenge is.
I know it feels longer.
You keep fighting right now!
PROBST:
Try to control your body.
Don't let it control you.
I know you're cold, too.
This rain is miserable.
Just discomfort,
so push through it.
This is part
of the test of Survivor.
What do you have
in that tank right now?
- Breathe, Frannie, breathe.
- PROBST: You want the necklace.
LAUREN: You got this, Frannie.
HEIDI: Get in the zone, Fran.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh...
PROBST: Danny with a bit of
a wobble and a nice recovery.
Wow.
Rain's getting heavier now.
Fight it off.
I know you're cold.
Take control of it.
You're warriors out here.
Frannie with a nice recovery.
That's how you do it! You get
a little bit of a wobble,
you get back in control.
Tiny adjustments.
Danny drops.
Frannie wins her second
individual immunity
of Survivor 44.
- Good job, Frannie.
- Good job. - Wow.
Another great performance.
YAM YAM: Good job, Frannie.
That was hard.
HEIDI: Good job, Frannie.
LAUREN: Good job, Frannie.
- Frannie, come on over.
- [whooping]
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Second individual immunity win.
Once again, you are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final eight.
As for the rest of you,
tonight, Tribal Council.
Somebody will be
the tenth person voted out,
third member of our jury.
The good news,
if there is some, is you are
going back to a camp
that does have tarp,
and now,
thanks to the four of you,
a lot of rice.
Grab your stuff, head back
to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
- Congrats. - Thank you.
- Good job, Frannie.
- Thank you.
- Way to go, Frannie.
FRANNIE: I never thought
I would come out here
and do so well in challenges.
When I first landed
on the beach on day one,
I looked around
and I thought to myself,
"I think
I'm the weakest woman here."
To now go up against some
of the biggest guys in this game
and crush 'em
at these challenges,
it feels good.
This adventure could be yours.
Apply to be on Survivor.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
LAUREN: Is that our rice?
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- [whooping]
LAUREN: At the challenge,
four of us sat out for rice.
It was super risky, but I was
like, I don't care. Like,
I finally get to eat rice,
and it
is amazing.
FRANNIE:
Oh, it's gonna be so good!
- YAM YAM: Oh, my God.
- FRANNIE: Oh, my God.
JAIME: This is like a feast.
- CAROLYN: Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
KANE: But I don't think
I would have won that challenge,
so it made sense to sit out.
And the good news is
the people who stepped out
will not be voted out tonight.
[laughs] Yeah, right.
Danny giving me scout's honor
that he's not going
to vote for me
when he completely blindsided
my plan at last Tribal Council.
So, I mean, these people's word
means literally nothing to me.
JAIME: I'm so grateful.
Thank you guys so much.
YAM YAM: Eating rice woke
me up. Like, now I'm, like...
I'm ready to play.
But that's the dangerous thing.
Everybody's like that now.
Fortunately, there's a war
between Ratu and Soka,
and I'm in the middle
with Carson and Carolyn.
I mean, I don't care. I...
I think that we-we have
the majority right here, right?
HEIDI:
As soon as we came back to camp,
the Tika members were wanting
to work with us.
And I'm like, "Thank you,"
'cause Ratu...
We just got one of their
big guys... Brandon... out.
So they're not going
to trust me.
So we have a better chance
with Tika.
CARSON: Well, I'm...
Kane is extremely smart.
He is a gamer.
He's a big guy, so he could do
challenges very well.
So I think it's a good idea
to send Kane home today.
I don't plan to play my idol.
However, I'm bringing it
because I'm ready for anything.
Are you okay with that?
But we, for sure, need
to get Jaime
- to flush the idol.
- YAM YAM: Yes. - Yes.
CARSON: Because Soka and
Ratu are both targeting each other,
it leaves Tika in the middle.
So it all comes down
to Carolyn, Yam Yam and I,
and we just have to decide
who to work with.
But regardless,
we want to flush Jaime's idol.
Hello, Jaime.
- No. No.
- CARSON: But they...
- They-they are.
- Oh, okay.
- We're just trying to circumvent that, so...
- Okay.
- JAIME: We need to break up Soka, then.
- CARSON: Soka?
JAIME: They're
gonna take it to the end.
They're all physical threats.
So we have to split
between... Danny
- and Heidi, then.
- CARSON: Yeah.
LAUREN: I am extremely happy
that Danny didn't win immunity.
I want Danny
out of this game.
Danny got Brandon out.
He's a strong physical player,
so he needs to go.
But Danny may have found
another idol,
and the lesson learned
from the last.
Tribal Council is,
we should have split the vote.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
KANE: If... Yeah.
- Okay.
- Good?
JAIME: Worst-case scenario...
We get Heidi out, but I am
very fearful
that my name is out there.
I do have an idol,
which I've tried to suppress
as much as possible,
but at this point
everyone knows everything.
Okay.
Knowledge Is Power.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I'm quite confident
that we have Tika with us,
but the one thing that could go
wrong is the Knowledge Is Power.
We don't even know
if it's in this game,
but people are scared
of Knowledge Is Power
because at the Tribal Council,
it allows a player
to steal an idol or an advantage
if they know who has it.
JAIME: Okay.
KANE: Yeah, that works.
So, Jaime's going
to give me her idol.
So, that is good news
'cause if Jaime goes home,
then that's my idol now.
So, we'll trade these back
sometime after.
Yeah. Yep. Excellent.
So this is the debut of
Kane Fritzler, the strategist,
because I have not voted someone
off this island yet.
And if I want
to win this damn game,
I got
to start voting people out.
FRANNIE:
At this point, it's become clear
that the three Tika members
are kind of
floating in the middle, and
if we don't do something about
it, at the end of the day,
Tika's going to be left,
and we'll be on the jury bench.
So, even though we know
that the old Ratu members
have idols and advantages,
rather than trying to vote them
out, we need to work with them.
- DANNY: Yeah.
- FRANNIE: So let's do this.
DANNY: Frannie wants to get
rid of Yam Yam and Carolyn.
Frannie, I love you, but you got
to play the game smart.
Working with Ratu...
I mean, that's sleeping under
the wing of a dragon right now
with two advantages.
It's not good gameplay.
Tika has no threats right now.
Ratu has an extra vote advantage
and-and an idol.
Just...
To me, feels like Frannie's
taking sides against the family.
CARSON: We got to think,
what is the best move
for the three of us here?
In my mind...
YAM YAM: Since the merge,
Josh, Matt,
Brandon voted for me,
and they're sitting
at the jury now.
You write my name down,
you're dead.
And the other person that
wrote my name down was Kane.
So I want to work
with Soka to take him out.
Let's go through the options.
- So that's why...
- I disagree.
- Like, what...?
- I think he is.
I'm trying to think, like, well,
what is the best, like, for me?
Yam Yam wants Kane out.
"Kane's this big threat."
I don't see it.
'Cause he's sneaky?
We're all sneaky.
It's so stupid.
I want to vote out Danny.
I have ever since
the muscle bro thing.
I'm sick of him. That's why
I'm voting him out, okay?
I just feel, we have the numbers
to legitimately get Danny.
Yeah, we do.
That's what I'm saying.
- If you... if that's not what you were thinking...
- So it's like...
CARSON:
Yam Yam wants to take out Kane,
but Carolyn really wants
to work with Ratu
and take out Danny.
So we have to make a decision,
and by being in the middle,
Tika has a lot of power, and
as long as I can keep the old.
Tika members together
to vote as a collective group,
we pretty much control
this vote.
Well, that's why
we have each other, so...
That's what I'm...
That's what I have been doing.
CARSON: The Three
Stooges are running this game.
It's crazy. So,
there's a lot
of different names on the table,
and we just have to decide
who we want to go home.
♪ ♪
PROBST: All right, let's
start with the challenge.
Frannie pulls out
her second individual
immunity win. Congratulations.
Heidi, the other big event
at the challenge was,
we had our rice negotiation.
We end up with four people...
You,
Lauren, Carson
and Kane all agree
to sit out of the challenge.
Still feel okay
with your decision
after being at camp all day?
HEIDI:
In all honesty, it was like
a last-second decision
fr-from me.
I'm a competitor.
I wanted to compete, too.
But I don't regret it.
I'm moving forward. Hopefully,
I don't go home today.
PROBST: Kane, one of the
things that was talked about
at the challenge was this idea
that four people volunteer
and everybody else says,
"For tonight you're safe."
KANE:
Yeah, I don't believe that.
Um, you know, everybody gives
different levels of trust and
different levels of their word,
but there's all kinds of bonds
that get broken in this game.
I feel like rice negotiation
is low on the totem pole,
given all of the type of trust
that has been broken
in the history of Survivor.
I did hear Danny say
"Scout's honor."
Yeah, I'm not a scout, Jeff.
[laughter]
Wow.
DANNY: So, I hear a lot of this,
"Oh, you know, well,
it was for the tribe."
So, it's not for the tribe. It's
for yourself. You're hungry.
"Oh, I just wanted my people
to eat."
Okay, you can't eat,
the other eight can.
Will you still sit out?
You'll get, "No."
KANE: I don't know if I
agree with that completely.
For me, it was just
risk assessment.
I saw that challenge,
and I did not think
it was going to happen.
The second best thing
I can do for myself
is get rice, and if other people
were willing to do it,
I was going
to take that step forward.
PROBST:
Jaime, this is fundamentally
why Survivor'sso interesting.
Every season is different
because the players
are different,
and they decide, "These are the
norms, these are the values."
- Where do you sit in this?
- JAIME: I think
you have these
opposite-side-of-the-spectrum
opinions on what it means
to sit out
for the greater good
of the tribe.
It tells you a lot
about the individual
and how
they're playing the game.
Danny?
Oh, yeah. I mean,
agree to disagree. [Laughs]
[laughter]
PROBST:
Carolyn, how about for you?
CAROLYN: Jeff, we
weren't even talking about
who sat out and who didn't
sit out because that rice
changed everything.
As soon as we got that rice,
we were...
Oh, we were different people,
right?
- We felt human again. Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
It changed us.
- Wow.
- And it made us even hungrier.
And I can see some of us talking
probably on the way back.
We're going to want rice
on the way home.
[laughter]
PROBST: So, Yam Yam,
what was the vibe today?
Because the rice
lifts everybody's spirits,
but it also puts everybody's
brains back together.
So now you can
actually strategize
at your full capacity.
YAM YAM:
As soon as that rice was done,
we went back to who we are,
you know?
Talking about possibilities.
Who is it? Is it me?
I always think it's me,
you know?
So, it-it makes you
a little paranoid.
PROBST: Lauren, is it every
player for themselves now,
or are there still tribal groups
that are trying
to work together?
I think there are still
some bonds that are still there
within old tribes,
but I'm still thinking
about my individual game
and thinking about
who has lied to me
and who has not.
- Oh, oh, she went, "Lied to me."
- You have lied to me, though.
PROBST: Frannie, what is it
about Tribals like this
that make everybody
spark so much?
That adrenaline burst that says,
"Yes, it could be any of us,
"we really don't know,
and yet I can't wait to vote.
"I don't even know
who anyone else is voting for.
I don't care.
I just want to see."
It's-it's... I mean,
it's just like you said.
It's electric, you know? Like,
you walk around with somebody,
and they say,
"I'm gonna do this plan."
And you're like,
"Great, we're doing that plan."
And then
they walk with somebody else.
And I'm like, "Was that real?
Which plan is it?"
And so, at the end of the day,
sometimes
it's just the last plan.
HEIDI: Jeff, even if logically,
just by numbers,
you think you have it,
there may be a Shot in the Dark.
We have idols out there.
We have extra votes out there.
So none of us know what's going
to happen tonight until
you start reading those votes.
PROBST:
Jaime, it hits on the excitement
and the dread of this game,
and what makes it so alive is,
"It could be me."
JAIME: Yes. I'm listening
to everything because
I need to make sure
that the last conversation
I had was solid.
So I'm trying to pick up
what people are putting down.
- YAM YAM: I'm pretty sure everybody has a plan.
- [others assent]
It's just, the surprise
is going to be...
- Which one are we going...?
- [overlapping chatter]
And who's the "it," you know?
- Bye-bye. Hope it's not me.
- [laughter]
This is going to be good.
PROBST:
Kane, if you had your choice,
you could play a season
of Survivorlike this,
where it's chaotic
and it's crazy,
or you could play
a very quiet season of Survivor,
- which do you choose?
- Probably quiet.
- PROBST: Really?
- I'm just kidding.
I love the chaos. It's money.
I would 100 times out of 100
times choose the chaotic season
because, to me,
every single person
sitting here
is playing this game,
and that's what
makes me excited.
That's why I'm here.
I'm not here for a walk in Fiji.
PROBST: Danny, how about you?
When you're playing Survivor,
this is what you want, right?
DANNY: Yeah. I mean,
in the game of Survivor,
sometimes you're going
to be driving the car,
but sometimes
you got to be all ears
and, uh, just pick
which back seat to get into
and, you know,
survive Tribal always.
Well, with this group,
I tend to believe you
that you're listening
even right now
for somebody to say something
that doesn't ring true,
that might change your mind,
even the way
you're looking at me, Carolyn.
How certain are you
about your vote?
I feel worse coming here.
I mean, honestly,
everyone's telling me
that they're going
back and forth on the plan.
So I'm looking, like,
can someone give me a nod
or something?
So, it's like...
Now we're whispering. I can't.
Yam Yam, does the whispering
make you nervous?
Yes.
- Um...
- [Probst laughs]
It make me super nervous
because...
I mean, this game,
it just explodes when
there are so many plans.
Who has the original one?
PROBST: Well, it is on.
I wanted to do this all my life.
I'm happy I stood up
on my stool to talk.
I have the best seat.
- I can see it all.
- [laughs]
Wow. Well, I feel like there are
no questions I need to ask.
Are we ready to vote?
It might change if we don't.
Yeah, I-I'm good.
PROBST: All right,
it is time to vote.
Danny, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote... Kane.
Heidi. One vote... Kane,
one vote... Heidi.
Jaime.
Kane. That's two votes... Kane.
Heidi. We're tied.
Two votes... Kane,
two votes... Heidi,
one vote... Jaime.
♪ ♪
Danny. One vote... Danny.
Kane. That's three votes... Kane.
Heidi.
Three votes... Heidi,
three votes... Kane,
one vote... Danny,
one vote... Jaime.
Kane.
That's four votes... Kane,
three votes... Heidi.
Tenth person voted out and
the third member of our jury...
Kane.
Need to bring me your torch.
Kane, the tribe has spoken.
Enjoy your rice, you bitches.
[laughter]
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
JAIME: Every single day,
it's a brand-new game.
The era of alliances is over.
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
HEIDI: Danny and I are close,
but I'm here to play the game.
CAROLYN: Something's not right.
They're stupid.
DANNY: We have an opportunity
to strike, let's strike.
CARSON: I just have to decide
who I am betraying.
The only thing worse
than going home with an idol
in your sock is going home
with your closest ally's
idol in your sock.
I had an absolute blast
out here.
Every second was a ride,
every challenge was amazing.
But I got duped. [Laughs]
It is what it is.
Everybody else is
playing out here, too,
and I got outplayed.
[roars]