♪ ♪
[laughter]
YAM YAM: Tribal Council sucked.
I almost didn't make it.
I saw my name
for the first time. Ugh!
It's a pretty name,
but you don't want
to see it written down,
you know?
Yam Yam. Three votes, Yam Yam.
YAM YAM: But thankfully,
at the end of the day,
Josh went home.
Josh, the tribe has spoken.
YAM YAM: Knowing that my
name was out there is always scary
because now it's an option.
"Yam Yam already
had a few votes.
Let's just kick him out
and not ruffle any feathers."
You bitch, you bitch,
you bitch, you bitch.
You... Nah, I'm kidding.
I'm so scared, so I do
my best Yam Yam thing, you know?
My strategy's always been
to charm people.
Hey, look, we all here.
We're all here.
The merge has happened.
[cheering, whooping]
We play an individual game, but
there's a lot of people here.
You need friends,
so I'm about making friends.
We need to sit down
and talk about this name.
CARSON: Yup, I-I memorized
the Fijian word.
If we want to use a Fijian word.
If we want to use...
- "Yam Yam" means "survivor" in Fijian.
- CARSON: What?!
- [laughter]
- It can be the Yam Yam tribe.
I like it.
- It means four, four.
- Okay.
- CAROLYN: Oh.
- Oh, I like that.
CAROLYN:
It's so simple that, like...
I mean, we have to talk with
Matt and who else is not here.
- DANNY: Va Va.
- Matt's not here.
Um, how's it going?
Good. How are you?
I'm good. I'm feeling, actually,
like, weirdly confident
and comfortable for the next,
like, phase of this game.
I went on a journey in the very
beginning of the game,
I lost two votes
at Tribal Councils.
But after last night,
I finally have a vote.
After all of this time,
I can play Survivor.
Like, I feel my wings have
suddenly sprouted
and I'm, like, soaring now.
And I made
some great relationships.
Me and Frannie, super tight.
Like, I couldn't do anything
in this game without Frannie.
Uh, and add on top of that,
right now, I have an idol.
I have power. [Whooshes]
I've, like, emerged into the
sunlight, and it feels great.
Trying to figure out
What's going... what's good
with this idol, cause obviously,
somebody has the it.
Yeah, the Soka idol.
Somebody has it.
But the one I had... the one
I had literally looked...
It was, like, beads.
MATT: Oh, no. Brandon says that
there were actually two idols
on the Ratu beach...
A fake one and a real one.
I only found one idol
in the birdcage, so immediately,
my mind is thinking,
somebody else might have
opened it
and taken the real one,
and I have
this worthless piece of metal.
The pieces start
to click together.
Back at Soka, we're looking
for the idol, Danny says...
You should be
reaching your hands
in each one of these guys, bro.
MATT: I find the key.
So Danny's already acting
a little bit
funky in that moment, which
I didn't realize at the time
because I was panicking.
[quietly]: Yes! Let's go.
I think it's the obvious
conclusion. I feel like
I've been set up
like a chump by Danny Bronx
to find the hidden...
like, the fake immunity idol.
- BRANDON: It was found.
- MATT: It was definitely found.
But, like, I found the fake one,
and I can show it to you.
So, someone has the real one.
Especially if you're saying
there was, like, one in there.
MATT: I underestimated
Danny, but clearly,
he's making big moves.
Have you...
What's the scariest thing
that's happening right now?
- Somebody... somebody has two votes.
- Oh, yes, totally.
- Yeah.
- Is that what y'all are thinking?
Yes.
It is common knowledge
Lauren has an extra vote.
If Lauren doesn't win
immunity tonight,
then she-she got to go,
get rid of the two votes.
Easy move.
- It's just straight logic.
- Okay.
DANNY:
We need to get rid of that.
So, I went around.
I spoke to Frannie,
I spoke to Carson,
I spoke to Kane.
I think Lauren's the smart vote
because to just get rid
of that two votes, it's, like...
The smaller we get, the more
- that extra vote has our name on it.
- Yeah.
I feel great.
This is a fun time.
I'm a little devious snake
over here, man,
running around like a... a-a...
causing mischief
like Dennis the Menace.
MATT: I'm not totally
opposed to a Lauren vote.
I'm also not opposed
to making Danny feel like
- he's in charge of things and, like...
- KANE: Yeah.
If-if Danny thinks
he's leading a Lauren vote,
I feel like
it could be a really good time
- to get rid of him.
- FRANNIE: Yes.
Yeah.
Oh. What? Looks who's here.
And let's get...
Yeah, let's get us up to date.
MATT: Yeah. So we
were thinking to do a Danny
- blindside...
- Yes.
...because Danny has a plan
that is his plan so he probably
won't play his idol.
CARSON: I feel like I'm
in a really great position
where everyone just really wants
to work with me.
And Danny and Lauren are really,
you know,
in the spotlight.
Danny's going after Lauren.
He just...
He wants her extra vote out.
I promise,
we're-we're in the good spot.
Myself and Tika are the ones
deciding who's going to win
the war between Soka
and Ratu, and it's perfect.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Day 14, Survivor44,
still looking good.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
[all voicing assent]
PROBST: For today's challenge,
you're gonna stand
on a narrow beam while balancing
a ball at the end
of a long pole.
At regular intervals,
you're gonna move
farther down the beam,
making it more difficult.
If at any point
you fall off the beam
or your ball drops,
you're out.
There's a twist
to today's challenge.
We're gonna divide
into two teams of five.
- Ah.
- No.
The player who lasts
the longest on each team
earns individual immunity.
You'll be safe
at Tribal Council
'cause you'll have this
around your neck.
This is what
you covet in the game.
If you are wearing this,
it means
you're safe. Without it,
you are vulnerable.
There's another twist
to today's challenge.
The player who lasts the longest
out of everybody
earns for their team...
immunity.
Wow.
PROBST: Everybody
on that team will be safe
- tonight at Tribal.
- Oh, my God.
PROBST: Here's how it works.
You will go to Tribal Council,
- but you will watch Tribal.
- Oh, my God.
From the jury box,
- and you will not vote.
- Oh, my gosh.
You will have no say
in who goes home.
It is safety without power.
We're not done.
You're also playing for reward.
- Yes!
- [cheering]
Want to know
what you're playing for?
[all voicing assent]
PROBST: Peanut butter
and jelly sandwiches.
[whooping]
PROBST: Salty potato chips.
- Oh, my God.
- PROBST: And iced tea.
[cheering]
The losing team... Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the eighth person voted out
and the first member
of our jury.
Big stakes.
All right, shall we draw
and see what our teams
are gonna be?
- DANNY: Let's do it.
- YAM YAM: Yes. MATT: Jeff.
- Do it. Here we go.
- All right.
All right, let's look
at our two teams.
On Orange:
Heidi, Kane, Danny,
Frannie and Carolyn.
On Purple:
Lauren, Yam Yam, Jaime,
Matt and Brandon.
There are 11 of you,
which means, Carson,
you drew the gray rock.
You now look at these two teams.
Who do you think
will last the longest?
I honestly think
that I'm gonna put my fate
into the Orange group.
PROBST: All right, Carson has
chosen Orange, which means
if Orange wins, Carson wins.
If Orange loses, Carson loses
with them. All right.
Everybody take your spots.
Carson, take a spot
on the Orange bench.
We'll get it on. Here we go.
All right.
Everybody has the pole
above their head.
This challenge... is on.
If you fall off the beam
or your ball drops,
you're out.
You want to be
the longest for your team.
That ensures your safety, but
if you are the longest overall,
you ensure the safety
of everybody wearing your color.
Seeing a little bit
of movement with balls.
Then out of nowhere, Carolyn
is the first casualty, -Oh, God.
And it didn't take much.
It was one little move,
and that ball was done.
You cannot lose concentration
in a challenge like this.
Lauren dropped.
Lauren is the first person out
for Purple.
We are down
to four on each team.
All right,
you're going to move now
to the next section of the beam.
You've got 15 seconds.
If you drop your ball
or fall off the beam
while you're making
the transition, you're out.
♪ ♪
You got to have both feet
in the color.
Brandon, you're good.
Jaime, you're good.
All right, everybody's good.
You've all successfully
navigated it, but Kane
navigates the transition,
but only lasts about a second.
Kane is out,
and we're down
to three on Orange.
Settle in,
but don't get comfortable.
Long time to go in this section.
Heidi's ball
is all over the place.
- Oh!
- Heidi drops. Heidi's out,
and we're down to two on Orange.
Carson's shot now getting
less and less likely.
It is Frannie
and Danny for Orange.
If one of you drop, keep going
if you're the other person.
Here you go, Fran and Dan.
Keep doing what you're doing.
PROBST: Danny drops
suddenly. Danny's out,
which means Frannie has won
individual immunity.
She is safe tonight,
regardless what happens.
It is now Frannie versus
almost the entire Purple team.
No pressure. You got it.
PROBST: If Frannie drops,
then it does not matter
what happens on Purple.
You all are safe.
You will all share
the individual win.
Lauren will be grateful.
Keep digging in.
Keep talking to yourself.
[whispering]
Out of nowhere, Jaime drops.
- Good job, Frannie.
- PROBST: That's one down for Frannie.
It is now Yam Yam, Matt
and Brandon left for Purple.
Frannie at the other end,
all alone on Orange.
All right, everybody, start
making your move down the beam.
This is a live transition
to the last section.
You've got to get a toe
on that red paint.
Brandon, very close.
If you drop
while getting there, you're out.
Brandon, you're good.
You're good, Frannie.
Yam Yam and Matt,
you got to keep moving.
You're not there yet.
Both have about six inches left.
Matt can't make it,
and we are down to three.
Yam Yam trying to hang on.
Yam Yam is out.
Yam Yam, great effort.
Take your time.
Okay, we have a real showdown.
The attention now
is on Frannie in Orange,
Brandon in Purple.
Both have won individual
immunity for themselves.
Now you're fighting
to win it for your group.
This is what you want.
Two warriors going at it.
Amazing performance
by Frannie on one end,
- Brandon on the other.
- Focus, baby.
PROBST:
That pole starting to shake.
Brandon with another adjustment.
Frannie with a little bit
of movement and a nice recovery.
You got it, girl.
You got it, Brandon.
PROBST: Brandon's
ball on the move again.
Another nice save by Brandon.
If you take your eyes off this,
you won't be able to recover.
Brandon... ball hanging
on the very edge,
but it's still there.
Nice adjustments.
Stay focused.
This is when you need to dig.
Right now, you need to dig.
You got to find another gear.
There's still some fuel left
in that tank.
Draw on it now.
- Brandon drops. It's over.
- [cheering]
Frannie has done it.
Frannie has won immunity
for her entire group.
- That was amazing.
- This is your moment.
PROBST:
Brandon gave everything he had.
He comes out of this with
individual immunity for himself
in a huge battle
between Brandon and Frannie.
Wow.
Brandon,
come on over right here.
Amazing job, Brandon.
Huge effort.
You are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game.
Congratulations. Head back.
- Frannie, come on over.
- DANNY: There you go, Frannie.
Here's the deal.
You don't even need this
because you're not vulnerable
at all tonight.
But this is an honor.
This is an iconic moment
to win an individual challenge.
Not only did you win individual
immunity for yourself.
You won group immunity.
Never happened before.
Kane, Danny, Carolyn,
Heidi, Carson, -Good job.
All safe because of you.
What is this feeling?
I... You know,
you come out here, and
you look at everybody else, and
everyone else here is so strong.
And I look at myself,
and I never think that I'm gonna
be the one who can do it.
PROBST: Congratulations.
You're not going anywhere.
- Head back over.
- DANNY: There you go, Frannie.
- Good job.
- You're a force, baby. You're a force.
PROBST: All right, here's
what's gonna happen.
This group... you six...
Are gonna head back to camp.
Peanut butter
and jelly sandwiches,
potato chips, iced tea. You'll
go to Tribal Council tonight,
but you will watch.
You will not vote.
You cannot be voted out.
All right, here's what's gonna
happen with the five of you.
You're gonna go
to the old Soka beach.
- Whoa.
- You're not going back to camp, where
- you will not have any food, and instead.
- LAUREN: Oh!
You will just have time
to figure out,
"who are we going to vote out?"
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
The game is constantly changing.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
MATT: I didn't even anticipate
that we wouldn't be going back
to our beach, so,
I left all of my stuff in my bag
and just brought my water bottle
with me to the challenge.
I'm an idiot. No idol,
regardless of whether it's real
or fake, no Shot in the Dark.
As much as it sucks not eating,
going to Tribal, all this stuff,
there's still a little part
of me that was like,
"Yeah, Frannie, let's go!"
I'm proud of her.
♪ ♪
- HEIDI: Oh, thank you, Frannie.
- CAROLYN: You did so... I...
I just... I couldn't...
I watched you,
and I was just in awe
the whole time.
DANNY: All hail Frannie.
- Salud.
- KANE: Frannie to our safety.
CAROLYN: Beautiful.
DANNY: Oh, man. Frannie,
an absolute force of nature.
And the fact that
I got the safety
and peanut butter and jellies...
That was epic.
- CARSON: Oh, my gosh, this is so good.
- CAROLYN: I know.
HEIDI:
I'm sorry, but I haven't eaten
in thir... 14 days?
All right.
DANNY: And the note...
it was a little terrifying.
You know? I'm not gonna lie.
But it certainly
wasn't enough to, uh,
perturb my peanut butter
and jelly experience.
I want all the protein
I can get.
- CARSON: So there's five people voting?
- HEIDI: Yeah.
I think Yam Yam or Matt are,
like, the two in jeopardy.
It's either Yam Yam or Matt.
FRANNIE:
I know that a lot of us feel,
like, strongly about, uh,
wanting Matt to stay,
but I don't even think
we'll be able to talk.
I... Yeah. Just gonna be,
like, a jury member.
We're just gonna
have to sit there.
DANNY: Yeah, it's so weird.
FRANNIE:
It was an amazing feeling,
winning immunity for myself, but
I feel like I put my best friend
in this game
possibly going home.
In some sense, I would rather be
on the chopping block myself
and have the power
to at least write a name down.
So I am gonna be watching
Matt fight for his life tonight,
and that terrifies me.
- I think everybody here wants Matt to stay.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- HEIDI: Yeah.
- DANNY: Um, Carolyn,
are you, like, super tight?
Are you okay with that, or are
you super tight with Yam Yam?
It's me... Yeah.
I mean, it's me and him,
but Yam Yam's gonna fight.
I mean, I know that.
They're all saying "Matty"
"or Yam Yam," which...
It's not gonna be Matt.
Like, come on.
I don't want Yam Yam going home,
but it comes down to, like,
who's more well-connected,
and it's-it's...
it's not Yam Yam.
But I have no control over this.
It sucks.
I just...
I don't want him to go.
And I feel, like, powerless,
like I can't do anything.
I... No, what's in that
is really intriguing.
DANNY: It's scaring me.
I hate little ominous notes
in Survivor.
Maybe...
- HEIDI: I hope so.
- DANNY: I mean, there could be
something in there
that could help him.
MATT: Yeah.
Like, I was trying,
and I did not want
to have to go to Tribal tonight,
and I did want that...
that meal.
Yeah. You did it, though.
I did try to compete
as hard as I could.
I wanted that win 'cause
I did want to get some food.
But honestly, this-this kind
of worked out well for me.
I have immunity tonight, and
there's only five of us here.
I have Lauren on my side,
I have Jaime on my side.
We've been Ratu strong
up to this point, so,
we can control how tonight goes,
and all we have to do
is stick together,
and we have the numbers
over Yam Yam,
who really doesn't have
anybody out here,
and Matt, who's separated
from the rest of Soka.
I sort of want
to talk with everybody.
- Yeah, same.
- Oh, I'll stay here.
MATT:
I'm feeling very vulnerable.
All of my closest allies
were in the other tribe.
Frannie... in the other tribe.
The old members of Soka...
In the other tribe.
So, it's just me out here.
I feel a little bit like
it's three Ratu
deciding who goes home
between me and Yam Yam.
And if y'all
have a different idea, like,
if somehow, like, my read
of this is wrong, and y'all are
thinking like, "We should get
Lauren out," or something,
like, crazy like that...
Yeah. I-I mean,
that makes sense, right?
Like, that just...
I get it, you know?
Game plan number one was
to flip one of the Ratu, but
they all seem like
they're pretty tight.
So game plan number two...
Self-preservation mode.
But I really don't want to go,
and I really want to work with
y'all, um, to make that happen.
BRANDON: I do see the
value, especially with you.
You already proved
we can work together.
- Yeah.
- I've been sketched out about working with Yam Yam
because I-I did put a vote
on him last night.
And so, my worry is
that somehow, some way,
that's gonna come full circle.
MATT: That sucks.
I love Yam Yam.
I want to keep him around.
But if it's gonna be one of us,
I hope it's Yam Yam.
I heard, like,
Danny wants you out
because you have an extra vote.
I don't know if Matt
or Danny are working together
- 'cause nobody ever tells that to me.
- Right.
- I get it.
- Oh, my Lord.
- So...
- Well, I want Matt out.
- That's who I want out.
- That's freaking awesome.
- And...
- And you guys have me, like, for real.
LAUREN: Danny put
my name out there and wanted
to flush my extra vote,
which makes me a little wary.
But if we get rid of Matt,
Soka numbers goes down,
and then their alliance
will crumble,
and we get
to break up Frannie and Matt.
That's a dynamic duo
that cannot go any further.
Matt... you heard him...
He doesn't have his back, okay?
- [mutters]
- So he doesn't have anything.
I'm down
for putting Matt's name.
- Put him down. Oh, my God.
- I'll see what they say.
YAM YAM: Oh, music to my ears.
Another name that is not me.
How big you want me
to write "Matt" down
on that parchment paper?
I'll write it, like,
on big, big letters.
But everybody might be
playing me and telling me lies.
I've been the person
that has been
the most in danger
this whole game.
Like, when am I gonna
get some power here?
♪ ♪
HEIDI: I needed that so badly.
FRANNIE: Is now a good time
to open the note?
I am scared. Who's opening it?
- Frannie?
- DANNY: Frannie.
[laughing]
KANE: I love this. This is
like I'm inDungeons & Dragons,
smiling, ripping around.
There's advantages,
there's magical items in play.
And we were all looking
for these little keys.
I see Carson. He's like,
"Aha!" And he rips off
to the birdcage.
I'm like, "What the heck?
Where are these things?"
All of us want the advantage.
Who knows what it's gonna be?
It's a complete unknown.
KANE:
I haven't eaten in 14 days,
and I just put a massive
peanut butter sandwich down,
so I'm like
a sloppy sasquatch.
Like, I can just feel
my gut shaking as I move.
So I'm not looking good,
but I'm looking for keys still.
Hell, yeah.
[groans]
Please, please, please.
Come on, baby. Come on, baby.
It's okay. We're good.
I'm so excited that I found
some sort
of advantage for myself.
It means the world.
FRANNIE: Danny? Danny?
Heidi opened it. Heidi got it.
HEIDI: They saw me open the cage
so it was a little bit tricky
because this is not
a secret advantage.
This is a very open advantage.
Whew!
I have a lot of power,
so, whenever Jeff says
"It's time to vote,"
I have to tell a player to vote
for whoever I tell them to.
That's powerful
because there's only five people
in tonight's Tribal Council.
So I really have to think
about this one hard.
So if Yam Yam and Matthew vote
for the same person,
and we have three votes,
I can swing the vote today
the way I want,
if I want to save Yam Yam
andMatt.
I'm excited.
Just got to use it the best way.
Oh. Wow!
Oh, my God.
MATT: You want to believe that
the person who's, like, the best
at Survivor, like,
does the best,
and that's not always true.
No, I-I kind of disagree
with that because I feel like,
yes, in a way, like, you can get
screwed, but there is also...
- There's a way out of every situation.
- Yeah, that's true.
Realistically, there's a way out
of every situation.
- Yeah, that's true.
- So if you can survive through that...
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah.
This game changes
literally every single day.
MATT: This is as close to death
as I have been
in this entire game.
And I miss Frannie.
I hate being apart.
She is like my rock
in this game.
It's impossible
to describe how important it is
to have someone
you trust out here.
Take a big, deep breath.
So right now, I'm feeling alone,
feeling unsupported,
and I don't even have my bag
or the Shot in the Dark.
Maybe Frannie will think of it.
"Matt left his bag.
We got to bring it to him."
Maybe if I shout loud enough...
"Frannie, bring my bag!"
"Frannie,
please bring my bag
to Tribal Council!"
So I don't have my bag,
and the Shot in the Dark
is in my bag.
- Oh, that, too?
- Yeah.
I know.
Yeah.
YAM YAM: Getting together
with Matt to vote against Lauren
or Jaime...
That would be a bomb-ass move.
That's risky, though, but
I come here to play hard.
What I'm thinking is
a Lauren blindside for tonight.
I mean, I don't know.
That's my plan.
- Oh.
- I would prefer that.
Oh, it's better...
it's better her than me.
What do you think
they're talking about right now?
'Cause they've been back there
talking for a while now.
LAUREN:
I don't know. At this point,
it's gonna be Yam Yam or Matt.
- Yeah.
- You agree, right?
- Yeah, 100%.
- So, I mean, that's the vote.
JAIME: Yam Yam doesn't have
a huge army behind him, so,
that's less damage control that
I'm gonna have to do at camp.
He's also fantastic socially
with everyone,
so he is a major threat
in this game.
However, if we choose
to send Matt home,
it puts a little ripple
in Soka, but
I don't know if Matt has his
Shot in the Dark or his idol.
It is so scary.
Matt has this, like, fake thing
he's showing everybody, right?
Could Matt be just saying that?
Does Matt have the idol?
That's why I'm saying we do need
to be careful how we vote.
I think we should split the vote
just in case
it's real or not, you know?
I know my numbers are solid, but
I think we're gonna split
the vote tonight just in case
Matt has his idol with him
or his fake idol with him.
This was the ideal situation.
Like, God was working
with me today because,
either way, I'm not going home.
- HEIDI: I want to tell you all.
- FRANNIE: Okay.
I can control the vote.
- How?
- Tonight.
It may save
bothYam Yam and Matt.
FRANNIE: Yes! Oh, my God!
We have to use this advantage
to try to save Matt, right?
That's the only thing
on my mind.
The only... the only person
who will be a little bit upset
is Carolyn,
but she'll totally understand.
She's receptive.
Heidi listens to other people
and takes other people's ideas
into account.
But at the end of the day,
Heidi is a woman who will do
what she wants
and what she thinks is best.
I would prefer Lauren.
Right now, while she doesn't
know this is happening.
It's gonna be sprung upon her.
We can get those two votes
on right now.
That's what
we talked about today, right?
I would need Heidi to play
the advantage against Lauren
to give Yam Yam
and Matt a heads up.
Put your votes on Lauren.
HEIDI: But I wanted
to tell you 'cause I knew
you were close with Yam Yam.
Oh, yeah, I've been worried.
Like, oh, amazing.
I was like, "Yes!
I love it."
I just immediately
was, like, trying
to work to save Yam Yam
'cause I know
he's in trouble.
And this is why
I want to talk to you.
I love Matt,
but it makes me wonder
if Matt is really dangerous
'cause everyone loves him.
- Yeah.
- Including you and I.
Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
HEIDI: Frannie... she's
awesome, she's my girl.
- KANE: Yeah.
- HEIDI: But she's very close to Matt.
- HEIDI: It makes me wonder
if that's against someone
like me.
I know Matt is closer to Frannie
than he is to me, and I think.
Yam Yam could potentially
even be a closer ally
to me than Matt.
FRANNIE:
Oh. How are you feeling?
No, I'm good. I-I... I just...
FRANNIE: I really think you do.
What?!
You're the only person here
who can do anything.
Of course you have the power
to save Matt.
We just need to figure it out.
- I feel really confident.
- Mm-hmm.
That Brandon is gonna
vote with Matt.
I'm not. Uh, you got
to convince me on that one.
Uh, just from yesterday,
you know?
- They will go for Yam Yam.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Yes, they will vote for Yam Yam.
So, I am just not
convinced of that.
Neither Lauren nor Brandon
is super tight with Yam Yam.
HEIDI: With this advantage,
this is a tricky one.
Tonight, we have four people
that could go...
potentially go home.
I think it's being well-known
that Lauren has two votes, and
that's what makes it kind of
interesting 'cause
I could just go for Lauren.
Are you okay?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous as well.
HEIDI: Maybe the
safest is go for Yam Yam,
but what they don't know
is I have
a sweet spot for Yam Yam.
I think I could work with him.
And I would love to save Matt,
but do we want
someone here staying longer
if everyone loves them?
'Cause that's also competition
for me, so it's a conundrum.
I mean, this is powerful,
and I like power,
but I have to use it in a way
that I gain friends
rather than enemies.
♪ ♪
PROBST: All right.
So Jaime, we finally get
everybody living
on the beach together.
"It's not a small tribe. I got
some room to breathe here."
Boom, twist happens.
More than half the tribe
is safe. You can't even
vote for them,
and we're back to a small tribe.
Yeah, I think
this is a great measurement
of how deep your social game is
because we could have three
people that we're working with
or zero people
that we're working with, and
they might all
be sitting over there,
the people that we're loyal to.
PROBST: Matt, what are
the lessons being learned
in terms
of expect the unexpected?
MATT:
This is so, so unpredictable.
I didn't even bring my bag
to the freaking challenge.
- So...
- Why is that significant?
Well, I got
a bag of tricks, Jeff.
You might have heard
that one before.
Um, I was wondering
if that is my bag,
if I was able to, like,
wander over there and...
[tongue clicking]
- You know what I mean?
- Did somebody bring his bag?
MATT: No. All right. Yeah.
- It was worth a shot, Jeff.
- PROBST: Yeah.
Um, instead, I've got this guy.
And what is it that
you're holding like it's a gift?
May I offer you a papaya
in these trying times?
You know, as a...
as a gesture of peace, Jeff?
I'm scared. This is crazy.
Maybe tonight, we don't have
to snuff any torches.
Maybe we can all just
go back to the camp
and be friends.
Like, this is crazy, this game.
I should have brought a papaya.
- [laughter] - Oh, my gosh.
- PROBST: So, Matt,
I'm just gonna say,
from sitting over here,
you sound like
you are very concerned.
I mean, do you want me
to break it down? I can try.
- PROBST: Sure.
- MATT: My perception here...
May be wrong... is that
we have three Ratus,
and they are the ones
making this decision tonight.
Let's not be, like,
cute about it.
So it's really me and Yam Yam
- pleading our case tonight.
- PROBST: And Yam Yam,
just because Matt is afraid
doesn't mean
Matt is the one
that's in trouble.
It just means
he's afraidhe's in trouble.
I feel exactly the same way,
and it's been like that
for the past four
Tribal Councils because
some of these people were
last Tribal Council against me.
So, today, I feel hopeless.
Oh, my gosh.
LAUREN: Can I add
to that? I mean, let's say
he plays an advantage,
he plays an advantage, then
it's one of us on the board.
You know, there's idols,
there's advantages,
there's Shot in the Darks.
Like, who knows what
anybody's gonna play tonight?
JAIME: I think another
important part is
the impact
of everyone sitting over there.
What does my vote do
to those relationships?
Because they're watching.
PROBST: So let's go with
what you're all alluding to,
which is
that it's Matt or Yam Yam.
Matt, what was your pitch...
Why keep you?
Listen, I do think
we have created bonds, right?
Like, we worked closely together
on the last one.
We were on Soka together.
Like, we were a Soka tribe.
And then, we went
on that journey on day two.
And so, I want to trust
in the bonds here.
If you're wanting those
qualities in an alliance member,
I'm sitting right here.
His name is Matt,
and he's really excited
to work with you all.
Brandon, that's a pretty
good pitch. It's very specific.
"Here's where I've worked,
here's what we've done,
here's the kind
of success we've had."
Are you open
to hearing something like that?
Yeah, I definitely take that
into consideration
when I think
about what I'm about to do.
He is somebody I want to work
with. I like working with Matt.
You know, I did put a vote
on Yam Yam at the last Tribal,
and so I'm the same way. I like
to stick with my alliances
and keep my word as well.
So Yam Yam, Matt's saying, "I'm
a trustworthy alliance member."
- That's valuable.
- Hey, he-he convinced me.
- I want to work with him, you know?
- [laughter]
I came into the merge
by myself, and I'm gonna play
with people that want
to work with me.
If you guys don't want
to work with me tomorrow,
then you let me know 'cause
we have that bond now already.
No, you know, you tell me,
"Tonight is not your night,
- "Yam Yam. Get somebody else."
- [laughter]
Um, I love Matt...
Don't get me wrong...
But I'm also good
for the long game.
And you know who's also mad good
for the long game?
A lot of those people.
So are you gonna
take him back to them,
or are you gonna
take me with you?
I think that's a fair point
because you're also considering
somebody that's vulnerable and
someone that comes with numbers.
So, how does that weigh
into our games?
PROBST: All right, so, Matt,
if this is it, what has
this journey been about?
Oh, Jeff, you're gonna
make me cry. [Laughs]
- Love you, man.
- Um...
...I came into this game
with a lot of things
that I wasn't sure
I would be able to do.
[sighs] Just...
from a social anxiety
perspective, you come in here,
there's a bunch of strangers.
You have no idea how
they're gonna perceive you.
You don't know who to trust
because your support system
is totally gone,
and you have to find a way
to just, like,
trust in yourself and believe
in yourself to get through that.
And so, all of these things
that scared me...
[laughs] ...um,
I've come out here, and I've
put my all into trying to do,
and for the most part,
I've done them.
And I'm very, very proud
of that.
Um, I'm very, very proud
of myself.
PROBST:
Yam Yam, how about for you?
Because one of the things
that you do really well
is you deflect with humor.
But this is real.
What have you learned
about yourself?
And I do deflect with humor.
It's something
that I use to protect myself.
But...
I'm doing this because
as a kid in Puerto Rico,
it would have been impossible
for me to be here.
You know? And these people have
been this support group for me.
Like, everybody knows
Carolyn and I fight a lot,
but we've been the support
for each other, you know?
I don't know if I should have
said that. This is my problem.
You know, I say everything.
But I'm so proud.
I've been able to compete,
I've been able to dig,
I've been able to run,
I've been able to push.
I have blisters to show for it.
Um, I can be a Badass, you know?
I'm a teddy bear,
but I can be a Badass,
and that's freaking awesome.
- [laughing]
- PROBST: And this is why one
of the most exciting parts
of being a part of Survivoris
when we find people who say,
"I want to see
what I'm capable of."
And what gives it stakes
is the fact that
somebody gets voted out.
And that's gonna
play out tonight
because it is time to vote.
Jeff.
- PROBST: Yes.
- I have something to say.
So, we had a little bit
of a scramble and surprise,
and I'm sure we'll talk
about all the details.
So, I'm not gonna read
word by word, but essentially,
I found a Control the Vote.
So I get to select one of you,
and then
you must vote
the way I tell you.
PROBST:
Okay, so just to be clear,
Heidi's advantage allows her
to pick one of you and say,
"I'm going to tell you
who to vote for,"
and you must vote
for that person.
All right, so, Heidi,
whose vote
do you want to control?
So, I'm going
to take Lauren's vote.
All right, so you're gonna
control Lauren's vote tonight.
And who do you want Lauren
to vote for?
HEIDI:
And I want Lauren to vote...
for Yam Yam.
Jeff, everyone knows
that I have an extra vote.
So does she control one vote
or does she control
more than one vote?
One vote.
All right, Lauren, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Yam Yam.
Matt.
One vote Matt, one vote Yam Yam.
Yam Yam. Two votes Yam Yam,
one vote Matt.
Matt. We're tied.
Two votes Yam Yam,
two votes Matt, one vote left.
Eighth person voted out
of Survivor44
and the first member
of our jury:
Matt.
Need to bring me your torch.
Matt, the tribe has spoken.
Thanks, Jeff.
Time for you to go.
- Love you, Matt.
- Thank you.
I'm proud of you, Frannie,
for winning today.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
All you have to do is say yes.
Apply to be on Survivor.
FRANNIE:
He's gone, and I've been
marooned with nothing.
PROBST: Next time onSurvivor...
BRANDON: We are dictating
the way this game is being played.
CARSON: I'm just
trying to push through.
[yelling]
- You got to twist!
- [screaming]
We need to take someone
from Ratu out.
I don't think that tribe split
could have been
any worse for me.
But sometimes that's just
how the cookie crumbles.
Frannie, I feel like
we've developed an incredible
relationship within the game
and also outside the game.
And I'm so very proud of you
for winning,
and I don't want you to blame
yourself for what happened.
[roars]