[thudding]
DREW [whispers]:
Oh. Oh, my God.
[Austin exclaims]
We start jumping,
we're cheering, like,
"I have my vote back.
We have an idol."
It's, like, the greatest
moment of all time.
♪ ♪
Bruce really does
annoy me deeply.
Like, to my core.
Emily's playing it smart.
She's listening. It's working.
-[cheering]
-PROBST: Belo wins immunity,
sending Lulu
back to Tribal Council
for the third straight time
this season.
BRANDO:
Oh, my God.
This isn't like, "Oh,
Emily trying to save her ass."
This is Emily
trying to save your ass.
Unless he writes
Sabiyah's name down tonight,
he is the one
that is going home.
SABIYAH:
"Congratulations. You have
found a hidden immunity idol.
"If you sacrifice your vote,
you gain more power."
[exhales, chuckles]
My decision tonight
is to not vote and risk it.
-Sabiyah, the tribe has spoken.
-[sighs]
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
-Oh, my God.
-SEAN: Well,
-way to...
-KALEB: Appreciate it.
Are you kidding?
Like, bring it in, you guys.
Like, I'm not even kidding.
I did not see that coming.
EMILY:
I'm sorry, Sean.
I want you to know that
we took no pleasure in that.
-At all.
-Yeah, I know. I know.
The plan tonight did not go
as I thought it would,
and I'm just...
...dumbfounded.
Oh, but...
Emily, I know I wanted to, uh...
We probably should chat later,
-but I just want to say,
"I love you, girl."
-EMILY: Yeah. Yeah.
-Thank you. I love you, too.
-SEAN: Oh.
KALEB:
Of course. Absolutely.
SEAN:
So, I guess Kaleb and Emily
got close at some point.
They planned that blindside
without me.
And so I'm just feeling...
I'm at the bottom.
Here I am, at the bottom.
-It's the game.
-Totally.
And I have, like,
mad respect, honestly,
like, sincerely,
for, like, the blindside.
I just wish I was, like,
in on it.
Do you know what I mean?
-[Kaleb chuckles]
-I know!
-Yeah. [chuckles]
-Come on.
[groaning]
KALEB:
I feel like Emily's
the first person I can say
I actually trust, because Sean
and Sabiyah were targeting me.
So when she had a very real
opportunity to come after me,
she chose not to.
It was awesome.
Considering
how much work I've spent
investing in Emily
these last seven days.
I will say, like, I'm not naive.
-Like, she was running things
around here.
-EMILY: Yeah.
-She was calling all the shots.
-KALEB: And now it's Emily and I
and Sean, who's been
cowering with his tail
between his legs,
talking about how
Sabiyah's been controlling him
this entire time.
No one's buying it.
I feel like every day's
a new day in this game,
and if you're willing
to move forward, I am.
-Yeah.
-EMILY: Yeah. Hopefully we don't
lose any more immunities,
and this is, you know,
water under the bridge.
I'm just grateful
you kept me around.
EMILY:
Sean has this persona that is
so friendly, so gregarious.
And he puts on this face,
right, and he
brightens up his voice a little
bit, and he completely changes.
He's like
this chameleon that's just
constantly changing its spots.
I'm just grateful that you both,
I hope, see a path
forward with me.
EMILY:
So the fact that
he so immediately
180'd his emotions
and, you know,
tried to get back
on good terms with us
just made me feel like
he was not being very genuine.
I will say it was never
my first idea to vote you out.
-Fair.
-Like...
-Again, I was...
-[laughter]
Which is fine. Which is fine.
Yeah. You know, this game.
-[Kaleb laughs]
-What-what...
-what the hell
are we all even doing?
-[laughs]
SEAN:
I went from being on top
to being the very bottom. So,
I don't know.
Maybe there's a pre-merge swap
coming up that I can be, like,
praying for, so that
I can make some connections
over on the other side.
That's my only chance
of saving myself right now.
♪ ♪
Hi, Jeff.
Welcome, Belo.
-Good morning.
-PROBST: Good morning.
-KELLIE: Or is it?
KATURAH: Morning, Jeff.
Morning, Jeff.
-Lots of smiles
from the winning tribe.
-Morning, Jeff.
PROBST:
Another fully intact tribe
enters the arena.
Everybody getting your first
look at the new Lulu tribe.
Sabiyah voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
DREW:
Whoa.
-Whoa.
-Wow.
PROBST:
The three remaining
members of Lulu
plant their flag.
[exhales sharply]
-Damn.
-PROBST: Katurah, this is
-the biggest reaction I've seen
-[laughs]: Sorry.
in a long time to a vote out.
Everybody at once, jaw dropped.
We obviously don't know
what's happening in their tribe,
but it just
came as a shock, honestly.
Sabiyah was strong
and voice of reason
for the tribe, and I'm shocked.
-Dee, Reba also shocked.
-DEE: Yeah.
That Tribal Council
must have been wild to watch,
-Yeah, definitely.
-but it makes me think that
there was some sort of, like,
idol plays in there
and maybe either
a blindside or maybe not,
but, yeah, definitely
did not expect that.
-Drew, is the game
starting to take shape?
-DREW: Yeah.
Sabiyah was one
of their strongest players,
and so, you know that,
over there,
the game has begun.
And that should be a signal
for everyone
that the game has also begun
over in our tribes.
Emily, I know
you take some perverse enjoyment
of the fact
that they have no idea
what is going on.
And they're speculating,
but they're not in the fire
with you and Sean and Kaleb.
Yeah, I do take some type
of perverse enjoyment
in the fact that
everybody's kind of wondering.
"Oh, wonder
what the dynamics are like."
But truth be told, nobody
wants to be in the situation
where their tribe is literally
cut in half. It's not fun.
So, Brando,
where are we in the game?
We're eight days in.
Uh, you know, we're
at a point right now, Jeff,
where everybody's thinking
and everybody's spinning.
Could there be some sort
of mix-up in the tribe?
Hmm.
Oddly...
-...I do have
a tray full of buffs.
-DEE: Okay. Okay, Jeff.
[gasping]
-Everybody drop your buff.
-[exclaiming]
-[groaning]
-Oh, my... Oh, my God.
-JAKE: Let's get it!
We are switching tribes.
Oh, my God.
No way.
For the first time
in the new era,
we are switching tribes.
KALEB:
Wow.
KATURAH:
I knew it. Knew it.
Oh, man.
Let me just do this. Finally.
[blows raspberry]
Is this
your perverse enjoyment, Jeff?
-[laughter]
-A little bit.
-Just a little bit.
-Just a little.
-PROBST: Say goodbye
to your old buffs.
-This is not fair. [laughs]
-[scoffs]
-[whimpers]
That's crazy, right?
Your fate in the game
is about to change.
-JULIE: Oh, my God.
-Take one. Don't open it.
-Oh, my God.
-Sifu might take a while.
-[laughs]
-KATURAH: Love y'all.
Love you guys. Yeah.
[whoops]
Good one.
[Katurah groans]
BRANDO:
I'll take this one.
Two left.
Jake gets what's left.
KENDRA:
Holy guacamole.
All right, shall we?
-Yeah.
Everybody reveal your new buffs
-and take a spot
on your new mat.
-DEE: Wow. Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Or maybe stay where you are.
-KENDRA: I knew it.
-DEE: Oh, my God.
-[Austin groans]
-PROBST: As you get new colors,
-Oh, my gosh.
head to your new mat.
[gasping]
PROBST: Wow.
Four people from Belo
are heading to Lulu.
-Hi.
-[overlapping chatter]
All right!
[cheering]
[excited chatter]
[laughing]
-[cheering]
-Are you kidding me?
All right, put on those buffs.
Let's see what
we got shaking here.
[indistinct chatter]
-I can't wait.
-[laughter]
[excited chatter, whooping]
♪ ♪
All right, let's start
down here with the new Reba.
Sifu, Dee, Julie, Sean, J.
So we have four Reba
joined by one former Lulu
making a new Reba.
Sean, would it be too much
to read into this?
There were only three Lulu
and one of you
went to each tribe.
My mind is blown
that all three of us
somehow ended up
on different tribes.
That is just unreal to me.
And these four
know each other very well,
so I'm just excited to come in
and get to know them
and see this new world of red.
-[laughs]
-Yeah, man.
-We love the energy.
-SIFU: Oh, yeah.
-[laughter]
In the middle, Lulu.
Equally fascinating.
Four former Belo members
all draw yellow buffs.
And you are now
part of Lulu with Kaleb.
So, Kaleb, on one hand,
you're going back home,
but on the other,
it's with a brand-new family.
Yeah, part of me is just
really excited, you know?
It's, like, uh,
the golden retriever got to
the dog park
and gets to hang out with
all the new dogs
and make friends.
-And so,
-Yay!
I am really excited
to get to know these people.
I did get really good energy
from all of them
from the very beginning.
But, also,
part of me is like,
"I have to go back to Lulu."
And the Lulu lounge
is basically Tribal Council.
-So I'm hoping
that this group...
-KATURAH: Oh, no. No, no, no...
-can turn that
around, finally.
-Kaleb. That ends here, Kaleb.
-And I believe we can do that.
-We're okay.
PROBST:
All right, over on Belo,
we have two original Belo,
Kendra and Brando,
two from Reba, Austin and Drew,
and Emily,
the lone person from Lulu.
Austin, what's the key
to surviving
this transitional point
in the game?
[sighs] The key
to surviving this part is to,
as people have been saying,
work as a team,
try building team unity.
And then just making it
through each challenge
as best we can
to stay as intact as possible
to move forward
to the next step.
All right, the game has changed.
-Grab your stuff, head out.
-Thanks, Jeff.
PROBST:
Start making relationships.
-[whoops]
-Thanks, Jeff.
Game continues.
-JAKE: Oh, yeah.
-PROBST: Have fun.
KELLIE: When Jeff says,
"Drop your buffs," it's, like,
the ultimate unknown
and uncertainty.
And it's complete crapshoot.
It's all luck, but I think
a tribe swap is where you
separate a good
from a great Survivorplayer.
Honestly.
♪ ♪
-[laughs]: Oh.
-JAKE: Oh, yeah.
Right, you guys?
JAKE:
Yeah, dude.
KALEB:
What are the odds?
-KELLIE: What up, Lulu?
-[excited chatter]
JAKE:
Oh, yeah, dawg.
-KALEB: New Lulu love. Come on.
-JAKE: Hey.
KELLIE:
Come on.
Aw.
[crying]
BRUCE: When I arrived
on Lulu beach, I didn't
expect to have as many feelings
as I have about this island.
Not only is this the beach
where last year, I was there
for a very short period of time,
but I could see the spot
where I was sitting
when I was taken away.
My head is killing me.
It took me back
to that scenario.
One, two, three.
BRUCE:
And I just needed
to get the emotions
that came over me out.
It had to come out,
because if it didn't,
then I just would have
bottled that up,
and that would have
done no good for anyone.
But now it's time
to build new memories,
backstab each other
and, you know,
play this beautiful game
calledSurvivor.
-Reset.
-KALEB: Yeah.
-What's up?!
-[excited chatter]
-Everybody in. Everybody in.
-KATURAH: Yeah!
-JAKE: Yeah, dude.
-KALEB: Yeah.
So looking at the tribe,
for me, it looks
really bad, because
it's four Belo, one Lulu.
But this is where I've been this
entire game. Back on the bottom.
Have to work my way up.
Nothing I haven't done before.
-I'm gonna get you guys
maybe some utensils...
-JAKE: Yeah.
You are such a hospitable host.
-Dude.
-[chuckles]
My job right now,
as the lone Lulu member,
is to be the most trustworthy
and likable person to be able
to bring into
an alliance as possible.
-I have a question.
-Yeah.
-Brandon came back
from the boat trip.
-Yeah?
Did he end up having anything?
-Did he...
-He said he didn't have a vote.
Oh, so he did
try to do the puzzle?
-Yeah.
-BRUCE: I was on that trip.
KALEB:
Do you mind me asking,
-while we're on the subject?
-Please do.
Go ahead and ask.
-[chuckles]
-Well, wait.
Before Bruce says it,
can you tell us everything
that Brandon
told you about his trip
-and then we can
hear what he said?
-KALEB: Yeah, he basically
told us you guys were split up
and had a choice to do a puzzle.
KATURAH:
I mean, I always have
my suspicions about what
Bruce came back
and told us about the journey.
So I was
really anxious to hear
what Brandon
told his Lulu tribe
to compare it
to what Bruce told us.
So that was essentially
what he told us,
but he said he lost it.
-And if you lose the puzzle,
you lose your vote.
-KALEB: You lose your vote.
-That's a risk-reward situation.
-Okay.
So I didn't even attempt it.
-KALEB: Yeah?
-Nope.
-[Katurah chuckles]
BRUCE:
That initial bonding
experience with Kaleb was cool.
But Katurah is on edge,
a little bit.
In that conversation
that we had,
in regards
to Brandon being voted out,
Katurah went like this to me,
and she said she wanted to hear
it from Kaleb, thinking that,
at some point in time,
I was lying to them.
I was already not
seeing eye to eye with Katurah,
but that was the final straw.
That's the foot
that you put in your own ass,
if you will,
and boot yourself out the door.
JAKE:
Day one on Sweat and Savvy,
I met Kaleb.
And he brought up,
when we hit the merge,
"Let's get something going."
[clicks tongue]
It's a little pre-baked,
but let's get
something going now, Kaleb.
But I got to be careful
of what Kaleb will do
with any information I give him.
I'd like to help him,
but I also don't
want him to bite my hand.
How are you feeling
with this group,
the four that you're with?
I feel good about Bruce.
-Like, I don't think
he's gonna come for me.
-Okay.
-You know what I mean?
-So that'd be somebody
you're good to, like...
That's... Yeah.
I mean, definitely, like,
I don't want to say a name yet.
-Like, I want to get a little
more comfortable with you.
-That's okay.
But, like, also...
You're locked or something
like that. Yeah, yeah...
-Yeah.
-That's fine.
Like, if you come back and say,
"Jake, maybe Kellie,
maybe Katurah," like,
I want me and you to be good.
Yeah.
I don't think that Jake overly
trusts me right now, but I think
he's open to a relationship.
He wanted me to know
that anybody was on the table,
which is, of course,
music to my ears.
If you do have conversations
with people that you know
more than I do, if you could,
like, please, obviously,
like, look out for me
or let me know if anyone...
-Yeah. That would be...
I'd really appreciate it.
-I want you at the merge.
Yeah.
Appreciate it, man.
JAKE:
You got to feel bad for Kaleb,
coming over here.
It's a tribe of five.
He's outnumbered four to one,
and now he's saying,
"Jake, I need you
to help me out."
And I'm like, "Yeah, you do."
This is an opportunity for me
to secure some more connections
and create
more opportunities for myself.
I'm not coming in here saying,
"Oh, Belo strong."
This is new eraSurvivor.
I got to be ready to jump ship.
Mm. [clicks tongue]
Thank God I'm a good swimmer.
[laughing]
♪ ♪
-Wow.
Welcome to Belo!
It's way prettier than ours.
-KENDRA: Welcome in.
-EMILY: Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
-This is insane.
-Holy cow.
New Belo now has me, Drew,
Kendra, Brando and Emily.
And I've got to say,
this is the most mixed
of all of the three tribes.
We've got two Reba,
we got two Belo,
and we've got one Lulu.
And Emily was
someone who we were
really curious about meeting.
And then we found, like,
a really good
fishing spot yesterday.
Like, really good.
-I think we can get, like,
a lot of fish tonight.
-DREW: Yeah. Let's do it.
Like, I really do.
Your face makes me so happy.
EMILY:
I've been alone in this game,
it feels like
since the beginning.
So this feeling
of being on the outs,
it's not entirely new to me.
So my strategy coming
into this tribe is to play it
a bit low-key,
genuinely get to know people,
show them the true Emily--
this kind, generous,
honest, open person.
Let them
get to know me before
they get to know my strategy.
-KENDRA: Ah. Go, go, go.
-AUSTIN: Oh, oh, oh, oh!
-DREW: We're running out
of stuff over here.
-KENDRA: Okay, I'm coming in.
Oh, my gosh.
This is real Survivor,you guys.
-[overlapping chatter]
-EMILY: My very first fire.
-Guys, watch out,
watch out, watch out.
-Yeah, yeah.
DREW:
Emily, new site.
-New site.
-KENDRA: Survivorbucket list.
Yay!
EMILY:
It's easy to say it,
butSurvivor
says it all the time,
fire represents life,
so it's breathing new life
back into my game. And it's
a little sigh of relief
for me, thinking this
could be me turning a new
chapter in the game of Emily.
So, I've been
on the outs of my tribe.
-Okay.
-Lulu camp was Sabiyah's camp.
[chuckles softly]
There's a lot of strategy
behind how I present myself
to this tribe. Kaleb
taught me a lot of lessons.
The main one being,
you know, take some time,
learn to get to know people
before you start taking actions.
And I get to start fresh
with entirely new people,
people who aren't familiar
with my previous game,
for the most part,
aren't familiar
with how I acted on Lulu,
and can kind of give me
a clean slate
to move forward with.
As we're going down
this mess that was yesterday--
-Yeah.
-everybody scrambling,
trying to figure out
where the votes are going.
Sabiyah pulls me aside
and she pulls out this giant
wax figure and she says,
"Emily, I have an idol.
My idol's in here,
and I have to burn it."
I'm afraid that sharing
this information could paint me
a bit as an easy target, but
I want the tribe to perceive me
as genuine, honest and truthful.
"She has
"no secrets, so moving forward,
she is somebody that we can
trust and put our faith in."
Sabiyah, she walked out
with that idol.
Very interesting.
Impressions are a little
different than I thought.
Emily has kind of been
built up as this, like, mean...
...cruel, browbeating lady,
and she's pretty normal,
you know?
So, okay. Now I see
the other side of the story.
-AUSTIN: Oh!
-DREW: Wow.
-Okay. She's actually good.
-You're not bad. Yeah.
-You're a natural.
-DREW: The new Belo tribe
is unique,
because it is the only tribe
that has members
from all three previous tribes.
So this is a tribe
that is going to fight
tooth and nail over Emily
as the swing vote.
Who is Emily gonna join?
Who is Emily gonna help?
So I'm very nervous.
And it's vital in these
first two days to take control,
to get Emily on our side.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
All right.
-Welcome home.
SEAN:
Yay!
[exclaiming, laughing]
How do you feel?
-I am so, so happy
to be with this group.
-Good.
I got stories.
[laughs]
SEAN:
I now am on a tribe
with four original Reba members.
I'm the only outsider
coming in, and so
that does make me
a little worried, like,
well, if they're
gonna stay Reba strong,
then if we lose
an immunity challenge,
I'm the next one out.
But...
Survivor is so much more
complicated than that.
Sit here.
-I'll just sit over here.
-Well, you can't.
-Oh, you should over here. Okay.
-Never mind. Right here.
This is the spot.
I think I can create connections
and feel out, you know,
"Where is Reba really at?"
Are they really
gonna be Reba strong
or are there some cracks
that I can
wiggle my little way into?
Uh, so when there was a swap
today, I literally was, like,
thinking to myself,
the best thing that can happen
for me at this point is a swap.
Wow.
-And look what happened.
Manifest.
-JULIE: Wow.
-SIFU: You sure have.
-We're big
on manifestation, okay?
-SEAN: Yes.
J. MAYA:
I don't know what it is.
Sometimes you read
people's energy,
and you're like, "I like you."
And I'm ecstatic
to have Sean on Reba.
I feel like he brings
this amazing positive energy.
So, Sean is fresh potential.
Maybe he will prove to be
a really loyal ally
and be a great contender
for someone to add
to our merge numbers.
SIFU: A thousand percent.
-If we want to make it...
-That's what I wanted to know.
SIFU:
Yeah.
-JULIE: I mean, I love him.
-Yeah.
-SIFU: Yeah, he's excellent.
-Good energy. Mm-hmm.
Do we think he really
doesn't have an idol?
If we have
to go through his bag,
we might have to do that.
JULIE:
It's sitting right there.
-Do you want to?
-Ooh.
-Well, now
we got to do it right now.
-Yeah.
Put this away. Go get it.
I like Sean,
and I do think that him and I,
the more that we get together,
I do think we're gonna click.
But right now,
Sean could potentially
have an advantage or an idol.
So we go to open his bag,
but we notice that the strings
in his bag are tied tight
and in a weird position.
They're all like this.
And we're like, "Hmm.
Is he doing this on purpose?
"That means
he has to have something,
so we have to go through
his bag."
-JULIE: This one
comes up this way...
-DEE: Under.
-and then goes through.
-Over and under this one.
So what we did is
we got one of our red bags,
and we tried to decipher
how he tied it, and then we tied
our red bag exactly
how he tied his yellow bag,
to tie it back up again
in the same way.
Okay, guys, we got it.
♪ ♪
-Okay, that was on top.
-That was on top.
-Socks.
-Socks in the middle.
-Shoes downward.
Yep.
Guys, I don't think
he has anything
unless he has it on him.
Even if Sean does know
we went through his bag,
you're at
the bottom, buddy, like,
you should expect that
we're gonna go through your bag.
So right now, that's, like,
at the bottom of my worries.
Like, from the barge,
I was like,
-"I want to be with this girl."
-Bro, I want...
I'm not even kidding.
For whatever reason,
I just got
a really good connection with J.
She was someone that I was like,
"Oh, if her and I
could ever get together,
I would love to work with her."
-That's his, like, story.
-Yeah.
-But he has been hunting like
crazy for one since day one.
-Mm-hmm.
And if we lose...
Right.
We don't want
to go into a merge situation
-with someone...
-You can't trust.
you can't trust.
SEAN:
J. shares with me that
Sifu is possibly on the outs.
This is music to my ears.
I totally plan
to capitalize
on this potential crack.
Now I need to talk
to Dee and Mama J.
to see where their head is at,
because the information I have
right now, which is so limited,
is the information from J.
But there is definitely
hope for me
here at the Reba tribe.
He's gonna take out one of us.
I know for a fact, because
right now we are the majority.
He sees the women's alliance.
He knows that he's
at the bottom of the tribe.
He's gonna play the idol
and then he's gonna
put one of our names down
to get the women's alliance
down to two.
-Okay, whatever it is,
the three of us are gonna agree.
-Yeah. Exactly.
'Cause we have the majority.
J. is really trying
to make a connection with Sean,
which worries me a little bit.
Why do we care?
Why don't we just say,
"Reba strong"
and be like, "What's up?
Glad you're here."
But she wants
to blindside Sifu,
and I don't see
how I can change J.'s mind.
[imitates playing guitar]
♪ Four steps...♪
♪ Down!♪
[imitating playing guitar]
[vocalizes]
You're a lyricist.
-[laughter]
-JULIE: At least
Sean brings good energy.
So I feel like
that's good for camp life.
How it will transition
into challenges-- which is
the most important--
we will see.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
EMILY:
Day number nine.
DREW:
Wow.
-Day number nine.
-Who would have thought?
BRANDO:
Day number nine.
-Nine days.
-I know. I wasn't sure I...
-I would, uh...
-No.
I was worried
I'd be the first boot.
Um, I was almost the first.
I've been...
-Yeah, right? You...
-That was my reality, so...
[chuckles]
This is three times
as long as I thought I'd get.
On this new Belo tribe,
it's a bit of
a sticky situation for me.
On one hand,
I could be a flip vote,
but on the other hand,
I could also be
an easy consensus to send out,
especially given the fact
that Lulu
was so keen to get rid of me.
-So crazy just having, like,
new people at the camp.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like my safety
net's gone, in a sense,
even though my safety net
was actually trying
to vote me out, but still,
like, you know, like,
-the-the safety net that exists.
-KENDRA: I get it.
It's people you know
and you're familiar with.
I do feel like there's
people that are more my speed
on the Belo tribe.
And in that case,
hopefully it means that there's
lots of opportunities
for me to actually make
real connections
and make strategy,
make alliances in a way
that I just never had
the opportunity to before.
Oh, man.
It's kind of hard talking
strategy around here, huh?
Yeah, it is. I know.
Everyone's very clustered,
but we can chat now.
What do you want to talk about?
I don't know, I mean...
Me and Drew, I feel,
together, we can
get over almost anything,
because not only
do we have this huge,
close, tight bond,
where we truly trust
each other, but we're stacked.
We've got an idol,
we've got a Goodwill Advantage,
and we have
a Safety without Power.
So truly, if we use all that,
we can take over
any tribe we run into together.
I don't know, I mean...
-Yeah.
-So we might
be able to save our stuff.
I think so, too.
AUSTIN:
I look at Emily
as an opportunity.
In my mind,
she absolutely cannot be
the first person voted off,
because if she's the first one
voted off in this tribe,
then it comes into a two-two--
me and Drew
versus Kendra and Brando.
So it is absolutely critical
we win Emily over.
She went from the bottom
to the perfect middle spot,
where everyone wants to be at.
She truly will decide
who takes charge,
moving into the merge.
We wanted to work with,
because we thought that...
Literally,
the first time I saw...
the first time I saw y'all...
Okay, so,
-I don't want
to get ahead of myself,
-DREW: Okay.
but as somebody
who's been through the scramble
55 million times,
it's good to have a plan
before everything happens.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Um...
If y'all are with me,
I'm with you.
We've been playing a loyal game.
We have been.
-Yeah.
-We are pretty
straight shooters, okay?
-We're not...
-EMILY: I'm 100%
a straight shooter.
-Okay. Oh...
-EMILY: I mean...
Stop, stop, stop.
Don't. No, stop.
Oh, I'm so happy.
EMILY:
Austin and Drew approached me
about, "This could be a thing.
"This could be an alliance,
"and we could be strong.
The three of us
could go to the end together."
And, I mean,
that's music to a girl's ears.
-We're just so happy.
-EMILY: No, no, no, no, no.
I feel like a commodity,
all of a sudden.
I feel like people
want to work with me
and actually making alliances
and voting together.
And they're not just
telling me what to do,
they're actually
including me
as part of the conversation.
So all of a sudden,
I feel this sense of autonomy
in this game of Survivor
that I've never felt before.
Literally,
the first time I met y'all,
I was just, like,
the vibes were good.
I wanted to work with you.
AUSTIN:
One hundred percent.
DREW:
Emily is a very rational person.
She picks stocks for a living.
She analyzes.
And the rational decision
is to work with Austin and I.
So we're hoping to win
the power struggle
against old Belo,
take charge with the core four
of Austin, myself,
Julie and Dee,
with probably the addition
of Emily, who we like a lot.
So I'm very hopeful.
Shut the front door.
♪ ♪
KELLIE:
Looking at the three new tribes,
I am extremely grateful
that I was playing the middle,
because if I got
swapped with all the girls,
I would be okay.
If I got swapped with the guys,
I feel like I got
to keep my eye on Bruce,
but at this point,
I have to work with what I have,
and what I have right now
is Jake and Bruce.
You know what I'm saying?
So, because...
I'm gonna... We're gonna...
KELLIE:
Bruce wants to pull Kaleb in.
Bruce also just told me
that I'm his number one.
Do I fully believe that?
I don't know.
But it's good to hear.
So nice to finally
hang out with you guys, eh?
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
-Happy to see you, man.
-Yeah.
KALEB: Yeah.
It is kind of obviously
scary being on the bottom
-when the numbers are four-one.
-Yeah.
Of course.
Can't blame you on that one.
KALEB:
My hope is that...
KATURAH:
OnSurvivor, I have to
think about every single angle.
And when I see Kaleb
going away with Kellie
and Bruce, that tells you
where we are
in terms of connection.
So my plan
was to get Kaleb alone
and give him some information
on Bruce so that he sees Bruce
as a bigger threat
than what he is.
It was cool getting
to know everybody,
like, as a group, and, like,
you guys seem so, like, kumbaya.
You know what I mean?
-Yeah. I was like...
-No, I mean, the thing is...
KATURAH:
Bruce is annoying.
I mean, I made an alliance
with Bruce on day one.
I liked him.
I thought he was cool.
Then, the more
he opened his mouth,
the more I was like, I just,
"This guy gets under my skin."
All of us can go back
and be like, "Yo, I was on TV.
I was a big thing."
[high-pitched voice]:
"Now you weren't."
[regular voice]:
"Yeah, I was.
You can't even do your ABCs.
Look what I did." [laughs]
KATURAH:
You know, and it's like,
"Oh, Bruce, you're so lovable.
"You cracked your head
and we all got sad,
and, yay, your head's fixed."
He only played Survivor
for 12 hours. Not a big deal.
He makes all these random
little faces and gestures.
"Bwee" and "Aah." "Blah."
Every time he talks to us
he calls us kids.
"When I was in the Navy SEALs,
and this is how we did it,
and this is my training, and..."
I don't know.
I'm annoyed by it.
I can see right through it.
I'm ready for him to go.
But I have to be realistic
that I was just on a tribe
with people
who didn't see that at all.
For me,
thinking about your safety,
unless you see
any bigger threat,
that might be the best way
for you to go.
KALEB:
The conversation with Katurah
was fast and very insightful.
I'm looking for somebody
that I can be like,
"All right,
we got the common goal.
Let's get to the merge."
If we need to do something,
-we're gonna have
to make a move at some point.
-Yeah.
And I honestly believe
if we don't move against Bruce,
Bruce will move against us.
KALEB:
We were at the water well,
but I was no longer thirsty.
I was finally quenched.
Somebody was finally telling me
what's going on around here.
Knowing that Katurah and Bruce
might be at odds
tells me already where
some of the divisions might lie.
And I feel like
I finally am seeing
how this forest is shaping,
and now it's time for me
to build the trail
that I'm gonna walk down.
-[laughs]
-Look, I mean...
Come on in.
All right.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-[all voicing assent]
-PROBST: First things first:
got to take back the idols.
Thank you, Dee.
Thank you, Kendra.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna swim out to a cage,
climb up and leap in.
You will then carry that cage
up the beach
where one tribe member
will have to dig out from under.
That person will be
your rebounder
as the rest of the tribe
attempts to shoot balls
into very tall baskets.
First two tribes
to get one ball in each
of their three baskets...
...wins immunity,
safe from the vote,
you're not going home.
Losers, Tribal Council where
somebody will be the fourth
person voted out of Survivor45.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint,
sorry for you.
Lulu, you are still fighting
to get yours
for the first time this season.
All right, give you a minute
to strategize, we'll get it on.
-Let's do it!
-Yeah!
-Let's go!
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, you got to get everybody
to the cage.
You can't start
getting into the cage until
all five tribe members
are at the cage.
Jake gets there quickly
for Lulu,
but you got
to get everybody there.
-You're good, Reba!
-There you go then.
-PROBST: You're good, Belo!
-Go!
-PROBST: You're good, Lulu!
-[Katurah gasping]
Now it's up and over.
You've got to release two poles.
You need those poles
-to lift the cage.
-JAKE: Drop it!
Drop it right there.
[overlapping chatter]
Now you've got to get
those poles down where you can
maneuver 'em to lift the cage.
-Ready?
-Yup, yup.
-Deep breath. One.
-Two, three.
-Lift!
-PROBST: It's Belo
heading out first.
Lulu right there with them.
Reba struggling
out of this phase.
-Reba's still struggling
to figure it out.
-Push.
Keep going! Push!
Yeah! Yeah!
It is Belo, Lulu and Reba
all very close
early in this challenge.
All right. Let's go.
PROBST:
It's gonna get even heavier
when you get out of the water.
[grunting]
-Lulu now in the lead.
-Come on!
[Jake grunts]
PROBST:
Now you're seeing
how heavy that cage is.
-Come on.
-One, two, three. Go!
PROBST:
There goes Belo.
Every step takes effort.
-Three, two, one! Go!
-KATURAH: Yeah.
PROBST:
There goes Lulu
pulling ahead even more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Ready?
You never know when it'll come
down to a few seconds.
-[Austin grunts]
-PROBST: And those seconds
matter right here.
-[grunting]
-Go, go, go!
PROBST: Here comes Reba trying
to give it another surge.
Three, two. Up!
PROBST:
This is what you dreamed about
when you thought
about playing Survivor.
These kind of moments,
where you got to dig.
[indistinct chatter]
PROBST:
Lulu is moving,
slowly pulling away
from the other two tribes.
All the way, all the way.
Come on!
PROBST:
Lulu has not won an
immunity challenge this season.
Will a new set
of tribe members change history?
Big lead for Lulu right now.
-All right, hold it.
-EMILY: Got it.
Nope.
Got to get all the way over.
Your orientation is good.
A little tighter.
Snug. Snug it up.
-Go.
-Pull it this way.
You're good.
Lulu, start digging.
Get those poles out of there.
-Here comes Reba...
-[grunting]
on the move.
Sifu with a nice burst
-of energy.
-AUSTIN: All the way. Let's go.
-All the way.
Let's go for it. Come on.
-There goes Belo.
-All the way.
-PROBST: Belo, a little bit
this way, and you're good.
This goes here.
Lulu digging now.
Everybody can dig.
Only one person needs
to go through.
JAKE:
Can you go on my other side?
It's stuck on that side.
[grunting]
-Pull back!
-No, keep going back!
Belo making a move now.
Sifu with another big surge.
Wow!
KATURAH:
Got it?
Here comes Kellie out for Lulu.
[grunting]
You're very close, Belo.
Right here. Drop it.
You're good.
Reba, you're good.
Start digging.
KALEB:
There you go. You got it.
JAKE:
There you go.
It is Lulu out first,
Kellie rebounding.
Reba now digging.
Belo now digging.
JAKE:
There you go. You got this.
There's one for Kaleb and Lulu.
Kellie goes to the second pole
for another ball.
Takes a lot of work just to get
somebody out of that cage.
Then they're gonna have to chase
down balls.
You want somebody
with some energy.
Kellie took on that role
for Lulu.
-Come on, Kaleb. Come on, Kaleb.
-There goes Kaleb.
He scored one.
Can he hit a second?
-Yes!
-PROBST: There's a second basket
for Kaleb.
Let's go, baby.
Kellie down
to the third ball now for Lulu.
Julie coming through for Reba.
Gonna be Brando trying
to squeeze out for Belo.
He'll be the rebounder.
Kellie has that third ball.
Kaleb's been hot.
For the win.
The highest basket, just short,
but that looked good.
Kellie got to chase it down.
Here comes Julie.
Julie's out for Reba.
Let's go, Julie.
It's Brando now untying
the first ball for Belo.
EMILY:
Quick, quick, quick.
-Untie quick.
-Lulu has not been
in this position.
Victory looking possible
for the first time this season.
-That's the one.
-Kaleb scores!
Lulu wins immunity
for the first time this season!
Nobody going home from Lulu.
-JAKE: Hell, yeah.
-PROBST: It will be a new tribe
-at Tribal Council tonight.
-All right, give me that.
-PROBST:
Austin going for that first one.
-Let's go!
-PROBST: And he scores for Belo.
-Good job, Austin.
There goes Sifu. He's short.
Brando now untying
his second ball.
-Julie's got
to get it back to 'em.
-Get closer!
-Julie continues to struggle.
-SEAN: Hustle. Hustle.
-There you go.
-PROBST: Finally gonna just hand
it off.
Dee gonna take a shot.
Dee way short.
Brando has the second ball.
Here goes Austin.
KENDRA:
Let's go! Let's go.
PROBST: Austin scores
the second for Belo.
Reba's got to get on the board.
Sifu scores for Reba.
That's one.
Julie's got to work quickly
to untie that ball.
Every second counts right now.
Austin going
for that third and final basket.
All right.
Keep his tribe safe.
-Just off to the left.
-EMILY: Try again, try again.
PROBST:
Julie's got the ball for Reba.
Will it matter? Maybe.
AUSTIN:
Aah!
PROBST:
Let's go, Sifu. Pick it up.
Sifu just misses.
Austin for the win for Belo.
No. Austin off the front
of the rim.
There goes Sifu for two.
-Yeah!
-Yes! We are tied!
One ball left,
but Julie's got to get it.
Austin off the front
of the rim again.
Julie's got
to get that third ball.
Good job, Julie.
-PROBST: Julie has the ball out.
-SIFU: Hustle, hustle.
-PROBST: But it won't matter.
-Yeah!
It's over.
Austin wins it for Belo,
sending Reba to Tribal Council
for the first time this season.
Wow, what an effort.
-Brando.
-DREW: Great job, Brando.
Oh, my God.
Emily. It's okay.
-So, for the first time
this season,
-Ah.
the Lulu tribe wins immunity.
Kaleb, I'm not sure
it's apples to apples
because it's not
the same tribe members,
but it is the same tribe color,
and that is all
you five care about.
There it is.
Immunity for Lulu, and...
Unbelievable.
-...you've earned your flint
-JAKE: How you like that?
-after nine days.
-Finally got it.
-JAKE: There you go.
-PROBST: Let there be fire.
-JAKE: Oh, yeah.
-Belo, nice job. Immunity.
Once again, nobody going home.
Emily, what does that feel like?
Um, well, I tell you what,
I didn't earn it as much
as these four did, but it still
feels great, nonetheless.
Nobody going home from Belo.
Lulu, grab your stuff, head out.
Enjoy the night off.
-Well earned.
-KALEB: Wow. Wow.
-Kaleb won't know
what to do with himself.
-[laughter]
Belo, grab your stuff,
head out. No Tribal Council,
nobody going home.
So, Reba,
obviously, for everyone
except Sean,
a new experience tonight.
Dee, is there
any weird excitement
about getting to go to Tribal?
There is no excitement
gonna Tribal.
There's never excitement, but
it is Survivor,and this is
what we signed up for.
We expect to fail,
and, you know,
we don't have as much muscle
as the other tribes,
but we still were pretty close.
So, no matter what happens
tonight,
we put up a good fight,
and that's all that matters.
All right, Reba,
Tribal Council tonight
and as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Sorry for you.
Thank you, Sifu.
You'll get a chance to earn it
back at the next challenge.
All right, Reba, grab your
stuff, head out. See you tonight
at Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the fourth person
voted out of Survivor45.
J. MAYA: This loss gives me
an opportunity
to make a big, beautiful,
bold move.
The second I step on the beach
after the challenge,
it's my mission to convince
the girls to blindside Sifu
and get him out tonight.
-KALEB: Let's go! Come on!
-[cheering]
[whooping]
We reversed the Lulu curse!
-Yay!
-Let's go!
BRUCE:
Didn't expect any less.
KALEB:
I can't believe
we won a challenge.
This is how I feel on the
inside. You know what I mean?
A little... Right?
And we finally had some
competent people on my tribe.
I don't need
to be on the Warriors, you know?
I can be Kawhi Leonard.
Just put me on the Raptors.
Put me on a halfway decent
organization,
and I know we can win games.
And so,
I finally have some players
who know how
to win a team challenge,
and it just felt great
to do what I knew I could do
and not feel like a crazy person
continuously losing.
We have fire.
Take a look at that bad boy.
Let's take a look at it.
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
I don't have it.
My pocket's empty.
Do I have a hole in my pocket?
Ah! [laughs]
Bruce, never again.
-Ah.
-[laughter]
Is this it?
Some Lulu magic.
It's going now!
[whoops]
Lulu has officially gotten fire.
Right? Nice work.
Not having fire
until night nine
is unprecedented.
I was excited to burn away
all of those bad juju vibes.
It's almost like
sage was burnt at my camp,
and now I can start
to look forward
like a regular player
in this game.
What a day.
This is my favorite day
on Survivor,
I swear to you guys.
And right now, I'm just so glad
I'm not Sean.
SEAN: I cannot believe
we lost the challenge.
I mean,
coming out of Lulu into Reba,
I was feeling so good
because Reba had been
on this winning streak.
They've got this momentum going
that I can just
slip myself into.
So I had every reason to believe
that Reba would win today,
and then
we lost, and I'm just, like...
Ugh. Like, deflated.
DEE: Yeah.
Honestly, though,
I'm the only person
-to go to Tribal
-Just saying. Just saying.
every single time.
-I didn't want to say anything.
-Like, why
-is this happening?
-DEE: I know everyone's
thinking it, so I just...
SEAN:
These Reba members--
they've been together
since day one.
And so, they've really been able
to bond and build connections,
get to know one another,
and then, here I come.
It's definitely daunting
to feel like
I'm stepping into a world that's
very, you know, just not my own.
How are you feeling
about things over here?
[Sifu sighs]
-I think Reba is pretty strong.
-Yeah.
I will say, the three of them
do seem really close.
SIFU:
Yeah.
-It's dangerous.
-I know.
-I mean,
if I'm with you, I'm loyal.
-Okay.
So, I'll be a number to
whoever wants to bring me along.
-Like, I am loyal.
-Right.
I think Sean is awesome.
He's just got that good energy.
But it's Reba strong,
and that's his bad luck there.
I know you don't want
to leave this game.
-I know.
-Right?
-I know!
-[laughs]
SIFU:
I mean, it's horrible
because of what
he's already been through--
being badgered and beaten
every single day.
But I do have to think
that if Sean stays in this game,
that means
everybody be pointing at Sifu,
and I really don't have an idol.
That means Sifu would have
to fight his way out,
and it would not look so great.
So I don't even want
to go that route.
I'd rather just
go the Sean route
and vote him out tonight.
Yeah, it has to be us for sure.
If we vote out Sean,
we actually have a chance
at a challenge tomorrow.
At this point, it doesn't matter
to me as much as...
-Yeah, it doesn't
matter, either.
-If Sifu plays an idol
with the three of us,
one of us goes home.
-So tonight's our best bet
at getting him out.
-Okay.
J. MAYA:
I'm not thinking about
"Reba strong" right now.
Maybe in the merge,
I'll start thinking that,
but what I'm thinking about is,
what is going to improve
my chances
of being successful
come the merge?
I don't think Sifu coming
into the merge with us is going
to be good for my game, and so,
to be honest,
I'm taking this opportunity
to try to take out Sifu
before it's too late.
He'll get antsy.
He won't believe us.
He'll play his idol,
he'll put one name down.
Yeah. He's too erratic.
Like, at least we can...
We have an alliance, and
at least we can pull Sean in.
-This is how I see it.
-Mm-hmm.
Sifu's first, then Sean.
Three, we merge.
But we've been saying
"Reba strong, Reba strong."
But now that the swap is here,
we got to pivot
and we got to adapt
and we got to take people out
that we don't trust.
And that's the game.
We have to play now.
Y'all don't even want to try
to win tomorrow?
J. MAYA:
It doesn't matter.
JULIE:
The challenge today
was so physical.
If we didn't have Sifu,
we'd still be in the water.
We would literally still
be in a cage in the water,
just waving.
But the girls, especially J.,
just want to go ahead
and get Sifu out now.
I hate that attitude.
The best way to not go home
is to not go to Tribal.
The best way to not go to Tribal
is to win a challenge.
But I feel like
my hands are tied.
I'm doing whatever... I want
to make sure we're strong.
-DEE: Yeah, yeah, same. Okay.
-J. MAYA: Hundred percent.
JULIE:
Because, as of now, the best way
I don't go home
is to keep the numbers.
DEE: So here's what
we're thinking tonight.
-SEAN: Yeah.
-Okay?
-Please. Please.
-But you're gonna live
to see another day.
-Please.
-SEAN: Done.
Done, done, done, done.
-JULIE: Yeah?
So, unfortunately, we're gonna
-tell him you're out.
-Okay.
-DEE: Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Because you're new.
It's the only decoy,
if that makes sense.
It's the only thing, 'cause
if we keep saying, "Reba strong,
-Reba strong, Reba strong,"
-Yeah.
-Right.
-he will believe.
-And we don't want him
to play anything.
-Right.
SEAN:
I hope they're being genuine
about wanting to get Sifu out.
They might not be.
Maybe they're just trying
to make me feel comfortable
so that I don't play
a Shot in the Dark.
And honestly, in this game,
where I'm at right now,
I don't have very many options
but to trust
what I'm being told.
JULIE:
Here's the other thing.
At Tribal-- I'm sorry--
we're gonna be talking
Reba strong.
-DEE: Yeah.
-SEAN: Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
SEAN:
Trustis a tricky thing
onSurvivor.
I was blindsided last time
at Tribal Council
and so, I want to come in, give
them the benefit of the doubt.
Maybe that's absolutely insane
of me to be doing,
given what I've been through,
but I feel like,
what other options do I have?
♪ We're all a little paranoid♪
♪ It's okay♪
♪ We got to vote that way.♪
-Yes.
-He didn't get to you guys?
No.
-Positive?
-Hundred percent.
SIFU:
So the plan tonight
is to vote Sean off, but
what's to say that
Sean hasn't gotten to them
and they're playing me,
they're playing Sifu,
and then I'm gone?
That is a possibility.
It's gonna take a lot of trust,
but I believe that we can
remain Reba strong, and
if not, I am the fool.
SEAN:
I did not expect
the SeanSurvivor story to be
going to Tribal Council
every single time.
And so, for me,
this particular Tribal Council
is about, will Sean
be in the game
ofSurvivor any longer?
That is literally what this
Tribal Council is about for me.
♪ ♪
-Oh, my God.
-Oh.
-JULIE: Oh, my God.
-SIFU: Oh, my God.
For everyone exceptSean,
grab a torch, dip it in,
and get fire.
PROBST:
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council because
in this game,
fire represents your life,
and when your fire's gone,
so are you.
All right, J.,
let's get to the switch.
For four of you,
nothing changed.
-Yeah.
-The odds that four Rebas stay
on the same tribe--
it's-it's mind-blowing
to think about.
We have a family dynamic
firmly established,
and Sean has to find a way
to kind of slip in
in under a day, it turns out,
because
we lost the challenge today.
PROBST:
Well, and Sean, at the beginning
of the switch, I said,
"Getting to the end
on Survivorrequires
at least a little bit of luck."
SEAN:
Totally. I would say,
"good luck" in that,
at the last Tribal Council
I was at,
I was on the wrong side
of the vote.
I felt like I had new life
in this game with the switch.
And you can also argue that
it could have been a bad thing
because I don't know
these people.
But I viewed it as a positive.
PROBST:
Julie, the obvious vote is easy.
If the four of you
just want to stay together,
there's nothing Sean can do
to stop it.
Yes. I mean, respect.
His-his experience
on Survivor
is nothing compared
to what we have.
And we like you as a person,
we wanted
to welcome him,
but yet, we've got four.
So, it felt
a little play-pretend.
I don't think he could have
done anything more than he did.
So, Sean, what do you do?
I'm just myself.
That's all I cando,
is just be me.
And I've expressed
that I want to connect
and bond and get to know them.
I feel like we have,
even in the little bit
that we've been together.
So, J., what is
the value system
that the four Reba have
in terms of a tribe right now?
You know, something
that I think about is,
how to get a tribe down
to its best
challenge strength formation.
I mean, look at Lulu.
What happened
when they decided
to vote Brandon?
They won the next challenge.
Like, this is what can happen
when you talk about
what your strengths are
as a tribe in this moment.
Sean, did you pick up on that
possible crack
that J.'s talking about?
Totally, because I know
Reba wants to continue
that winning momentum,
and I give my absolute all
in challenges.
Not only that.
I am extremely loyal.
I'm someone
that will align with you,
that you want
to bring with you, because
I'm a number for you,
and you need to be
on the right side of the numbers
when you go into the merge.
Dee, he's basically saying,
"If there's anybody here
that you doubt, I'm loyal."
Yeah, I can definitely
feel for him.
He wants to be on
the right side of the numbers.
But then, there's also a part
of me that's like,
"We don't know Sean.
It's only been 24 hours
"and I've spent eight days
with these other people
that I've built
such great relationships with."
And that, for me, is where
I struggle, but it is something
that we have to weigh.
Sifu, Sean was
very straight-up.
He's saying, "If there is
anyone in this group
"whose word you question
come a merge,
I'm your guy."
You know, I read energy
in my day-to-day life.
I mean, Sifu
is a master instructor,
and I've been doing tai chi
since I was six
and it's just integrated
in my-in my blood.
And as soon as I met Sean,
I felt a really positive energy.
-JULIE: Mm-hmm.
-You know what I'm saying?
It is very enticing, and I have
to take it for what it is,
but it's not the burger I want.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you want a pizza?
What do you want?
-[laughs]
-Jeff, come on!
-I'll take a pizza.
-DEE: We all do.
We all want pizza.
-I know. I'll be your pizza.
-SIFU: I might
cut somebody out if...
you start bringing pizza.
-Right? Right?
-Can you be a veggie burger,
Sean?
There you go. I'll be...
Girl, I'll be whatever you want.
Um, I mean,
Sifu's comment makes me
feel great that, you know,
that he sees my energy
as authentic and genuine,
and that's exactly what it is.
That's what I bring
to the tribe.
PROBST:
So, Sean, if
what everybody is saying
is authentic,
you're in trouble.
So what has Survivor
been for you?
What'd you get out of it,
if this is it?
Oh, Jeff,
you opened up the gate.
Okay, so,
in the game of Survivor,
I have experienced
a ton of failure,
but it reminds me
of what I learned
from my first grade teacher.
She said, "Failure is good.
"It helps us grow.
It teaches us
what we need to know."
And so, I've decided,
intentionally,
to embrace that failure.
And, Jeff,
if I'm being completely honest
with you, and with my tribe,
my family right here,
I seriously have so much love
-DEE: Oh...
-and respect for all of you.
I want to share with you.
Growing up
in a very conservative world,
-being Mormon...
-Mm.
-was incredibly complex
and challenging for me.
-Mm-hmm.
I tried everything,
everything to live a straight,
faithful, Mormon lifestyle.
And because of those many,
many years that I lost,
Survivor,for me,
was an opportunity
to reclaim that lost time.
JULIE:
Mm-hmm.
SEAN:
It's being here
that I've realized
that my true...
...adventure of a lifetime...
is back home
-with my husband, Matt.
-Oh.
-Ah.
JULIE:
Yeah.
-Wow.
-[sniffles]
SEAN:
And I know how bad that
all four of you
really want this.
I don't want to take your dream
away from you because this--
it's not mine,
and I'm at peace with that.
Because my dream's at home.
[sniffles]
So, respectfully,
I would kindly ask...
...that when you vote tonight,
that you write my name down
on the parchment.
♪ ♪
Sean, what just happened?
I had a ton of time out here
to reflect, Jeff, on...
what means
the absolute most to me
in this entire world.
And that's my husband.
And this is me saying,
really and truly,
write my name down.
All four of you
can stay in this game.
You can be Reba strong.
Sean, I think
everybody might be
just taking a moment
to make sure
-that you know
what you're saying...
-JULIE: Mm-hmm.
-DEE: Mm-hmm.
-Yes.
-versus sitting in the moment
and then
letting the game play out.
But I just want to make sure
you're clear that you are
telling people to vote for you,
which is basically
engineering a quit.
Yeah.
And I can understand that
they're processing
all this right now.
It's been on my mind.
I've been thinking about it
this entire game.
PROBST:
So what is it about
leaving tonight on day nine
that is different
from leaving on day 26?
SEAN:
You know,
Survivorhas been an absolutely
incredible experience.
I'm never going to forget this.
This has been impactful
and informative
to every single bit of my life.
I'm gonna think about it
for the rest of my life.
And the core of me,
everything in me...
just wants to be spending
every single moment
that I can with my husband.
So the only question left is
what is the group gonna do?
Were they already
voting you out?
Maybe they weren't
and you've changed their mind.
Maybe they weren't and
you didn't change their mind.
That's what we're
gonna find out.
And it is time to vote.
Dee, you're up.
♪ ♪
I just got a last-minute audible
that I'm supposed to vote Sifu.
[sighs heavily]
Oh, my gosh.
What is with
this last-minute stuff?
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sifu.
Sean.
One vote Sifu, one vote Sean.
Dee.
That's one vote Sifu,
one vote Sean, one vote Dee.
Sean. That's two votes Sean,
one vote Sifu, one vote Dee,
one vote left.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor45: Sean.
It's three. It's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Love you.
I want you to have...
Sean, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Thank you.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
SIFU: Seeing my name--
it's like a volcano.
[imitates volcano rumbling]
Boom! Ready to go.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
DREW:
I look down the periscope,
and I see tribes
ripping each other apart.
AUSTIN:
They're gonna get my revenge.
This is war.
JAKE:
If I'm going out of this game,
that stabs me
right through the heart.
I came into this game
with every intention
of getting to that very end.
I have no doubt
that I could have gotten there
if I wanted to.
I was coming out here
to win a million dollars.
I got so much more than that.
I quit on my own terms,
because at the core of my heart,
I did exactly
what I feel is right.
[roars]