♪
DREW:
I am one of the smartest people
you've ever had onSurvivor.
And I don't say that to brag.
I say it factually.
But the show is very different
than the Ivy League.
There's
a level of sophistication
and finesse that's required hee
that you don't learn
in the classroom.
KATURAH: I studied this game
and I already know
that if you come off
really intelligent or strategic,
you're getting voted out early.
And so I can't tell
that I'm a lawyer,
I can't tell
that I'm strategic,
until I can, like,
show my true colors
and start slicing throats.
[laughs]
EMILY:
There's a lot of people out hee
who are just happy to be here,
happy to have the experience.
I don't really care.
I'm a goal-driven person.
If I'm not gonna win the game,
I would rather be
the first person voted off.
It's a complete waste of time
if you're not the Sole Survivo.
Excuse me for being honest.
Aah!
[exclaims]
JAKE:
I live in Boston, Massachusett,
with my 85-year-old grandmothe.
I sleep on a bed
straight out of the '60s.
It's painted bright pink.
So, yeah, if I make a million,
I'm paying off loans,
I'm getting a place,
I'm moving
out of Grandma's house.
I'm Sifu,
which is S-I-F-U.
It means "master instructor."
I've been doing tai chi
for 24 years
and I'm also
a traveling musician,
so I'm always
doing those really cool licks.
[imitates guitar playing]
[laughs]
And I do that when
I'm doing tai chi, too.
I listen to super heavy metal,
so I can kind of
contrast the yin and yang.
♪ I am surviving!♪
♪ On an island.♪
Yeah. [laughs]
♪
PROBST:
These 18 strangers
will be abandoned
in the islands of Fiji.
SEAN: I am here to reclaim lost
time, when I was trying to be
someone who I wasn't.
PROBST:
They must learn to adapt
or they'll be voted out.
KELLIE:
People think nurses
are, like, nice ladies,
but you have to be tough.
So, you know, it's like
I got a smile on my face,
but then
the dagger behind my back.
PROBST:
In the end,
only one will remain
to claim
the million-dollar prize.
DEE: I was made for this,
and I'm gonna play like
this is the only chance.
And it is the only chance.
♪
Who will have
what it takes to outwit,
outplay and outlast
all the rest?
This is Survivor45.
♪
AUSTIN:
I cannot believe
that this is happening.
Right over here.
AUSTIN:
I want to, like,
run around, find idols.
I want to, like, make a fire.
I want to build.
I just want to do everything.
I'm so frigging pumped for it.
Right here in the yellow.
SABIYAH:
Survivor is just like boot camp.
Being in the Marines,
I've had to sleep outside.
I've had to be eaten
by sand fleas or whatever.
It don't bother me.
So right off the bat, I know
I'm probably one of the strongr
people in the tribe.
[breathing sharply]
I am obsessed with my tribe.
I'm a Libra,
and that's all about balance.
And I feel like we have one of
the most balanced teams.
Like, our girls are
all strong, and, like,
I see Bruce next to me.
So, those vibes
are just immaculate, like,
for sure.
All right, welcome
to Survivor45.
[cheering]
[whooping, laughter]
PROBST:
I'm gonna mark it down.
I don't know if
I've ever seen this much energy.
[cheering, whooping]
PROBST:
Wow.
All right,
so let's get into this.
We've been doing this
for 23 years.
And certainly, over the years,
there have been
new advantages
and twists and themes.
But at its core,
Survivoris essentially
the same game
it was in season one.
A group of strangers are forced
to rely on each other,
while voting each other out.
And in the end,
the people who were voted out
get the final say, 'cause they
decide who wins the game.
Guy right here with
the long hair, what's your name?
-Brandon.
-PROBST: Brandon.
Lot of emotion when
you were getting up here.
[crying]
Yeah, a lot of it. Yeah.
Some... Too much.
Some would say too much. Yeah.
[whooping]
PROBST:
Okay, is that emotion
or is it just energy
that's just trying to get out?
It's emotion, baby.
This is my dream since I was 11,
to be on this boat with you,
right here.
I am beside myself
that I'm here right now,
and I'm with my new family.
What's better than this, man?
This is the best.
Okay, well,
there's one face here
that should be familiar
to everybody.
-[laughter]
-Bruce is back.
[cheering]
Back, back, back, back.
-What's up, baby?
-[laughter]
Bruce was here in Survivor44,
at this exact same moment
in the show,
the opening challenge.
Suffered a very serious injury.
Everybody, stop!
Had to be evacuated 12 hours
later. So, first of all,
so happy that
you are back and healthy.
You come into this game now
in a different vantage point,
because people already
have an impression of you.
What's the advantage for you
of coming in with everybody
knowing that about you?
BRUCE:
There are gonna be questions.
People are gonna be,
"Oh, Bruce had an advantage.
Bruce was already here.
"Bruce, you know,
he already had his shot."
And I really didn't.
What I have for an advantage
on all of you guys
is essentially done.
We are all on the same beach.
If there's anything I can ever
say is whenever you look at me,
I want you to do one thing
and one thing only.
Just know that your dream
is a frigging reality,
and this is awesome.
-It's absolutely awesome.
-[laughter]
Yeah.
Jeff, I'll push back
against Bruce a little bit.
You know, I think it's really in
his advantage to come out here
and say, "Look, I'm just
like you. I'm like everyone."
But we've all been looking
at him. We recognize his face.
He's had the experience
leading up to this.
He is in some way more mentally
prepared-- even if he hasn't
physically experienced it--
than we are right now.
And, Bruce, you were
prepared for that answer?
Oh, of course.
The thing is is that
if there's anything that we need
to really, really narrow down
is that any advantage that
you bring to the game is you.
And if you can utilize that,
utilize it.
If not, it's gonna eat you up...
But-but you see this? He's
already talking with authority.
He's already
giving us instruction.
And then
coming out here and saying,
"Well, I don't
have an advantage."
So it's a little contradictory.
Wow. I love it.
[excited chatter]
-Hey, I do, too.
-KELLIE: Me, too.
All right, let's get into it.
Let's start with tribe names.
Wearing red, you are Reba.
[cheering]
Reba! Reba!
[laughter]
I'm just watching.
Reba!
[laughter]
In yellow, you are Lulu.
-[cheering, whooping]
-Lulu!
And wearing blue, Belo.
-Belo!
-[cheering]
[whoops]
All right.
You are in the first stage
of this game, the tribe stage,
where you don't know each other
and yet you're
about to compete against
two other groups
who also don't know each other.
So your first challenge is
designed to test who should be
in what role,
who works together the best.
That's who's gonna win this
challenge. Let's get into it.
For today's challenge,
two players from each tribe
will race
to empty a massive crate
filled with very heavy
rope and sandbags.
You'll retrieve a key.
Then the next pair
will leap off of this barge...
...swim out to a boat,
where there is another key.
You'll get in the boat
and paddle back.
The remaining pair
will take those two keys
and use them to unlock two pols
that you will then use
to try to retrieve your flint.
The first tribe
to get their hands
on their flint
earns their camp supplies.
Not much-- pot, machete
and the flint.
That's it.
The losing tribes
will have to try
to earn it another way.
All right, so take a moment
and figure out your three pairs.
Who's gonna run which leg?
[indistinct chatter]
♪
Here we go.
For your marooning challenge.
Survivors ready?
Go!
[cheering]
You've got to empty
this large crate of everything.
Lots of heavy rope
and very heavy sandbags.
[overlapping shouting]
All three tribes
doing the same strategy.
One person grabbing it,
tossing it to the other person.
Nice, guys.
KELLIE:
Come on, guys!
PROBST:
Bruce and Katurah
working together.
Kaleb and Sabiyah.
That's Austin and Sifu.
[grunting]
[chanting]:
Reba! Reba! Reba!
[yells]
[chanting]:
Lulu! Lulu! Lulu!
You're good. Now get your key.
[overlapping shouting]
Austin working on the bag.
Got to untie all the knots.
Let's go!
KENDRA:
You got it.
Get it to stay!
You're good! Go, Kaleb!
Reba has their key.
Got to go up and over.
[cheering]
Let's go, baby!
[cheering, whooping]
Go, Reba, go!
Kaleb has the key
untied for Lulu.
-SIFU: You got it,
you got it, you got it.
-[screams]
PROBST:
It is Julie and J.
in the water for Reba.
You're good, Bruce!
Start untying.
Let's go, guys.
Let's go, let's go.
-Go, Lulu!
-KENDRA: Go, Belo!
We're right there!
♪
PROBST:
It's Sean and Brandon
in the water for Lulu.
[cheering, clapping]
Bruce has the key for Belo.
EMILY:
Keep going, Lulu! Keep going!
-Go, Belo!
-DEE: Go, Reba!
PROBST:
It is Kellie
and Jake in the water.
♪
EMILY:
Let's go, Lulu!
PROBST:
You got to swim out to
your boat, then paddle it back.
Reba in their boat.
KENDRA:
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Lulu's in their boat
and making up
a lot of ground quickly,
-as Belo in the water.
-[overlapping shouting]
-Right. Right, right!
-Yeah!
PROBST:
Sean and Brandon
paddling back for Lulu.
It's Lulu in the lead.
-[cheering]
-Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
Let's go!
Brandon and Sean, clip in.
You're good. Climb up.
DEE:
Let's go, Reba!
DREW:
PROBST:
Brandon struggling
on that ladder.
Let's go!
You got it, Brandon.
-SABIYAH: Let's go, Lulu!
-[whooping]
-PROBST: Brandon is struggling
to get up that ladder.
-You got it, Brandon.
You got it.
Squandering their lead.
-You got it, Brandon! Dig deep!
-Come on, Brandon!
PROBST:
Brandon now in the water.
Sean is up.
Here comes Belo.
They're clipped in.
Here comes Reba.
Let's go, Brandon.
[overlapping shouting]
PROBST:
Kellie's back.
Brandon's still struggling.
-Yeah!
-Let's go, Jake!
You're good. Go, Belo.
-Go help him out of there.
-BRANDON: Oh, my God.
Brandon, still struggling.
Sean's gonna
go back to try to help him.
DEE:
Let's go, Reba!
[overlapping shouting]
SABIYAH:
Pull him! Pull him!
AUSTIN:
Yeah, let's go!
Here comes Julie.
SEAN: Ready? All right.
SIFU:
That's what I'm talking about.
-BOTH: One...
-KALEB: You got it, Brandon.
PROBST:
Now we're into dexterity,
using two poles to try to unloop
your flint off the ring.
KATURAH:
Go!
-Yeah, swing it.
-[whoops]
PROBST:
We've got Belo
with Kendra and Brando.
We've got
Drew and Dee for Reba.
And we've got Sean and Brandon
still working together.
Maybe that'll give us...
[grunts]
PROBST: Brandon
getting a hand from Sean.
There you go.
That's how you do it.
Helping each other out.
Now Brandon's got it.
Let's go!
Brandon, you got it, baby.
Come on.
[cheering loudly]
Don't stop!
-Don't stop!
-SEAN: You're right there.
You got it. You got it.
Brandon's over.
Brandon,
come on, come on, come on!
-SABIYAH: Let's go! Let's go!
-PROBST: Crawling over.
-PROBST: You're good, Lulu!
-Go!
SABIYAH:
There we go. There we go.
Good job.
Hey, you can swim, buddy.
PROBST:
Kendra and Brando for Belo.
We've got
Hannah and Emily for Lulu.
Dee and Drew for Reba.
-Camp supplies on the line.
-[cheering]
Dee and Drew
making good progress.
Brando is stuck now.
Emily and Hannah
making some progress, too.
We got a challenge.
Lulu's in this.
Reba's in the lead.
Drew using that height.
-Come on! Let's go!
-[whooping]
Reba getting very close,
but Lulu is closing the gap.
Emily doing another nice job.
There it is.
This is gonna be very close.
It is Emily and Hannah,
Drew and Dee.
They've got it.
You got to get the flint out.
Breathe, breathe...
PROBST:
Drew untying for the win.
Get the flint.
-Yes!
-There it is!
-Reba wins.
-[cheering]
Tribe supplies. That's it.
-It's over.
-Good going, guys. Nice job.
It's okay. You killed it,
you killed it, you killed it.
-It's okay.
-Yeah, it's all good.
All right. So, Reba,
you won your tribe supplies.
It's not much, but in
this new era, it's all you get.
Your pot and machete will
be waiting for you back at camp.
You already have your flint.
As for Lulu and Belo,
you're gonna
have to try to earn your
camp supplies in another way.
You're gonna each choose
two members from your tribe
to participate
in Sweat versus Savvy.
Big decision. Take a moment,
figure out which two people
are you gonna send
on Sweat versus Savvy.
I'm gonna sit out
of Sweat for this one,
-but thank you.
-[laughter]
PROBST:
All right, so who's going
for Lulu? Sabiyah and Kaleb?
-Yeah.
-Belo, you got a big task ahead
for camp supplies.
How'd you decide?
I'm willing to volunteer myself.
Whatever it takes to help us
get a little bit further.
-PROBST: Who's going with you?
-I'm going with him.
Brando, Jake,
hop over, climb on board.
-Kaleb, Sabiyah, head out.
-After you, Brando.
KENDRA:
All right. you guys got this.
PROBST:
Good luck.
-You got it.
-You got it, guys.
KENDRA:
Go, Belo!
Reba, map to your new home.
Climb over. Get on your raft.
Good luck.
[exhales sharply]
Belo, map to your home.
-Head over. Good luck.
-Yeah!
Let's go. [laughs]
All right, Lulu,
map to your new home.
You three are going on the boat.
Brandon, if you're cool,
we're gonna bring medical in
before you head out.
HANNAH: Watching Brandon
essentially have a panic attac,
it was, like,
a shock to the system.
-[burps]
-HANNAH: And so I am
feeling entirely overwhelmed.
[screaming]
What did I get myself into?
I know people
on the show always say,
"This looks easier
when you're on the couch."
It looks easier
when you're on the couch.
[whooping]
-[laughs] Okay.
-All right.
Victory tastes good. Look,
it's a bucket list
item-- winning
your first challenge
onSurvivor.
[cheering]
And I got to say,
Reba is stacked.
We have
the brawn,
we have the brains
and we have the morale.
On top of all of this,
having your supplies
off the bat is
such a win.
You're not
getting anywhere
without a machete or a flint
here on Survivor.
[cheering]
Oh, my God.
And some letters
in a foreign language
-that I don't recognize.
-AUSTIN: Oh, man.
Oh, boy.
DREW:
Wait, should we do,
like, introductions first?
AUSTIN:
All right, let's do this.
I am a professional
singer-songwriter.
-[excited chatter]
-Wow.
SIFU:
That's sick. Yeah.
Uh, I'm Sifu.
Uh, I've just
been doing tai chi, uh,
since I was six years old.
My father taught me.
-Wow.
-SIFU: So I got
to grow up with that.
JULIE:
My name is Julie.
-J. MAYA: Hi, Julie.
-AUSTIN: Hi, Julie.
-Hello, family.
-[laughter]
AUSTIN:
Mom...
JULIE:
Yeah.
I am a single mom.
I teach
art classes out of my home.
I told them I was an
art teacher, but in reality,
I'm a late lawyer.
I went back to school
when I was 40 years old.
But as far as my teammates,
I feel like they don't
need to know I'm an attorney.
Who wants to give a million
dollars to an attorney?
My name is Drew, Drew Basile.
I am from Metro Detroit.
I'm 22, college student,
last semester, and...
I think that's it. I think
that's everything to say.
My name is Drew Basile,
and there are two identities
built within that.
There is Drew.
Drew is kind of moody
and introspective.
He writes poetry.
J. MAYA:
I didn't really, like, get along
with other kids growing up.
And, um, I...
[laughs]
And in contrast,
Basile comes out at the bar
or at the frat parties.
Basile is outgoing.
He's got
his hand on your shoulder.
He wants to be friends
with everybody.
-Oh. Okay!
-There we go!
So I have Drew. I have Basile.
I would love
to hear your poetry,
-and I'm not just saying that.
-I'll-I'll come up with some.
But between these two,
there is this full, well-rounded
and confident person,
and that is
something that will work to my
advantage out here on the beach.
This is a lot of fun.
♪
KENDRA:
We're home. Oh, my God.
Yeah!
BRUCE: To be reliving this
over again, getting this second
chance at something that people
don't even get
a first chance at--
it's euphoric.
Let's go!
There's so much here.
We checked out the beach first.
This is, like, crazy.
Aah!
-[laughs]
-KATURAH: Look
at our beautiful space.
BRUCE:
I wanted to joke around
with them and say,
"Well, you know,
you're with a celebrity,
so they're gonna give us
a good beach," but... [laughs]
How are you feeling?
BRUCE:
I'm feeling amazing.
Tell you this, though.
The other tribes--
they were coming hard.
-It was extreme, right?
-Oh, my God. They came.
And the curly hair, she...
She started
walking up to me, like, "Bitch."
I was like, "Oh, my God!"
And Emily was
trying her hardest
to run that bus over me
as many times as possible.
"There he goes again,
telling us what we need to do."
I am officially not--
and I got to say this--
I am not Dad, okay?
Don't look at me as Dad.
I'm Uncle Bruce.
-Crazy Uncle Bruce.
Just Uncle Bruce.
-KATURAH: Oh, I was like, "Dad?"
-Okay. Okay.
-Whatever you want to call me,
but let's have a damn good time.
I don't want to be the leader.
And I want to be that way in
order to lower my threat level.
So, the role
that I want to play is
crazy drunk Uncle Bruce.
[laughs]
Do you guys
know how to weave palm fronds?
-BRUCE: Okay, so, um...
-Um, I read it in a thing.
-Cool.
-I was gonna say, I'm-a try.
I want to-I want to just give
one tidbit of advice.
-Remember,
I've made it this far.
-Oh, boy. Okay.
Biggest waste of time
is weaving palm fronds.
-Oh, okay.
-Really?
Great.
First thing that Bruce says is,
"I'm not the dad of the tribe.
I'm the fun uncle."
But he can't help it.
He still is giving advice.
What I'm gonna do is
I'm just gonna make an area
and this will be where
our fire pit's gonna be.
Oh, that's another thing, too.
We got to eat.
Yeah, we just got to, I would
say, push everything that way.
KENDRA:
I was like,
"Okay, so you don't want
"to be in charge, but you do
want to be in charge."
Sounds like a Leo. Great.
Um, I'm 30.
Okay. I'm 29.
KATURAH:
Oh, my God. I'm 29, too.
-Oh, my God!
-KATURAH: Wow!
-Look at us.
-I know.
-When do you guys turn 30?
BOTH:
September.
-No ... way. September.
-[screams]
-No way!
-[excited chatter]
-Wait, are you a Virgo?
-I'm a Libra.
I've definitely, like,
been looking at Kendra, like,
just getting a good vibe
from her.
We're super different people,
you know?
She's, like,
kind of a free spirit.
I am a weird astrologer girl.
I did stand-up comedy for,
like, almost two years.
I'm from Salem, Mass.
So if you're
picking up on the witchy vibe...
KELLIE:
That's not who I am,
but, you know,
we're vibing
at the same frequency.
-Yeah.
-KENDRA: The whole time
we're, like,
getting all these supplies,
we're, like, hoping
that Brando and Jake
are gonna come back
with the machete and the flint,
because right now,
we've got nothing.
SEAN: Lulu!
-Lulu.
-EMILY: Hey.
Before we get into,
you know, all of this,
I just want to say, I don't
know when the other members
of our tribe are gonna get back,
but to me, it's, like,
way more suspicious.
Both of them volunteered.
Nobody else raised their hand.
They're saying,
"I can do Savvy,"
but if anybody comes back
without anything...
-Makes you wonder. Yeah, so...
-Yeah.
-No, that's a good point.
-[groans]
EMILY: Kaleb and Sabiyah
being the only volunteers
for the Sweat
and Savvy challenge,
-I wasn't overly happy with it.
-Okay.
Oh, I'm just like,
"Oh, they're gonna go, like,
-work their asses off
for a flint and machete."
-Right.
-"This is so great for us."
-And they may.
As somebody
who proclaims themselves
to be a little bit
of a pessimist,
anytime we're sending
anybody off
to do anything by themselves,
it makes me very, very nervous.
Let's have fun. Let's have fun.
-Yeah, let's explore.
Let's see our camp.
-Okay.
EMILY:
You always have
to assume that there's
some other
type of gameplay element
that's going to become involve.
Um, and in this case, we knew
that our flint and our machete
was on the line,
so I have nothing
but suspicion now.
I was literally
just gonna say that.
BRANDON:
I'm disappointed in myself.
I wanted this for so long,
and I'm the guy who,
at the first challenge,
just passed out
in front of 18 people.
I'm really, really embarrassed.
I'm going into the camp thinkig
that they've
already planned a funeral.
There's candles lit in my honor.
Huh.
-Hey!
-Brandon!
-SEAN: Hey, Brandon!
You found us.
Where are you from?
We're, like, just
getting to know one another.
EMILY: Yeah.
Jersey.
Bad. No, I feel fine.
Everybody welcomed me
with open arms, but
I'm very shaken up about my
future challenge performance.
Uh, what's
the last thing you remember?
-I don't remember
getting onto the boat.
-Okay.
I remember
just being on the land.
My biggest fear
is that I'm gonna
have to be on the ground
after each challenge.
-It was, like, a panic attack.
-Oh, it was
definitely panic... Yeah.
Everything here
is so anxiety-ridden for me.
I really want to, like,
know everything about you all,
-but should we do shelter stuff?
-OTHERS: Yeah.
-HANNAH: Because I don't know
what to do. [laughs]
-Yes. Yes.
Who is a shelter person?
SEAN:
It's so exciting to be here.
And then reality sets in,
and I'm thinking,
"Oh, where are
we gonna build our shelter?
Where are our shelter supplies?"
I'm trying
to think of anything useful
that we can do
without-without a machete.
-I'm gonna sit on this bench
for a second.
-HANNAH: Yeah.
SEAN:
Brandon is essentially
out for the count,
and Hannah was like,
"I'll sweep the ground."
And I'm like,
"Girl, let's do that later."
The sun is going down.
Kaleb and Sabiyah
are not back yet.
I hope they come back soon
and come back
with the materials that we need.
-All right, let's do it.
-Here we go.
This is new.
[clicks tongue]
Here we go.
-May the best, uh,
duo win, I guess.
-JAKE: Yeah.
[chuckling]
SABIYAH:
Oh, no.
This is Sweatand Savvy.
It's a competition, at that.
You got one hour to move 40 los
and to finish the puzzle.
[grunts]
And at least one tribe
is leaving with nothing.
I'm winning.
[grunts]
These logs are big.
This is the real deal.
Oh, yeah.
And this is a race.
This isn't "take your time."
This is "haul ass."
BRANDO:
In the new era ofSurvivor,
we've had Sweat versus Savvy
four times.
There has never been a tribe
that failed Sweat versus Savvy.
And so it could be
the nail in the coffin
for somebody who isn't able
to get what they need
for their tribe.
SABIYAH:
I am scared, and at this point,
the whole team's
on our shoulders.
I start feeling exhaustion.
Lord, help me.
What if I can't do this?
The Sweat's about
to take me out the game.
♪
[grunts]
Ready? Up.
[grunting]
Hey.
This is not an easy challenge.
I'm exhausted,
but I know I can't give up.
So I just start
talking to myself.
I felt my dad just saying,
"You got more."
I hear you, Dad.
Way to go. Mad respect.
I'm gonna give you
everything I got right here.
KALEB: Sabiyah--
I'm honestly, like,
so impressed with her.
Like, she was talking me up.
Make me chase you.
We need to win.
KALEB:
We're winning this thing.
BRANDO: I can easily say
that that is the hardest thing
that I've ever had to do
in my life. I felt like
there were at least
four opportunities
where I was on
the verge of passing out.
[exhales heavily]
JAKE:
Yeah.
But there's sort of
this unspoken agreement
when you've got the buff dude
and you've got the scrawny guy,
that he might
carry us through Sweat,
and I might
carry us through Savvy.
Let's go.
JAKE:
They get to the puzzle first,
but we're close, so I'm not
really worried about that.
I'm looking over
at Sabiyah and Kaleb.
They're not
getting anywhere with it.
Dude, we got this. We got this.
This is what I think it is.
So when we get
to the Savvy portion,
there's, like,
this crazy, intricate
sculpture-looking thing, where
we've got the flint tied aroun,
and we've got to get
it unlooped all the way off.
And so there's
some sort of trick
to this challenge that--
I'm gonna be honest--
I don't think
I know how to do it.
That did not work.
JAKE:
He's some wicked smart, like,
computer engineering kid
and I'm a lawyer.
We're supposed to be the savvy
people here. Apparently not.
BRANDO:
Oh, my God.
At this point,
the panic starts to set in.
The clock is running down,
and we can see it
on each other's faces,
like, we're in trouble.
This is crazy.
We got, like, 20 seconds.
KATURAH: Damn.
This coconut is hitting.
I'm not even gonna lie.
Like, I was like,
"I'll take a bite."
-I was, I... You were right.
-Ain't that what she said?
KATURAH:
We're, like, anxiously waiting
for Brando and Jake to get bac.
And we don't have a machete.
So we're just
kind of improvising.
[whistles]
-Are they back?
-Oh. Oh.
Nobody got it.
No one got it.
-KATURAH: Oh, my God.
-Thinking about you
-this entire time.
-How-- What happened?
JAKE:
So when we get back,
we have to
break the news
to the tribe that,
for the first time
in the new era, we lost
Sweat versus Savvy.
We don't have a pot.
We don't have a machete.
We don't have flint.
That puts us out of luck
on a lot of things
moving forward right now.
But the good thing is, too,
they don't have anything either.
-BRANDO: Yeah. Yeah.
-KATURAH: Okay.
Please, tell me you did it.
We didn't get it.
Yeah. Both of us
failed the challenge.
BRANDON: Yeah.
EMILY: Kaleb and Sabiyah have
no machete for us,
and, oh, my anger was palpable.
-Let's all sit down, and...
-Okay, let's sit.
Let's sit. Let's chat.
In my mind, they
took an advantage as opposed to
helping the tribe out.
We had these logs.
We finished that part first,
so we beat them...
-And you didn't get anything
for beating them?
-SABIYAH: No.
EMILY:
They're insistent that
nothing nefarious happened.
"We just weren't able
to complete the challenge."
That's BS.
-[whispering]: Emily.
-[whispering]: Yes.
-She was... I-I like her...
-Yeah.
-She, when we got here,
she was very just...
-Yeah.
-I know that she's
very skeptical about things.
-Mm.
-She's like, "What if they
don't come back with anything?"
-Mm.
"Do you think that means
they got an advantage?"
Mm.
I want to just do this quick,
and then lay down.
-I know.
-I-I'm just in, like,
-a lay-down mood, you know?
-Same.
Which is, like, again,
not what we can do or should do.
-I know. I hit a wall.
-Or will do.
I hit a wall.
I hit a... What's that?
-All I want to do is, like,
lay down in the shelter.
-Yeah.
But we don't have one!
The moment that I realize we
don't have flint, machete, pot,
it's hard to not be emotional.
I think I'm just, like,
stressed about sleep.
-I am so upset
with all of today's events...
-[laughs]
but I'm having so much fun.
-Like, this is...
-Okay, I need to remember that.
-Yeah.
-Like, even though my feet
are really wet in my s...
-They're so wet. Oh, my God.
-[laughs]
-I feel disgusting. I know.
-I'm, like, so upset
about my wet feet.
-I know.
-HANNAH: There's dirt
and bugs and sweat everywhere.
And I'm
so hangry it's unreal.
-Hard. It's really hard.
-It's really hard.
-It's literally day one.
-Yeah.
And this is the hardest thing
I've ever done so far.
-And I've done hard things.
-Yeah.
Listen, I'm gonna cry with you.
Hannah's having this meltdown,
I had a meltdown
a couple hours earlier,
and this is day one.
-We weren't supposed
to get this ... machete.
-I know.
That's what happened. We got
to deal with it, you know?
Day one is hard.
You watch this at home,
you see people crying,
and you're like,
"Oh, my God, it's day one."
I-- Tell-- Go out and do this.
Come do this.
I had no idea how hard it is,
and I am
as big of a fan as they come.
I really wanted to give up
earlier, you know,
and I didn't because
we got to see this-this through.
-We're good.
-This is temporary.
-Temporary.
-We can do hard things.
We can do hard things.
I know what it's like
to be anxious.
And I feel better,
as an anxious person,
being able
to comfort somebody else.
-We're good.
-You're very grounding.
If I can make somebody else
feel better, good.
-It definitely
made me feel better.
-Yeah. We're good.
I think suffering
bonds folks together.
HANNAH:
Oh, you know why I'm crying?
It's probably
the nicotine withdrawal.
BRANDON:
Right now, we are all
hungry.
We're all tired.
Oh!
I can do hard things.
BRANDON:
But we're all gonna figure
out this thing together,
because that's the only shot
we have of succeeding at this.
-EMILY: Oh, my gosh.
-SEAN: Wow.
-Look at you.
-[chanting]: Hard thing,
hard thing,
Hannah and I
are doing a hard thing.
♪
KENDRA:
I feel like I've connected
with you guys the most.
-Me too, yeah.
-KENDRA: Like, I want to go
to the final three with, like,
-people who I would
feel good about winning.
-KELLIE: Yeah.
-KENDRA: I want to win.
-We could all
support each other.
-And then, may the best one win.
-Yeah.
KENDRA: In the last few season,
women have gone first,
and, like, I'm trying
to change the status quo there.
And all three women here
are all September birthdays.
This is, like,
written in the stars
for us to, like, be
in this alliance together.
People that I respect
and, like...
Jake? Yeah.
No?
KATURAH: Kendra says Jake
'cause he's a lawyer!
This is why I told my tribe
I'm an office manager
at a nonprofit.
I don't want people to know
I'm a lawyer because
I know it's gonna
put a target on my back.
People are gonna be like,
"Damn, you're a lawyer?
"How'd that happen?
You're really strategic.
You're really smart."
Hell, no. I'm not
letting them know I'm a lawyer.
So what's it like
being a lawyer?
Scary.
-Is it?
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
Nothing better
to sell my lie
that I'm not a lawyer
than putting all the attention
on another lawyer,
and Jake's a baby lawyer.
You just passed the bar?
You're excited
to tell people you're a lawyer.
I-I'm a public defender,
so, like...
The ADAs are, like, the state,
-so, like, they're like, "You've
been charged with this..."
-Oh.
-District attorney. Okay. Okay.
-Yeah, district attorney.
Yeah, assistant
district attorneys.
-So...
-Oh, assistant
district attorney.
-Yeah.
-KATURAH: I don't really get
super strategic,
threatening vibes from Jake,
but if you want to come in
and say you're a lawyer,
this is the consequence.
Like,
I knew better
than to say it, Jake.
Should've--
You should have known better.
-This is cool to know. Like...
-It's like...
-I'm not around lawyers
that much.
-Yeah.
Oh, I'm sor... Oh, don't let me.
-Yeah, don't let me...
I'm sorry.
-Y'all be careful.
Make, like,
a little hut type thing.
I'm in workhorse mode.
We have, barely, a shelter.
You know,
we're working on it today, but
all of the structural ideas
have been mine.
It's not much
'cause you don't have a machete.
-But, I mean, that's something.
-Yeah, this is hard,
-but I'm just... This is hard.
-However, it's something.
SABIYAH: We can't chop
palm fronds down from the tree.
You know, we can't cut bamboo.
But I feel like everybody is
really making an effort.
Whoa. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-We can do hard things.
-That's right.
SABIYAH:
Everybody has a good attitude.
Wait.
SABIYAH:
Um, everybody, except for Emil.
We're just trying something out.
Emily is a glass-half-empty
kind of person.
It's smaller.
It's not level.
Right. That's part
of why I like it.
EMILY:
It's not that I don't want to.
I want to just be thoughtful
about it.
KALEB: Emily has a lot of
pessimism. She's not the person
who's like, "This is how we're
gonna do this and fix this."
She's like, "Well,
this is why we can't do this
and can't do that,"
without bringing a single idea.
HANNAH: I can't be around,
-like, negativity.
-Yeah. Yeah.
I feel like
our tribe would be stronger
-and more cohesive without her.
-Yeah. Yeah.
That sounds bad,
but it's just really
just because she is so negative.
-It's looking like a camp.
-Yeah. Love it.
-Yeah, right?
EMILY:
They're patting themselves
on the back
for the world's worst
Survivor shelter.
And I know
that I have this personality
that is so different
than the people
that I'm around,
and I can't even
pretend to be, you know,
the same as them.
-SABIYAH: Aliens.
-Aliens.
-HANNAH: Aliens.
-KALEB: We're all
on the same page?
-SABIYAH: Yes.
There's, like, a theory
that they were batteries
'cause, like, the chambers
make more sense for, like,
-energy harvesting...
-HANNAH: What?
than... tombs.
HANNAH [laughing]:
Yeah.
EMILY:
"Oh, my God. The pyramids--
they're giant batteries."
I can't.
There were no mummies
in there.
EMILY:
I feel like I've been isolated
with crazy people.
-What do you think?
-Um, I have genuinely
never given any thought
to the pyramids
before this exact moment.
I don't know
what to say to these people.
I'm not this person
that jives
with the mood of the tribe.
And I'm an easy person to say,
"Well, you know,
"Emily's kind of hard
to get along with right now.
-Let's just vote her out."
-SABIYAH: Exactly!
-the biggest cover-up ever.
I just
-Yeah, yeah.
don't know what
they're trying to cover up.
Coming into this game,
I'm willing
to make my Survivorexperience
like it's my second time.
I'm looking for idols, baby.
I'm looking for advantages
every chance I get, and I think
they don't notice that,
and that is a part
of my strategy.
-Anyone know what Sifu's up to?
-J. MAYA: I don't.
Yeah.
DREW:
Do you want to come
and see what's going on?
SIFU:
I'm giving this game everything
because I want
to play fearlessly.
I'm willing
to put it all on the line.
-My...
-AUSTIN: Oh, oh.
I forget I'm carrying,
like, a bamboo.
SIFU:
I'm going stealth mode.
I'm going
like Tony Vlachos times five.
I feel like
he's playing a Tony game
'cause, like,
he's, like, everywhere.
He has if not more than one
advantage or idol.
-I would agree with that.
-Because of all the times
he's been by himself.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
DEE:
Oh! [laughs]
-He was spying on us.
-[Sifu laughs]
-This is your shack.
-No, no.
I'm like,
"There's no freaking way."
Like, we just look,
and he's right there just...
-I was messing with you guys.
-Wow. It's a great spot.
Oh, yeah. Do you think...
How about you?
So, you're going to get water.
Back home, my mom says
I'm a little fireball,
and if this was the real world,
I would not hold back, but
if he's going around
spying on us like that
so early on in the game,
he can't be trusted.
If only
I was really spying on you.
[laughing]
That's a...
AUSTIN: I think right now,
the only person
who has at least been caught
searching is Sifu.
But, I mean, whenever
I'm doing anything,
I've always got my eyes
looking in trees,
looking on the ground,
seeing anything
that could point me to any sort
of advantage
or clue.
I'm just like,
"No flipping way." Like,
I didn't even look at it.
I was like,
"Oh, my gosh, is this an idol?
Is this a clue? What is this?"
[sputters]
"If you take it, it's yours,
and you must do what it says."
So I thought about it
for, like, three seconds.
Then I was like,
"Screw it. Let's do this."
Playing too safe--
that is so lame.
I mean, like,
if I left it there,
Sifu is gonna
open it and get it.
I like tasks.
This sounds good.
"Until you've taken possession
of the idol,
"you cannot vote
at Tribal Council.
That's why it says 'Beware.'
Your first task..."
Oh, my goodness.
My first... A series of tasks?
My first task?
And inside of it
is this.
And immediately, I know.
On our tribe flag, we have
a bunch of random symbols.
Getting this idol
is gonna be pretty difficult.
And if there's one thing I've
learned about being on Survivor,
is it's gonna be even
more difficult than I expected.
So I'm really hoping
we can win immunity
so I don't have to worry
about not having a vote.
♪
Come on in.
All right, are you ready
to get to your first
-immunity challenge?
-[all voicing assent]
-[cheering and whooping]
-We are ready!
-Go, baby.
[whooping]
Let's get into it.
On my go, one player at a time
will race up and over a ramp
into a mud pit.
Then the next person goes.
Once everybody's through,
you'll drag a very heavy bag
of coconuts to a net basket
where two players will race
to shoot their coconuts
into the basket until it's heay
enough to release a set of key.
You'll then work together
to get everybody
to the top
of a very tall tower
where two different players
will use those keys
to unlock and then solve
a massiveSurvivor puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity.
This is what you covet
in the game.
[cheering, whooping, exclaiming]
I like it.
Two pieces... for two tribes.
You have this at your camp,
it means you are not going home.
Losers, Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the first person
voted out of Survivor45,
and as a penalty
for losing,
I will take your flint.
Now, in the case
of Belo and Lulu,
because you failed
in your second attempt
at earning your camp supplies,
you still don't have them.
They'll be waiting for you back
at camp after this challenge.
But if either of you lose,
I'll still be taking that flint
as penalty.
All right, give you a minute
to strategize. Get it on.
-Here we go.
-[whooping]
♪
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Sifu, Sabiya and Bruce
out of the gate first.
-AUSTIN: Yeah, baby!
-HANNAH: Let's go! Let's go!
-PROBST: Keep your head down.
-AUSTIN: Get up there.
[whooping]
-PROBST: Sifu goes down.
-Aah!
PROBST:
Sabiyah's in.
-Bruce is good.
-KATURAH: Yes!
PROBST:
You got to get through the mud
and to your mat
before the next person can go.
That mud is thick.
Sifu's through first.
Go, Reba!
Here comes Bruce.
-Go, Belo!
-[exclaims]
PROBST:
Sabiyah's still working
to get through it.
Here comes Austin.
He's through.
Jake now, for Belo.
Lulu's falling behind now.
Let's go, Sabiyah!
HANNAH:
You got this!
Go, Reba! Keep going, Sabiyah.
You got to
get out of that mud.
Get out.
Go, Lulu!
Lulu's just lost a lot of time.
-Go, Belo!
-KENDRA: You got this.
-PROBST: Here comes Hannah.
-[shrieks]
PROBST:
Face first.
That's how you do it.
There goes Katurah.
[shouting, clapping]
Dee in the mud now.
-Here comes Brando.
-KELLIE: Come on, Brando!
Come on!
PROBST:
Everybody going tentative.
Sean, that's how you do it!
Get through that thick mud.
Come on, Dee!
Get out and to the mat.
Go, Reba!
Go, Lulu!
We got Kendra working
through that mud quickly.
There goes Emily.
There goes J.
Belo down to their last player.
It's Kellie.
Belo in the lead.
JAKE:
Stay low, stay low!
PROBST:
Let's go, Emily!
It is Lulu in dead last.
Back, back, back, back!
You're good, Belo! Go!
Belo's through the mud.
Now you got to drag that net.
You got to get to the mat! Go!
KALEB:
Let's go, Brandon!
PROBST:
Reba's good.
They can start
dragging that net.
Here comes Brandon.
He struggled
in the marooning challenge.
How will he do with the mud?
[overlapping shouting]
You got to get it up and over.
These bags are heavy.
One, two, three!
PROBST:
Brandon's still in the mud.
[overlapping shouting]
-You got it.
-There it is!
Go, Lulu.
Here comes Kaleb for Lulu.
-One, two, three.
-[groaning]
PROBST:
Kaleb working quickly
-down into the mud.
-[grunts]
One, two, three!
[grunting]
PROBST:
Kaleb is whipping through this!
You're good, Lulu. Got to get it
all the way to your crate.
[grunting]
You're good, Belo!
Start unloading.
It is now Belo emptying that net
of coconuts and sandbags.
Reba working toward the end,
and Lulu right behind them.
We got a challenge.
Reba, you're good.
Start unloading.
You got to get every coconut
in that trough
and every sandbag out.
-One, two!
-Go!
Lulu's back with their bag.
They can start unloading.
Belo has everything out.
Belo, you're good.
Two players now rotating.
JAKE:
Go, Kendra!
PROBST:
Kendra tosses first.
Here goes Bruce for Belo.
-You got this!
-PROBST: That'll do it.
KENDRA:
That's what I'm talking about!
There you go. You're good.
-It's gonna be Austin
with the first toss.
-Yeah!
And he sinks it. Sifu.
Austin has one.
-You're good! Go, Lulu!
-HANNAH: You guys got this!
It's going to be Sabiyah
and Kaleb for Lulu.
You got to get
enough coconuts that
that net becomes so heavy
that it releases your keys.
Kendra, will that do it?
Yes! You're through, Belo! Go!
-Okay, let's go!
-I got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it.
-Good job!
-There's another.
That's it for Reba!
-You're through!
-[whooping]
[overlapping chatter]
PROBST:
Lulu still in dead last.
BRUCE:
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
KATURAH:
Bruce, you're on the bottom!
PROBST:
Belo at the wall.
It is now Reba
working to the wall.
It's Drew going first for Reba,
-Brando going first for Belo.
-Yeah, buddy!
PROBST:
Lulu getting closer.
Will this do it?
-Yeah!
-PROBST: Almost.
Lulu, you're good.
Up. On my shoulder,
on my shoulder.
PROBST:
Bruce making a human ladder.
There goes Katurah.
-Hold on.
-Got you.
Got you. I got you.
PROBST:
Kaleb is up.
Sifu making a ladder.
It's now Julie getting up.
There goes Kellie.
There goes Hannah. It's Kaleb
and Sean trying to drag her up.
Austin trying
to lift that heavy guy.
Nothing about Survivoris easy.
You are earning it
every single day.
-Oh.
-Brandon takes a big fall.
Let's go, Brandon.
Dig through it.
KALEB:
You got it, Brandon.
Don't quit. Don't quit.
You wanted Survivor,buddy.
You got it right here.
There goes Austin.
-Look at that!
-Yes!
-That's okay! Legs!
-PROBST: Reba's got it.
You're good.
Two people on the puzzle.
[Austin groans]
PROBST:
Bruce with a big run at it.
And he's got it.
-Grab my hands.
-PROBST: And he's up!
Belo's good.
-Start working on your puzzle.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Lulu struggling,
but still fighting.
-[groans]
Sabiyah's literally crawling.
-Oh!
-PROBST: And falling.
Meanwhile, we got a puzzle
being solved over here.
That was a huge...
-You got it.
-Pull.
-Brandon now working his way up.
-There you go!
-Brandon is up!
-Let's go!
It is now Kaleb and Sabiyah.
Right here.
PROBST:
And Belo has
made up a lot of time.
Reba had a very big lead,
but Brando and Kellie
have squashed that lead.
-Yes, they have.
There goes Sabiyah,
using that Buff.
Can they get her all the way up?
Sabiya's up. We're down to one.
Kaleb reaching for a Buff.
He's got one. He's got two.
Will the Buffs hold?
Look at that!
Let's go, Kaleb!
Keep working.
Kaleb is up!
You're good, Lulu.
Buffs have never served
such a unique purpose
as pulling humans up a wall.
Belo very close
to winning this challenge.
Reba right on their tail.
It would take a miracle
for Lulu.
This is more about pride
of getting to the puzzle
rather than having any chance
of winning the puzzle.
JAKE:
Close it up! Let's go!
-Jeff?! Jeff?! Jeff?!
-The last piece. It's Brando.
-Belo wins immunity!
-[cheering]
We're looking for one more.
Reba down to two pieces.
Brandon, Emily, still working.
Try and put that piece
before it.
PROBST:
It won't matter.
Drew with the last piece
for Reba.
-That's gonna do it.
-Yes!
-Reba wins immunity,
-[whooping]
sending Lulu to Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the first person
voted out of Survivor45.
All right, Belo,
-congratulations.
-[cheering]
Tribal immunity is yours.
-[whooping]
-Nobody going home
from your tribe tonight,
and all of your camp supplies
will be waiting for you
back at camp.
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
-Yes!
Reba, smaller piece,
counts just the same.
Nobody going home from Reba.
Lulu, Tribal Council tonight,
where somebody will be the first
person voted out of Survivor45.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
All right.
Let's head back to camp. See you
tonight at Tribal Council.
BRANDON: I wasn't contributing
really much of anything
in this challenge,
and I know that people
have to think that.
And what I'm having
this struggle with is
that I'm gonna
vote for somebody
who performed better than me
in this challenge,
and I feel bad.
All right.
You guys down to maybe
just, like, hit the water first
before we do any, like,
real strategizing?
-Oh, 100%. Yeah.
-Yeah.
-SEAN: Yup.
HANNAH: I hate to admit this,
but the moment that we lost,
I felt relief
because I was like,
"Maybe they'll vote me out
and I can go home."
Now we have a machete
and a pot--
like, it's a completely
different game.
-That's true.
-BRANDON: I agree.
HANNAH:
And then we got
into the water to wash off,
and it was really nice,
and for a second,
I forgot about how hungry
and kind of miserable I am.
And so,
it's just like this constant
back and forth, and, like,
it's exhausting in a way
I've never experienced.
Someone from our tribe
has to go anyway.
Every single person except me
really wants to be here.
But, like,
everyone wants Emily out.
My concern is, like, how can
I get them to write my name?
I want to sleep
in a bed tonight.
Maybe I like my comfort,
and that's okay.
-You're-you're...
-I want nicotine
and I want food.
I know, but you're fine.
You are good.
-You want to be here.
-Ugh!
Ugh. Do I have to?
-I don't want to.
-You have to.
You literally have to.
Okay, fine.
BRANDON:
Hannah is going
on this diatribe.
She wants to quit
'cause she's hungry, but I dont
necessarily want to be here
without Hannah.
I'm gonna cry. Um...
I've felt a zero
for a while now.
It's heartburn,
it's reflux, it's...
A lot of it could be
stress-induced,
but it just is uncomfortable.
You know,
-it's just...
Geez.
BRANDON:
Last night,
I woke up
with the worst chest pain
I've ever felt in my life
right around
the here area,
and it didn't go away.
I have reflux.
I take medication
for reflux at home.
But just being
in literal physical pain--
it is genuinely
one of the worst feelings
I've ever had in my life.
I-I would love
to do this without...
Like, it ... hurts, dude.
It hurts.
-It's still there?
-Yeah.
-What's going on?
-Just in a lot of pain.
Like, a lot of physical pain.
And I don't want to, like,
look weak or whatever.
-I'm just ... in so much pain.
-Oh. What happened to you?
-KALEB: It's still your chest?
-Yeah. ...
My chest for, like, 20 hours.
Like, can't ... focus, man.
So, what are you saying?
I'm playing
my Shot in the Dark tonight.
Why?
Because I feel like
I'm a liability, I'm gonna
continue to be a liability.
Why? We already know
what's going on.
Emily's who we were assuming
we were gonna vote for,
but Brandon--
he straight-up
told me and Kaleb,
"I'm playing
my Shot in the Dark today."
-This is just... I don't know
what this is, and I...
-SABIYAH: Anxiety?
You know, he deals with panic
attacks and stuff like that,
which I empathize with,
but it's just
getting to the point
where it's like,
can Brandon do it?
He's so down on himself.
SABIYAH: Yeah.
Well, it means that he could be
Plan A and Emily be plan B?
Yeah.
That's a solidified
alliance, right?
But I-I'm concerned.
They're obviously very close.
It's kind of my perspective
that the two of them have been
so strong for so long,
haven't given a ...
about running off together,
and they will systematically
pick us off one by one.
The only chance
we have is breaking apart
that really strong duo because
every single day that passes,
they get stronger
and stronger and stronger.
-HANNAH: Yeah.
-Yeah.
EMILY: Tonight's vote
is about survival
'cause I feel like
my days here are limited.
And the relationship that
Sabiyah and Kaleb have built
is a massive liability
to my game.
So, I need to break up that du.
We would not have even
gotten halfway through
today's challenge
if it hadn't been for Kaleb.
But this is me trying
to think three steps ahead.
And I think Sabiyah
without Kaleb by her side
will be much less of a threat
to my game, long-term.
-The three of us write
Kaleb's name down?
-100%.
-EMILY: We have to do it.
-And then we just roll down
-until we merge.
-Exactly.
It's clear to me that if I dont
play this vote right tonight,
then my game is kaput.
So I'm willing
to risk it for the biscuit
in this scenario.
Um, don't-don't look
too conspicuous.
Emily thinks we're...
She wanted to vote you.
I think she thinks
she successfully got me.
Good, man.
It's just stressful to hear.
Emily is throwing my name
out there.
Her gameplay is just...
it's crazy to me.
I'm at the point now
that my trust level
for her is less than zero,
but a vote for Brandon
is very possible.
He's been so bad in challenges.
That is an easy vote
that I'm still kind of tempted,
if I'm not gonna lie.
I said it to Sabiyah.
If everyone wants to do Brandon,
we could do Brandon.
But Emily, I feel like,
if we take her
-to a swap or a merge,
I think she's gonna...
-She's bouncing.
She is not loyal.
KALEB:
But the most important part
when you're facing a challengig
decision is to make a decision.
-So I'm on board either way.
-Yeah.
-I'm really either way.
-There's pros and cons to each.
So if we want to just
go Brandon, I'm on board.
KALEB:
We have been
the Lulu losers
so far.
We haven't won jack,
and so my goal with this vote
is to not only come back
stronger for the next challeng,
but to also make sure that
I build the strongest coalition
that I take
into the next part of the game.
♪
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council because,
in this game,
fire represents your life,
and when your fire's gone,
so are you.
So before we get into the tribal
politics, let's just talk.
Let's have a little jungle talk,
starting with the idea of how
you are as a person when you are
so out of your element.
Sean, have you noticed
anything about yourself
that's different
than you would behave back home?
Oh, coming into this game,
I was like,
"I'm pretty sure of myself,
who I am,
my capacities,"
and now I'm, like,
this jungle rat sleeping
on the floor with palm fronds
carving into my back,
and I'm like,
"Who am I?"
[laughing]
-Emily, how about you?
-I actually feel like
I'm just a more extreme version
of myself.
I feel like this weird,
aggressive Emily
that is, um, palpable at camp.
"Weird, aggressive Emily."
-That is what I said.
Is that what I said?
-Yeah.
-EMILY: That's what I said.
-PROBST: Hannah,
can that be healthy
to say up front,
-"Here are my liabilities"?
-Hundred percent.
But I think sometimes
we can lean out of that
instead of embrace it
as identity.
Right? Like, the identity
that I came in here with
is not at all
what I'm experiencing out here.
Like, I am the most
emotionally-wrecked
out of anyone here.
I'm crying every other,
like, 30 minutes,
and I'm in a constant battle
in my head of
where my heart is in this game.
PROBST:
Sabiyah, that could be
the siren call
of "Just vote her out."
Right, but there's still
a lot of politics
to discuss,
and if you want to go later,
that might be a better decision.
You know what I'm saying?
For us, we need the best
possible team, and honestly,
we have to vote you out
unless you're gonna quit.
And I doubt Hannah will quit.
Emily, Sabiyah just made
a tribe-oriented statement
centered around
strength of tribe in the moment.
Yeah. I mean, I think it's easy
for Sabiyah
to talk about strength
because it doesn't take a genius
to look at this group
of people
and pull out the two people
who are the strongest
on this tribe,
and they have made no attempt
to hide their alliance
in this game.
-Who are we talking about?
-Well, Sabiyah and Kaleb.
And it's annoying
because you feel shut out
because two people have already
made up their mind
about something.
I mean, Sabiyah was like,
"Okay, yeah,
"let's get somebody else out
'cause I know that when,
you know, we lose again,
Hannah's an easy vote."
And that's literally
the thought process.
I mean, Sabiyah
literally just said it.
And I'll-I'll stop you there
because
I feel like I'm taking
kind of a whupping.
But me and Kaleb
have not once begged
to be in a strength role.
-Let's just get that
straight, all right?
-Yeah.
Y'all have slapped us together
since day one,
and it hasn't been our decision.
I feel like, because
you look at us that way,
you have kind of
isolated yourself.
Well, you know,
there's obviously one person
who has really struggled
the most out of here.
That's how every single
conversation has been.
-And whenever...
-Talking about me?
No, I-I... Actually.
[laughs]
-Oh.
-KALEB: Brandon's, actually,
by the way,
-for a guy who passed out
on day one,
-To be... to be...
doing pretty well today, right?
I'd love to talk about it if
I get a chance to talk about it.
-I'll love to chat about it.
-PROBST: All right, Brandon,
let's talk about you, because
you struggled in
the opening moments quite a bit.
Yeah, I made a sizably large
first impression, for sure.
But when I got back to the camp,
my immediate line was,
"Oh, he's not dead, he's here."
You know, I wanted
to alleviate with a joke.
You know, to talk about
a strong tribe.
I can't pretend
that I'm gonna be able
to lift a thing
or swim a far distance.
I'm very good
at comforting people, right?
And that's what I can bring
to these people
that I'm here with right now,
and I'm gonna see how long
that gets me here.
So, Hannah, when you have
you on the end saying,
[whistles]
"H-A-double-N-A-H,"
and you have Emily saying,
"Well, I don't know.
I can't get on with Kaleb
and Sabiyah right now,"
and then you have
Brandon saying, "I know I had
a bad start,
but, hey, I'm really funny..."
So, give me
the tribe dynamic here.
HANNAH:
I mean, I think it's amazing.
And I just keep thinking
I'd love to watch it unfold...
from the comfort of my home.
-[laughter]
-I'm not kidding.
I'm having a really hard time.
I was thinking about food while
they were all talking, and I see
five people who want
to be here more than anything,
and I love them, but, like,
everything in my body is like,
"I'm not going back
to that camp.
Please don't make me go back
to that camp."
And, like, I'm just
gonna be really honest.
Like, I don't need
to be voted out to go home.
PROBST:
Okay, wait.
I want to be clear
that I'm hearing it.
Did you just imply
that maybe you're just going
to quit anyway
and not have them vote?
I don't know how much
more forthright I can be.
I'm not bringing heart to this.
I'm not.
I'm not mentally here.
Emily, is this changing
your opinion about the vote?
Yeah, it is.
I don't want to...
keep somebody here
who doesn't want to be here.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Um, and I can say, you know,
as much as we've just outlied
all this drama or something,
I have no doubt,
Kaleb, Sabiyah, Sean, Brandon--
we want to be here.
BRANDON:
I want to very quickly say,
that you know, I,
-Hannah, love you.
-I know. [laughs]
-I've had so much fun with you.
-HANNAH: I love you so much.
BRANDON:
But we all love the game.
We all respect the game.
Why boot somebody else out?
PROBST:
So let me ask the group.
The question is
is everybody here
on the same page?
I'm gonna
vote Hannah out tonight.
I really hate this, but, yeah.
-Yeah, me too.
-I mean...
-I'm making you guys do this.
-PROBST: How about you, Sean?
Yeah, I mean,
if that's what Hannah
-really wants.
-[laughing]: Stop. I know.
-PROBST:
How about you, Emily?
-EMILY: Yeah.
-I'll vote Hannah out
if that's what she wants.
-Sabiyah?
-Yeah. She's gonna go today.
-I love you guys.
-I love you, too.
-HANNAH: And... [sniffles]
But all I care about right now
is how I feel
and how these five people feel,
and I know
one of them was going home who
wanted to be here more than me,
and that's not fair.
All right, Hannah.
Grab your torch.
[mouthing]
-I love you guys.
-We love you.
I love you so much.
We love you.
Hannah, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Okay. I love you guys so much.
-SEAN: Love you so much, Hannah.
-BRANDON: See you soon, Hannah.
-[Hannah whoops]
-[laughs]
What was that?
Oh, my God.
Is this Edge of Extinction?
Because I'm not going.
PROBST:
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
BRANDON:
Emily is desperate. She is now
public enemy number one.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
DREW:
This is gonna be the solid
group, and I'm so excited.
There are explosions in my head.
-Yeah!
-Yes!
Aah!
KATURAH:
Bruce does a lot
of stupid stuff.
I'm just like,
"Who is this guy?"
I feel fear and anticipation
that, like,
the world is going to hate me.
Here I am in front
of millions of people
being like, "I have to bow out"
I've read so many articles
and books,
and I've researched this,
and nothing can prepare you
for what it's like
to be completely at zero.
I have nothing in the tank.
I have so much more respect
for every single
Survivorplayer
that has ever played.
[roars]