Bruce does a lot of
stupid, annoying stuff.
Aah!
He name-drops.
It really does annoy me
deeply, like, to my core.
There's Bruce and
Jake on one side,
Kendra and katurah on the other.
Me and Brando are in the middle.
I found a beware advantage,
and I have to find an x.
But right now I have no vote.
Myself, Julie, Austin and Dee...
This is gonna be
the solid group.
I don't have a vote now.
Okay.
People are hating on her,
but maybe I can nurse
her back to health.
One of the things
that I can do is...
So you guys have my trust.
Thank you.
I'm learning from my
mistakes, learning to tone down
the more harsh qualities
and rebuilding trust.
Brandon. That's
two. That's enough.
The tribe has spoken.
My gosh.
I will say, I never
second-guessed my decision,
but, you know, obviously,
Brandon was gonna
make it really
hard on all of us?
I can't imagine how tough
that was... decision was.
So thank you, guys.
In the marines, we
have a concept...
"No man left behind."
But I'm starting to realize
that doesn't apply here.
This team could
not win with Brandon.
I know that could have
gone either way, and I
I don't have words to express
- how appreciative that I'm still here.
- Yeah.
I like Emily, for
what it's worth.
Yeah, we bump heads 'cause
we're from two different places,
and we process things different.
But I don't dislike Emily,
so I don't feel like keeping
Emily's shot in the dark
would serve me at all.
If Emily continues to
prove herself worthy of trust,
we can go forward as a four.
I'm shocked that sabiyah gave me
my shot in the dark back,
because they have to
know that if we lose the next
immunity challenge, that unless
something crazy is happening,
I'm playing that
shot in the dark.
There is a growth
that's happening here
between all of us that
I feel like that's there.
If that wasn't there, then we
may have stuck with Brandon.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
But because there's, like,
this belief of the potential
of us four working together,
that's why it just made sense.
Tribal council went
relatively well, but
I was really confused
because Jeff read my vote
I had voted for
Brandon... a second vote,
and then said, "Brandon,
you're voted out."
And according to my math,
knowing that Brandon
did not have a vote,
there should have
been four total votes.
So that made me think that
maybe there weren't four votes.
Maybe there were
only three votes.
- What do you mean?
- 'Cause I'm confused.
Jeff read two votes
and then said.
"Brandon, you're evicted
on the second vote."
Which means there's only
three votes in there, right?
So why did he call it
after only two votes?
Emily is right.
I couldn't vote because
of the beware advantage.
She's very smart.
So Emily will always
be on my radar.
He only read two.
He said, like, "second
person voted out."
I was like, "what?"
This is like the island of
misfit toys that I'm living on.
Emily cracked
again tonight. Probst
was reading out the votes, and
there was only two that he read.
And she was like, "sabiyah",
"do you not have a vote
tonight?" Just immediately
picking a fight
with the one person
she's not supposed
to pick a fight with.
Old Emily is just bubbling right
there underneath the surface.
Like, she's not gone, right?
But she is getting better
and smarter, and Emily
is somebody who I think
knows that she has a home
with me, and I'm gonna be
the most real with her out
of anybody on this island.
You good?
Are you okay?
Well, then what just happened?
Jake kind of takes a tumble,
and it looks like a...
Almost small seizure.
He kind of, like, gets
shaky for a minute.
It was kind of weird.
And then he
popped right out of it.
So it was really, really scary.
It's the smoke, man.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm good.
- I feel perfectly fine, yeah.
- Sit down for a second.
- Okay. My god.
- I was
trying to blow on the
embers to get the fire
restarted, and I
started seeing stars.
I felt like my whole hand
shaking and everything.
Like, my body was,
like, convulsing.
I-I-I may have fell over.
I don't... I don't really know.
- You kind of had a spasm.
- Yeah.
So that was a
really scary moment.
People can't
understand from home.
There's constant heat, constant
dehydration, lack of food.
It's gonna take a
toll on your body.
We're on survivor,
man. Dude, I, like...
You got to just... It's,
like, random moments.
You're just, like...
Like, that's what makes
me scared, because, like,
emotionally, like,
obviously, I'm, like,
I'm not gonna play an
emotional game, but, like,
I... love everyone here.
- I think, um...
- I know you guys are boys, but, um
I'm boys with everyone.
- I feel like I'm boys with you.
- Yeah.
Have you heard my name?
The only time your
name has been mentioned
was in the beginning when
we found out you were a lawyer.
Jake having that
moment this morning
made me feel
protective over him.
We chatted for a bit, and
I said, "you know what?"
"Actually, in the beginning,
"I kind of threw
your name out there,
because you're a lawyer."
And lawyers are
threatening in this game.
They know how to talk to people,
and, you know,
they're trained in that.
I'm not trained in anything.
I am a wild creature out here.
My biggest thing is, like,
I'm coming here
with an open mind.
- Okay.
- Like, we haven't talked strategy.
- This is our first time talking.
- No, we haven't...
Which made me nervous.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, Bruce hasn't
talked to me at all, like
I apologize for
that, because, like,
communication, you know,
two-way street, because, like...
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly.
- It's on both of us... yeah.
- So that's why I'm being honest with you.
There's kind of two
groups right now...
The three women and the boys.
I feel good with you.
We're definitely,
like, drinking after this.
However, I am changing
my tune about Jake.
I feel like we would
work so well together.
We communicate well.
He's easygoing.
I'm me.
I feel like we'd
balance each other out
- really well, actually.
- Let's go, baby.
And so, Jake
could be a good ally.
I think, in the
total of six days,
we've had, like, 300 calories.
I found two
earthworms for us to eat.
Y'all, there's no worms in here.
What?
- Is there a crab in there?
- Yes, and he's very active.
Crab ate our breakfast.
No way. There's no way.
Damn.
Even though I am
starving, all I can think about
is finding the
hidden immunity idol.
But I haven't had time
to get out of camp alone.
The last clue said,
"dig at the fallen palm tree x."
So now I'm like, "all right,
where is this fallen palm
tree, and what is this x?"
So, at this point,
only drew knows.
And we have a good idea
of where this location is.
There's, like, this
obviously fallen palm tree
that's right by camp
with two palm trees
next to it forming an "x."
So I'm thinking to
myself, "this has to be it."
So now we need to
find this frigging idol
and get my vote back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna go
up here a little bit, then.
- I'm gonna go a ways out, and I'll stop.
- Cool.
Finding the idol in that
spot, so close to camp,
requires some killer instinct.
It requires entrepreneurship.
That's nasty.
So Austin digs first,
and I'm on lookout.
And so I'm pacing
down the trails,
and I'm waiting to see somebody,
so I can start yelling about
how much I love
tacos or whatnot.
And he'll-he'll run out, too.
And he'll be like,
"I also love tacos."
And, you know, there
would be our alibi.
But I'm very nervous.
So, I was thinking last
night about Austin and drew.
Do you not feel the vibe?
- You think?
- Yeah.
I've noticed that him and Austin
have been having a lot of
one-on-one time together.
And then every time
we're walking a tree mail,
walking back, they
whisper to each other.
So right now, I have a great
alliance with mama Julie.
And then mama Julie,
Austin, drew and I,
we got, like, a
four thing going on.
But there's certain
things that I've noticed
about drew and Austin
which makes me think
that something's going on there.
Yep.
So, in the peripheral
of my vision, I see drew
digging and digging,
but drew doesn't see us
because his back is towards us.
So then we decide
to just keep walking
and see how he reacts.
And as we get closer, he
gets up, and he walks away,
'cause I'm sure he
was, like, so nervous.
It was an odd moment, right?
I'm digging in the dirt.
And they say, "what's up?"
And I walk the wrong way,
you know? So that was bad.
So I need to kind of
do some damage repair
and regain control.
If you catch me with my
pants down, I got to give you...
Give you something,
to make up for it.
Okay. So we're digging.
- Yeah.
- Digging? For what?
We think there might
be something over here.
Why?
We sifu digging, but
then he-he, gave up.
- Wow.
- Did he know... Did he catch you guys?
No.
Here comes Austin.
I was on watch,
and I'm, you know,
grabbing coconuts
to make it look like
we're, like, you know,
doing stuff for the tribe,
and next thing I
know, I come back,
and Dee and mama j. Are there.
And my heart just drops.
So...
So I'm feeling real awkward.
I'm like, "gosh. What
is about to happen?"
We just wanted to,
like, find you guys,
'cause we have noticed
that you guys have been, like,
taking walks, and we just
wanted to, like, be honest.
Thanks for... yeah.
And we just want to, like,
come together, and, like,
whether you have something
or not, like, we respect it,
but we want to make
sure that we're four strong.
Yeah. No, we are four strong.
- We do not, like...
- Four strong. Four strong.
We're trying to find the
idol. We don't have any...
We're trying to get
to it before sifu does.
Okay. Okay.
Right now I'm just trusting
my intuition, and my intuition
tells me that something was
off between the two of them.
This is the four that
can take us all the way.
Yeah.
Drew is just uneasy
and there's, like,
a worried face in Austin's
face, like, something's going on.
If we're really four
strong, and we caught him,
why would he walk
away all nervous?
- Okay. You're right.
- I mean, there's no...
Mind you, this is a
game of dishonesty,
but I thought we
were working together.
It kind of felt like a
boyfriend was cheating on me
and I caught him
cheating, so it's game on.
Come on in!
Belo and reba
getting your first look
at the new Lulu tribe.
Brandon voted out at
the last tribal council.
Wow.
All right, are you ready to get
to today's reward challenge?
- Yes!
- Hell yeah. Let's go.
Please.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna start
in the ocean and
race to the beach,
where one at a time,
each player will toss a
ball into an overhead track
and then try to catch
it at the other end.
Once all four players
have achieved this,
they'll take one of those
balls, throw it in a basket,
that will raise a
series of targets.
Two players will
then race to land
three rings on their target.
First two tribes to land
all three rings win reward.
- Want to know what you're playing for?
- Yeah, Jeff.
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Been dreaming of it.
- Come on, now,
- bring the food.
- First tribe to finish
should have a nice
afternoon back at camp.
My god!
- Ooh.
- Called it.
A large fruit platter.
My god.
Man.
Second tribe to finish,
smaller, but still appetizing.
- Look at those bananas.
- That's a feast.
Thank you, Jeff!
In addition, the winning tribe
earns the right to
send one person
to either of the
two other tribes
for a camp raid, where
you will get to steal one item.
Let's go.
In a game in which
there is very little to steal,
you can inflict some punishment.
You can also visit and
see the tribe dynamic.
So there is a lot at stake.
All right, sit-outs. Belo,
you have two extra people.
Who are you gonna sit out?
Bruce and Jake
gonna sit this one out.
All right, reba, same thing.
You're sitting out two
people. Who's it gonna be?
Yeah, yeah. Got it. Yeah...
It'll be me, Jeff.
- And me.
- J. And drew gonna sit this out.
Sit-outs, take a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give
you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
All right, here we go.
For reward. Survivors ready?
Go!
Everybody in the water at once.
Let's go!
We have had some close
finishes between first and second,
so every single second matters.
Belo, baby.
You got to get everybody back
before you can
start tossing the ball.
Here we go. Let's go, belo.
Nice job, belo.
- Go, go, go, go...
- Here we go, here we go
Lulu, you're good.
Belo's good. Reba, you're good.
- You got this, sifu.
- Let's go.
You got to get that ball
to roll down the track.
That's the first task.
There goes Kaleb.
He is moving quickly
and makes it look easy.
Go, Sean.
You got this, kid.
Good job. Nice job. Nice job.
There you go.
Sean has a good roll.
Kendra with a good roll.
Kendra's got it! Sean's got it!
They're both good!
Sabiyah now for Lulu.
Brando for belo.
There goes Austin,
making it look easy.
Reba's on the board. Go, reba!
Sabiyah's got it. Go, Lulu!
Brando's good.
Go, katurah!
Emily is the last
member for Lulu.
Go, go, go, go!
Emily takes a big hit.
Can't get there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on... Sifu's good.
That's two for reba.
Go, Dee!
Go. You're almost...
Katurah drops.
She's got to go again.
Go, go, go.
Dee with her first toss.
Come on, Dee!
And she is ripping it up.
- Yes! Yes!
- You're good!
Go, Julie!
It is now Lulu with
one person left
and reba with one person left.
You got it, turn!
- Yeah, kel! Yeah!
- Nice!
Belo. Belo with one person left.
Down.
Yes.
Emily's got it.
Lulu, you're good.
First, you got to
get your target up.
Kaleb with his
first shot. Hits it.
Go, Lulu!
Go, go, run.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
You're good, belo.
Right in there, baby.
Belo now tossing.
Julie's got to land this.
- She's got it!
- Everyone, everyone!
You're good, reba.
Everybody in it now.
Kaleb lands the first ring.
Lulu is in the lead
for the first time
in the challenge.
Here we go, Kendra.
Here goes Kendra.
She's got to raise that
target first, and she does.
Yeah!
Here goes Austin.
Trying to get his target
raised, and he does.
Everybody is now firing rings.
It is Lulu.
They are win less this season.
It would be a huge victory.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
Kaleb sticks a second ring.
Lulu could win it right here.
- And they have it...
- A new tribe and a real result.
Lulu has broken
their record of losses
with a massive win.
Big fruit plate and a camp raid.
Who will get the
other fruit plate?
Austin sticks one for reba.
Yes!
Can Kendra match right here?
Here we go, Kendra.
No. You are on it,
Kendra. Right there.
- Austin with a second ring.
- He's got the hang of it now.
Belo with none.
Come on, guys. All right.
Come on. Here we go.
Brando sticks it for belo.
Austin can win it right here.
Yep.
There it is! Reba wins
the second fruit platter,
sending belo back
home empty-handed.
All right. Lulu.
When you're losing,
there is nothing
worse on survivor,
but when you're winning,
is there a better
feeling, sabiyah?
There's nothing that
feels better than that, Jeff.
I mean, I know
everybody's hungry,
everybody wants to be
here, but we are literally
starving in the jungle.
So if that's not motivation
for you to get after
it, I don't know what is.
All right, Lulu,
big fruit platter waiting
for you back at camp.
In addition, you're gonna
have a big decision to make.
Who are you sending? Which
camp are you gonna raid?
Reba, waiting for
you back at camp,
smaller, but still
something in that belly.
And you have to
anticipate whether or not
you're gonna have a camp raid.
Belo, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp,
and ponder what you're gonna
do if they decide to raid you.
All right, reba,
enjoy the afternoon.
So, Lulu, now you get
to make a big decision.
Which camp do you want to raid
and who are you going to
send as your ambassador?
I'd like to go, if you
guys are cool with it.
Yeah.
- I'm down.
- Yeah, I'm cool.
- It's Kaleb?
- Yeah, it's gonna be Kaleb.
Why Kaleb?
It's no surprise, Kaleb
is probably the most
social player
amongst the four of us.
He's probably the one
person we can all agree on
is perfect for this type of job.
Now the bigger question:
Which tribe are you gonna raid?
We won the challenge
and my tribe chose me
to go to the camp raid.
So here I am, geared
up, going to the boat.
And what do I see? On
the boat is a little script.
The goodwill advantage
means that if somebody
loses their vote, they
get to retain their vote.
They get to
cancel out that loss.
So, not only am I coming to
the tribe and trying make a friend,
but I have a gift to
be able to give 'em.
Who doesn't love gifts?
- Potassium, right here.
- My god, you guys.
- This is so incredible.
- I'm gonna cry.
I think I would have
paid hundreds of dollars
for this specific banana.
I know.
Lulu gets to send one
person from their tribe
to either our
tribe or belo's tribe
and raid the camp.
Lulu could go to
reba and weaken them
or they could come over
here and try to make bonds.
What are they gonna do,
come here and take our spear,
when they could
take the other ones?
- Like, that's not really gonna weaken us.
- Exactly.
If Lulu comes over
here, I will lose my...
There's no way
that's the boat already.
My god. They're here.
- Who is it? Who is it?
- Who is it?
Is that Kaleb?
- Kaleb.
- Yeah, it's Kaleb.
Hey! How's it going, Kaleb?
Kaleb. Nice to meet you.
I knew it would be
Kaleb, because I can tell
Kaleb is running that
tribe, front to back.
I'm a hugger, by the way.
That guy is charismatic.
He is persuasive.
He is a salesman.
- Where are you from?
- Canada.
I'm a city guy, so I
mean... So I knew he would
be the person they send
to kind of schmooze us,
sell us some "whatever he sells"
and, take all of our
stuff in the process.
What do you guys
all do for work?
Travel and compose
my own music. I love it.
- Right on. That's awesome.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I'm a professional
singer-songwriter.
Interesting.
Have you guys just been
harmonizing this entire time?
- Yes, we've been...
- Should we do that? - Sure.
- I love "four steps down."
- Take it away.
- Ooh.
- Ooh. A nice riff there.
- Yeah.
- That's the beginning, yeah.
Hey. You guys.
Well, this is fun.
In sales, when everyone's
having a good time,
they tend to let their
guard down a little bit more,
which gives you more
opportunity to be able to capitalize.
So what brings you here?
- It's a raid.
- We thought it just made sense
to grab the fishing
gear. Is that all right?
What fishing stuff were
you thinking of taking?
We were supposed
to get the entire set,
but we would leave
behind the spear.
This isn't about
trying to, like,
- absolutely pilfer you guys.
- Demoralize. - Yeah.
Throughout the entire
time of meeting them
and getting the
pleasantries out of the way,
all I'm thinking to myself is,
"how can I put this
goodwill advantage to use?"
You know, would
it be cool if I, like,
met with some of
you guys individually?
Maybe have, like, a little
bit more genuine sense?
You know, it's hard to kind
of, like, talk to everybody.
- You know what I mean?
- For sure.
What information can I
gather to make a decision?
Yeah. Yeah.
Kaleb comes in peace,
and, "hey, you guys,
you know that we
have to do this."
But he's definitely
a player.
- So, y'all, he is a salesman.
- He's a player.
- Yeah, he's a player. He's in sales.
- He is playing...
- What's his job?
- Marketing, but he's in sales.
When it came down to
it, the thing he wanted...
Which was so
smart... is information.
No. I have the
safety without power.
Drew telling me that, yes,
he went to the journey, and,
yes, he got an advantage,
means that he's a
player in this game.
And I like that.
I got an advantage
to give to somebody
- on this tribe.
- You're kidding.
This is the goodwill advantage.
Essentially, if somebody
has lost their vote...
Okay.
It allows you to at least
have that chance to...
To vote anyways and
use this to counteract that.
Interesting.
I'd like to give it to
you, start building trust.
Yeah.
I don't think that
people really see us...
- No, I don't think so, either.
- Working together quickly.
- And I think you're here to play.
- Yeah, I hope so.
Kaleb gives me this
beautiful piece of paper,
goodwill advantage.
And right off the bat, goodwill.
He likes me.
Advantage. He's
trying to help me.
And so, right away, he tells
me that with this advantage
you can vote at
one tribal council,
even if you have lost your vote.
And this is an
excellent advantage,
not for me, but
for my dear buddy
Austin, who doesn't have a vote.
I've had really good
conversations with everybody,
and I feel like if
there is a swap,
I will let our tribe know
that I feel really good
about you guys as well.
Yeah.
- 100%.
- Okay?
Today was a really good day.
I was ecstatic about
how this raid went.
I think not only did I
maximize the supplies,
I maximized the
absolute most amount
of information that I
could have gathered.
What is it?
"Goodwill advantage.
It allows somebody who
has lost their vote to vote."
The plan is definitely
to tell Julie and Dee
about the goodwill advantage,
because we didn't
tell Dee about the idol
and she was a little fussy
about it, you know? She was like,
"are you keeping things
from me?" She was suspicious.
So right away when
I get it, I tell the truth.
- This is huge.
- Yeah.
This advantage
I mean, music to my
ears. Like, this is fantastic.
I don't have a vote, so
for me, that is exactly
what I need. Hopefully
not anytime soon,
but it's always nice
to have one little
piece of protection
if this stupid frigging
idol isn't found.
- Man.
- Yeah.
I can't believe
we're eating grapes.
- I forgot what grapes tasted like.
- I know.
Best day of my life.
- For real.
- I can't believe that this morning
we were eating raw papaya.
We are no longer
the Lulu losers.
We have been down and out.
We've been defeated
multiple times,
over and over and over.
And to finally win
feels super great.
- We killed that challenge.
- Honestly,
- we killed it.
- We did so well.
When Kaleb threw
that toss, it was like
I literally ran into
his arms. I was like
I know.
I've never jumped in
somebody's arms like that before.
And you know what?
We're gonna go into that
immunity challenge tomorrow,
and we are going to crush it.
Emily really made
a shift in her energy,
in her conversations,
in her demeanor.
And now that she's
a little more calm
and not as chaotic,
I'm like, "okay, this
Emily I can work with."
And so we have the right
ingredients now to win.
I mean it when I say,
like, "I'm with you."
Yes. And that's that.
- No, seriously, like... right.
- I really don't care about anybody else.
- So, like, if... right.
- But I'm acting like I am.
Me, Kaleb and Sean...
We've been together
from the beginning.
I love Kaleb. He's a great guy.
But I know I do not want
to sit with Kaleb at the end.
Of course, Kaleb,
great guy, very likable.
- And he's a very eloquent speaker.
- Yeah.
Yep.
I mean, did you see him
in the challenge today?
I know.
Yep. Killed it.
Is it too early?
It's very early.
Don't get me wrong.
But doing it now, we
wouldn't have to rely
on other people that we don't
really know to vote for him.
It would just be our
decision. And that's that.
Yeah.
I would love not to go
back to tribal council,
but if we have to
go, Kaleb's a beast.
He is the biggest
threat on this beach.
Come on.
I still don't have my vote.
We actually need to talk
to you about something.
So it's very, very important...
Your behavior... no.
Don't do that to me.
To get Emily to vote Kaleb out.
- Me and Sean both kind of agree...
- Really?
That none of us want to
sit with Kaleb at the end.
Yeah. Yeah. He wins. I agree.
He's already proven
himself to the whole...
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- He wins.
The smile and
the hair and the...
- "Hey, how you doing? What's up?"
- And the story.
- Yeah.
Because I'm aware of the fact
that it's, you know, a strong
situation that I go home
if we lose, then I
am open to anything.
If you guys tell
me who to vote for,
I will vote for that person.
My jaw just drops.
I mean, I'm shocked,
because I've seen
those three as a
power three for a while.
We have this new trust
thing going on with you.
- It's got to be Kaleb.
- Yeah.
Is that him? Is that him
coming up? I think that is him.
- I heard woo-ing.
- I guess we should go greet him.
There's a lot of
situations that are
running around in
my head right now.
My gosh.
On one hand, I have Kaleb,
who has been really kind to me
ever since the
first tribal council.
And he's come up to me and said,
"I want to work with you."
But at the same time, he's
an extremely social player,
in a way that I'm not
and that Sean's not.
And sabiyah's social, but
not to the extent that Kaleb is.
Kaleb is kind of running the
social game around here at Lulu.
They were like, "we love Lulu."
So I think there's some
opportunity to work with them.
I don't think Kaleb
is quite aware
that there have been
those conversations
around what a
threat he is, socially.
It seems to me that he's lacking
a little bit of the perspective
of what a threat these social
connections have made him.
- Have fun!
- Thank you.
Goodbye, sailors. Au revoir.
Today, the boys
took the raft out, and
we were out there
having a great time.
We were out there, you know,
trying to provide for the tribe.
There's nothing like it.
It's like going
to another world.
It's just me, the
fish, the coral,
and I'm the king down there.
There's nothing bigger than
me down there, so, I'm the boss.
Jake... I had, like, a
small talk with him... finally.
- Okay. What did he say?
- And it's like, "hey,"
"like, we haven't
really talked, and, like,
"I really like you,
and I feel like
we've been connecting a lot
over the past, like, two days."
And he's like, "I
know." He's like,
"that's my fault. I'm so sorry."
I think the looming threat
of tribal council is
on everyone's mind.
It's been on everyone's mind,
especially after
losing a challenge.
So, the boys decide
to take out the raft,
and then, I'm back
behind with the girls,
so we have an
opportunity to talk
pretty freely while
they're out on the water.
Jake is not an option,
I feel like, at this point.
Okay.
Bruce is annoying, and
I get the vibe that my
tribe... they love Bruce.
So any slight thing that
they say about Bruce
in a negative way... I
want to validate, highlight,
emphasize, like, repeat
over and over again
in order to make sure
they feel comfortable
voting Bruce out.
You think it might be a
good idea to get Bruce?
He's a dangerous player as
far as, like, merge goes, 'cause
people are either gonna
love him or hate him.
What did Jeff say?
"Play like it's your
second time." For Bruce,
- it's his second time.
- It is his second time.
Katurah wants to target Bruce,
but Brando is my number
one, so I know I need
to talk to Brando.
I'm in the middle with you.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's you and me.
Yeah, definitely.
- So I want us... I want us to touch base.
- Yeah.
We're right in the middle
'cause on the one side,
you know, we have the
boys you can go with.
On one side, we
have the girls, so
we're in the hot seat.
Yeah.
I want us to debate
and to make sure that
we make the right decision.
She's a little scary.
When I cast that vote,
the line is drawn in the sand,
and I will piss off some people.
- Last night, we were crabbing, hunting.
- Yeah.
- We found a beware advantage.
The first thing that came
out was a clue, which was...
Well, there's multiple
tasks that have to be solved.
The first one was to
decode that message.
- So, I got a piece of paper.
- Yeah.
It's, like, the bottom half,
and you just line it up,
and then, eventually,
it spells a word.
So it took, like,
literally, like, a minute
once you had the...
Drew and I want to continue
to build strong trust,
so, I came... 80% clean.
You know, I-I told
Dee and Julie that,
"hey, I found the
beware advantage."
But what I lied about
was when I found it.
All good.
Yeah, yeah. Okay,
thank you guys.
- Yeah. - Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
You know, I don't
think they would have
told us had we not caught drew.
But regardless, the
moment that we found out
that he did find a
beware advantage,
and he was looking for an idol,
mama Julie and I... we
decided that it's like, "hey."
"All right, we're
gonna work together,
and we're gonna
help you find this idol."
I'm pretty sure
it's in this area.
What we have to
do is just dig around.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So right now, the plan is,
one person babysits sifu and j.
While the rest of
us start looking.
And if we can pull
something like that off
and have three people digging,
we might be able to find
this sooner rather than later,
and I need this badly.
We've dug around here,
we've dug around there.
- I don't know.
- Like, what the heck.
We cannot find the idol,
and honestly, I am
ready to give up.
- We got to think smarter, not harder.
- Yeah.
What the hell?
So under the palm tree,
I see a rope, and I'm like,
"what the hell is a rope
doing under the soil?"
And we're like, "god, please",
"please, please,
please, let this be it.
Like, this will change
the entire game right now."
"Break a rock near water well."
- Okay, so...
- You got something?
That rope looks obvious,
though. They're gonna know.
- Okay.
- So let's hide it.
So we're freaking out.
We're, like, going
crazy. We're like,
"okay, let's put
the evidence back."
So we threw the rope away where
we knew nobody would go grab it,
and in that exact same moment,
j. Was walking towards us.
Ooh. So I don't know. Maybe
we should look around here.
What do you think, around here?
Mama Julie and I are, like,
in an unspoken agreement.
Like, "dude, we need to
put our best acting faces on."
I'm gonna look over there.
You guys want to spread out?
- Yeah, let's do it. I'll look here.
- All right.
I don't want j.
Suspicious, but right now,
I've got to get this
hammer to Austin, asap.
What do we got here?
Julie hands me a hammer
that says, "break a
rock near water well."
- Right now, you need...
- Go, go, go, go.
At this point, my
heart is racing.
In my head, I was
like, "I'm never gonna
get past the stage of digging."
And the fact that we got past it
is, like, I was
exhausted, I was tired.
And all of a sudden, I had
all the energy in the world.
- Do you want to do it?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Okay.
My god. My god.
Okay, let's see what it says.
What does it say?
As soon as I read that sentence,
I hugged drew, we start
jumping, we're cheering.
Like, I have my vote
back. We have an idol.
It's, like, the greatest
moment of all time.
This has a lot of text.
So I start reading it
and immediately, I get
slapped in the face with,
"this idol is only good
for one tribal council."
And I'm like, "are
you kidding me?"
- So...
- Nobody's gonna believe it, but...
The mechanics of this
are very complicated.
They are.
This idol is new
because it's conditional.
It has a very short lifespan,
but you can
extend that lifespan.
You can buy some health care.
- What a good day, what a good freaking...
- Let's go.
If you sacrifice your vote
that first tribal council,
oop, you're after the merge.
You know, can
live a little longer.
If you sacrifice your
vote that second time,
oop, all the way to
the end of the game,
all the way to the final five.
It is as good as a legitimate,
real, tried and true idol.
- You're kidding me.
- Are you kidding?
- Yeah. -It's... you're kidding.
- You're kidding.
Mama Julie and I...
We didn't really need to
give that hammer away.
We could have gone to
the water well by ourselves,
smashed it and kept
the idol for ourselves.
But to be honest, at this
point, good alliances...
That's what's gonna get
me further in the game.
We're good.
Solid.
And also, it solidified
the four of us.
Now we know that there is trust.
You know, like,
before, we felt it.
Now we can prove
that there is trust.
- Love you.
- I love you so much.
Come on in.
Good morning, reba.
Good morning, Jeff.
- Good morning, Lulu.
- Morning, Jeff.
Good morning, belo.
- Jeffrey.
- Good morning.
All right.
Shall we get to today's
immunity challenge?
First things first.
Got to take back the idols.
Come on, j.
We'd like to exchange
this one for the bigger one.
Okay.
Once again, immunity
is back for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna
race out with a cart
and release two keys.
Those keys will release
very heavy puzzle pieces
that you're gonna
put on your cart.
Then you're then gonna
take your cart apart,
get it through a barricade
and reassemble it.
Once you reach the end,
one person will be
your caller, your eyes.
The rest of the group
will work together
to solve a massive cube puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
Losers, tribal council
where somebody will be the
third person voted out of survivor45,
and as a penalty for
losing... sorry for you
I will take your flint.
Lulu, remarkably, still have
not had flint, seven days in.
Sit-outs. Reba, sitting out two.
Cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Who's gonna sit out of this?
We're both sitting out.
Julie and Dee are gonna sit out.
Belo, two extra people.
Sit-outs today gonna
be Brando and kellie.
Sit-outs, take a
spot on the bench.
Everybody else, give
you a minute to strategize.
Get it on! Here we go.
All right, here we go.
- For immunity.
- Best of luck. Best of luck.
Survivors ready?
Go!
- Let's go!
- First you got to get your cart
to that first stopping point.
You're good, you're
good, you're good!
You got to release your pole...
- Go, Sean.
- And then knock the key off.
You've got it, Austin.
- Yeah!
- Austin has his.
- Get it, Kendra!
- Beautiful.
Kendra has hers.
- Yeah, Kendra!
- Yes, girl!
Reba and belo
did it very quickly.
Lulu taking a long time.
You got to get your
puzzle piece on.
- Come on, reba!
- Yeah, reba! Let's go!
- Sean's still working.
- No. No, not through.
From the top.
There you go. Push.
- There we go.
- There it is for Lulu!
Aah!
Let's go, belo! Let's go!
Here goes Kendra,
heading up for belo.
Let's go, belo!
Austin again for reba.
Come on, reba! You got this!
Austin has the key!
Okay, reba!
Kendra has the key for belo.
Sean working on that key.
Yeah, from the top. You got it.
- You got it, you got it.
- There you go.
- And he's got it!
- Good job, buddy.
- Good job. Good job.
- That's right, belo!
- Keep it up!
- Belo's through.
Now you can start
taking it apart...
And getting their cart
through the barricade.
Here comes Lulu and reba.
Come on, baby. Let's go, Lulu.
Lulu's made up some time.
- We got a challenge right now.
- Yes!
- Raise.
- Come on, come on, come on.
Belo still in the lead.
- Yes!
- Watch your fingers. Watch your fingers.
Push! Yeah!
- Yes!
- Belo has everything through.
Lulu's working to get
everything through.
Let's go!
- Now we go. Perfect.
- I'll go.
Let's lift.
Reba has hit a roadblock.
Puzzle pieces that they put
through first are blocking them.
Got to go.
Belo may have their
cart back together.
- Go! - Yeah!
- Yeah, belo!
It is belo back on the move.
Ripping through that obstacle.
That's how you do it!
Push, belo! Push!
Now you got to get
your puzzle pieces
on that stack before you
start working on the puzzle.
That's right, belo! Keep it up!
We've got Lulu.
Watch your feet.
Let's go fast!
- You're good, Lulu.
- Let's go.
Lulu win less in
immunity challenges.
Will that change?
They are back in this.
Ready? Yeah.
Here comes reba now.
Go! Go! Keep going!
You got it! Go, go, go!
You're good, reba.
Good job, good job, good job.
Got to get all the
pieces off first.
It's gonna be Emily
calling for Lulu.
Look for a piece
of the "I" piece.
Kendra calling for belo.
We need to find something
that goes into this corner here.
And j. For reba.
Let's go, j.! You got it!
This is a massive cube puzzle.
There we go.
It fits inside this frame.
Question is how
does it go together?
- That's it.
- That worked?
- Guys, this one.
- I think this one's in the middle.
- Okay.
I put belo in the
lead right now.
Then Lulu, then reba.
No, it doesn't fit. It doesn't
fit, sabiyah. Pull it out.
Look for the parts that
don't have anything on them.
Lulu, yet to win an immunity
challenge this season.
They are the only
tribe to go to tribal.
They won the reward challenge.
Can they do it again here?
Out the way, out
the way, out the way!
This is where
frustration will set in.
- Sorry, Kaleb.
- You're exhausted.
These pieces are heavy.
- That's it. Yup. Go.
- There we go.
- Yup, yup.
- Good job. You're almost done.
Reba now making
a lot of progress.
- You guys, you got to hurry.
- These puzzles can
- come together very fast.
- Go! Push!
Reba with another piece.
Austin, drew, sifu and
j. Doing a great job.
- Okay. You guys got...
- Are you ready?
We got to kick it into
gear, and we got to move.
There we go.
Belo with another piece
of the outside frame.
You can't slow down, belo!
Lulu's taking everything apart.
You want to take that? I'm
gonna work on the bottom piece.
Sure.
Sabiyah frustrated
but still laughing.
There goes reba
with another piece.
And then that goes here.
- Come on, Jake, Jake!
- Belo with another piece.
Come on!
Lulu quickly starting
to fall out of this.
It's okay, guys.
It's all right. Just keep going.
Reba's down to one piece left.
Yes! Yes!
Reba has it.
Reba wins immunity.
We're looking for one more.
Yes!
- That goes right there.
- Belo, one piece left.
They feel it.
- All right. Awesome.
- Is this it?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Push in the middle.
- You have time to push?
- Yup. That's it!
- Yes.
That's it!
Yeah, belo!
Belo wins immunity,
sending Lulu to tribal council
for the third straight
time this season.
You're a beast.
And the emotion
starts to pour out.
We worked so hard!
A familiar despair
- I am so proud of you guys.
- For Lulu.
It's all right. Take
a deep breath.
Reba, congratulations again.
Thank you.
No tribal tonight. Belo,
- you pulled it out again.
- Yes. Yes.
Belo stays intact.
Nobody going home.
Reba, belo, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
No tribal council tonight.
Nobody going home.
Stay strong, guys. Everybody.
That is a good
feeling on day seven.
All right, Emily, you
have this great victory.
You win the reward.
But out here, when
it really matters,
when your life is on
the line, another loss.
So I know what's gonna
happen back at camp.
What's the feeling right now
before you get to that strategy?
It's the worst feeling, and
to tell you the truth, like,
I go through my stages
of grief differently.
I'm not sad right
now. I'm angry.
I'm frustrated 'cause
I just watched belo
and reba celebrate their victory
'cause they have
no clue what it's like.
They have no clue what it's like
to get to know
people this deeply
and then go and
then send them home
because someone's
heart's breaking tonight,
and none of us want that
to happen, but it's going to.
All right, Lulu,
three immunity
challenges, three losses.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight
at tribal council,
where somebody
will be the third person
voted out of survivor45.
Come on.
Lulu just cannot win.
I'm exhausted, I'm hungry.
I'm destroyed from
that immunity challenge.
But I have gotten hints
from sabiyah and Sean
that maybe they're interested
in flipping the vote on Kaleb.
However, realistically,
I know I'm at the
bottom of this tribe
and they can take the easy vote
and send me home
at this tribal council. So,
I'm anxious, I'm shaking,
and I'm honestly afraid.
Man, that was a huge fall.
Deep in my gut, I feel
that the only reason
Lulu won the reward was so
that we can have the inevitable fall
that we always have coming
into the immunity challenge,
and losing once again
and once again going
to tribal council.
We're gonna be moving
down to three people
while everybody
else has full teams.
It's crazy. I can't
believe this is happening.
Again.
God. Nobody imagines
this is what their
survivor journey
- is gonna look like, you know?
- I know.
Sean and sabiyah are
gonna go after Emily.
And as much as I
want to work with Emily,
I don't think I can save her.
It may be smarter
to try and work
with Sean and sabiyah
and be able to try and make it
to the next stage of the game.
And if she does put
her shot in the dark
I can make it seem
like we're voting you.
- "Man, we can't win with Kaleb"?
- Yeah.
Then we don't have to
worry about a shot in the dark.
- Tell her me.
- You?
You tell her me
and I'll tell her you.
Okay.
We got to be real careful,
and we got to think.
We got to make sure
our stories are straight.
Yeah.
It's got to be Kaleb tonight.
So I'm letting him believe that
he's running the show tonight.
With a character like Kaleb,
you got to do it
really, really carefully.
If he even smells that
I feel a different way
or Sean feels a different way,
he could vote for me.
I don't have a vote.
He could-he could tell
Emily to vote for me.
I'm gonna put my idol in
the fire as soon as we walk in.
I'm dropping it in the...
'Cause I need the most time
to let all of the wax melt.
So, let's try to
drag this tribal out.
Tonight, I plan to drop
that idol in the flames
in the middle of tribal council.
I'm hoping that that fire
in the middle is hot
enough to melt it.
I'm hoping that we sit there
long enough for it to happen.
I need that idol.
I need my vote to
be reactivated tonight.
Yes.
- Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect.
- Same.
Okay.
So I'm gonna have
to burn that at tribal.
Exactly.
The idol. Yes.
Okay.
You're just like.
Emily feels like
she's on the bottom.
She feels like she's on the
bottom because she knows
that there's information that
she's been left out of the loop.
So I'm telling Emily
that I have an idol
to cement the trust of our
three because it's Kaleb.
Yeah.
What sabiyah and Sean
want me to do is
to vote out Kaleb.
But sabiyah pulling out
a waxed immunity idol
makes me think
that she hasn't been
honest and truthful with me,
whereas Kaleb has actually
been willing to work with me.
So I need to do everything
in my power to keep him here.
But Kaleb doesn't
realize that it's him.
Kaleb thinks it's me, and he's
still playing with these guys.
And unless I tell Kaleb
that unless he writes
sabiyah's name down tonight,
he is the one that
is going home.
It's not me. I know that.
I'm 100% positive they're
writing your name down.
So I need you to write
sabiyah's name down
because I'm writing
sabiyah's name down, too.
I...
This isn't like, " Emily
trying to save her ass."
This is Emily trying
to save your ass.
Whose name are you writing down?
I'm 100% writing sabiyah's name.
I'm telling you, I
don't know how to.
Emily says, "hey, the
votes are against you."
Do I believe that
100%? Not necessarily.
Because sabiah's
plan was to tell Emily
to vote me out tonight.
And I really do believe
that sabiyah and Sean
want to work with me.
So, even though I
absolutely am a possibility
of going home tonight,
I don't think that's
how it's gonna go.
- There's a chance that...
- Okay? I promise. -Okay.
We're not switching.
"So you need to
get on board." Yeah.
Okay.
Right now, I have two options
in front of me. I can ride
with my alliance
and take out Emily.
Alternatively, I can
vote out sabiyah.
It'd be a big, big, big move.
But what happens if
there's a tie? What happens
if sabiyah gets her vote back?
I actually haven't fully
made a decision yet here,
as I'm sitting
here in this forest,
in terms of what
I'm going to do.
I've really built myself
in to two different sides,
and it's now up to me to decide
what I'm gonna do about it.
All right. Well, let's
start with the obvious.
What's up, sabiyah?
So, I found an idol,
but it's in the wax,
and as you know,
we don't have fire.
So, I haven't had a vote
since I found it, and,
tonight is just too critical
- to not have a vote.
- Okay.
- So I brought some tools.
- Wow.
So, that I can, see
about this. Yeah.
You know, Tony...
he had a bag of tricks.
I got a trucker tool set.
You know what I mean?
- Well, it's burning.
- Exact...
That's the gist, ain't it?
I wanted to come out
and just get it over with.
I mean, these guys...
they've been briefed.
I mean, if we're
going down to three,
it's gonna be our alliance
if there's a possible
switch, possible merge.
So, you know, this
is gonna potentially
save one of us
in the future, so...
Let's check on it.
I knew that there would be
something in the center, so,
we'll just let that cook for
a little bit, if that's all right.
All right.
Well, while that's melting,
let's review the
past couple of days.
Kaleb, you went
to do a camp raid.
How did that go and what
did you share with the tribe?
Unfortunately, the only thing
that we could really steal
of impact was fishing gear,
and we don't have fire.
But it was really great
because I was able to meet
with different members of that tribe
and bring information
back to our team, which,
in a swap or in a merge,
will hopefully help us navigate
the next stage of the game.
Wow. Look at that.
Sabiyah's on the grill.
It is a survivor cook out.
Machete, I felt like,
is kind of built
for this, right?
It's like a spatula almost.
It's working.
So, Emily,
at the end of today's
challenge, you were frustrated.
What part of that carried over
when you got back to your camp?
Yeah, it was frustrating
because I know it's my game line.
So, me failing in the calling
position, the rest of the team
failing in the puzzle
position felt like
this stamp at the end of
my game of survivor, right?
And so, coming back to camp,
we did what we always do,
which was scrambled. And
is my brain now scrambled?
- Yes, it is.
- It sounded like
you were talking past
tense, that you feel
the stamp is done,
that you're going home.
First tribal council
we were at, Jeff, I said,
"look, these three are
clearly working together.
They're very strong together."
And so, yeah, I've
done everything
in my power today,
but ultimately,
I'm not the person who's writing
down everybody else's votes.
Sabiyah, is Emily
close to being right
that she still feels on the
outside of the three of you?
I think so.
I mean, I feel like anybody
that would take such
harsh jabs early
I mean, she was coming at
me, she was coming at Kaleb.
Of course it lingers in
the back of your mind,
especially when you
have other teammates
that have never said your
name in a conversation
about going home.
Might be about that time.
Looks like the wax is gone.
Canteen?
- Throw it right here, okay? On the ground.
- Okay.
This is an entire operation.
Gonna leave it for a bit.
So what is it you're
kicking over? It's dark.
Looks like we have
some type of scroll,
but I'm gonna let it
cool out for a little bit,
just for safety.
All right, so, Kaleb, was there
a conversation or was
this an afternoon where
the three of you said,
"this is easy... it's Emily"?
You know Emily is not
gonna just say, "hey, guys,
you know, it's been a pleasure."
She wanted to meet with all of
us, she wanted to make plans.
I would say the fear
in my shoes is that
she would paint me as a target.
- How about you, sabiyah?
- What's your fear
that Emily might have done
today behind your back?
I would say a lot of the same.
I mean, she's been left
out of a lot of situations.
Even with the idol. She
just found out about it today.
So it could make her feel like,
"let me pull Kaleb and say,
'hey, sabiyah, you
know, she has an idol.'"
and, you know, Kaleb... he's
been my guy from the beginning.
We are perceived as a couple,
we are perceived as a pair.
And sometimes, that
could be good or bad.
And Jeff, survivor
is a game with a lot
of twists, swaps, advantages.
So, having the strongest core
is gonna be a
great thing because
- anything could change tomorrow.
- So, sabiyah,
how are you feeling
about your idol right now?
- It's cooled down.
- It's cooled off.
Yeah, I'm feeling
pretty good about it.
I can't wait to
see what's inside.
All right, well, sabiyah
has her idol. It is cooled.
It's in her pocket
and it is time to vote.
Emily, you're up.
Okay.
I know that Emily and
Sean are voting Kaleb,
and Kaleb voted Emily.
So, if I don't vote,
I get the idol until the
merge, which is huge.
My god. Y'all are killing me.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an
advantage or an idol
and you want to play it, now
would be the time to do so.
Y'all good?
I'm good.
- I'm good.
- Yeah.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Sabiyah.
Kaleb.
One vote sabiyah,
one vote Kaleb.
One vote left.
Third person voted
out of survivor45...
Sabiyah.
That's two. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
- Wow.
That's wild.
Well, I didn't think I'd
be here this early, Jeff.
I'm not gonna lie.
Sabiyah, the tribe has spoken.
- Who?
- Lulu!
- We love you, sabiyah.
- Love you, sabiyah.
Way to rock it.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
Everybody drop your buffs.
We are switching tribes.
This is music to a girl's ears.
Next time on survivor...
Now we're starting
to build new memories
and back stab each other.
We got to pivot and
we have to play now.
I got to be ready to jump ship.
Thank god I'm a good swimmer.
I didn't vote because I
just didn't think I needed to.
I mean, after all the
conversations that I had,
I was sure it was Kaleb
going home tonight.
But, um, even though,
you know, I got blindsided,
you blindside the best players.
You blindside the people
that you're afraid of.
So it's good to know
that they were scared,
and they did what
they had to do.
So, they got me
tonight, I'm not gonna lie.