Welcome to Survivor45.
[cheering and whooping]
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
What I have for advantage
is essentially done.
I'll push back against Bruce.
He's literally
instructing us
on how to play the game,
so, a little contradictory.
"Until you've taken possession
of the idol,
"you cannot vote
at Tribal Council.
"Your first task: decipher
the coded message
on your tribe flag."
And inside of it
is this.
EMILY:
It doesn't take a genius
to look at this group of people
and pull out
the strongest alliance.
-Who are we talking about?
-Sabiyah and Kaleb.
SABIYAH:
Because you look at us that way,
you have kind of
isolated yourself.
Everything in my body
is like, "I'm not
going back to that camp."
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
But I have a ton of respect
for Hannah and her decision.
I knew Hannah had been
having struggles,
but not to that extent.
So, she was like,
"Send me home, please."
And part of me can see why
she would do that because
I'm feeling like
a Lululemon right now.
We are going
through the wringer.
I mean, the fact that we didn't
get a machete and pot
for a few days, and now
we're still without flint
and fire is
literal life out here.
EMILY:
For what it's worth,
tonight, for me, you know,
I realize as it's coming
out of my mouth, it sounds like
I am attacking you guys,
and that's not what
my intention was. I... I just...
It's been hard for me
to make inroads with people.
It doesn't necessarily give you
the right to point guns at us.
I was kind of offended,
I'm not gonna lie...
Like we have this,
like, secret alliance.
Like, you called him
"Number One"
and Sean's "Number Three"
and all this stuff.
I feel like I'm kind of
being gaslit here because
y'all are coming for me.
That's genuinely how I felt.
SABIYAH:
'Cause, like, you kind of
already see yourself in a way,
and it makes it hard
for us to even get to know you
because you're so adamant
about being somebody
that's not liked.
EMILY:
Well, my game blew up tonight,
that's for sure.
Um, it's hard
to even know where to begin.
Um, I definitely knew that my
name was on the chopping block.
My thought process was "Okay,
well, let's point out, Sabiyah,
Kaleb and Sean
have gotten really close."
I did not expect for Sabiyah
to react the way that she did.
She took it
extremely personally.
Is there anything
I said in particular
that I can apologize for
that will make you feel better?
I mean, I can't help how I feel,
just like how you can't help
how you say things.
But do you understand that
I knew it was do or die for me?
I had a choice to make, and
I wanted to stay in this game,
and excuse me for trying
to do something to, like,
you know, better that situation.
If that's how you feel,
then that's okay.
-Like I said, you feel
how you feel, I feel how I feel.
-Yeah.
Hannah quit,
and we're stuck with Emily.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't feel like
she's as aware of herself
and how she comes across.
Do you think
she wants to be alone?
SABIYAH:
I feel like she's blaming us
but then not trying
to change her behavior at all.
I'm having a tough time
with Emily.
Emily, like, it matters
what you say to people.
Like, I don't care
if you mean it or not.
It matters.
Like, tact is a thing.
If Emily wants to be Emily,
there's no way
I could work with her.
I mean, as you can see
at Tribal tonight,
she doesn't really mesh well
with the group.
EMILY:
I didn't know
that she was so sensitive.
SABIYAH:
Obviously,
she's bad news,
and I know she is.
♪ ♪
SIFU: Everything is going well
for Reba.
We're actually a winning tribe.
I feel like a kid
in a candy shop.
This is the islands of Fiji.
Like, this is amazing,
a place to be.
I want to have fun for my soul,
for my spirit, my mind,
my physical. I'm being pushed.
And I'm enjoying
every bit of it.
That's something
really weird, Austin,
is I can punch things
really hard with this hand,
and I don't really feel it.
But I used to punch trees as a
kid like it was practice for...
SIFU:
Yes!
-You okay?
-Oh, yeah. Yeah.
J. MAYA: I get that we have
a really good thing going,
but at some point, we're gonna
lose an immunity challenge.
So I just want an advantage
so desperately,
and I truly believe
that there is a code
hidden in that flag.
The first word, so to speak,
if we take this pattern
to be true, is
one letter, which could
only hypothetically be "A."
It makes sense.
It's exactly the kind of thing
thatSurvivor would do, is put
a language on the flag
that we have to decode.
If we can just figure out
which letters form words,
we can maybe
reverse-engineer the cipher.
I've always maintained
that visual puzzles
are kind of my specialty,
but I could be just
completely overthinking this.
But this is the kind of game
where you do feel like
you have to overthink things.
There's two lines and then
there's another two lines,
but then the lines get weird,
but there's...
-It does...
-Returns here.
Yeah, I don't... That's why
I don't really think that...
DREW: Yeah.
AUSTIN:
We're all superfans.
We are very smart,
very perceptive.
Everyone's looking
at these weird symbols,
trying to figure out
how to crack it.
Little do they know, on day two,
I found a Beware Advantage, and
I have this message here
that I can use to decode
the message on the flag.
Finally, I'm by myself at camp,
and in my head I know I have
maybe, like, 15, 20,
30 seconds, maybe.
So I got up,
grabbed this note, ran.
My mind was racing.
My adrenaline was pumping.
I put it on the symbols
and just slid it around,
trying to find anything
that I could match it with.
No luck.
Until I realized the spacing
was what was important.
And once I was able
to figure that out,
I'm 99% sure that it says,
"Dig in the fallen palm tree X."
Now I have to find
a fallen palm tree,
I have to find an X
or I have to find fallen palm
trees in the shape of an X.
Finding this idol is proving
to be so much more difficult
than I thought it would be.
And right now, I have no vote,
which is terrifying.
JAKE: Bruce, you want
to give this a shot, man?
Flint. I need it.
I'm ready to go.
You're working
your ass off, man.
KATURAH:
Damn, Bruce.
JAKE:
Nice, dude.
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
-Hey, seriously...
-Oh, yeah.
That is a bonfire.
Yes, dude. Yes.
We got a pot and machete now
and flint.
It makes our lives
a whole lot easier.
In fact,
we were able to get
the fire going immediately.
Bruce is killing
that fire thing.
We call him Uncle Bruce
because you know what,
he's taking care of us.
[vocalizing]
JAKE:
But more importantly,
Bruce is hilarious, man.
Ah! [laughs]
JAKE: He is always coming up
with a joke.
He's always making a face,
making a funny sound.
[speaking gibberish]
[laughs]
JAKE:
Reminds me of a lot of people
from Boston.
Like, that's kind of why
I vibe with Bruce.
-Little dunce cap.
-KENDRA: It's terrifying.
That's right.
BRUCE: The plan
of being crazy Uncle Bruce
seems to be working out
very well.
I put on that smiling face,
I laugh and giggle, but
we have things
that need to get done.
They're working
at a snail's pace.
You know, in the back
of my head, I'm like, "Aah!"
I feel like you're gonna
uncle me right now.
-Yup. He's got the uncle face.
-He's got his uncle face on.
[Jake laughs]
BRUCE:
I want to say,
"Go get it done,
and once it's done,
go do what you want."
But I can't do that to them.
Do I do it to my own kids?
Hell, yeah, I do.
We can have the pot, so put it,
like, right in the...
Middle. Right there.
That's good. Right there.
KATURAH: Every five minutes,
Bruce is
explaining you something,
telling you how to do something.
I used to navigate
via the stars,
and I know that right now,
it's about 12:00.
KATURAH:
He's like, "Don't call me dad,
call me uncle."
But you're acting like dad.
Bro, I'm gonna need you to do
me a favor. Focus on one thing.
KATURAH:
But the whole tribe--
they're, like, hungry for him,
and, oh, he eats it up.
It's, like, it feeds his soul.
I can see him happy.
"Let me show you how to do it."
Oh, there were so many, so many
videos that were made online.
-JAKE: Yeah.
-Like...
KATURAH:
And then secondly,
Bruce became a little bit
of a celebrity
after his episode aired, and
he will keep
reminding you of it.
And what's the most
annoying thing
people can do? Name-drop.
And now, I've talked to him
a bunch of times. Coolest dude.
He's a threat, and he's trying
to play it down,
and nobody sees it.
I'm like, "What the hell?!"
Is everybody blind here?
EMILY:
There has to be something hidden
in this camp somewhere.
I feel like my game--
it's do-or-die right now.
I can't just sit around
and do nothing.
So I need to do something
to at least
make myself feel better,
and I need to just keep looking
to the extent that I can
without it being suspicious.
Yeah.
BRANDON:
I think one of you guys have
to go with her.
KALEB:
So our option would be
-to do an idol search
in pairs or in teams...
-SEAN: Yeah.
so that way there's somebody
who has an eye on her.
-BRANDON: Yeah.
-KALEB: Seriously.
Emily's, like...
She's already searching,
so we might as well... find her.
BRANDON:
Emily is desperate,
and she's looking for the idol.
That's not good.
She is now
public enemy number one.
BRANDON:
We were kind of running around
like chickens
with our heads cut off
searching for Emily,
but really, I would love
to go find that idol.
I know how to find these idols.
I've watched people find these
idols. I know the strategies.
Not only did I want to get it.
I just
didn't want Emily to get it.
Emily?
Hey. Just had a talk
with everybody.
We all agreed
we're all splitting up.
It's me and you,
and then the boys are going.
This was our way
of including you.
-See? You know what I mean?
-Yeah. I mean, I can read
between the lines on this,
though, which is
that y'all don't want me
to find the idol independently.
-Yeah, if you...
-Um, so...
Okay. I mean,
that's your prerogative.
EMILY:
I think it was
a little bit obvious to say,
"Hey, Emily,
pair up with Sabiyah
so you guys
can go look together."
So, I kind of had to speak up,
but I realized
that probably put a bad taste
in the tribe's mouth,
but I think the tribe
already has a bad taste
in their mouth about me,
so I have very little to lose.
Where are you gonna head to?
I'm just gonna follow this path,
see where it leads me.
KALEB:
Cool.
EMILY:
There's a scramble right now.
We're all looking for idols, so,
I prefer to search on my own.
But the problem is that
everybody won't leave me alone.
I'm doing everything in my power
to kind of separate.
If I don't find this idol,
and if the rest
of the tribe finds it, then,
I'm 100% the person
being voted out
the next time
we go to Tribal Council.
It's gonna be somewhere
we've looked at this point.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
We just got to look better.
I would love
-to know where this thing
is at today.
-Shut the ...
Wait, wait. And...
Holy ... dude. Holy...
[Brandon speaks
high-pitched gibberish]
Okay, okay.
BRANDON:
I found an idol inSurvivor,
and I freaked out.
Oh!
Okay, so here's my thing
with these.
I don't want to open it.
It's the Beware Advantage.
I know that
you're not allowed to vote
if you have the Beware Advantage
in your possession
and you don't complete the task.
Do you want to open it?
Like, I don't...
I am adamantly saying
I don't want to open it.
BRANDON:
My vote is integral
in this game.
I didn't want to risk it.
And giving that advantage
to Sabiyah solidifies us.
We're bonded to each other.
"Retrieve it..."
Oh, my God. All right.
SABIYAH:
Fortunately, Brandon, he's like,
"Uh, Sabiyah,
I don't want to open it."
And I'm like,
"Yeah, buddy, bring it on!"
'Cause I... I want to...
I'm here to play.
Give me that Beware Advantage.
Oh.
So, if you line up
the corners...
like that, it perfectly aligns
with that tree right there.
SABIYAH:
I was on the move.
Come on.
I knew exactly
where I was going.
I hadn't been there,
but it was almost like a call.
Mm-hmm.
You think you can give me,
like, a little tabletop?
One, two, three.
-All right.
-Okay.
SABIYAH:
I'm looking high and low
for something that sticks out,
something
that's not quite right.
God, this is killing me.
But this seems like
it's about to be
a scavenger hunt from hell.
God, I feel like
we've been gone too long.
Yeah, man. I might have
to ask Sean what he thinks.
The next step was to tell Sean
and to tell Kaleb, 'cause
if I have it, they...
they got to know about it.
This is the note.
I don't have a vote.
Dude, you keep
pulling out more paper.
[laughing]
SABIYAH:
I know that that would cement
our alliance going forward.
-You think it's this one?
-For sure.
-Are you... are you okay?
-I'm good.
SABIYAH:
I could feel the presence
of the idol,
you know, and I start getting
that tingly feeling.
And we walked all around that
tree, and we couldn't find it.
Dang, Jeff, for real.
All right.
I need my vote.
I need to think this through
and then come back
at a later time.
If it's in this tree,
I don't care if we have
to lift it out of its roots,
it's here.
-DEE: It looks worse
in the sock.
-[laughing]
DEE: So, my toes are pretty.
It's just that
my big toe is just abnormally
longer than my other toes,
'cause it's usually
like this, right?
But then this toe is like this.
[laughs]
I think it looks worse
with the sock on.
Can you take my sock off?
SIFU:
I don't know, man.
Ooh. Ooh.
-Oh, my God.
-[Dee laughs]
SIFU:
Dang!
DEE:
Is that, like, really long?
[laughing]
DEE: But you know what, guys?
SIFU: Great grip. Yes.
-DEE: You want me to pinch you?
-SIFU: Yeah. Do it, do it.
-Ow!
-[laughing]
DEE:
Everybody's laughing now,
but they won't laugh later
when I win
based off a balance challenge.
AUSTIN:
Oh, my God.
Well, you could, like,
-pick up, like, a backpack.
-[laughing]
DEE:
That big toe, baby.
Let's go. Big toe energy.
[whoops] Let's go! [laughs]
SIFU:
This is such a weird thing
to say, but do you honestly
think, we're walking
down the street,
any of us would be friends?
Like, you know
what I mean? Like,
you would just look at me
and be like,
-"I would just want
to talk to Nick." You know?
-Not like...
I mean, only if, like, y'all
were, like, my kids' friends.
Yeah. Yeah.
-Right? Right.
-DEE: I guess it depends
on the situation.
JULIE: I've taken on
the role of Mama. I am Mama J.
And I'm kind of
leaning into that.
I was, like, super paranoid
the first two days.
-That's all I was.
-Yeah.
JULIE:
Dee is my closest ally.
I feel like she's gonna play
a loyal game, but I have
to have other alliances.
You know what, Drew?
You said that you
try to work hard
to listen to people?
-Yeah.
-I feel like you do that.
-I really try to.
-I feel it.
-Yeah, I...
-No, I feel like
you're engaged in that.
I really like Drew.
He's my son's age.
Drew needs a mom out here,
so I need to make him think
he can get through another day
because I'm here.
-You know?
-That's what I'm saying.
-I'm starving too much
to like, "Ooh, ooh."
-I know it.
But see,
I feel "loyal game" with you.
Oh, my God. I'm...
Literally, I could give you
a hug. I'm so happy.
Okay. Here's the other thing.
I work...
DREW: Yeah. Okay.
DREW: I love Austin.
-Yeah.
-Like, do you...?
Oh, Julie,
I can literally cry, man.
DREW:
Oh, I've been so nervous.
Julie wants to go
with the same four
I had already been planning.
Myself, Austin, Dee and Julie.
-I'm so glad, dude. So glad.
-All right, good, good, good.
DREW:
This is gonna
be the solid group.
So, I have
a lot of allies at this point,
which is a nice feeling.
AUSTIN:
Us four, 100%.
Okay, cool.
You feel good with us four?
-Like, 100%.
-Me too.
There is a part of me
that wants to be the king,
that wants
to domineer the tribe,
and I have
to tone that down now.
But I do envision a time
when my realm will stretch
to the whole beach.
Right now,
I am marshaling my troops
and making my feudal alliances
to bring this kingdom
into fruition.
♪ ♪
KALEB: I think I'm really
starting to get Emily.
She is somebody who likes to go
by facts and the numbers.
The problem with Emily
is she has a big mouth
and she can't get out
of her own way.
You know, I don't have
very many cards at this point.
What can I do
to build that trust?
-I think just try
and keep the strategizing lower.
-Yeah?
KALEB:
People are hating on her, but
all I'm thinking to myself is,
"How can I possibly help?"
Maybe I can nurse her back
to health,
nurse her as a stronger,
better player.
-I want to look out for you.
-Okay.
But for now, just be helpful,
be positive.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know? And, um,
-like, sharing stories
about yourself.
-Mm-hmm.
-Like, it's gonna really help.
You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
But I just feel like
it's just, like...
It's what the tribe needs
right now.
I think I brought a bazooka
go to a tea party.
-Mm-hmm.
-Um, and I need
to put the bazooka down.
KALEB:
A bad player is gonna want
to continue to isolate her,
continue
to make sure that she knows
that she's on the outs,
and, "Don't even try
and talk to me."
I want to play with you, and I
hope you can see me as an asset.
You're the only person
who's talked to me, really.
KALEB:
A good player is probably
gonna realize that
everyone needs an ally,
and Emily doesn't have anybody,
and I'm the person who's being
the most up-front with her.
And I think that I'm making
really good inroads.
-Hmm?
-You're very kind.
EMILY:
We had a good conversation.
Kaleb actually showed me
there's definitely
a lesson for the game
moving forward, right?
But there's also a lesson
for life,
which is, you know, when things
get stressful, what do you do?
In my job-- analyzing stocks--
it's analytical at nature,
but this is an emotional game.
I'm discovering that.
These people are not stocks.
Uh, people have feelings
and emotions.
Yeah.
I was being defensive,
-and I apologize for that. Yeah.
-I was being defensive.
-And I wasbeing defensive.
-I apologize
for being defensive.
EMILY:
You can't brute-force
things in life,
and I tried to brute-force
this game. And now I'm taking
some of these lessons
to heart, right?
Learning to be more calm,
learning to be less aggressive.
Yeah.
I-I can't wait
for you to eventually see it.
-It is stunning.
-[laughs]
EMILY:
But it's hard,
you know, for a tiger
to change its stripes
in some sense,
and so I need-I need
to try more than I am.
...and further kind of
irritating people.
But I also don't want it
to be like,
"Oh, Emily's not even, like,
trying to talk with us."
-I know.
-It feels like a weird situation
where I don't even know, like,
what the right thing
-to do is, kind of.
-Right.
EMILY:
I worry about playing too hard.
I feel like so much
of the issues
that I've had here
has been attitude.
And that's so hard to change.
Because attitude is so ingrained
in who you are.
And I've always been
this anxious,
nervous pessimist,
this-this...
It sounds good
to say "go-getter,"
and I mean that
in the worst way possible.
This go-getter that can't know
when to just kind of stop.
You all right?
Emotional day for me
for some reason.
-Don't worry.
Wow, the tide's really gone out.
I'm so sorry. I don't know why
I'm getting emotional.
It's that I feel like all these
emotions are just bubbling up.
But I have to remind myself
that just being here--
you know, it's something to be
proud of, and it's really nice
to think about that, you know,
this game isn't over for me.
Every day that I'm here,
I'm, you know,
-learning a bit more.
-Mm-hmm.
Are you seeing smoke,
or am I just delusional?
EMILY:
Is that a boat?
Boat!
-What?
-EMILY: We got a boat!
Do we think it's for us?
No, I think
they're delivering food.
Yeah, it's ...
Why wouldn't it be for us?
It's for us.
DEE: Guys, there's a boat!
Ay ay.
KENDRA: Thank you.
All right,
let's gather around, children.
-Gather. Come on in.
-Oh, my God.
"One person
must get on this boat.
You will return
to camp this afternoon."
BOTH:
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Okay.
[cheering, whooping,
indistinct chatter]
We are all in consensus
that I'll...
-I'll-I'll take this one?
-SABIYAH: Yeah.
-It'll be good.
-BRANDON: Well,
I'll get back,
and I'll share whatever we got.
And I totally get it,
um, but, yeah,
I mean, like, obviously, I'm in
a bad position right now, so...
-All right.
I'm putting on my shoes.
-SABIYAH: All right.
All right.
EMILY:
It felt like they were trying
to prevent me
from getting any advantages.
The same motivation as
hunting for the idol together.
-Bye, Brandon. We love you.
-[whoops]
EMILY:
This is another example
of an opportunity to change
my circumstances
slipping out of my grip.
JAKE: You two want
to rock, paper, scissors for it?
KATURAH:
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
-Oh, Brucey! Let's go, baby.
-[indistinct chatter]
KATURAH:
Bruce-- my nemesis.
He gets to go on this journey.
I'm pissed.
He doesn't need access
to anything
that would give him
any more power
than he already has.
-[laughs]
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
My tribe is eating out
of Bruce's hand,
everything he does,
and he does a lot
of stupid, annoying stuff.
-Brando, what's this?
-BRANDO: Oh, the robot?
-Yeah!
-BRUCE: Yeah!
KATURAH:
I guess I see through it.
It seems really stupid to me.
I'm just like...
I don't know. Who is this guy?
-[laughing]
-Where'd he go? Oh.
There he is. Oh.
[Jake laughs]
♪ ♪
-What's going on, everybody?
-What's up, fellas?
Man, this is happening.
-Brandon, right?
-What's happening, Drew?
-How are we doing?
-Good to see you.
So, I've seen you on TV before,
but never, never in the flesh.
[Bruce laughs]
-I'm wondering
what we're here for today.
-BOTH: Yeah.
DREW:
I want mySurvivor experience
to have a footprint,
and going on the journey
is the first step
in putting myself out there.
What do we have here?
DREW: This is
a networking opportunity.
Maybe that's
the Ivy Leaguer in me.
But this is a great time
to make some connections
that could,
you know, print me some cash
in the future.
DREW: All right, uh...
BRUCE:
I'm older than you guys,
so the way that I look at it,
-let's get some stuff together.
-DREW: Yeah.
Um, you know, so it's not moving
at the speed
that I want it to,
but the collusion that we have
-is pretty good.
-DREW: All right.
Well, how about in your camp?
-Well, I think
I started off on a bad foot.
-DREW: Yeah.
And Emily's just been kind of
the person who's...
You know,
Emily came at you immediately.
-Right? You know,
on the barge, you know.
-Yeah.
-In bad taste, I thought,
a little bit.
-Yeah. Yeah.
And it's... That is kind of
her personality.
DREW:
Brandon and Bruce--
you had the two sides
of the spectrum.
Brandon was very forthcoming.
He told us the entirety
of the tribal dynamic.
Bruce is playing it close
to the chest, and he was not
giving me anything. Probably
does not want to work with us.
Bad gameplay by Bruce, in
my opinion, very bad gameplay.
I like both of you tremendously.
Yeah, so...
-we'll see what goes around.
-Yeah.
-We'll see.
BRANDON:
Let's pick a path, everybody.
DREW:
Good luck, everybody.
-BRUCE: Yes, sir.
-Good luck, guys.
BRANDON:Survivor is all
about highs and lows,
and as a superfan, I thought
I was gonna thrive out here,
but after nearly passing away
on the barge day one,
I feel like
I have performance anxiety.
If I want to succeed in this,
I can't
spend this whole time anxious,
and the journey
for me-- it's just a chance
to see if I can let go of
all of it.
This could be
an absolute game-changer for me.
Oh, that sucks. God.
It's an opportunity
to gain power, right?
I'm playing an individual game.
As much as
I'm gung-ho
about the Lulu Tribe,
I got to stay here past the time
where my expiration date
might be up.
I am geeking out at this thing.
I've always wanted
to pull that thing.
I am the worst at puzzles.
I hate puzzles, hate 'em.
But it'd be nice
to have an advantage
with everything going on
and people recognizing who I am.
DREW:
I have, potentially,
a solid four going into
my first Tribal Council.
So it might be wiser
to hang on to my vote
to build confidence
of that group.
BRANDON:
I am at a challenge
that I don't have
to move
or lift anything or swim.
I'm...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna protect my vote.
I put too much work in
to risk my vote.
DREW:
The risks
of doing this are huge.
On the other hand, I know
that the game
is just getting started,
so it might be important
to get an advantage.
I absolutely am gonna play.
Why would I not play?
Of course I'm gonna play.
If I can't do this,
I need to get on a boat
and I got to go back
to New Jersey.
This is... this is my shot
to win something.
I'm thinking I'm gonna play.
You know,
there's really no other option.
You're out here on Survivor.
Time to get things
a little spicy.
Game time, baby.
Let's do it.
DREW:
The challenge is a puzzle.
BRANDON:
So you have, in a bag,
there are pairs
of matching tiles.
DREW:
I've got to match them all up,
and the patterns
are complicated.
And there are three
that won't match.
BRANDON:
And they have numbers
on the back of them.
You put them in the little
Survivor lockbox,
and if I do that all correctly,
you get your advantage.
We got a thin "H."
We got "H" in a pair.
We're good. Pair, pair, pair.
We got these guys-- pair.
These guys-- pair. Love it.
That's it. Okay.
We got 22, 54, 62. I'm shaking.
Let's do it. Let's do this.
Okay. That's not right.
So let's do 22.
Okay, let's do 54.
I've been waiting
a long time to do this.
And we're still gonna wait.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
This is embarrassing.
Come on. Damn it.
God, I'm choking.
Let's just calm down.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes!
Come on! Let's go!
Ah!
I want to vomit.
Oh, my God. How?
How is this happening?
This is a comedy of errors.
No.
Did I screw up a tile?
That's the same.
My matching was bad. My...
I was not good at matching.
Oh, my God.
I thought I had low points,
but this is the challenge
that was made for me!
A matching game that you would
give a kid in day care
to keep them occupied
for 20 minutes.
Well, I get to go back to camp
with no vote, so that's good.
I didn't want
the Beware Advantage
'cause I didn't want
to not have a vote.
Now I don't have a vote.
Great!
Luckily, if we lose the
immunity challenge coming up,
I feel good going
into the next Tribal Council.
I know that Emily is going
to leave once we get there,
but this is my low point.
Heck, yes.
I'm so happy.
I could have fallen to my knees.
It's the Safety without Power
Advantage.
It is
a get-out-of-jail-free card.
I have power in the game.
You know, a guy like me
is very ambitious.
You know,
he's always looking for more.
I have the Survivoritch,
and the only thing
that's gonna scratch it
is more firepower,
more ammunition.
[whooping, yelling]
Welcome home, buddy!
SABIYAH:
Yeah!
-That feels like a win.
-Yeah.
-That feels like a win
if there ever was one.
-Oh, sure.
EMILY:
I'm so excited
to hear what happened.
-How'd it go?
-Um,
so we get there,
we walk up a mountain, and
we get to the game
where we can risk the vote...
-EMILY: Oh.
-and play the game,
-which I did, and I-I...
-SABIYAH: Mm-hmm.
You had three minutes to do it.
I didn't do it.
-SABIYAH: Oh.
-So I have no vote.
-Okay.
-BRANDON: So...
SEAN:
In the first immunity challenge,
Brandon really struggled
with the puzzle.
Now he goes to this journey,
was unsuccessful.
You told us
you're the puzzle guy.
And so,
it makes you wonder, like,
"Where are your strengths?"
DREW:
Hello?
Huh.
-Hello?
-ALL: Surprise!
DREW:
Oh, my God. My tribemates--
they all run right out
from behind the shelter,
and they all start
rubbing my head.
I don't know why
that is a thing,
but they are all
rubbing my head.
All right, do you want
the best bits first, or just,
like, the dollar score in order?
DREW:
It's such a warm welcome
that I know
the right route is to tell the
truth, to tell the full truth.
All right, so here's the story.
Walked up this long beach,
and on the island is,
like, a puzzle.
If I solve the puzzle
in three minutes,
I'll get, like, an advantage.
And I did well. I solved it.
-Nice.
-And so...
-Whoa!
-[gasping]
DREW:
The advantage is
a Safety without Power.
"It allows you
to leave Tribal Council
"just before the votes are cast
and return to camp.
"You will not cast a vote,
but more importantly,
you cannot be voted out."
AUSTIN: So Drew comes back
and straight-up shows us
the note saying,
"I have a Safety without Power."
I feel that he's really trying
to play a loyal game.
The real utility is gonna happen
come the merge.
So my hope is that if one of us
is, like, in real danger...
-You give it to us.
-Yeah, we can just give this
to the Reba member
who is in trouble.
AUSTIN:
Drew came very clean
about his journey,
and I feel like
he is someone who wants to truly
play with somebody like me.
-Yo.
-Yeah.
I found a Beware Advantage.
-You're kidding.
-No.
-Okay.
-I found it.
I was gathering wood
right by the beach over there.
DREW:
Austin shared
his Beware Advantage with me.
There are, like,
explosions in my head, there are
fireworks. I'm so excited.
It spelled out,
"Dig at the fallen palm tree X."
DREW:
The best partnerships
inSurvivor are ones
that complement one another.
He has the physicality,
he has the good looks,
he has the charm,
and I have the brains.
I came into this game saying
I wanted, like,
-a J.T. to my Stephen, you know?
-I know!
Like, and you're the guy, so
I'm willing to go all the way.
Austin right now
is my ride or die.
I am committed to him
to the moon and back.
[laughing]
KENDRA: Oh, God. I knew
-I was gonna suffocate myself.
-Oh, my God.
KELLIE:
It doesn't stretch that much.
-Oh, yours looks pretty good.
-No.
-I'm going for it.
-Yeah, I was gonna...
-Oh, my God!
-Yas, queen!
[laughing]
Don't know how you do this
on regular basis.
-Not easy.
-No. Just...
[yelling, indistinct chatter]
KELLIE:
Doesn't stop, he doesn't stop.
BRANDO: Coming into this game,
I was really worried
that as a 22-year-old, young,
scrawny, Asian guy, no one would
really want to work with me.
But being out here and being out
of my comfort zone
is what makes it exciting, and
I'm kind of killing it
right now.
KATURAH: Come on, Brando.
KATURAH: You got it. You got it.
-Hilarious.
-[laughing]
BRANDO:
Putting on my own Buff
as a top--
Uh, I don't think
it's the most common thing
for guys inSurvivor to do.
But, you know, honestly, I feel
really comfortable
in that situation
'cause I've never been someone
who, you know,
bros out with the big guys.
I really like the idea
of working with you,
-KELLIE: Yeah.
-and I just wanted to say that.
Well, that's a good thing
to hear.
-Yeah, we love you.
-No. And I wanted to, like,
pull you aside
and just say that to you.
You always see like, "Oh, the
weakest woman goes home first."
And I really did not want that
to happen.
KENDRA:
I would love
to work with Brando.
And right now, the girls
are three strong, and you're not
gonna break us up.
So, I think he sees the numbers.
He's a smart dude.
He knows percentages.
So better
join us than be against us.
I want to go far
in this game with people
that I admire and I trust.
The only thing we can have is,
like, trust in people.
Right. Right.
KELLIE:
I don't know. Right now, so...
Yeah. I'm sure
they're talking right now.
-Can I just tell you how I think
it's gonna go down?
-Yeah.
You definitely
hit it on the head saying
that they're gonna
go after the guys.
I would 100% bet it was me.
-I think this time...
-They're gonna come at me first.
-It is what it is.
-You're very social, dude.
You have the charisma
of, like, 25. It's crazy.
BRUCE:
I know that I am a target, 100%.
I had a very good idea that
that was gonna be the case.
So Bruce has got
to protect himself,
be a social player and talk
to as many people
as possible on this tribe.
If you wouldn't mind,
have an open line
of communication with me.
-I'll have the same exactly
with you.
-Yeah, I got it. I got it.
BRUCE: Brando-- I've been having
a good conversation with him.
We're great friends now.
Like, I love this kid to death.
I'm trying to, you know,
team up with someone
that's got what I'm missing,
got those big muscles,
got, you know,
whatever it takes.
Want to throw everybody off?
-You're 22. I'm 46.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I feel like
you're my coach right now, man.
-Yeah, right?
-Hundred percent.
BRANDO:
I'm gonna be keeping
every option open.
I've got a strong alliance with
the girls, but at the same time,
you know, Bruce is definitely
trying to pull me in, and so,
I feel like I'm in a really
good spot right now.
BRUCE:
Brando is on board.
Kellie and I--
like, we've hit it off
from the very beginning.
BRUCE:
The four of us are definitely
coming together, so,
the beautiful word
that we can use is
"going with the majority."
-I hear you.
-Who does?
KELLIE: In terms
of working with the boys,
I hate this,
but there is an element
of strength in challenges.
Ah.
And honestly, one of
my strengths coming out here was
that I can bro out with dudes,
and I can, you know, be besties
with the girls.
-Oh, I think I smell better.
-Yeah.
Me and Brando are in the middle.
There's Bruce and Jake
on one side,
Kendra and Katurah
on the other.
I have gone back and forth
which way I want to go.
-I think we're in a good spot.
-Okay.
Think
we're in a really good spot.
KELLIE: So, if we lose
the next immunity challenge,
I'm gonna have a lot
of fallout to deal with. I...
I don't want the hammer
to come down on me.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
[whooping]
Belo and Reba,
getting your first look
at the new Lulu tribe.
Hannah voted out
-at the first Tribal Council.
-[gasps]
All right, you ready to get
to today's immunity challenge?
[whooping, cheering]
First things first,
got to take back the idols.
It's just going on a field trip.
He's coming right on back.
PROBST:
All right.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
-KENDRA: Go, let's go.
-PROBST: For today's challenge,
one player at a time
is going to climb
to the top of a tall tower,
gonna leap off,
smash a tile,
releasing your key.
You must then navigate
a floating balance beam
and swim to the end.
Then the next person does.
Once you've retrieved
all three keys,
two other players
would use those keys
to unlock your puzzle pieces
and solve a coral puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
-Yeah!
-PROBST: In addition,
you're playing for a reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
[all voicing assent]
Everything you need.
A massive set of fishing gear.
[indistinct chatter]
Second tribe to finish--
smaller but effective.
Mask, snorkel fins
and a Hawaiian sling.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
PROBST:
The last tribe to finish--
otherwise known as
the losers-- Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the second person voted out
of Survivor45,
and as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Lulu, you are still playing
to get your flint
for the first time.
-Yeah.
-All right.
Sit-outs. Belo,
Reba, you're
sitting somebody out.
New rule. It used to be
that the sit-out would reset
after a Tribal Council.
So here's the new rule.
You cannot sit out of
back-to-back challenges, period.
So whoever sits out
of this challenge will run
in the next challenge.
-Makes sense?
-Yeah.
All right, Belo,
who's gonna be the sit-out?
-Me.
-Katurah gonna sit out
for Belo.
Who's it gonna be for Reba?
-Sifu.
-PROBST: Sifu gonna sit out.
Sit-outs,
take a spot on the bench,
everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
-We'll get it on.
-[howling, hooting]
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
-[cheering, whooping, shouting]
PROBST:
It's Dee in the water for Reba,
Emily in the water for Lulu,
Jake for Belo.
You've got to climb
to the top of the tower,
get a club,
and then smash a plate,
releasing your key.
There goes Dee.
There goes Jake.
[cheering]
There goes Emily.
That's how you do it
on Survivor.
-Let's go!
-PROBST: It's Jake
to the balance beam first.
KENDRA:
Go, Jake!
PROBST:
Here come Dee for Reba.
It's a three-tier balance beam
floating in the ocean.
Nothing easy about that.
-[overlapping chatter]
-PROBST: Jake is in.
He's gonna start again.
Here comes Dee.
Here comes Emily giving it a go.
-[overlapping chatter]
-BRANDON: Are you kidding?!
PROBST:
It's Emily, very fast.
Emily, you're good!
It's Lulu in the lead.
Dee, you're good.
Jake, you're good.
[indistinct,
overlapping shouting]
SABIYAH:
You're first, Em. Keep it going.
-PROBST: Jake is up.
-KELLIE: Put it in the basket.
PROBST:
You got to get that
in the basket.
Go, Belo!
There goes Bruce.
Yeah, boy!
PROBST:
Bruce has the second key
for Belo.
Go, Reba!
Here goes J. with a big leap.
And she got it.
Just barely, but she got it.
BRANDON:
You got it, you got it.
Go, Lulu!
[grunting]
[whooping, clapping]
PROBST:
Sean connects, both
with the plate
and with his face.
There goes Bruce.
Making it look easy.
J. doing a nice job.
J. is in the water for Reba.
Sean's across.
And another face-plant for Sean.
You got to get that buoy
in the basket.
Go, Reba!
There goes Austin.
-Yes!
-And he obliterates the tile.
BRUCE:
Come on, baby.
You got it. You got it.
Go, Lulu!
Kaleb up in the air.
He's got a key.
Here comes Bruce.
-Go, Belo!
-BRUCE: Come on, baby.
Kendra smashes it.
She's got a key.
There goes Austin on the beam.
J. MAYA:
Keep it up! We're winning!
PROBST:
Austin across the beam faster
than anybody.
Kaleb now on the beam.
And he's across.
-Okay, let's start.
-You're good, Reba.
Start working on the puzzle.
JAKE:
Come on, Kendra, you got this!
PROBST:
Kendra struggling
on the beam for Belo.
Oh! Wow.
-Ooh.
-PROBST: Kendra with a big fall.
JAKE:
You got it, Kendra! You got it!
-Good job. Good job.
-PROBST: You're good, Lulu.
Start working on the puzzle.
Lulu has made up a lot of time.
It is now Belo in dead last.
-BRUCE: Go, go, go, go!
-DREW: It's a hard one, man.
[indistinct chatter]
PROBST:
It is Drew and Julie
on the puzzle for Reba,
Brandon and Sabiyah
on the puzzle for Lulu.
And here comes Kendra.
You're good, fellas.
Start working on the puzzle.
It's gonna be Brando and
Kellie on the puzzle for Belo.
KATURAH:
Let's go, Belo!
[shouts indistinctly]
Okay. Oh, my God,
that's a lot of pieces. Okay.
PROBST:
It's a brand-new
Survivorpuzzle.
Nobody knows this one.
Try to fit 'em in.
PROBST:
Put yourself in the puzzle role.
It comes with a lot of pressure,
and if you lose, it's on you.
BRUCE:
Nice and calm. Nice and calm.
-PROBST: It is Reba in the lead.
-Come on, Drew!
-Yeah.
-Good job. Good job.
-Yes!
Belo making a lot of progress.
And another piece by Brando.
We're now very tight
between Belo and Reba.
A familiar story with Lulu,
where they've been
the entire season--
dead last.
Look at the lines.
Follow the lines.
-BRANDON: I'm-- I see it.
-SEAN: Here you go, Brandon.
SABIYAH:
No, no, no, no, no.
Still very close, and
we're looking for two tribes.
Drew with another piece
for Reba.
-You're my man, Drew.
-PROBST: Belo with
a two-piece lead at this point.
It is that close.
Yeah, I'm looking.
I'm looking. I'm looking.
PROBST: Lulu, almost time
to start thinking about
who's going home tonight.
-Okay. Yes.
-Trying to find this.
Huge reward on the line.
-You want that
massive fishing gear.
-Yeah!
Belo with another piece.
I'm just grasping at stuff here.
No. Help me.
Ain't no grasping. Come on.
PROBST:
Lulu out of it.
Put it in the deep freeze
for Lulu.
-Belo down to four pieces.
-JULIE: Are you sure that's it?
-Yeah, that's it.
-Reba down to five pieces left.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is gonna be very close.
When you have it, step back.
[overlapping shouting]
Reba making a run for it
with another piece!
We're down to two pieces
for Belo.
-AUSTIN: Keep going, you guys.
Keep going.
-PROBST: Now one.
Three pieces for Reba!
Now two.
It's coming down
to the last pieces.
[indistinct shouting]
[cheering, screaming]
-PROBST: Reba pulls it out!
-Jeff!
Reba's done it.
-Huge fishing reward.
-[Sifu yells]
Belo wins immunity
-and a smaller fishing reward.
-Let's go!
Wow. What a comeback.
What a match.
That was a challenge.
-Wow.
-[whooping]
-And a familiar result.
-[Sabiyah laughs]
Lulu in dead last,
made no progress
for most of that challenge.
Back to Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the second person voted out
of Survivor45.
You got to be kidding me, man.
A very tight,
for two of you, challenge.
Reba, you pulled it out.
Immunity is yours.
-[Julie whoops]
-Nobody going home from Reba.
Belo, you pulled it out,
as well.
-Yes! Let's go!
-[cheering, whooping]
PROBST:
No one going home from Belo.
Fishing kits will be waiting
for you back at camp.
Reba, yours is huge.
Belo, yours is small,
but will get the job done.
All right, congratulations.
Swim out.
Enjoy another night off.
Everybody stays in the tribe.
-Thanks, Jeff!
-[whooping]
PROBST:
You earned it.
Let's go.
Lulu, another loss,
you're winless,
you still will not have
your flint.
And tonight,
you lose another tribe member.
All right, swim out. See you
tonight at Tribal Council.
KALEB:
This tribe is so bad.
We're like the Cavaliers
when LeBron left the first time.
We suck. We can't win anything.
This tribe is falling apart
emotionally, physically,
everything.
♪ ♪
BRANDON:
You guys-- you did phenomenal.
And the leg that I got selected
for, the leg that I felt
confident in, I lost.
I know I lost that for us,
and I have no vote tonight.
I don't have any power.
Nobody wants this experience.
Nobody wants to lose twice.
Nobody wants to have a...
a dead fire pit, but I'm telling
you this. This is-this is...
All I've ever wanted
is to be out here.
I just want you all
to know that. I love you all.
-SABIYAH: We love you, Brandon.
-The feeling is mutual, Brandon,
-We love you.
-KALEB: Yeah.
EMILY:
Is it too bold of me
to say that I think
-we know that it's between us.
-Yes.
It's one
of the two of us, right?
-EMILY: Yeah.
-They're going to come
-to a decision,
the three of them.
-BRANDON: Yeah, I'm aware.
SEAN:
Emily knows she's on the bottom,
but Brandon's
a liability in every
single challenge, in every
aspect of the challenge.
How are we ever gonna win?
I think Brandon
is not serving
our tribe at all.
SEAN: I mean...
-SEAN: Can't even do it, yeah.
SABIYAH: Right.
But Emily--
I don't want her to play it.
Oh, my God. I mean, honestly...
-Yeah, we should.
-Um...
-Right.
-Well, Brandon knows,
but she don't.
I'm hoping Emily goes home,
but I don't have a vote tonight.
Tribal Council is approaching,
and that means my time
is running out
to find this idol.
So we go back to the tree.
Try to get to the next level up.
-It's covered with ants.
-SEAN: Oh, no. It's crazy.
[Kaleb groans]
-SABIYAH:
Check in this hole here.
-Oh, my God! [exclaims]
-Oh, my God, my shoes.
There's nothing else up here.
-Yeah.
Okay.
-Yeah, exactly.
-You got to stomp, stomp.
SABIYAH:
Yeah.
They've been gone
for such a long time.
Wow. It must be so hard
to be in the power alliance,
-having to make
such tough decisions.
-[laughs]
Wow. Pity me.
What are we missing?
KALEB:
What about this vine?
This is not a coconut tree.
Do y'all see it?
-KALEB: Where?
-SEAN: Yeah, I see it.
-That's true.
-And the vine goes up that way.
-[Sabiyah gasps]
-SEAN: Shut up.
-Swear to God. [laughs]
-Shut up!
Do you see it? Do you see it?
Come on, vote. I need you.
[gasping]
[laughs]
SEAN:
Shut.
-Ah!
-KALEB: What?!
-[Sabiyah exclaims]
Yo...
Oh, holy...
KALEB:
All right.
-[laughing]
-No!
The note says,
"You must melt the candle
to get the idol."
Thanks, Jeff, 'cause Lulu
hasn't had fire this whole time.
So I don't have a vote
and I don't have my idol.
My heart drops.
[Brandon whistles]
Yeah.
Shut up.
But it's in a candle.
I have to burn it
but we have no flint.
I will not even
be voting tonight.
That's what I was thinking, but
I'm worried about everything.
BRANDON:
I hate this.
Sabiyah doesn't have a vote
and nor do I.
This is now
a three-vote Tribal Council.
I'm very nervous, but listen,
I know how good I am socially.
Socially, I am the bomb.
My pitch is that, you know,
I will be loyal.
If we hit any kind of situation
where we have to split up,
I'm Lulu strong.
-I'm with y'all.
-Totally.
-SEAN: And we trust you.
BRANDON:
It's gonna be me or Emily,
but one of us
is gonna be here tomorrow.
We don't know who it's gonna be,
but whoever it is has
got to fight, and Emily has
made people angry. I haven't.
I don't know if this...
I want to help solidify trust.
-SABIYAH: Yeah.
-I don't have a lot of options
-right now
to help solidify trust.
-Okay.
-Wow.
-You guys have my trust.
This is getting on the same page
at Tribal Council knowing
that we can trust each other
and move forward as a team.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. Of course.
Yeah.
EMILY:
I am at the stage
of desperation, so,
I gave Sabiyah the
Shot in the Dark to build trust.
I'm trying to buy myself
enough time to permanently
change my position,
instead of treading water
like I am right now.
I gave Sabiyah
my Shot in the Dark just
-to show, you know, like,
I'm not gonna play it.
-Trust.
Yeah. Trust me.
I'm just praying
the tribe truly wants
to vote out Brandon.
And I hope
I can turn this around,
and I think if it does turn
around, it's all on Kaleb.
When we started this momentum
of working together,
this has just...
It's been great so far, okay?
Emily's playing it smart,
and I'm standing there being
like, "You're doing
a great job." You know?
Like... she's listening.
It's working.
And I think having Emily
as an asset is gonna
be a very valuable thing
for me.
-And we'll have
each other's back, okay?
-Awesome.
KALEB:
And I hope
Sean and Sabiyah realize
we can actually work with Emily
deeper into this game.
SABIYAH:
Emily just makes me feel like
she will just cut my throat
in the night.
Brandon is just... I love him...
-It's true. It's true.
-I have it.
SABIYAH:
Emily has given me her word
and her Shot in the Dark, but
she's someone
that's a snake in the grass,
and that's scary
to keep that around.
You really want
to play with us or what?
Yes. Yes, more than anything.
-Seriously?
-More than anything.
And I hope you can see
that I bring a bit of vitality
to this tribe in a way
that Brandon doesn't.
SABIYAH:
I have friends like Brandon.
I know I can
trust Brandon to the end.
If we vote Brandon tonight,
do we win with Emily?
Realistically?
It can go either way.
But I don't trust Emily.
I don't have a vote,
but in a way, I do.
Kaleb and Sean--
they basically have said,
"Well, who do you want?"
I haven't considered
myself being in control
of this tribe,
but it's kind of been that way,
and I like it.
♪ ♪
All right.
Welcome back to Tribal Council.
So, Sabiyah,
what I'm most curious about
is what happened last Tribal
in what was clearly
a heated Tribal
that then took a left turn
as Hannah pleaded
-to go home and you let her.
-Right.
I thought that all that heat
was gonna get resolved
with a snuff, you know?
So let me just interrupt.
Does that mean that it was Emily
going home because
the heat was between you two?
Either it meant it was her
or it was gonna
be a snuff to kind of
shut her up a little bit.
-You know?
-PROBST: So, Brandon,
what do you read into that,
because somebody was going home?
Yeah. I knew Emily and I
were on the bottom.
I went in not wanting it
to be me. I was gonna do what
I thought the most people were
gonna do, so I was voting Emily.
PROBST:
So, Sean, give me
the tribe dynamic here.
SEAN:
You know, coming back
from the challenge today,
both Emily and Brandon said,
"Sabiyah, Kaleb, Sean,
why don't the three of you
go off and talk?"
So that's where
the alliance right now stands.
So, are all five of you
in agreement that
it's Emily or Brandon tonight?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
PROBST: Okay. So,
we rarely have this, where it's
so clearly between two people.
Brandon, let's start with you.
What case do you make
to remind everybody
what qualities
you bring to the tribe?
So, Jeff, this is something
I'm certainly not used to.
Like, this is my first team.
Right? I don't play sports.
I'm not used to losing because
I'm not used to playing, right?
I came back from the challenge
very defeated.
This is my second puzzle
that I did not do.
And the puzzle at the journey--
I lost that one, too.
So maybe it's just,
puzzles aren't my thing, but
it's a situation where...
-But you told us that they were.
-Well...
And that's-that's really
my caveat.
We just really,
as a tribe, need him
to be like, "This is
what I can do," and it be true.
BRANDON:
I do maintain that the puzzles
that I do were just bad day.
But I am loyal to you guys.
You know, Emily has had issues
with these people,
and these people know
that I'm Lulu strong.
Kaleb, Brandon's saying,
"I'm loyal, I'm with you."
That also is a valuable quality
in this game.
KALEB:
Yeah. You know, his ability
to be vulnerable, to bring
people in, to tell a story--
it is really valuable.
Emily, you know,
was trying to play
all 26 days of Survivor
in the first, you know, week.
But, you know, what does
an open mind at least look like?
Maybe it would be
taking a chance with Emily
or it would be knowing we
already have that with Brandon.
Now, I will say,
to Emily's credit,
after our last Tribal Council,
a few of us gave her
some feedback, and
Emily's taken that to heart.
And she's shown
a good faith effort
to be the sweet Emily
that we know she is.
PROBST:
So, Brandon, what do you do now
in this moment
when you're hearing the three--
who seem to be in charge--
saying that they are weighing,
and it's not a slam dunk?
BRANDON:
It's a gigantic decision, but
there's gonna be a challenge
that I know
that I will be able
to compete, physically.
-I've gotten unlucky.
-PROBST: It's interesting to me
that you just pitched yourself
physically again.
-Yeah.
-And this is not to liken
my story to yours, but
when I was a kid in junior high,
tried out
for the basketball team,
didn't have a left-handed layup.
I didn't make the team.
But you know what
they asked me to be?
The water boy.
-Yeah.
-Because I was fun
to be around,
and I wanted them to win.
And what I felt like
these three just said is,
"You're the water boy.
"You're not gonna help us
in the challenges,
but you've got
a secret weapon."
-BRANDON: For sure.
-You're likable.
I will happily
be this team's water boy.
I'm more than happy to do that.
PROBST:
So, Emily, what case do you make
in terms of "I could do better"?
It's more like learning
from my mistakes.
And a lot of that is learning
to tone down
the more harsh qualities,
um, for people
that I'm living with 24/7
and rebuilding trust.
You know, one of the things
that I did to rebuild trust
was I gave Sabiyah
my Shot in the Dark tonight.
And Sabiyah
was very kind and said,
"I'll give it back to you
after Tribal."
Now, that could be,
"Because you're not coming back
"to camp after Tribal,
so it doesn't really matter,"
or that could also be
Sabiyah saying,
"Look, Emily, I trust you, too."
PROBST:
So, Emily, if this is it,
what's it been about?
EMILY:
Well, it's certainly not
gone the way I expected,
and I can tell you right now
that I've learned
a lot about myself,
I can tell you
right now that I think I've made
friends for life. I never
thought I'd say that
after spending five days
with strangers.
You know,
I was told coming into this
that I can be
a little bit aggressive,
uh, but all of those things
in my everyday life,
I think, are very muted.
I mean, I live a very
normal life, believe it or not.
I have friends,
believe it or not. I mean...
And so, coming into
this scenario and seeing all
of these things on hyperdrive
and then potentially
re-watching them on TV,
I think that is going to be
a somewhat
traumatic experience.
You know, it's interesting
what you just said,
that, "I have friends,
believe it or not."
-I wouldn't doubt
you have friends.
-No.
What I think is interesting
about Survivoris
that they aren'tyour friends.
Our friends don't always
tell us the truth,
but out here,
people will tell you.
And if you take that,
you can shift how
you interact with the world.
That's what I feel like
is happening tonight.
All right, Brandon,
if this is it for you,
what's it been about?
My journey started
in September of 2008.
You know, my sixth grade teacher
mentioned Survivor.
I didn't think she liked me,
so I watched it
'cause I'm a kiss-ass,
'cause I wanted her to like me
so I could talk
about it with her.
And every day since that night,
I wanted to be here.
I pictured myself here.
This is everything that I'm not.
I don't like the outside.
I hate the beach.
These challenges are so out
of my realm, and if this is it,
I hope I learn
why I needed to come here.
And I think that
it's not for this game.
It's outside of it.
I'm so anxious, Jeff.
I am wildly anxious.
I... My whole five days here
have been ruled
by my anxiety and my neuroses
and worrying.
But being on the beach
with these guys,
with these Buffs--
it's incredible, man.
This is the most fun
five days I've ever had.
This is what I waited for.
And if this is how it ends,
I would have waited 40
more years to do Survivor45
with these guys, no doubt.
PROBST:
Well, the two of you remind me
tonight that Survivor
is always a unique experience
for every single person
who plays.
Sadly, that adventure
is going to come to an end
for one of you
'cause it is time to vote.
Kaleb, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Brandon.
Second person voted out
of Survivor45:
Brandon.
That's two. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
All right, I want hugs.
-Come on. Hug, please.
-Yeah, of course.
-SEAN: I'll hug you, buddy.
-BRANDON: Before
I get out of here,
I just want to thank you
for giving me the opportunity
to meet amazing people,
play this game,
and live my dream.
Brandon, the tribe has spoken.
Oh.
This is cool. It's really cool.
[laughing]
Get out of here.
SEAN:
We love you.
-Bye, Brandon.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
DEE:
It felt like a boyfriend
was cheating on me
and I caught him cheating.
It's game on.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
EMILY:
My jaw just dropped.
I'm shocked.
The winning tribe
earns a camp raid.
I will lose my ...
I might have lost Survivor,
but I did it. I didn't give up.
I made it all the way here.
And I would have liked
to have stayed longer.
I would have liked
to have won something.
Something would have been ideal.
But otherwise,
I got to authentically
live my childhood dream.
And I don't know a lot
of people that can say that.
You have to come do this.
Hopefully,
you end up doing better
than I did by a little bit,
but otherwise,
you will have the most
incredible time of your life.
[roars]