Yeah.
I've got two idols, and
I placed one of my idols
in Julie's bag
to make sure she stayed safe.
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
JULIE:
I want to get Bruce out,
but Bruce is gonna
play his idol tonight.
Really?
EMILY:
The only way he doesn't
play his idol
is if he feels
comfortable enough
that he's not
the person going home.
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
[sighs]
Eleventh person voted out and
the fourth member of our jury:
Bruce.
[mouthing]
[soft laughter]
-The tribe has spoken.
-Yes, sir.
♪ ♪
-DEE: Oh, my God.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my God.
-DREW: Let's go! Let's go!
-[cheering, laughter]
-Are you kidding me?
-[whooping]
Oh, my gosh.
-That was epic. Epic.
-Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
The unimaginable happened.
Bruce did not play his idol,
and he went home.
AUSTIN: Oh, my gosh.
Uh, me, too.
Sorry, I'm-I'm still... [laughs]
I'm still in shock.
Like, I'm still processing.
I can't even belie...
I-I can hear silence.
You hear the silence?
It's Bruce not lecturing me,
not micromanaging everybody.
-[cheering]
-AUSTIN: Yo.
KATURAH:
I cannot believe that
he would not play his idol.
That is so shocking.
It's honestly a testament
to his lack of self-awareness.
He really wrote down
the only name
that would have
worked with him. [laughs]
-EMILY: I know.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my God.
Yeah, that was a weird, uh,
turn of events.
-Yeah, that was shocking.
-Yeah.
DREW: Yeah, all right, tell us.
EMILY:
Um... [chuckles] So, yeah...
And I had...
OTHERS: Wow.
-Oh!
-[exclaiming]
-KATURAH: Emily!
-[overlapping chatter]
-Emily, you are a strong player.
-Yo, girl. Let's go.
JULIE:
Complete props to Emily.
Bruce knew he was
getting names thrown his way
and she convinced Bruce
that I was playing him.
But he's thinking
he's gonna blindside me.
And,
goodness gracious,
he didn't play his idol.
Emily, you're sweet,
but that was you, girl.
DEE:
Yeah, that was. That was.
JULIE:
So her threat level has gone up.
It was a genius move, and
she came up with the whole plan.
♪ ♪
[snoring]
What really matters,
at the end of the day, is that
I still have my core four
with me, Drew, Dee and Julie.
And we're just so excited
because we have the majority.
AUSTIN:
We have worked so hard
to make sure the four of us
stayed in the numbers,
and now there's four of us
and three of everyone else.
DREW: Yeah?
[yawns]
AUSTIN:
Somehow we've been able
to slip by everybody,
and we've
just been taking people out
like the friggin' mafia,
one at a time.
AUSTIN: Oh, my God.
It's crazy. [laughs]
Coming into this game,
I felt, like, a very calming
presence with Austin.
And now that
it's getting closer to the end,
our relationship is progressing.
It makes me happy,
because I feel like
he's such a genuine guy.
[gasps] Really?
-A little bit.
-Why?
-You did?
-Yeah.
I thought that you were so,
like, introverted.
I think, initially,
Austin wasn't someone
that I'd be interested in, but,
you know, you spend
so much time with people here.
You know, when they say,
"26 days on Survivor,"
it really is like
six months out here.
[both laugh]
AUSTIN:
Dee and I-- we've become
so close during this.
Like, we have this
super, super tight bond.
She's the only person who,
you know,
I could sit out at the beach
and just talk with for, like,
two hours about
nothing about the game.
We're just hanging out.
We're laughing.
I'm gonna definitely
go visit her as soon
as this whole thing ends.
-Oh, my gosh.
We're gonna do sushi.
-That'd be so fun.
We're gonna do Cuban food.
We're gonna do milk tea.
-We're gonna watch Survivor.
-Oh, my God.
It's gonna be so much fun.
AUSTIN:
And we've just been
our rocks out here,
trying support each other,
having someone that we can
truly trust and connect with.
And that is, like,
super special.
So, one of my favorite
moments on Survivor
was the whole, like,
All-Stars thing.
The whole
Boston Rob and Amber thing.
-Oh, hell yeah. Of course.
-I love that.
ROB:
It'd be nice to have
a million dollars
and take the girl away, too.
[all cheering]
-[laughs]: Yes.
-MAN: Wow.
And then I, like, wrote,
I was, like,
"You know, maybe one day
I'll, you know,
maybe I'll find my, uh,
my Amber on the island."
[both laughing]
-You want to know
something hilarious?
-What?
Before coming here, one
of the big things I said, like,
-"No showmances.
Number one red flag."
-[laughs]
But then even funnier than that,
before coming here,
my friends are always like,
"Oh, maybe you'll
find your husband out there."
I came into this
game saying, "No showmances."
Literally, one of my biggest
things was "no showmances."
But that doesn't mean I can't
have a little fun. [laughs]
Yeah, it is.
AUSTIN:
We don't even have to say it.
We know we have each other's
back through everything.
And I would love
to be at the end with her,
because we've
had such this unique, incredible
relationship out here on
the island that if I didn't win,
I would want her to win.
Aw.
♪ ♪
JAKE:
I'm a little bit, you know, sad.
Last night,
there was votes for me.
So right now,
I have to tread carefully.
I think I got seven votes
in this game now.
I'm becoming very popular.
Hopefully
seven's a lucky number,
and it stays there,
and there's no more.
Day 20.
We thought
the last few days were crazy.
It's gonna get worse.
Hopefully the applecart's
upset in some way.
-The what?
-Hopefully the applecart
is upset in some way.
Yeah.
I think so.
-I don't think I made it up.
-I've never heard of that.
JAKE:
You know, I'm used to
being here in my...
cesspit of the bottom.
Hopefully if there's
a backup vote, I'm not it again.
[both laugh]
I mean, I tried to switch it up
so I wasn't a backup vote,
but whatever.
KATURAH:
Well, just know I'm down
to work with you
for the next three votes.
Yeah.
[laughs]:
I love it.
-Who would've thought?
-I know.
[laughs]
I'm working with a lawyer.
Yeah.
KATURAH:
No one knows that I'm a lawyer,
but if I'm trying
to get closer to Jake,
and he's a lawyer, then
I'm gonna, you know, pretend
to be, you know,
interested in that stuff.
I hope you know people
appreciate that kind of work.
JAKE:
Thanks.
-Can I join y'all?
-Absolutely.
-Yeah.
But there's
a lot of people, like,
who, like, really remind me of
you, Katurah, that I work with.
-Really?
-Yes.
KATURAH:
I thought about being a lawyer,
kind of helping
in that way, but...
I'm really kind of
playing it up, but I am
genuinely enjoying the moment,
because it's allowing us
all to bond.
You hear so many people
who are like,
"Oh, I don't think I can do it,"
when it's, like, dude,
like, I did it. Like...
I graduated high school
with, like, a 2.6, I think.
-KATURAH: Really?
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
But also, talking
to Jake and Julie,
it really got me thinking.
And I'm like,
okay, I'm at day 20,
and I don't
want to leave this game--
'cause you never know when
you might have to leave it--
without having told my story.
I actually had a little bit
of the opposite
experience, 'cause
my family took me out of school
after my fifth grade graduation.
-And so...
-Why did they do that?
Religion.
-JAKE: What? Religion?
-Religion.
They-they joined
a religion that said
kids should be homeschooled
and not in public school.
But, you know,
a few weeks in, it was,
"Mom's going back to work
and figure it out," you know?
When I was a child,
my family joined
a quite extreme religious cult.
And it just, like, instantly,
my childhood
got taken away from me.
And so, you know,
they started putting me to work.
And I worked, like,
three, four jobs.
[crying]: You know, nobody said,
"Let me think about Katurah.
"Like, what does
it mean that this child
is not in school for years?"
Years.
And then when I was 13,
they told me
the leader decided that,
you know, you're gonna
be his next wife. And
that's when my mom-- I think
something in her clicked,
and we put all of our belongings
in, like, two trash bags.
[breathes sharply]
[crying]: And just ran away
in the middle of the night.
[sniffles]
When we finally
left that religion and, like,
-joined the real world again,
you know, it was, like...
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
I was 14.
So they just put me in
high school because of my age.
-And so I was just so afraid
that I would be the dumb one.
-JULIE: Yeah.
I'm gonna be the stupid one.
I don't have...
-Never having
been to school in years.
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
I just got, you know, shuffled
back into the world again.
[exhales] And then I realized
I was Black and I was poor
and I was a woman
and I was gay.
And that is when,
at, like, 14, I said,
"I'm gonna become a lawyer
who advocates for Black people."
And I'm so proud
that I literally can say here,
you know, 15-plus years later,
and I did it.
But, like,
this isn't a sad story.
It's a story of redemption. It's
a story of resilience. Like,
I live in my fantasy city.
I live in my fantasy apartment
and I empower my community
and I help people.
And I'm, like, also saying this
while on an island in Fiji,
you know, playing Survivor.
Could be a lot worse.
♪ ♪
Just another beautiful day
here in Fiji, playing Survivor.
The only thing missing: you.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
I can hear something.
[grunts]
JAKE:
Oh, that is a boat.
[indistinct chatter]
-That's a boat.
-JULIE: No, it's not.
-AUSTIN: Well, relaxation...
-JULIE: I hope not.
-I literally just laid down.
-JULIE: No.
JAKE: So we're all sitting down,
and a boat pulls up.
When a boat
pulls up to your beach,
you never know
what's gonna happen, so
if anyone's going on
this boat, I want it to be me.
Thank you, man.
Appreciate it.
At final seven, like,
this affects my strategy
moving forward.
And this late in the game,
I-I need
my strategy to be on point.
I need to start making moves.
I can't have
any misplays anymore.
I'm out of... [chuckles]
I'm out of strikes, man.
Oh.
DEE: The note says
one person has to go,
so that's huge.
I'm open to going.
-DREW: I'd like to go.
-Yeah, I'm open.
-EMILY: Should we all
just draw rocks?
-DEE: Yeah, just draw rocks.
DEE:
It's day 20. We need to all pull
some big moves at this point.
So we all decide
we're gonna draw rocks.
EMILY: I hate this.
DEE:
And I'm hoping and praying
that it's
in my hand.
Okay. Three, two, one.
-No.
-OTHERS: Oh!
-Okay.
-DREW: Do you want to go?
-Yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah...
-DEE: You want to go?
-EMILY: I want to. I want to go.
-Yeah. Okay, perfect.
-Let's go.
-Oh, you guys.
I reach in, and I'm like,
"Oh, no." Of course
it's the green rock,
because I can't
catch a break in this game.
[laughs]
It's terrifying.
You don't know what's
gonna happen on a journey.
But at the same time,
this is a way
to push myself forward
in this game.
-KATURAH: Bye.
-DEE: Bye.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
JULIE:
On journeys, there's always
a chance to get an advantage.
And Emily
now has a chance
to build her résumé even bigger.
How do you feel
about Emily going?
I don't know. She's
starting to get some clout.
JULIE:
I would have sat with her
at the end, except for now...
JULIE:
Boy, I do not want to cut Emily.
I think she's smart,
but she's making
an amazing résumé for herself.
DREW: She's got
so many friends on there.
She made a big move last night,
you know?
Yep. Yep.
Interesting.
DREW:
At this point, it's final seven,
and the core four from Reba--
Julie, Dee, Austin and myself--
is still intact.
And so last night,
there was a real, you know,
atmosphere of bonhomie.
There was a real atmosphere
of friendship.
You know, you go out
and get drunk
with your buddies,
and you're like,
"We're, like,
the best friends ever."
Then you wake up
the next morning,
and you're like,
"Are we really, you know,
the best friends ever?"
Like, I'm not sure.
No.
Could be a good idea.
So you do size up that group--
the Reba four, the core four--
when you say, "Who can I beat?"
And I think right now
Austin and I
are in similar categories.
But Julie is a threat
with the jury because she's Mom.
She has great relationships
with all of them.
And Julie has an idol.
Julie got the idol
in a huge blunder by Austin.
Austin gave her the idol
to hang on to
in case she got in trouble.
But now she thinks
it's her idol.
She's hanging on to it greedily,
like Gollum to the Ring.
And that's a scary thought.
Well, whatever you decide,
I mean, it's your...
you got the idol.
Y'all got one, too.
-Austin's got another one.
-Yeah.
My gut right now is that
all four Reba members
want to go final four together.
But if one of them
wants to distinguish themselves
and make a big move,
it's Drew.
He's acting so suspicious.
I'm thinking, "Boy,
is now the time that people
are gonna start taking shots?"
He asked me if I need... wanted
to make any big moves
with my idol.
If I'm planning
on doing something?
-Yeah.
-I know.
If they did want
to pull a move on us,
like, we have the idol,
and then we know
so much information, too.
Yep.
DEE:
After Tribal Council,
we got together, the four of us,
and we made a pact
that it's gonna be
the four of us strong.
Drew, Austin, Julie and I--
we still need each other
because there's still
six days left in the game,
and we don't know
what Jeff is gonna throw at us.
The thing is that
it's important to stay four,
because we still
have the numbers.
I know.
And once this four is done,
-they're coming for us,
one by one.
-Yep.
DEE:
But I feel like
there's a crack in Drew,
and that kind of scares me,
because I know
how close he is to Emily.
Look, I really think
that when she gets back,
-she's gonna lie to everybody.
-I know.
We can all put it in people's
head that she can be dangerous.
-Right.
-Yeah, we can.
So, right now,
I'm looking at Emily next.
However, on these journeys,
there's usually opportunities
for an advantage, an idol.
Anything can happen.
Yeah, I'm very curious
to see what she comes back with.
♪ ♪
EMILY:
If somebody is gonna go on
a journey and get an advantage,
I would rather be the person
making that decision.
But it's still really scary
because if I thought I already
had a target on my back
after the Bruce blindside,
then going off and
taking part in this adventure--
that just puts more
of a target on my back.
"Trek down the coast to
make your decision. Good luck."
But we're coming into
the fourth quarter of Survivor,
which means that
this is when the decision
for the winner
ofSurvivor will be made.
And I like being
in a position where I have
the opportunity to make
a decision, but I'm conscious
of the fact that I could
put what position I've built
in a very precarious spot
by making the wrong choice.
For the first time
in my Survivor journey,
I have a moment to reflect.
And it's funny. I came
into the game ofSurvivor,
and I said, "I don't need
to change as a person."
I'm usually a very direct
and aggressive person,
and I still, to an extent, am.
But at the very first
Tribal Council...
I know one of them
was going home
who wanted to be here
more than me.
EMILY:
...it was obvious that my name
was on the chopping block.
You have kind of
isolated yourself.
EMILY:
I was told I'm aggressive
and confrontational.
This is an emotional game.
I'm discovering that.
So I've changed.
My game has changed in terms of
softness, right,
that I bring to conversations.
Now I'm able to have deeper
emotional connections
with people,
hear about what's important
in their life, and that is
going to extend far outside
the game of Survivor.
Oh, no. Another puzzle.
I like puzzles
when it's a Sunday morning
and I'm drinking a coffee.
When I don't like puzzles
is when I'm playing a game
for a million dollars
and my vote's on the line
and I feel like
I could be going home.
Suddenly, puzzles
are a lot less fun, then.
Wow. That's huge.
There's no guarantee in
Survivor,except for immunity.
What is immunity worth? Mm.
If you could choose
between having a vote
and having immunity,
you pick immunity every time.
So having immunity
is extremely appealing to me.
But the flip side of that is
you'll be safe,
but if you can't do it,
you'll lose your vote.
I'm imagining that there's
probably conversations
back at camp, talking about,
"Hey, maybe
we should target Emily."
At this stage in the game,
my vote is my life.
If I have no vote,
then I'm easy pickings.
I'm scared that, while
I might be able to solve this,
if I try and fail,
I could be guaranteeing
my return home.
And I don't think
it's a trade-off worth it, so...
I can't... I can't participate.
I will be getting on the boat
and returning to camp.
I can't risk my vote.
I'm playing the best game
that I know how to play.
I really hope
the decision that I made
is the right one and that
everybody believes me
when I tell them
about what happened.
♪ ♪
[flint scraping]
It's exhausting.
Yeah.
Why can't we just
vote somebody out at four?
Why does there
need to be all this, Jeff?
DREW:
Is that a boat coming?
♪ ♪
JAKE:
Got to.
DREW:
Yeah, obviously.
You guys don't have to tell me,
but was wondering
if you guys were thinking
about going to the end together,
who, uh, who you were
thinking about your third.
What we're more
talking about is, like,
who's in the way or
who would I not want to sit by?
DREW:
Well, there are some people.
Who do we think?
We be listening.
DREW:
Some people down on the beach.
Uh, listening a little more.
DREW:
I mean, you guys think
you can beat Julie and Dee?
Would you feel uncomfortable
doing that next?
DREW:
Right now, I'm ready
to take some shots.
And at this point, people look
at Julie, Dee and Emily, now,
as probably
the three biggest threats,
but my instincts are telling me
Julie has to go.
DREW:
Yeah, I think Austin
may want to do something.
-KATURAH: Really?
-Yeah, I think so.
I do feel
like Dee's threat level
has been going
down a little bit, though.
I'd rather go
with whoever the biggest is.
-Okay. Yeah.
-KATURAH: Yeah. Yeah.
There's a lot in my mind
right now about my game,
and I do feel like this
is the moment that I plan
to start picking up steam,
coming out of the shadows,
making the bigger moves,
being a little bit bolder.
So I think I have options.
But for me,
I know that I'd like
to blindside Julie first.
How are you feeling
about everything?
I mean, have you been
thinking about your final three?
Honestly, I don't have
a thought of, like, who I,
-for sure, want to sit by,
-Mm-hmm.
-but I have thoughts of,
like, who I don't.
-Who probably don't want to.
-I-I agree. Yeah.
-Like, who would kill the game.
So initially,
I was thinking Dee and Mama J.
Mm-hmm.
-But I think
Mama J. is climbing. Yeah.
-She has excelled. I think...
So, basically,
Katurah says to me
kind of what I've already
been thinking, which is
"We should not
go to the end with Julie."
And I agree with her.
-Mama J.'s just been
friends with everybody.
-Yeah.
-AUSTIN: Everybody loves her.
-Yeah. Yeah.
AUSTIN:
Everybody trusts her.
-Everybody loves her deeply,
and she's sharp.
-Yeah.
How do you not love Mama J.?
She will be a tough person
to beat at the end.
She is someone that,
even if she backstabs you,
she can still win your heart.
So we might have to consider
cutting her off
before the final four,
even though that's
what we agreed to do-- to bring
the Reba four to the four.
I'm definitely open to it.
It is gonna be weird
writing her after all this,
-I know. I know.
-but, like, I do understand
that if she's in the end,
we all lose.
-Yeah.
-And, like, that is, at the end
of the day, we need to win.
Yeah. I would like
to do Julie and then Emily.
I think Drew
might be on board
for either of them, too.
KATURAH:
I honestly think
everybody would
be on board with Julie
-for this vote, except Dee.
-Okay.
I think
if anyone
were to pull the trigger early
on this Reba four to the end,
it would most likely be Drew.
So I just had a, uh,
chat with Katurah.
-She wants Julie gone next.
-DREW: What do you think?
I just think that would, uh,
absolutely crush Dee.
Dee really wants
to do the four to the end.
And that puts us
in a difficult spot,
because we don't have
the guaranteed numbers anymore.
I would almost rather Emily
and then Julie go.
DREW:
Emily and I have
a great working relationship.
She's a close ally of mine.
So it's got to be Julie.
In my talk with Austin,
I need to
walk him through how
few opportunities we might have
to vote out Julie.
I agree.
My concern is that
I think that Emily
really is willing to work
with us and genuinely is willing
to go final three with us. She's
a much more tractable number
and reliable number
than Julie is.
-You think she is at this point?
-I do.
I want Julie gone next.
AUSTIN:
I'm on board, I think.
I'm just worried about Dee.
'Cause then she would...
I don't know if
she'll believe our final three.
I truly think
the best move for me
right now
is to get rid of Julie.
The scary thing is, though,
blindsiding Julie
would likely
require blindsiding Dee.
And that is a thought that
really hurts me
and I don't really know
how I'll be able to do that.
-And then the idol's gone.
-And then the idol's out.
-Um...
-Man, flushing my idol.
-Can't believe I gave her that.
-I know. It's a bummer.
-Oh!
-Hey.
AUSTIN:
Emily is certainly becoming
a bigger threat, but
I have to take out Julie
because
she has my idol.
And my idol that I gave to her
is stronger
than the amulet I have.
My amulet
has the power of an idol,
but it only lasts
until the final six.
Julie's idol, which I gave her,
lasts to the final five.
-EMILY: So,
the boat picks me up
-DREW: Okay.
and takes me to an island.
AUSTIN:
I don't want to ask for it back.
That could set the alarm bells
ringing in her head.
So I need to vote her out
and flush my own friggin' idol
out of this game.
The sign says, "You can choose
to participate in this puzzle.
"If you solve the puzzle,
"you win safety
at the next Tribal Council.
"And if you don't
solve the puzzle,
-then you lose your vote
at the next Tribal Council."
-[Dee gasps]
-Oh, my God.
-JULIE: Wow.
And I chose not to complete it,
because I was not confident
in my ability to solve it...
DREW:
I think it's the right call.
DEE: I don't buy that
Emily just played it safe
and came back with nothing.
I don't buy it.
It's just the easy story to say.
We were all worried
the decision would involve us.
So this not, uh, not bad news.
Yeah.
EMILY: So I come back
and I decide to be
the best part about myself,
which is open,
honest and transparent.
I tell them
exactly what happened.
By being genuine in my story,
telling them the complete
and honest truth,
I'm hoping that it will
remove some of the target
that was put on me by the fact
that I went on this journey.
AUSTIN:
Well, thanks for telling us.
-DREW: Yeah. Appreciate it.
-JAKE: Yeah.
-DREW: No, no, no, yeah.
-Really.
But I need
to circle around
with my closer alliance
and Drew and Austin
and find out what happened
while I was gone.
Okay. Well...
-Yeah.
-But we want Julie out.
-Okay. Okay.
-Austin and I talked about it.
I-I think I want Julie,
but it has to be a blindside.
I agree.
EMILY: It's no fun
to go away
and then find out that,
in the few hours you were gone,
that you're in trouble.
But that's
the game ofSurvivor.
And with that in mind,
I need to target the person
who is reportedly targeting me,
which is Julie.
I think we're headed into
a Julie and Emily showdown.
We're both gonna
have smiles on our faces,
but we're both
rallying the troops right now.
[quietly]: Stop.
Uh, yeah.
My hope is that the alliances
that I've built up
will defend me enough
that she's the one
who goes home instead.
KATURAH:
So...
Okay.
-No, you're not.
-Yes, I have.
EMILY:
I feel like I've grown a lot
as a player and as a strategist
in the game of Survivor,
but it's scary.
It might be my last
Tribal Council
and I might discover,
in that moment,
that the alliance I had built
and had been
making my game decisions on
never really had my back.
It was a fake alliance.
Dee has said
she'll never write Julie's name.
-I-I believe that.
-I don't think we can tell Dee.
-We can't tell Dee. I-I...
-Okay.
-I'm so...
-I'm so glad. Oh, my God.
I'm so glad.
-We're on the same page.
-Okay.
Or I might discover
that I made the right choices
to this point,
and that alliance is real
and, you know, they defended me
to the very bitter end.
I love you. [chuckles]
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Day 21.
Oh, yeah.
-PROBST: Survivor45.
-Hi, Jeff.
Look at those smiles.
[sighs]
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-ALL: Yeah.
-First things first, Austin.
[exhales sharply]
-Thank you.
-Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
-[whoops]
For today's challenge, you're
gonna be attached to a rope.
On my go,
you're gonna race to gather
that rope by untangling it.
When you think you have enough,
you'll go over
and under a series of obstacles.
You'll then throw sandbags
at a stack of blocks.
You'll then
gather all those blocks
and use them
to solve a word puzzle.
♪ ♪
First person to finish
wins immunity.
Safe tonight at Tribal.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
-In addition,
playing for a reward.
-[excited chatter]
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-ALL: Yeah.
Do-it-yourself barbecue
back at camp.
-Hamburgers.
-KATURAH: Whoa.
-Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Hot dogs, soft drinks
and all the fixings.
-Everything you need
for that taste of home.
-JULIE: Whoa.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the 12th person
voted out of Survivor45
and become the fifth member
of our jury.
-Worth playing for? All right.
-Oh, yeah.
Let's draw for spots,
and we'll get it on.
-Ooh.
-PROBST: Here we go.
♪ ♪
All right. Here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Your first task
is to collect enough rope
to get you
to the end of the course.
This will be
a very big strategic decision
because you have
more rope than you need.
The question
is how much do you need?
So you're looking
at the length of the course,
you're trying to follow
how much you've gathered.
-When you think you have enough,
you go for it.
[grunts]
You are attached to that rope
and you will be
for this entire challenge.
So if you get tied up in there,
you can't
unclip to free yourself.
You just got to get unstuck.
So rope management
is a big part of this.
You don't want
to get knotted up.
Jake thinks he has
enough rope to make a go of it.
It's Jake out of the gate first.
Will he have enough?
Over and under. Over and under.
Jake got to go back.
That's part of this challenge.
You don't know for sure.
So at a certain point,
-take a shot, see what you got.
-[grunts]
I think I got it.
PROBST:
Drew looks like
he's ready to head out.
-I am!
-PROBST: Drew going for it.
Julie gonna give it a go now.
We got two people
out on the course.
Will they have enough?
It would be a big lead,
as nobody else is out.
Drew has enough.
He's gonna start untying
his bag of sandbags.
PROBST:
Jake gonna give it a go now.
Here comes Katurah.
Here comes Dee.
Here comes Austin.
Everybody making a move now.
It is Drew
with the first sandbag.
Nothing.
Here comes Jake.
He's all knotted up.
-Okay.
-PROBST: Drew misses all three.
He's got to go around
and get his sandbags.
Does he have enough
to get there?
-He can get one. He's got two.
-Do I need all three?
-No, you don't need all three.
-DREW: Okay.
PROBST:
You've only got two.
He can't reach the third.
Drew with another bad toss.
There's a few.
Emily's stuck.
-[sighing]
-PROBST:
Katurah doesn't have enough.
She's got to go back.
-Here comes Dee.
-[grunts]
PROBST:
Dee has to head back now.
Jake got
to get all those knots done
before you can reach
for those sandbags.
Here comes Austin.
There goes Jake
with a nice shot.
Drew trying
to just gently toss his bags.
Now Jake's got to go out.
Does he have enough to get
to his sandbags? He does not.
A massive setback for Jake.
Got to go all the way back.
Half his blocks are knocked off
but he doesn't have enough rope
to get the sandbags.
Here comes Austin.
Here comes Julie.
Will they have enough?
Austin looking good.
He's gonna start untying his
bag.
Julie short.
Got to head back.
-Damn it.
-PROBST: Drew still trying
to knock off
those last four blocks.
[mutters]
PROBST:
Austin tossing his sandbags.
Knocks a few off.
-Drew's got all his blocks.
-I got 'am all.
He can now restack
and start spelling that word.
Austin-- does he have enough
to get to his sandbags?
-[Austin groans]
-PROBST: Or will he be short?
Austin can reach one
and that's it.
Fortunately,
that's all you need.
So now you got to think
about tossing that sandbag
so you don't throw it too far
that you can't reach it.
Emily gonna give it a go.
Does she have enough? Let's see.
She does not.
Drew's try to solve that
by looking at it.
What word could it be?
Here goes Austin with
another toss, and that's enough.
Austin can start
stacking his blocks.
Drew is quickly
putting a word together.
You're gonna be forming
an arch with your puzzle.
Got to be right on both sides.
So first,
you figure out the word,
then you make sure it matches.
It is Drew and Austin,
and that's it.
-Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST:
Everybody else is stuck.
DEE:
Let's go, girls. Don't give up.
PROBST:
Unable to get their rope
untangled enough
to get out here.
Huge time advantage
for Drew and Austin.
Drew trying to keep it all
together, but he can't.
Austin now working on it.
You're looking for one word.
Here comes Julie.
Once again, Julie's short
and got to go back again.
Here comes Katurah.
Will she have enough?
-Can Katurah get in on this?
-Yes, she can!
Katurah's got enough rope.
She can start untying
her sandbags.
Here comes Jake,
giving it another go.
Here comes Emily.
Drew once again trying
to form that word.
Thinks he knows what it is.
He's got an idea.
But you got
to get the puzzle together.
He drops again.
Drew's got to start over.
Austin sees that
as an opportunity.
Emily is now here.
She can untie her sandbags.
Katurah got
to knock those blocks off.
Jake's still two blocks left.
He's got enough rope this time
to get all three sandbags.
That'll help.
Nice toss by Emily.
Emily can't retrieve
her sandbags,
doesn't have enough rope.
It's now Austin trying
to solve the word.
Drew right next to him.
You're looking for one word.
You want it to be right
on both sides.
Look at that.
Katurah with a nice toss.
Here comes Julie.
She's in it now.
-Jeff.
-Austin thinks he has it.
And he does not.
Something is not right
with that puzzle.
Got a match on both sides.
If it does, you're right.
If it doesn't, you're not.
Day 21.
Cognitive ability struggling.
You're trying to figure out
what's wrong. What is it?
It's just one word.
Dee now trying to get in on it.
Jake still one block left.
-There we go.
-PROBST: There it is.
-Now Jake can start solving.
-Come on!
PROBST:
Katurah still two blocks left.
Drew slowly and patiently,
one piece at a time.
If he can get it together
and get it to stick.
Austin's stuck.
Want it to be right
on both sides.
Drew down to his last piece.
Jeff. Jeff, Jeff, Jeff, Jeff,
Jeff, Jeff.
Drew thinks he has it.
It's right on that side.
-It is right on the other side!
Drew wins
-Yes!
-Yes! Let's go!
-individual immunity.
-Whew.
-EMILY: Good job, Drew.
-KATURAH: Congrats, Drew.
Way to go, Drew.
-[grunts]
-PROBST: Nice finish.
Drew is safe. Guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
JULIE:
Good job, Drew!
PROBST:
Huge victory on day 21.
Oh, my gosh.
Drew, come on over.
-Great job.
-Nice.
Yeah, Drew!
DEE:
Tallest one, even.
JAKE:
Yeah, it was.
Yeah, it was. Yeah.
Individual immunity is yours,
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
-Guaranteed a spot in the final.
-Yeah!
-JAKE: Way to go, buddy.
-[whooping]
PROBST:
You're getting a lot of love
-from your competitors.
-I am. I am.
What is that about? Because this
is a game for a million dollars.
Listen, I mean, I'll say it.
No one else will.
I-I... I'm kind of a goober
around camp, and so, the idea
that I could be winning an
immunity necklace is unheard of.
Probably to them,
but certainly to me.
Austin, you had a shot at it.
Did you not hear me
saying "both sides"?
I heard you.
I just couldn't register.
You're in the heat
of the moment. You're like,
"Oh, my gosh, I must have
spelled something wrong."
You know, I missed it,
so I'm-I'm with everyone else.
All right, Drew, you are safe.
You are also the recipient
of a nice reward.
-Yeah.
-KATURAH: Yeah.
Back at camp,
do-it-yourself barbecue.
Invite one person
to join you and tell us why.
So, uh, coming out here,
Jake and I had been the longest
since we had a reward.
Uh, I'm gonna choose Jake.
-Thanks, man.
-PROBST: Come on over, Jake.
-[applause]
Thanks, man.
Dude, I appreciate it.
Can I give you a hug, brother?
-Yeah, of course.
-Thank you. Thanks.
That's huge, man.
-Aw.
-[Dee laughs]
-[Jake laughs]
-All right,
pick one more person.
-[cheering]
-Yeah.
-Guys Night 2.0.
Beep, beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep.
-Don't knock me over.
-[laughing]: Yeah.
Ah!
PROBST:
All right,
here's what's gonna happen.
Everybody's going back to camp,
but Drew, Jake, Austin--
you're gonna have your own
barbecue.
Burgers, hot dogs,
all the fixings.
-Ooh.
PROBST:
Katurah, Dee, Emily, Julie,
got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back
to camp. Enjoy the afternoon.
-Thank you.
-Good job, boys.
-AUSTIN: Thank you all.
-Good job, guys.
-Congrats.
-Hey, thanks, man.
DEE:
What I'm nervous about
is the fact
that pre-challenge,
we all had a pact
that it would be Emily who would
be the next person to go home.
But is that changing up
after the boys getting together?
Because I know that
they're gonna talk strategy.
You know, all of our names
are gonna be in their mouths.
♪ ♪
JULIE:
So Drew wins today's challenge,
and he picks the boys--
Jake and Austin.
It feels like the right choice.
The boys are all starving
and the last reward,
Emily took all women.
So the boys get to peel off
to go do their barbecue
and the girls have a spa day.
KATURAH:
I mean, where is our sun?!
-EMILY: Oh.
-KATURAH: It was just blazing
-a second ago.
-EMILY: I know.
DEE:
It's kind of nice that
there's not a lot of waves.
Yeah, and it's not crazy.
EMILY:
This tide's low right now,
so it's kind of hard to wash,
but easier than if there were
waves smashing at us.
Yeah.
It's awkward
to go back to camp
with just the women because
we don't have anything to really
talk about, strategy-wise.
Half of us are plotting
against Emily,
the other half are plotting
against Julie.
And so, the four of us together
are kind of, like,
"I guess
we'll talk about our Buffs."
"Buffs is a registered trademark
proper of Original Buff."
[laughing]
-Oh, like, a Buff is just...
-Made in Spain.
-KATURAH: Oh.
-Whoa.
-JULIE: Mm.
Made in Spain.
KATURAH:
So, you know, we play along,
and somebody throws out
Jake's name,
because that's just the easy,
safe route.
So who are we taking on next,
then? Which boy is...
DEE:
Yeah, he is an easy target.
-KATURAH: Yeah.
-DEE: I know.
EMILY:
Julie is smiling at me.
I'm smiling at her, and
we're pretending like
everything's perfectly fine.
But the fact is,
I'm pretty sure
every single person at camp
has been approached
by either Julie or myself
to vote the other one out.
JULIE: I know.
AUSTIN:
This is incredible.
This is an amazing reward.
AUSTIN:
This is absolutely incredible.
DREW: I win the challenge,
and so, obviously,
the immunity's great--
I-I'm not complaining--
but I get the chance
to go on a reward.
And that reward
is so key because
I do need to have an important
strategy talk with Jake.
No, man. This is unreal.
This should keep you all
for the rest of the game.
Up to this point,
I've been critical of Jake.
I've dished on Jake.
I... We even got in an argument
the other day.
But at the same time,
he's a free agent,
he's got nobody in the game.
And so it really is important
to take the leap of faith
and to bestow some kind
of strategic trust
in Jake, just to get
on the same page,
and to build a relationship
which could be valuable
come a final six.
-So, let's talk strategy.
-Absolutely.
DREW:
Where's your head at, Jake?
'Cause I feel like
seven is a big time
to make a move.
Yeah.
I hear Emily, Dee, and Julie
as the targets.
-Yeah. I'd rather not do Emily.
-DREW: Okay.
-AUSTIN:
Yeah, me, too, actually.
-JAKE: Okay.
What do we think's
the smartest thing to do?
Like, who do we think is
more likely to win immunity?
Julie has a better chance
-DREW: I agree.
-at the end.
Yeah, I'm just concerned
about final four fire-making,
and I think
Julie's more likely to win it.
I agree.
JAKE: Prior to this reward,
I have been a backup plan
to Drew and Austin, but
numbers are dwindling,
so I do think they need my vote
now more than before.
I don't trust 'em for long,
but I do believe
they need me for this round.
Okay, who are we gonna pull in
for this one?
Emily or Katurah?
-I think, uh,
both would be game.
-Yeah.
I do my job as an attorney,
but I also teach theater
to kids, and,
as an actor, I felt like
the past couple votes,
I've been kind of an extra.
I've been playing the tree.
I've been doing a very good job
at playing a tree,
but, to be honest with you,
I'm sick of playing
a ... damn tree.
So, now,
I think with this vote,
I'm more, you know,
more of a supporting role,
and as long as I'm moving up,
I'm going in the
right direction, I'll take it.
I am.
AUSTIN: I think...
DREW:
Right now, everyone is committed
to vote Julie out.
The tough one in
this blindside is Dee, because
Dee and Julie are really close.
So, we have to keep Dee
out of the loop.
Who's ready
to play some Survivor?
AUSTIN:
I mean, it's time
to do this, man.
DREW:
If Julie found out
about this plan,
the fear is that
she could wig out.
She would play her idol
and she could take a shot
at anyone.
And that would be a disaster.
You know, 'cause who knows
where the vote could come down?
Look who it is.
-Hi, guys.
-Hello.
-How was it?
-[overlapping chatter]
-It was-it was...
-Yeah, Drew, right there, buddy.
-Take that.
-Yeah!
-JAKE: Fetal position commence.
-[overlapping chatter]
[laughter]
AUSTIN:
Getting back to camp,
I'm feeling a little bit uneasy.
Every time I think
about this vote,
there's one thing
that holds me back, really,
and the one thing
that makes it really hard
for me to ultimately decide.
"Let's get Julie out."
And that is telling Dee.
We're at the stage
in this game where
every move we make
is gonna hurt a lot.
And that's the cost of getting
close with people in Survivor.
It's been a big, big battle,
trying to figure out what
the best move to make will be.
AUSTIN:
On one end,
I could blindside Dee
and potentially ruin one of my
greatest relationships out here.
Or I can tell Dee
and potentially have
that information leaked back
to Julie
and ruin the entire plan.
So I've been doing the numbers,
crunching everything,
thinking it through for days.
Do I tell Dee, and if so, how?
Well, first off, like...
DEE:
Well, I can tell you
what we talked about
-and then, or if you want to...
-Okay. Sounds good.
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Well, we're thinking Emily,
and then we're telling Emily
Jake, but, um,
-I don't know. I just feel
-Yeah. No.
that that's not the plan
for you guys.
-[soft, rolling thunder]
-It's a weird spot right now.
-Yeah.
-Um...
I guess, first off...
I definitely, like...
[clicks tongue]
I think this is gonna be
the hardest vote right now.
I think there's a strong...
Well...
[sighs]
I mean,
if we think about
potential ways to the end...
No.
-[soft, rolling thunder]
-AUSTIN: Um,
-it's a weird spot right now.
-DEE: Yeah.
There's a strong movement
against Julie.
-...
-I know.
And my heart, still, like,
it hurts thinking
of voting for her.
And I-I don't know. That part
of me is still telling me
that that's not gonna happen.
But I just think,
everyone wants it
really badly now.
What do you want?
[sighs]
I would not
write her name down, just like
I won't write your name down.
I don't want
to write hers down, either,
but I think even if we don't,
even if neither of us
write her name down,
-She's still gone?
-I think she still goes home.
DEE:
For sure, I'm gonna cry.
Like, I don't even want
to think about it,
because I love Julie,
but I can't show
what I'm feeling
because my emotions right now
don't matter.
I knew that this day would come.
Like, I knew
that we would have to...
break apart from each other.
But I never...
thought that it would be me
making a decision
with Julie involved.
It feels like
it's still too soon.
Why is Emily not an option
right now?
-She is.
-Mm-hmm.
But there's Drew, Emily,
Jake, Katurah wanting Julie,
and on the other side,
there's you, Julie,
and in a way, me.
So the only way
to save her would be
to get her to play the idol,
and then
-that could come back
and bite us.
-Yeah.
Oh, a thousand percent,
it would bite us.
-Yeah?
-Everybody would be against us.
-Exactly.
-Well, me, for sure.
My mind is going crazy right now
because Julie's
my other number one.
If I choose to vote Julie out,
it's just me and Austin.
There's still seven people
left in the game.
Like, there's still more game to
be played, more twists to come.
And if I don't have
my two number ones,
then I'm in the chopping block.
Nice. Gosh, you're great, Julie.
DEE:
And then if I tell Julie
about her potentially
going home,
then my game is blown.
-EMILY: Nice.
-JULIE: Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
DEE:
This is the biggest decision
I've had to make in the game.
Austin is trusting me
by telling me this information.
And so far, I've played
this game with heart.
I'm gonna follow my intuition,
and I'm gonna
continue playing this game
with heart.
But you need to put on
your biggest acting face
you've ever put on in your life.
Not me again.
You have to
play your idol tonight,
and we're gonna vote Emily out.
But you have to put on your
biggest acting face, okay?
Okay. So, you think
I'm another option?
-No.
-Mm-hmm.
But you're not gonna go home.
You're gonna play your idol
-and we're both gonna
put it on Emily.
-Wow.
They're actually gonna
try and blindside me.
Drew, Austin-- my alliance
from the beginning--
they all want to vote me out?
I'm mad.
I have done nothing
but protect you people,
and you're turning on me now
when we've got easy votes to do?
Come on.
Man up and face me
when there's three left.
That was the plan.
[soft, rolling thunder]
Y'all feel comfortable
about tonight?
-Not a bit.
-No.
-EMILY: Mm-hmm.
-...it's one of you guys.
Who?
[crackling thunder]
If y'all feel good about it,
I'll write Austin.
If I don't hear from y'all...
-EMILY: Mm-hmm.
-I'm going rogue, people.
They're not gonna make a move.
They're gonna go
with the numbers.
They don't know
that I have an idol.
Austin gave me an idol, and
I'm playing it, so,
if every single person is
writing down my name, whoever
I name goes home.
Okay.
So everyone here
is on the same page?
-Yeah.
Um...
-...to flip it on Austin.
-Austin.
So she's like,
"Maybe we can get Katurah
to write down Austin."
-So she knows?
-She's scrambling
for what's supposed
to be an easy vote.
-She's trying
to flip it on Austin?
-Yeah.
DREW:
I think someone
spilled the beans to Julie.
That's exactly
what I don't want.
I want a cool and calm,
complacent camp.
If Julie found out about this
plan, she would play her idol,
and then anyone could go home
in this vote.
That is the real danger.
AUSTIN:
Anything while I was gone?
DREW:
Yes.
When it was Jake,
Emily and Julie alone here,
Julie got paranoid
and pitched you to them.
-Me?
-Yeah.
So basically, Julie was just
like, "I can maybe get Katurah
to write down Austin's name."
-For real?
-EMILY: Yeah.
AUSTIN:
I had to tell Dee.
If I were to blindside Julie
without telling Dee,
then, our trust
is completely broken.
JULIE:
Dee, can I talk
to you for a second?
-Yes. Okay.
-Very quick second?
AUSTIN:
It is crucial
that Dee does not tell Julie.
And in Dee's shoes,
that's so hard.
Hmm.
I don't think so.
But now that
my name's out there...
Yeah, if she plays something,
I'll play something.
-Okay.
-Right.
Right now, there are two
potential targets--
Emily and Julie.
If worst comes to worst, we can
easily vote out Emily tonight.
But logically,
I can't bring Julie
because she will win.
Tonight,
I'll be bringing my amulet,
which is an idol that's active
until the final six.
If things get crazy, I might
have to it play tonight, but
I'm planning on playing it
at next Tribal.
Why don't I just write Austin?
No, you're getting
too personal about it.
No. Emily is more of a threat.
Austin's about
to write my name down.
But he doesn't want to.
Like, I don't think
he's the mastermind behind this.
-It's Drew.
-I know.
-We have to separate them.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
If I take out Austin,
Drew's weak.
-Hmm.
-I mean, I don't want
to take out Austin, but...
Yeah, but Austin's also
my number one, though.
-I know he is.
-You know what I mean?
-I know that. No.
-Please don't do that.
DEE:
She's paranoid, and that's
what scares me. Literally,
my world is in Julie's hands.
My family's lives
are in Julie's hands.
Everything that...
My biggest whys,
the reason why I'm in this game
is in Julie's hands right now.
This is what's gonna happen.
-They're gonna write you, okay?
-Yup.
-I'm gonna write you, too.
-Because then we're gonna
hate each other after this.
-Okay.
And you're gonna play your idol
and you're writing Emily.
-Got you. Got you.
-Okay?
JULIE:
She just told me
that Austin's her number one.
Will she pick him over me?
Maybe it's better
that I take her number one out.
Heading into
Tribal Council tonight,
Dee wants me to vote for Emily,
but I want to vote for Austin.
I hate someone telling me
what to do.
[thunder crashing]
I've never had my back
such against the wall
that whichever move I make could
either save me or destroy me.
Like, it's... it's overwhelming.
[soft, rolling thunder]
♪ ♪
All right.
-So, Jake?
-Yeah.
PROBST:
21 days in, does it get
easier or more difficult
to differentiate between
it's a game,
but these are real people?
You know, I think it gets harder
because you get
to know people better.
You get to learn more
about their families,
learn about their mentality,
where they come from in life.
So it gets a lot harder,
I think.
-PROBST: How about you, Drew?
-DREW: Yeah, Jeff. I do think
that, paradoxically,
as the game goes along,
it does get actually easier.
Like, we are so close
to the end, and
that gives you a lot
of perspective
about why you're out here and
who you're playing for at home.
And it's like a wake-up slap
that, like,
it's time to get going.
-It's now or never.
-PROBST: Julie, do you agree
with Drew that it gets easier?
Yes.
Actually, I do, because,
like, the first ones that
made the jury--
those hurt so much.
But at some point you just got
to give yourself permission
to play the game.
So, Katurah,
how do you separate it?
"I like these people.
I've only known 'em 21 days.
"I have to vote somebody out.
"I really don't want
to hurt 'em, but I want
to get to the end
and I want to win."
So, how does that play out?
I think it plays out differently
for each player,
and I think some people
can acknowledge the closeness
of a relationship
but still understand,
"I have to remove emotion
from this decision
if I want to get far."
Otherwise, we've seen people
say, "I'd rather you win.
I don't want to vote you out."
Things like that happen,
and you can only imagine
it's due to the closeness
of those relationships.
PROBST:
Emily, how about for you?
You know, to sum it up, I think
there's a lot
of very full bags tonight.
I'm not sure
if anybody came here--
with the exception
of maybe Drew--
without everything packed.
And so I think a lot of people
are planning on possibly
not going back to camp.
So, Drew, it was
an interesting afternoon, then?
Yeah, absolutely it was,
and I'll tell you,
I was very glad
to have this bad boy on,
uh, giving me some protection
for it... for it all.
That's the quietest
and shortest answer
-you've given
this entire season.
-[laughing]
-So let's dig a little more.
-All right then.
-Oh, boy.
Let's get the shovel out.
What do you want to know?
I'm just looking, Drew,
for a sense of
-what was happening
back at camp.
-DREW: All right.
But first, an historical
reference, a callback.
Please.
DREW:
When the philosopher
Hegel first met Napoleon,
he wrote that it was
as if a new era of history
had stood before him
right there.
And I think when Bruce left,
there was a real sense that
here was a hinge in the game,
and that now, more than ever,
you needed to start
to prepare yourself
for a final three.
And I think that a lot
of people are wondering, like,
on this new page of history,
uh, where they stand.
So, Julie, it sounds like
anything can happen.
JULIE:
This next vote,
it's not just
staying alive anymore.
It's who you're gonna be with
at the end.
And I feel like we all
love one another so much,
but-- ugh!-- I am forced
to write
someone's name down that
I love just as much
as the next person.
PROBST:
Is that what it was
for you, Emily?
EMILY:
Yeah, I think that's
definitely accurate.
Just, there's an element of this
game that you don't prepare for,
which is, you know,
getting really, really close
to somebody, and we all
like each other so much.
Like, look, I-I put
on a stone face a lot of times,
but, like, you know,
you have to have a heart,
and this... this is...
This game rips your heart out
sometimes.
AUSTIN:
You know, Jeff, we're all
huge fans of the game.
We've been dreaming of this
for so long, and knowing that
you're playing a part
in potentially, you know,
ending someone's dream--
it takes a toll.
And we've been
walking this line between
playing really hard and ruthless
but also really connecting
as a family.
And so, now it's trying to
figure out whose paths align.
Do you have any paths that align
with other people's paths,
and can you work together
to get to the end?
Katurah, how much talk is there
of idols being in the game
or advantages being in the game?
And does the fact
that there hasn't been
a lot of advantages or idols
played this season make you
more comfortable
or more unnerved?
KATURAH:
I'm extremely worried.
I actually think that means
people have been holding their
cards close to their chest,
and that's a higher risk of
things to start coming out now
when the numbers are tight,
when people are more at risk.
And so, all it takes is one
person to say, "You know what?
I'm feeling too worried.
Let me play something,"
and your plan
completely goes away.
And as much connecting
and relationship-building
and alliance-forming
that you may have had,
that really doesn't matter
if you're the,
you know, ricochet vote
because somebody played an idol.
All right, on that note,
it is time to vote.
Drew, you're up.
♪ ♪
If you're still here
at the final three,
you have my vote
for a million dollars,
and that's a problem.
Keeping you here another day
with my idol could be
a million-dollar mistake.
If this doesn't work,
I blame Austin
and his stupid, emotional heart.
Play the damn idol.
[sighs]
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
-JULIE: Jeff?
-[gasping]
-I want to play it for myself.
-Okay.
[sighs]
This isa hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast
for Julie will not count.
Ooh!
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Julie.
Does not count.
♪ ♪
Julie. Does not count.
One vote left.
PROBST:
Twelfth person voted out
and the fifth member
of our jury:
-Emily.
Need to bring me your torch.
-I'm so sorry.
-EMILY: It's okay. This was...
Such a pleasure
to play with you guys.
-I'm so sorry.
-Do not feel bad.
I'm so sorry.
-JAKE: Hey, great game, girl.
-EMILY: Great... great game.
Uh-huh.
Emily, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
My vote's going
to the best player.
-There goes a badass
right there.
-Mm-hmm.
JAKE:
There goes a badass.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
AUSTIN:
This was an absolute disaster.
Julie and Drew--
they are at war with each other.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
I agree.
JAKE:
I'm not out of this game.
I'm a wolf
in goat's clothing.
We're so frigging close.
DEE:
You cannot let your emotions
get in the way.
I am risking a million dollars.
Nobody wants this
to happen to them in Survivor,
but what an epic way to go.
But this has been the most
amazing experience of my life.
I learned that
when I come on really strong
and aggressive, that it's
probably not the best way
to make friends
or alliances in this game,
but I'm so pleased that I was
given so many extra days here
to really change myself,
pivot my strategy
and learn a lot along the way.
[roars]