Okay.
We all know I'm the backup.
We know I'm on the bottom.
-Sorry, Jake.
I don't even want to say
I was left in the dark.
I wasn't even left
in the same dimension.
Previously onSurvivor...
Yeah.
I placed one of my idols
in Julie's bag
to make sure she stayed safe.
This is it.
-Julie drops.
-Bruce wins his second
individual immunity in a row.
Wow.
Ugh. Bruce winning
another immunity is tough.
I already know
everybody wants Jake out.
Such an easy vote,
but I don't want that.
She's trying to get me out.
I want Kendra out,
and that's what
I'm gonna push for.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member
of our jury: Kendra.
The tribe has spoken.
That Tribal Council...
Oh, my gosh.
And thank you for, uh,
not voting for me tonight.
Appreciate it.
So tonight, Kendra was
blindsided, and I'm still alive.
I had to play the dead dog
for the last two votes,
and I don't have
to do that anymore.
I got friends in this game.
I got people
who want to look out for me.
Knock on wood, but I think
I'm back in this game.
I'm back in this game
as a player, not as a pawn.
That was a huge thing,
and that was like, whoa,
but I hope you guys know that,
like, I got your backs.
You know what I mean?
Jake, you know, he's just
bumming through the game.
He's like Charlie Brown.
There's a rain cloud that
follows over the top of him.
And miraculously,
people are just
aiming right past him
at other targets.
Interesting that
Bruce ended up...
I mean, I guess he never
really liked Kendra, but...
-Just let her go.
Voted with it-- for her.
Yeah.
Just-just went with it.
On the other hand,
Bruce continues to be
in a very interesting spot
in the game,
where he has power, right?
He has the idol.
Okay, so we need to get rid
of Bruce's idol the next go.
Oh, yeah.
We do.
And so he pretty much
is guaranteed to play that
at next Tribal Council.
Unless
he wins immunity again.
-Yeah.
The problem is that
Bruce winning
all these challenges
shreds any possibilities
of flushing his idol.
When I was in the Navy,
I was a young, strapping lad.
Okay. Okay.
Too soon. Too soon.
-Okay. Okay.
So for my sake, and for the sake
of everyone else out here,
Bruce's immunity run
has to come
to a clean and swift end ASAP.
Like a freaking baby.
We're in
such a small group here.
-It's just so crazy.
I know.
It's kind of weird.
-It's like...
It is weird, man.
We're really gonna be leaning
on each other after this.
-That's for sure.
Yeah.
I did not sleep last night.
I just couldn't sleep.
Because I am
connecting with people.
They're trusting me,
and I'm lying to their face.
Ninth person voted out
and the second member
of our jury: Kellie.
What the hell, guys?
I mean, oh,
with both Kellie and Kendra,
I was devastated.
They just wouldn't even
look at me. It felt so personal.
The feeling of betrayal
is hard for me.
I am used to being very loyal
and trustworthy,
and you can count on me
no matter what.
Just the thought that there
are two people out there
that are like,
"Man, I wouldn't trust Julie
as far as I could throw her"
hurts me.
-Oh, come on, Julie.
-Sorry. Sorry.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
It's just,
I don't lie in real life.
I didn't understand
how powerful my role--
that I agreed to,
that they put me in--
as this mama, trusting character
would make it hurt that much.
There is a chance,
at the end here,
-that things could get hairy.
-Yep.
You four are, like,
people who, like,
I-I really, you know, I really
care about deeply, and...
-And I'm saying, you...
-Okay.
I just want to know that, like,
we're all gonna be okay.
-Like, we're good no matter
what. We're good no matter what.
-100%.
-Hundred percent, Drew.
-Okay. All right.
We're getting close to the end,
and it's even more complex
and harder than I thought.
It's an emotional mental test
for all of us.
I mean, I have
loved my alliance of four
with Drew, Austin,
Dee and myself,
but, at some point,
we got to turn on each other.
I almost can't even go there.
How do you vote them out
and they love you?
I mean, are you kidding me?
Yeah, it's four-four.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's what's scaring me.
-Yeah.
Who's making decisions
for those four?
Do we know?
Is Dee the one that says,
-"Here's the vote,"
and they all...
-Um... I don't know.
Right now,
there's still four people
who have come in
from a majority alliance
into the merge.
And part of me
thinks they're not
going to turn on each other.
It scares me.
I-I hope that
Drew, Austin and myself
are working together,
but I am now re-questioning
my alliances,
where people are standing.
And I'm being forced to go back
and forge new relationships.
If we want to make something
happen for the other side...
-Yeah. Yeah.
-we're gonna all have
to get together, and... Yeah.
What are
your thoughts about that?
Um...
If I were to make a big move
against this strong Reba four,
I need support.
And what's extremely frustrating
about working
with Jake, Bruce and Katurah
is they don't know
how to work together at all.
I'm on the chopping block
for the next time we go,
-just because of...
Only your idol.
-That's the only... Yeah.
-Yeah.
Then on top of it, Bruce
doesn't seem interested at all
in playing
his idol strategically.
He's only interested
in protecting his own butt
-with his idol.
-Uh, all right.
And what he's not realizing
is he actually
has an opportunity to flip
the power dynamic
while there's still,
theoretically,
four and four on this tribe.
I'm so glad
we're back working together.
-Thank you very much.
-Yeah.
It just feels so good
to be back on the same page.
Between you and I
and nobody else...
Yeah? Uh-oh.
-What?
-The worst thing that
you could ever do in Survivor.
What's the thing you did?
You gave her your idol?
Wait, no, you didn't.
Hypothetically,
someone could take my idol
if they had the
Knowledge Is Power Advantage,
so I gave my idol to Kellie
to hold on to,
because I was nervous
of the Knowledge Is Power.
Kellie got voted out
with my idol.
Worst-case scenario.
Well, "Oh, no.
I lost my-my idol."
But it's in my pocket.
So...
I tested out
my first really big lie.
-I still have that. I'm not...
-Why...
-But here's the deal. I need...
-What is that...
-Listen. Listen, listen.
-Damn it.
I'm saying it to you,
'cause how did you feel
about my acting
when I told you about that?
-I believed you.
-One of them are gonna get that.
Okay. Okay.
-You feel me?
-No, I don't.
Bruce's plan is ridiculous.
I didn't believe it
for a second.
I mean, I don't believe
anything he ever says to me,
but it doesn't really matter,
because this won't work.
Everybody knows he has an idol.
No one's gonna believe this,
by the way. Like, no one will.
-I started freaking out
because Knowledge Is Power.
-Okay.
So she got voted out
with an idol in her pocket?
With an idol in her pocket.
-My...
-Your idol in her pocket.
Yay.
Okay, that's a...
that's a problem.
Now I got
to fight a different way.
My diabolical plan--
it's working.
So I'm leaking information.
I'm like my own TMZ right now.
I mean, look,
it was the right move,
but you bet on the wrong horse.
That's all.
-You know what I mean?
-Right.
With this lie
that I'm telling Jake,
it will get out.
I know it will.
He's going
to spill the beans to Reba,
because Jake
does not have the ability
to play this game in a way
to keep his mouth shut.
Okay. All right. All right.
All right. Cool.
I need them to think
that I'm vulnerable,
because now, the four Reba--
they're all gonna vote for me,
and then I play that idol,
I could turn and look and say,
"Sorry, not today," and then
kiss your backside goodbye.
I'll see if the plan works.
Come on in.
Oh.
Wow.
Oh, no.
Crazy.
Morning, Jeff.
-Good morning.
Hey, Probst.
All right, shall we get
to today's reward challenge?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race through
a series of obstacles,
collecting a ball along the way.
You'll then crawl under a net
and, ultimately,
maneuver that ball
through a maze.
First person to finish
wins reward.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yeah.
You'll leave here
and be taken to the sanctuary...
...where good things happen.
-Today, very good things.
-Ooh.
You'll have dinner.
-Turkey.
-Ooh.
Mashed potatoes and gravy.
-Yeah. There it is.
-Oh, my gosh.
Little apple pie.
Yes.
-Oh!
Beer. Soda.
-Oh, my God.
Juice.
-He's not stopping.
-Oh, my gosh.
-I'm not stopping.
Let's make it even better.
You're gonna spend the night...
-Whoa! Whoa!
...at the sanctuary,
where you will have pillows...
-Oh, my gosh.
...blanket.
Worth playing for?
-Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Hell yeah. What?
All right, we're gonna draw
for spots. We'll get it on.
-Let's go, baby!
-Oh, my God.
Here we go. For reward
and a night at the sanctuary.
Survivors ready?
Go!
-This first stage
is over, over and then under.
That's how you do it.
Attack this challenge!
Austin's through first.
There's Bruce. There goes Dee.
-There goes Jake.
Now you've got
to untie a series of knots.
Emily's through.
Here comes Katurah.
Julie now through.
You got to untie every knot.
Once you have the bag
released from the knot,
start crawling underneath.
Jake is through first.
Look at that.
Here comes Dee.
There's Bruce. Austin now in it.
Day 18, Survivor45.
Ain't nothing easy.
It is Emily and Julie
all the way back.
It is Jake in the lead. You're
trying to get to that maze.
Wow. And very quickly,
Austin makes up a lot of time.
Austin is now to the maze first.
There's Jake.
Here comes Dee.
Keep digging.
Drew is through.
Here comes Bruce.
Here comes Emily.
-What?
Here comes Katurah.
Kneecap by kneecap,
Julie is
working her way through.
There you go, Julie.
Big reward on the line.
Night at the sanctuary.
-Oh, shoot.
This is a lot of touch.
You got to figure out the maze.
Then you've got
to have that deft touch
to avoid the holes,
like Emily just did.
Your ball will drop.
That's okay.
Learn each time you do it.
That's the key.
Austin drops.
He's got to start again.
Jake drops.
Got to start again.
Drew drops.
No.
Bruce drops.
Dee making some nice progress.
Relax.
But drops.
-Damn it.
Emily's out on it now.
Austin, once again,
giving it another go.
No, no, no, no.
Katurah drops.
Got to start again.
Julie drops. Somebody's
gonna get a rhythm going.
And out of nowhere,
they're gonna win this.
That's how it goes.
Emily making a lot of progress.
Austin gaining a lot
of ground on that maze.
It is Austin and Emily
in a showdown right now
to win it.
Emily very close to the center,
but one big obstacle left
for the biggest reward
of the season.
It is literally side by side,
neck and neck between these two.
Emily really
is going for the big move.
She's in the center.
Can she stick it?
Austin right on her tail.
Literally inches away
from disaster or victory.
Austin very close,
but he drops at the last spot.
-Emily gets it.
Emily wins reward.
Wow.
Biggest reward
of the season.
Her body is shaking.
Literally shaking.
It has been an emotional
18 days for Emily
of highs and lows.
-This has got to be at the top.
-Unbelievable. Good job, Emily.
Yeah!
You're going to the sanctuary!
On your own, too.
Wow.
Emily, walk me through
what happened
right after you won,
because even where I was,
standing behind you,
I saw your body start to shake.
Um, honestly, it's surreal.
I've said it from the beginning.
I came here not expecting
to win anything.
I mean, look at all of them
and look at me.
Um, but coming into today's
challenge, we had talked.
We figured
it was a reward challenge,
and everybody was saying,
"Well, Emily, if we have
-the chance to take someone,
we'll take you."
-Mm-hmm.
"You haven't been
to the sanctuary yet." And it...
And I really appreciate
that mentality, but it kind of
makes you feel
really bad about yourself,
because, you know,
I want to deserve it.
I want to earn it. If I get
there, I get there on my own,
and I'm really happy
that-that I'm gonna
-get there on my own today.
Yes.
You are.
-Yes, you are!
Come on over. Right here.
-There you go, Emily.
Dance, dance, dance.
All right,
so here's the deal, Emily.
You're gonna spend the night
at the sanctuary,
where you're gonna have turkey,
mashed potatoes, gravy, pie.
Oh, my gosh.
After you enjoy your dinner,
as you cozy up with your pillow,
you will have
a very clear reminder
of why you are here,
-with your letters from home.
-Oh, you g...
So now you have
a very complicated decision.
Choose one person
to join you at the sanctuary
for the biggest reward
of the season.
Mama J, you have not
been sleeping.
Your neck woke up this morning,
and you
were in such severe pain.
I know that letter from home
and that bed will do you good,
so come join me.
Julie, what's the feeling?
You're not
even at the sanctuary,
but clearly
you're already starting
to anticipate what this
is gonna do for you.
I don't even know
if I can talk about it.
I can't even imagine.
This morning
was the roughest I've had, so...
-In terms of missing home.
-Missing home,
and, um, I'm hoping that
this gives me the strength.
-Thank you.
-All right, Emily,
choose another person
to join you at the sanctuary.
Mm.
-Katurah, come join.
-Really?
:
Really?
I'm the last one I expected.
Do you not want to?
-No, I want to.
I'm just so happy.
-Okay.
-I'm glad you want it, too.
Like,
I didn't expect it at all,
and I was just bracing myself
for not getting it.
Drew.
-Yeah.
What's going on?
It's a hard choice,
and I think everyone wants it.
Everyone wants the food,
everyone wants
the comfort from home,
and I-I don't
have anything more-more to say.
It's a tough spot.
-Emily, you have one more spot.
I know there's
one person out here
who has talked about
her family every single day.
Dee, let's
make it a ladies night.
-Yes.
-Come on over, Dee.
All right, Emily,
Dee, Julie, Katurah,
grab your stuff, head out.
Enjoy the sanctuary.
-Have fun, ladies.
-Congratulations.
:
Oh, my God.
All right, Drew, Austin, Jake,
Bruce, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Thank you.
All right, massive pot of rice.
Extra big.
This reward
is the most significant
in terms of bonding
that you get.
Letters from home
would bring anyone
tighter together,
so obviously, yes,
I'm a little nervous
about a girls night.
You just have to hope that
everything you built
is enough to carry over
one amazing night
at the sanctuary.
Emily just made the biggest
decision of the season.
And it's these kind of moments
that make Survivor
so fun to play.
Apply to be on Survivor.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, look at the beanbag.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
:
Emily! Emily!
Thank you so much.
-Darling, thank you.
-Oh, my God.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
For Emily to win
is one of the greatest moments,
I think, of our season.
She did it. She brought
herself to the sanctuary.
When I heard that this
was gonna be an overnight,
I already knew
I was taking my girls.
-For what it's worth. Yes, 100%.
-Yeah! Oh, my God!
This is probably the greatest
reward. Turns out, she picks
all the women on the tribe.
So the men are back.
They're having their boys night,
and we're gonna
have a girls night.
This whole adventure
has been so weird.
I feel like, in my little time
of knowing you,
-I think you underestimate
yourself a lot.
Yes.
I don't think that you realize
how big of a force you are.
I hope you see
what we see in you, and...
Not just us. Like,
everybody else, too, you know?
Mm-hmm. Agreed.
Thank you, guys.
To be honest,
I never thought I'd win
any sort of challenge--
nonetheless
a reward challenge of this size.
I am so proud of the fact
that I'm sitting right here.
I know what I've been through,
and it's absolutely
just a little tiny piece
of paradise in what has
otherwise been this kind of,
like, hellscape
of an experience for me
on Survivor.
We are going
to have a female winner
-for season 45 of Survivor.
-I love this. I love this.
-I call it. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
We're over here
drinking sangria,
we're chatting. I mean,
we're just connecting
as humans.
The four of us
get along wonderfully.
And those vibes--
I mean, just great vibes.
Julie, you've been in there
-for every single challenge,
every single one.
-Oh, you're sweet.
I haven't
brought it home, but...
-You'll bring it home.
You will. Watch.
-We just got to, you know...
-All right. This is...
Then
we can win these challenges.
-He has an idol, too, so...
-Yep.
He needs to go.
Well, I think
he's gonna try to...
The lie he told me he's gonna
try to push off on everybody
is that Kellie...
w-walked out the door
with his idol in her pocket.
I think it's a little
too late to make that comment.
-I'm just gonna say,
like, the day of.
Yeah.
He was like, "Do you think
people will believe it?"
I said, "I mean, I believed it."
That's good.
Bruce made this half-brain plan,
and I told the girls, because
I have no loyalty to Bruce.
He was a terrible
alliance member,
and that's
why I'm in revenge mode.
We, fueled by this
wonderful Thanksgiving meal,
show up to the immunity
challenge tomorrow, crush it.
-Mm-hmm.
-Flush Bruce's idol.
We get him out next time.
I agree. A thousand percent.
Or if he plays his idol,
then Jake,
but we got to flush his idol.
Are you guys okay with putting
more votes on Bruce, though?
Like, in case
he doesn't play the idol,
-so he can go home first?
Of course.
-Yeah.
And that would
just be even more delicious.
-Yeah.
I can't wait
to get Bruce out, but
Bruce is gonna play his idol.
So having Jake
as the backup vote is very safe.
He's kind of alone.
He has no real allies right now.
What do you think
the guys are saying right now?
-It'll be fine.
-They're having boys night.
We're having a girls night.
Let's go.
This is heaven.
Wow.
Boys' camping trip tonight.
Yeah.
Yeah, what's up?
-None of mine have had
much volume out here, honestly.
-Same.
-Yeah.
-I don't know
if I've farted in 18 days.
That's not true.
I did fart once.
-Ah. What-what spurred it?
Okay.
It was, uh, it was
definitely a merge feast fart.
Oh. Nice.
Nothing from the candy, though?
-Italian.
-Oh.
Oh, there we go.
There you go.
That was good.
Passing gas is happening.
Men's day, baby. Let's go.
-Oh!
-Guys being dudes.
Ladies night at the sanctuary.
Boys night out camping.
There's a little more
flatulence, little more burping,
and it's nice to just be
the guys sometimes, you know?
You haven't
gotten that in 18 days,
and it's just the boys.
Like, let's do it up, guys.
Oh, yeah. My man.
Yeah. Come here. Come here.
You know, I have
never been one of the boys.
I have never bro'd out.
Like, I've observed
the "bro-out" only from
an anthropological distance.
Yeah.
We can talk about all this, uh,
this locker-room stuff, I guess.
We talked about food a lot.
We talked about,
like, action movies.
Like, the stuff that the girls
don't want to talk about.
It's, like, okay, bacon is good,
-but it's not, like,
amazing. I mean...
-Bacon is pretty good.
It's a little overrated.
Pork is very fatty.
I'm doing my best,
but, you know, it was fun,
and you got to try new things
out here on Survivor.
So I-I tried to bro out.
All right.
Here we go, man.
Bring home the fish.
It's so much fun
trying to catch your own fish.
I've never done it before.
I've never speared fish before.
I've been fighting for fish
for hours out there,
only getting little tiny ones.
But it's not only about eating,
but just, like,
enjoying all this wildlife.
Fiji is gorgeous.
To be able to have,
like, my backyard
be this gorgeous
Fiji coral, like,
unbelievable.
And, oh, my gosh.
Finally, my first big catch.
It was amazing.
Hey, it's
a Thanksgiving feast today.
-Whoo!
Yeah, man.
-That's an actual fish.
Everyone got excited.
They're like,
"Wow, we're actually
gonna have some meat tonight."
-I'll try one more.
Go ahead, Aquaman.
We know the women are feasting.
We have to eat
something substantial
just so that we can keep up with
the ladies when they get back.
-Whoo!
Got it?
Got another one?
Hey, it's working.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
I think, for you and I,
the preemptive strike
to talk about now would be...
I see what you're saying.
-Remember,
I'm trying to c...
find ways to save my own ass.
No, I know.
Me not having my freaking idol,
I'm, you know,
I'm putting all my chips
on the table right now.
Yeah, no. Dee needs to go.
It's just, how do we do it?
Very much so. But I got
to find out where her mind is.
I know that she's not
too keen on going after Dee.
Bruce is like, "Dee, she's
a huge threat in this game."
But it's not happening.
As much as I love Bruce, I need
to unhitch my wagon to him.
We've been
connected this whole game,
and if I'm attached to him,
people see us as a pair,
I become a bigger target.
And so what he's thinking
is that it's gonna be Dee.
Hmm. I think the odds
of that working out are slim.
Yeah, I agree.
People have said
Bruce is only dangerous
because he's
holding on to that idol.
If he gave his idol to Kellie,
there's a good chance
that idol is no longer here.
That puts Bruce's butt
in a dangerous place.
All that matters,
that idol goes.
-It doesn't matter who goes.
-Yeah.
-I got
to tell you something, man.
-What?
See how disappointed
Kellie was leaving?
Yeah. She had an idol?
She had his.
You're kidding.
You're kidding. You're
shutting-the-front-door kidding.
-He doesn't have an idol.
-I don't think so.
Oh, my freaking God.
We're good.
-We're good. We're totally good.
-We're good.
I don't want Bruce's
threat level going down.
I want it staying up.
So I'm telling Drew.
I have a working relationship
with Drew.
I think he's helping me out
right now,
and I think he's valuable to me.
Like, it's like there's, like,
two headlights on Bruce,
and he's, like,
America's Most Wanted.
Yeah.
Oh.
Jake is kind of
a puppy dog, at this point,
for Austin and myself.
Jake,
who hasn't had a clue in days,
suddenly comes to me
with a pressing bit
of confidential information.
Immediately,
I was overjoyed.
Bruce came up to Jake
and told him that
he had given his idol to Kellie.
-Oh, my freaking goodness.
-My God.
-If it's true. If it's true...
-Dude, that move was,
like, one of the best moves.
Oh, it was so trusting.
Oh.
Things are looking sweet.
The chopping block right now
is Bruce, and Jake is desperate.
Both of them are essentially
drawing dead in the game.
Kind of nervous
for these letters.
Like, our family wrote to us.
Oh, my God.
Okay, are we opening?
-Are we doing this?
-I'm like, I'm sorry.
I can't even wait.
Just seeing all the letters,
it just reminded me
I am so rich
with an amazing family.
OnSurvivor, if the food is
the fuel, the letters are fire.
In this game, fire is your life.
So these letters, they just
reminded me of who I am.
And my brother Dan said,
"At the time of your divorce,
"with no career,
no home and two small children,
you needed a hero,
so you became one."
"I just want you to know
that long before that,
and to this day, you have
always been a hero to me."
My dad says...
I haven't, like, let myself
think about the fact that
while I'm out here, Eric is,
like, moving into our house.
Oh, wow.
-Um... And it's like
this big life moment
-that I'm just missing.
-Yeah.
Like, it's our first house
together,
and I'm just not there
at all for any of it.
And he's like, you know, "When
you come back to the house..."
and "So excited
to bring you to the new house."
And, you know...
Anyway, I just...
I think I feel a lot of guilt
for missing what should be,
-like, a big life moment.
-Yeah.
The first letter I open
is from Eric, my boyfriend.
We've been together
for almost a decade,
and I've said,
almost my entire life,
"I don't think
I want to get married."
I don't view myself as a wife.
I don't view myself as...
It's not a term
that I use to describe myself.
And now I'm out here,
and I can't imagine myself
not spending
the rest of my life with Eric.
You think about somebody
every single day, and...
It's funny, when you get
stripped of everything else,
when you get stripped of all
this BS that exists in life...
...that makes
you realize what's important.
All these notions
that I force on myself
to be a certain way,
I don't need to be that.
I can just be Emily.
And maybe Emily loves Eric,
and maybe that's okay.
And maybe Emily
will get married.
That's a really
weird thing to say.
I'm not making any promises, but
maybe Emily will get married.
Thank you for letting us
have this moment.
-Thank you so much, Emily.
-Yeah, of course.
Thank you, guys.
This is
the best day of Survivor.
Nothing will top this.
I'm having a little bit
of a conflicting feeling.
Aw...
-And I just did not expect it.
Yep.
-And now I'm feeling all,
like...
I bet.
Just, I don't really know how
to feel about it.
I went no contact with my mom,
like, a year ago.
And so I'm not, like, hiding it.
I just did not
expect that to come up.
-You are a warrior,
and I'm so proud of you.
Thank you so much.
I-I support you 100%.
My true whole life story
is just literally all sad,
and I don't want to let myself
fall into that pit of darkness.
I need to win this game,
and I'm not gonna win this game
if I'm thinking
about all my sad stuff.
So, yeah, I'm gonna finish
this glass of wine.
Morning!
Morning.
-Morning.
-Oh, hi, boys.
How are y'all?
Yeah?
The boys day
was an interesting experience.
It was like letting
your hair down a little bit,
but it's nice
to have the girls return home.
And I'll be interested to hear
the details
of that whole sanctuary trip.
Nobody in that group
of four wants to target y'all.
-Yeah.
-Especially not
before Jake and Bruce.
Bruce came up to Jake yesterday
and told Jake that
he had given Kellie his idol
to hold on to
for Knowledge Is Power.
-Oh, it's, it's a lie.
-Yeah?
-You know for sure?
-Yeah, because he told Katurah
that he was gonna say that
to try to convince people
that he didn't have his idol.
-Great. Great.
-Yeah. So it's 100% a lie.
So ideally, Bruce and Jake--
neither win immunity.
If Bruce wins immunity,
-we just take out Jake.
-Yeah.
That's how
I would like it to go.
Me, too.
If Bruce loses
the immunity challenge,
he's going to play his idol,
and it's probably
gonna cause Jake to go home.
Everybody has been
kind of lying to Jake
for a long time now.
And I've done my best
to be honest with him,
because
if he is sitting on the jury,
I want him
to have some respect for me--
that I was
talking to him like a human
and not just
like a chess piece.
If Bruce plays his idol...
Okay. Let's...
Well, like...
Everybody?
-Is that surprising to you?
-A little bit, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Um, I'm in a decent spot
in this game right now,
and if I do that,
I blow up my spot,
-like, oh, by a lot.
-Yeah.
So that sucks.
I'm sick
of being the backup target.
I don't want
to be the backup target.
You don't want to be that
in this game, and
I'm a little pissed about Drew
'cause this whole game,
he's been feeding me M&Ms,
trying to string me along.
But he doesn't care
if I'm the backup vote,
so I don't care
if he's the vote.
There are bigger threats
in this game than me.
-Like Drew.
If you want to do something,
like, we can do something.
Yup, yup.
I got to go on the... I...
Yeah, yeah. No, I know, I know.
So I pitched Drew's name.
Everyone's kind of
giving me the runaround.
It really sucks,
but I'm ready to do something.
Everyone else here is ready
to sit on their hands
and do nothing,
or they're not ready
to do it with me.
Jake was trying to get me
to go in with him
on numbers.
Yes.
-Really? All right.
-How you feeling?
I'm not nervous.
I trust you all.
-All right, well...
-So, you're the name
that he's doing.
Well, I think he was the...
I'm the last-ditch effort.
Jake has been throwing my name
out there, and I'm indignant
because he was going to go.
And I said,
"No, let it be Kellie."
He was going to go.
I said, "Let it be Kendra."
And so for him
to throw my name out there
is a slap in the face.
Why me?
I don't understand.
Wait. So you don't care
if I catch a stray bullet,
but I got to care if you do?
-I just wonder, "Why me?"
-Why not?
-Island full of people.
-Yeah, but why me?
Because
you don't have any allies.
I mean, I'm the only person
who's been batting for you.
Drew's mad 'cause
I said his name.
He wants to feel like,
"I've kept you in this game."
No, dude.
There's other people
looking out for me.
You are not a gift from God.
Relax.
-Sucks hearing your name?
-Yeah, of course it does.
And who did you talk to?
Who?
I think our conversation's done.
-Ours is?
-Yeah.
All right, all right. All right,
mobster, go have fun with it.
"Oh, you want information
fromme now?
Oh, that's funny, Drew, 'cause
I don't want to tell you."
Dude, I'm on the bottom.
How am I the mobster?
-How am I in charge?
-Because you're like,
"Our conversation is done."
Like, okay, like, all right.
What do you want to say
to me, Drew?
You're not...
You can't help me.
Are you for real, dude?
He thinks he's the big
Boston mobster ofThe Departed.
You gonna like, gonna, you know,
"This conversation's over."
So I'm like,
"Get out of here, dude.
You're a goon.
Your game is dunzo."
Bring in the boat.
Not a bad way
to arrive to a challenge.
-No, definitely not.
-Not at all.
Come on.
Oh, no.
What?
Oh, man.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-For the second time, Bruce,
I'm gonna take it back.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're going to lie
on a steep ramp
suspended over water.
You're going
to hold yourself there
by holding on to handholds.
At regular intervals,
you're going to move
to smaller handholds...
-Oh.
...making it more difficult.
If you drop, you are out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity, guaranteed
a spot in the final seven.
Losers, after 19 days,
11th person voted out,
fourth member of our jury.
Big enough stakes?
-All right, we're going
to draw for spots,
and we will get it on.
-Let's go!
Let's go!
All right,
everybody take your spots,
maneuver your body.
You're going to be lying
on that plank.
You're going to go down
to that second set of handholds.
Everybody is good,
and this challenge is on.
It is dead quiet.
You'll be in this position
for five minutes.
Then we'll move down
to a smaller handhold.
It will get more difficult.
You're going
to feel it everywhere.
-You're going to feel it
in your hands,
your shoulders, your arms.
Everything is very uncomfortable
already.
You can see it.
Emily's going to be first out.
No shot at immunity.
And we are down to seven.
How you doing, Katurah?
I just think
I'm too in my head right now.
-About the water?
-Yeah.
Katurah,
the ladder's right here.
Ooh. Ooh.
You got this.
And if we drop,
is somebody around?
We have safety swimmers
in the water, I'm here,
and a ladder's right here.
Ooh.
Katurah, if you want
to let go, we got you.
-I'd like to.
Okay. You do you.
-Hey, go ahead and do it...
-Can somebody be here?
Let go, slide down
and get right over here.
Take care of yourself.
Let go and start swimming.
-I'm dropping.
Drop and start swimming
toward me immediately.
-Ready?
-Come on, you got it, kid.
Just go. Just go.
If you can maneuver your body
to get off, just get off.
-Okay.
Water's not a part
of the test.
It's up to you.
I don't know why.
I'm so sorry, guys. So sorry.
You're perfect.
Don't worry about a thing.
No sorrys, Katurah.
Come over here. Emily,
you want to give her a hand?
You're gonna be all right.
All right, Katurah is out.
We are down to six.
Jake trying to stay in.
Use those feet as a wedge.
That'll help.
Does not have to be pretty.
Only thing that matters
is staying up there.
All right, in a moment,
you're going to move down
to the third handhold.
Here we go.
Start making that move.
Everybody has moved down
to the next smaller handhold.
And you're still in it.
Everybody's good.
Now it's getting
even more difficult.
Sorry, guys. I'm out.
Julie drops, and we're down
to five, fighting for immunity.
-Good job, Julie.
This challenge
will sneak up on you.
Don't lose your focus.
Channel whatever you need to.
This is kind of
a fun challenge
you might do at a carnival
for laughs
while you're having a scone.
-What carnival
have you seen this at?
Yeah.
I don't think
anyone does this for fun.
It is Drew, Jake,
Dee, Austin
and Bruce...
lying on a ramp of wood
over the ocean in Fiji
with a million dollars
on the line.
All right, in a moment,
you're going to move down
to the next handhold.
And what you're going to do is--
those feet,
which you've been using
as a wedge--
your legs got to go flat out.
That's going to remove a lot
of your leverage.
This is your last move.
Here we go.
Begin your move.
This is a live transition.
You got to get down
to the next smaller handholds.
And now, legs out, everybody.
It just got a lot harder.
Let's go, Dee.
You got to move.
Great job! Wow!
Well done. We're in
-the last phase
of this challenge now.
-That's amazing.
-Whoo!
This is it.
Good job, boys.
Dee is out immediately.
We're down to four.
-Good job, Dee.
Good job, Dee.
It is Drew, Jake,
Austin and Bruce.
You want to be safe tonight,
guarantee yourself a spot
at seven.
Don't drop, Jake!
Nah, man.
Hold it!
Okay.
Aah!
-Drew drops out of nowhere.
And we're down to three.
It is Jake, Austin and Bruce.
That's how quickly it can end.
Bruce now starting
to move a little.
Jake still struggling.
Hold tight.
And once again recovers.
That's the grit
right there, Jake.
Y'all are killing it.
That's why
you keep digging.
You don't know
when the other player or players
are about to drop.
Hold on!
Hold tight!
You got this!
Jake drops. We got a showdown.
-It is Austin versus Bruce.
Good job, Jake.
Good job, guys.
Bruce has won it twice.
Austin has never won it.
Will history repeat,
or will Austin have immunity
for the first time this season?
Austin looking very calm,
but looks can be deceiving.
You got it.
Bruce looking
at Austin,
looking for a sign.
It would be Bruce's
third win in a row.
Both guys digging.
Somebody gonna have
that necklace tonight.
Let's go.
Bruce drops. It's over.
Austin wins
individual immunity.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
Another epic showdown.
Austin, come on over.
Yeah, Austin.
-Well earned.
Thank you.
-Austin,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
cannot be voted out
of this game,
guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
As for the rest of you,
after 19 tough days,
somebody going home tonight.
11th person voted out,
fourth member of our jury.
You have the afternoon to figure
out who that's going to be.
Grab your stuff, swim out.
-Katurah, I have a question.
-Oh, God.
The tradition
in a water challenge...
-Yes, I know.
-...is to dive in
-and celebrate
and swim over to your boat.
-I know.
You clearly don't like
being in the water.
I like being in the water.
I prepared for this moment.
I saw the challenge, and
my hands just started shaking.
:
I don't know. Something just...
I don't know.
So you have the option.
Everybody else
is going to jump in
and swim over.
We'll bring the boat to you, or
if you want
to just take this opportunity,
surrounded by your Tribemates,
to give it a go,
you can give it a go.
Whatever you want to do.
-There's no pressure.
Yeah, there's no pressure.
This is just if you want to.
All right, let's do it.
I'll see everybody tonight
at Tribal.
-Let's do it. Let's do it.
-Aah!
I cannot explain it.
: I would never
step out of a challenge.
It's just...
I would never do it.
Maybe I can just
appreciate the joy of, like,
a lot of people being like,
"We're just here with you.
We're with you the whole way."
-Three, two, one.
It was really beautiful,
and I...
I deeply appreciated it.
Nice work, Katurah!
Well done.
Thank you.
Good job, Austin.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you. Thank you.
-Oh, my gosh.
That was really inspiring.
That was
an incredible showdown.
-You pushed me so freaking hard.
This is my first time
not getting the necklace,
but it was okay. I have an idol.
I'm gonna play it.
I'm gonna be safe.
No votes cast against Bruce
is gonna count.
Tonight's going to be fun.
Honestly, I feel like
you're probably going to have
to play the idol tonight.
That is correct.
I think every single person here
knows that I have an idol.
I got to do it.
I got to play it.
I don't want to be the guy
who's gonna be sitting here
holding hidden immunity idol,
and I get voted off.
It's going to come down
to the ricochet.
-It is.
Exactly.
The easy one is Jake.
-I'm ready for Jake, y'all.
Yeah?
I feel like I've been so good,
and I've been waiting.
Okay.
I want to get Bruce out
or Jake out,
but Bruce is going
to play his idol tonight.
So, Jake's the ricochet.
I'm still mad he voted for me.
Dude, I'm writing
Jake's name down. He's gone.
-Okay, what do you...?
-I would like to do
a Bruce idol flush.
-Oh, yeah...
-Yeah.
-Bruce is going
to play his idol 100%.
Of course. Yes.
And Jake still goes home.
Obviously, we're going
to split votes
between Jake and Bruce.
They're huge threats
for my alliance members.
And we've been pretty much
dominating together.
If we hear names,
we go after them.
I just think getting Jake out
is a wasted vote,
and I think you cannot go
to the final three
with anybody
who people call "Mama."
Who do you love more
than anybody in the whole world?
-Your mama. Yeah.
-Your mama.
And Julie has been so warm.
I mean, just listening
to how people talk about her,
and, like...
-Everybody loves her, right?
-Yeah.
-She's impossible not to.
-Exactly.
Deep down, I'm seething
and ready for Bruce to go,
but he has that damn idol,
so I want Julie
to be the backup.
Like, we're calling Julie "Mama"
'cause we love her.
And, heck,
I love Julie so deeply
that I would give Julie
a million dollars.
This is such a sick,
twisted, disgusting,
ridiculously delicious,
enjoyable, terrifying game.
She's super strategic,
she's in with the Reba people.
Bruce is super close to her,
and everybody loved her.
That makes her super dangerous.
-I hate to be the one
to tell you this.
-I... What's up?
-Really?
-No, not with you.
I'm sorry. It's like Kellie.
She wants your jury vote.
And that's why
she's being nice to you.
I'm so sorry.
-No, listen. Hey.
-Please don't tell her
I told you that.
No, no, no, no, no, I don't
really give two poops about it.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Because I'm playing an idol
tonight.
Yeah, so, me, you,
Katurah, Jake...
I mean, you tell me. I...
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
If we take this shot at Mama J,
we cannot miss.
So I need to be 100% solid.
You have me at 110%.
I'm going to talk to Jake.
I'm trying to stress to Bruce,
"Let's make
this big move
and take Mama J out."
The truth is,
I am lying straight
to Bruce's face.
If I can appeal to Bruce's ego,
outsmart him a little bit,
outwit him a little bit,
then it's possible
that he doesn't play
his idol tonight, and he goes
home with an idol in his pocket.
It's just, the onus is on me.
As much as I'm, like,
for putting out Mama J's name
for this vote just to get,
like, potentially
-Bruce's idol flushed...
-Mm-hmm.
...I am 100% serious
about her being a real threat.
Perfect. Yeah.
I doubt Bruce falls for it, but
if Bruce doesn't play his idol
tonight, Bruce is going home.
Here's what we got.
-Lots of votes are going
to be split.
-Yeah.
Three for you, three for me,
and then... Ugh!
-Whatever else happens.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Hands-- like, two groups,
Rebas, everybody else.
"Bye, Jake. Bye, Bruce."
-Here they are.
-Yeah.
Here's the deal. We walk
back over there right now,
we come up with no plan, you're
going home tonight. That's...
-Right, right, right, right.
-There's no getting around that.
-Do you want to go home?
I don't want you to go home.
-No. No. Okay.
You are good for my game,
and I'm good for your game.
-I do still have an idol.
-Okay.
I just want to know, why'd
you lie to me about the idol?
Because I-I... Listen,
this is a game of Survivor.
You got to be able to play
the game somehow, some way.
So, Bruce does have his idol.
Bruce, honestly, man.
It's wicked frustrating
being lied to by Bruce.
I'm sick of it. I've been
lied to and rope-a-doped
and made to look like
a big fool in this game.
Bruce said he wants
to vote for Mama J.
On paper, it's a great plan.
I'm good with anyone but me.
But the problem is,
I don't know who to trust.
I just keep getting lied to.
I don't feel like
I've had any ground.
I'm at the bottom
every single time.
I've-I've just,
every single vote,
I'm playing
everyone else's game.
I'm just trying
to stay alive, and...
I know it's a game,
and everyone's playing a game,
and I don't take it personally.
It's just...
It's just like
a disappointment in myself.
You want to come out here
and be better.
You okay?
Dude, I don't know
what's going on, man.
-I don't know what's going on.
-Okay.
I don't know who's lying to me,
who's telling me the truth.
-Yeah.
-I don't know what the deal is.
It's hard to know if people are
lying daily in your face, yeah.
Yeah, dude, like, it's hard.
Yeah, man. Like, it's just hard.
It is. I got you.
-Okay. I just...
-Don't panic. We can do this.
-No, I'm not panicking.
-We can do this together.
-Okay.
-Okay, let me get back,
-'cause I said I was getting
salt water for the rice.
-Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, Katurah.
I appreciate it.
I'm just having a tough time.
You know what I mean?
-I know. All right, listen.
-I-I'm sorry.
I'm not trying to, like...
I'm-I'm good with the plan.
It's just, I just thought I'd,
like, be better at this game.
-I just always feel so dumb.
-Look at. Look at. Ready? Ready?
Don't drop yourself down
to what you're not.
Look at me.
You know what you just hit?
The Survivorwall.
But congratulations, though.
You did it longer
than it took me.
I hit mine, like, four days ago.
-You're going to look back
at this, I promise you.
-Yeah.
You're gonna look back
and you're gonna be like,
"Yeah, I was smarter
than I thought I was."
-All right?
-Yeah.
-Thanks, man.
-All right.
-Love you, brother.
-Love you back.
I feel for the kid.
I really do.
He's an extremely smart kid,
but he's got
to sit there
and realize that himself.
But here's the rub.
Jake is the key
to this plan working.
The Reba people tonight--
they're gonna split
on me and Jake.
So, there are votes
that are definitely going
to be cast against myself, but
if me, Emily, Katurah and Jake
go in, vote for Mama J,
she's out.
Once the Reba Four is broken up,
this will
definitely flip the game. This
will turn the game on its head.
Yeah.
So am I.
This whole time I've been trying
to manipulate Bruce,
and I think the only way
he doesn't play his idol is
if he feels comfortable enough
that he's not
the person going home.
This is like a Hail Mary,
but if Bruce does
play his idol,
there is a question mark
about who is going
to be the person voted out,
you know, the backup target,
and Mama J is a massive threat.
I do think,
if you're going to the end
with someone like Mama J,
you just have
to be prepared to lose.
And then
you have Jake on the outs.
Jake has been on
the chopping block for a while
as potentially an easy vote,
and he seems
to be the safer option.
Full moon out tonight.
Things are getting weird.
But I really don't like the idea
of Bruce being here another week
with that idol sitting around.
Everybody agrees.
Now we want Bruce to be gone.
By some miracle,
if he does not play
his idol tonight
and he goes home,
everybody says, "Wow.
Look what Emily pulled off."
-All right.
Something feels different,
or am I crazy?
What's different, Emily?
No, I don't think you're crazy.
I think we've had a couple
Tribal Councils now
where one person
has been wearing a certain kind
of necklace, and now
that necklace is on a different
person. I think the energy
might be a little different
because of that.
Well, that's very direct, Bruce.
-Very much so. That's okay.
So as Emily noted,
first time in a couple
of Tribals,
you don't have the necklace.
-Yeah.
-How is that different
for you today?
It's different for me
because I'm looked at
a heck of a lot harder now
than everybody else.
And I know where I stand with
everyone, so I need to be able
to do the things
that I need to do to...
to ensure
that I'm here another day.
Jake, did you feel
a different energy today?
I felt a different energy today.
I feel like
I have been approached more
than I have
in, like, at least the past
couple days, so that's...
-That's got to feel good.
-Yeah. You know,
not to be the tribe pariah is,
you know,
nicer than being the pariah.
Is that really how you felt,
just because
your name has come up?
Just not being in the know,
not knowing,
not knowing, not knowing.
It's just, that's...
that's tough.
It kind of calls upon,
like, a lot of, like,
insecurity and stuff,
'cause, like, I mean,
everyone has insecurities.
I have a lot of insecurity.
I think, like,
at least with, like, lawyers,
there's a lot
of impostor syndrome out there.
There's always like,
"Am I smart enough?
Am I working hard enough?"
So, when you feel like
you're on the outs,
it weighs a little bit on you.
I'd be lying
if I said it didn't.
Austin, it's hard
to not take it personally
when they write your name down.
It's got to sting a little bit.
Yeah. I mean,
on one hand, you know,
you hate to hurt people
at a personal level,
and you never want to do that.
But on the other hand,
there's a million dollars,
and someone not knowing a piece
of information could be
the difference between getting
that and not getting that.
Sorry. I don't believe
it's a personal thing
from anybody. I just want
to get that out there right now.
I'm not trying
to say it's a personal thing.
But it does play into, like,
"Man, I'm missing stuff, man.
"Things are getting
over my head,
and, like, I just feel dumb."
You know what I mean?
I appreciate you sharing
that because you were not
the first person
to be out of the loop.
-Yeah.
-You're not
the only person tonight
who's probably out of the loop.
You're not dumb.
You're just playing
a very difficult game
where withholding information
is job number one.
Right. I know that,
like, in my head,
but sometimes
the feeling's still hard.
Julie, Jake is saying,
"Huh. You know, I have times
"where I feel like I'm out
of the loop, people are lying.
-I wonder if I'm getting it."
Yes.
On the flip side,
they call you "Mama J."
-They've anointed you
as the mom of this group.
-Yeah.
That's a beautiful gesture until
-it's threatening.
Yeah, but
it's also terrible
for me personally
when you then lie to someone,
um, and I felt terrible
after Kendra.
Like, I can't even look over
at the jury.
:
Um...
Because I feel like
there was an extra bit of,
"No, I trusted you.
You were Mama J."
So then that feels
like an extra burden.
So I'm having my own
crisis of faith,
-just with that name.
But I will say,
there's benefits
to being Mama J, I think.
-There's benefits that...
-I got to go to the sanctuary.
...that Julie has experienced.
This is one
of the drawbacks,
and that's true for anybody.
You know, somebody
that we are close with,
we are going to have
to lie to and vote out,
and it's going to be painful.
So, Drew, when you walked in,
I said
I felt a different energy.
What was it like at camp today?
Was it different
-in terms of the discussions
that went on?
-Absolutely, Jeff.
The merge so far
has been defined by steamrolls.
There was a target, and they
were tied to the train tracks,
and the train came
and, you know, drove over them.
Today the vote is a little bit
more logistical, and I think
it resulted in a little bit
more ambiguity around camp.
Bruce, do you agree
with what Drew said?
Much more complicated today?
Much, much more complicated
today.
You know, you can try
to see through certain words
that people are saying.
Even here now,
when people are talking,
you try to see
through these words.
Is it something that is
meaningful that could either
affect now or later on
in the game?
Katurah, did you feel
the intensity
that Drew spoke about?
It's exactly
as everybody has said.
We see the jury getting bigger,
we feel our numbers
getting smaller,
and the tension is intense.
We also have potential
advantages and idols in play,
and so you're starting
to feel that pressure and think,
"Okay, wow, I got to put my foot
on the gas pedal now
because this game is moving
with or without me."
Big statement, Emily.
Yeah.
And I will say this. When
you get down to eight people,
this is the time
for a move, right?
And I suspect
the power dynamics are going
to shift after tonight's vote.
So, Jake, is that good for you,
or are you just as uncomfortable
as you've ever been?
Look, let's do something.
Like, I'm here.
You want to vote? You want
to sucker punch someone?
Like, let's go.
You know what mean? Like,
that's kind of what the game is.
Like,
-I'm here.
That'll get rid
-of the impostor syndrome.
-Yeah. Right?
Maybe. Fingers crossed, right?
Julie, would you be
a little surprised
if it was you tonight?
I would.
Yeah, based on the conversations
that I've had.
Austin, Katurah mentioned
advantages and idols.
How much talk is there
about if people have them,
if so, who?
Yeah. A ton, and I think,
you know, this Tribal Council,
one's going to be played,
and I'm glad to be safe today.
Julie, you're smiling.
I think one will be played.
Drew,
do you think
one will be played?
-Indubitably, Jeff. Indubitably.
So there's one thing
-you all seem unanimous about.
Yeah, we all do.
Does that mean
everybody knows who has it?
-Brucey. Bruseph.
-Brucey?
So, Bruce.
-Yes, sir.
-There is speculation...
-There is.
...that you have an idol,
and that
-you are going
to play it tonight.
-That is correct.
Whatever I can do
to keep myself safe
in this game--
that's how it's gonna work.
And, Emily, what's interesting
about that is,
that doesn't mean
he's going to play it.
Yeah, that's-that's true, right?
Bruce could not play his idol
if he's confident in whatever
it is that he thinks is going
to happen tonight, but
I would be surprised
if that were to happen.
I think everybody here
would be surprised.
I think Bruce has made
his intentions really clear.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Dee, you're up.
Third try's the charm.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Jake.
Jake.
Two votes Jake.
Jake. Three votes Jake.
Julie.
That's three votes Jake,
one vote Julie.
Bruce.
That's three votes Jake,
one vote Julie,
one vote Bruce.
Bruce. That's three votes
Jake, two votes Bruce,
one vote Julie.
Bruce.
We're tied.
Three votes Jake,
three votes Bruce,
one vote Julie, one vote left.
11th person voted out and
the fourth member of our jury:
Bruce.
Need to bring me your torch.
Good game.
-Aah!
-Good game, old man.
Playing this game
with you guys--
it has been an honor
my second time back.
Honestly, I appreciate you.
-Love you, Bruce.
-I love you back.
Bruce,
-the tribe has spoken.
-Yes, sir.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
At this point,
every move we make is gonna
hurt a lot.
Next time onSurvivor...
I'm ready to take some shots.
Literally, my world
is in Julie's hands.
This could either save me
or destroy me.
Not too bad, huh? It's cute.
I didn't play my idol today
because I was
convinced otherwise.
They-they hatched a good plan.
Um, it made me feel comfortable,
which, kudos to them.
I'll keep smiling,
no matter what, though.
That's what I do.
I had a blast.
It's just been
absolutely amazing,
and I'm very thankful
to have the chance to come back.
I love this game, man.
Truly love this game.