AUSTIN:
I need to be
the first to strike.
I'm turning this
into a full-blown idol.
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
BRUCE:
Boom.
Hidden immunity idol, baby.
In my hand.
This is freaking fantastic.
[laughs]
You are my nu... Come on.
Co-Co-Come.
You are my number one.
KELLIE:
Bruce just follows
me around and, like,
refuses to let me be free.
And at this point,
I would be fine
with blindsiding Bruce.
PROBST:
This is it.
-JAKE: Bruce, Bruce!
-DEE: He's moving.
PROBST:
Julie's out.
Bruce wins individual immunity.
JAKE:
We all know
I'm the backup to Bruce.
We know I'm on the bottom.
KATURAH:
Jake is desperate.
He's not trying to hide it.
Everybody sees it.
DREW:
We can just
take her off the table,
and then the core four
can take charge.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it.
JAKE:
Jeff.
Jake, you are...
...not safe.
Ninth person voted out
and the second member
of our jury: Kellie.
Whoa!
Sorry. Whoa.
What the hell, guys?
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
Cheers, Kel.
Love you, girl.
[Jake laughing]
I was just like, "Wow."
[laughs]
Good. I'm glad you have some,
uh, positive energy.
Oh, yeah, Got to have positive
energy, man. I'm in the game.
How could I not
have positive energy?
Hi.
I'm Jake.
I'm still on Survivor.
[chuckles]
Didn't get voted out tonight.
I was aware that I was
not reading people well,
but I was not aware
how bad I was reading people.
I had
no idea that
that would be Kellie.
I don't even want to say
I was left in the dark.
I wasn't even left
in the same dimension.
But now I have
a brand-new opportunity
to entirely change
the way I've been playing.
Knock on wood.
Jakey's not out of this.
EMILY:
Bruce, how are you feeling?
BRUCE: Um...
JULIE: Yep.
Then somebody
explain it to me so I know.
-She was.
-DREW: Nobody wanted to tell you
because we thought that you guys
were, like, tight with her.
You would tell her and then
she'd turn things against us.
BRUCE:
Listen, uh, this is a game.
This is a part
of what things are.
I'm not gonna be...
I'm just...
I'm not salty against anybody.
At Tribal,
I was extremely shocked.
I had no idea
that the votes were gonna
go down the way that they did.
It's extremely scary to lose
your closest ally in this game.
But then
to find out that Kellie was
trying to,
you know, vote me out--
that was devastating.
So I'm under the understanding
now that I
was a target from Kellie
to try to get out.
DEE:
From what we've been
hearing, Kellie--
she always felt like
she was under your wing.
These are her words, yes.
Like, she kind of felt like
she was on house arrest by you.
I didn't overreact,
but on the inside,
I'm-I'm panicking.
I'm thinking, like, you know,
"What the hell?"
My closest ally is gone.
And it's shocking to hear
that she felt like
I was overbearing.
That sucks.
That's not my personality.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, we said
that in the beginning, and...
-I...
-we meant it.
I mean, I meant it.
Yes.
It's so shocking
to me how hard it is to watch
my literal day one first friend
on Survivorget snuffed.
But then on the other side,
she's no longer a threat
for winning the game,
I probably have a jury vote
from her if I get
to the end of the game,
and my hands are clean.
But now we got to figure out
how to shake the game up
and maybe
get a bigger player out.
Okay. Okay.
Is Dee the biggest threat
on Reba?
A hundred percent.
We're sure we're sure?
-A hundred percent.
-Okay.
KENDRA:
Dee is a beast at challenges.
She's super social.
Dee is very, very likable.
KATURAH: Right now,
it's either go with old Reba
or go with old Belo.
And I've been
with old Belo since day one,
and that clearly
doesn't do anything for me.
So for Reba,
I'm sure that I'm fifth,
but I'm the fifth
that can bring them information
from Belo and help them
knock off Belo people.
Mm. I figured. It's okay.
They're gonna come after us,
for sure.
Well, we do have two idols.
We can defend it
to a certain extent.
With Kellie gone, my amulet,
which started out as just
a three-way shared extra vote,
is now a full idol.
So I have a lot of firepower
to play with right now.
I've got two idols.
It doesn't shock me
that she wants to come after me.
I just didn't know if...
Right.
DREW:
Number one priority
is flushing the idol.
And...
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
-And Kendra needs to go, too.
-AUSTIN: So pretty much,
-we need to win
the next immunity challenge.
-Yep.
AUSTIN:
So right now,
my next step is to make sure
we get rid of Bruce,
who has an idol,
Jake, who is doing whatever
he could to find an idol,
and Kendra, who's now
going after our alliance.
-Aw, we're still
at the same beach.
-I know.
-This is our home.
-This is it.
-We're defending our home.
-Yep.
♪ ♪
BRUCE:
Now I'm in a little bit
of a weird mind space right now.
To find out that Kellie
was trying to,
you know, vote me out.
That's what others you think
were supposed to do, not Kellie.
Now it's becoming scary.
I'm officially
in a spot that I am...
Personally,
I don't know where I am.
KENDRA:
Morning, Brucey.
KATURAH:
Morning, Bruce.
Did you sleep
on the beach, Bruce?
I don't even want to, like,
talk about anything today.
I don't want to do anything.
I don't even
want to be by the fire
with them.
Even Jake.
Last night,
he was over-celebrating
when someone literally is having
a visceral moment
of just sadness.
KENDRA:
Got it.
-DREW: Nice, dude.
-KENDRA: Nice, Jake.
BRUCE:
But what irritates me the most
is that it doesn't make sense.
Kellie was my closest ally,
saying that I was overbearing
for them. Like, that's...
That... that doesn't feel good.
Like, that sucks.
-Oh!
-Yeah!
BRUCE:
And it's weird, because I have
my daughter back home, and
I don't treat them
any different than I treat her.
When I go back home, I'm gonna
ask my wife and my daughter,
"Am I overbearing?
Do you feel as if
I don't allow you to grow?"
Especially to my daughter.
And if she sees me as that way,
then I will make the changes
that are necessary
to make sure that she can live
a different life than what I...
than what I've gone through.
When I started in this world,
I started
in the foster care system.
My life isSurvivor.
My life has
always been that way.
So many kids come
in and out of the house.
You get to know them,
and then they leave.
So you build
a little bit of a thicker skin,
because I've been
through the muck.
In my normal, everyday life,
this doesn't happen to me
very often,
when I have to,
like, dig into my-my own
emotions.
Must be getting soft
in my old age.
[chuckles]
DREW: Bruce is kind of
in a-in a tempestuous place.
Today, he doesn't
want to work around camp.
-Just let them do it.
-JULIE: Ooh.
-I mean, you know what?
Somebody could take a chance.
-Yeah.
DREW:
He's obviously upset.
And I think
a lot of that
comes from the fact that
he's been playing
an imaginary game of Survivor
and now that imaginary
game of Survivor
has come down,
he has two choices.
Either A, confront
the reality of his situation--
which is pretty bleak-- or
reject that reality.
One of them
would be moving forward.
would be holding back an ego.
And for a guy like Bruce,
a lot of times,
it can be difficult to stop,
take a look at the crossroads
and say, "Maybe I went
the wrong direction."
-DREW: Yeah, true.
-EMILY: I know.
I have this alliance with Austin
and Drew, but Drew and Austin
have a very close relationship
with their old Reba tribe,
and Dee and Austin have
been getting especially close.
And I wanted
to broach the subject about
getting her out sooner
rather than later.
It'd be a little bit
of a sign of-of,
"No, our true three
is with you, Emily,
not with somebody else."
So I think you can
get Bruce, Katurah,
Kendra and Jake
to put their votes on--
oh, I hate-- somebody like Dee.
Thing is with Dee
is she's kind of taking
the target
off of everybody right now...
DREW:
I kind of agree.
I still think that flushing
the idol is probably number one.
I agree.
Wow.
The hesitancy
on Austin and Drew's part
to kind of
cut down on
any of those old Reba numbers
definitely has me rethinking
my alliance with them.
I don't want to be
at the bottom
of a five-person alliance.
My-my only thought is if Dee
is in the final three, Dee wins.
-AUSTIN: Yeah.
-That's... Honestly, that's
my 100% thought right now.
-DREW: I agree.
-Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah. Yeah.
AUSTIN:
I completely understand
where she's coming from.
If I were Emily
and I saw my two closest allies
have equally close relationships
with two other players,
I would be terrified as well.
So the key right now
is to make sure
Emily's fears are dwindled down
as low as possible
so that I can continue
working with both sides.
I don't know, honestly,
if I can bring myself
to blindside Dee.
We're just
such good friends out here.
I love talking with her.
I love hanging out with her.
And I'm not ready
to see her go. So I just
need to push it back
a little bit further.
I-I definitely need
to think a little bit.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah.
-But, like, I totally agree.
Yeah. Yeah.
♪ ♪
[excited chatter]
-KATURAH: I knew it.
-KENDRA: Oh, come on.
-Nervous.
-DREW: Hmm.
KATURAH:
Oh, boy.
That's hot.
KATURAH:
Oh...
Oh, what the hell is going on?
Who wants to be with me?
DREW:
The note says we have to
immediately divide into thirds.
Three groups of three.
And so are we gonna do,
like, random picks?
Are we gonna
do just team selections?
I don't want that at all.
Should we try
and make them balanced?
That's what I was...
Okay.
Yeah.
I try and make it
as fair as possible
while maintaining
a numbers advantage for myself.
So I say, "Jake, Dee and myself,
let's pair off."
-Cool.
-All right, let's go, guys.
I mean, we might
be against each other.
We might be against each other,
but whatever this is...
KATURAH:
My head is going
a hundred miles an hour,
because what do those
groups of three mean?
And who do I
really want
in my group of three?
Maybe I want to have
my alliance. Maybe I want
to have my enemies in this
group of three, because Bruce
is a huge target
and we're all working
really hard to get him out.
But I'm on a team
with Austin and Emily.
-Okay. So that means
me, Katurah, Austin.
-KENDRA: I'll go with you guys.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
AUSTIN:
I felt pretty good
about my team,
but I don't feel good
with Julie, Bruce and Kendra.
This is a tricky team,
and if something were to happen
within that group of three,
I think Julie is the one to go.
[chuckles]
It's terrifying,
because we've got the core four,
but Jeff keeps splitting us up.
So now I'm like, "Oh, my gosh.
What if each tribe has
to vote somebody out? I'm out."
So I go running to Austin.
Yeah.
I can give it to you now.
Before we headed out for
the challenge, I felt it was
in our best interest if I placed
one of my idols in Julie's bag,
just in case
anything happened,
to make sure she stayed safe.
JULIE:
I still don't know what this is,
but at least I've got
an immunity idol in my bag. But
I'm like, "What's ahead?"
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Take a look at what
we have in store today.
Day 17, Survivor45.
If you're looking for a break,
you're on the wrong show.
[chuckles]
-Oh.
-Whew.
All right, let's get into it.
So, this morning,
you received tree mail
telling you to divide
into teams of three.
Katurah, how did that go down?
What happened?
KATURAH:
Well, the tree mail
said something about
panic and anxiety.
And immediately,
that's what I felt.
And we tried to figure out
how we would divide ourselves,
and there was
a lot of back and forth,
but I think we ended up doing
what we thought
was the most fair.
Can I see? Why don't you
get into your groups of three,
just so I can see?
All right,
so we have Drew, Jake and Dee.
We got Kendra, Bruce and Julie.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Austin,
Katurah and Emily.
All right, interesting.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
First things first,
Bruce, I'm coming for it.
-KENDRA: Aw.
-[chuckling]
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
Today's challenge
is gonna run in stages.
Here's how it works.
For the first stage,
you're gonna retrieve a disc...
...and use it to balance a ball
as you navigate a balance beam.
Once all three players
are across,
you will race
to dig up three rope rungs.
The first two groups to finish
move on to the next phase.
Last group to finish is out.
No shot at immunity.
For the next stage...
...you will use those rope rungs
to build a rope bridge.
Once each person
is across their bridge,
you'll race to land three balls
on three very small rings.
First group to finish
moves on to the final round.
Losers out.
No shot at immunity.
For the final round,
you are no longer a team.
You will now
compete against each other.
You're gonna have
your arms outstretched
with your fingertips pressed
against two wooden discs.
If at any point a disc drops...
...you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed
a spot in the final eight.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the tenth person voted out and
the third member of our jury.
In addition,
you're playing for a reward.
-Yeah!
-What?!
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Want to know
what you're playing for?
-ALL: Yes!
The group that makes it
to the final stage--
regardless who wins
individual immunity--
the three of you
will go to the sanctuary,
-Oh!
-where good things happen,
and enjoy an afternoon
of rotisserie chicken.
-Oh, my God.
-I like good things.
I like good things.
Good things are good.
PROBST:
Worth playing for?
-Hell yes.
-Yeah, baby.
-PROBST: All right.
Oh, there is one other twist.
-Oh.
-Oh, Jeff.
PROBST:
Back to that panic, Katurah.
Yeah, and anxiety.
Don't forget that part.
-The first group that's out...
-Oh, no.
-all three players
-KATURAH: Oh, no.
will lose their vote...
-You got to be kidding me.
-Whoa!
PROBST:
...at tonight's Tribal Council.
You will take a journey
where you will have a chance
to earn it back.
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
So, Austin, what does that do?
Just the thought that
there could be three votes
not in play tonight?
It puts any plan that anyone had
out the window.
Clearly, big stakes
on day 17 in Survivor45.
Let's get ready and do this.
KATURAH:
All right.
PROBST:
All right, first two groups
to finish move on.
Big stakes on Day 17.
Survivors ready?
Go.
It's Emily, Bruce and Jake
going across
the first balance beam.
-You got to grab a disc
and get to the end.
-KATURAH: There you go.
-AUSTIN: Nice.
-You're good, Blue. Go.
-You got this.
-PROBST: Here goes, Bruce.
You're good, Yellow. Go.
Jake trying
to get across that beam.
You're good, Red. Go.
-Whoa. [grunts]
-PROBST: There goes Katurah.
No, Katurah, back!
-No, no, Katurah.
Back, back, back, back.
-PROBST: Back, Katurah!
Julie struggling. Julie's off.
She's got to go back.
Here's Dee navigating that beam.
You got
to get all the way to the end.
You're good, Dee. Go, Drew.
-DEE: Focus. Just focus.
-JAKE: You got it, Drew.
-Good job.
-AUSTIN: There we go.
-Okay. Sorry, guys.
-PROBST: Katurah
giving it another go.
You're good. Go, Austin.
-BRUCE: Beautiful, beautiful.
-PROBST: Julie's across.
Go, Kendra.
-DEE: Good job. Good job.
-PROBST: Drew, you're good.
Next phase for Red.
BRUCE:
Nice. Come over.
PROBST:
Kendra has hers.
Austin has his disc.
You're good, Austin.
Kendra's good.
You cannot trap that ball,
cannot use your hand.
Got to get across that beam.
Jake gonna struggle. He's
got to go back to that beam.
Austin doing a nice job.
Austin, you're good.
-Let's go, baby!
-Kendra, you're good.
Here goes Katurah for Blue,
Julie for Yellow,
-Jake for Red.
-BRUCE: You got it. Nice job.
PROBST:
Jake has got to get to the end
before anybody else can try.
He's struggling again.
It's not gonna do it.
Jake's gonna
have to go back again.
BRUCE:
Focus, focus.
PROBST:
Katurah doing a nice job.
Katurah, you're good.
-Go, Emily.
-Oh, thank God.
PROBST:
Julie taking her time,
close to the end.
-You're good, Julie. Go, Bruce.
-Yes! Go, baby!
PROBST:
It's now Emily the last person
for Blue. Blue is in the lead.
Yellow on their tail.
Red in dead last.
Jake drops again.
He's got to go back.
Bruce drops.
You're good.
Start digging, Blue.
You're looking for three
rope rungs at four stations.
Jake got
a little momentum this time.
Can he get across?
You're good, Jake. Go, Dee.
Bruce the last person
for Yellow.
Red trying to play catch-up now.
-Yes, yes!
-You're good, Bruce.
Let's go. Let's go.
PROBST:
You're good, Dee. Go, Drew.
DEE:
Let's go. Let's go. You got it.
Yellow can start digging.
Now the pressure is on Drew.
-He's got to go for broke.
-Focus, Drew, focus.
PROBST:
You're looking for three
rope rungs at four stations--
which means
one will not have one.
-Drew doing a nice job.
-Good, Drew.
-You're across.
You're good, Red.
-Let's go, baby.
-We got a challenge.
-Let's go, baby. Let's go.
I got one.
PROBST:
Blue with their first rung.
Uh, one for three.
Oh, that's it?
Red with one rung.
I got the second one.
PROBST:
Blue has a second rope rung.
You're looking for three total.
-Look at that. Dead last.
-Got one here.
Red is in it now
with a second rope rung.
It is Yellow
with nothing right now.
Three people
are gonna lose their votes.
Right now, that looks like
Kendra, Julie and Bruce.
-No way.
-All right, one.
Yellow has one rope rung.
Red looking
for one more rope rung.
-We got it.
Red has it. Get to your mat.
-Go, go, go.
-Red is moving on.
-Drew, Jake and Dee
move on to the next round.
-Yeah, baby!
Oh, my God.
-We're looking for one more.
-[Jake whoops]
JULIE:
Okay, one more.
PROBST:
Yellow has another rope rung.
Now the challenge is on.
Both teams looking
for one more piece of rope.
AUSTIN:
Keep digging. Let's go.
PROBST:
Blue has been
looking for that third
rope rung for a long time.
DEE:
Let's go, guys. Keep going.
PROBST:
It would be
a huge comeback for Yellow,
if they can find
that last rope rung.
-Got it. We got it.
-I got it!
PROBST:
There it is.
Yellow pulls it out.
[groans]
Kendra, Julie and Bruce
moving on.
[breathing sharply]
PROBST:
Emily, Austin and Katurah
come up empty-handed.
Where was it?
PROBST:
After having the lead,
could not find
that third rope rung.
Jake, Drew, Dee moving on.
Julie, Bruce, Kendra moving on.
Emily, Katurah, Austin out.
Vote is gone.
You're gonna have to earn it
on a journey this afternoon.
Let's move on to the next stage.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, time to move on
to the next stage.
For this phase,
you're gonna use your rope rungs
to build a rope bridge
and you must cross it.
Once you're at the other side
and all three people are here,
you're gonna toss balls,
trying to land them
in very small rings.
The first group through
moves on to the final stage.
The losers are out.
No shot at immunity.
Big stakes continue. Here we go.
Survivors ready? Go.
One rung at a time.
You're building a rope bridge,
going from
one side to the other,
crisscrossing every time.
Slowly but surely, everybody
making their way across.
Jake doing a nice job.
Thanks, Jeff.
PROBST:
Drew out there.
There goes Dee stretching.
Bruce finds a nice
comfortable spot on his butt.
There's Kendra.
Julie working it.
You've got to use
every rope rung.
That does not look easy.
PROBST:
Bruce down to his last rope.
-Got to get to the mat.
-[grunting]
PROBST:
Bruce is across.
Good.
PROBST:
Drew's across. Jake is across.
It is coming down to Dee,
-if she can finish
before Julie and Kendra.
-JAKE: There you go, Dee...
BRUCE:
Scoot, scoot, scoot.
-DREW: You got it.
JAKE: There you go.
One more, Dee.
-BRUCE: You're good, you're
good. Beautiful. Nice job...
-PROBST: Julie's across.
-Dee's across.
Red moving on to the balls.
-Let's go.
PROBST:
Jake gonna be up for Red.
Come on.
Kendra dropping ropes now.
She's got to grab 'em.
Nice balance.
-BRUCE: Nice job. Come on...
-Jake trying
to go for that top ball.
Is it gonna stick?
-[groans]
-Off and on.
-DEE: You're good, Jake.
-BRUCE: Perfect.
Come on, Kendra.
PROBST:
Kendra's got the last rope rung.
Got to get to the mat.
You're good, Blue.
Start on the balls.
Bruce in for Blue.
That ball
has got to land just right.
-Takes a lot of touch.
-Oh!
DREW:
So close. So close.
KENDRA:
Let's go, baby.
-Bruce lands
the highest one for Blue.
-BRUCE: Let's go!
PROBST:
Julie now up for Blue.
Drew comes in.
Going for the highest one.
-Drew sticks it.
We are tied one-one.
-Yes!
-Get in there. Get in.
-Oh. Oh, oh...
PROBST:
Julie sticks one for Blue.
Dee now looking to tie it up.
She's going for that bottom one.
There goes Kendra trying to get
that middle one. It's tricky.
You don't want to knock
the ball out that is below it.
Dee sticks a second.
We are tied again.
It has come down
to Jake for Red,
-Oh, careful.
-Kendra for Blue.
Kendra almost
knocks the ball out again.
-That's twice.
-There.
-Here goes Jake.
-Oh!
Sits on that ring, but drops.
[cheering]
Kendra does it for Blue.
Let's go!
PROBST:
Blue pulls it out.
Sanctuary visit
for Julie, Bruce and Kendra.
-And they will move on
to the final round.
-EMILY: Good effort, guys.
We will reset
-and get to an individual
immunity challenge.
-Good job, guys.
EMILY:
Good job, guys.
Awesome job.
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
All right, we have
Julie, Bruce and Kendra
ready for this final stage.
And this challenge is on.
♪ ♪
Your arms
are fully outstretched.
You have just your fingertips
holding on to a wooden disc.
If that disc drops, you are out.
You're gonna celebrate together
at the sanctuary,
but only one of you
will have this necklace.
Complicated game.
You helped each other
get to this phase,
and now you're
competing against each other,
'cause you want
to be safe tonight.
♪ ♪
Very, very, very hot spot
in Fiji.
Bruce with a little slip.
That's how fast it can happen.
We've only done
this challenge two times.
It has never been won by a man.
Wow.
PROBST:
Bruce with another slip
and another good catch.
Trying to readjust now.
♪ ♪
Kendra with a bit of a wobble.
When you start to feel that,
just get it back.
Push that energy right back
out through your fingertips.
Lock back in on those discs.
You have all learned
since you've been out here
that you do
have more in the tank.
You just don't
call on it as often.
Kendra wobbling again.
One disc starting to slip.
A nice recovery.
Arms are shaking.
You don't know when
somebody else is gonna drop.
They could be
seconds away from being out.
You hang in
until your arms go numb.
Kendra now wobbling again.
Nice recovery.
Moving those discs back up.
Bruce looking down.
"Is she gonna drop?"
[chuckles]
PROBST:
"Can I have another
showdown with Julie?"
You take your eyes
off the prize in this challenge,
that wooden disc will drop.
Kendra fighting to stay in it.
And another
nice recovery from Kendra.
-Look at that.
-Keep pushing, guys.
That's how you do it
on Survivor.
[spectators exclaiming]
-PROBST: Kendra once again
fighting to stay in it.
-JAKE: Come on, Kendra.
Fight, kid. Come on.
-Push.
-Keep digging, Kendra.
Kendra hanging literally
by the edge of her disc
-as she does it again.
-KATURAH: There you go.
-There you go, Kendra.
-JAKE: Good job. Come on.
-Come on, Mama J.
-PROBST: Julie now struggling
at the other end.
Bruce looking down,
not showing anything.
JAKE:
You got it, Kendra.
PROBST:
Kendra on the edge.
Another nice save by Kendra.
Body completely distorted.
Look at her arms.
Trying to hang in there.
Kendra drops. She's out.
We're down to two.
-Kendra, take a spot
on the bench.
-Good effort, Kendra.
PROBST:
No shot at immunity.
We got another showdown.
Just like last time.
It is Julie versus Bruce.
Bruce won last time.
It would be Bruce's
second individual immunity win.
It would be Julie's first.
Julie starting to struggle.
Nice recovery.
You want to get to day 18.
You want to get to eight.
Keep digging.
Julie slips again.
She's gonna have
to get that disc back up.
Barely holding on.
Bruce fighting to stay in it.
-[groans]
-PROBST: Julie drops.
-Bruce wins his second
individual immunity in a row.
-[applause]
Guaranteed a spot
in the final eight.
Cannot be
voted out of this game.
Wow.
KATURAH:
Good job, guys.
Bruce, come on over.
-KATURAH: Yeah.
-[applause]
JAKE:
Good job, Bruce.
Second time in a row.
Individual immunity.
Once again safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Cannot be
voted out of this game.
-Good job, Bruce.
-Good job.
-Thanks, guys. I appreciate it.
Julie, Kendra, Bruce--
even though you just competed
against each other,
if there's a consolation prize,
-you're gonna go
celebrate at the sanctuary.
-Yeah. That's a big one.
Some nice chicken.
Grab your stuff, head out,
enjoy your afternoon.
-You will return to camp
in time for Tribal Council.
-Good job, guys.
Thanks, Jeff.
That was fun.
[chuckles]
-Drew.
-PROBST: All right,
Drew, Jake, Dee--
no sanctuary,
but you retain your vote.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Bye, guys.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
Emily, how does this potentially
change the game, knowing
that you, Katurah and Austin,
as of now, don't have a vote?
What does that do for everybody
else who's scrambling now?
Yeah, right now,
four is the majority,
so everybody
who just walked off is,
in their head,
doing the calculus.
"Okay, let's operate
under the assumptions,
"these three don't have a vote.
Who am I working with
to get four tonight?"
And, uh, the pressure's
really gonna be on us
to earn our votes back.
Otherwise, I think it's fair
to say, all of our names
are on the chopping block.
PROBST:
All right, Emily,
Katurah, Austin,
here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna leave here,
take a journey.
You will have a chance
to earn your vote back
and you will be back at camp
in time for Tribal Council.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at Tribal.
[groans]
KATURAH:
I feel like everything has just
hit me like a ton of bricks.
Bruce has now got his second
immunity win in a row.
I don't have a vote.
I'm going into a journey
that I've been hearing
terrible things about,
and add icing to the cake,
I don't get chicken.
[laughs]
That's my life today.
♪ ♪
JAKE: Yeah.
That... that freaking sucked.
-DEE: Yeah.
-DREW: Ugh!
Bruce winning
another immunity is tough.
He has that idol which
he's hanging onto,
like, viciously, greedily,
and we can't flush it.
-Didn't lose our vote, at least.
-DREW: Yeah.
-JAKE: Yeah.
DREW:
Could have been a lot worse.
On the other hand,
if you come back to camp, not go
into the sanctuary,
not go into the journey,
you're in the middle ground,
and so you have some nice time
to relax, to nourish yourself.
-You want to eat some rice?
-Hell, yeah. Rice.
-JAKE: Sure.
DREW:
But also, you can't really
begin strategizing
because you're waiting for that
power group at the Sanctuary
to come back with their plan.
DEE: Yeah, they got rotisserie
chickens, and then we got
-three extra scoops
for ourselves, baby.
-DREW: Yeah.
-JAKE: We got
a little extra ourselves.
-Absolutely.
DREW:
And then you're also
waiting to find out
what votes
will be available to you
from the people on the journey.
DREW: Yes.
I think there's a potential
for all of them to get it.
I think there's a potential for
all of them to lose it. Like...
-Yeah, or maybe
just one have it, either, even.
-Yeah.
So there could be six votes
or nine.
-Yeah.
-Wow.
DREW:
So, it's all up in the air.
You're kind of
in this uncomfortable,
like, puberty middle zone
where you got to wait for one
of the outcomes to happen.
How are you feeling after,
uh, having the shock wear off
about last night?
I mean, obviously, I'm wicked
happy to still be in the game.
-You know what I mean?
-DEE: Yeah.
-Yeah. Yeah.
I just got to figure out
what I do moving forward.
-DREW: Yeah. Where to...
-Kind of like...
I mean, I'm basically
a free agent right now,
and I don't think
that's a secret.
-DREW: That's a thought, yeah.
-DEE: Yeah.
I'm here. I don't want
to, like, force anything.
I don't want to, like, freak out
like I did yesterday.
Prior to the last Tribal,
my alliance was supposed
to be original Belo members,
but original Belo
voted for me.
So, if things stay the same,
I'm still on the bottom,
and my game plan right now is
to build the trust with people
that I haven't really
worked with before.
If there's any way I can build
trust with you guys, just
-let me know.
I'm open to conversing.
-Yup.
So right now, I'm trying
to learn from my mistakes.
Kind of a tough thing
to do mid-game,
but this is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity,
so I have to do it now.
I don't like to think that
my foot has come off the gas
at all, but
I'm turning the high beams on.
-Oh, that's ready.
It's still kind of hot, but...
-DREW: Yeah.
Me too.
Yeah. Exactly, yeah, yeah.
-You're at our mercy. [laughs]
-Yeah.
I swear, Austin better get
his damn vote...
-Oh, for real.
-'cause that's gonna be...
We're gonna probably have
to play an idol for sure.
Yeah, um, if we do,
I think that we should play
the idols on you and Austin.
Yeah, we'll wait.
We'll wait to see, yeah.
-For sure.
-'Cause they're definitely
gonna come
-for me and Austin
for sure, yeah.
-Yeah, I think so.
And then
if we're in the majority,
who would you want to take out?
-Kendra.
-Okay, I think the same thing.
DEE:
The fact that Kendra did not win
made my entire year.
DEE: She got to go
'cause she's stirring up the pot
and she's putting my name
out there.
So, yeah, okay, Kendra,
get some rotisserie chicken,
but you're gonna be eating more
of that soon
when you're out of this game.
[laughs]
I definitely am full on rice.
That was good.
Oh, yeah,
you ate the whole thing.
-Did I really?
-Yeah.
-Are you kidding me?
-[laughs]
DREW:
Oh, my God. I ate it all.
But we have some put aside
for him, don't we?
-DEE [laughing]: No, I didn't.
-Oh, my God.
-This is all.
-I thought we had some put aside
for the guy.
DEE:
I'm chilling right now.
There's nothing else
for me to do.
I'm just gonna
be mentally prepared
for when everyone
starts rushing back to camp.
We got some rice for you.
Some of it burned.
-It was inedible.
-It was inedible, yeah.
-DREW: A lot of
the burned stuff got tossed.
-Oh, no worries.
DEE:
We did not get
some rotisserie chicken.
All done yet?
DEE:
But we got a ton of rice that
Jake didn't eat because we ate
more than he thinks we ate.
-Appreciate it. Oh, wow.
-Yeah.
KENDRA: Oh. Oh.
That is just one
big ol' chicken.
JULIE:
Oh, look at that
roasted chicken.
Thank you, Jeff!
Oh... my God.
I have not eaten chicken
for 15 years,
and chickens
are my favorite animal!
But I'm about
to eat you right now.
-Oh.
-Sweet little chicken.
Thank you for
giving us your...
-This is for you.
-energy.
BRUCE:
There it is-- the most beautiful
rotisserie chicken just
begging to be feasted upon.
No utensils whatsoever.
And I just start
devouring this thing.
KENDRA:
Oh!
-Yes!
-JULIE: There you go.
Cheers, you guys.
-Cheers.
-Great win today.
-Absolutely. Oh.
-Awesome job.
BRUCE:
I got grease and gristle
and a chicken wing
all over my hand, and
that is a stark contrast
in regards to this morning.
It just revived the reason
why I'm here.
I'm playing this game
for my family,
and I couldn't leave
my negative space this morning.
I just couldn't get out of it.
But sitting there, you know,
with this big ol' drumstick
and immunity
and a hidden immunity idol,
and knowing
that I'm safe tonight
made it so much...
made the chicken taste
so much better.
Mmm. That's really good.
It's really good.
I'm really nervous
about tonight.
-So...
-JULIE: So what are y'all
thinking? Like, what...
How do y'all see the end?
What is next for y'all?
How are you
with your Reba people?
Um, I just feel like I'm on
the bottom of the Reba people
and I got to make a move
at some point.
KENDRA:
Who do you think is at the top
of the Reba people?
-I don't know.
-I'm kind of nervous
-about the Austin-Dee thing.
-What do you think?
-Ooh. Maybe.
-I think
they're, like, secretly in love.
Which I love, and I want them
to get married after. [laughs]
-BRUCE: Mm-hmm.
-JULIE: I mean,
-Dee's my girl, but...
-KENDRA: Yeah.
-I hear what you're saying.
JULIE:
I know Kendra wants Dee out.
She just wears it.
All of her emotion.
It's obvious.
But I do not want Dee out.
I want to go
to the end with Dee.
I would never write her name.
Oh, my gosh.
Uh, here's-here's what
I would like to also propose.
Okay. Yeah, okay.
I would love
to write Jake's name again.
Dee thinks Kendra's got to go,
but I would like
to see Jake go out next.
I am fine with the easy votes
right now. Plus,
he wrote my name down.
Like, he obviously doesn't want
to work with me.
Listen, if you want Jake...
-KENDRA: We want Jake.
-Then you got...
you'll get Jake.
BRUCE:
I'll tell you this.
Tribal lines are gone
because this game is fluid,
it has to keep moving,
and Jake has no footing
with anyone now.
I'm not going down
with the ship, so,
if Julie wants to vote Jake,
then that's fine.
I'm okay with Jake going
because he is unpredictable.
Yeah.
KENDRA:
Julie throws out Jake,
and to my surprise,
Bruce agrees with Julie.
And in the moment, I'm like,
"Okay, anyone but me."
I'm just wondering who's gonna
get their vote back.
Yeah.
KENDRA:
The three people who
lost their vote-- we don't know
if they have their vote,
so we kind of have
to get a name,
which maybe only six people
are gonna be voting for.
And so, Jake kind of seems
like a easy target.
He doesn't have
a Shot in the Dark.
We know he doesn't have an idol.
Let's send him home.
So, us three are on Jake?
-Until you tell me different.
-Perfect.
JULIE:
If I can believe
Bruce and Kendra
that we all write Jake,
that's music to my ears.
That's best case scenario
for me.
I just don't see it
going that easy.
-Oh, boy.
-Okay.
-AUSTIN: All right.
-Let's do it.
EMILY:
The vote inSurvivor--
it's everything.
It's your life inSurvivor.
If you don't have a vote,
you're totally useless
to everybody here, so,
if there's any opportunity
to get your vote back, you need
to do everything in your power
to get your vote back.
The only thing that's going
on in my head is, "Don't choke,
"don't choke, don't choke.
"Just finish the journey,
"complete whatever
you need to complete
and get your vote back."
AUSTIN: My mind is racing,
and I'm hoping,
I'm just hoping
it's something in my wheelhouse.
I really don't want
to leave it to chance.
-Okay.
-KATURAH: Good luck, guys.
Yup, good luck.
Basically, the note says,
"You need to solve
"this logic math problem
in order to get your vote back."
And in my mind, I'm like, "Okay,
this actually kind of is
in my wheelhouse."
Oh, boy.
All right, let's see.
Basically, it's nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four, three,
two, one equals 100.
And you have to place
three plus signs
and one minus sign
in order
to make that equation equal 100.
But there's so many
different combinations.
Where do I even begin?
♪ ♪
And with
the time ticking,
it's stressful.
I am freaking out.
[mumbling]
KATURAH:
It literally is,
at its core, just
a basic math problem.
I can add to 100.
That's an easy, round number.
Sure. But we have three minutes
to complete the entire equation.
Plus, the fact
that you don't know
how the numbers
should be combined
or subtracted
or added together.
That's what makes it difficult.
Ugh! Okay.
EMILY:
Immediately, I...
the panic strikes me,
because if there's one thing I'm
terrible at, it's mental math.
My mind just
goes black.
There's a conception
that because
I'm an investment analyst, that
I'm gonna be able
to crunch numbers
in my head really quickly.
I've never been capable of it.
In fact, it's always been
a struggle of mine.
My hands are physically
shaking from the nerves.
It's like my mind
can't function.
AUSTIN:
Math is something
that I'm kind of strong with.
You might not be able
to tell by looking at me.
I might just look like
this surfer, brawny dude,
but I also don't look
like a typical MBA student.
And this is gonna be
a mental task that I feel like I
have a good shot at completing.
Okay, we're close. We're close.
So I start plugging in pluses
and minuses, and didn't work,
didn't work,
didn't work, didn't work.
I'm running out of time,
running out of time.
KATURAH:
I have seven or eight
digits completed,
and there's only three left.
And I am like, "Just zone in.
"Just get these last three,
figure out how they go,
and you'll be good."
But I'm looking at the time.
Oh, Lord.
And then, I switched from kind
of being methodical to saying,
"Holy crap,
the time's running out."
And then
I kind of had brain freeze.
Ugh!
So close!
This means
I really don't have a vote.
Got it, got it, got it,
got it, got it. Okay, okay.
Minus 76.
I have, like, 15 seconds left.
I quickly
scribble in the pluses,
the minuses equals 100.
Hundred. [sighs]
So, I open up the answer,
and I check it.
Let's go!
All my plus and minuses
checked out.
And I am freaking out.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
Ah. I didn't want to get
made fun of by all my MBA
friends for screwing that up.
EMILY:
When I look at the solution,
I mean, I wasn't even close.
I write something random in
'cause I'm running out of time.
Honestly, it's mortifying.
I... Afterwards,
I just wanted to curl up
into a little ball and die.
I'm embarrassed to call myself
an investment analyst right now
that I didn't get this,
and I have
to reap the consequences now,
which is I don't
get a vote tonight.
This is absolutely
one of the worst times
in the game for me
to lose my vote,
because if I had my vote
right now,
I could be the person who is
making the decision about
who is best to go for my game.
But I-I robbed myself
of that today
when I failed
to solve a math problem.
Survivorcan be a brutal game,
bring you lower
than you ever want to go.
But if you want a life-changing
adventure, this is it.
Apply to be on Survivor.
JAKE: Do you want to talk, like,
-long-term? Yeah, yeah.
-Endgame? Yeah.
Like, who...
We got to wait and see
who lost their vote, what the...
-what the competition's
gonna be.
-I know. Yeah.
'Cause it could be...
It literally could be, like,
a six-person vote tonight.
I know. That's the crazy part.
I do feel in danger.
I always got to believe
there's a possibility
that I can go next,
especially
after the vote last night.
-What do you think?
-You think there's any world
that doesn't involve
getting me out?
-Uh, yeah, I think
there's a lot of worlds.
-Yeah.
That could mean Katurah,
it could mean Kendra.
I feel like your threat level
is pretty low right now.
Whatever you come up with,
man, like,
-I can be an assistance,
but I'm open to anything.
-Yeah.
JAKE:
I'm trying to make people
feel comfortable
around me and feel like
they can use me.
I do got to act a little bit
like a dog out here. You know?
"What do you want from me?
What do you want from me?
"You want to cook?
You need some space, whatever?"
But... I think
that's the move right now.
-Honestly, like,
between me and you, I think...
-Really?
I actually have
a similar thought.
DREW:
You think that's them?
Yeah, probably.
♪ ♪
They look so good when
they're coming in.
-DREW: Yeah. Wow.
-DEE: Right? Yeah!
-Sexy tribemates.
-[Dee whoops]
EMILY: I'm feeling not great
about my position in this game
coming back to camp.
Welcome home.
EMILY:
It's the first time in a while
that I've really felt
on the outs and like
I'm not doing anything right.
It feels like
my old days back at Lulu.
Well, journeys aren't fun.
It turns out they suck.
Um, it was basically
just a big math problem.
I mean, long story short,
none of us have a vote.
-Yeah, and...
-I wasn't even close.
Just pure panic.
It was an absolutely
miserable experience.
It was just awful.
We're sorry that we couldn't
pull it out for you guys.
We know that it sucks
to have three people
with no vote,
and I really did try.
-DREW: Don't worry at all.
-Right.
AUSTIN:
My lie of not having a vote
was because
I don't want everybody
to know Reba has the numbers.
But I always come clean
to my alliance of four.
And I think that's
really the reason
why we've been so strong
throughout the game is because
they know I'm gonna
tell them the truth.
Y'all really think
I'm gonna let us go
-into Tribal
in a three-three deadlock, baby?
-Of course not.
-You got it?
-I have it.
-[Dee laughs]
-DREW: Oh, my God.
DEE: Austin has his vote,
which is so freakin' awesome,
because without his vote,
we would not
have the numbers tonight.
Yeah, I'm kind of smart.
I'm kind of smart.
I know. Look at you. What?
-Yeah.
-You, me, Julie, Drew.
Yeah.
DEE:
So now, there's seven people
who are eligible to vote,
and obviously,
the four of us
are gonna vote together.
And I know that Kendra's
coming for me, so right now
that I have the numbers,
I have to take Kendra out.
Okay.
Well, Kendra was like,
"Well, I want Dee."
I said... I said,
"I'm gonna be honest with you.
I won't write Dee."
-Yeah.
-I said, "Can I write Jake?"
And then Bruce goes,
"Well, I'm fine with Jake."
And Kendra was like,
"I'm fine with Jake."
-So we will have them think
it's Jake then.
-And?
And we go and vote Kendra out.
JULIE: At the sanctuary
with Kendra and Bruce,
we all agreed on Jake,
and Dee's like,
"Kendra's got to go."
I'm annoyed because I'm like,
"Okay, I'm working
Bruce and Kendra
to get Jake out," so,
it doesn't align with my game.
But what
they really want is Jake.
-We want Kendra.
-Yeah.
I don't know about Kendra.
So, Dee's got
her own personal agenda
and I've got mine,
and I don't know how
that's gonna play out yet.
-So, yeah, we... like...
-Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
The plan is still Jake,
as far as I know, but
it seems easier
than it should be.
I think they're gonna...
-And then throw my name.
-Okay.
KENDRA:
And I'm having an extremely
hard time with that
because last night seemed easier
than it should be,
and I got blindsided.
-How are you doing?
-I'm doing okay.
-Um...
-Yeah.
Me, Mama and Bruce
decided on Jake...
-Okay, awesome.
-when we were eating together.
Thank you for letting...
Oh, okay.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Thank you for letting me know.
-Yeah.
-But I think you're right.
I think
it has to be Jake tonight.
-Me too.
-So, yeah.
There's no other option.
Sorry, Jake.
KENDRA:
But Emily reassures me
she feels the same way,
and that's where the vote
is going tonight, so...
Okay, I just need
to not be paranoid.
Sound like everybody's
doing Jake.
Wait, really? I thought
we wanted to do Kendra?
-Really?
-Yes.
That's the first
I'm hearing about it.
But why Kendra?
She's 100% a vote for us.
Yeah. Talk to me
about how you came
-to the Kendra conclusion
and with whom.
-Uh...
Okay.
EMILY:
The old Reba now is
potentially throwing out
Kendra's name as somebody
who they think
that they can't trust.
I hate hearing
Kendra's name.
I understand
that she can be
a little bit of a wild card,
but there are so many other
people that are, in my opinion,
bigger threats, less likely
to work with me in this game.
I think Jake is more loyal
to Bruce than Kendra is.
Jake doesn't have
his Shot in the Dark.
We all tried
to send him home earlier.
Easy, in and out.
Yeah.
I feel totally powerless
because I have no vote
to offer, which is
kind of scary when you're not
the one in control.
In the game of Survivor,
you always want
to be the one
making the decisions.
This is suddenly seeming more
complicated than it needs to be.
-Really?
-But... Yeah, a little bit.
I'm in a little bit of
a compromised situation because
I have my alliance with Emily,
and Emily wants Jake
out of here.
Help me.
Yeah. I... I want to...
-We haven't had a catch-up.
All right.
-Yeah.
I could change the vote to Jake.
Jake is erratic.
He's a sunken ship. He's got
a hole in his broadside.
And you feel bad for the guy,
but nobody wants
to go and help him.
DREW:
I know Austin
would be willing to do it,
and Julie, of course,
would happily agree.
I think that everyone else
is gonna pile on Jake.
Hmm.
I'm not 100.
I already know
everybody wants Jake out,
which seems like
such an easy vote.
But I don't want that.
She's trying to get me out.
I need to do
what's best for my game,
and right now
I want Kendra out
and that's what
I'm gonna push for.
♪ ♪
DEE:
I know that the four of us
have to work together,
so right now,
we need to make sure
that we're good and make sure
that we're on the same page.
But in this game,
whoever throws out my name,
I'm gonna come for them.
I'm gonna come for them hard.
♪ ♪
[chuckles] Hi, Dad.
-[laughing]
-DEE: It feels like
-you're just gonna ask us,
"How are you feeling?"
-Yeah.
DEE:
But we're not feeling too great.
We're at Tribal Council.
You think that's
what I was gonna ask?
Probably.
"How are you feeling today?"
I think you were gonna say,
"All right."
That is my go-to, isn't it?
-All right.
-[laughing]
So, I've seen
every single Tribal Council,
and I've seen
some amazing blindsides,
but I'm pretty sure
last Tribal's
blindside of Kellie
will go down on a lot of lists
as one of the most devastating
and surprising.
Kendra, you were
-visibly upset.
-KENDRA: Yeah. That's something
I did not expect
coming into this game.
Like, I am emotional person,
I wear my heart on my sleeve,
but it is a game.
And just looking
at my first friend...
Literally, Kellie is
my first friend here
on Survivor,like, literally.
And that was so much harder
than I ever expected it to feel.
PROBST:
And Dee, was there
also the feeling
that, "Wow, the game is on.
Because if that happened
-to Kellie,
it could be me next time"?
-DEE: Yeah.
You come into this game,
and everyone wants
to make a big move,
everyone wants to do blindside
and you're watching it on TV
and it's super cool.
But when you're out here,
we're not robots.
Like, we're playing with humans
and their feelings.
It's tough.
It's a lot tougher here
than what you see on TV,
and I don't think
anyone will ever understand that
unless you're playing Survivor.
PROBST:
Jake, how about for you?
What was that feeling
when you saw
your name come up,
come up, come up, and then
you saw Kellie's name?
What was happening emotionally?
Honestly, I was prepared
to see my name,
so I kind of already mentally
steeled myself to see it.
But when I saw Kellie's name
come up, I was floored.
There-there was relief,
but it was also like,
that's not a spot
that you want to be in.
Obviously,
I'm at the bottom, Jeff.
So, does a blindside
of that magnitude
shift the game simply because
it is like an earthquake,
-JAKE: Yeah.
-and now the earth
is not the same out here?
I'm-I'm hoping that
it did shift the game because
I'm trying to catch up
as fast as I can,
you know, because
I made a lot of mistakes.
Fortunately, I didn't get
voted out last night,
so I do have the opportunity
to correct those mistakes,
and hopefully
make it beyond this Tribal
right here tonight, Jeff.
PROBST:
All right, let's get into
today's events.
A lot went down.
It was a three-stage challenge,
but once again, we had
another battle
between Bruce and Julie,
two of the older players
in the game.
They have dominated
the last two challenges.
So, Julie, I realize it would
feel better if you had won,
but it was
very competitive again.
So, I hope
I've made my kids proud.
-You have.
-That's my number one.
But other than that, I forget
that I'm not one
of these young'uns,
and so, I'm kind of like,
"All right,
I'm doing great
and I'm the oldest."
So there is that, and yes...
[groans] Yeah, it would
be better if I'd beaten him.
That... [groans]
PROBST:
Bruce, how about for you?
Back-to-back wins
in any season for any player
is a big deal.
Not a good thing,
but it's a big deal.
Wait, wait.
Let's examine that answer.
[laughing]
PROBST:
"Not a good thing."
Why don't you solve that dilemma
by taking that necklace off
and putting it on someone else
-and burden them with it?
-JULIE: I'll take it.
Why are you speaking
blasphemy right now? No, no, no.
Um, I-I say that because
it's one of those things.
You know, you want to be able to
protect yourself in this game.
Like, immunity is huge,
but it paints, also,
a big target on your back.
I want to hear them
cheering for me. I do. Like,
"Go ahead, Bruce! You can
do it!" You know, like, "Yay!"
But no.
People are gonna be like,
"Damn it, dude, just pass out
"so somebody else could win.
Just get the hell
out of the way."
Drew, it is a tricky thing.
When you win, you're safe,
but you show everybody else,
"I could win again."
Yeah, absolutely. And, you know,
to Bruce's credit,
people don't just see
the two immunity wins.
People see the hours of hard
work and practice and training
that is both
physical and mental.
But with the necklace, it's like
a sword of Damocles situation
where there is the reminder
that eventually,
there will be a moment where
you don't have the necklace.
And all of those wins
will build up
into a bigger and bigger target.
Okay, there was
one more twist today,
which was the first
group of three
that finished last
lost their vote
and had to go
on a journey
to try to earn their vote back.
So, Drew, three people
lose their vote.
That we know.
Then three people
go on a journey
and come back and say
they didn't get their vote back.
-That we don't know.
-DREW: We don't.
Typically, when you go
into a Tribal Council, you know
how many votes they're gonna be.
This twist adds a complication
where, suddenly,
it's not clear if you're voting
with six people,
seven people, eight people,
nine people.
And that's really scary because
it throws off any possible
voting calculation from
a strategic standpoint,
and you have to default instead
to your relationships
with these people
-in hopes
that they're being honest.
-PROBST: Kendra,
what's your reaction to that?
Because you seem to have one.
Honestly, my reaction
is right now is
did y'all really
lose your votes, or...
-No.
-Okay. Sorry. I was...
With what Drew was saying,
it was like, "Wait,
did three people
lose their votes, or..."
Well, I mean, that's just
the strategic implication,
-the twist, you know.
-I didn't even think about that.
-Anyways...
-PROBST: Wait, wait. Kendra,
You didn't think
about the fact that what?
So-Somebody could be lying.
[laughs]
You know, Jeff,
I ate my first chicken today
for the first time in 15 years.
I think my mind's working
a little differently
and, I don't know,
it got a little bit
of meat sweats today.
PROBST:
Dee, it sounds like
these missing votes
-are going to play
a big part tonight.
-DEE: Yeah, Jeff.
We're at a point in the game
where, like,
things cross your mind, and then
you don't know if it's paranoia,
but you don't know
if it's the truth.
And as players, I feel like
we're evolving. Like, you know,
as a Pokémon, you evolve
into, like, Charizard.
I feel like that's
what the new era is.
It's like an evolution.
And now with three less votes--
if they did lose their votes--
players are more strategic,
and they are thinking
a little bit more,
like, evil-ish, you know?
PROBST:
Kendra, if these
three votes are gone,
does it help your game tonight
or hurt it?
KENDRA:
It's really hard to say, Jeff.
Last night was a big...
Like, the curtains
are wide open.
The show is on.
Like, we are moving on
to act two.
And so, I am not sure
I was included
on these, like, bigger-picture
conversations
that could be happening.
PROBST:
Jake, does the potential loss
of three votes
help you or hurt you?
Um, I think it helps me more
than hurts me,
but the game is changing,
and I'm behind.
I need to catch up right now.
I need some friends out here.
I mean,
I'm trying to, like,
build relationships with, like,
different people and, like,
let them know that
I'm a free agent out here.
You can use me.
I'm looking for a home.
Let me in.
All right, it is time to vote.
Bruce, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Jake.
Kendra.
One vote Jake, one vote Kendra.
Two votes Kendra, one vote Jake.
Kendra.
Three votes Kendra,
one vote Jake.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member
of our jury: Kendra.
That's four. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Kendra, the tribe has spoken.
Love you, Ken.
Time for you to go.
-JULIE: Love you, Kendra.
-KATURAH: Bye.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
...we cannot miss.
BRUCE:
Once the Reba four is broken up,
this'll turn the game
on its head.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
This is such a sick,
twisted, delicious,
enjoyable, terrifying game.
JAKE:
You are not a gift
from God. Relax.
He thinks he's a big Boston
mobster. Dude, you're a goon.
I just got blindsided, and...
Ugh! I'm just bummed at myself
for not following my gut,
even though I'm a gut player.
Clearly, the stars
weren't aligned.
And I don't even care
that I'm starving.
I don't even care
that it's raining.
Like, I love feeling alive
and free
and having an adventure, so
this is the greatest adventure
I've ever had, and I'm
so grateful for the opportunity.
[roars]