[babbling, grunting]
[hisses, screeches]
[hissing]
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
What I have for an advantage
is essentially done.
He's literally instructing us
on how to play the game.
So a little contradictory.
DREW:
Myself, Julie, Austin and Dee.
This is gonna
be the solid group.
-So...
-Do y'all want amulets?
-I'm down with that, too.
AUSTIN:
They're gonna get my revenge
for getting in between
me and that friggin' sandwich.
I think we have Emily
in a good spot.
EMILY:
There's been lobbying
from both Belo and Reba.
The pressure is on
to make the right decision.
Fifth person voted out
of Survivor 45...
Brando.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
KENDRA: We survived.
DREW: We did.
Yeah.
No, for sure.
-EMILY: I'm sorry.
-No hard feelings.
KENDRA: No, it's all good.
No.
Like, I want
to work with you guys.
EMILY:
I'm feeling good.
I voted with Drew and Austin
to get rid of Brando, because
that's the first time
in this game
that I felt like I was
being brought in on a team
as opposed to just being
manipulated or dragged along.
But my heart
goes out for Kendra.
She took it very kindly.
I expected her
to be a bit more upset.
No hard feelings.
Like, my biggest hope
is that we can, us four,
can, like, come into this game
and, like, really, really,
really, like, ... up.
-[laughs]
-Yeah, totally.
-Totally.
KENDRA: I seem cool, calm,
collected. But really,
I'm devastated.
I was blindsided.
This is messed up.
Emily flipped on me. And so
I want to get revenge on Emily.
I don't want you to feel like
I don't trust you
-at all.
-Yeah.
-Please don't read this as you--
-"Oh, you're on the bottom."
That's not what it is at all.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
-At all.
KENDRA:
There's this little petty part
that lives inside me
that I can't use
in my day-to-day life
because I live in karma.
But Survivorseems
like the perfect place
to let this
little, petty Kendra out,
and I'm coming for them.
[laughing]
♪ ♪
I'm 99% sure
this is exactly where
Sabiyah found her first idol.
Saying we search this area now.
We can also split up
and do left and right later.
You know what I mean?
BRUCE:
Is that a leaf?
Oh, that looked
like a piece of parchment.
KALEB:
Since the swap,
I've been building some goodwill
with these people.
Now my number one focus
is to find the idol.
But if I can't have the idol,
I'd rather know who has it.
So I want the rest
of my tribe to also be looking.
JAKE:
Ooh, there's a snake over here.
-KELLIE: Really?
-Yeah.
-KELLIE: Where?
-It's right here.
Hidden immunity idols.
Like, what the hell?
Where are they? I mean,
I'm running into snakes.
I've taken so many spiderwebs
right to the face,
which is disgusting.
JAKE:
Just be careful. When we
were looking earlier, Bruce,
there were snakes
in these trees.
Hey.
Uncle Bruce.
-We have something.
-KALEB: Totally.
-Now...
-Let's find out what it is.
-Doesn't say "Beware." [gasps]
-What-what is it?
We do it right now. Open it.
BRUCE:
When I see "Beware," at this
point in time, I don't care.
I don't.
I'm just happy
that I found, you know,
potentially,
a hidden immunity idol.
I just now lost my vote. I...
That's-that's in there.
Boop. I lost my vote.
I got to try like the dickens
to find this idol.
-Ready?
-JAKE: Run.
-Let's go. Go, Bruce.
-[chuckles]
BRUCE:
It's up for grabs.
So I took off running.
Took off running.
[trilling]
[laughs]
We get back to camp,
and Katurah's not there.
Perfect.
In this game, I'm not
seeing eye to eye with Katurah.
Our relationship is fractured.
So I want Katurah
to be left out.
And I just start digging
in the middle of the shelter.
I'm doggy-paddling through it.
I'm back of my hand,
front of my hand.
I'm moving dirt as much
as possible, and I can't find
a thing.
Kellie, she's my lookout.
When is Katurah coming back?
Then all of a sudden, like,
"Oh, no, she's coming."
[Katurah scoffs]
How's things over here?
-KATURAH: Oh.
-BRUCE: All that's on my mind
is "How the hell
can we get her out of here
so I can start digging again
to find this damn idol?"
[whoops]
Ready for today.
JAKE:
Little halt on the plan
right there.
And if Bruce can't find it,
he doesn't have a vote,
he's a sitting duck.
So I have to help him out.
In Survivor,
you got to get creative.
You got to think
of different strategies.
Dude, I lost
one of my rings, man.
-BRUCE: What?
-I lost one of my rings, bro.
I give Kaleb a wink right away.
He knows what I'm doing.
And then, you know,
I give Bruce a wink right away.
He knows what I'm doing.
Dude, it's got to, it's got
to be in here somewhere, dude.
My ring is a decoy, and
we don't want to tell Katurah
because we've been trying
to vote her out a little bit.
And I got to put on
the performance of a lifetime.
I'm looking for my rings,
and I'm so upset.
I'm cursing to the high heavens
of how upset I am.
Damn it!
Sorry, Nana.
KATURAH: Oh, my God.
Kaleb, there's a boat.
-[whoops]
-KELLIE: Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
-Oh, my God. There's a boat.
-Oh, there's a boat.
-DREW: Oh, my God.
-[Austin whoops]
Oh, my God, you guys.
-Yeehaw!
-AUSTIN: We frigging made it!
KENDRA:
I don't know.
I don't want to guess anything.
DREW:
It's happening!
"It's day 12,
and the game is about to change.
-Drop your Buffs."
-[cheering]
"You have ten minutes
to collect your things
and a boat is waiting
to take you to your new home."
Let's go!
[cheering, whooping]
"Drop your Buffs.
Your fellow castaways
will be joining you soon."
-SIFU: Here?
-[screaming]
We have to get ready!
We got to get ready!
-Get ready, get ready...
-[laughs]
Do you guys want to do,
like, a little welcome
on the beach with our fingers?
Like, "W..."
DEE: No.
J. MAYA: Coming into the merge,
this promise of, like,
fresh blood in the game
this morning--
I can't even tell you how
excited I am.
To get to this place
in the game,
I feel like
is a huge triumph for me.
And if this adventure
was a song,
I would say that
everything up until this point
has been the verse.
You know, storytelling,
building the scene, exposition.
And the chorus is coming.
It's gonna be big,
and it's gonna be a hit.
♪ ♪
"You have ten minutes
to collect your things.
A boat is waiting
to take you to your new home."
-[screaming, cheering]
-Yes, baby! Yes, baby!
BRUCE:
"Drop your Buff.
You're going to a new home."
Holy crap.
We're gonna be leaving soon.
So, clock's ticking,
and now my heart's racing,
knowing that
I don't have a vote.
So I'm looking at the center,
where it could very well be,
and then
I put a straight line down...
Boom. There it is.
Sweet Caroline.
[laughs]
Seconds before
leaving this beach.
Ah! I have a hidden immunity
idol, baby, in my hand.
This is friggin' fantastic.
The idol is huge.
Me being a celebrity,
quote, unquote, that was on TV,
I'm on a high list of people
that need to get voted off.
I told Kellie, Kaleb and Jake.
They're solid with me, 100%.
-Hey, stock the boat and
let's get the hell out of here.
-[excited chatter]
Toodle-oo, Lulu!
BRUCE:
I'm smiling, I'm laughing.
I mean, I have fun,
but I'm most excited about
blowing somebody's game up.
That's what this is gonna do.
♪ ♪
[cheering]
DEE:
Oh, my God.
-Wow.
-[Sifu laughs]
[whooping]
[cheering, whooping]
SIFU: Yeah, we made it!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
-Let's go!
-[Dee whoops]
DEE:
The first thing
I was looking at was,
"Are Drew and Austin
on that boat?"
And they were waving.
We're like, "Oh, thank God."
-We made the merge!
-♪ We made the merge♪
♪ We made the merge...♪
DEE:
This is perfect. I still
have my four-strong alliance.
So, Mama Julie and I
are still extremely close.
Then Drew and Austin,
like, they're
the people that I trust
the most in this game.
I'll put anybody's name
out there except theirs.
-SIFU: Bro. We did it.
We did it.
-[excited chatter]
[screaming]
[exclaiming]
KALEB:
I can't believe
I made it to this beach.
I don't know what's crazier,
being here
or being here with Emily
as my number one ally.
EMILY: What's up?
I have some apologizing to do.
KALEB:
I can't believe that
Emily made it this far.
She was so bad
to start the game,
but I can see
she's really come into her own.
-Should we go see
what we're working with?
-Let's go check it out...
KALEB:
She is an ally that
I can truly trust in
to be able to navigate
the rest of this game
when we're the only two people
on Lulu left.
And hopefully
we get to be the swing votes
that are pulled
into either Belo or Reba.
-We have
a surprise for everyone.
-Oh, yeah.
KENDRA: What?
[cheering]
And we got a big-ass fish, man.
-[excited chatter]
-So, like, there's enough.
There's a lot to eat.
DREW:
If you haven't eaten, I think...
KENDRA: I am so hungry. I start
absolutely losing my mind.
Like, I'm freaking out.
I'm fully freaking out.
[screaming]
[others screaming]
-[breathing heavily]
-KATURAH: Ah!
-It's fish!
-[laughing]
Let's go.
DREW:
Oh.
[laughing]
KENDRA:
Besides all the fish,
this is a big moment right here.
We finally
get to be at the beach
with everyone left in the game
for the first time.
I'm so happy to,
like, meet everyone,
just to, like, be at this point.
KENDRA:
But it's a lot coming in here.
Everyone's overwhelmed.
Everyone's trying to,
like, meet each other.
I'm trying to find my footing.
Luckily, my people know
that I'm an old
"Belo strong" person.
So,
I'm already close with Jake.
I'm already close with Katurah.
I'm already close with Kellie.
Me and Bruce are cool.
It starts raining,
we're screwed.
So let's get to work
and get some stuff done.
-That's Bruce Brucin'.
-[laughing]
KENDRA:
So I'm just
connecting with old Belo
and giving them information.
Information
is huge in this game.
Emily flipped on me and voted
Brando out with the boys.
So she's playing the game,
which is good.
It's good to know.
EMILY:
I think my position right now
is relatively precarious.
Day one, I called Bruce out.
I didn't think twice
about the comments I made.
Um, these comments have
taken on a life of their own,
almost pitted Bruce and I
against each other.
There was the conversation that
we had at the marooning, right?
EMILY:
Yes. I...
For what it's worth,
I-I... at my job a lot,
but in general, I love to play
devil's advocate a little bit.
-You don't need to apologize.
-Thank you.
I'm dead serious,
like, it's just...
I-I look at this as the game.
This is the game.
What you were saying
made sense to you.
-That's what you wanted to say.
-Exactly.
BRUCE: She apologized.
On the surface, I'm like,
"Oh, my God, you're so fine.
Everything is good."
Underneath, I'm like,
"I'm-a get you.
Your time's coming."
So what happened
last night with Brando?
Yeah.
So Brando was a tough vote.
Um, I'm sorry. I know
that you guys were close.
I think both Bruce
and I can move forward.
But just because
we can move forward
from the comments on the barge
doesn't mean we can
move forward in an alliance.
You know, we hug and we move on,
but in the game ofSurvivor,
it's about understanding
if we can trust one
another moving forward,
and we don't hold grudges.
There was an option
to choose food or strategy.
-I wanted food so friggin' bad.
I was going for food.
-Yeah, we figured...
And J. was the one
who wanted strategy the most.
-Really?
-Basically
we each have an amulet.
Ever since losing
that sandwich at the journey,
I've been just wanting revenge.
Like, I wanted
only those sandwiches
and nothing else in this world.
But J. was adamant
on these amulets.
I need people to know
that I'm pissed at those two,
that I want
them two out. If they're out,
it's better for me
and I finally get revenge
on losing my sandwiches.
The only issue is
it can upgrade.
So if one of
the three gets voted out,
it gets turned
into a Steal a Vote.
-Then if there's one left,
-DEE: How can we flush that out?
-Uh-huh.
-then it's a full idol.
Not only do I have
my amulet in my pocket,
I have an idol that expires
after this first Tribal Council
unless
I sacrifice my vote again.
[whispers]: Okay. Run!
I would like
to sacrifice my vote,
but in order to do that,
we need to bring in the numbers,
and we need
to find a common enemy
that people
are willing to vote out.
Okay, at what point
are we getting J. out?
DEE:
Dude, she needs to go.
For me, it's J. For sure.
-Me too.
-It has to be J.
-J. first?
J. could be a good option,
because we can get
Belo on board.
We can get Reba on board.
-We can get Lulu on board.
-DEE: Yeah.
JULIE: It should be so simple
that Reba has six,
but I think
that we're not six strong.
I think that
J. has been on the bottom,
and J. is gonna
cut us the minute she can.
-We are.
-Yes. Yeah.
Absolutely.
DREW: This is a core four. So,
I'm in a good position
right now, because
I like to be in charge.
I like to be the leader.
And we have the numbers
to kind of whittle down
some of our first targets
in the merge.
We could just squash them.
KENDRA:
Oh, look
at that little stick bug.
Hello.
Aw.
Like, I want
to get going right now.
I don't want this, like,
this, like, meet and greet.
You know, pretend like we're all
buddy-buddy. We're all chums.
[beatboxing]
DEE:
♪ We made the merge♪
♪ Merge♪
-♪ We made the merge♪
-OTHERS: Hey! Hey!
-Hey! Hey!
-♪ We made the merge.♪
[singing continues in distance]
DREW:
Everyone's laughing,
but I'm thinking
we've entered
a new stage of the game,
and it's time to elevate
yourself to that new stage.
♪ We made the merge.♪
-Hey.
-[excited chatter]
KENDRA:
We are so easily entertained.
45 seasons in
and still going strong.
Want to be part
of the adventure?
Apply to be on Survivor.
[thunder rumbling]
♪ ♪
This is coming down.
Yep.
What a merge day, eh?
Rain, please stop.
SIFU:
[whoops] Yeah.
[laughs]
-This is what
we're here for, baby.
-[chuckles]
I like this.
Bring us some more rain.
-AUSTIN: Easy.
-Ah!
I love the rain.
People probably think I'm psycho
for that, but I'm over here,
"Ah! Let's go, rain!"
Screaming at the top
of my lungs. I just love
the adversity that it brings.
You don't like
getting rained on?
-EMILY: Definitely not.
-Um...
I like getting rained on
-if I know I have a place that's
warm and dry to go back to.
-[laughs]
EMILY:
Yeah.
The beginning part of my game
was about having fun,
but now it's crazy with
friggin' 13 people
at your camp. This is
psychological warfare,
where we're
getting to know each other.
[screaming]
"Oh, I'm super nice.
You're super nice.
We're lovey-dovey
and all this stuff.
And then someone comes up
silently behind you, and...
[grunts]
No, I didn't do...
-[gasps] [laughing]
-I'm just messing with you guys.
We're just
talking about Tribal.
Or they're like,
"I have some information."
And that's what we want to know.
I see divisions
on the Reba tribe
that I didn't necessarily
see on the old Belo tribe.
-Uh-huh.
-And so I was like,
I think that gives us
a better shot to...
-Exactly.
-Yeah.
100%. I trust you.
I... Me too.
I know
Emily is somebody
who's trustworthy to me.
So that makes her the most
valuable person to me right now.
And Emily's
already in with Reba.
She's already
worked with them on a vote.
And I've been
with Belo since the swap.
So, there's a lot
of opportunity for us
to get information
and play both sides,
hopefully without
getting caught in the middle.
-Reba doesn't
care about the lines.
-Yeah.
But then it's, like,
who do we pick off?
-Do you know what I mean?
-Oh, yeah.
I just don't know how close
things are at Reba, still.
AUSTIN:
Things have been
getting fractured.
This last Tribal Council,
both Sifu and Dee's
name came up.
At this point,
I'm in Belo's ear.
-You know what I mean?
-Okay, good.
And so I can hopefully
use that to help
-kind of triangulate what...
what's going on.
-EMILY: Okay.
KALEB:
My focus at this point
is to present
the most trustworthy
and likable version of Kaleb.
So I'm selling myself,
and what I want people to see
is not this monster
who's coming to destroy
all the players in the game--
which is true, by the way.
-Know what I mean?
-Mm-hmm.
KALEB:
I've been able to work
the whole group. We're vibing.
I might look like the golden
retriever on the outside,
but they should
never let me in their home.
Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Um...
Physically good?
-All you have to do
is win, then. Yeah.
-Yeah.
No pressure.
BRUCE:
Nobody's talking to me.
Nobody's having
a conversation with me.
Nobody's talking
strategy with me.
No one's having even
a-a personal, one-on-one
relationship conversation
with me.
Am I, like, a pariah,
at this point in time?
Someone that's
kind of just lurking around
and, you know,
not a part of what's going on.
Nobody's, like,
nobody's talked to you?
-No. I have not
had a single convers...
-Besides, like, to Belo?
Not even to Belo.
-So...
-Oh...
What's Kaleb doing?
He is trying to run this
using his slickness.
I'm seeing Kaleb,
literally, floating around
around between everybody.
And I'm standing there like
the last kid being picked
for a game in the playground,
twiddling my thumbs,
waiting for someone to come
talk to me and... nothing.
What do you mean?
Belo. Why haven't we
gotten together and talked yet?
I think people are nervous
to talk right now.
But that's the thing--
like, what-what...
Maybe your leadership will be,
you know,
enough to wrangle people.
'Cause Kaleb's doing it. He's
bouncing around to everybody.
Yeah.
BRUCE:
If we're running a race,
the starting gun goes off,
Reba's ahead.
Belo hasn't even started.
We're going around in circles.
Kaleb is masterminding this,
and we are losing.
Belo is losing.
For that fact.
-Okay?
-All right.
BRUCE:
My game plan was
to sit back and just chill.
Well, now I got
to shift gears a little bit.
Nobody's talking to me.
Not a single soul
is talking to me.
-I had no conversation.
-We're completely open with you.
-Dude...
-You are powerful right now.
You just might not realize it.
-Yeah.
-I can't take my leadership role
that I had over on Belo
and bring it here and say,
"Let's all get together."
I can't do that here now because
everybody doesn't want to talk.
It leaves Belo
in a bad situation,
puts you in a great situation.
You get to walk around
and talk to whoever it is
that you want to,
because it's just you and Emily.
KALEB:
Bruce is mad at me
for having conversations
with people who aren't Belo.
It was like
I was a guy
who got pulled over by a cop,
getting shaken down
for every piece of information
and telling me how wrong I was,
when I didn't even do anything.
If you want the original Belo
to do their thing
together with you, then
you have to seriously
do some damage control.
-Okay.
-And that's gonna help me,
it's gonna help you,
it's gonna help Belo,
and we're gonna go from there.
We're gonna pull one person in.
KALEB:
He has a very archaic way
of looking at the game.
He wants us
to not talk to the enemy.
And I think that's the stupidest
thing ever, you know?
I appreciate what you're saying.
Please, obviously keep it,
as much as you can, on the low.
-Oh, of course.
-Now I'm gonna try and just...
Who would I talk to?
Nobody's talking to me.
So we're good, dude.
[chuckles] 100%.
KALEB:
If Bruce doesn't trust me,
I don't trust Bruce.
It's that simple.
Yeah. He's, like,
not happy with you.
Basically saying you're
talking to too many people.
Which it's, like,
what am I supposed to do?
I know. I know.
He was like,
"You're not hearing me.
Like, we have
to be Belo strong."
I'm like, "What? What are
we gonna tell the other side?"
-He's like, "It doesn't matter."
-Yes, it does.
I know. But that's, like...
-He's impossible to play with.
-I know.
KELLIE:
Bruce I have been working
with this whole game,
but he's a liability
to play with.
It seems like he really,
truly cannot help himself.
And everyone on Belo is annoyed
with him. He has an idol,
which makes him scary.
I'm, like, so done with him.
I'm gonna be honest.
He's really pissing me off.
KALEB:
I think he'll be so confident.
It'll be the perfect time
to do something.
KELLIE:
I'm over Bruce.
I'm tired of him
trying to tell me what to do
or anyone what to do.
At this point, I would be fine
with blindsiding Bruce
and getting him out of the game.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
-KATURAH: Hi, Jeff.
-SIFU: Hey.
Good day.
Shall we get to it?
-Yes.
-Absolutely.
-Let's do it.
All right, first things first.
Got to take back tribal idols.
Thank you, Kendra.
Thank you, Sifu.
Tribal immunity is no more.
But there is
no individual immunity yet,
because you have not
made the individual phase.
So, Jake, how do you view
that state of limbo?
I mean, I think
everyone's meeting new people.
Everyone's trying
to get their ducks in a row,
and you show up, and there's
13 damn fine ducks over here.
So... [chuckles]
It's, like, what do you do?
PROBST:
Katurah, given that
you are literally
in between stages,
what's the key,
from a game point of view,
for the individual player?
I think the key right now
is to make
as many connections as possible,
since we literally have no idea
what's gonna happen, Jeff.
-[chuckling]
-You know,
we're terrified out here.
PROBST:
Shall we get to it?
-Yeah.
-Let's do it.
For today's challenge,
you will be randomly divided
into two groups of six.
On my go,
one player at a time will crawl
under a muddy net to a cart.
Once everybody's at the cart,
you'll push the cart
across the field,
collecting very heavy
sandbags along the way.
You're then gonna
use those sandbags
to get to the top of a tower.
Once everybody's at the top,
you'll retrieve a set of keys,
slide down the other side.
♪ ♪
You must then work together
to get to the top
of a very big boulder.
Once you're at the top,
two players will use those keys
to unlock the pieces and solve
the first part of your puzzle.
Then two more players
will solve the second.
-Oh, my God.
-KATURAH: Oh, my God, Jeff.
-What are you doing to us, Jeff?
-What's going on, Jeff?
PROBST:
The first team
to finish this challenge
earns their merge Buff...
Ooh.
...the merge meal and immunity
at tonight's Tribal Council.
Losing tribe,
somebody will go home
and fall one day short of making
the next phase of this game.
Clearly, we're
gonna have one extra person
with 13 people here.
So whoever draws
the rock that has no color,
you won't participate
in the challenge.
Instead, you'll put your money
on one of the two teams
and live or die with them.
-Sound good?
-[groans]
-Yep.
-PROBST: All right.
Let's draw for teams.
-I'm nervous, man.
-PROBST: All right, take one.
Don't look at it.
I love to share
in this excitement.
-[Drew exhales]
-[Kaleb whoops]
PROBST:
Game is turning right here
with every hand
that goes in the bag.
♪ ♪
Let's see what we got.
Everybody reveal.
If you are blue, head to Blue.
If you're red, head to Red.
-No.
-PROBST: And
if you have no color,
-get in between the two mats.
-Good night, Katurah.
Katurah, what a reaction.
Whoa.
-We got it.
-Here we go, guys.
-[whoops]
-All right, squad, let's roll.
PROBST:
All right, let's
look at our two teams
in the biggest challenge
so far in Survivor45.
Wearing red,
it is Kaleb, J., Jake,
Dee, Emily and Kellie.
Wearing blue, Sifu, Drew, Bruce,
Austin, Julie and Kendra.
Drew, what do
you like about your group?
And if you have a concern,
what is it?
So, one of the things
I love about this group
is the physicality. I mean,
we have probably some of the
strongest people in the game.
Uh, but that being said,
there's, like,
a two-part puzzle down the line.
Puzzles in Survivor
are the great equalizer.
PROBST:
Kellie, same question.
I mean, obviously,
there's a bunch
of big dudes over there.
But I've never
been afraid of big dudes.
[laughing]
These are, I think,
interesting groups,
and it's gonna be a real doozy
for Katurah to pick one.
All right,
who are you going with, Katurah?
I am terrified,
but I am going to go with...
...Blue.
All right. You're gonna
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize,
and we will get it on.
Biggest challenge of the season.
-Let's go.
-Beast mode.
PROBST:
All right, here we go.
To earn your spot in the merge.
Survivors ready?
[whispers]:
Go, let's go, let's go!
-Go! It's Kaleb and Sifu...
-JAKE: Here we go, Kaleb.
Here we go.
...into the mud first.
That's how you have to do it.
You have to attack it.
That rope is heavy.
That's your resistance.
Sifu's out.
You're good, Blue.
-Go, go.
-Go.
Kaleb's out. Go, Red.
Here comes Austin and Jake now.
Still pretty even right now.
Austin using his head
to get some clearance.
Austin gonna get out first.
Go, Blue.
KALEB:
You're right there, Jake...
PROBST:
Here goes Bruce.
-Go, Bruce!
-KALEB: You're
right there, Jake.
You're right there,
you're right there.
KATURAH:
Let's go, Blue.
-Go, Red!
-KATURAH: Let's go, baby.
-PROBST: Here comes Dee.
-You got it.
Bruce working his way through.
JAKE:
Here we go, Dee. Here we go.
You're good, Blue.
Here goes Drew.
Let's go, Blue.
JAKE:
Here we go.
Go, Red.
Here comes Kellie.
Right here, right here.
My voice, my voice.
Go, Blue.
Here goes Kendra.
KATURAH:
Let's go, Kendra.
Go, Red.
Here comes J.
-SIFU: Push, right now.
-AUSTIN: There you go...
PROBST:
Kendra's through.
Here goes Julie,
the last person for Blue.
J. is really
struggling for Red.
-KALEB: It's all right.
-[overlapping shouting]
PROBST:
That rope has
a lot of resistance.
-KELLIE: You got to get lower.
-She cannot get through it.
Julie now passes J.
-Blue, you're good.
-Come on. Let's go.
Blue is moving on
to the next stage.
They're at the cart.
That's it, Sifu.
-Right here, right here.
-All right, sandbag.
PROBST:
All the bags
in the center section.
This is
a turning point right now,
because Blue is in the lead,
and J. continues to struggle.
She's got to get to the mat.
Go!
Here goes Emily,
the last person for Red.
BRUCE:
One, two, three. Hard push.
-Hard push.
-Watch your legs.
PROBST:
Blue is on the move.
They've got
their first set of sandbags.
Blue extending their lead.
Get to the mat.
JAKE:
Let's go.
You're good, Red.
Red now at the cart phase.
-AUSTIN: Push.
-JULIE: We got it.
PROBST:
Whatever it takes
to get momentum with that cart.
Kaleb's gonna try
to pull it a little.
JULIE:
Go, go, go.
Blue continues to move ahead.
These bags are heavy.
Kellie trying to do one herself.
-JAKE: Oh, yeah, baby.
-That's how much they weigh.
[grunts loudly]
Let's go, Blue. Let's go.
PROBST:
This last section's so heavy,
but Blue has got it.
-Into the cart. All the way.
-KATURAH: Yes! Yes, Blue, yes!
PROBST:
You're good.
KENDRA:
Okay.
Those last sandbags now
are strategic.
You're gonna use them
to build a pile
-to help you get up
to the top of the tower.
-KENDRA: Pile it up.
-JAKE: Go!
-[straining]
PROBST:
Here goes Red. Can they do it?
They're over one.
Get that momentum.
-JAKE: Keep going! Go!
-PROBST: They're over two.
-Wow. Nice work by Red.
-JAKE: Yeah, baby!
PROBST:
Small tribe in stature,
clearly big in effort.
KATURAH:
Don't give up that lead!
PROBST:
It is Blue, still with
a sizable lead.
Now you got to work together
to get to the top of the tower.
Everybody's
got to get to the top
before
you can release your keys.
[grunting]
PROBST:
Red has closed the lead.
They are gaining on Blue now.
Blue, one by one,
moving up
to the top of the tower.
-Yes.
-BRUCE: Come on, baby.
PROBST:
Austin last to the top. Good!
You can untie your bag of keys.
AUSTIN:
What order? Who's up first?
-JAKE: Go!
-PROBST: Red has all their bags.
One more big push.
-Let's go, let's go, let's go!
-Go.
PROBST:
Here goes Sifu,
down with the keys.
-On his butt.
-[grunting]
Look at that. That's
how you do it on Survivor!
[whoops]
-Organize them.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Let's go, Red.
Keep digging.
-DEE: I'll help over here.
I got wedgied myself. Ugh.
Drew, you're good.
Here comes Austin.
-Blue extending the lead again.
-KATURAH: There we go.
PROBST:
Well done, Blue.
Everybody to the globe.
-Let's go.
-You are amazing.
Get a couple up,
and then we'll get Sifu.
PROBST:
Still got a two-part puzzle
left to solve.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-One, two, three, up.
PROBST:
That mud makes it so difficult.
-Next one.
-DEE: Guys, we got it.
They're still
getting up the ball.
-We got it, okay?
-PROBST: If you want
to get to the merge,
you got to dig in right here.
[grunting]
Kendra now pulling Sifu.
He's up.
A lot of teamwork with people
you're competing against.
Right now, hold your life
in the game in their hands,
or in this case, their foot.
Austin hanging on
through the slippery mud.
-Yes!
-PROBST: Nice job by Blue.
I think Austin
and I are gonna go first.
KELLIE:
Okay. You're good. Go.
There's Kaleb. Let's go.
Untie the keys.
Let's go. We got to go, go, go.
PROBST: You're good, Red.
Here goes Jake.
[groans, grunts]
PROBST:
He takes a big tumble.
Aah!
-Through the piles.
-PROBST: Drew and Austin
with a huge time advantage on
this first part of the puzzle.
BRUCE:
Piece this together, guys.
We got to do everything
together.
[overlapping chatter]
Ow!
PROBST:
Kellie took a big hit.
JAKE:
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm good.
You're good, Red. Hit the globe.
-KELLIE: Who's going up first?
-Me.
-Everybody got to get up.
-[indistinct chatter]
You are still in this, Red,
but you got to move.
[grunting]
KALEB:
You got it?
Beautiful work right there.
PROBST:
It is Drew and Austin
with a big puzzle to solve.
This is part one.
It will indicate
what part two is
when you get there.
-BRUCE: Okay, okay.
-AUSTIN: Okay.
KELLIE:
You got it. You got it, baby.
Let's go.
PROBST:
Red has made up
a ton of time right here.
Kaleb digging.
Kaleb's up for Red!
Let's go, Red, to the puzzle.
You're on the platform now.
-DEE: Stay calm, okay?
-PROBST: Now Jake
and Kellie doing
part one for Red. Could
they make up the time here?
-Yup, yup, yup.
-PROBST: Katurah
put all of her faith in Blue.
Right now, Blue is in the lead.
Drew with another piece.
-Come on, guys.
-DREW: Austin
with another piece.
-All right.
-Blue thinks they have it,
and they do.
Next two moving on
to the next puzzle.
It is now Julie and Kendra
trying to solve the rebus puzzle
that Drew and Austin
just put together.
What is the phrase
you're looking for now?
JULIE:
All right, guys, you got it.
Get your puzzle!
Hey, move that one.
PROBST: This is it.
Winners move on to the merge,
will have a merge meal
and get that Buff,
immunity at tonight's
Tribal Council.
Kendra ripping
through it quickly
with another piece and another.
She thinks she knows the phrase.
Red is gonna have
to get something going fast.
Jake, this one. This one.
Jake, this one.
DREW:
Wait. "Safe."
PROBST: Kendra gonna take pieces
out, start again.
-The door is open for Red.
-DREW: Safely.
PROBST:
You got to keep digging.
-Come on, come on, come on.
-PROBST: Red with another piece.
Kellie hefting another piece.
Julie and Kendra are gonna
try something different.
-Okay.
-PROBST: Say it.
-And you are.
-[yelling]
Katurah picked the right six.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
They will move on
and enjoy it with a merge meal.
Different result
at the other end.
Big effort, came up short.
Somebody going home tonight.
No food, no Buff, no security.
-Blue, congratulations.
-KENDRA: Thank you so much.
Here are your Buffs.
Katurah, here's yours.
Open it up and put 'em on.
-You earned 'em.
-KENDRA: Yes.
Sifu, Bruce, Kendra,
Drew, Julie,
Katurah and Austin, you have
successfully transitioned
into the next phase of the game.
You are now part
of the merged tribe.
It's awesome.
PROBST: All right,
here's what's gonna happen.
Tonight at Tribal Council,
you can't be voted out.
You will still cast a vote
and decide who goes home.
This afternoon, you're gonna
head to the sanctuary,
where good things happen.
Your first real proper food
in 13 days.
Well earned.
On the other end,
look at the difference,
these faces.
Kaleb, what do you do
in a situation like this,
where there isn't anything
to do other than accept it?
Yeah, I'm actually
weirdly at peace.
We lost, and it sucks.
But I've been losing a lot out
here, as well, along with Emily.
We fought as hard as we could,
and so, we go back,
and we play the game.
-That's all you can do
at this point.
-PROBST: All right,
Kaleb, J., Jake, Kellie, Emily,
and Dee,
you're gonna go back to camp,
try to figure out
what you need to do
to make sure it's not you
who is the sixth person
voted out of Survivor45.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
-Good effort, guys.
-You guys rock.
-PROBST: All right,
-head out,
head to the sanctuary.
-[yelling]
-Yes!
-PROBST:
Enjoy your well-earned meal.
You rock, man.
-Yourock.
You literally just rocked it.
-[Sifu laughs]
Yeah.
JULIE: I feel terrible
that six are starving
and not safe, but
being safe tonight... is huge.
If you do the numbers,
the seven at the feast
can decide who goes home.
Who's gonna risk
throwing out a name?
KENDRA: To making the merge,
Survivor45, let's get it!
[whooping]
[shouting]:
Blue.
-[whooping, cheering]
-Let's go!
KATURAH:
We're eating for the first time
in 13 days. What the hell?
DREW: The challenge today
was the singular
most important challenge
in this game, because not only
do you win a Buff, you have
made the merge, officially,
and you are then
awarded a feast.
-Oh, my God. Butter.
-KENDRA: I friggin' love butter.
-I would make love to it.
-[laughs]
DREW:
That food empowered me
physically and strategically,
because when you go
to that merge feast,
everyone's guard
is on the floor.
-Ah. [whoops]
-KATURAH: Yeah.
DREW: Everyone wants
to talk to one another.
Everyone is open
to working with another.
We all know we're safe.
None of us can be targets.
We should talk a little bit
about the vote tonight.
Open the floor.
What do you got?
SIFU:
I will put this out there.
J. is top of my list right now.
KATURAH:
J.? Okay.
DREW:
There is no love
for J. here, and
I think I would be fine
with that decision.
So y'all don't have, like,
a deep connection to J.?
JULIE:
She wrote Sifu's name down.
KATURAH:
Oh, really?
I think she's literally
just trying to slither up
and trying
to cut people's throats.
JULIE: Sifu thinks
that J. wrote his name down,
so he's, for sure,
ready to let her go.
What he doesn't know is
that Dee wrote his name down.
But I'm fine
with J. going home tonight,
because I do feel like she'd
cut me if she had the chance.
Here's just a thought.
Kaleb and Emily are the only two
left from Lulu, right?
-AUSTIN: Yeah.
-KENDRA: In my mind,
Kaleb is a dangerous player,
and from the beginning,
I've had my eye on him.
That's just where I stand.
KATURAH:
The only thing I'm thinking is
Emily is kind of
not connected to Reba,
not really connected to Belo.
She's a safe vote in the middle.
He's a threat in this game.
Like, he's talking to everyone.
Like, he's great at challenges.
Yes. I've seen a lot
of gameplay by Kaleb.
Being, like, social,
Kaleb, you know, it's time.
KENDRA:
I 100% agree with you.
-Really? Okay.
-SIFU: He's a player.
I thought all Belo
is working with Kaleb.
So why the heck are Kendra
and Bruce over there saying,
"Oh, yeah, Kaleb's got to go"?
I like the guy,
but I see it. I see it.
KATURAH:
We like him. We trust him.
We want him.
He's a clear number for us.
So I don't want
to get rid of Kaleb.
They're just
blowing up the whole game.
Their strategy is all messed up.
-[whooping]
-KATURAH: Happy merge, baby!
EMILY:
Oh, my God. I am so disgusting!
KALEB:
Yeah. You got dirt
on your, like, neck and stuff.
KELLIE:
Oh, my God.
JAKE:
That immunity challenge
was tough, man.
That kicked my ass.
I am freaking out.
I haven't been
to Tribal yet, so,
if I could describe the feeling
right now in one utterance,
it's, "Aah!" [laughs]
No. You got
to teach me your ways, man.
-You survived
a couple of these.
-Yeah.
-I need to take some lessons.
JAKE:
Yeah, I'm scared.
I need to save my ass tonight.
I'm gonna be here tomorrow, J.
I want you to be here tomorrow.
-You know what I mean?
-I want you to be...
I want us both
to be here tomorrow.
-Yeah, yeah.
-And so,
I think a Lulu
should go home tonight.
It's either Emily or Kaleb.
I-I do like Kaleb.
-Kaleb, would...
-I like him a lot,
but he's a physical threat.
-He is.
-He's a social threat.
Physical, social. Yeah.
No, he is.
J. MAYA:
Kaleb has been
the smile-iest guy onSurvivor.
He's working really hard
to charm everyone
that he speaks to.
That kind of puts you
on high alert.
So I bring up
Kaleb's name,
because in my head,
I think that
he's a good, safe vote.
-I think it's good to project
Reba strong right now.
-Yeah.
Because people are scared of us.
-And they should be.
Obviously, I do know that my
Reba Tribemates have my back.
We have the numbers on Reba, so,
that's how tonight's gonna go.
If you had to choose someone,
who would you choose?
My trepidation--
and, like, I don't know
-if you feel the same way--
is throwing out a name.
-Yeah.
Can't give all, like,
the cards away, and, like,
-I know you get that, you know?
-Right, right. Okay, look,
I'm a bit more open,
I think, than you are.
I'll tell you the name
that I want.
-Okay.
-J.
-Like, I'm, like,
shocked by that, but, um...
-Yeah.
-I know,
'cause it's Reba, but...
-What you...
What you tell me to do,
I'm down with, man.
DEE:
Voting off J.--
it's not gonna burn bridges
between Reba, Belo and Lulu,
and J. wasn't really part of
our Reba alliance
with the four of us.
So, sorry, J., but
whatever. It's gonna be over,
and we're gonna
forgive each other.
I wouldn't mind
writing her name down.
KALEB:
I'm a little bit surprised.
-Yeah.
-'Cause I just thought, like,
it sounded like
the girls were so close.
I mean,
she'll be surprised, too.
-Yeah.
-Dee told me she wants J. gone.
-KELLIE: What?
No.
She said I didn't, like...
-So there's a lot
of animosity with J.
-So... Yes.
KELLIE: This is perfect for me,
because if you take out J.,
you're knocking down these sort
of traditional Reba numbers.
And the other benefit is
if we do vote her out, now
me and Austin have upgraded
the level of our amulet.
EMILY:
I feel really bad
for her because
-I think she's so lovely,
and she's so kind.
-She's lovely.
But it's survival right now.
Yeah, that's how I feel.
But at this stage of the game,
there are so many people.
It's very difficult to say,
"This is where
everybody stands."
Because people had a decision
at the merge feast among people
who would probably
never work together.
Like, it was
a hodgepodgey group.
Oh, look at these full bellies
-coming up here! Geez.
-They're back!
KELLIE:
Would they ever have really
all gotten together--
all seven of them--
and come to some consensus
decision? No friggin' way.
How the heck do I know
what's really gonna happen?
[whooping]
Some good waves right now.
[indistinct chatter]
We're like,
"Hey, come on back up.
-Let's get you talking."
-"We're just waiting." Exactly.
JAKE:
Yeah, yeah. No, we're just
waiting. ♪ Sitting around ♪
-♪ Couple of sitting ducks,
quacking. ♪
-I am ready.
I hate them. [laughing]
[laughing]
KALEB:
Loserville-- population six.
As they go wash off their mud,
we're sitting there
in the shelter
like cattle, just wondering
which one of us is gonna
get picked next.
They have all of this power.
They want,
from that seven of us,
-J. and Kaleb.
-KELLIE: Okay. Yeah.
-So who are y'all thinking?
-J.
-Okay, so we're all good on J.?
-Yeah.
And the good news is,
the Reba folks are fine with J.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Yeah.
KATURAH: The only other name
that they want is Kaleb.
He's been on my radar
from the beginning.
I don't want us
to lose Kaleb just yet.
Kaleb is, like,
Belo strong right now.
What we need
is a Reba girl to go home.
I actually...
I do agree with that.
-KATURAH: Yeah.
-KENDRA: Okay.
Well, Bruce
made it seem different
-to me.
-Yeah, that's it.
-We can't, like... It...
-I'm not.
-Okay. Right.
-As part of the plan,
I'm voting J.
-My vote will say
J. tonight, 100%.
-Okay.
Katurah doesn't want
to vote Kaleb.
Kaleb-- he's dangerous.
I see little butterflies
flying around.
That's what he's doing.
With his smile,
his little, you know?
Kaleb can bounce around
like little butterflies.
We got to watch out for this
dude because he's conniving.
Over J.?
BRUCE:
Kaleb is bouncing
back and forth.
I don't want that in my way.
Sorry. You got to go.
Reba, Belo, Lulu.
[blows raspberry] I don't care.
Tribal lines are gone.
Oh, all day. All day.
-Yeah, I'm sure you know.
-Yup.
And I think
that makes a lot of sense.
-All right, there you go.
-Okay.
DREW: Bruce opens and says,
"Kaleb is the right pick."
I am elated
because my fear
in voting Kaleb was
you could be kicking
the Belo hornet's nest,
and they could all
come right after you stinging.
But now,
I can kick the hornet's nest
all day.
They're out to lunch.
You know, they're with me.
They don't care.
Right now, Bruce
is feeling very vulnerable.
I want J. gone.
[laughs, mumbles]
AUSTIN:
She took my sandwich,
so I don't mind her going.
DREW:
If we can keep the Rebas,
especially one who has nowhere
else to go, that helps us
in the long run.
It's numbers. Okay.
-I feel like we shouldn't split.
-No, I don't think so.
I think we go in there,
and we vote 100% on Kaleb.
AUSTIN:
I absolutely want J. out.
She prevented me
from getting a sandwich,
and ever since then,
I've had it out for her.
But getting rid of J., we are
kind of sacrificing a number.
I got all your backs.
AUSTIN:
I think what makes sense most
is to get rid of Kaleb.
Yeah.
AUSTIN:
We need the blindside of Kaleb,
and the more votes
that are going to him,
the easier it is for me
to sacrifice my vote again
to upgrade my idol.
Uh, so we're
kind of thinking Kaleb.
DEE:
Are we splitting it?
AUSTIN:
No. So we have
to all vote Kaleb.
EMILY:
The moment I heard
that all the votes are basically
switching to Kaleb,
my heart sunk.
I don't want to send out Kaleb.
That is me
sacrificing a significant
portion of my game,
because moving forward,
I've lost what is effectively
my number one ally.
AUSTIN: I do feel like
there's enough momentum
-behind it at this point.
-DEE: Yeah. Yeah, I do, too.
EMILY:
I'm between a rock
and a hard place.
I need
to keep up my relationships
with the old Reba tribe.
So if I fight too hard,
then they see me
as showing my true alliances
to Kaleb as opposed to them.
It is exactly the way
Survivorworks.
Kaleb has saved my butt
in the past, so, I just...
I need him here.
I need him here,
and I need to convince people
that they need him here, too.
But it might be out of
my control, when voting against
what the majority is doing
puts a target on my back
even more so
than I already have.
-AUSTIN: Yeah?
-Shot in the Dark,
actually, I didn't think about.
We just have to convince him
that it's not him.
Yeah, just reiterate
like, it's okay. Yeah.
-J. MAYA: Yeah. Yeah.
-AUSTIN: Cool.
Pretty, pretty strongly
against you.
Like, Shot-in-the-Dark level
I want you to have the chance
to try to save yourself somehow.
-So what about Bruce?
-Bruce is voting for you, 100%.
-He doesn't like you at all.
Sorry.
-Yeah.
I came out here
to play a strategic game.
I was gonna try
and lower my threat level.
And they're coming after me. Of
course they're coming after me.
And I'm doing everything I can
to stop it.
JAKE: Yeah.
-JAKE: Okay.
-Yeah, yeah.
Bruce does have an idol.
-You're kidding.
-Yeah, he has it.
KALEB:
So what do I do?
"Guess what? Bruce has an idol,
"and I'm not working with him.
"I'm not working
with any of Belo.
I want to work with you guys."
And I'm trying to rally Rebas
to get rid of J.
-Will you guys do this with me?
-Yeah.
-[overlapping chatter]
And I swear to you guys,
I'm ten toes down at this.
-This is exciting!
-KALEB: Okay.
What we had back
at that Lulu beach-- it's done.
You go with the masses.
We have to vote for Kaleb.
Is there anything else
you feel like
would really work
with these people?
Selling myself
and selling my case
is not something
I'm unfamiliar with in sales.
However,
people can sense desperation,
and I am bleeding
at this point with it.
I feel like
I'm about to throw up.
[babbles]
KALEB:
My life is completely
on the line.
We'll see what happens.
Gonna be okay.
KALEB:
I have to hope
that the numbers go my way.
I need a group to work with.
You can't run through this game
by yourself
like a vigilante. That's--
I'm not Batman, you know.
I'm Kaleb.
I'm-I'm the Canadian. [laughs]
♪ ♪
If this is your first time
at Tribal Council,
grab a torch
that does not have fire,
dip it in and get fire.
♪ ♪
This is part of the ritual
of Tribal Council, because,
in this game,
fire does represent your life.
And it is crazy
to be saying that on day 13.
So let's talk about it.
Drew, let's go back
to yesterday.
13 people together
for the first time.
What goes down? Is there a lot
of sharing of stories?
Sharing of any
and all kind, Jeff.
It's too much sharing
for my taste.
I mean, I felt like the nerd
who accidentally
walked into the frat party.
Like, everyone
is so extroverted.
Everyone's so outgoing.
But you have
to straddle a line, because
am I still, you know, Belo?
Am I still Reba?
Am I still Lulu?
It's not quite clear.
And so, that uncertainty
is a big thing to chew off.
PROBST:
Emily, what about
first impressions?
Now, I'm thinking
specifically of you and Bruce
on the first day.
-Anything change?
-EMILY: Oh, yeah. No,
we had an opportunity
to talk about it.
-I think we squashed any beef.
-Amen.
Uh, we'll see if he writes
my name down tonight.
[laughing]
J., is it hard to separate,
"Oh, my gosh, I want
to get to know these people,"
versus, "Oh, my gosh, I need
to get to know these people
in a certain way"?
A hundred percent. I mean,
yesterday was overwhelming.
I've been with Reba members,
essentially, from the beginning
of this game, and then suddenly,
you have to decide
quickly who you vibe with,
who you read well,
and then you have
a ton of time,
and then suddenly,
you have no time at all.
Sifu, did you find
that same thing-- that you were
quickly running out of time
and starting to scramble?
Yeah, I don't know
who coined it,
but we had office hours today,
where we're checking in.
You might be
9:00 to 5:00,
you might be 7:00 to 3:00.
KENDRA:
Oh, yeah.
I had to close my office hours
because you have 12 voices.
I have my own voices
in my head.
They're like, "We're having
a party over here."
JULIE:
However,
-there were a lot
of non-office hours.
-Mm-hmm.
-"So, hey."
-People knocking.
-I'm...
KATURAH:
I want overtime.
-Yeah.
-EMILY: Can I build off of that?
Because I don't feel like
that paints
the full picture, right?
The six of us have been
sitting there
for a couple hours
at this point, thinking,
"What can we do
to save our tushies?"
Katurah, where's
your empathy for the six
who are desperate to join you
in the next phase of the game?
I mean, it's inevitable
that all of our names
will be written down,
and I cannot think
about that moment
without my heart dropping.
Even the concept
of someone saying,
"Let me write
Katurah's name down."
The other day, Sifu asked me
how to spell my name,
and I was like, "Wh-Wh-Wh-Why?
You don't need to know
about how to spell my name."
You know what I mean?
He was joking.
But, like, that's where we are.
And I got lucky today.
-Yes.
-It very well could be me
sitting right over there,
and I will not act like
that's not a possibility.
PROBST:
So, Kaleb,
let's get down to it now.
There are only
six possibilities tonight.
What was your thought process
of how you want to approach it?
I'm an optimist,
so I do want
to work with people.
However, when your name
gets thrown out enough times,
then you start to think,
"How can I just be safe?
"Like, who do I need
to talk to be able
"to make clear that I might be
a big threat here,
but I'm not the biggest
strategic threat here,"
and I think
that's the big difference.
So you heard your name today?
It's like,
wouldn't be Tribal Council
if I didn't hear my name
at this point.
-Oh.
-I get it every single time.
I don't know what to do.
It's, like,
when you reach that kind
of low,
you just get this happiness
for every day that you do get,
every person
that you do get to connect with,
right? And so,
this Lulu curse has not lifted
off of Emily and I,
but knowing
that we gave our best effort--
that's where
you can be at peace.
PROBST:
Emily, is it really
a Lulu curse, or is it just
the way it went, or am I wrong,
and you feel like...
Are you sure about that?
Because I think the numbers
are saying something else, Jeff.
-No, really, I mean...
-Let's go with that
for a minute.
EMILY:
Yeah. You know, whether or not
it's a curse, I don't know.
But now, on the flip side, look,
seven of us are wearing
orange Buffs right now.
The tribe dynamics are no longer
relevant in this scenario.
It's becoming
an individual game.
And, um, if there's a Lulu
curse, it ends tonight.
PROBST:
J., was there a point today
where you shifted from, "Hey,
what are we trying to do?" to
"I just got to make sure
it is not J.
that gets written down tonight"?
J. MAYA:
I think you have
to kind of go with the people
that you know
you've built connections with,
because, you know, tomorrow,
you might still be here,
but you've burned those bridges
in the process
of trying to get
to the next day.
And then, you know,
where are you left?
Kaleb?
KALEB:
As one final thing I'll say,
you know, 'cause it might
come down to just a few votes.
Like, I might be
the biggest threat here,
but I still don't think
I'm the biggest strategic threat
to everybody here.
-Who comes to mind?
-Yeah.
I think it makes sense for
everybody here to write down J.
That's very interesting, Kaleb.
Um, well,
I'm curious what you mean
-by, you're the biggest threat.
-Ooh.
KALEB:
I think that
a lot of people
have talked about me
as a physical threat
and a social threat,
but I think that
the most dangerous thing is
the fact that there's a block
of three Reba women
who've been together
for 13 days.
And I think
for Dee and for Julie,
there's an opportunity,
if you guys let go of J.,
that it lowers
your guys' threat level a lot.
J. MAYA:
Lowers the women of Reba--
their threat level?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-That's interesting.
-And then, in addition
to everybody else, if
we're moving into a tribe of 12,
that's three votes
that they would already have,
and anybody can go home,
and then,
you really lost a lot of power
in the game, right?
You want to mention some other
threats while you're at it?
I'm comfortable
with what I said.
I mean, do you guys see
what he's doing right now
before we're about
to cast votes?
I mean, he's a self-admitted
biggest threat in this game.
Like, no one else said that.
He said that right now.
Not strategically.
I'm by myself.
If I go into the next round,
literally,
who... what do I have?
I can't do anything
to change the course
of this game right now.
DEE:
So how would we trust you
if you're saying
you're by yourself,
and you're trying
to find a home? Who's the home?
-KALEB: Yeah.
-DEE: Nobody knows.
And of course,
I feel strongly about it
because I heard my name,
and I'm Cuban,
so I got to push and fight.
But do I want to work with you
now that you threw my name out
in Tribal Council?
I understand and respect it.
I did hear that you were
throwing my name out first.
-I respect...
-That you were planning
on voting for me.
-So, to be fair.
-Okay.
J. MAYA:
I just want to remind everyone
that this is now
an individual game,
and this is a player that was
losing and losing and losing
and is still sitting here.
If you don't think that he will
be a threat to your game,
that is so... I just...
I can't imagine that, and...
KALEB:
To be fair,
yes, I said J.'s name. I have
to say someone's name, right?
DREW:
I mean, Jeff, you know,
we all love the game,
and there's been
some big swings here,
and I think I and everyone else
am excited to see
if they were home runs
or strikeouts.
KENDRA:
Ooh, that's a good one.
-Hit it.
-Damn.
-There he is.
-Drew.
PROBST:
On that note, it is
time to vote.
Jake, you're up.
Thanks, Jeff.
Whew.
[clears throat]
J.!
[laughing]
Kaleb. [laughs]
Ooh, yeah,
that was a wild Tribal,
but I'm not gonna vote
'cause... um...
Instead of voting,
I'm gonna be sacrificing it
in order to extend this
to a fully-fledged idol.
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, Jeff.
I do have one last thing
I'm gonna try.
It's my last punch.
-Bring it up to me.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-I'm gonna buy a lotto ticket
if this works.
So, fingers crossed.
Kaleb played his
Shot in the Dark, which means
there is not a vote in here
from Kaleb.
Has a one-in-six shot
at safety in the game.
Kaleb, if this says
you are safe,
any votes cast against you
will not count.
If it says you are not safe,
any votes cast against you
will count.
I'll open the scroll.
♪ ♪
Kaleb, you are...
-No way!
-Oh!
-Whoa!
-...safe.
[whooping, shouting]
-Holy...
-Buy a lotto...
buy a lotto ticket!
Oh.
Wow.
-KENDRA: Yeah, that was good.
-[laughing]
So, Kaleb is safe.
Any votes cast against him
-will not count.
-Oh.
-No way.
-Wow.
PROBST:
I'll read the votes.
KENDRA:
Aah!
Kaleb. Does not count.
[laughing]
-Kaleb. Does not count.
-Oh, my God.
AUSTIN:
Wow.
Kaleb. Does not count.
KALEB:
Oh, man.
-Kaleb. Does not count.
-BRUCE: What?
-Wow.
-Oh...
-KENDRA: Amazing.
-Kaleb. Does not count.
[laughing]
Kaleb. Does not count.
-Kaleb. Does not count.
-Wow.
Kaleb. Does not count.
[laughing]
That's crazy.
One vote left.
Kaleb.
-Does not count.
-[gasping]
Oh, my God.
So, all the votes
were for Kaleb.
Kaleb is safe.
So we're going to revote.
Here's how it will work.
Kaleb, you won't vote because
you played the Shot in the Dark.
You can't vote.
And just to remind you,
you can't play
a Shot in the Dark on a revote.
There will be no more
Shot in the Darks played.
♪ ♪
Do you need to take a moment?
-J. MAYA:
Yeah, we need a moment, please.
-Yes. Yes.
-We need a moment.
-AUSTIN: Yeah.
-Oh, that's crazy.
-Yeah, appreciate it.
Oh, man.
Finally, for once,
this game goes in my direction.
[laughing]
PROBST:
All right, time to revote.
Jake, if you would,
come grab the urn.
Oh, I'm a little honored.
I couldn't be more thrilled that
Kaleb's Shot in the Dark worked.
You've been throwing
my name out.
I just hope this vote sticks.
Oh, my God.
Crazy, this is crazy,
this is crazy.
No words.
Really is you or me.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: J.
Emily.
One vote J, one vote Emily.
J.
Two votes J., one vote Emily.
Three votes, J.
J.
Four votes, J.
That's five votes, J.
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor45: J.
That's six. That's enough.
-Need to bring me your torch.
-Okay.
EMILY:
Good job, J.
-Miss you guys, seriously.
-Bye, J.
-Good luck.
-KENDRA: Love you, J.
-Bye.
[sighs] I'm grateful
I got to play, Jeff.
Glad you were here.
J., the tribe has spoken.
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Time for you to go.
Peace.
Congratulations. You are merged.
-[cheering]
-Yeah, baby!
-KELLIE:
I forgot what clean smells like.
-KENDRA: Yes.
KENDRA:
Survivor45, baby.
-No way.
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
-Good night.
-KATURAH: Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JAKE:
I see the Reba-Belo war coming.
I need to take control
of the game.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
Two people will be going home.
Oh. What?
This is a do-or-die moment.
That is it.
KELLIE:
All your cards on the table.
All the marbles are in.
Boy, bye. [laughs]
It was a unanimous vote
for Kaleb.
He got saved
through a Shot in the Dark.
I guess I was the collateral
damage on the revote.
However upsetting it is,
it is pretty freaking wild.
This was the greatest
adventure of my entire life.
There are no regrets here,
and now it's just smiles.
So I'm just happy that I got
to come out here
and play a great friggin' game.
[roars]