AUSTIN:
Dee and I-- we've become
so close during this.
We don't even have to say it.
We know we have each other's
back through everything.
PROBST:
Previously on Survivor...
- You do?
- DREW: I'm ready to
take some shots,
but we have to keep
Dee out of the loop.
DEE:
Austin is trusting me, but
Julie's my other number one.
If I choose to vote Julie out,
then my game is blown.
- Okay. Got you.
- Okay?
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
- and you want to play it...
- Jeff?
I want to play it for myself.
Julie.
Does not count.
Julie. Does not count.
PROBST:
Twelfth person voted out
and the fifth member
of our jury:
Emily.
The tribe has spoken.
- DREW: The fire's still going.
- KATURAH: That was a great
save, Mama J.
- That was...
- Julie packing heat.
That was a fantastic play.
JULIE:
What a crazy night.
They all turned on me,
but I played an idol
that Austin gave to me.
I'm safe.
Emily went home.
I don't blame you guys.
I know you're just
playing a game.
Dee's the one that
told me everybody
was gonna blindside me,
but we want to keep that cover
that Dee and I are
working together.
So in order to hide that,
we're acting totally pissed
at each other, but in reality,
we still got to keep
that friggin' alliance.
So that's kind of exciting.
AUSTIN:
Tonight was an
absolute disaster.
This is the one thing that
we did not want to happen.
But even though
Julie played her idol,
I thought Julie would either
vote for Jake or for Emily.
So I kept
holding on to my amulet
instead of playing it,
and I'm glad that I did.
Because my amulet that
I have is a full idol,
but it's only good until
the final six Tribal,
meaning this next Tribal
Council, I need to play it.
So this amulet is very
important right now.
Plus, everyone's eyes
are focused on Julie.
DEE:
I basically had to act
when Julie played her idol.
I had to be so surprised
and look at everyone
like...
Even though I knew
what was gonna happen
because I told her what to do.
I had to automatically become
awkward in front of everyone.
I got to be the best actress
that I've been
in my entire life.
It's a game. We're almost done.
We can act for a few more days.
It was so nerve-wracking
because I knew that there was
a possibility that they thought
I told her. So I have to
pretend now that
I am in trouble,
because I wrote
Julie's name down.
She's gonna come after me.
She's not gonna come after you.
I think this is actually the
best-case scenario for our game.
- Everyone's trying
to get rid of Julie...
- You're right.
And then Emily... and Emily...
- Yeah. Emily and Drew
separate is a good thing.
- Exactly.
Yeah, obviously. Who?
I don't know, because they
know how close you all are.
- DREW: Can I join?
- DEE: Yeah, you can sit.
- DEE: Have you talked to Julie?
- DREW: No.
- She's gonna come for me.
- Julie?
- Yes.
- Did you tell her?
- No, of course I
didn't tell her.
I think if this group
showed one thing,
it's that we are not
gonna win an Oscar, you know?
There are some bad actors
in this tribe.
All we had to do
was just lie to Julie
for one vote, and we failed.
- She's smart. She's a very
good social player.
- She's not under...
...underestimated.
DEE:
I have no idea how I sold it.
I just pretended to be stupid.
I don't think I'm a good
actress. That's the crazy thing.
Like, in my day-to-day life,
there's no point for
me to lie to anybody.
But out here, it's a game.
It's almost just as important
as finding an idol and
keeping it to yourself,
at this point-- the acting.
AUSTIN:
I actually think this
is better for our game.
Everyone's eyes are
gonna look onto Julie.
- DREW: Yeah.
- This keeps us safe.
So she has to go next.
- DREW: She has to go next.
- Or the next.
AUSTIN: We're safe.
This is the final three.
- Yeah, I think.
- Okay.
- AUSTIN: Julie.
- You remember the good old days?
- DREW: Oh, my God, Julie.
I don't know, Julie, do you
remember the good old days, man?
- AUSTIN: Oh, my gosh.
- What's been going on?
Dee, Austin and myself
are sitting on the beach,
and Julie, like, throws
herself on top of me.
Like, "Remember when
we were the Reba four?"
Like, "Get off me. Get off me."
Like, "I don't know...
We're not friends right now."
We all wanted Julie to go home,
but she didn't, you know?
She's like the guest
who shows up
uninvited at the party, like the
ex-girlfriend at the wedding.
I was for real.
- I was Reba four strong.
- AUSTIN: I said... Julie, okay.
JULIE:
What does the Reba alliance
mean now?
I just don't know if I could
trust the Reba four again.
I mean, Drew pretty much
just blew it up.
So it's game on.
KATURAH: Last night,
Julie played an idol at Tribal,
and that blew up the vote.
I do know that once
an idol is played,
historically, in Survivor,
it's planted back on the
island the very next day.
Now, I haven't had the best luck
with finding idols.
It's been 22 days.
I found literally nothing.
I'm hoping that changes.
I'm still gonna be looking,
because I don't want
Julie to find it.
DEE:
This morning, I wake up,
and I count the people
that are in the bed.
I'm like, "Who's here?"
Katurah wasn't in the bed.
I'm like, "Girl, you
don't wake up that early.
You've never woken
up that early."
And it's clear that she's
up early idol hunting
because she's scared and she
wants to find something.
So me and Austin
look at each other.
We're like, "We got to go."
KATURAH:
I'm getting nervous as heck.
I 1,000% need to
add to my résumé,
because I'm afraid I might
get to the final three
and I may not
have as compelling of a speech.
I want to win and I
need to be able to show
that I've had an
evolution in this game,
that I haven't been
a passive player.
And finding an idol--
that would be huge.
So I'm searching and digging
and looking on trees. What else
can I do but try in this game?
I have to give it my all.
Damn. You snuck
right up on me. Hi.
Sorry.
I look up and I see Austin.
And I'm like, "What are you
doing here?" Literally
nobody goes down that path.
There's no trees down there.
- Good morning. How you doing?
- Nervous.
Yeah. That-that is a good point.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
AUSTIN:
We all know that another idol
could very well be planted
somewhere on this island,
and I don't want anyone to
find it, especially not Julie.
JULIE:
I did not sleep last night.
I just couldn't sleep.
Last Tribal's vote showed that
this is not a "Kumbaya, let's
get to the end with friends."
JAKE:
Ooh!
JULIE:
This is, "Who do I want
to sit with?" and "I want
to take out people
that I don't think
I can beat at the end."
Do you want to have
our talk in a little?
- JULIE: Yes, I do.
- Okay, great.
- Whenever you're ready.
- JULIE: Yeah. Yeah, I'm ready.
I think it'd be smart if the
four Rebas were at the end,
but I don't know if
that's a possible thing.
- Good morning.
I think we're in agreement
who cannot win.
So, when we said,
"100% final four Reba..."
- Yeah. I'm still, I'm
still fine to go with Reba.
- ...I meant that 100%.
Yeah. I-I think there are
still plenty of routes forward
for Reba, and, uh, most of them
start with, uh, voting out Jake.
- So...
- Yeah, see,
- my insecurity is I don't
want to be an idiot
- Yeah.
- and y'all tell me that again.
- And getting it the second time?
- Yeah, I mean...
- Like, I don't know
how to build this back.
Like, I want to 100%,
because if I...
I think for both of our games...
- ...there should be Reba there.
- Yeah.
After I stomach and
I swallow the rage
of-of this-this blown-up plan,
my first play is to kind of,
you know, coddle Julie
and to say,
"No, there is a route forward.
No, Reba needs
to stick together."
But realistically, she is on an
island alone. There really is
no getting around the fact that
Julie is a perennial outsider,
like, now and for
the rest of the game.
I don't think the Reba four
is a dead and buried thing.
- I'd be more than happy to...
- I'd love to bring the
band back together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can go on a reunion
tour after a break...
after a break...
a short breakup.
- No, we-we didn't...
We-we weren't ready.
- Short difference of opinions.
We weren't ready for
our solo careers yet.
JULIE:
We're like, "Yeah, we're getting
the band back together," but
I just feel like it's...
...lies.
Band's getting back together
for a reunion tour.
JULIE:
Drew organized this
entire blindside against me,
and he now says he
wants to work with me.
I think he's just
feeding me what he thinks
I want to hear or
what I will believe.
So, at this point,
there's only one person
that I trust 100%.
I don't think
that people are onto the fact
that Dee and I are
as close as we are
and are working together.
But there's six people left,
and Dee's the only
one that I trust.
'Cause she's proved it.
She saved my life.
So we need numbers.
It's even harder to
act back at camp.
When you orchestrate
such a big blindside,
you cannot tell anybody,
because the moment that
that comes out of my mouth--
even if it's to Austin,
who's my other number one--
I am risking a million dollars.
At one point, they came up me,
and they're like,
"Did you tell her?"
And I was like,
"No, I did not tell her.
- I swear on my mom."
- Right.
- I had to swear, like, on them.
- Yeah.
- I know.
- Because Austin came up to me,
- and he's like, "Dude,
people think you told her."
- Right.
- So I had to swear
on my parents.
- Yeah. Yeah.
DEE:
Out here, I'm gonna
swear on everybody.
I'm gonna swear on my dogs.
I'm gonna swear on
my mom, on my dad,
and they're gonna still be
alive when I leave here,
and they're gonna
be happy when I win
and that I swore for them.
You're my only in, because,
like, I swear Drew wants me out.
- Drew is the master...
Drew-Drew is...
- He is.
Drew is the one that had
said your name before.
- I swear. I swear.
- I know.
- Like, I know you mentioned
Austin, but...
- No, no, no.
Austin's playing into Drew.
- He is. That's what I'm saying.
- Yeah. 'Cause they're close.
- Austin will not write
Drew's name down.
- No, he won't.
- But Austin was the one
that told me about you.
- Yeah.
Drew-- we all know
that he's a mastermind,
and he's good at Tribal talking.
- You know what I mean?
- Yes. He's got to go.
Yeah, he's got to go.
JULIE:
I got to get Drew out.
He wants me out, therefore
I have to get him out.
What happened to Reba strong?
What happened?
We were so good.
I'll tell you what happened.
Drew happened.
Come on in.
And then there were six.
The faces of warriors.
PROBST:
Today, I see some smiles
and some very stern faces
that are now turning
into smiles.
- All right, shall we get
to today's reward challenge?
- Yeah!
PROBST:
All right, for today's challenge,
you're gonna race
in from the ocean
till you get to a barrel.
You're gonna stand on the barrel
using ropes to guide you
through a course as you
collect three keys.
Once you have all three keys,
you'll use them to
unlock and then solve
a Survivor slide puzzle.
First person to
finish wins reward.
- Want to know what
you're playing for?
- Hell, yeah!
- It's a perfect day
for a picnic.
- JAKE: I love those.
- JAKE: Yeah, baby.
- AUSTIN: Let's go.
- JAKE: Let's go.
- PROBST: Everything you need
for a beautiful
afternoon picnic.
You could do this back at camp,
but today we're gonna
do something different.
You're gonna go somewhere
you have not been--
a beautiful sandspit in
the middle of the ocean.
PROBST:
It's truly one of those places
where you're gonna look around
and it's gonna be
just you, the food ..
and the waves lapping
against the sand.
And I'm looking at the ocean,
it's kind of rough,
so let's get there
by helicopter.
PROBST: Everything you need
for a once-in-a-lifetime
experience.
All you got to do is
win this challenge.
Worth playing for?
All right, we're gonna draw
for spots. We'll get it on.
Let's do it. Here we go.
KATURAH:
Like, why?
Why? Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Okay, here we go. For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, it is a race to get
back here to that barrel.
You can walk it
or you can swim it.
Everybody racing back.
Austin gonna get here first.
Here comes Drew and Jake.
Julie and Dee.
Here comes Katurah.
Everybody now working
on that second phase.
Now you got to get
up on that barrel
and use these ropes to
move across the course.
You're trying to grab
those three keys.
It is Austin with his first key,
moving, now looking
for that second.
If you fall off,
you got to go back.
Drew has his first key.
Jake working on his first key.
Drew trying to hang on.
Nice recovery.
Katurah's in this now.
There you go, Katurah.
Big reward on the line.
Austin with his second key.
Right now, it is Austin
doing a nice job
using these ropes as a guide.
Drew right on his tail.
Here comes Jake.
Dee struggling to hang on.
Julie doing a nice job.
Katurah's in it.
You got to figure out
that balance point.
Austin having no trouble
with this course at all.
Austin, you're good.
Start working on that puzzle.
You got three keys. One
of them will unlock the puzzle.
You're good, Drew.
Drew has all three keys.
He's in it now.
Jake working toward that second.
He's got his second.
Julie looking for
that third key.
Julie's got two.
Dee has her second.
This is awesome.
PROBST:
Katurah's got one.
Working on that second.
Everybody is in this right now.
Austin has his unlocked.
Austin working on the puzzle.
Drew has his unlocked.
Jake, you're good.
Julie's good.
She's got her third key.
Julie's here.
Dee has her third key.
Get to that mat, Dee,
and you're good.
You're good, Dee.
Slide puzzles can take forever
or they can be solved
very quickly.
You slide pieces left
and right or up and down.
- You'd love to just pick
one up, but you can't.
- KATURAH: Am I good?
Katurah, you're good.
Katurah has her third key.
Start unlocking that puzzle.
You've seen how long
a slide puzzle can take.
You've also seen how quickly
they can come together.
You can feel like
you're nowhere,
and then, suddenly, three
moves and you got it.
Austin got here first.
He's been working on it
the longest, then Drew.
Will that time advantage help?
When you think you
have it, step back.
AUSTIN:
Jeff. Jeff.
Austin thinks he has it,
and he does.
Austin pulls it out
and wins reward on day 22
-Amazing, man.
-of Survivor45.
-Good job.
PROBST:
Wow, that was fast.
Austin led that challenge
-from start to finish.
-Awesome.
-PROBST: Wow.
-Great job, man. Great job.
All right, Austin, come on over.
Right here.
Big reward on day 22.
You're gonna leave here,
go to a beautiful place
in the middle of the ocean,
and have a lovely picnic.
Choose one person to join you
-for this afternoon's
once-in-a-lifetime experience.
AUSTIN: Oh, my gosh.
I-I have to pick Dee
on this one.
PROBST:
Come on over, Dee.
All right, Austin,
you have one more spot.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: You have four people.
Everybody clearly wants it.
Walk me through,
before you tell me who,
why are you choosing
the last person to join you?
AUSTIN:
It's obviously, at this point,
a mix of both
personal and strategic.
You got to make sure that
when you're gone, the people
you send back are not gonna
be the ones who are gonna be,
"All right, let's talk Austin.
Let's get him out now.
He didn't pick me."
PROBST:
So that implies that the loyalty
or the alliance might
want you to choose one person,
but you might need that person
to actually be back at camp
to try to hold things together
or stop them from falling apart.
-AUSTIN: Exactly.
-PROBST: Tricky.
What's the decision?
Katurah.
-PROBST: Katurah?
-Really? [chuckles] Wow.
-Shocked.
-I am always shocked.
Thank you, Austin.
I appreciate that.
All right, Austin,
here's what's gonna happen.
You, Dee, Katurah,
gonna leave here,
be taken
to a beautiful sandspit.
-Have you ever
been to a sandspit?
-Never.
Should make for
a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Helicopter will take you
to your destination.
Oh, my God.
-DEE: Grab this?
-KATURAH: I'll grab...
PROBST:
Take it all.
-This one.
-Yeah.
PROBST:
And enjoy. Well-earned.
-JAKE: Have fun, guys.
-JULIE: Y'all, have fun.
KATURAH:
Thanks, guys. Sorry, y'all.
DEE:
Oh, my God.
KATURAH [laughs]:
-Oh, my God. An actual...
-[sighs]
Drew, what was that sigh for?
DREW:
I don't know, man.
Like, you know,
I'm used to being, like,
the last schoolyard pick
growing up,
and, like, the only time
I've ever been on a reward
is when I won it, you know?
And so I had to come. Nobody's
ever picked me, you know?
I'm the only person out here who
never gets picked on a reward.
You know? I know
there are reasons for it,
but there were reasons for it
in middle school, too,
and it-it sucks.
And, Julie, even though
they've anointed you the mom,
it doesn't mean
you don't have your own things
that go through your mind,
as a person who also
wanted to go on that reward,
I'm sure.
Well, absolutely.
And especially since
it was a unanimous vote
to kick me out last Tribal...
I feel like I'm getting
babysit back at camp.
So it felt more like...
make sure
they've got eyes on me.
PROBST:
All right, Drew, Julie,
Jake, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Thanks, Jeff.
AUSTIN:
It hurt not picking Drew,
but my plan
is to keep all eyes on Julie.
And I also knew
a combination
of Drew, Julie and Jake--
yeah, they're
not going anywhere.
They are at war with each other.
Are you feeling like something's
missing in your life?
You need
a little hip in your hop?
I got an idea.
Apply to be on Survivor.
Okay.
Do we want to eat their rice?
-Yeah.
-We can have dinner later.
Whatever you want to do.
Sorry y'all didn't get picked.
Sorry you didn't get it,
Julie, too.
Sounded beautiful.
-You guys been in a helicopter?
-I would've been sick
on the helicopter ride.
I've been only in a helicopter
once, and I threw up.
Me too.
DREW:
So, the reward challenge,
Austin chooses Dee and Katurah.
So he basically says
that I'm the babysitter
and that here at home,
causing a ruckus,
are these two demon children,
Julie and Jake.
And I need to just stick there
and make sure they don't
get into too much trouble.
Let's just sit and make some
rice for a while and chat.
-JAKE: Yeah.
-But I can get some peppers
from that other bush.
Jake can come with me.
We'll stick together,
so you don't have to worry.
I know you have a job here.
That's to watch me.
DREW:
The babysitting thing sucked
because I didn't
get any food, I had to
go and take the social heat.
It made Julie distrust me
even more,
and I couldn't
look for idols myself,
because I was stuck
watching those two.
-I know me, personally.
-Yeah, no.
JULIE:
Up until now, I've had
this great alliance,
but my alliance
has already taken shots at me,
so I can't trust them anymore.
So, now
I got nothing to save me
unless I can find an idol.
Great.
-That's what I'm saying.
Let's be the fun ones.
-[chuckles]
JAKE: Austin clearly thinks
Julie needs babysitting,
but I'm not
babysitting a grown woman.
I'm not doing that.
There's only a couple days
left in this game
and I need to focus on me.
I don't care about Julie.
So, yes, we were telling Drew
we were looking for peppers.
We were looking
for peppers under rocks.
We were looking for peppers,
you know, under the leaves,
in the trees.
We were looking
for peppers everywhere.
I need some spice in this game.
-What?
-He's coming back,
so we got to find those peppers.
Yeah, we were looking for idols.
Yeah.
[group cheering]
Aw...
[Dee laughing]
Oh, no!
[Jake vocalizing]
I want you to know
that I spend an hour a day
scraping rice off the side
of this crusty,
gross, dirty pot, so...
Yeah, but
we're doing pretty bad.
-[laughs]
-Oh, that's awesome.
[Dee whoops]
[both laughing]
KATURAH: When I first
got picked for the reward,
I was just too excited to think
about anything else. But then,
as the two of them
were sitting closer
than me and Dee were sitting,
I was like, "Oh, right.
I'm a third wheel."
And of course I would
look over every now and then,
and I'd see
a little hand on another thigh
or something like that,
but, you know, do what
y'all need to do.
Keep your head
in that lover's lane.
I'm-a be over here thinking
about how to win this million.
-AUSTIN: This is amazing.
-KATURAH: Oh, my God.
This is
the best friggin' day ever!
-[chuckles]
-AUSTIN: I love this.
This is awesome.
DEE:
Wow.
KATURAH:
I'm so happy you chose me.
Like, I mean, I knew
you were gonna choose Dee.
I was like, "Yeah." Well, I was
excited that you were going.
-Looking at me.
-Did you know?
-Yeah, did you know?
-I had a feeling.
-[chuckles]
-DEE: Austin's relationship
and I is progressing.
Um, any time a man
tells you something,
you should never believe them
until he puts actions
behind his words.
And Austin did that
when he chose me
first for the reward.
When he said, "Okay, Dee,"
I'm like, "Oh, damn. Okay."
I'm feeling like
I'm your number one, then.
Like, you put some action.
It wasn't really strategy.
It was more like, "Hey,
I want to spend this afternoon
having this experience
with you."
That's the way I took it.
And I was happy about it, so...
Yeah.
What's the question?
Yeah, I need to spice things up.
KATURAH:
Mm-hmm.
DEE:
Well...
[laughing]:
I am a little bit smitten.
I don't know
how to answer the question.
He's a cool guy.
I like him.
DEE:
Austin, this is
the best day ever.
-Thank you so much.
-AUSTIN: This is
the best day ever. Of course.
-We can finish this.
-Mm-hmm.
You can definitely
finish it more.
I've got space.
-You've got space?
-[Katurah laughs]
AUSTIN: Dee is someone,
in the real world,
I would be intimidated
of ever talking to,
because she is just, like,
she's... she's awesome.
She's, like, so cool. You know?
The past few years,
I've really been able
to develop
my own self-confidence.
I used to be very nervous,
very anxious, more introverted.
I was a little chubby.
I had braces from elementary
school till high school
and, like,
12 years of bad acne.
And I've come so far.
But coming out here
has pushed me to a new level.
It's made me way more confident.
And it's, like,
definitely a crazy,
big confidence boost
to have someone
as cool as Dee,
like, like me or whatever.
You know?
Like, I love it.
I'm so glad
to be here with y'all.
-Survivor45!
-AUSTIN: On a helicopter.
[all cheering]
DEE:
New era, baby.
All right,
how's this for seawater?
More or less?
What do you think?
Good. Perfect.
DREW:
Do you have
the scooper for me, Jake?
Let me look.
Where did it go?
The reward challenge,
uh, did not go my way.
I lost.
Austin wins.
He takes Dee
and he takes Katurah.
Everyone on that helicopter
is the people I want
to scheme with right now.
Meanwhile, I'm stuck here
with my next two targets.
In my head, I'm thinking,
the only way I can win the game:
if I get something
and do something flashy
in front of the jury.
And to do that,
I need some firepower.
I'm going down the beach
a little bit. I'm gonna change.
So I need to find
my idol now.
Julie played an idol
last Tribal.
It's here somewhere.
I need to find it now.
I want the hidden immunity idol
to remain hidden
from everyone else
other than me.
Even though
I want to work with Julie,
she can't know
that I found something.
I need to focus on me.
I don't care about Julie.
I care about Jake.
I've looked a bunch
in this game for idols, so far.
I've been very unlucky,
but I'm looking in the trees
that look similar to where Bruce
found his Beware Advantage.
I'm digging around.
I got it.
And then I open it.
It's not an idol.
It's a clue
to the hidden immunity idol.
Okay, I can do that.
I need to go get this now.
No one else is finding my idol.
That is my idol.
So I go over to the raft,
I strip down to my underwear.
So, you know, if people find me,
they're gonna know,
"Yeah, hey, I'm getting changed.
You know,
I'm not fully clothed."
Plus, it's fun to search
in my underwear, you know?
I've done a play before where
I had to be in my underwear
onstage
in front of other people,
so I'm not super concerned
about searching
for this idol in my underwear.
It's-it's good. It was...
it was a show.
I was in college. Uh...
[laughs] Um... So,
I'm searching for this idol
in my underwear.
Nothing comes easy this season.
Jeff is pulling zero punches.
He is going all out,
making this difficult for me,
which, you know, it's fine.
If nothing's a challenge,
is it really worth doing?
You know what I mean?
And then I see it.
It almost looks like a cap
that I can pull off.
You got to be kidding me.
[vocalizes]
Ta-da!
It's my hidden immunity idol.
Yeah, my idol...
is now my crotch idol.
"Congratulations. You have
found a hidden immunity idol."
Let's put that back,
make it look good as new.
No one's gonna know a thing.
I would like
to get innovative with this.
I need to play this
and have it do more
than just save me in this game
for another vote.
I need this to earn me votes
in Final Tribal.
That's what this is right here.
And I need to figure out
how to best implement it.
I'm coming back.
I'm not out of this game.
I'm still in it.
I'm still a threat.
I'm a wolf in goat's clothing.
Come on in!
-Looking good, Jeff.
-So are you all.
Yeah.
PROBST:
Day 23 Survivor45.
-[whooping]
-All right.
PROBST:
Jake, Julie, Dee,
Austin, Drew and Katurah.
How you feeling today?
I feel like
now there's more energy today.
Jake, you're talking
to your buddies,
and you're telling them
about this moment right here.
"Probst is asking
what it's like.
You know what I told him?
I told him..."
I told him
it's no-holds-barred right now.
This is every man and woman
for themselves, you know?
Two whole tribes
have been eliminated.
Six? That's a starting tribe.
This is what we started on,
kind of.
-[Julie squeaks]
-So now...
we're cannibalizing ourselves,
and, you know,
we're gonna have a fun time
doing it, right, guys?
-Yup, for sure.
-Yeah.
-JULIE: Right, right.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-[all voicing assent]
-First things first, Drew.
Got to take it back.
-DEE: He kneels down.
He goes down.
-KATURAH: He kneels.
Thank you.
Appreciate the kneel.
Just a little bit. [laughs]
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna put one foot
on one end of a hinged beam.
At the other end is a ball.
Your job: keep that ball
up there as long as you can.
When your ball drops,
you're out.
-Last person left standing
wins immunity.
-[whooping]
Safe tonight
at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Losers, Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the thirteenth person voted out
of Survivor45
and become the sixth member
of our jury.
Big enough stakes?
-Heck, yeah.
-Of course.
-All right, let's draw
for spots.
We'll get it on. Here we go.
All right, here we go.
I'm gonna count you in.
When I get to zero, you need
to have a foot up there,
release your gate,
challenge is on.
Five, four,
three,
two, one.
Everybody release.
Everybody's good.
This challenge is on.
And balls are moving right away.
Your job: steady it out.
If you're at the far end
of the beam,
that's the safest spot,
because you've got a little lip.
Katurah's ball
right where it started.
Little movement by Austin.
Dee nice and steady.
Jake looking good.
Drew, nice balance work.
Julie very steady.
That ball has not moved
from where it started.
It's a brand-new
Survivorchallenge.
You are the first to do it.
Whoever wins it will be in five.
You'll have that necklace
tonight at Tribal Council.
It's hard to balance on a day
when you're feeling 100%,
much less day 23 of Survivor.
-Julie's ball moves.
-No, no, no!
Julie's the first casualty.
-Julie is out.
-JULIE: Son of a gun!
PROBST:
And now we have Jake,
arms flapping
to get his balance in control.
Jake drops. Jake is out.
We are down to four,
just like that.
Drew, then Dee,
Katurah and Austin
fighting for immunity.
You are only two minutes
into this challenge
and you're already hurting.
You're gonna feel it
on that down leg
as much as anything.
-More.
Katurah's ball
slowly on the move.
And a nice adjustment
by Katurah.
Katurah the only person left
in this challenge
-who hasn't won immunity.
-Aw, no. No, no, no, no.
-JAKE: Don't. Relax.
-PROBST: Can she save it
right there?
-JAKE: Relax.
-PROBST:
Katurah in a dangerous spot,
but she's held it.
But she can't anymore.
Katurah's out.
We're down to three.
It is Drew,
Dee and Austin.
All three have won
individual immunity.
It will be the second win
for one of them,
and it will guarantee you a spot
in the final five.
Question is who will it be?
How are you feeling, Austin?
Uh... I don't know.
How about you?
-I feel good.
-AUSTIN: All right.
I feel how I felt minute one.
[Austin and Dee laugh]
PROBST:
Been up there seven minutes now.
Right now, all you're thinking
about is eye on that ball.
Keep that ball
at the far end of this beam.
You just don't want
any erratic movements.
You can see how just
a tiny twitch is all it takes.
A lot of movement from Drew,
but he's hanging in there.
Another nice save by Drew.
And another.
DEE:
Nice job, Drew.
PROBST:
And another.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: Drew continues to fight
in this challenge to stay in it.
DEE: Keep fighting, Drew.
Keep fighting.
What the heck is happening
over there?
PROBST:
Look at that. Hopping around,
trying to keep it going.
-Oh...
-Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: Drew's ball
-is all over the place,
but he continues
-All right, easy,
-to save it.
-easy, easy, easy.
-JULIE: Wow.
-KATURAH: Wow.
-JAKE: Wow.
JULIE:
Drew, that was amazing.
PROBST:
Drew back in that safe spot
at the end.
JULIE:
Looking good, Drew.
PROBST:
Been up there 12 minutes now.
KATURAH:
You guys are killing it.
PROBST:
Keep digging.
You never know when
two people are gonna drop
and it's you that wins.
-JULIE: Oh...
-PROBST: Drew drops.
Drew is out.
We're down to two.
-KATURAH: Great effort, Drew.
-It is Dee and Austin
fighting for immunity.
Here we go.
Day 23.
-Drew, that was awesome.
-That was incredible.
Dee and Austin
have been very steady.
Austin, little bit of movement
with that ball,
but he's in the safe zone.
Why are you moving so much?
I'm getting bored.
Comes down to this.
Dee, who's won immunity,
versus Austin,
who has won immunity.
There's only one necklace.
One of you will be
guaranteed safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
Been up there 19 minutes now.
-[whooping]
-Wow.
When we tested this
with our dream team
to make sure it works,
the winning time was 21 minutes.
-KATURAH: Wow.
-JAKE: Whoa.
[laughs] Right.
PROBST:
Balls in two
very different spots.
Austin is safe right now,
but Dee is very close
to being in trouble.
But her ball has not moved
in a long time.
Little bit
of movement from Austin.
What's going on, Austin?
I just want
to get a little movement in.
-Why? It hurts a little bit?
-No.
Smack talk
at an all-time high on day 23.
You've been up there
21 minutes now.
-Ooh. Good job, guys.
-Well done.
Nobody cares about a record.
You want the necklace.
Austin's ball on the move again.
Yeah, don't worry, don't worry.
PROBST:
Making its way around
that safe zone and back in.
-Not worried?
-No. Why would I be worried?
As Dee continues
to be like a statue.
Oh, man.
PROBST:
Keep digging.
You never know when
the other player is gonna drop.
Mine's not gonna move.
PROBST:
Austin in trouble.
-Can he save it again?
-[grunts]
[gasps]
PROBST:
And he doesn't. Austin drops.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my gosh.
-PROBST: Dee wins her second
-individual immunity.
-[Katurah whoops]
PROBST:
Safe tonight at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Austin can't even walk
as he goes to congratulate her.
-Good job. Good job.
-PROBST: Wow. Both feeling it.
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
Dee, come on over.
-Yeah.
-There you go, Dee.
For the second time
in Survivor45,
immunity is yours.
Well earned.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
Cannot be voted out
of this game, which means
you are guaranteed a spot
in the final five.
Let that sink in and share.
I feel so grateful.
Like, I don't know.
I was just thinking of the
million dollars in that ball.
I'm like,
"I can't drop that ball."
And I just feel grateful
that it was a showdown, too.
I feel like it means more
when it's a showdown
'cause you really
have to dig deep.
PROBST:
Well earned. Dee safe tonight.
Cannot be voted out,
guaranteed a spotted at five.
As for the rest of you, 23 days
is a long time in Survivor.
It's not enough.
Somebody voted out tonight.
Thirteenth person voted out
will become
the sixth member of our jury.
You have the afternoon
to figure out
who that's gonna be.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
-See you tonight of Tribal.
Congrats.
-Thank you, Jeff.
DREW:
I have a plan.
It's in place. I don't want
to have to retool it.
There's no editing.
I don't take notes.
Julie's existence at camp
is a reminder that we failed,
we were outsmarted,
we were beaten.
It's certainly not a reminder
I like having around.
I'd like Julie
to go at this point.
-Dee, Dee, Dee, Dee, Dee, Dee.
-[whoops] Let's go.
-Thank you, guys.
It feels so damn good to win.
This guarantees me a spot
at the final five,
which is absolutely insane.
But even more than wearing this
necklace, as pretty as it is--
you know, I want to go out
partying with it--
it makes me feel good
'cause I'm a woman.
And, like, I'm going against
these men, and it's like,
"I'm gonna give you
a run for your money,
whether you like it or not."
I'm gonna beat you next time.
No, you're not.
-I'm gonna
beat you next time.
-No, you're not.
AUSTIN:
One hundred percent.
Honestly, there wasn't anyone
else I'd love to go head...
-I know. That was awesome.
-head-to-head at it with them.
You gave me a rough time.
Uh, damn.
[scoffs] Didn't look like it.
What the heck?
I was like, "This guy's
not gonna freaking quit."
AUSTIN:
That immunity challenge went
almost as well
as I could have hoped.
Obviously, if I won, that would
have been the cherry on top.
It definitely makes it easier
losing to someone
that I care about,
someone who is very close to me,
both strategically
and personally.
But immediately,
Julie goes down.
That's who we needed
to be out.
That way, we can finish what
we started last Tribal Council.
It took one time
to knock out my idol,
and this is the time
we finish the job.
So, I think
we all know what, uh...
JAKE:
Yeah.
DREW:
Where our heads are at.
-JAKE: No, we're good.
-AUSTIN: Yeah, um...
'Cause in my book it's, like,
it's a sure thing, so...
JAKE:
It would be very easy
for me to say,
"Yup, we're going
on Julie again.
We're putting
all the votes on Julie."
But...
that doesn't help Jake's résumé.
That doesn't help Jake's résumé
one bit, so...
Julie and I don't have
the best history, but
Julie playing in desperation
is a great thing for Jake.
-Yup.
-Right?
-Right.
-What would I be doing
if I decided
to dogpile on you again?
-Yeah.
-Like, I don't think
that helps my game at all.
-It doesn't... It'd be...
-So, I don't... I would be...
-It'd be following
somebody else's.
-Yes. Yes.
So, are you open
to anything this next round?
-Yes. Yes.
-Okay, so here's
what I want to do.
-Ooh. Interesting.
-Because
anyone sits next to him
in final three, it's over.
-Yeah.
-It's over because he's one
-of the best speakers
I've ever met in my life.
-You're right.
JULIE:
Since the entire tribe
tried to vote me out,
this is my only play.
So, he's saying the words,
and I'm just,
"You're right, you're right,
you're right."
What he doesn't know
is that I'm working with Dee,
and that she is down
for writing Drew's name.
But I can't
let Jake know that.
Oh.
If it all goes well, there will
be actually four names on Drew.
-That's how I'm looking at it
right now.
-Okay.
Are you opposed to that?
-I'm not.
-Okay.
Right now, every move I make
is absolutely crucial.
I need to take ownership
of every person
who gets voted out of this game
up until Final Tribal.
I need to be
in absolute control.
If we go on Julie tonight,
where's the move
in Jake and Katurah?
-Exactly.
-It doesn't look like
we're the boss.
-You know what I mean?
-Exactly.
-They're three, we're two.
-I was thinking the same thing.
-It might be time
to blindside somebody.
-I agree.
JAKE:
You want to put three on Drew?
-KATURAH: I'm 100%
down with that.
-JAKE: Okay.
Julie is 100% in.
Julie would be fine.
I was like,
"Julie would be 100% in."
I think I can get Dee.
I wouldn't even pull Dee.
Dee might ruin it.
Because if it leaks
and he plays an idol,
we don't get a move.
The way that
this is supposed to work
is myself, Julie, and Katurah--
that's three votes.
That's 50%.
We put them all on Drew.
We put three votes on Drew.
Now, if Drew, Dee and Austin
put three votes on Julie,
we run into a tie.
If I get the votes to be a tie,
I believe I can get Dee
or Austin to flip at a revote.
Now, this is very similar
to the move
that I tried to pull with Kaleb,
and to save Kaleb
and pull Julie out.
So, in a way, I'm hoping
to get some redemption tonight.
-It's 100% a move for us.
-Okay.
Dee can't take credit for it,
and we have something over Dee
-in final three
if she's there with us.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
Damn, that makes sense.
I didn't think of it that way.
JAKE:
Now, some people might think
it's ludicrous
for me to rely on Katurah twice
in a similar manner, but
I believe our interests align.
Katurah needs some moves.
If I can make her feel
like it's her thing, too--
even though it's not--
my winner potential goes up,
so I don't want her telling Dee.
-KATURAH: One, two,
-DEE: Two,
-three. Drew.
-three. Drew. [laughing]
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
-Yeah, they're coming
for us for sure.
-Yeah. Exactly.
So here's what I'm thinking.
DEE:
At this point in the game,
Drew needs to go.
Drew is the mastermind behind
a lot of moves in this game.
-Ooh, he's very smart, though.
-I know.
-We got to be careful. He...
-He's extremely smart.
And that's why I'm, like,
we have to be so good
-at making him believe
it's Julie.
-Yeah.
DEE:
I think the fact that I voted
for Julie last Tribal Council--
thank friggin' God that
I did that because it showed
that I was still with them
in this game.
Drew trusts me right now
and he won't see it coming.
However, then that puts me
in a position where Austin might
feel like I betrayed him.
It's gonna suck because I'm
worried about lying to Austin.
But when it comes
to lying to Drew,
I could care less.
[laughs]
DEE: It's crazy.
I know. It's right there.
-It's in our hands.
-It's right there.
DREW: Up to pretty much today,
everything has gone to plan,
and that's an amazing thing,
because it really doesn't
happen in Survivor.
You know, maybe I'm full of
hot air on this accomplishment,
but I really did
control the merge to this point.
The only true hiccup
was Julie's idol play.
But even that-- there was
some convenience for that.
Emily got out of the way
with no blood on my hands.
And I think that
with Julie headed home tonight,
I'm cruising into probably
a cleaner final five
than I would have if Julie had
gone home in the first place.
My thought is that tonight,
she's gonna try and, like, spike
somebody's name out there,
and it probably will be me.
-But Austin could also play
his amulet on me.
-Yeah. Okay.
So we're set.
This is the plan.
-I'm locked in.
-Chill.
DREW:
I do think that
if I was really in danger,
Austin would play that amulet
on me and he would protect me.
And maybe that is tremendous
complacency on my part,
but I do think that he's sincere
wanting to go to the end with me
and that he would protect me
if push came to shove.
-It's not over yet,
but, I mean...
-It's looking promising.
AUSTIN:
It almost feels like
it's been too easy, you know?
It was, like, day two,
I was with Drew,
and we kind of had been talking
about working together,
and, you know, by day seven,
we had this final two alliance,
and we knew
we can take over this game.
And we figured out a way
as soon as the merge hit
how we can knock each person out
to finish this game,
and we've been able
to get it done.
We have not had any single
breach of trust,
-Nope. Never.
-ever, which is crazy.
This could go down
as the greatest duo
-in Survivorhistory.
-It could go down
as an all-time.
I think it's an all-time.
-I do too.
-It's just cool.
Oh, I love it.
DREW:
If you look at the greats,
you look at J.T. and Stephen,
you look at Gervase and Tyson,
when things came down to it,
especially,
you know,
at this point in the game,
they had each other's backs.
Now I'm seeing visions
of me at the final three.
Maybe I'm counting my chickens
before they hatch,
but at the same time,
how could you not?
It all seems so tangible.
Just staying in the moment--
it's hard.
I'm speeding ahead,
but I have to stay grounded
in this vote tonight.
Otherwise, I might find myself
on the way out.
That sucks, lying to Julie,
but at the same time, it's part
of the game,
but we're so freaking close.
-No, we're so close.
-I know.
I'm so happy you lost.
[laughs]
You're not gonna
let me forget that, are you?
Never. Never.
I'm going back and forth
with whether I should
or should not tell Austin
about blindsiding Drew.
He trusted me so much
to come and tell me about Julie
because he didn't
want to blindside me.
So I feel like I don't want
to blindside him either.
But there is a possibility
that he might
use his amulet on Drew
and then blindside Julie.
It would basically be the
same situation that I was in.
Um, you know, so...
I don't know.
It's getting tough.
Like, this... Oh, man.
I mean, it's kind of crazy,
you know?
I think after tonight,
we're gonna have to have a...
-Heart-to-heart?
-Heart-to-heart, long hangout
-I agree.
-at the beach.
-Well, let's do it.
-But, uh, I mean, at that point,
-it's game over.
-Yep.
It is hard because, like,
my morals are coming in the way,
you know?
And... But then, I also told
myself, coming in here like,
"Dee, you cannot let
your emotions get in the way."
Who are you voting for tonight?
Are you...
DEE:
I don't know.
Should I tell Austin
or should I not tell Austin?
Out here, you're forced
to make tough decisions.
And I told myself,
coming in here,
I made a promise to myself.
I knew what was gonna
be my weakness. I knew it.
I didn't know who was gonna
be in this game,
I didn't know
who I was gonna meet,
but I knew that my weakness was
my emotions getting involved.
And trying to balance my morals
in the real world
with my morals onSurvivor...
[sighs]
It's hard. It's hard.
All right.
[Survivors laughing]
Let's start with
the reward challenge. Austin,
you won that.
Came with a big reward.
A helicopter trip to a sandspit,
a nice picnic.
One of the things that I noticed
is when I asked you
who you were
gonna bring with you,
first, you chose Dee.
But with your second choice,
you said, "Now it's about
"who I leave behind
to kind of look out,
make sure nothing happens."
Did you get any kickback
from people
saying, "What does that mean--
you don't trust us?"
AUSTIN:
A little bit.
You know, not too much.
But, you know,
the helicopter went
in front of the camp,
we all screamed.
So, like, I'm just thinking,
"Oh, my gosh.
If they didn't already hate me,
they're gonna hate me now."
But people were
really respectful
of the decision, and, uh,
you know, that's
all I could ask for.
PROBST:
Julie, what's your take on this?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
he just wanted me
to keep an eye on Drew and Jake.
No. No.
So, my suspicion is
-I was to be babysat.
-PROBST: But you're the mom.
-You're the one who babysits.
-JULIE: Right?
-My kids are turning
on me, Jeff.
-[laughing]
JAKE:
Well, you know,
we let Julie stay up late.
We let her eat ice cream
past bedtime.
And you know, she was, uh...
I thought
-she had a fun time. Yeah.
-Got to jump on the bed.
-You know what I mean? Like...
-We were cool babysitters.
-Yeah, we were cool babysitters.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
PROBST:
Katurah, we just
literally talked about
Austin making a strategic move,
and it's one big joke,
but it's not a joke.
That's a move
in a million-dollar game.
I think that
we're trying to separate
as best as we can, Jeff.
Yes, we recognize
this is a game
and there are gonna
be tough moves
that must be made, no matter
how difficult they are.
But at the same time,
we really like each other.
We enjoy each other's company.
I mean, dare I even say
we throw the word "love" out
around here.
PROBST:
So then, Drew,
how do you separate
voting somebody out
but spending all day with them,
being friendly?
So, the separation
is a complicated task--
and I'll be blunt--
that some people can do it
and other people can't.
Uh, and it's to different
degrees for everybody.
-PROBST: Which one are you?
-DREW: At first,
I was really caught up
in the relationships, and now,
as we get closer to the end,
I start to get a clearer vision
for that, you know,
million-dollar check,
and I'm sure that a lot of us
are starting to feel that way.
I know Julie is. You know,
I know some other people are.
All of us have families at home,
we have friends.
A million dollars
is going to mean the world,
not just in my life,
but in their lives, as well.
And that brings you back
to reality pretty quickly.
Dee, how do these relationships
complicate a vote so much?
Oh, man.
Honestly, like, I think
we all respect each other enough
to know that
we enjoy each other's company,
but at the same time,
we know we're all
lying to each other,
and someone's gonna
go home tonight
and everyone knows
except that person.
PROBST:
So does that mean that alliances
are locked in and you're lying
to who you're lying to
or does that mean the opposite:
that alliances
are not locked in?
That's why everybody's
lying to everybody.
Yeah. I think it's more
that alliances are not locked in
at this point.
We're getting to the stage
that you're starting to think of
the game versus
your personal relationships.
That's just the way it is
and we all accept it.
Drew, do you agree
alliances are not locked in?
Maybe I'm
the country bumpkin here,
but I feel like there are people
out here
who I'm 100% honest with.
I feel like I have alliances
I've locked in.
PROBST:
Drew, that's a very
confident statement.
So then, do you feel
like you're able
to look a little further ahead,
or is everything about tonight?
Um...
I think
if I get through tonight,
I have a clear vision
to the end.
Wow.
-Julie, that's a big statement.
-JULIE: Yeah.
PROBST:
Drew's saying,
"I get through tonight,
I see the end."
I'm jealous.
I-I'm in a different spot.
I mean, I'm in final six
and I might not make final five.
I hope I do.
But if I let my mind
go to final three,
I feel like I might lose focus
on just getting there.
PROBST:
Drew, it's really interesting
hearing that,
because if you survive tonight,
you just need to survive
one more Tribal,
and no one can vote you out.
And yet Julie can't even
see that far ahead.
That's how big the game
feels right now.
Yeah, I mean, there's a sense
in which Survivor
is like limbo, and the bar
is a different height
for everybody at every vote.
And so, we obviously could tell
Julie's feeling
the squeeze here,
and she's feeling like the bar
is so low that she'd have to
get on her hands and knees
just to see under it
-past this vote.
-PROBST: Julie.
Drew was very clear
-with his beautiful analogy
-JULIE: Yes. Yes.
that for you today,
limbo's difficult
-'cause the bar
is way down here.
-Right? Right?
And I'm hoping
that's not the case.
-Drew clearly thinks it is.
-JULIE: Right.
So I got to go into trust mode.
I have to.
It's almost like
that first day of high school
that you're hoping
your middle school friends
will be there for you or your
summer camp friends will be.
So I'm hopeful, but, like,
there's-there's bigger threats
than me.
I'm like, are you kidding me?
Like,
there-there's better play
out there.
There's got to be.
So that's kind of my plea.
Austin, what do you make
of Drew's analogy?
AUSTIN:
Yeah, I think
he's absolutely spot on.
Like, when you're worried
about where you are
in a given Tribal Council,
it's impossible to really think
far ahead, because you're just
trying to survive that one.
And once you do that, then
maybe things start opening up.
Whereas for Dee, obviously,
it's much, much,
much easier for her
to see,
"Okay, one more and I'm four,
and then that means
I'm very close to three."
So, 100%.
-Just another
solid analogy by Drew.
-[laughing]
Jake, Julie talks about
having a hard time seeing
past this vote.
How about you?
JAKE:
I mean, in this game,
you got to fight.
And I sympathize with Julie
'cause, you know,
I've been in that spot.
That's a tough spot to be in.
But look, Jeff,
the game is in overdrive
right now.
Like, we're looking at the end,
we're looking at each other
thinking like,
"All right, three people
"are gonna be on the jury.
"Three people are gonna
be sitting in final three.
How do we want that
to play out?"
Dee, has everybody
got their final three?
I think everyone
has their final three, yes.
However, I don't think
that the final three
that we all have in mind--
even my own--
will play out like that.
So you got to be prepared
for multiple options, for sure.
PROBST:
All right,
it is time to vote.
Katurah, you're up.
Can't go to the end against Mom.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
AUSTIN:
Yep.
Uh, this is an amulet that I got
when I was on a journey
with, uh, Kellie and, uh, J.
It started as a three-way
shared extra vote.
Now it's an immunity idol, but
I don't think I need any, uh,
souvenirs, so...
PROBST:
Playing this for yourself?
AUSTIN:
Um...
gonna play it on myself.
PROBST:
Okay.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast
for Austin will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Julie.
Julie.
Two votes Julie.
Drew.
Two votes Julie,
one vote Drew.
Drew.
We're tied. Two votes Julie,
two votes Drew.
Drew.
That's three votes Drew,
two votes Julie.
Thirteenth person voted out and
the sixth member of our jury.
Drew, need
to bring me your torch.
Drew, the tribe has spoken.
See you, Drew.
Time for you to go.
Congratulations on making it
to the final five.
Tonight, you will not be
returning to your camp.
You will be taken to a new
island where you will start over
and begin the final
push to the end
of Survivor 45.
Good luck.
Grab your torches.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
JAKE:
I'm focused
on a million dollars.
No one is going to say
that Jake ever gave up.
PROBST: Next time on the
season finale ofSurvivor...
DEE:
I'm literally unleashing myself.
My family's waiting for me
to come home
and tell them that I won.
JULIE:
I'm putting destiny
back in my hands.
PROBST:
Nothing about Survivoris easy!
KATURAH:
I'm at the finish line.
I can see it.
AUSTIN:
I need to make one final push.
We are in the endgame.
Oh, man.
I got totally blindsided.
It's a tragic, time-old story
of a young guy
who goes intoSurvivor
with a lot of brainpower
and a little bit
of too much confidence.
I'd love to tell you that, like,
Survivor
totally transformed me,
but it's a deeply ambiguous
experience that breaks you down,
and I'm hopeful that I'll be
given the opportunity
to grow, building off this.
[roars]