PROBST:
Everybody drop your Buffs.
-[exclaiming]
-Oh, Jeff!
We are switching tribes.
Previously onSurvivor...
AUSTIN:
Me and Drew, I feel, together,
we're stacked.
We've got an idol,
a Goodwill Advantage,
and we have
a Safety without Power.
SIFU:
I really don't have an idol.
That means Sifu
would have to
fight his way out.
Respectfully, I would kindly ask
that you write my name down
on the parchment.
I love you as a person,
but I hate you as a player.
First vote: Sifu.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor45: Sean.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Yeah.
SIFU: Yeah.
[laughs] Right.
Was it surprising to see yours?
Yeah, very much, but it was...
-DEE: Same thing.
-part of the game, I guess.
Exactly.
Tribal Council could not
have gotten any worse.
It should have been
Sifu going home.
But he's still here.
And now it's bad
because he's pissed
that one of us voted him,
which, yes, it was me.
[chuckles]
But...
we had the perfect plan
to get the person
out of our frickin' tribe
who has been causing chaos
this entire time.
This is the time where you need
to put your heart aside
and play the game.
What did you guys write?
I wrote Sean,
with a smiley face.
I wrote Sean, too.
I'm guessing Sean wrote Sifu.
No.
Sean said on the way out,
"I didn't vote for you."
-He said that to you?
-Mm-hmm.
I feel sick.
Who knew
that Sean's parting words
would be like,
"Didn't write your name down."
Why is he trying
to throw a grenade on us?
We were nothing but nice.
We were gonna save him.
So, if Sifu believes Sean,
then that means
one of us
wrote Sifu's name down.
We all think Sifu has an idol.
So next Tribal,
we all vote for Sifu,
he plays an idol,
Whoever he names is going home.
Yeah. It was bad.
No one here wrote Sifu?
I did not.
Did you write Sean?
I wrote Sean.
Well, there it is. [chuckles]
Maybe Sean voted Sifu.
...just think on that.
The vote that I got for me,
it's suspicious.
I'm looking left, looking right,
looking here, looking there.
These ladies deserve an Oscar,
because I can't tell
which one wrote my name down.
So I'm gonna
do some reconnaissance
and figure this out.
♪ ♪
We are so spent.
-All of us are so spent.
-AUSTIN: I know.
Well, PB and J
would help so much.
Savory, sweet,
nutty, soft.
AUSTIN: Day ten has got to be
the most difficult day yet
on Survivor.
No food.
Nothing.
AUSTIN:
I am starving.
And not only that,
like, I have no energy.
I always wondered what it'd
be like to die by starvation.
AUSTIN:
And all I want to do
is lay in camp,
and all I can
think about is food.
Can Jeff come up on a boat
with, like, a fruit platter?
Please.
We deserve food.
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
Chicken.
All-you-can-eat sushi.
A glass of merlot
and a bowl of vegetarian chili.
Fatty chocolate.
I would scrape peanut butter
into it with banana.
-Oh.
AUSTIN:
We just want food.
We're starving.
Oh, is that a worm?
Where?
Good eye.
Oh.
I hope it's a worm. Yeah.
AUSTIN:
Do it, do it, do it.
-I don't know!
-AUSTIN: SurvivorFactor.
You just put in your mouth and
you swallow it and it's done.
70% protein.
-It is?
-Mm-hmm.
30% poop.
Just kidding.
Am I gonna eat you?
As a kid, after it would rain,
I would go out
and I would save the worms.
I would take them
off of the sidewalk,
so nobody would step on them.
Oh, I don't know
if I want to eat this worm.
I'm a Libra.
I can't make up my mind.
But I'm so hungry
and I need protein.
Maybe it's 'cause I'm
ten days no food,
I'm getting a little...
[whistles] ...out here.
♪ ♪
[gagging]
Oh. Didn't go down.
No. Can't happen.
[groaning]
There goes my chance.
Bye. No. Uh-uh.
[sighs] Haunted forever.
Nope. Uh, toodly doodly not.
I, like, took it like a pill,
and then
it got stuck in my throat,
and I spit it back up.
-[Drew groans]
-BRANDO: Ew.
KENDRA:
It was disgusting.
Worm versus Kendra.
Worm one, Kendra...
DREW:
I thought Kendra
was gonna be, like,
yoga mama, astrology nerd,
you know, aunt.
She's exactly
like I was expecting.
She's a character.
She's a lot of fun to be around.
[burping]
Mm. There it is.
DREW:
She's got more energy than
anyone out here in the beach.
She's like a windup toy.
You spin the wheel,
and she goes... [babbling]
EMILY:
Kendra, how do you
have so much energy?
'Cause I'm happy.
Like, I just love being here.
It's nice to have
that presence in camp.
My motto is, "Whatever, man."
-EMILY: Yeah.
-I'm gonna be 31 in September.
30 fun.
DREW:
I might not ever
really fully understand
how Kendra thinks, but maybe
part of the magic
ofSurvivor is that
all of these different,
isolated worlds
collide together like marbles.
And that's really exciting.
Do you guys believe in aliens?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
We're the alien alliance.
-Oh, I like that.
-DREW: We're the E.T.
♪ ♪
Like, playing
my stomach like a bongo.
It makes a different sound now.
KALEB: Yeah.
-BRUCE: Y'all already?
-KELLIE: Yep.
Should we try one of the nets?
Yeah.
Thanks, Uncle Bruce.
[groans]
Mm.
♪ ♪
Dude, I...
-KELLIE: You okay?
-KATURAH: What's going on?
Dude, I passed out.
-I passed out.
-Did you fully pass out?
-BRUCE: You all right?
-Yeah, I'm good.
KELLIE:
Are you sure?
-Slow, slow, Jake.
-No, baby, I'm fine.
Slow and steady wins the race.
You did the same thing...
You're supposed
to laugh at me now, dude.
-I just fell. Laugh at me.
-I can't. I don't know
why I can't,
but I just can't right now.
Okay, well,
why don't you go ahead
-and sit down for a little bit.
-Yeah.
KELLIE: This morning,
we're all at camp,
and Jake pretty much
has a very similar episode
as to what happened
a couple days ago
at Belo,
where he stood up too fast.
♪ ♪
Oh, you good?
And he lost consciousness,
and then regains consciousness.
JAKE: No, I'm just pissed, dude,
that it happened again.
-KELLIE: You don't have
to be pissed.
-JAKE: Dude, I know,
but I'm doing fine in,
like, the challenges,
and I'm gonna pass out
just walking from here to there?
KELLIE:
You just stood up
too fast and got dizzy.
And your blood pressure dropped,
and that's why you passed out.
KELLIE:
I'm happy to step in like that.
That's just, like,
a natural thing for me to do
and-and try to have him
not go to that
worst-case scenario of,
"They're gonna
pull me out of the game,"
because that's
where his head was at.
Oh, dude,
I'm-I'm not mad at anyone here.
-I'm just mad at myself, dude.
-Don't worry, Jake.
I'm like,
"What the hell, dude?"
-Give yourself a break.
-[Jake mutters]
It would-it would just, like,
kill me, dude, for, like...
...me to do, like,
what I've done with my body
in the past two years, and then
just for it to, like, give out,
like, that would be, like...
Before I came out into
this game, I weighed 287 pounds.
When I was overweight,
I-I wasn't feeling
too great about myself.
I had a serious
binge eating problem.
And I know there's
a lot of people out there
who do that, and they just
don't talk about it,
and they try
to ignore their problems.
But you got to face them.
Like, I knew
what I was doing.
I didn't want to acknowledge it.
I ignored it. I hid it.
The day that everything
kind of turned around for me,
I'm eating in my car,
outside my parents' house.
My whole family's inside.
My mother comes out
to me and says,
"Jake, you don't
have to be embarrassed
"about what you're doing.
I love you no matter what."
And I just said to myself,
I'm just like,
"I'm not okay with this.
Like...
"I can do better. I'm...
"This isn't how
my life is meant to be.
I can overcome this."
And I... and I did.
I spent the last two years
working my ass off, man.
I started working really hard.
I felt better.
I do feel better.
Survivor's not
something I could have done
two years ago,
and it's been my absolute dream.
And the fact that
I was able to do that
and then come out here
and do this-- it's a celebration
of all my hard work
and everything I overcame.
I don't know, man.
Dude, I don't know. Yeah.
I just, I don't
want to get pulled, like...
I want to stay. Like, I want to
stay, dude, like, you can't...
So when I feel my body give out
and I realize that I passed out,
that's... [grunts loudly]
That's frustrating.
Like, to work so hard
on something
and then for it to be
the thing to give out,
that stabs me
right through the heart.
But if I'm
going out of this game,
I'm going out fighting,
not falling. I am
fighting my way
to the end of this game,
and I am fighting
to win.
I'm a survivor,
and I'm gonna survive.
♪ ♪
BRUCE: Yeah.
KALEB:
Cool, cool.
I came back to camp,
and the whole camp was empty.
Nobody was there.
Y'all want to all walk away
and not say anything to me?
I don't know where you're going.
I'm gonna
start looking for an idol.
I'm not gonna be just sitting
at camp, twiddling my thumbs
while everybody is gone.
I searched my ass off.
Like, I'm looking in every spot,
and it seems
like I'm still missing it.
So I start looking for an idol
in this really big,
obvious tree,
and, all of a sudden,
I hear Kaleb say...
Who is that?
Hey.
Where were y'all?
I throw my idol-searching stick
to the ground and I turn around
real quick, and I'm like,
"Oh, hey!"
Did you have any luck looking?
I just came back.
So I was gonna look for,
um, papayas.
♪ ♪
KELLIE:
Katurah is a hot mess out here.
I am concerned about Katurah.
Legitimately, she is sloppy.
We all caught her
looking in the tree today.
It couldn't
have been more obvious.
It's, like, very...
It's very obvious.
-Yeah.
-KELLIE: In front of everybody.
BRUCE:
There's nothing you can do.
Like, we now know her--
I don't want to say gameplay--
just temperament.
Like, it just is what it is.
You know?
KELLIE:
So I understand
Bruce's hesitation with her.
I have hesitations with her,
as someone who's, like,
a liability to play with.
Uh, my...
Did you see me
looking in the big tree?
Damn it.
Kaleb says, "I saw you
"searching for the idol
and I wanted to stop you before
everybody else got close."
And I was like,
"This feels like
a show-me action.
This feels like
a real alliance number."
-[laughs]
-All right.
KATURAH:
Let's do this. Okay.
KALEB: I'm a big fan
of the law of attraction,
but the most important
part of that is action.
It's the last part of the word.
-I want to work with you
long into this game.
-Yeah.
-Seriously.
-Me too. I love that.
[laughs] Yeah. Yeah, dude.
To me,
my focus has to be
one-to-one relationships.
I like this. [laughs]
KALEB:
You know, my superpower
is getting people
to work with me,
you know, and to build trust.
Just want to make sure
you're good,
-'cause you know you're good.
-I'm solid, man.
-All right.
-Yeah, we're, man...
We're so good.
But the one person I haven't
had a connection with is Kellie.
Every single person
wants to work with Kellie.
Kellie seems to be, like,
this person
who everyone is, like,
interested in talking to.
That is correct.
KATURAH:
I think the best thing
that we could do
is love up on Kellie.
KALEB:
If I could partner with Kellie,
that's where I'd actually have
the most control in this game.
I think...
Yeah.
There was an idol here.
Sabiyah had it.
-Sabiyah had it?
-Yeah, it's gone.
Bro, you're
dropping bombs right now.
KALEB:
I told Kellie
really valuable information.
It's one of the last nuggets
I was having in my pocket.
I want to
keep her as close
as possible, because
I think that Kellie's
the best player on this tribe.
And honestly, I feel it makes
the most sense for us to...
-Yeah.
-to kind of, like,
stick together.
-100%, dude.
Let's hug it out, man.
-Do you know what I mean?
And I want her to know that
Kaleb is not a name that needs
to get sung anytime soon.
♪ ♪
-JULIE: Mm-hmm.
I do believe that.
-DEE: Yeah.
See, now
I respect him even less.
I do too.
'Cause we had a plan,
and then to tell Sifu
that he didn't vote for him,
like, what does that do to us?
You blow up the game without you
being in the game, like...
-Yep.
-DEE: That's kind of messed up.
I-I can't respect that.
I can't fathom quitting.
I always go back to my why,
like, my family.
I think about them
every single day.
Like, they are the reason
why I want to succeed.
I was born in Cuba,
and I'm an immigrant,
so my parents brought my brother
and I to the United States.
And every time I think
that I'm starving out here,
I just try
to cut that thought out,
and I say, "Well, my parents
literally starved
in Cuba their entire lives until
they came to the United States."
Like, they had one piece
of bread for the entire family
and I'm out here, like,
at least drinking fresh water.
And they had
to carry buckets on their head
up flights of stairs every day.
They came from Cuba
without having anything.
So quitting, for me,
is not an option,
because I don't come
from a family that quits.
JULIE:
Yep.
DEE:
It was the most
perfect plan in the world.
J. MAYA:
It would have been so perfect.
[sighs]
And then we left
with the worst possible outcome.
JULIE:
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
♪ ♪
Yeah, there's
definitely a lot to unravel.
Interesting.
Seeing my name
was a big wake-up call.
It's like a dormant volcano,
but, man,
it was triggered last night,
and that volcano is like...
[grumbling]
Boom! Ready to go.
And I'm ready to rock and roll.
I just don't know who wrote who.
The game has begun.
♪ Dun, dun, dun.♪
I think all three
of the women are playing me,
but, uh,
I do have a trick up my sleeve.
I've got this fake idol.
It's actually pretty nice.
I put it together.
It's taken-taken a few days.
And I'm hoping that people can
believe that this idol is real.
Mm-hmm.
Shh.
Oh, that's huge.
JULIE: I do.
I mean, at least it'll
give me another day in the game.
It's aggressive.
It's not normally who I am,
but it's kind of the game
I have to play for Survivor.
This is, like,
one of those things, uh,
where the dealer's like,
"Hey, uh, you all in?"
And I'm like, "All in."
But I am trying to get
to the bottom of the Sifu vote.
You know, in tai chi we have
this thing called "push hands."
You ever heard of it?
...not let them throw you off.
It's really cool.
It's, like,
how you learn how to fight.
But you just take it slow.
♪ ♪
J. MAYA: Sifu pulls out this
tai chi metaphor about
when someone pushes you,
you have to push back.
So, yeah, you know,
I think Sifu is essentially
trying to tell me that
he thinks I put his name down.
For the record, I didn't.
But you know what?
At this point, I...
Sure. Sure.
♪ ♪
[burps] Ew.
[whistling]
She's cool.
-Kendra?
-Yeah.
Ten days, 24/7 Kendra
can also be a lot.
-[chuckles softly]
-Yeah.
Honestly,
I don't think I was ever
really that close to Kendra.
Um, when it comes to old Belo,
I think she and I had the
smallest connection. And so,
being out here with her
as my only lifeline--
it's kind of terrifying.
Because I don't really know
how much I can trust her
and we don't really have
that much that we can bond over.
Uh, I play Pokémon
competitively.
-[Brando gasps]
-Yeah.
-KENDRA: Yes.
-What?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, awesome.
BRANDO:
But Drew is super into Pokémon.
He's super nerdy, just like me.
-Legendaries and Raids
are one in 20.
-Mm.
Can you, like, transfer them?
Yeah, you can
transfer them to Home.
You get a special-colored
Magearna for doing that.
-That's cool.
-BRANDO: He's someone
that I spend a lot
of time nerding out with.
Pokémon Go, I think,
is permanent one in 400 odds.
Some of them are perma-boosted.
Masuda Method
is when you get a foreign Ditto.
Consistently catch something
back-to-back-to-back-to-back.
Dude, I honestly just, uh, pay
people to hack the guys I need.
-Oh, really?
-[laughs]
BRANDO:
So I'm just enjoying
his presence and so,
it'd be pretty cool
to work together.
We're kind of like
the smaller, nerdier people
on the tribe right now.
-Mm.
-It's not all that often
we get a whole bunch of nerds.
Do you think we get targeted
for being smart people,
come merge?
100%.
Nerds never
get to go far in this game,
and I'd like to change that.
I mean, I'd be open
to a nerd alliance.
I'm not gonna say I wouldn't.
I think Belo
is strong as a rock,
and I think that, uh,
until somebody from Belo
goes home, then it's, you know,
it's a false hope.
Nerd alliance.
I think it is garbage.
Brando is just about
the last person in the world
I want to work with,
because I don't want
six original Belos
standing together
as a strong unit
at the merge.
That's gonna be a disaster.
So I basically tell him, like,
"I don't buy this
for a second, dude."
Yeah, those are, those are not
music to my ears, those words.
Well, sorry,
I had bad news for you, man.
Because I would be open
to voting off a Belo
when the merge comes.
Drew kind of immediately
shuts it down, and if Drew's
not gonna be open
to an alliance with me,
then I'm gonna
have to work against him.
And my plan right now is to
solidify that bond with Kendra.
[hiccups]
-[hiccups]
-BRANDO: Right now,
the numbers are breaking down
with Drew and Austin
working together from old Reba,
Kendra and I working together
from old Belo,
and Emily in the middle
from old Lulu. So Emily's
sitting pretty right now.
Well, I think you're
in the best spot, to be honest.
Uh, I don't know about that.
-Really?
-Yeah.
EMILY:
Coming into the swap, clearly
I was the odd person out.
But old Belo are, right now,
fighting for the numbers.
They're looking out
at the post-merge world
and thinking
to themselves,
"Who can I have on my side?"
No way.
EMILY:
There's been lobbying
from both Reba and Belo--
the former members--
and I am
theoretically an asset
to both of them.
AUSTIN:
Like, right now,
We have the power to change
-this whole thing.
-Yeah.
Initially, I wanted
to work with Austin and Drew,
but if you
look at just the numbers,
old Belo
looks like the place to go.
How are y'all
feeling about tomorrow?
-KENDRA: I feel good.
-Yeah, I feel good, too.
I am, too. I am, too.
I feel terrible,
because I promised both sides,
"Hey, I'm with you.
I'm voting with you."
I think we have Emily in
a good spot with the two of us.
Yeah.
I think
she's in with us, though.
I think, with Emily,
we've laid all the groundwork.
EMILY:
I'm genuinely so torn.
I can see path forwards
with both of them, which is
a really scary thing, because it
just means that the pressure
is on
to make the right decision.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
Back in the day,
when we used to, you know,
ride dinosaurs...
KATURAH:
Bruce is a lot.
He's always gonna be a lot.
But when we first
got to Lulu, I saw
Bruce try to, like, hold down
his Bruces-ness, you know?
'Cause we're trying
to get to know Kaleb.
But you only need to give Bruce
a little bit of time
to get comfortable.
And once he's comfortable,
his Bruce-isms
just gonna come right back out.
What the hell is push presents?
...for ... creating life.
Presents now
for pushing out a baby?
-For creating life.
-Your present is the child.
That's your present. [laughs]
No, seriously,
you have push presents?
Like, enlighten me, children.
KATURAH:
I'm trying to hold it in,
but part of me is like, "Hello,
alert. Is anybody hearing
this crap that this man spews?"
Oh, same...
JAKE: You don't think
we should eat it today?
I mean, unless we can find
another papaya.
-JAKE: Huh?
-BRUCE: What are we...?
Maybe we just skip today.
Uh, that is...
I'm gonna be Bruce right now.
That is probably one of the d--
not the dumbest things.
-I'm sorry. Don't mean
to come across the wrong way.
-JAKE: [laughs] There he is.
KATURAH:
"Don't mean to come across
the wrong way, but...
dumbest ... I ever..."
Bruce immediately barks,
"That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard."
Something so ridiculously
rude and disrespectful.
We can't not eat anything.
Like, I... that I cannot do.
And if I'm coming across
aggressive, I do apologize,
but it's, like, let's think
above and beyond, like,
trying to be nice to each other.
-I agree. No need to be nice.
-KALEB: Yeah. I'm with that.
BRUCE:
What is wrong with you people?
It's a stupid idea.
Like, people my age,
we don't debate things.
"Do I jump off this cliff
or not?
"Uh, well, oh, I could die.
"I don't want to jump off it.
You think I should jump off it?
Oh, maybe I should jump off it."
KATURAH: Yeah.
Huh?
I think Kaleb is becoming more
and more aware of how Bruce is.
It gives me hope
that they may be finally
starting to see what
I've been saying since day two.
[laughs]
KALEB:
Bruce is a bossy leader.
He's saying,
"Hey, Kaleb, go find coconuts."
As I'm going fishing,
as I'm climbing trees
to get coconuts,
he's like, "Well, actually,
can you chop it, as well?"
BRUCE:
Yes, keep going.
No, no, no.
No, no. No. [laughs]
KALEB:
It's frustrating,
but if you can't bend a knee
to your enemies,
doesn't matter what you do,
they'll see you coming
from a mile away.
I want Bruce
to know that
I'll do anything he says,
because when
the time comes to strike,
my hope is that
he never sees it coming.
♪ ♪
...you and Dee
have to act like...
Okay.
J. MAYA:
I am operating
off the assumption
that Sifu has an idol.
And I think the high likelihood
is that if we lose a challenge,
we go to Tribal Council,
Sifu pulls out his idol,
votes me out.
And so my only lifeline
in this game
is convincing Sifu
that I'm on the outs
and that I'm the one
that voted for him
and that he doesn't
need to play his idol.
And so now I am going to
make myself the decoy.
You've got
to listen to J.'s plan.
...once before Tribal.
And I'll say,
"I think I'm on the outs
and I made a desperate move,
and it was me."
And then
hopefully that's enough
for him to buy that...
JULIE:
He doesn't play his idol.
-DEE: Yeah.
-JULIE: And we write Sifu three.
DEE:
Yeah.
J. MAYA:
What do you think?
-DEE: I like it.
-Okay.
-It's all we have.
-DEE: I like it.
-J. MAYA: Yeah.
-DEE: Right now,
it's operation
Throw J. Under the Bus.
It makes the most sense.
Sifu and her
don't have a good relationship.
But there's something
I've been thinking about,
and that is maybe
the smart move
is to flat-out vote J.,
once we do go
to the next Tribal Council.
She's been
at the bottom this entire time.
She hasn't been
in any strong alliances,
unlike Mama Julie and I.
And so I feel like
we have to be very strategic
in this next gameplay,
and we also
have to weigh out the options.
We got to, like,
talk about what's the best move.
Moving forward,
who can we trust more?
I know we want
to get his idol out...
Aah! So many ants.
But...
I don't know. I'm just
thinking different options.
♪ ♪
[mouths]
The plan was, we convince Sifu
that Dee, Sifu and I
are in an alliance and we're
all writing J.'s name down.
Part of me wants to say,
"Dee, let's just
write J.'s name down
and we're safe."
The other part of me says,
"If we really can convince him,
we send him home
with an idol in his pocket."
I don't know
what we're gonna do.
Man, this is tough.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Good morning.
Jeff.
PROBST:
Belo and Lulu,
getting your first look
-at the new Reba tribe.
-KENDRA: Oh.
PROBST:
Sean voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
All right. Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
Yeah!
First things first,
got to take back the idols.
Thank you, Kendra.
-Ah.
-[laughs]
-Thank you, Bruce.
-BRUCE: You're welcome.
-Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
-Ooh.
PROBST:
For today's challenge,
one at a time,
you're gonna
race through a massive
three-level obstacle course,
collecting keys along the way.
Once three players are through,
the remaining player
will use those keys
to release a long hook.
You'll use the hook
to get your sandbags.
You will then race to fire
those sandbags at three targets.
First two tribes
to knock down all three targets
win immunity,
you are safe from the vote.
-In addition...
-Oh, yeah.
-...playing for a reward.
-There it is.
-Yeah!
-[excited chatter]
-KALEB: Jeff. Come on. Show us.
-JAKE: Let us see it.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
-Yeah!
-Yes!
PROBST:
First tribe to finish...
-KENDRA: Oh, my God!
-[excited chatter]
-JAKE: That's fish. Fish.
-BRUCE: Fish!
KENDRA:
Oh, my God. Oh, my...
Ten fresh fish...
[exclaiming]
...and everything
you need to cook them.
Those are big boys.
Second tribe to finish, smaller,
-will still
put something in the belly.
-DEE: All right.
That still looks good.
-That's a lot.
-Wow.
Last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers,
Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the fifth person
voted out of Survivor45.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Reba, you are playing
to get yours back.
All right, sit-outs.
Belo, one extra person.
Cannot sit out the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Emily's gonna sit it out.
All right, Lulu,
who's gonna be your sit-out?
Okay.
-Kellie. Oh, you don't look
happy about that.
-KELLIE: That's okay.
Whatever the team needs,
I'll do it.
PROBST:
All right, Kellie's
gonna sit out for Lulu.
Sit-outs,
take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
♪ ♪
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
-KELLIE: Go, Kaleb! You got it!
Kendra, Kaleb and Sifu
out of the gate first.
-JAKE: Let's get it, Kaleb.
-KELLIE: Let's go.
JAKE:
Come on, Kabe, you got it.
PROBST:
You're collecting three bags...
-BRANDO: You got this, Kendra!
-PROBST: ...in order.
-DREW: Great pace, great pace.
-One, then two,
then three.
Kaleb has his first bag.
That's how you do it, Kaleb!
PROBST:
Kaleb heading up top.
There goes Sifu.
There's Kendra with hers.
Nice, nice. Keep it up!
PROBST:
Kaleb up top first.
It's Lulu in the early lead.
There's Sifu, now Kendra.
It's a giant maze
of an obstacle course.
There goes Kaleb quickly now,
extending his lead.
-BRUCE: Good job!
-PROBST: You're good, Kaleb.
KELLIE:
All right, Kaleb. Let's go!
Great job. Let's go.
-PROBST: Kaleb.
-JAKE: Yeah, buddy!
-Go, Lulu!
-Go!
Go, Reba!
-Go, Belo!
-KENDRA: You got it, Austin!
PROBST:
It is Austin now on the course
for Belo,
while Katurah for Lulu,
and J. for Reba.
DEE:
You got it, J.
PROBST:
J. has her first.
Katurah has her first.
-Austin has his first.
-DREW: Great job, Austin.
Now you're going up the ladder.
JAKE:
Here you go,
here you go, here you go.
J. working on bag number two
for Reba.
-JAKE: Go, baby! Go!
-PROBST: Katurah working
for Lulu.
Austin ripping
through those knots
for bag number two for Belo.
It is now Reba in the lead.
J. is really working
this course.
-Way to go, J.!
-PROBST: Got to get
all the way back, J.
Go, Reba! Go, Belo!
-Here we go.
-Go!
-Go, Lulu!
It is now Brando
on the course for Belo.
-KENDRA: Go, Brando!
-PROBST: Bruce for Lulu.
-JAKE: There you go.
-KELLIE: Let's go, Bruce!
...Dee for Reba.
-[whooping]
-PROBST: It is now Reba
in the lead.
Dee working for that second bag.
Brando right on her tail,
and there's Bruce in it.
JAKE:
Yeah, baby!
Everybody at the same spot
on the course now.
Dee, having to stretch.
-Bruce has his.
-JAKE: Yeah, buddy!
PROBST:
Brando still working for Belo.
SIFU:
Go! Go! All the way. Three.
-Keep going, keep going.
-Quick, quick, quick.
Stay on that level.
PROBST:
Bruce heading back down.
It's Lulu back in the lead.
-Nice work!
-You're good, Lulu! Go!
-Right there, right there.
-PROBST: You're good, Reba.
-Go!
-SIFU: That's it, Mama.
You're looking
for the one key you need
to release that hook.
Julie has it with the first bag.
Got a little
Survivorluck there.
Nice, nice, nice.
Come on. Come on.
PROBST:
You're good, Belo! Go!
You got to get all the rope off,
and then you pull that rope
and release your sandbags.
KELLIE:
That's what
I'm talking about, Jake!
PROBST:
Jake has his free.
He can start now.
-We're good, we're good.
-We're good?
Do they have the keys?
Don't worry about that. Breathe.
PROBST:
But it is Reba in the lead.
[overlapping chatter]
J.:
Push forward.
Push forward and then back.
-Julie is very close.
-DEE: Pull it down.
-Pull! Pull! Pull!
-Pull it down!
-Yes!
PROBST:
There it is.
You're good, Reba.
DEE:
Let's go, baby. We got it.
PROBST:
Now they've got to relay
with those sandbags.
Go, Reba!
-There we go.
-Drew has his hook free.
He can start working.
-Belo's now in it.
-That's okay.
-Spin! Spin! Spin!
-PROBST: Jake very close.
-KELLIE: There you go, Jake!
-Pull!
-PROBST: You're good. Pull it.
-Yes!
There it is, Lulu! You're good!
Go down there,
go down there, go down there.
KELLIE:
Beautiful.
That's what I'm talking about.
PROBST:
You got to get all your bags
in your bin
before you can
move on to this next phase
of firing the sandbags
to your targets.
-Right here. Go!
-Now you're good, Reba!
Drew still working to release
the sandbags for Belo.
Yeah.
Immunity on the line.
Drew feeling the pressure.
-Pull! Pull!
-DREW: I am.
-Let's go. Go.
-Come on.
-Drew releases for Belo.
-[overlapping chatter]
Here goes Bruce. Here goes J.
J. a little low.
Bruce with a big shot.
Each player's got
to knock down one target.
SIFU:
Yeah. Go a little more back.
Right there. Yeah!
-SIFU: Yeah!
-JULIE: Yeah!
-J. does it for Reba.
That's one.
Bruce for Lulu.
Bruce just misses.
Here goes Dee for Reba.
There's another one for Reba!
It now comes down to Sifu.
He's got to knock off the
third target for Reba to win.
JAKE:
Here we go, Bruce.
PROBST:
Here goes Bruce.
And he's got one for Lulu.
Here comes Katurah
-for Lulu.
-JAKE: Here we go, Katurah.
PROBST: Austin trying
to get through those knots
-to release his slingshot...
-EMILY: You got it, Austin!
so Belo can get in this.
Belo has not been
to Tribal Council
yet this season.
-[overlapping chatter]
-Austin just misses.
Sifu could win it right here.
[indistinct shouting]
PROBST:
There it is!
-Reba wins immunity!
-[cheering]
Safe from Tribal Council.
We're looking for one more.
PROBST:
Austin trying to get Belo in it
with a long toss.
Just misses.
-Go! Come on, kid. You got it.
-There you go, there you go!
-Yes!
-KELLIE: More!
Pull! Pull! Nice!
-KALEB: Got it.
-PROBST: There it is.
-Katurah knocks one over
for Lulu.
-Yeah, girl!
Lulu down to their last target.
-PROBST: Kendra going
to come in for Belo now.
-You got it, Belo!
All right, man. You got this,
man. This is all you!
-There goes Kaleb
for the win for Lulu.
-Send it home!
Kaleb has a lot of time.
-JAKE: Yeah!
-PROBST: And he does it!
Lulu wins immunity,
safe from Tribal Council,
sending Belo to Tribal Council
for the first time.
You've got this. Good job.
Good job.
Reba, congratulations.
Immunity is yours, as well
as the return of your flint.
Lulu, once again,
immunity is yours.
Nobody going home
from your tribe, Kellie.
In addition, reward
waiting for you back at camp.
Reba, ten freshly-caught fish.
Lulu, five freshly-caught fish.
Before we go,
there is one more twist today.
We're gonna take a journey.
Reba, because
you finished first,
you are in charge of who goes.
You're gonna choose one person
from each of the three tribes
to go on a journey.
You will return back to
your camp before Tribal Council.
Take a moment, figure out
who you're gonna send
and then I want to hear why.
I'm sorry.
PROBST:
All right, let's start there.
From Reba, who won
the rock, paper, scissor?
-I did, Jeff.
-And that means you're going?
-That does.
-All right, J. going from Reba.
Now as a group, you're deciding
who's gonna go from Lulu.
-Kellie.
-PROBST: Kellie. Why Kellie?
We just saw her face
when she sat out...
-Oh.
-Yup.
Thanks, guys.
That's very sweet.
All right, one decision left,
Reba.
Who from Belo?
Knowing they're gonna
vote somebody out tonight,
this could have big impact
on what happens.
Who did you decide and why?
We picked Austin, Jeff.
PROBST:
Austin. Why Austin?
Um, well, well, we know Austin,
and I'm curious
to see what information
he can give us
from the other side.
PROBST:
So that's about
getting information in the game?
-[Austin scoffs]
-J.: It's about
many things, Jeff,
-but maybe that's one of them.
-PROBST: All right.
J., Kellie, Austin, grab your
stuff. You're heading out now.
Boat's gonna
take you on your journey.
-See y'all.
-PROBST: Austin will be back
in time for Tribal Council.
[Austin sighs]
Reba, Lulu,
grab your stuff, head out.
No Tribal Council tonight.
Nobody going home.
SIFU:
Watch your head. Watch.
KALEB:
Best of luck, you guys.
JAKE:
Good luck, guys.
All right, Belo,
as a penalty for losing--
sorry for you--
I got to take your flint.
Thank you, Emily.
All right, Belo,
grab your stuff, head out. See
you tonight a Tribal Council,
where somebody will be the fifth
person voted out of Survivor45.
EMILY: Wow. Feels like
it's par for the course
for me now
that we lose
the immunity challenge.
I've been to every single Tribal
Council except for one so far,
and it's not fun.
And now I have to make a really,
really tough decision.
♪ ♪
♪ I don't like this part
of the game, hey!♪
-This is the whole reason
we're here.
-I know.
This first time for me going
to Tribal Council--
it's almost unreal
that I could be
leaving this game tonight.
So we're gonna
do chaotic scrambling
or organized scrambling?
DREW:
I got a lot of respect
for you guys.
We could do it in,
like, an orderly way.
-Yes.
-That would be less stressful.
BRANDO:
We take turns. Everybody gets
to talk to everybody.
Yeah, maybe.
Let's get ready to scramble.
KENDRA:
While Austin's off on a journey,
we decide that we're gonna
take a very, uh,
respectful scramble.
-I truly think me, you,
and Brando are the three.
-Okay.
Well, I feel the most secure
about us three
voting through tonight.
Okay. Awesome.
Then let's do it.
And, like, I don't want
to get rid of Austin.
-Yeah.
-God forbid there's
physical challenges.
I don't want to be the worm,
but Drew's the worm tonight.
He's got to go.
He's not that big of an asset.
He's tall, he's lanky,
and he's running out of steam
really quickly.
So how-how sure do you feel
that, like,
we can get Brando
in on this three for this vote?
-Yeah.
-You really think so?
Like, 100%? He's not gonna,
like, turn on us for...
-I really don't think so.
-Okay.
It's gonna be you, Austin,
and Emily versus me and Kendra.
And so, my proposal to you...
...is that I will give you
my Shot in the Dark
if you are willing
to keep me instead of Kendra,
and... on my side...
-There's no need.
-Okay.
-Really?
-There's no need.
-Okay.
BRANDO:
When I tell Drew that I'm open
with voting for Kendra,
it's a flat-out lie.
I'm just hoping
that he'll trust me and
maybe keep my name
off his parchment tonight.
But I do think she's
gonna be a much bigger threat
-come merge.
-I agree.
BRANDO:
The truth is, Kendra is someone
that I definitely
want to work with.
You know,
working with her will help
keep my old
Belo alliances intact.
And I'm feeling really good
about working with Emily, but
I'm gonna do anything
that it takes.
I'm gonna lie to people
in order to get to day 12.
-Shake on it?
-All right. Yeah.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
[laughs]
I really like you, man.
DREW:
Brando was interesting
because the guy
did not even put a fight.
Immediately, he says,
"Let it be Kendra."
Hello!
Are you gonna take a break
or do we want
to do the next round
of speed dating?
DREW:
So right off the bat,
my suspicions are raised
because you got
to give up a little more fight.
And so, I'm thinking, "Okay,
he's playing me."
Kendra pitched me on you.
I mean, Brando and I just had
a very interesting conversation.
Oh, really? What did he say?
Brando said that
he wants to work with,
um, us four and take out Kendra.
Interesting.
Drew said that
Brando approached him and said,
"Why don't the four of us
work together
to vote out Kendra?"
-Okay. Whatever.
-All right.
EMILY:
I'm so confused
because I thought Kendra
and Brando were like that.
Yeah.
-makes me kind of afraid
that, like...
-Uh-uh.
That's funny.
That's what he told me.
So I guess he's trying
to say that it was my move.
-Interesting.
-Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
EMILY:
According to Brando,
voting Kendra was Drew's idea.
According to Drew, that's
Brando's idea, and it makes
a lot more sense to me that Drew
would be the one pitching it
as opposed to Brando
since Brando and Kendra
are obviously so tight.
So, Drew is not off
to a great start with me
if he's already
lying to me about
who is pitching which ideas.
But what did he say to you?
He said that, uh,
Brando had approached him,
and Brando had suggested
the four of us work together
to vote you out.
He made it seem like
it was Brando's idea.
... for throwing my name
out there so hard.
It flat-out
just doesn't make sense.
KENDRA:
Man, that makes me so mad.
I have, like,
a rage burning inside me.
When I heard my name,
I just wanted to...
[hisses]
...reach out
like a cat in a trash bag.
[imitates yowling, hissing]
[yowling]
Aah!
I feel like
a little pit bull terrier.
[growls, barks]
Ah. I need a mantra.
Oh, I remember my mantra.
Whatever, man.
But it's all good
'cause I'm gonna put my trust
in Brando and Emily this evening
to vote Drew out.
Hopefully, I'm sitting there
with my torch still lit tonight
and I say,
"Bye-bye. You thought you
tricked me, but I tricked you."
[hisses]
♪ ♪
-All right.
-Wow.
-Oh, well.
-This is so exciting!
-What could it be?
What could it be?
-I've actually thought...
-KELLIE: Oh, my God.
-AUSTIN: And...
KELLIE:
Me and two Rebas.
I arrive on the beach with
two people I've never met
and two original Reba members.
So I kind of
feel like the odd man out
a little bit, but...
it's a good opportunity for me
to learn a little bit
about them and, you know,
potentially
make some new allies.
Ooh.
Okay. I'm excited for the hike.
-All right.
-KELLIE: Let's do it.
That's a tall mountain.
J. MAYA: Oh. Wow.
[laughing]: I take back
my excitement, actually.
[Austin whoops]
J. MAYA:
Kellie and Austin and I
are hiking up this
ridiculously uphill mountain,
and by the time
we get to the top,
we are physically exhausted.
And we turn over
the crest of the mountain,
and the first thing we see is...
KELLIE:
Oh, my God, guys.
-Sandwiches.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my goodness.
-Oh, my goodness.
-No. Sandwiches?
Oh.
No.
KELLIE:
Okay.
Oh, my God.
-Okay.
-All right.
KELLIE:
Okay.
That's wild.
I'll be straight-up.
I'm leaning sandwich.
-Really?
-You really just want
to do sandwiches?
I'm trying to fight
for food right now.
-I know.
-So I'm not trying
to play any crazy games.
-I know. It's hard. I know.
-You know what I mean? So...
AUSTIN:
All I can think about is food.
My stomach is caved in.
I am starving.
♪ ♪
And these amulets
don't have much power.
In fact, I view them more
as a disadvantage
because you need to use
these amulets together, and
it upgrades every time
one of the three amulets
is taken out of the game.
The last thing I need is
to make my target even bigger.
So you don't want to get
the amulet because you're afraid
it's gonna put
a bigger target on your back?
Pretty much, yeah.
And on all of us
'cause then we have incentives
to knock each other out.
What do you think, J.?
[laughing]: So...
KELLIE:
What?!
I am not gonna
make this decision.
-No, no, no, it's fine.
-No way.
It's fine.
KELLIE:
I am smack-dab in the middle.
This is an extremely
tough call for me.
Like, it definitely feels
like angel and devil
on the shoulder,
where the angel is like,
"Kellie, just eat the sandwiches
and stay the safe course."
And the devil is like,
"You need this advantage."
This is new-eraSurvivor.
Are you really
going to make the entire way
through this game and not have
any sort of extra power?
I'm really pretty
split down the middle.
But, you know, this is a once...
maybe the only opportunity
we're gonna get.
AUSTIN:
I want the sandwiches.
And I am absolutely famished.
I am so hungry.
And J.'s like,
"I want the strategy,"
leaving Kellie right in
the middle to make up her mind.
This is a difficult decision.
I will say,
the reason
I'm interested in using
the amulets is 'cause, like,
I want to keep my options open.
-Mm-hmm.
-And we can make a pact.
No one touches the other until
seven players left in the game?
-Mm-hmm.
-If y'all want amulets...
-KELLIE:
I'm down with that, too.
-J. MAYA: Okay.
KELLIE:
I mean, I like both of you guys.
AUSTIN:
But I could tell she was
leaning towards the strategy,
so I didn't want
to be the guy saying,
"No, no, no. I don't want
to work with you all.
I want my sandwiches."
Like, I have to convince them
that I'm down to play strategy.
You know, like,
"Let's all work together
and use this stupid
extra vote between
the three of us,"
even though we're never gonna
agree on one person to vote out.
-[laughing]
-So this is a newborn alliance.
-There you go.
Yay! I like it!
AUSTIN:
In my head, it's like,
"This is not
"a symbol of an alliance.
This is absolutely
a symbol of war."
-KELLIE: All right...
-Let's get some amulets.
AUSTIN:
All right.
I need to be the first
to strike to take them down.
I'm turning this
into a full-blown idol.
They're gonna get my revenge
for getting in between me
and that freaking sandwich.
Oh, my gosh.
Back to starving.
[J. Maya laughs]
-KELLIE: Sorry, Austin.
-AUSTIN [laughing]: It's okay.
You know, I think allies
are worth more than food, so...
KELLIE:
Aw.
This has been
my best Survivorday.
This has got to be, uh,
probably the worst day
in my Survivorcareer.
♪ ♪
EMILY: If we're gonna
move forward together,
I really want us
to be 100% honest.
-DREW: Okay.
-And my conversation
with Brando was,
"Drew basically told me, like,
'Hey, I wanted the four of us
to vote on Kendra.'"
But I'm not sold
on that idea at all.
Brand... That's what Brando
pitched-- the four of us.
And I said, "Of cour..."
I said, "Sure,"
because, I mean,
what was I gonna say, "No"?
But that's what he pitched.
-I don't think that's the truth.
-What do you mean?
Are you the one
throwing out all this stuff?
-No, no. They said that to me.
-Really?
Yes. I promise you.
I promise you.
Emily says, "Oh, you told Brando
that the four of us are
all gonna vote Kendra."
And she's like,
"I don't think you're being
completely truthful to me."
What are you talking about?
What would I lie about?
I don't know who to trust, and
I need people
that I can, like, trust.
-Sorry. I don't mean...
-No, it's okay.
-It's okay. I mean,
I'm glad that we're talking.
-Yeah.
DREW:
That is the moment
that I begin to question
whether or not I really
could be going home tonight.
Like, it's the first time
that it pops in my head
that she could swing the
other way, and it's terrifying.
I'm being 100% with you.
I really am.
I'm being 100% with you, too.
-Literally,
there's no point in lying.
-Yeah.
-What is... what is...?
-I understand.
-Okay, well, let's go back.
-Yeah. I agree.
DREW:
You know, I did all I could
to set things up
and tell her I trusted her,
to a mixed effect, but
I really am counting on my guy
Austin to solidify things and
to make sure that we're 100%.
BRANDO:
Hello.
-How are you?
-I am so freaking exhausted.
-Yeah?
-That was the worst journey
of all time.
Oh, no.
AUSTIN:
Come back to the Belo beach.
I'm thinking,
"I wonder what's happening
back at camp.
Who's scrambling?
What's the plan?"
Did Kendra and Brando
somehow win over Emily?
And not only that.
How am I gonna
keep my story straight?
Here's what happened.
So, you have two options.
-DREW: Okay.
-One is sustenance.
Everybody gets a sandwich.
And the other one is this, like,
sweat strategy where you work
together to bring up
ten bags of coconuts within
an hour, and if you do that,
you get some sort of advantage.
So I was like,
"I want the sandwiches."
-But it was majority vote.
-Yeah?
AUSTIN:
What I lied to them about
was the whole idea
that we had to carry coconuts
up and down this hill
and that we failed at that,
and we didn't get any advantage.
-It was just a miserable
experience, overall.
-Oh, Austin.
AUSTIN:
Lying to my tribe--
it's not ideal, but
my best buddy
in this game, Drew,
is someone I can totally trust.
-Drew,
I wasn't entirely truthful.
-What does it say?
-DREW: Mm. So, basically,
we have to...
-All three of us
have to combine,
and we get one extra vote.
Well, we just basically have
to vote them out.
-Exactly.
-Okay, good to know.
Should I tell Emily?
I was leaning towards "yes"
to telling her,
but what do you think?
They're coming for me right now.
Brando and Kendra
with Emily in the middle.
And she was like, "I don't think
you're being honest with me."
I was like,
"What are you talking about?"
AUSTIN:
Drew's a little bit nervous
that maybe he's gonna
go home because
Emily might not be as 100%
as we originally thought.
So I should tell her about this?
I think you should tell her.
AUSTIN:
So right now, in Drew's pocket,
he has a Safety without Power.
So if things get wacky,
he could use it,
dip out at Tribal Council
and not have to worry
about getting voted out.
On the other hand,
I have a one-time use idol
which I can extend the power of
by sacrificing my vote,
while at the same time
using my second advantage,
which is a Goodwill Advantage,
which restores the vote.
Dude, it would be a breaking
of a potentially epic duo.
We're gonna win over Emily.
I do not want
to use these advantages yet.
But the big question tonight is
do we trust Emily
to work with us
or do we need to use
all of our advantages
out of our pockets
to ensure our safety?
Like, I had a moment of doubt
with Drew because
-Brando was, like,
telling me some lies.
-Uh-huh.
And I thought that the lies
were coming from Drew,
-but they're coming from Brando.
-Drew mentioned that.
Yeah, and so,
I didn't know who to believe.
Brando's, like, playing.
I want this Tribal Council
to go away.
I'm extremely torn right now
between voting out Brando
or Drew tonight.
I'm worried it's gonna
be me tonight, but, uh...
be me tonight,
so we're in the same boat.
EMILY:
I want to position myself
well for a potential merge,
but seems like
no matter which direction I go,
I am burning some bridges,
either with the old Reba tribe
or the old Belo tribe.
-Battle of the nerds out here.
-Yeah.
EMILY:
I'm worried that if I vote out
an old Belo member,
that the Belo tribe
will easily turn against me.
So, the journey--
I was 90% truthful.
There was a choice. It's a very
underwhelming one, but if
-we had to vote all together
-I've seen this before.
-Yeah, they had this
in the past.
-to get one extra vote.
Yeah.
But on the flip side, I
genuinely do feel a connection,
especially with Austin,
even though
he got some sort of advantage.
But Drew seems to be
more of a game player.
So I'm really torn right now
between the part of my brain
that's like,
"Go with the numbers,"
and the part of brain
that's like, "Go with your gut."
Now it's about who actually
has my best interest at heart.
I keep flip-flopping in my mind,
and I'm scared the sun is going
down, and I still don't know.
♪ ♪
If this is your first time
at Tribal Council,
grab a torch,
dip it in the flame
and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
of Tribal Council because,
in this game,
fire represents your life.
And when your fire is gone,
so are you.
Brando, you're nodding.
When you hear those words,
do they sound different when
it's you sitting on that stool?
You know, as a player,
you never want to be here.
But as a self-proclaimed
superfan,
when I hear you saying
those words,
and when I'm looking
at the, you know,
beautiful ambiance
of Tribal Council,
it's really hard
not to be in awe.
PROBST:
Austin, what is that?
Because I hear it a lot,
and I do get it.
It's the thrill
of playing Survivor.
But this ambiance,
this fire that can be romantic
and kind of cool,
is death until
somebody is crowned a winner.
AUSTIN:
Every cycle,
it ends right here.
This is the ultimate moment
where everyone puts their pen
to the paper
and decides
what exactly happens.
PROBST:
And Emily, does
having been to Tribal Council
give you a leg up,
just generally speaking?
To some extent,
I think I'm calloused from it.
And heading
into the ringer again,
you've mentally prepared
yourself for the battering cage
that is Tribal Council.
But I'll tell you,
at this point, Jeff,
I'm over it.
Clearly, I'm on tribes--
I might be the problem--
where I keep losing. [laughs]
Brando,
let's go back to the switch.
Part of the design
of the new era is
to constantly make you check and
assess and adapt all the time.
So when you see a tribe swap,
and how do you handle that?
Um, you know,
it was heartbreaking to know
that I wouldn't be with that
many of my old Belo members,
but I think new Belo is honestly
where the focus
of everybody else was pointed,
and we're the only tribe
that has relationships
that span to everyone else
in the game.
And I think having
those relationships and having
that experience with old Belo,
for example,
is something that
makes me pretty valuable.
Drew, that's a pitch.
DREW:
Yeah, it definitely is, Jeff.
If somebody's
very well-connected,
that could be useful
for me as a guy trying
to make my way through
a very complicated merge.
But it also could be
threatening
because
they're so established that
I have no room going forward
with them.
BRANDO:
It does also mean that
I have knowledge of the cracks.
It's having that knowledge
of those relationships
that I think is valuable,
not just that they exist.
Kendra, the other, obviously,
tricky part about Tribal is
sometimes players send a message
with what they're saying.
Sometimes they're distracting
with what they say.
You don't know
until you get to the very end,
and all
the secrets are revealed.
I hate it. [laughs]
I'm a pretty independent person.
I don't often trust people
that heavily in my own life.
So, where my fire, my life,
my passion in this game
relies on people here
who I've had conversations with
is absolutely terrifying to me.
Drew, when you hear
somebody tell you something
that's very vulnerable,
does that change
how you would treat Kendra
or could you still lie to Kendra
because this is not
our real life,
we come here to play a game?
Yeah, absolutely,
and I came into this tribe
not expecting
to get along with Kendra,
and we kind of bonded
over being open
about who we were.
And so, that level
of personal investment
kind of steeps the decision
I've got to make today
because, like,
I'm not betraying a chess piece.
I'm betraying, like,
a real person
who I have had a tremendous,
unexpected bond with.
And that is a tough thing to do
and it's not something
that I'm accustomed to doing
in my real life, either.
Emily, how about for you?
When you hear that,
any impact on you? Why do you
laugh when I ask you?
Oh, 'cause I hate
to be the contrarian,
but I... I, of course, am,
and, you know,
we come into this game
acknowledging the fact
that we're gonna
get to know people
for the genuine people
that they are
and then backstab them.
In the game of Survivor,
it's about survival.
PROBST:
So, Austin, are we past
the part of tribe strength?
Have you already
started shifting
into relationships
when we merge?
Oh, definitely. I mean,
we know that there's cracks both
in original Belo
and original Reba.
And what we have to do
is figure out
what group we can move forward
into the merge with
that's gonna work with us
not just for one vote
or two vote,
but for the long haul.
And that's ultimately
what my vote is coming down to.
So, Drew, tonight's vote
is about what for you?
DREW:
Oh, it's tough. I look down
the periscope,
and I see this big battle ahead.
Tribes coming together
and colliding
and ripping each other apart.
And my vote right now is based
on best positioning myself
for that.
Not for, like, going forward
as a group of five or four,
but on surviving
this coming onslaught.
PROBST:
Emily, are you
in the middle of this?
Because I hear talk
of Reba and talk of Belo.
I don't hear talk of this five.
It's odd, Jeff, because when
I'm doing that calculation about
where I'm going to be, look,
I haven't had an alliance
in this game.
I'm sitting here at Tribal
Council for how many times now?
For me, it's kind of like
when you analyze stocks.
There's this qualitative
and quantitative component
where you're doing the numbers
on it, right?
Who has the majority,
who has whom, and you're trying
to calculate
who could vote where.
But there's also
this qualitative component
of who can I trust?
And that's kind of what I need.
That nice mix
between the qualitative
and the quantitative,
moving into a potential merge.
Um, this is
the only opportunity where
we really get to put our money
where our mouth is
in the game of Survivor,so I
actually look forward to proving
-that loyalty.
-All right, with all that said,
it is time to vote.
Brando, you're up.
♪ ♪
Wow.
[sighs]
This is my idol,
and I'm going
to sacrifice my vote
in order to extend the lifespan
of this idol.
But...
with this...
bad boy right here...
[sniffs, sighs]
...Goodwill Advantage,
I'm gonna restore my vote.
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Drew.
Brando.
One vote Drew,
one vote Brando.
Drew. Two votes Drew,
Brando. We're tied.
Two votes Drew,
two votes Brando,
one vote left.
Fifth person
voted out of Survivor45...
...Brando.
Need to bring me your torch.
-BRANDO:
Hey, well played, y'all.
-What?
Well played.
-EMILY: Good job, Brando.
-Good playing.
Brando, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Hey, one of y'all
win it for me.
-Good job, Brando.
-I love you all.
-Good luck.
-KENDRA: Love you.
-EMILY: Love you.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
[whooping]
SIFU: It's crazy.
With 13 people, this is
psychological warfare.
[yelling]
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
Yeah.
We've entered a new stage
of the game,
and we could just squash them.
KALEB:
I'm not Batman.
I'm the Canadian. You know?
Playing Survivor
is absolutely unbelievable.
And I got to meet all
of these amazing people
and learn so much about myself.
I can push myself to limits
that I never thought
that I could.
And as someone who, you know,
wasn't the most social
kid growing up,
being out here
with a bunch of strangers,
learning about them
and just being vulnerable
is something that, you know,
I wouldn't trade for anything.
[roars]