Back in the day
when we used to ride dinosaurs.
KATURAH:
Hello? Is anybody hearing
this crap that this man spews?
JEFF PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
BRUCE:
Clock's ticking, heart's racing
'cause I want Katurah
to be left out.
Boom. Immunity idol, baby.
[laughs]
We did it. We did it.
-We did it.
-KALEB: Right now,
we have 13 people.
We have six original Reba,
five original Belo,
and two original Lulu.
We got to watch out for this
dude because he's conniving.
BRUCE:
Kaleb-- he's dangerous.
Sorry, you got to go.
All right, Jeff, I do have
one last thing I'm gonna try.
Kaleb, you are...
-No way!
-...safe.
[all clamoring]
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor 45--J.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
KELLIE:
Oh, my God.
That's got to be one of the
craziest Tribal Councils ever.
KALEB:
Let me officially say it.
We made it to the merge.
-[cheering, applause]
-Let's go! Come on!
Whoo! Holy...
People at home would call me
a pretty lucky guy,
and tonight
they are absolutely correct.
I appreciate everybody, as well,
like, the respect, compassion
the whole time,
letting me fight at the day,
Tribal Council.
It's easy to bully the guy
at the bottom, it feels like.
I just appreciate
the way you guys handled it.
I know it's 12 votes,
but we'll be okay.
-We'll be all right.
-KENDRA: Kaleb,
nothing but respect.
KALEB: Tonight
they tried to write me off.
Every single person on this
entire tribe voted against me.
Has that ever happened--
12 votes against...?
EMILY:
This might be a record.
KATURAH:
I think this isa record.
Dude, that's insane.
That's insane.
I know. I'm so lucky.
KATURAH:
I was completely shocked.
When he said "safe,"
my mouth dropped.
KALEB:
The first time
a Shot in the Dark
has been played correctly,
when somebody was supposed
to go home.
First time 12 votes have ever
been canceled out,
and I was this close
to going home.
So, big picture--
I have a couple of people
I think I can maybe trust,
but ultimately
I don't have any friends here.
-What a... what a pre-merge.
-I know.
-Let me ask you a question.
I have a question for you.
-Me?
KATURAH:
Here comes old Papa Bruce.
I am... Ugh!
In front
of the other Reba people,
he says,
"I know you were really hesitant
to write Kaleb's name down,"
which is true,
but that puts a target on me.
I am, like,
currently, seethingly,
ridiculously,
annoyingly pissed!
-Yeah, absolutely.
-Oh, good. Hi.
BRUCE:
My relationship with Katurah
at this point in time
has been intense.
So the narrative that I'm trying
to push right now is, she didn't
want to vote for Kaleb.
All I'm doing is just
setting paranoia a little bit
and being like,
"Katurah is definitely
a little more dangerous
than we thought."
We know that we trust each other
and everything.
-BRUCE: That is correct.
-I think just, like,
if we have, like,
a question for each other
or something like that,
I'd just rather you ask me
in front of us
and our people
instead of in front of others.
Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
KATURAH:
Like, I can be having
the best day of life,
and the thorn in my thumb,
as usual, is Bruce.
I'm like,
"Old man, you're trying
to isolate me
from what was a unanimous vote."
So, not only are you annoying.
Now you're a serious liability.
As long as you know
we're good and everything.
I'd let you know if you weren't.
-You know that.
-Okay. All right.
So that's who I am.
I will not hold punches.
Okay.
KENDRA:
Bruce and I are supposed
to be working
with the same people.
We were on a tribe
from the beginning of the game--
Belo strong.
But he is starting rifts
with his own alliance members,
which makes him extremely hard
to work with.
KATURAH:
I'm like, "Why would you say
that in front of everybody?"
KENDRA:
So I'm nervous about
moving forward in this game
with Bruce.
♪ ♪
[birds singing]
KATURAH:
Tell me about it.
You should be so proud.
I tried.
I know you did.
And honestly...
KALEB:
I know. I...
Five seconds after--
no, not even five seconds.
-During the merge feast.
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
So, right now I am
still in a close connection
with Kaleb,
so I can still work with him.
Mm-hmm.
[Katurah laughs]
"I agree."
Like-like, he's immediately...
Technically,
we're working with Bruce,
but I love the idea of
old Belo plus Kaleb,
and then
we can just let Bruce go.
I always had this weird feeling
with Bruce,
and I felt like Bruce was
kind of putting distance
-between me
and other Belo people.
-Oh, really?
What?
Ugh. He is so annoying.
Kaleb is becoming more
and more aware of how Bruce is.
What?
So all I have to do is convince
a few other people around that
he's got to go.
The problem is this.
Cool. Let's agree.
Let's agree with Bruce.
100%.
KELLIE:
I've been saying,
I'm over Bruce.
I mean,
he's not the most strategic guy.
He's an extremely
emotional player.
But I think he does have
a lot of trust with me.
And he keeps telling me
a thousand times over
that I'm his number one ally,
which is exactly what I want.
So, at this moment,
I'm happy
to keep him in this game.
I do hope that, but...
and there's, there's hope.
-Good.
-Yeah.
EMILY: I have this very kind of
special relationship
with Kaleb in a way that
I think is only cultivated
going through the kind of trauma
that we experienced on Lulu.
So I'm feeling really sad
about lying to Kaleb.
-Yeah.
-So I'm so excited.
It's hard, but, I, myself,
as this kind of lone
remaining Lulu player
with Kaleb, realize that if
I'm sticking my neck out
on the line for him too much,
then that shifts the target
from him onto me,
and I can't have that happen.
So I've resigned myself
to letting Kaleb go.
Yeah.
EMILY:
So my game plan right now is
to really resolidify
the alliances that I had
with Drew and Austin
that we cultivated
when I was
on the new Belo tribe.
Yeah, but...
Because it's like
right now I don't have anything.
Yeah. Yeah.
AUSTIN:
I think everyone knows,
now with J. gone,
instead of a three-way
shared extra vote,
I'm gonna have
a two-way shared Steal a Vote
with Kellie.
But one piece of information
that only I know,
and I guess maybe Drew,
but I don't even know
if he put
the pieces together yet--
Kaleb only stopped 11 votes,
instead of 12,
because I didn't vote for him.
Bummer. I'm not gonna vote.
Instead of voting,
I'm going to be sacrificing it
in order to extend this
to a fully-fledged idol.
Finally, I have a regular idol.
It is fully active
until the final five.
After all this work, it took
13 days for it to get there,
and I have it now.
My idol has reached
its final form,
and I could be the most
powerful person on this island
with one of the best shots here
to win this game.
♪ ♪
AUSTIN:
Yeah.
-Everything goes with.
-Yeah.
SIFU:
But if you push me here,
most people will move
their whole body like this.
Boom. I'm still here.
-Don't knock me over.
-I won't. I won't.
All right, all right, all right.
So now if we're here...
-So, you-you hit...
-...I'll make hit-- boom.
'Cause naturally,
I'm going to want to get
-on the outside
and get like this to you.
-Correct.
-If you do that, it's holding,
and it's a penalty.
-Yeah.
Uh, like, do not call the master
out on his bull ....
-[Sifu mutters]
-See? Old dog, new tricks.
You're trying
to teach him some new tricks
to bring back to his kids,
and he's like, "Nah."
[Bruce laughs]
KALEB: Every moment
I'm on the beach with Bruce,
it's apparent to me
that he's only played the game
for about 14 hours
before coming here.
But I have to find a way
to work with him.
-In football, that's holding.
-I know.
-JAKE: So what's up?
-Couple things.
-JAKE: Yeah.
-I mean, number one, like,
how do you feel about, like...
Do you think he's, like, still,
like, coming after me hard,
or, like, how do you think
I can repair some of that?
-JAKE: Bruce?
-Yeah.
At this point,
we haven't talked about it.
KALEB:
Yeah?
JAKE:
I am wicked excited
that Kaleb is still here.
I want Kaleb to stay
in this game
for a significant period
of time.
I want my alliances to be
original Belo members and Kaleb.
And the problem is,
Kaleb and Bruce--
they're not seeing eye-to-eye
on most things.
So they got
to come together because
I need to build numbers
in this game.
You got up before,
you know, the-the ten,
-and now just go with it.
-Yeah.
BRUCE:
Kaleb-- first off, I like him.
I could see myself
in Kaleb at 30.
Very manipulative,
always smiling.
But because of that,
he was a primary person
to be voted out last night.
I love your honesty.
I love your fight.
Like, your fight was your fight
at that moment in time.
It humbled him.
How long it's going
to humble him for, I don't know.
'Cause
he's got a great personality.
But it humbled him
for at least...
at least 12 hours or so.
13 hours.
My son was a quarterback
on the team.
He throws a pick.
I talk to him in a way that...
It's kind of like a...
it's like a... a check.
KALEB:
I want to reassure Jake
that I can work with Bruce,
but I had one
of the most frustrating
Survivor conversations
of my life with Bruce,
and I don't care
what his viewpoint is.
BRUCE:
Like, okay,
you threw a pick. Check.
KALEB:
And it's taken everything
inside of me
to try and work with this guy
since Belo beach.
BRUCE:
'Cause when you're quarterback
of the team,
now you're thinking
that the other ten guys
on that side of the ball
are going to be like,
"Oh, what the hell?
Dude's gonna throw another pick.
He's got to throw another pick.
He threw one last time."
KALEB:
I feel like one of his kids,
and I don't know
how I made it 28 years
without Bruce telling me
what to do.
BRUCE:
I'm going to say, be wary
of the bedfellows
that you keep because...
No, no, no, no. Sorry.
I'm using
my parents' terms now. Uh...
Okay. I-I took that
maybe too literally.
BRUCE:
Kaleb and I are trying
to mend the fences that were
perpetually out there,
but Kaleb is on the outs.
So, as far as for allies,
I have Jake,
and then there's my number one,
which is Kellie.
I would like to know later on,
you know,
-about kind of moving forward.
-Sure.
Conversation
that we're going to have, um,
about who you're coming closer
with.
-Yeah.
-'Cause everybody's doing...
What do you mean?
Oh, for ... sake.
-All right.
-Not too many. Not too many.
Just keep...
It wasn't even
too many questions.
No, no, no. Listen.
Remember,
I have always played this game
with the highest level
of honesty.
-I know, Bruce. I know.
-You know?
-And I'm just asking
simple questions.
-Yes, yes.
My main problem
right now is... [scoffs]
...is dealing with Bruce.
Like, I'm giving him
genuine advice,
and I'm having a hard time
kind of
getting through to him.
BRUCE:
There's never any malice
in the questions that I ask.
No, I don't think it's malice.
I think it's just low-keyness.
I think that's more
of what it is.
So, at some point,
it's a liability.
And I don't really know
what to do with him right now.
He has just been this,
like, anchor
I've been dragging around
this whole game.
KELLIE:
Bruce is just, like,
his way or the highway.
He keeps these vendettas
against people.
A vendetta against Katurah
that he cannot let go,
a vendetta
against Kaleb that he can't
let go, and it's like,
sometimes you need people
for the numbers, man.
I'm doing it with you right now.
Like, I like Bruce as a human,
but as a player, it is just...
it's so difficult.
What'd you guys talk about
this morning?
He was just saying
that people are noticing
that Katurah and Kendra
are too happy that Kaleb's here.
JAKE:
We can still use him as numbers.
So what are you thinking
right now?
I do think Bruce is gonna be
in the hot seat a little bit.
If he keeps acting like this,
like, it's gonna be a problem.
I know.
We have five original Belo,
and we need to come together,
and that's what
I'm trying to push.
I know.
And if we can get Bruce
on board,
I can get Kendra and Katurah.
I know, but old Reba--
they want to stick together,
and I see
the Reba-Belo war coming.
So,
I'm going
to need numbers in this game
going down the line,
and if I'm going
to have numbers,
Kaleb's going to be one of 'em.
Yeah. "You have
to just suck it up."
But he doesn't listen.
JAKE:
Belo is looking
really, really bad.
I got to do
something about that.
That is not the direction
I need this game going.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Oh, my God.
-PROBST: It's a classic.
-Oh, God.
-[laughs]
-Bringing 'em back.
Everybody looks good merged.
-Yeah, right?
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Yeah, it feels good.
Orange is our color.
All right.
Shall we get to your first
individual immunity challenge?
-[all assenting]
-Hell yeah. Show it to us.
-Show us. Let's see it.
-Yes.
-You want to see it first?
-I would love to see it, yes.
-Yes, let's see it.
[gasping]
That is so beautiful.
PROBST:
There it is.
The individual
immunity necklace.
With this draped around you,
you are safe.
Here's how you earn it.
For today's challenge,
you're going to hold onto a pole
for as long as you can.
-JAKE: Yeah, baby.
-PROBST: When you drop,
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
cannot be voted out
of this game.
There is a twist...
-Of course there is.
-Why not?
...to today's challenge.
You're going to be divided
into two groups of six.
The person who lasts the longest
for each group
earns individual immunity.
-KELLIE: Ah, ah...
-KALEB: Oh, snap.
Come on, Jeff.
KATURAH:
Hey!
-Two necklaces today.
-Yes. Yes.
Yes.
In addition,
you're playing for a reward.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-[all assenting]
The person who lasts the longest
out of everybody
earns for their group a visit
to the sanctuary,
-where good things happen.
-[gasping]
You'll enjoy an afternoon
of do-it-yourself tacos
and soft drinks.
KENDRA:
Oh, my God.
-BRUCE: Yeah!
-DREW: Oh, I need that.
Yeah.
I want tacos so bad.
And you earn the right
to go to Tribal Council second,
which matters because
both groups are going to go
to Tribal Council separately.
-EMILY: Wow.
-Wow.
So tonight
two people will be safe,
two people will be going home.
What?
PROBST:
And at that first
Tribal Council,
the first person voted out...
will not make the jury.
-Oh, what?
-KALEB: Wow.
-Wow.
-PROBST: So, after 14 days,
not only will you not
win this game, you won't
have a say in who does.
Big enough stakes?
-[all assenting]
-All right,
we're going to draw for groups,
and we'll get started.
AUSTIN:
Wow. This is
absolutely brutal.
Here we go again.
KATURAH: The stakes are
super high. Whoever's getting
voted off at that first Tribal
Council doesn't make the jury.
It's like the dreaded position.
We all hate this position.
Your fate is determined
by drawing rocks.
Like, literally, you put
your hand in a bag of rocks
to figure out what group
we're going to be in.
It's terrifying.
-AUSTIN: This is it.
-PROBST: Moment of truth.
Everybody put your palms out.
Let's see what we got.
Everybody reveal.
And take your spot
on red or blue.
This is your competition
for today.
[Katurah laughs]
All right,
let's look at the groups.
Competing against each other
on red
will be Jake, Dee, Austin,
Julie, Kaleb, Katurah.
One of you's going
to win immunity.
The other group, wearing blue,
is gonna be Bruce, Sifu...
-Mm-hmm.
-...Kendra, Kellie,
Emily and Drew.
One of youwill be safe.
All right.
-We'll get it on. Let's do it.
-Yeah, baby. Let's go.
All right,
everybody's in position.
And this first
individual immunity challenge
of Survivor 45...
-Oh, my God.
-...is on.
Emily immediately starts
to slide down a little.
Various starting heights
for people, which is fine.
You can start at the top,
you can start
at the near bottom.
That doesn't matter.
You got a fear of heights?
Get rid of that.
Slide down.
All that matters
in this challenge is,
when your feet hit the sand,
you're out.
Emily's first out.
No shot at immunity.
Take a spot over here
on the bench with me.
Sorry, guys.
PROBST:
Julie going
to be first out for red.
Julie, take a spot on the bench.
We are down to five now
on each group.
Kendra starting to reposition.
-Those footholds are very small.
-Oh.
PROBST:
It is very difficult.
Your feet hurt, your body hurts.
Every time you slide down that
pole, it tears a little skin.
-[groans]
-EMILY: Come on, girl.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Kendra's out.
Jake is out.
We're down to four on red.
KENDRA:
Looking good, red.
All you need
is for everybody else
to drop out before you.
That's it.
-[groans]
-And you want
to at least make sure
you make the jury.
-Drew, you look great.
-Thank you.
I know I'm a model up here.
-Bruce, you are solid.
-You're solid.
Bruce sliding down
to a different position.
That could be indicative of pain
or just strategy.
[groans]
Sifu now dropping.
-[groans]
-Sifu looks like
he's on his way out.
-Sifu drops. He's out.
-KENDRA: Good job, Sifu.
PROBST:
14 days of Survivor.No joke.
Bruce drops out, and we're down
to two on blue.
We have a showdown
with Kellie and Drew.
If I win, Jeff,
you got to help me come down.
[laughing]
JAKE:
You got it, Austin.
There's the ledge.
-That's the last ledge...
-Austin starts to slide down.
He's got his feet on that last
and lowest foothold.
Kaleb is down one section.
Katurah right where she started,
in the middle.
Dee still at the top.
JAKE:
Looking good, guys.
-[clapping]
-Oh, yeah, good.
-KENDRA: All of you.
One of the toughest challenges
we do on Survivor.
[Kaleb groans]
It hurts the minute you start.
[Austin groans]
Austin going to drop,
and we're down to three on red.
It is Dee, Katurah and Kaleb.
And it is Kellie and Drew
for blue.
My legs are numb.
PROBST:
Keep digging!
[indistinct,
overlapping chatter]
Hey, lock your legs, Drew!
Just lock 'em!
PROBST:
Drew starting to slide.
This is not looking good
for Drew.
He's going to have
to find another stable spot.
Kellie looks very comfortable
up top.
Dee looks very comfortable.
DREW:
Okay, I got to go down.
I'm sorry,
my legs are going numb.
PROBST:
Drew is coming down.
Drew is out.
-Nice job, Kel, amazing!
-PROBST: Kellie, stay up there.
Kellie has won
individual immunity.
She cannot be voted out tonight.
KENDRA:
Our lives are in your hands,
Kellie.
You are now competing
for reward, Kellie.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Stay in there.
KENDRA:
You got this, baby.
I'm trying, guys,
but it's hurting.
-I know, babe.
-You got it, you got it.
-JAKE: Kaleb, you got it.
Katurah. Katurah, you're good.
You're good.
PROBST:
It is now Kellie,
who knows she's safe,
fighting against Dee,
Katurah and Kaleb
for that reward
and going to Tribal second.
-Kaleb is struggling.
-JULIE: You got this.
-Do not drop. You got that.
-PROBST: A personal test
right now.
[groans]
Kaleb is out.
-We're down
to a showdown on red.
-Here you go.
PROBST:
It is Dee and Katurah
on one end,
fighting for immunity.
It's Kellie on the other end,
who has already won immunity.
She's fighting for reward.
-Katurah's starting to slip.
-There you go.
-[indistinct chatter]
-I'm sorry, guys.
You're doing so good, Kellie.
PROBST:
Katurah sliding closer
to the bottom.
Katurah's out,
and we have a showdown.
Dee just won
individual immunity for red.
Both women are safe.
You are now fighting
for sanctuary, for fuel,
-for your body.
-You got this, Kellie!
EMILY:
You got it!
KENDRA:
Let's go, baby. For Gabby.
JAKE:
Dee, this is yours.
PROBST:
Dee on one end,
Kellie on the other,
battling for reward.
♪ ♪
Been up there 17 minutes now.
[cheering]
-SIFU: Amazing.
-You are both amazing.
PROBST:
Even more impressive
that it is Dee and Kellie,
given they didn't eat
that merge meal either.
No, they didn't.
PROBST:
They have had no food.
Kellie's slipping now,
or readjusting. Hard to tell.
KALEB:
Oh, yeah, Dee.
PROBST:
Kellie finds a new spot now.
Now Dee adjusts.
[overlapping shouting]
PROBST:
It would be the first food
for Dee and Kellie, proper food,
since they've been out here.
Something as simple as tacos
at the sanctuary
-can change your game.
-Dude, she's dropping.
She's dropping.
PROBST:
Kellie slides down
to the next rung.
This is it for Kellie,
her last foothold.
Dee is hanging on.
Dee looks confident right now.
Gives a nod to her group,
saying, "I got this."
The question is, does she?
Is Kellie out,
or is there another gear?
Believe in yourself!
PROBST:
Keep digging, Kellie!
Keep digging, Dee!
Don't give in.
Make the other person drop.
Let's go, Kellie! We're here.
PROBST: Force your competitor
to give in.
Don't let it be you.
Kellie adjusting again.
-Kellie's out!
-[cheering]
Dee wins reward for her group.
-Yeah!
-PROBST: What a challenge.
-Wow.
-JAKE: Come on down!
PROBST:
The tears start to flow
from a huge effort
on day 14, Survivor 45,
where you are earning it every
single second of every day.
First taco's to Dee, right?
Right? First taco's to Dee?
Girl, oh, my God.
Kellie, come on over.
[cheering]
JAKE:
Good job, Kel. Good job.
KENDRA:
Let's go, baby!
Let's go, Kellie!
The individual immunity
is yours.
You cannot be voted out tonight.
You will live
to see another day.
What is the feeling?
I know you're in pain.
I'm in a lot of pain, Jeff.
Um, I'm really proud of myself
for pushing myself,
and I love to see it come down
to two badass women,
-and I'm really proud of myself.
-SIFU: Yes!
There's honestly
no greater feeling.
Congrats. You are safe.
Head back. Have a seat.
[indistinct chatter]
Dee, come on over if you can.
[whooping and cheering]
-KALEB: That's it, Dee!
-Come on.
[red team assenting]
Individual immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council.
I saw tears the second you won.
What's the emotion? Share.
Jeff, I was just thinking
about my family up there--
my parents, my brother,
and, like, the pole signified,
like, the American dream for me.
And I knew
I wasn't going to let go.
And then I just
kept thinking, like, "I want
"to take care of them,
I want to take care of them.
You got this. You got this."
And I just want
to make them proud,
I want to take care of them.
-And that's what got me through.
-I have a feeling they're proud.
Congratulations. You are safe
tonight. Have a seat.
-Hell yeah, they're proud! Yeah!
-[whooping]
Hell yeah, they're proud!
-PROBST: All right.
So here's how
the afternoon will play out.
If you're wearing red,
you're going to leave here,
go to the sanctuary.
Do-it-yourself tacos
and soft drinks.
For the other six,
you are having
a different afternoon.
You're going back
to the old Lulu camp.
-Oh.
-What?!
-Don't send me back there.
Thanks, Jeff.
You will have nothing
except time
to figure out what you're going
to do tonight at Tribal Council.
You will go to Tribal first
and vote somebody out.
And that person will not only be
out of this game.
They won't be on the jury.
Grab your stuff, head out.
Ugh.
PROBST:
Katurah, Julie, Dee, Austin,
Jake, Kaleb, grab your stuff.
-Head out. Enjoy the sanctuary.
-Oh, baby.
-Oh, we will, Jeff.
We will. Trust me.
-We definitely will.
DEE:
My freaking toes
came into play today.
I said,
"This is going to help me out."
They're kind of cute,
but they're just, like,
too long right here.
But look at where it saved me.
Survivor.
Who knows? This may have been
the million-dollar gameplay.
I'm here winning
the first immunity challenge
because of my toes.
[laughs] Oh, boy.
♪ ♪
-KATURAH: The sanctuary.
-[yelling]
Yay!
DEE:
Today's challenge was no joke.
There was so much on the line.
Individual immunity.
-Is there guac?
-[laughter]
-Oh!
Meal for the team.
KATURAH:
Thank you, Dee,
for not giving up. Yes!
DEE:
We're going to Tribal second.
-14 days, and we got food.
-Amazing.
DEE:
So in my team,
whoever goes home tonight
makes the jury!
-To Dee. Hey.
-[cheering]
AUSTIN:
Let's go!
It feels so good to win.
You're in the final ten, Dee.
-Wow.
-KALEB: What a huge jump.
-KATURAH: Yay!
I didn't even think that far.
-I was just thinking
about the food.
-[laughter]
DEE:
We're all having fun.
We're enjoying the moment,
but at the same time it's weird
to be in the sanctuary
and have someone
next to me
that I have to vote out.
All right, guys.
We survived two weeks.
-We can do two more.
-I'm so close.
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
We still got
to worry about Tribal tonight,
but being able to, like,
share a meal,
like, not be stressed--
-it feels like it takes
a little bit of, like...
-Yeah.
JULIE:
We're all voting Kaleb, right?
Like, that's all I'm thinking.
I'm a little worried because
all I'm thinking is,
"I'm not safe."
And what if
Kaleb is going, "Hmm.
"If I can get Jake and Katurah,
maybe I can
split the votes,
maybe I got something"?
Because Kaleb doesn't stop.
He isthe cat with nine lives.
I am just hoping
he doesn't find his ninth life
at my expense.
-I mean, that was insane.
-KATURAH: Crazy.
JULIE:
Craziest thing ever.
JAKE:
Dude, that was a clutch move.
I know everyone's like,
"Kaleb-- he played a good game.
He got lucky last night.
He has to leave."
But I'm like,
"I don't think so."
That would be bad
for my game right now.
I need him as a shield,
and I do want
to go deep with him.
We're halfway there.
Game starts today.
Now is the point where
you're trying to figure out,
what alliance am I going to be
in moving forward in this game?
And I think everyone's looking
for that right now.
-I know.
-She is.
JAKE:
People know who's tight
with who. We all see it.
I think Dee is
the biggest threat in this game,
but she's safe tonight.
Makes me cry for you.
I'm not even kidding.
I'm, like, so proud.
JAKE: And I think
Julie's a weapon for her.
I want to disarm Dee, so
my target tonight is Julie.
-SIFU: Come here.
-KELLIE: I'm sorry.
-I tried really hard.
-[overlapping chatter]
You don't know how badly
I wanted those tacos.
I do know how badly.
I'm so proud of you.
[indistinct chatter]
SIFU:
You fought
with everything you had.
KELLIE:
I'm obviously thrilled I won.
Like, that's the best feeling
ever, but
because I wasn't able
to outlast Dee,
whoever goes home is going
to not make the jury.
-That was incredible.
-It was really good.
Really, really incredible.
I appreciate you guys
all saying that.
And it's really difficult
to think about
playing a part in...
in killing someone's dream.
So, my thoughts are
that I'm willing to go,
you know, any way with you.
Uh...
DREW:
Honestly, my preference would be
to take out Bruce,
but Belo has the numbers.
Bruce, Kendra and Kellie.
All of them are old Belo.
I have Emily, who I do trust,
but she is on the outside.
And then, of course, you have
Sifu, who probably has an idol.
So if they want to target Reba,
I am screwed.
There would be a saving grace.
I have
my Safety without Power,
and it would allow me
to just leave Tribal Council
before voting
and just be exempt.
There's only one problem.
I left my bag
back on Reba Beach,
so I have nothing.
I'm at Lulu.
I can't get to it.
I am out of luck. S.O.L.
So at this point,
my game plan has been reduced
to begging.
So, like, like,
100% honestly,
what are you thinking?
'Cause I'll go either way.
I don't care.
I just want to be
on the same page.
Okay.
-KENDRA: Okay?
-DREW: All right.
I will pull you in for that.
So, the way the tribes
are broken up,
I see this as my shot
to finally get Bruce out.
What is it?
Yeah, okay.
I was, like,
y'all were, like, hiding that
-like there was
gonna be some crazy thing.
-SIFU: Yeah.
-Well, it is a crazy thing.
-It is.
-You know what I mean?
-It is kind of, but...
Yeah.
DREW:
So the point is to keep it cool.
-Don't give him any sense of...
-Yeah, keep it cool.
-DREW: Yeah.
-EMILY: Yeah.
KENDRA:
We have to be smart
about getting Bruce out,
because he's paranoid.
And that's really scary,
especially if Bruce feels
like he doesn't trust me.
If he plays an idol,
it could be
one name written down,
and I could be going home.
All right,
what are your thoughts?
My thoughts.
My name is being
dropped right now by Kendra.
-KELLIE: You think so?
-BRUCE: Oh, yeah.
I don't think that's, like,
good for any of us,
-at this moment, you know
what I mean? Even for her.
-Yeah.
I know you guys have had
some sort of disagreements.
Yeah, well...
Or whatever, but...
BRUCE:
So right now,
if my inclination is correct,
Kendra wants me to go.
I can see her running around,
talking to everybody.
And from day one, I've not
had a conversation with Kendra
in regards to strategy,
alliances or anything like that.
When it comes down to it,
I have a great level
of protection.
Kellie and I are rock solid, and
I have my idol.
So if I...
if I feel that I need to use it,
I'm gonna use it.
KELLIE:
This morning I know that Kendra
wanted to target Bruce.
The thing in my head is,
I don't think
tonight is the night to do it.
Bruce is a hard person
to work with,
but I know he trusts me,
and that's valuable for me.
So the plan right now
is for me to get
Kendra and Bruce
to just get on the same page.
Whether that can be salvaged
today is gonna be hard.
♪ ♪
Yeah, I am thinking Kaleb.
-I want to do
whatever you decide.
-Right, right.
-And I'll push whatever story
you want. I mean...
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-Yeah, a thousand percent.
After today.
-Like...
-After today.
After the callout yesterday.
-Yeah.
AUSTIN:
So there is potential benefit
of keeping someone
-who also has
a high threat level.
-DEE: High threat level?
I just think that everybody
put his name down last night.
Like, that just says something.
Austin doesn't
want to vote Kaleb.
I feel like he wants
to keep the big threats,
but I'm the one who's
in the position of power.
So we're voting Kaleb,
no matter what.
-Come, come, come, come.
-Please.
-AUSTIN: Please join.
-DEE: Please join.
And I think Jake
will want to work with us,
because I feel
like he's easy to persuade.
And he knows that
if he were to go
against us,
we're gonna go against him.
And today we're
literally in the power position.
-Kaleb's got to go.
-JAKE: Okay.
-Sure.
-DEE: Yeah.
We're gonna have fun,
'cause he mentioned
our names last night.
-[chuckles]
-I don't think much
is gonna go wrong tonight,
because last night at Tribal,
every single person
wrote his name down.
So if we take him out tonight,
no one's gonna be against us,
because everyone
wanted him out to begin with.
So Kaleb is a goner. [chuckles]
Boy, bye. [laughs]
Has there ever been,
like, a second elimination
where everybody voted
for one person,
and then they were gone
the next?
-No. Everybody always changes.
-I don't think so, right?
All right,
let's do it this time.
JAKE:
I feel like all these votes,
I keep getting told what to do.
I don't want
to be told what to do.
Guys, I'm gonna go for a walk.
-JULIE: Okay.
-JAKE: Have fun on your walk.
I need to take
control of the game.
I know I'm gonna get flak
after I do this, but
I don't just want to survive.
I want to play Survivor,
and I want to win Survivor.
Well, congratulations
on making the jury phase.
Congratulations to you
on making the jury.
KALEB:
I'm thinking
the exact same thing.
I've been thinking about,
strategically,
what makes the most sense.
What do you think,
strategically, moving forward?
'Cause I got a couple ideas.
What do you got?
Right now?
And the reason
for that is because...
Why does Austin know?
Austin does know
about Bruce's idol,
and Katurah doesn't.
And Katurah is the third vote
that we need
at this Tribal Council.
And so, if we let Austin share
that information with Katurah,
she might flip
on our entire alliance
and-and end our game before
we even have a chance to begin.
Yeah.
...100% are
voting Julie tonight.
-100%.
-And you know what?
It comes to a tie...
-Yeah.
-He's scared.
He doesn't want to be a target.
I open my fat mouth
and start going,
"Austin, I'm a bigger target
than you right now.
"This kid just got 12 votes.
-He's a bigger target than you."
-"What are you doing?"
-Yeah.
Yeah.
JAKE:
So the plan is...
...tonight at Tribal Council,
we put three votes on Julie.
If Katurah,
Kaleb and myself vote Julie,
and Julie, Dee and Austin
vote for Kaleb,
that will put us in a tie.
-We would then get
the opportunity to revote.
-Kaleb.
-JAKE: If the revote
is still in a tie...
-Julie.
...then Dee's safe, the people
who got votes are safe.
So then Katurah,
myself and Austin draw rocks.
Austin's really scared
in this game.
And once we get to a revote,
I think I can convince Austin
that we don't
have to go to rocks, bud.
So it would have to be
me, you, Jake and who?
Potentially Austin...
Yeah. Yeah.
I also think he would.
Yeah, he's been afraid.
Um, okay.
What did
you want to say about Bruce?
-No. No.
-Yeah. Yeah.
He has, he has the idol.
The Belo idol?
-No. The Lulu idol.
-What the ...?
-How'd he get the Lulu idol?
-He found it.
It was buried in our shelter.
That's crazy.
That means that I'm actually
on the outs, even of Belo.
-I swear...
-You guys knowing that Bruce
had the idol for a long time,
honestly,
that's-that's big, like...
I know. I'm so sorry, Katurah.
-Okay, so we know the three
of us will vote together.
-Yeah.
And try and flip Austin
at the revote.
-Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, that sounds good.
-Does that make sense?
-I appreciate you.
-Yeah, I appreciate you.
Jake and Katurah
are ready to fight for me.
The big thing that I learned
over the last 24 hours
here onSurvivor
is that the quantity of options
is not nearly as important
as the quality.
-You just know who your people
are when you need them.
-Yeah.
KALEB:
When you really think about
how serious a word "trust" is,
it means having
a strong alliance
of multiple people
that you will do anything for.
If you show
that type of loyalty,
then you will get it in return.
-[laughs]
-We'll be fine. We'll be fine.
-As long as we keep talking,
we'll be fine.
-Yeah.
At this point in the game,
all bets are off,
tension is high, anything goes.
If you thrive
in that kind of environment,
this might be
the adventure for you.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
KATURAH:
Genuinely,
in your heart or hearts,
would you rather
Mama J. or Kaleb go home?
Mama J.
Of-of-of the two of them?
I... Kaleb's not voting for me.
Kaleb is a target in this game.
Yeah, that's
what I was thinking, too.
Jake wants us
to vote out Julie tonight.
And he wants it
to be me, Kaleb and Jake.
It's a good plan for me
because I need to protect Kaleb.
He is my shield against Bruce.
And on the other side is Austin,
Dee and Julie
want to vote Kaleb.
That's a split.
That's a three-three split
down the middle.
Before we even go any further,
I need you to tell me
what's going on with Bruce.
He has an idol?
Yeah.
[sighs]
Is that why you were
looking for the rings?
Yes.
♪ ♪
-So that's why all of y'all
were looking for the rings?
-Yeah.
-So you weren't...
Your ring wasn't even lost?
-No.
-Damn.
-I thought Kaleb told you.
-No, but just now. I mean,
I didn't know about all of this.
-Yeah.
KATURAH:
Turns out that
all these people who I thought
were in my close alliance
all know about Bruce's idol.
Everybody except for me.
Okay. Look, Jake,
you know I trust you.
Katurah, I got your back.
I think
if it's a three-three vote...
...we can pull Austin.
KATURAH:
I don't know.
I'm hoping I'm not falling
into theSurvivor trap
of emotions and stuff, but
now I'm kind of feeling like
I might vote
with the Reba people tonight.
The problem is,
me, Dee, Julie and Austin,
we don't really know each other,
which is really scary.
And on the other hand,
I've been working with Jake
and Kaleb for quite a while,
but I don't fully trust them.
The stakes are super high.
I'm still processing it all,
so I really just
don't know what to do.
♪ ♪
EMILY:
But we're gonna
make it through this.
Yeah, we have to. We have to.
So, uh, me...
I just think it makes sense
to go votes on-on Bruce.
Oh, yeah, 100%.
I have no working relationship
with him, really, so...
-But in this dynamic,
I think I'm the target.
-Yeah.
-I don't think so.
-I do.
Hitting this beach
at Lulu really made me realize
my mortality in this game.
People are saying
their vote's Bruce, but I feel
like Belo wants
to take out Reba, and
I am a big target.
So I know that it could
potentially be me tonight.
And...
me going tonight means
that I am not on the jury.
And making the jury
to me is a dream of mine.
So it does break my heart
that tonight could be it for me.
[bats chattering]
KELLIE:
Mm-hmm.
-He's worried you're
gonna come after him.
-Me?
Uh-huh.
And I was like...
He just doesn't change...
He's, like...
Like with Katurah,
he, like, can't get over it.
I know, man.
Also...
KENDRA:
Yeah.
Dude.
Kellie's head is...
we can't go for Bruce today.
He is a shield.
Nobody's
gonna take him to the end.
And that we can really rely on
him as a number in this game.
What do you want to do, then?
Man.
KELLIE:
Sifu is someone that they're
happy to take out, potentially.
KENDRA:
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
If I had my choice, Bruce
would be going home tonight.
SIFU:
Look at that.
KENDRA:
But Sifu's
a great second option,
because Reba's
having problems with him,
Belo would love to see him gone.
So Sifu
is kind of an easy target.
-DREW: Okay.
-That is it.
-Okay.
DREW: Kendra comes to me,
and she says that
she wants me to vote for Sifu,
but I don't know.
My relationship
with Sifu is not great,
but at the same time,
I can't help but think
that Bruce
is the better move for my game.
Bruce has a lot of power.
-Mm-hmm.
-You have my...
like, I'm with you.
-I got you. I got you.
-I'm with you.
I want to give this
a chance to flourish.
You're good. You're good.
-This is locked in.
-Yeah.
-Yes, it is.
-This is locked in.
Yeah, I'm-I'm... I'm game.
With this group of six,
I think it is an opportunity
to get Bruce out,
but it requires
Kendra keeping her nerve.
-Let's talk through it.
-KENDRA: Okay.
-So we-we-we want
to go against Sifu, right?
-Yes. Yes.
There's also Bruce,
which is a possibility.
-Yeah.
-Um, but the thing about Bruce
is that he's
such a hard guy to read.
-He's such a hard guy to read.
-When I talk to him, I think
he must be targeting me, because
he doesn't give me anything.
He doesn't give me anything.
That's what
I've been telling you.
Yeah.
KENDRA:
I don't know.
I'm really nervous right now,
because this is a big decision.
We got Sifu on this side.
We got Bruce on this side.
And, like, they're tipping
back and forth, and, like,
I'm not sure which one
is gonna... [clicks tongue]
...hit the bottom and
get out of this game tonight.
Can't get
a straight answer from him.
It's really crazy.
Hmm.
Kendra says
she wants to vote with me.
She wants all the things
in the past to be squashed.
Girlfriend,
trust is definitely earned,
it is not given.
And I trust you
as far as I can throw you.
Going into Tribal tonight,
if I feel
a little bit of tension,
and I'm not sure
about what's going on,
I'll play my idol.
I'm probably gonna play...
-You are?
-Probably.
-Why?
-Because
there's too much
going on right now.
I don't know, Bruce.
You don't know what?
If you should or not.
And Bruce
has become extremely paranoid.
Working with him
is the worst part of my game.
[sighs]
You know, I-I don't know.
I'm still sussing out
exactly what I want to do.
-It could just be
a safe option... tonight.
-Yeah.
-Actually?
-Actually.
KELLIE:
I'm still very torn, honestly.
I need to make sure
that I'm making
the smart decision
for me.
Right now
I'm feeling very stressed.
This is a real do-or-die moment.
This is like
all your cards on the table,
all the marbles are in,
and which way do
I want to go, Sifu or Bruce?
I know that Reba wouldn't have
a problem with Sifu going home.
In fact,
they might be happy about it.
And he's also a huge wild card,
and wild cards can make it
through this game and win.
Now, Bruce has been
my struggle this entire game.
He's obviously a huge threat.
I know he has an idol.
I know he needs to be
blindsided
in order to get him out.
And Bruce has just
been dragging my game down.
And so,
when I choose to take him out
is probably going to be the most
important move for my game.
♪ ♪
All right, so, big twist today.
You're divided
into two groups,
which means, once again,
a very small Tribal Council.
Why is everybody looking
and shaking their heads?
Can't catch a break.
-[laughter]
-Yeah.
Just what you said, Jeff.
Big twist today.
-Yeah.
-Very big.
Drew, for me, that is
the pivot point in this new era.
You are either glass half empty,
"Oh, no, another twist,"
or you're glass half full,
"Oh, boy, another opportunity."
DREW:
Absolutely,
because this one determines
whether or not
you make the jury.
And all of us
want to be on the jury,
so the stakes are extra high.
-Mm.
-And you look at this group
of people, it's an eclectic mix.
You've got one from old Lulu,
two from old Reba,
three from old Belo.
So it's the will she,
won't she question.
Like, are they gonna, you know,
stay with the tried and true,
or are they gonna branch off?
And that's a scary thing.
So, Kendra, how did you see
this uncertainty play out today?
You got to have,
like, a bird's-eye view,
and you got
to see all the options.
And so this is a good chance
for me to build trust
with people who I want
to move forward with.
That was the basis
of my conversations today.
Bruce, one of the opportunities
with a small group
is, if you survive,
you can solidify a bond.
That is correct.
Um, but also keeping in mind
the bonds
that you also still have.
So you can solidify
a bond with someone here
in a small group, but if
that bond does not hold true,
that could be friction.
And now you're
looking at fracture.
So in this fracture,
someone could come in
and fill in those gaps,
and then you're out.
PROBST:
Kellie, that's scary.
If you're trying
to trust somebody,
and on one hand,
they're saying,
"Yes, I'd like to trust you,
"provided it doesn't mess up
-my other trust
I already got going."
-[soft laughter]
Yeah, it's terrifying, Jeff.
I mean, all through
this merge portion of the game,
we've been
put into random groups,
-literally by random rock draw.
-Yeah.
So that automatically
blurs tribal lines.
Are those really gone?
It's still hard
to say at this point,
because we haven't
actually had an opportunity
where every single person
is on the table.
PROBST:
Sifu, how did
you approach this afternoon
from your perspective?
What I sense tonight is...
something
I've never sensed before.
Is that based on just the way
people are behaving around you?
Yeah. To be real, it's...
I know I'm a threat.
And I know people
are seeing me that way,
and I'm hearing it as well.
So...
Bruce,
do you understand why Sifu
might feel on the outs tonight?
Yeah, everybody has
a different take on it,
and I do understand
how he feels.
You know, I feel the same way.
I have
that little knot in my stomach,
but it's one of those things
that if you can
rely on conversations
that you've had
and the trust that you've built
with the people that are here,
and just observe
throughout the course of the day
and kind of see how their body
language is towards you,
and you can
read people that way.
SIFU:
I have to bounce off that.
I don't think anyone
wants to come out and say it,
but I feel like there's complete
division right now, and...
it's pretty easy to see.
Three Belo, two Reba, right?
That's the way
they could look at it, easily.
I mean, Kellie,
Bruce, Kendra could easily say,
"Hey, Sifu, you look beautiful,
but sayonara."
But my pitch
is loyalty moving forward,
strong, meat shield.
There's a lot at stake there
that I don't know
if they're
taking into consideration.
Kendra,
is it a fair assumption
that you, Bruce and Kellie
might work together?
I can see how
somebody could say that,
but following
the words of my mom,
"You know what they say
about assuming?
You make
an ass out of you and me."
PROBST:
Bruce, the tricky part is,
you really don't ever know.
And just because
the three of you wore blue
doesn't mean
you're still together.
BRUCE:
That's correct.
You can perceive
whatever it is that you want,
you can assume
whatever you want,
but if you feel
that you're gonna be
continuing to build
something that you started
in the past, execute.
And if you have loyalties,
you can strengthen them
with the decisions
that you make tonight.
All right, it is time to vote.
Sifu, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
All right. I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Bruce.
Sifu. One vote Bruce,
one vote Sifu.
♪ ♪
Sifu. That's two votes Sifu,
one vote Bruce.
Sifu. That's three votes Sifu,
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor 45,Sifu.
That's four, that's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
[laughs]
-You guys are awesome.
-KENDRA: You're amazing.
SIFU:
Wow.
[laughs] Thank you, guys.
Is this even
real life right now?
-It is.
-KENDRA: Aw.
[exhales sharply]
Sifu, the tribe has spoken.
[sighs]
Thank you, everybody.
Pleasure.
-SIFU: It's been a pleasure.
-Absolute pleasure, Sifu.
[mouths]
SIFU:
Whoo!
[laughter]
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
We'll bring in the next group.
[sighs]
So, I felt, the whole day,
something gloomy.
It was my impending doom.
I did everything
that I wanted to do,
and in my day-to-day life
I'm a master instructor,
but out here I'm a student
of the game ofSurvivor.
I appreciate it.
♪ ♪
All right.
So, thanks
to the huge efforts of Dee,
you will have a say
in who wins your season
as the first member of the jury.
You also had the chance to enjoy
an afternoon at the sanctuary.
-[laughter]
-So, Dee, how long
after the tacos had settled
did people start to say,
"Well, should we talk?"
So, we got back to camp,
and we all just were like,
"All right, well, we got to have
our little office hours now."
Um, and for the most part,
I feel like I had
genuine conversations today,
and very open and honest ones.
And whoever makes the jury
today, like, we're a family now.
Like, it's insane.
Even just being at
the sanctuary bonded us today.
Jake, how did you
experience the afternoon
when you got back to camp?
And now it's tribal politics.
Now we got to figure out
who's going home.
Yeah, we had
a great time at the sanctuary,
and that was a lot of fun,
but, yeah,
someone's gonna go home today.
And it's tough,
because you come out here
and you think you're gonna be,
like, I don't know,
some kind of, like, robot,
but, like, I respect all these
people and I like them all,
but there's not
12 Sole Survivors, there's one.
-PROBST: Julie, agree with that?
-JULIE: Yes.
The way he said it was perfect.
We're not robots.
I really thought that I could
come in and compartmentalize.
Now it's you have
to invest in them and they have
to invest in you
for that trust to matter.
So if that gets severed,
it's not just a game.
It's part of you is devastated.
PROBST:
Katurah,
the way Julie just said it is,
"You can't be a robot,
"and yet if you
allow yourself to be real,
and people were lying to you,
and it's you, it's devastating."
For me, this is my first Tribal
that I'm not safe.
So I know
exactly that feeling of,
"I talked to some people.
"Can I trust them?
I told people some things.
Can they believe me?
You know, would they react?"
And it's just, like,
you literally won't know
until you come in
with that terrible snuff.
So, Jake, from a stress
and paranoia level today,
where was everybody?
I feel like everyone's
just trying to be like,
-"Everything's good.
Everything's good."
-[laughs]
And it's, like,
everything's not good, Jeff.
It's crazy. I'm like...
My mind's going wild,
and I'm sure everyone else's
is, too, you know?
But tonight's vote's
about getting
to the next step of the game.
It's about:
who can I go forward with
that I can trust,
that I can rely on,
that I think
wants to take me farther?
So, Kaleb, how did you see this
play out today?
It's interesting, Jeff.
I tried
to take my foot off the gas--
not necessarily
after the sanctuary
but over the last day.
It's been a crazy ride for me.
Last Tribal, I got 12 votes.
I was way too popular here,
and, you know...
[laughter]
I appreciate the shout-outs,
but at the same time,
you realize, "Am I moving
forward in this game alone,
or do I have the possibility
to move forward with allies?"
So what I've really
tried to do is just show people
transparency to see that,
you know, I could actually
be an ally
that people can rely on.
PROBST:
Dee, can that strategy work,
-even though he got
every vote at the last Tribal?
-[Katurah chuckles]
I feel like it depends
how people perceive
what Kaleb told them, you know?
And, like, how much he's built
the bonds he has right now.
That's just
all it comes down to.
Katurah,
did Kaleb approach you and say,
"Listen,
I want to be transparent.
-Nothing to lose, let's talk"?
-[laughs]
Yes, exactly that.
And I think we know
that Kaleb has been really
transparent with all of us
about where he stands.
I mean, he kind of
really doesn't have a choice.
We were all here last Tribal.
We all saw what happened.
So on one hand, great,
because you have someone saying,
"I'm willing
to give it everything.
I'm willing to be with you along
the way. I got nothing to lose."
On the other hand,
you got somebody
who's got nothing to lose.
But I know it's gonna
boil down to: what's my gut say?
-Hmm.
-KATURAH: Who did I feel
like I could really trust?
Who did I have a conversation
with and I felt good about?
Who's having
a conversation with me
and saying, "Katurah,
I feel good about you"?
That's what
it's gonna come down to.
All right, it is time to vote.
Julie, you're up.
♪ ♪
Could have worked together, but
you burned the bridge last time.
♪ ♪
I didn't have
a say in it last night.
I'm hoping I do now.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has
an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
♪ ♪
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote, Kaleb.
Julie. One vote Kaleb,
one vote Julie.
Kaleb. Two votes Kaleb,
Julie. We're tied.
Two votes Kaleb,
two votes Julie.
Kaleb.
That's three votes Kaleb,
two votes Julie.
One vote left.
Eighth person voted out
of Survivor 45
and the first member
of our jury, Kaleb.
Need to bring me your torch.
[groans]
♪ ♪
All right. Congrats, you guys.
-AUSTIN: Fought so hard.
-[Kaleb laughs]
Good fight.
Appreciate it.
-Love you, brother.
-KALEB: Love you.
-Well-played, man.
Kaleb, the tribe has spoken.
-Time for you to go.
-Always a pleasure.
-DEE: Bye.
-Bye, Kaleb.
-Bye, brother.
[sighs]
[quietly]:
So close. So close.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
KENDRA:
This could be our chance
to start taking out some guys.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
JAKE:
If I'm going out of this game,
I'm going out swinging.
[cheering]
It's game on, baby.
It's game on.
Right when I thought my game
was about to take a turn,
I got voted out.
And I couldn't have
played a more different game
than the one I thought,
coming onto this beach.
First member of the jury,
not at all the place
that I wanted to go.
But I never gave up, and
I fought until the very end.
And so I am really proud of
how I pushed through this game.
[roars]