BRUCE:
Clock's ticking, heart's racing.
Boom.
The hidden immunity idol, baby.
[laughs]
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
No.
The thorn in my thumb, as usual,
is Bruce.
You're gonna be divided
into two groups of six.
Two people will be going home.
-Oh, what?
-KALEB: Wow.
-Okay. Sure.
-DEE: Yeah.
I don't want
to be told what to do.
I want to playSurvivor,
and I want to winSurvivor.
DREW:
Kendra wants me
to vote for Sifu, but
Bruce is the better move
for my game.
[groans]
I'm very torn.
Bruce has been my struggle,
and so, when I choose to
take him out is probably going
to be the most important move
for my game.
PROBST:
It is time to vote.
Seventh person voted out
of Survivor45--
Sifu.
The tribe has spoken.
I trust him more than
I trust you.
Julie. We're tied.
Two votes Kaleb,
two votes Julie.
Eighth person voted out
of Survivor45
and the first member
of our jury: Kaleb.
[groans]
The tribe has spoken.
Hey, guys, we made the jury.
BRUCE:
Yeah, buddy!
Wow.
DREW:
We got back to camp.
It's kind of a mixed atmosphere
because everyone's very happy
they made the jury.
But eliminating Sifu
was a little bit tougher
on the heartstrings
than expected.
You know,
I actually felt bad for the guy.
That was such a hard send-home,
especially with somebody
who's a little wild card, but...
DREW:
Emily and I were in lockstep,
which is great to see
because it means
she'll be a core reliable ally
I can trust for at least
a few days out here.
But the downside of
the Tribal Council was giving
Bruce a symbolic victory,
letting him survive.
I don't want him
to have symbolic victories,
and I plan to take it away
at first opportunity.
I kind of do.
DREW:
I think there
is some anticipation
to find out the results
of the following Tribal Council.
Everyone expects it
to be Kaleb, but
we only have half the picture
right now.
Anybody home?
Kaleb went home.
[indistinct chatter]
JAKE: Tonight,
I wanted to push wicked hard
to keep Kaleb here.
I-I trusted Kaleb.
But it was ridiculous to ask
Katurah to go to rocks.
And I shouldn't
have voted Julie.
But I'm still in the game.
I think I can
make something work.
I just can't be
as reckless as I was tonight.
-Kaleb was going home
no matter what.
-Yeah.
If you would have voted
party lines,
then it would have been
no harm, no foul.
Jake became a liability tonight.
He put his emotions into it.
Like,
bro, what are you doing?
Like, you're following
a dead horse to water.
You're never gonna get there.
Things now are ... so we need
to go back
and make some adjustments.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
JAKE: At Tribal,
I wanted to make a move.
I didn't want to dogpile
on Kaleb.
That's not a move.
That's following the herd,
and I'm not gonna do that.
Ten people aren't
all at the top.
Why would you upset
the status quo? It's 'cause
you need
to better your position.
I don't know.
I'm kind of sucking
atSurvivor right now.
Hopefully, I stop sucking.
That's the goal.
First and foremost, that was
not a personal thing whatsoever.
I understand
-this kind of, like,
puts us at odds, game-wise,
-Right.
and that's fine.
JULIE: At Tribal Council,
I got two votes my way.
One from Kaleb,
totally expected.
One from... Jake,
and not expected.
It was more of a
"Can I get Kaleb to stay?"
rather than
"Can I get Julie to leave?"
-Right.
-I understand I lied
to your face all day.
-And I get that.
-Yeah, you did.
I know.
-Was I convincing?
-Yeah.
-Not anymore, though, right?
[laughs]
-Right.
There's absolutely no way I'm
working with Jake going forward.
There's no way I can trust him.
He lied to my face
and I believed him.
He's scary to me.
What are we gonna do
moving forward?
I think that
lines have been drawn.
It's kind of feeling like
old Belo versus
old Reba now.
This is a fun game,
isn't it, Julie?
Regardless of anything,
it's fun, right?
-Wait till you see your name.
-I know, right?
-You tell me how fun.
-[laughing]
-Buddy, it won't be me.
-No, I know.
It'll happen. It'll happen.
DEE: Good morning.
DEE:
I don't know.
Down to six-four.
Girls, baby.
EMILY:
It's, like, overwhelming.
I don't know.
Maybe we should talk.
KENDRA:
It's six-four right now.
This could be our opportunity
for these six badass women
to start taking out some guys.
DREW:
Hey, tell me about tacos.
Tacos are really good, man.
Mushrooms, dude, avocado, guac
and refried beans.
BRUCE:
Mozzarella or cheddar?
You think they're smart enough
to be scared?
I'd really like
to start picking them off.
I would love
a woman's alliance,
but it's gonna be tricky
because Dee and I
are still four strong
with Drew and Austin,
who I trust 100%.
JULIE: Yeah.
-KATURAH: Yeah. Oh, my God.
-DEE: Oh, man.
-And then it's like... war.
-KATURAH: And his freaking...
But if we get him out, it has
to be a blindside, though.
And there has to be
the most shocking blind...
Like, we have to be in love
with him five seconds before.
Yeah, we really do.
He's definitely very dangerous.
There's six women
who want to get Bruce out.
This is perfect for me
because I am fed up.
Bruce has just been dragging
my game down this entire time.
Like, the fact that he's tied
to me, it's because
Bruce keeps telling people
he's close to me.
Bruce has been trying
to control not just me
but multiple other players
this whole game.
And you don't want
to keep living
with someone
who is inhibiting your gameplay
in any way.
So, if these girls want
to help me take out
that target, wonderful.
♪ ♪
[theme music
of Survivorplaying]
♪ ♪
-What the hell's going on here?
-Whoa!
-What?
-Boat!
Oh, hell, no. We got to go.
KENDRA:
Boat!
What do you think of this, dude?
JAKE:
Are we doing a challenge here?
What is that? Is that benches?
DEE:
Oh, my God. I'm sweating.
-JULIE: Oh, my
God, they're coming out.
-DEE: Wait.
KELLIE:
As much as I want
to be optimistic in this game,
all of these twists and turns
that we've had so far
have always had a catch.
EMILY:
Oh, this is not good.
-This is not good.
-KENDRA: This is not good.
EMILY:
This is bad. This is bad.
Why is it so ominous?
I've never seen a table
like that onSurvivor.
I got a nice amount
of Survivorknowledge
and Survivorhistory up here,
so I'm trying
to think about prior seasons.
Was there ever a table
on a boat?
I got nothing.
This is sick, Jeff.
Oh.
KATURAH:
No.
[cheering, yelling]
Hey!
[cheering]
What?
[Jake laughs]
[screaming]
EMILY:
This is so fun.
I have no idea
what I'm looking for.
Bamboo shoots
look the same color
as the trees.
I don't know what path to take,
but I'm running.
Here.
Once I found my first one,
I'm like,
"Okay, I know
what I'm looking for."
It's game on, baby.
It's game on.
Oh.
Thank you, Lord!
-JAKE: So cool!
-This is so fun.
I'm thinking to myself, like,
"And I'm old as hell.
I ain't running around
"out there with
these young kids. I'm gonna use
my senior intuition
to try and find some."
Oh, there.
AUSTIN:
Everyone's searching.
It was, like,
so much excitement.
It's unlike any auction
ever done before,
and it is so exciting because
we're all gonna have
different amounts.
We're all gonna have
different spending habits.
KATURAH:
I'm running back,
dropping one in my basket
and looking around.
Oh, I like that, Bruce.
To my utter joy and amusement,
Bruce's basket was empty.
Dude, I got nothing so far.
-You got zero?
-Zero.
Damn it.
Everybody's running by me
with one in their hand,
and I'm like, "Oh, no."
I royally screwed up.
A couple steps forward,
I would have got the one
Emily just picked up.
DREW:
Bruce, for all his talk about
hard work
and the older generation--
what the heck?
Zero.
I'm-I'm looking.
I'm not stopping.
Oh!
Yay!
Bruce, that's why you got zero.
Go friggin' run.
Bruce was walking back.
I'm like, "Dude, that's why
you're not finding anything.
You got to run back.
Like, what are you doing?"
Just chilling, you know. Like,
this is not vacation.
BRUCE:
Really sucked.
-Oh, it's real money!
-[whooping]
-We're rich now.
-Ah!
AUSTIN:
Holy... They all have
a different amount in them.
KELLIE:
Wait, really?
-Oh.
-Yeah.
AUSTIN:
The awesome thing is that
each of these pieces
of bamboo have a different
amount of money in it,
so I'm doing pretty well.
I've got
One, two, three...
Four, five, six, seven...
A hundred twenty,
140, 160, 180.
KENDRA:
Three hundred
and sixty dollars here.
-EMILY: Five hundred.
-Emily, you got 500.
Jake, what'd you get?
-Three forty.
-Julie?
I think I got 420.
I think I got 480.
-I got 700.
-What?!
JAKE:
Nice, dude.
-AUSTIN: Dee?
-DEE: Nine hundred
-friggin' dollars.
-What?!
-Dinner on you, baby.
-Dinner on me, then.
-DREW: Dee is our winner.
-DEE: That was a lot of fun.
KELLIE:
TheSurvivor auction
is back, baby.
I mean, I never thought
it would come back.
I am excited.
I hope there's not a catch,
but there's always the catch.
-I'm starving, man. Let's eat!
-Yes, let's go.
♪ ♪
Welcome to the Survivorauction.
Ah!
PROBST:
Up for bid:
a variety of food items.
-[screaming]
-Yeah!
-PROBST: Fruit bat soup.
-[contestants groaning]
-Oh, dude.
-[cheering]
PROBST:
If you see something you desire,
bid on it.
MAN:
Yeah!
Come on in!
Smiles.
-Ooh!
-PROBST: Come on in
-and let's have some fun.
-[indistinct chatter]
I see you back there, Jeff.
I like that.
-DREW: Oh, wow.
-Take a seat, everybody.
-Wow.
-PROBST: All right.
Welcome to the Survivorauction.
[cheering, whooping]
Beautiful words.
I love it.
The last time we did this
was our 30th season,
Survivor: Worlds Apart,
back in 2015.
-Oh, my God.
-JAKE: Damn.
PROBST:
We have updated the auction
for the new era in three ways,
starting with the money.
This morning,
you received a note
saying, "There's money hidden
in the jungle."
I'm sure there was a scramble.
The second change--
there are no advantages,
-so get that out of your head.
-Yeah.
-All right.
-KATURAH: We like that, Jeff.
-We love it.
-We like that!
-Yeah! Let's have some fun.
We like that.
-PROBST:
The last change is this.
-Oh, no.
We have prepared 15 items
for today's auction.
Only the first five
are guaranteed.
Once we get to beyond five--
between six and 15--
that number
will be determined by me
drawing a number between
six and 15 from this bag.
I'll take that number.
I'll put it right here.
I'll know what that number is.
You won't.
So if that number is nine,
that means
there will be nine total items.
So the auction will end
without warning.
Here's why you care.
At the end of the auction,
whoever has the most money left
loses their vote at the next
-Tribal Council.
-What?!
BRUCE:
Oh, my God!
PROBST:
So, at any given point,
whoever has the most money
has the most buying power,
and theoretically,
the most risk.
Holy moly.
PROBST:
All right, let's see who has
how much money.
-Jeff.
-Oh. Let's be revealed!
-JAKE: Ooh. Look at that.
-DREW: Look at that.
BRUCE:
Yeah, baby.
-Bruce, what happened?
-[Bruce laughs]
My thought was,
"Slow and steady wins the race.
"Let them run out there
"and I'll just put my shoes on
and I'll get out...
'Cause there's gonna be enough."
It was like
a chicken was picked clean.
So you got just one tube?
-Just got one tube.
-PROBST: All right.
-Shall I draw the number?
-KENDRA: Yes. Go for it.
Hope for 15, guys.
DEE:
Go, baby, 15, let's go.
I know how many total items
in this auction.
You don't.
That's the game.
-BRUCE: Aah!
-[laughs]
Let's birth a new auction.
-Yeah!
-[indistinct chatter]
Oh, I love this.
PROBST:
Bidding is in $20 increments.
Should we have this one covered?
-ALL: No!
-PROBST: All right.
-First item.
-KATURAH: Wait. What is it?
-Salty pretzels and a cold beer.
-AUSTIN: Oh, my God.
-One hundred.
-PROBST: Wow.
Out of the gate: Kendra, 100.
I'll do 200.
-Two hundred to Dee.
-Three hundred.
-[all exclaiming]
-PROBST: Three hundred to Jake.
-Three sixty.
-Kendra at 360.
[exclaiming]
She deserves that pretzel.
Jake clearly does not have 360.
I do not, Jeff.
-Sold to Kendra for $360.
-KATURAH: You better taste that
first auction item, baby!
-Wow!
-Let's go, baby!
-JAKE: There you go.
-Drink that beer.
-This is for my dad.
-JAKE: There you go.
KATURAH:
Yes!
Oh, look at that.
-Cheers!
-Oh, that's huge.
BRUCE:
Look at that thing. Damn.
DEE:
It looks smaller
from over there.
JAKE:
Some pep to that bad boy.
Just like that,
one person is out
and safe and enjoying
their pretzels and beer.
-Shall we get to the next item?
-[overlapping chatter]
[gasping]
French fries, ketchup
and a soft drink.
-Two hundred.
-PROBST: Two hundred
out of the gate to Emily.
-Two twenty.
-Three hundred.
-PROBST: Wow. Quickly. $300.
-Four twenty.
-PROBST: Four twenty.
-Four forty.
-Five hundred.
-PROBST: Five hundred
going once, going twice.
-[gavel bangs]
-Sold to Kellie.
[cheering]
Five hundred dollars
for a bowl of fries,
ketchup and a soft drink.
This is the most
I've eaten in two weeks, Jeff.
-Here we go.
-PROBST: Just give us a taste.
[overlapping chatter]
[cheering]
PROBST:
All right,
take 'em back and enjoy.
KENDRA:
Yeah, baby.
-KELLIE: I love you guys.
-KENDRA: Cheers.
The next item
in the Survivorauction
-shall remain covered.
-I knew it, Jeff.
-Sixty.
-Sixty to Katurah.
-Eighty!
-Two hundred.
-Three twenty.
-Three sixty.
-Four twenty.
-I need to eat. $440.
-Aw. Damn it.
-PROBST: Four forty.
Going once. Going twice.
-Sold to Emily for $440.
-All right, Emily,
-get something good.
-I mean, I'm sure it's edible.
I don't care what it is.
I'm gonna eat it.
Four hundred forty dollars.
Please don't do this
to me, Jeff.
-I... Please don't do this.
-What do you think
-I'm gonna do to you?
-I'm afraid that
that's bat soup.
Everybody is afraid that
-that's bat soup.
-It won't be, Emily.
-It won't be.
-EMILY: Oh, it's worse.
-No, it's good.
Here's what $440 bought you.
-[screaming]
-[cheering, whooping]
JAKE:
Get that! That's what
I'm saying! Yeah!
-[applause]
-KATURAH: There you go!
-There you go!
-That's what we've been
talking about!
So, take a little sample.
Oh, I don't even know
where to start.
-Oh, I love salami.
-KENDRA: Oh, my God.
Oh, it's my favorite.
-DEE: Yes!
-KENDRA: You deserve it, girl.
[whooping, yelling]
[Probst laughs]
-KENDRA: Happy dance!
-[chanting]: Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
-Who are you?!
-[laughing]
-PROBST: All right, take it back
-and enjoy.
-DEE: Let's go, Emily.
-JAKE: Yeah, Emily.
-Good show.
-[whooping]
[indistinct chatter]
Emily down to $60.
Pretty hot day here
in Fiji, right?
Oh, yeah?
Chocolate milkshake.
I'm sorry.
I got to put in my money.
-Nine hundred.
-[all exclaim]
Whoa!
-That's a $900 milkshake!
-Yeah, I got
-to buy a milkshake.
-Damn, Dee! Nice!
Sold to Dee for 900.
Here you go, Jeff.
Take my cash.
Wow! Everything you had.
-Can I try it already?
-You've got to try it.
-That's no joke, man.
-Oh!
EMILY:
Oh, girl, that looks amazing.
Mmm. I feel like
I'm on vacation.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you, thank you.
-PROBST: Wow.
-JAKE: Yeah.
-There you go.
-Nice, Dee.
Next item will remain covered.
-Two hundred.
-Two hundred to Katurah.
-Three eighty.
-PROBST: Julie now in at 380.
Hell, 480!
PROBST:
Katurah gonna spend
all her money.
Four eighty going once, twice.
Sold to Katurah.
Come on up.
[groans]
All your money.
Hey, Survivor.You got this.
These are all good. We're due
for something terrible.
Okay, so if you think
that's terrible...
Oh, no!
I hate this!
You can trade it for this.
-Whoa.
-Damn!
-KENDRA: Go with your gut.
-BRUCE: Go with your gut.
-Just go your gut.
-I ain't got no gut. It's empty.
[Bruce laughs]
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, baby.
-I'm gonna go
with the first one.
-All right.
Here is what you bought...
-Jeff!
-for all of your money.
[Katurah whimpers]
-Oh! Oh.
-PROBST: Two giant...
-What is this?
-fish eyes.
-Oh.
-[all groaning]
PROBST:
These are two
of the biggest eyes
-you'll ever see in a fish.
-It's like sushi.
-BRUCE: Get in there. Come on.
-JULIE: Katurah is killing me.
[gags]
I like sushi, but
this is going a little extreme.
Try to tell yourself
it's gonna fuel your body.
BRUCE:
Come on, kid. Get in there!
I'm fueled. I'm fine.
I'm good. It's good.
All right, head back, Katurah.
I knew it was gonna happen.
All right,
Katurah did not want this.
Let's put it back up for bid.
-Hundred.
-PROBST: One hundred to Austin.
Going once, twice.
Sold to Austin. Come on up.
-[cheering]
-KENDRA: Austin,
probably better than
a sea cucumber. You've got this.
-That's what I'm telling myself.
-[insect buzzing]
Yeah, you know,
when on Survivor.
Oh, my g... I can't believe
he's doing this.
-Here we go. Just dig in.
-All right.
Um, no way.
-JAKE: Yeah, buddy.
-[screaming, exclaiming]
PROBST:
Wow.
Two giant fish eyes.
KELLIE:
Oh, my g... I can't believe
-he's doing this.
-Here we go.
-AUSTIN: All right.
-PROBST: Just dig in.
-No way.
-JAKE: Yeah, buddy!
-[screaming, exclaiming]
Get in there, boy! Yeah!
-PROBST: Wow.
-[screaming]
It's like sashimi.
[Survivors laughing, exclaiming]
Wow. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm good.
-I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
-Oh!
I got to say, Austin,
I'm impressed.
And I still got 600 bucks, so...
Do you want to take it,
or have you had enough?
-I'll take it. Whatever.
-DEE: Yeah!
I don't know if I'll eat
the rest, but I'll take it.
I can't believe the size
of those things.
Oh, my gosh.
PROBST:
So, that was five items,
which means
from this point forward,
any item could be the last item.
The number's right here.
But if you get stuck
with the most money and
there's no item left to bid on,
you lose your vote.
We've got Austin at 600,
Drew at 520,
Julie at 420, Jake still
trying to spend that 340,
and then Kellie at 200
and Bruce still at 80.
And the big question is
how many more items there are.
Let's put the item
that Katurah did not swap for.
-Two hundred.
-PROBST: Two hundred to Kellie.
-Five twenty.
-Five twenty to Drew.
Sold to Drew.
$520
for an unknown covered item.
See a lot of appetizers
out there, Jeff.
-I'm hoping for a meal.
-PROBST: All right. Let's see
-what $520 bought Drew.
-Let's see it.
DREW:
Ooh. Okay.
-That's pretty good.
That's pretty good.
-Pretty good.
-Not what you were hoping for?
-I wanted the carbs, Jeff.
-Yeah?
-I wanted the calories, and this
is gonna be coming out
if I eat it all.
So, I'm happy. I'm happy.
I'd be open to a negotiation
if you had one in mind.
-No, I don't.
-Oh.
-Ah.
-[laughter]
PROBST:
Ready for another item?
-JAKE: Yeah.
-JULIE: Pizza?
PROBST: A giant slice
of pepperoni pizza.
-Oh, I'm sorry, y'all.
-Three forty.
-Two hundred.
-Six hundred.
-PROBST: Austin takes it
at $600.
Does not hesitate,
gets rid of all his money.
No threat of losing his vote.
Julie now
has the most buying power
and the most risk, because
that could be the last item.
Take a big bite of that.
[cheering, exclaiming]
It's a little bit better
than the eye.
-[laughter]
-PROBST: All right.
-Thank you.
-PROBST: We are down to
five people left with money.
Julie, if that is the last item,
it means the auction is over
and you lose your vote.
-Yup.
-PROBST: The slice of pizza...
-was not...
-KATURAH: No!
-DREW: Not!
PROBST:
...the last item.
-Jeff!
-Jeff, man.
Let's take a different path.
A toothbrush, toothpaste,
-and mouthwash.
-Oh!
-DEE: Wow.
-KELLIE: All right.
-Two hundred.
-Four twenty.
-Sold to Julie for $420.
-Yeah, you better
get that toothpaste!
Everything you have.
All of America want
to watch me brush my teeth?
-Yeah. Give it a little sample.
-[laughs]
DEE:
Let's go.
-[whooping]
-KATURAH: Yeah.
I can feel it.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: All right, take it.
-Enjoy.
-Good. Thank you, sir.
KENDRA:
Yeah. Good job.
PROBST:
Julie now out of danger.
Jake, you've been trying
to spend that $340...
-Yeah.
-out of the gate.
You have, fortunately,
one more item,
-at least.
-Thanks...
-thanks, Jeff.
-You did not lose your vote.
-Yet.
-JAKE: Your smile is just
the world to me right now
that I still have my vote,
and you're smiling,
happy for me. Thanks, Jeff.
PROBST:
Let me get another item.
JAKE:
I would love that.
I would love that. Yeah.
Well, there goes me.
KATURAH: That looks heavy.
PROBST: This item will be bought
by one person,
-shared by three, which means
-Oh.
whoever buys it
will choose two people
to come up here and share it.
-AUSTIN: Oh!
-JAKE: What's that?
-PROBST:
Beautiful chocolate cake.
-Oh, my God.
JAKE:
Excuse me, Jeff.
-I'm buying that cake.
-Jake's buying it for $340.
-Everything he has.
-[gavel bangs]
-That looks good, too, Jeff.
-All right, so,
you're gonna have the amount
of time in the sand timer
to share it
with two other players
that you must choose,
and you do it without utensils.
Julie, you have a clean mouth
right now.
-Julie.
-Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
-Let's go!
-PROBST: All right,
one person down.
You have one left to choose.
Anyone feeling
especially hungry?
Uh, Bruce.
PROBST:
Bruce, come on up.
KENDRA:
Yeah. Yeah, Bruce.
Here's how it's gonna work.
Slide it over and let it begin.
Here we go.
Shove it down!
KATURAH:
Bruce, get in there.
Take bigger bites!
Oh, my God.
It hurts, y'all.
PROBST:
I'm gonna pull the cake
-when the last grain drops.
-JAKE: Mmm.
Grab it now before I do.
AUSTIN:
Final grab. Come on, big one.
PROBST:
And that is it.
-Wow.
-Yeah!
-PROBST: Well done.
You killed
a huge chocolate cake.
-KATURAH: Insane. Insane.
-Oh, yeah.
PROBST:
We are now down
to only three people
left with money.
Kellie has 200,
Bruce has 80, Emily down at 60.
The question is
what number is on here?
That was nine items.
If that's it, it means,
Kellie, you will lose your vote
at the next Tribal Council.
Kellie?
Yeah?
There is... another item.
[cheering]
Jeff, I love ice cream.
I could use a margarita.
EMILY: Oh!
There's 100% chance
it's a margarita.
The next item
in the Survivorauction.
KELLIE:
Don't tell me.
-Oh!
-[cheering, indistinct chatter]
-DEE: Enjoy it, baby.
-Oh, my...
-With all your money?
-JAKE: She just went down.
I have a sandwich!
PROBST:
PB and J,
potato chips
and a margarita, as requested.
KENDRA:
Let's go, girl.
-[gasping]
-DEE: Oh.
-I can stay here all day, Jeff.
-That's pretty good.
-It's pretty good.
-I can see it.
KELLIE:
I got to go play the lottery,
Jeff. I don't know.
Wow. I can't believe
this is happening.
-AUSTIN: Wow.
-PROBST: We are down to two.
-Oh, that PB and J.
Bruce at $80, Emily at $60.
Bruce, somehow you went
from starting this auction
at the bottom,
and now, you are at the top,
which means
you're the one now
in danger
if that was the last item.
Bruce, that...
wasthe last item.
DEE:
Oh.
There's the number-- ten items.
This auction is over.
You will not be voting
at the next Tribal Council.
The Survivorauction
is finished.
Leave your food behind,
grab your stuff, head out.
[insects buzzing]
BRUCE:
The auction went horrible.
Losing a vote automatically
puts me in a position
of vulnerability.
Could that make me a target?
Of course it could.
Luckily,
I have a hidden immunity idol
to be able
to protect myself,
at least for the next Tribal.
♪ ♪
-EMILY: God.
-AUSTIN: Oh, that was awesome.
Guys, we did the auction,
and the last time was 2015.
KATURAH:
This is insane.
-KELLIE: Katurah.
-KENDRA: Katurah, you were like,
"I know it's gonna
be something bad,"
and then
it's friggin' fish eyes.
TheSurvivor auction was
a dream come true for me.
I would say I won the strategy
of the auction.
You could have put a bowl
of worms in front of me
and I would have paid $360
for that
first bid off the bat,
so I could have my vote.
When I drink that beer,
and I'm standing there,
I'm just like, "Ha, ha,"
and all my money's gone.
-Yeah.
-I didn't even care
about the beer or the pretzels.
Well, I did care
about the beer 'cause, like...
...he's tall, blonde, blue-eyed,
like, football, American guy
who just loves his beer,
and, like,
he is the big inspiration
for me being out here.
Getting the beer at auction
fueled me to, like, keep going
in this game,
like, unexpectedly.
I grew up with my mom
and my adopted dad,
but I grew up thinking
that he was my dad.
No one told me
that he wasn't my dad.
But I eventually found out my
biological father was out there,
so I got his contact information
from my aunt.
Nervous as hell.
Scariest moment of my life.
Phone rings, and
my dad picks up and says,
"I've been waiting for
this phone call for 18 years."
And then we talked
for, like, three hours.
We cried, we laughed,
and we just have the most
amazing relationship now.
♪ ♪
And so, having that beer
just hit me.
♪ ♪
Having my biological father
watch me on the show, like...
I knew, like, he's gonna be
so proud of me being out here.
And I... I... I...
As soon as I held that beer,
I just thought of him
immediately,
and I had to cheers my dad.
I had 18 years without him,
but we have the rest
of our lives together.
-I'm like... Yeah.
-DEE: Yes.
♪ ♪
DEE:
Are you guys
getting in the water?
-Drew?
-Uh...
EMILY:
There's talk
of a women's alliance.
You know,
we have six women, four men--
easy pickings
if we all just stick together.
Conceptually, it's great, right?
However,
I have really
deep relationships with Drew
and Austin,
and, um, I've built up
a lot of trust with those two
in a deeper way than I have
with any of the women
in this tribe.
Yeah.
EMILY:
So as much as I like,
conceptually,
working with a bunch of women
in this game,
I also have to keep an eye out
for my own game
and think about the alliances
that I've already built.
Like, after
the vote yesterday...
Yeah.
I don't know.
I was just, like, reflecting
on that experience, and
I was just really thankful that
I had somebody in this game that
I could actually really trust.
Are you kidding me? Me too.
And, yeah,
I don't know, I just,
-I really want to work with you.
-Yeah.
-I want to go forward.
I intend to.
-I know. Yeah, yeah.
-So I'm gonna
tell you something.
-Okay.
-And I might need you
to not tell anyone.
-Yeah, for sure.
Um...
There's an all-girls thing
going on.
Kind of started
'cause everybody was just like,
"Oh, there's six girls,
only four guys, and..."
I really, like...
You know, it's-it's a worry,
but I don't believe
that it would hold long-term.
I don't think so, either,
which was, you know,
part of the reason
why I'm telling you.
Everybody likes you,
-and nobody's
coming after y'all right now.
-Okay.
But Jake and Bruce
are kind of, like, targets.
-Targets number one?
-A and B. Yeah.
DREW:
The girls think that they are
very sneaky and that they have
formulated an all-girls alliance
to take them to the end.
In actuality, this potential
all-girls alliance
is porous as it gets,
but right now, I can use them.
It could be very convenient
for flushing Bruce's idol.
The Reba four
wants Bruce gone, and also,
this all-girls alliance
wants Bruce.
This is great news for me,
because I want him
on the outs.
I want him targeted.
I want Belo weakened.
And so part of that is gonna be
building a relationship
with the women-- especially
with Katurah,
because Katurah
doesn't like Bruce one bit.
Look, let me tell you
from the old Belo days,
-Bruce and Jake
are thick as thieves.
-Yeah, I could tell
-from how they talk.
-If they're telling you
that they're not,
-they're lost...
-AUSTIN: I think, last night,
-it really proved,
like, a trust with us.
-Yeah. No.
If you have
a target or anything,
-and we got to
talk through everything...
-That's what I'm saying.
-Absolutely.
-I'm down. 100%.
-You're invested...
-I'm... Look, I'm here.
I'm with y'all.
So what do we want?
I'm down
with whatever you guys say.
DREW:
Katurah, I feel like,
as a, uh, as a sign of trust,
because, you know,
we don't really know each other,
-I'm willing
to follow your lead on this one.
-I, 100%, me, too.
KATURAH:
Honestly, I feel
like it needs to be Bruce.
-Yeah, we could do that,
if you'd like.
-AUSTIN: Yeah.
KATURAH:
We could target Bruce.
Then we got Jake as a backup.
-JULIE: I'm in.
-KATURAH: All right.
Once Bruce goes,
everything opens up.
-It's like...
-I think that the pieces
will scramble out again...
It's like
the last latch on the door.
KATURAH:
There is not
a single one of them
that doesn't know
that I dislike Bruce.
And I have said that Bruce
needs to go for a long time.
Okay. All right.
-Oh. Oh.
-Okay.
-Guys, should we, like,
touch or something?
-Yeah. Yeah.
KATURAH:
I feel like
I've laid the groundwork
to create enough of an alliance
to support me
finally getting out Bruce.
So I'm ecstatic.
I'm freaking out.
I'm like, "Thank God. This is
exactly what I was praying for."
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Good morning.
-Hi, Jeff.
-Morning.
-Morning, Jeff.
All right. Look at this bad boy.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
ALL:
Yeah!
PROBST:
First things first,
-Dee, Kellie,
got to take back the necklaces.
-Oh.
You really don't have to, Jeff.
-Oh, but I do.
-[others chuckle]
PROBST:
Thank you.
DEE:
Oh, no.
Oh, no, Jeff.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna hold on to a rope
that is attached
to a log containing
one third
of your pregame body weight.
At regular intervals,
we're gonna move one knot lower
on the rope,
making it even more difficult.
When you drop, you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final nine.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury.
In addition...
...what I have is...
Oh, gosh.
Jeff.
...a bag of rice.
-Oh!
-What?
AUSTIN:
Oh, my God.
Enough rice to easily get you
through the end of this game.
What's interesting
about today is
you are on the heels
of an auction.
So, question is
have you forgotten
what hunger feels like?
'Cause I promise you,
the hunger will be back.
This offer may not be.
Four people need to sit out
of today's challenge,
give up their shot at immunity.
In other words, vulnerable
tonight at Tribal Council,
in order to get this rice.
Start talking or start sharing.
I'll start, Jeff.
PROBST:
Dee, first one out.
Emily. That's two.
KATURAH:
Can we agree we all need this
and, like, we'll respect
the people who sit out?
I'll tell you what, Katurah,
let me help
incentivize you
just a little bit.
Yeah, yeah.
You got it.
-[gasps]
-What?
That's your rice.
I'll sit, I'll sit.
Somebody else. Somebody else.
PROBST:
Drew is number three.
Somebody's got to go. Come on.
Come on, somebody.
-Is it running out?
-Yeah, it's running out.
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
PROBST:
Katurah gonna sit out.
We have a deal.
Wow. Thank y'all.
-Thank y'all so much.
-[clapping]
-Thank y'all.
-Wow.
That's your rice.
KENDRA:
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
All right, Drew, Katurah,
Emily, Dee,
gonna sit this out.
No shot at immunity.
Take a spot on the bench.
Everybody else, take your spots.
We'll get this going.
Here we go.
Everybody grab your rope.
Then get back on the platform
and I'll tell you when
and you're gonna
pull on that rope
so you're gonna have
one hand above that top knot.
That's it.
All right, everybody
pull back on your rope.
Release your brace.
This challenge is on.
Straight arm, Jake.
Straight arms.
Anything that would
make this less uncomfortable
is not allowed.
-That's the basic rule
on the Survivorchallenge.
-[laughing]
Maximum discomfort.
It's a lot more fun
from over here.
It is.
DEE:
Yeah, that is very true.
PROBST:
We'll be in this section
for five minutes.
Think of this as your warm-up.
So, to remind you,
you each have a third
of your pregame body weight.
That's a lot of pounds up there.
Thank you, Jeff.
PROBST:
And ultimately, it's gonna
be a test of mind over matter.
How much willpower do you have
to hang in there
just a little longer?
All six making round one
look very easy.
I wish it was a little lighter,
but it's not bad.
Let's see if we can
make it a little heavier.
[laughs]
Everybody move down one knot.
And I'm gonna count you in.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Everybody back to one arm,
straight out.
-[whoops]
-PROBST: There you go, Jake.
EMILY:
You got it.
-Am I looking good?
-You're looking good.
-Everybody's looking good.
-Thanks, man.
PROBST:
It just got heavier.
JAKE:
It did. It did.
Can you feel it, Julie?
Oh, I can feel it.
Bruce, how you doing?
It is ironic
to be somewhere so beautiful
doing something so painful.
All right,
move one knot farther down
on that rope.
Five, four,
three, two, one...
Back to one arm.
Let go. Arms straight.
No bending the arms.
JAKE:
Ooh.
PROBST:
Now you're gonna feel it.
That leverage is pulling you.
We'll be here for five minutes.
Got to say, I am impressed.
Everybody's still in.
It is not as easy as it looks.
He is?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
[exhales]
How's Bruce?
He's pretty solid, but...
Okay.
All right,
we're gonna move one knot lower.
Five, four,
three, two, one...
Release.
Ooh!
PROBST:
Kellie cannot make
the transition. Kellie's out.
-KATURAH: Good try, Kellie.
-DEE: Good job, Kellie.
-Good fight.
-Good job.
Kellie is the first casualty
and we are down to five.
Ooh-wee!
PROBST:
Keep your arm out. Out.
Kendra can't hold. Kendra drops.
Julie.
We're down to four.
-EMILY: Sorry, Kendra.
-KATURAH: Awesome job.
PROBST:
Julie and Austin on one end,
-Bruce and Jake on the other.
-[exhales]
Battling for immunity.
Day 16.
Survivor45.
KELLIE:
Jake, keep holding.
KATURAH:
You got this.
Go wherever you need to go.
I'm right here. I'm on Survivor.
I'm not going anywhere.
[laughing]
PROBST:
All right, in a moment,
you're gonna move down
to the final section.
You're not gonna
have a knot for leverage.
-Just that rope. No wrapping.
-No wrapping. No wrapping.
No wrapping. I won't wrap.
PROBST:
Five, four,
three, two, one...
Release. Straight arms, Jake.
Let's go.
-KENDRA: Yeah!
-KATURAH: You got it.
You got it.
Everybody has navigated
the final transition.
[cheering]
PROBST:
Austin trying to hang in there.
KATURAH:
You got this, Austin.
EMILY:
You got it.
PROBST:
It's as heavy as it can get,
and it's heavy.
DEE:
Keep focused.
-Keep focused.
-KATURAH: Come on, Mama J.
It's impressive all four
of you are still in this.
That's a lot of weight you're
holding, a lot of leverage
trying to pull you
off of that platform.
You got to fight against it.
You got to pull back on it.
-Engage those muscles.
-KATURAH: You got this, Austin!
PROBST:
Get that
isometric strength going.
KELLIE:
Just a few more. You got this.
Come on, buddy.
-Nah-nah, baby.
-PROBST: Jake struggling,
but he's hanging in there.
-Austin's struggling,
but he's hanging in.
-Yeah!
-KELLIE: Come on.
-DEE: Get out of your head.
Stay in there. Keep fighting.
-Day 16.
-DEE: Fight it.
Get out of your head.
PROBST:
Austin drops. He's out.
We're down to three.
Julie on one end,
Bruce and Jake on the other.
-Whoa! Mama's up there!
-Julie, you got to
represent, baby.
-Let's go.
-You got this, babe.
PROBST:
Remember to
keep your arms straight.
You're doing well, Jake.
Keep fighting, Bruce.
Jake drops. We got a showdown.
Julie and Bruce for immunity.
-[cheering]
-You guys are looking amazing!
-PROBST: The two oldest
people in this game.
-[whooping]
KENDRA:
You guys, that's amazing.
-[overlapping chatter]
-KELLIE: Hold on, Julie.
Hold on, Mama J.
PROBST:
Let's go, Julie.
This is it.
You want to get to nine.
It's right here
in your hands, literally.
-A piece of rope.
-JAKE: Bruce, you got it!
PROBST:
Bruce's hand slipping
farther down on the rope.
Julie's out.
Bruce wins
individual immunity.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council
and guaranteed a spot
in the final nine.
What an effort.
Huge showdown
by Julie and Bruce.
[laughs]
Bruce, come on over.
-KENDRA: Amazing.
-JAKE: Great job, brother.
Amazing.
PROBST:
You got a big smile today.
Yeah, man. [laughs]
I'm gonna put this on you.
Give it to us.
-What's the story right now
for the second chancer, Bruce?
-[laughs]
My kids mean the world to me.
My wife means the world to me.
And then I saw that I was yellow
for my daughter Sydney.
Like, that-that threw it over.
-PROBST: Really?
-Yeah.
So something as random maybe,
or are you saying
maybe it's not?
[stammers] [sighs]
I talk to 'em every day,
so maybe she sent that my way.
Syd strength.
That's what I have.
However it was,
it worked out for you.
Safe tonight,
cannot be voted out.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final nine.
[laughs]
As for the rest of you,
after 16 tough days
on Survivor45,
somebody
will be voted out tonight--
ninth person out,
second member of our jury.
Grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
Don't forget to take
your basket of rice. Congrats.
-Thank you, Jeff.
-[indistinct chatter]
Oh, my God!
As soon as Bruce wins immunity,
I immediately say,
"You got to be kidding me."
I know that it's gonna be
a crazy, scrambling afternoon.
Come on. Day 16, Survivor45.
We've had an auction
and a rice negotiation
in two days.
I know what you're thinking--
I should do that.
You should.
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
Bruce, congratulations, man.
KATURAH:
Yeah, Bruce.
-Solid as a rock up there, man.
-Solid.
-That was hard.
-That was... Yeah, it was hard.
Definitely.
KENDRA:
Bruce won.
Horrible thing.
[laughs]
KENDRA:
I was like,
"Aah! He doesn't have a vote.
This is my chance to strike."
Everyone was 100%
in on it, and now
he has another day here
with, also, his idol.
So no vote,
he's got an idol in his pocket
and he's got
an immunity necklace on.
Not a bad day to be Bruce.
So I'm gonna start...
Listen,
I'm gonna start on the fire
so we can
get that rice cooking.
-What's up? What's up?
-[whooping]
KELLIE:
Bruce won.
Of course Bruce wins.
Can't get rid of Bruce.
Bruce is gonna be here forever.
He's my ball and chain.
I don't think Bruce realizes
how absurd it is
that he's still here.
And now he's literally
a spectator
at this Tribal Council.
He's not voting
and he's not on the block.
So he can just sit there--
♪ la-da-da♪--
and talk his crap
and enjoy it the whole time.
KENDRA:
Okay, let's look
at the options here.
KELLIE:
What do you think, Emily?
You're the most logical of all.
Am I the most logical?
The fact that Bruce
won immunity today
did throw a little bit
of a wrench into today's plan.
That shifts
the target onto Jake.
But Bruce could potentially
play his idol for Jake.
So tonight,
every single vote matters.
I do think that it's
very likely that Jake goes home.
-Okay.
-However, I do think it's
very likely that somebody else
gets votes, in case
that Bruce gives Jake his idol.
I think it would be me, because
they think I'm close to Bruce.
People keep saying that,
you know,
it looks like me and Bruce
are really close--
which is, like, not my doing.
Bruce just
follows me around and, like,
refuses to let me be free.
You are my nu... Come on.
Co-Co-Come.
You are my number one.
I've said that
-from the beginning.
-It's gonna make me panic,
Bruce.
That could be
the problem for me tonight.
So, is there another name?
Backup?
I'm, like,
trying to rack my brain...
Who wants to be the first person
to throw out another name?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-JULIE: That's the truth.
But if we can convince Jake
that something's not up,
-he won't play
his Shot in the Dark, right?
-BOTH: Yeah.
KELLIE:
My biggest concern now is,
if Bruce and Jake are safe, am I
the last resort
contingency vote
or could the votes
ricochet onto me
because I'm sort of seen
as part of that group?
What are
your thoughts for today?
"Don't go home."
That's my thoughts.
-Okay.
-Do you have anybody
that you would want to go home?
Well, do you guys
have anything in mind?
Yeah, maybe. A little bit.
Do you have an idea?
No. I felt like you guys
just said you had an idea.
-[Kellie laughs]
-And now you're...
I feel like they're baiting me.
They want me to say a name
first. They're pushing so hard.
That tells me one thing.
They want
me to trip up. They want me
to throw someone out there.
And you know what?
I'm not gonna play that game.
Here's my thing. I feel like
I need to take my foot off the
gas a little bit and, like...
-I get that, I hear you.
-My problem
last time was, like...
Here's our concern, is that
if we do want to do something,
we need your vote.
-If you're down.
-Yeah. Oh, yeah. I'm down.
I'm down. I'm down for not...
Yeah, no, I'm down for
not-not me. Love that. [laughs]
EMILY:
We'll circle around.
I feel good about this, though.
-Okay. All right.
-I'm good for not me.
We all know
I'm the backup to Bruce.
We know I'm on the bottom.
I put my name out last Tribal
by putting myself out there.
I failed.
But...
if I'm going out of this game,
I'm going out swinging.
No one is discussing
an alternate name.
And you know what?
That tells me one thing.
They're still
planning on voting for me.
And if they are,
I need an idol, man.
So I need to find one fast.
KATURAH:
Jake is visibly
looking for an idol.
He's not trying to hide it.
Everybody sees it.
DEE:
Jake just passed by,
and he's idol searching.
Okay, good call.
Jake is really desperate.
Jake is canvassing this island,
searching for an idol.
What if he finds an idol?
Then who do
we split the vote between?
And also, Bruce, maybe,
in a charitable gesture,
a fit of generosity,
could play his idol on Jake.
Hey, like, just...
[both laugh]
DREW:
Tonight's vote was going to
come down to a dogpile on Jake.
I think that could be a risk.
So I have a plan.
What if we avoid
the Jake question altogether?
♪ ♪
DREW:
Kellie has a lot of power.
She's a leading threat
right now.
We can just
take her off the table and then
return the next round to
that question of Bruce or Jake.
Yeah.
Personally, I'd like Jake out.
DEE:
Yeah, for sure.
-I'd want to think about it.
-AUSTIN: Okay.
-DEE: 'Cause it
doesn't feel like 100%.
-Okay.
Something just doesn't feel 100.
Yeah.
Everyone is so gung ho
on that Jake plan, that now,
I'm trying to reel the fish in
a little bit, and I'm having
some difficulty, because
I have a second thought. I say,
"Gee, maybe they have a point.
"Jake is a loose cannon.
"Do I really want
to give him a second chance?
Let's just boot Jake.
Nice and easy peasy. Done."
The decision between
Jake or Kellie
is something that
we have to figure out
and decide
before Tribal Council.
Either way,
Bruce winning immunity
is gonna be a major problem
for somebody else tonight.
♪ ♪
All right.
-Ten players left.
-[laughing]
Jeff, I would like
to know the, uh, statistic
on the person
that doesn't have a vote
but wins immunity
so that they can actually have
some kind of relevance
in the game.
-I'd like to know what that is.
-Sure. Hang on.
-Oh. Oh. Yeah.
-[chuckling]
I think you're it.
-Yeah. Nice.
-[indistinct chatter]
-There you go.
-PROBST: Yeah.
Yeah, put that in the books.
So let's talk now
about today's rice negotiation.
-You had fun with that. [laughs]
-DEE: He definitely did.
We're still a little bitter.
-Evil Jeff came out.
-[laughter]
Had a little flair there.
Are you gonna
pull out a knife right now?
-'Cause you got
the same face going on.
-[laughing]
I don't like being predictable.
-Ah.
-I love it.
Yeah.
One of the things required today
to get the rice was four people
had to volunteer to sit out.
Drew, what made you stand up
and say, "I'll do it"?
DREW:
Well, listen, I mean,
in that moment, it didn't matter
who was stepping up
so long as the body stepped up
and the rice flow was stanched.
Jake, the rice negotiation
is a reminder that, even though
you're in the individual portion
of the game, you are still,
in many ways,
relying on each other.
I-I don't think altruism
exists in Survivor.
It-it really doesn't,
because there's a benefit
or a negative
to doing everything that you do.
Um...
I think there's a couple reasons
you decide to...
...step out. I think, you know,
you're hungry.
Um...
you do feel comfortable.
It's-it's...
I'm sorry,
what was the question?
Yeah, I was gonna ask.
You're being so thoughtful.
Is that because
you're exhausted
or you're thinking through
the question?
I'm honestly trying to think
through the question, but...
Do you mind if I make a pitch?
-No.
-JAKE: Okay.
-Good. Um...
-PROBST: It's your Tribal.
I-It's not...
The way...
Wow.
Talk about
the gas out right there.
-[laughs]
-Take your time, man.
You'll find it.
JAKE:
Yeah.
The past couple votes, Jeff,
have kind of been a dogpile,
but I don't think
that's playing Survivor.
And if we're all gonna
dogpile on me, the person who's
next from the bottom is
making the wrong move tonight.
Why would it be you, Jake?
I stuck my neck out
on the line for Kaleb.
I tried to take a big swing.
I was willing to go to rocks,
but I missed.
I came up short.
Kellie, what do you make
about what Jake is doing?
KELLIE:
He does make some good points.
And I understand
that there is a balance
between playing it safe
and playing big moves.
I think a real hard thing
to do in this game
is figure out
where is that line.
And unfortunately,
right now, I think Jake
just teetered a little bit
on one side too fast.
Dee, how comfortable
are you that the vote
is going
the way you think it is?
Right now, it feels united.
If it's united, like,
eight votes on me tonight,
like, someone's
making the wrong move.
I-It's shocking
how many people think
they're in a safe spot
in this game right now.
PROBST:
Katurah, it would seem
that if it was a unanimous vote,
that it isn't a bad move
to go with the flow,
because you just get rid of
somebody, and there is no blood.
So what do you make of this?
I think Jake's kind of
making a variety of points.
He's a lawyer.
His intellect is clear.
We all know that.
-I think... [chuckles]
-I don't know about that.
I think he's trying to rally up
some votes and get people
who may feel that
they are on the bottom
or they could potentially
be the next vote
to start getting
a little nervous and think,
"Well, should
I do something differently?"
PROBST:
Emily, what's your take on this?
Just where we are, once again,
one person feeling it's them,
and on the surface,
everybody telling them
that is the case.
It's funny, 'cause
rarely in the game of Survivor
is every single person
on the exact same page.
So it's interesting
to me that Jake
is as concerned as he is, right?
Because history says that with
Survivor,that rarely happens.
PROBST:
Jake, a couple of people
have suggested that,
but you keep the Heisman out,
which is,
"No, it's me. It's 100% me."
I-I feel like
people are lying to me.
I feel like it's me tonight.
But the thing is, if there is
a vote split tonight,
who is this
getting split between?
'Cause if I pull out my i...
If I pull out...
KENDRA:
Mm.
If I pull out an idol tonight
or I decide
to play a Shot in the Dark...
...you're gone.
You're gone
if there's a vote split
or whoever I decide is gone.
Katurah, you had a reaction
to Jake's last comment.
I was reacting to him saying,
"If I play myidol."
It just heightens the fear.
You never know
what's gonna happen.
I mean, I feel like Jake could
have some tricks up his sleeve.
And, you know, you don't want
to get hit with a stray bullet.
All right, it is time to vote.
Katurah, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
JAKE:
Look, Jeff.
I've had terrible reads
in this game so far.
That's why I'm in
the spot that I'm in.
But, Jeff,
I would love to be wrong.
Maybe?
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Thanks, Jake.
Jake played
his Shot in the Dark,
which means there is not
a vote in here from Jake.
He forfeited that vote
for a one-in-six shot at safety.
If this says you are safe,
any votes cast against you
will not count.
If it says "not safe," any votes
cast against you will count.
Does lightning strike twice?
Jake, you are...
...not safe.
Any votes cast against you
will count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote.
Jake.
Jake. Two votes Jake.
Jake. Three votes Jake.
Kellie.
Three votes Jake,
one vote Kellie.
Kellie. Three votes Jake,
two votes Kellie.
Kellie. We're tied.
Oh, people are playing Survivor.
PROBST:
Three votes Jake,
three votes Kellie.
[mutters]
Kellie.
That's four votes Kellie,
three votes Jake, one vote left.
Ninth person voted out
and the second member
of our jury: Kellie.
Whoa!
Sorry. Whoa.
What the hell, guys?
[sighs]
-[quietly]: I'm so sorry.
-JAKE: Oh.
All right. I mean, I respect it.
I'm sorry, guys, I mean,
I'm just really shocked.
Can we hug you?
JAKE:
Love you, Kellie.
Should have trusted my gut.
Kellie, the tribe has spoken.
KENDRA:
I love you, Kel.
-I love you, Kellie.
-KATURAH: I love you, Kellie.
-PROBST: Time for you to go.
-JAKE: Love you, Kel.
Love you, kid.
Talk to you soon.
Bye.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
BRUCE:
My closest ally is gone.
Now it's becoming scary.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
If Dee's in the final three,
Dee wins.
AUSTIN:
I can't blindside Dee.
I love talking with her.
I love hanging out with her.
All three will lose their vote.
Whoa!
My mind just goes black.
This one burns.
I'm not gonna lie.
I feel like I had
a lot of game left in me,
and I had
a bad gut feeling today.
I didn't listen to it
but I did everything I could
to try to set myself up
in a good position,
and I just
was one step too slow.
So, credit to everybody else,
and I'm honored to have had
the opportunity
to play Survivor.
[roars]