What was the... point?
He's literally an idiot.
No one's gonna trust q from now on.
Karma is a bitch.
Previously on survivor
that now we could pull off a blindside.
Everyone is so distracted, I could
drive something that's a little risky.
The idol has zero value to me now.
- I'm ready to burn it on the spot.
- Right.
Tiff's gonna play her idol, so now
we've got to figure out what
the heck we're gonna do.
- Yeah.
I'm beginning to feel pretty nervous.
So I am 100% playing my idol.
If anybody has an advantage or an idol,
and you want to play it, now
would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member
of our jury... hunter.
Hunter, the tribe has spoken.
Yes, they have.
There it is in all of its splendor.
After tribal council, I was so ticked off.
No one told me there was a split vote
between q and hunter.
And so I am trying to...
Hold my composure so I don't explode,
but I'm thinking, "what
the heck, you ho-bags?"
How y'all feeling? Y'all okay?
I just want to know what is it about me
that made y'all say, "no,
we don't want to let Liz in
on the split vote"?
Honestly, Liz, everything happened
ten minutes before
tribal, and there was...
- By the time...
- Is that true?
- That is straight-up what happened.
- That's straight-up.
Well, damn.
We thought he had an idol,
and we was like, "all right, well,
just in case, let's just split the votes."
They're like, "how
are we gonna do that?"
We're like, "well, Liz is already voting..."
Okay.
'Cause I felt stupid as...
We said, "Liz is already voting with you."
Like, stupid as... just now.
Considering I was the only person
left out of this vote, I feel pretty dumb.
On top of that, I wanted to get q out.
He did almost blow up my game,
and he's not someone that
I can trust moving forward.
Hunter's also got to be crazy
to not see that blindside coming.
If he had an idol, he
should have played it.
No, he overplayed his
hand and he thought,
"I can save this for the next time
because clearly everyone
hates q right now."
Tonight,
tribal erupted as Jeff predicted it would.
Once again, q was causing chaos,
and because of that,
it kind of threw hunter off the scent.
If he did have an idol,
I guess the smokescreen was so good
that he didn't play it because now
our biggest physical threat is on his way
to the jury house.
He's grown. If he wants to...
If he wants to reconcile
things, he could come talk.
At this point, my immediate
next step is to get q out.
I'm tired of the drama,
I'm tired of the chaos.
That man did too much.
He flew too close to the
sun, and his wings burnt off.
And now he's feeling the pressure.
Is Maria on the beach with q?
Yeah. Maria went to go talk to q, I think.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
- Okay?
- Come on. Come here.
Right now q is, like,
sitting back in the shadows.
Q is sort of checked
out of the game mentally.
But I think that q still
has some fight in him.
So, for me, this is a great
opportunity to connect,
but he's a wild card at this point.
I know, basically, I got
to win the rest of the way,
and, you know, I'm cool
with going through like that.
And when I lose, if I go home, I go home.
At this point, I think
everyone wants me out,
so there's no need for me to go around
and sit around the fire
and talk to these people.
They really don't want to talk to me.
So I'm okay with that.
Right now my strategy
moving forward is,
first win the immunity.
If I can win, and now that
it's in the individual stage,
I control my own destiny.
I'm not out of this game, trust me.
It might look like it, but it's not.
Yeah.
Q is not only a good person,
but, like, he's also a
number that I can use
to vote with me, and so I
I definitely want to keep him around.
Q's an easy vote.
Everybody wants him out, but in my mind
there are bigger targets here, and so
it may be time to focus
on somebody else.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Kenzie.
How do you feel about yesterday's vote?
I mean, I'm glad it went
the way it did. Like.
I think we can.
I know that this is a hard thought for you,
but I think q would be
willing to work with us,
in that, he told me last night,
"I'm a vote. Use me."
Yesterday the plan was to blindside tiff,
but then we switched it to hunter.
But the biggest thing for
me is that tiff has an idol.
That's not a secret.
And...
Tiffany's sort of been
on my radar for a while.
Evidently, she's still
on Kenzie's radar, too,
which is just music to my ears.
- I want her gone regardless.
- Okay.
Tiff has been my number
one since day one.
We have voted the exact
same way this entire game.
Tiff and I have made
every move together.
We have played almost
the exact same game, so
I've got to differentiate.
I've got to build my résumé,
and a huge checkpoint
on your résumé is voting
out your number one.
That means I just need to be
a little more sneaky than her
to get her out first
before she comes for me.
'Cause I know it's
coming. I know it's coming.
Come on in!
Very quiet today.
- This course... this is crazy.
- Yeah.
- This is day 18, survivor46.
- You're gonna
earn it again.
Yay.
I got to say, Charlie,
today you all look noticeably smaller.
- Yeah.
- I can see the clothes are big.
Your bodies are shrinking.
Are you starting to feel
that cumulative effect?
Listen, every time I stand up,
I literally feel like I'm
about to faint, you know.
I have to go back down
on my hands and knees.
I've never felt that ever
before in my whole life.
All right, shall we get to
today's reward challenge?
For today's challenge, you're gonna race
through a series of
obstacles until you reach
a sack of sandbags.
You're gonna throw those
sandbags into a net tunnel
and then use your hands
to get 'em out the other side.
Once they're all through,
you'll grab one last sandbag,
go under a net, crawl, and attempt
to land that sandbag on a very tall target.
First person to finish wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
- Yes. - You know we do.
- It's day 18.
You've gone a long time without food.
You passed up the opportunity at rice.
So I know you're gonna be
glad to hear that you're playing
for the biggest reward of the season.
Applebee's.
Yes!
- Wow.
- My god.
My god.
You want burgers?
- Wings. -Yeah.
- Yes.
- I want chicken wings.
- Wings.
- And French fries.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- French fries?
- Yes.
I think we got you covered.
- For real?
- Yes.
Every Wednesday,
my daughter and I have
- survivor sleepover.
- Wow.
We go directly to
applebee's, I get the burger,
she gets the pizza,
and then we go home.
Then we watch survivor. Yay!
If only you can win this challenge.
All right, let me walk you through
what's in store for the winner.
All the apps you love.
Boneless wings.
Oh, my god.
- Spinach and artichoke dip.
- God.
Chicken quesadillas.
We're just getting started, Charlie.
Perhaps you're interested
in the bourbon street chicken & shrimp.
- Yeah.
- Or maybe you're in the mood,
like Liz, for a burger.
How about the bourbon
street mushroom.
- Swiss burger?
- That's my favorite.
- My god.
- That's 100% ground beef.
It's my favorite one.
Damn.
Smothered in sauteed onions
- and mushrooms.
- Jeff, you're killing us.
- My god.
- Somebody say dessert?
- Yes. Yes. Chocolate. Chocolate.
- The chocolate one
- I was telling you guys about.
- We got some dessert.
How about the oreo cookie shake?
Yeah.
I might eat it even though I'm allergic.
And to close it out,
an applebee's reward
would not be complete
without the shark bowl.
Applebee's rum
cocktail favorite.. Ooh, careful now.
All this can be yours if...
you win this challenge.
All right, we'll draw for spots.
- Get it on. Let's do it.
- Do it.
All right, here we go.
Applebee's. Biggest reward
of the season, survivor46.
Survivors ready?
Go!
You're going over,
over and through with this first obstacle.
Everybody moving quickly.
Q is out first, then tiff.
Here comes Ben. Start
untying your sandbags.
Charlie's through.
Liz is through.
And Kenzie's... through.
Once all your bags are
out, start launching 'em
in that net tunnel.
Keep tossing.
Q has all his through.
Q in the lead.
Ben is now through.
Tiff is through, working on hers.
It is q, tiff, Venus, Charlie and Ben.
Maria, Liz and Kenzie still working to get
all their bags in.
Q is through.
He's working on that last sandbag.
That's the money right
there. That's the one
you're going to land on the target.
Day 18, applebee's on the line.
It's q in the lead.
There's tiff.
Q working through that net crawl.
Here goes Maria. She's in it.
Here comes Tiffany.
Everybody else is working
on their sandbags now.
Tiff is moving quickly
through that net crawl.
That's how you do it.
Q is out. Get that
sandbag and start tossing.
All you got to do is stick that sandbag
at the top of that target.
Charlie's in the net crawl.
There's Ben. Venus is there.
Kenzie struggling to get through.
My god. It's so hard.
Liz in dead last.
18 days of fatigue showing up right now.
The answer to your
problem is applebee's.
You just got to earn it.
Q with the first toss. He's got a time lead.
Tiff is out. Start untying, tiff.
Q with another toss.
Q just misses.
Here goes tiff.
Tiff on and off with her first toss.
Here's Maria.
Got to get that sandbag out.
Here comes Ben.
Charlie's through.
Venus is through. Bunch
of people through at once.
Everybody on the sandbags
except for Kenzie and Liz,
taking a very long time
through the net crawl.
- My god.
- Keep fighting!
You're still in this.
Q is on and off.
Here goes Maria.
Maria's short.
Ben way short.
Charlie's short. Everybody's short.
Somebody's gonna win this, and
the whole day is gonna change.
Want that burger!
Here comes Liz.
- Kenzie's through.
- My god.
Let's go!
One toss is all it takes.
This is what you dream about
when you dream about survivor.
This moment right here.
Venus with the right
height, just a little short.
Tiff is on and off again.
Tiff and q have been
very close several times.
Who's gonna pull it out?
Kenzie way short.
Here goes Liz with her first toss.
Liz almost sticks one.
- That was close.
- That was close, Liz.
Sandbags everywhere.
Day 18, applebee's on the line.
All it takes is one toss.
Tiff a little long.
Here goes q.
Q does it!
Q wins reward!
- Way to go, q.
- Applebee's.
- Biggest reward of the season.
- Good job, q.
You killed it, my guy.
Nothing easy out here.
Everybody exhausted.
All right, q, come on over.
Got some talking to do.
- Whoo! -All right, so, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You have earned a great reward,
biggest of the season... applebee's.
Gonna sweeten the deal a
little. This reward is gonna
take place at the sanctuary,
where good things happen.
And it's an overnight stay.
- My god. Wow.
- Wow.
You have a lot of power in the game
and a lot of strategic decisions to make.
Choose one person to join you.
So, Jeff,
in my everyday life, I always
try to make things right.
So, for my first choice,
I'm gonna choose tiff.
Tiff, come on over.
Yay.
What an interesting choice, given
the last tribal where you two were done.
Jeff, I'm-I'm actually surprised,
but I am excited because I
do feel like we need to talk
in, like, a setting where
it's not high pressure,
not a whole bunch of people around
and just really be able to hash things out.
All right, q, choose
another person to join you.
- I'm gonna beg.
- Before you decide
I'm gonna beg. Please.
Well, Liz is already begging.
Please.
The next choice that
I'm gonna make, Jeff,
it's just based off,
when I was out there by myself,
there was one person that came
and checked on me, genuinely,
wanted to know if I was all right.
So I just want to say thank you.
And the next choice
I'm gonna make is Maria.
- Thank you.
- Maria, come on over.
- Yeah.
All right, q, you have one more person.
So it's gonna be four people
at the sanctuary for applebee's,
four people back at camp,
and you have one person,
Liz, sobbing,
has talked about food this entire season,
how she can't eat certain things,
therefore she's more hungry.
But it's also a million-dollar game
with only a few people left.
Liz... she hasn't eaten,
in almost 18 days.
This is something that
she could potentially eat.
But Kenzie was with me since day one,
and it's something in me is saying,
"bring the family back together."
So my decision
is basically going to be to bring Kenzie.
- My god.
- Come on over, Kenzie.
The yanu three is back together again
after declaring they
were dead at tribal council.
Sorry, y'all.
Liz, do you feel comfortable
talking about what you're feeling?
I'm pissed!
Y'all say you ain't gone without eating.
I see you eat every day!
Q, you almost blew up my whole game!
You overshadowed
everything I was trying to do!
And I said it's cool.
I didn't say nothing!
I don't even want to be around y'all!
I'm just... q
you blew up my whole freaking spot.
I didn't even know about the damn
- split vote last night.
- But, Liz,
you voted for me last night, so.
I made decisions based off
where my head is right now
in the game. I'm sorry.
I'm over it now.
Thank y'all for letting me have that.
I feel better.
I just exploded.
I'm sorry.
Back to your regularly
scheduled program.
Liz, you don't have to apologize
for having your emotions.
Obviously, missing out on rice
is coming into play now.
I haven't eaten since the merge.
I've had zero calories since the merge.
But there's hope in the game always.
I don't even think I screamed
that hard during my divorce.
All right, here's what's gonna happen.
Q, Kenzie, tiff, Maria,
you're gonna leave
here, go to the sanctuary.
Applebee's chef is there waiting for you.
Fresh, beautiful applebee's food.
You will spend the night,
get a good night's sleep,
and return to camp in the morning.
Head out, enjoy a
well-deserved afternoon.
Thanks, Jeff.
Thank you. Thanks, q.
Liz, Ben, Venus, Charlie,
got nothing for you. Grab
your stuff. Head back to camp.
I am... So... angry.
Q screwed me over. Not only
am I not going on this
reward, not only am I not eating,
but now I'm not feeling that
connection to my daughter
and our survivor ritual,
and I'm gonna have to go back
and just sit in all this disgusting feelings.
Look, survivor'stough.
Think you can do it? Let's
see. Apply to be on survivor.
Okay.
Thank you for letting
me have my moment.
I let it out.
I'm over it.
Thank you for letting me...
- Spew what I had to spew.
- Hey.
My god. I was, like, literally
screaming at this person.
We've all wanted to do
that to q at least once.
I'm so mad at q.
I mean, everyone's
aware that I have allergies.
Onsurvivor, I can't really eat much.
I'm allergic to coconut,
most fruits, chicken.
A lot of everyday foods
causes my throat to clench.
But I can eat any kind of beef, and
the burger is the exact
burger that I order.
It's like our thing. Like, the...
So, to not pick me and deny someone
who has barely eaten in 18 days,
who has this emotional
connection with this meal
I don't know what kind
of person does that.
You, of all people, should have been...
He's a villain, yo, straight up.
There's nothing else to say.
He's a villain, bro. Like, that's it.
You know, Liz has a daughter at home,
and when the applebee's
reward gets revealed,
Liz very publicly states
that this would make her feel at home.
That bourbon burger is what I get, too.
And on top of that,
the bourbon burger
is her go-to menu item.
My anger is satisfying
my hunger right now.
Yeah, my need for vengeance.
Like, how can you not feel for that?
But I think q is working from the bottom,
so the only option he has is
to rekindle his old alliances.
But I think they would be
idiots if they fell for this crap.
If I were in their position, I'd be like,
"yo, let me get the applebee's
and still get q out next."
Bula. Welcome to applebee's.
Bula.wow.
- Look at that food.
- Wow.
- Cheers.
Applebee's, literally, like, is the spot.
- Okay.
We get these big,
beautiful shark bowl drinks.
I take one sip and I'm like, "yeah.
Yeah. We about to
have a good time in here."
Hell yeah. Think amazing.
Giddyap.
- This never tasted better.
- In my entire life.
Me and my friends go to applebee's
every week just for the
spinach and artichoke dip,
I promise you.
This the appetizer, y'all.
I know. My god. This
is an appetizer. I forgot.
As soon as it entered my body,
I felt, like, 18 days of
starvation just evaporate.
I'm ready to play survivor again. Let's go.
Well, Liz was pissed.
- My god.
- Yeah.
- That was tough.
- Q, you might have to watch your back
when you get back to the camp.
It was tough, but, you know,
I've dealt with that, like firing people.
So I was just like, "man,
that's sad, but dang."
- Yeah?
- It was really hard to watch.
- Yeah.
- It was tough.
It was hard for me
to see Liz crying like that, but
at this point I think
everyone wants me out.
So my only option
is to make my bed back where I started,
and that's with the yanu three.
Man, it would make
sense for us and siga,
your two... Ben, Charlie and you,
and then the three of us, and...
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We'll see what happens.
I mean, I really have no
strong ties to Venus or Liz,
so I have... I have no qualms
- about that whatsoever.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I don't either.
For me, this moment was about
pushing my game forward
with the right people.
Maria... she is someone
that's been in my corner,
and those are the
reasons I made my choices.
I don't owe Liz anything.
- Thank you, q.
- Yeah. Thank you, q.
I can't believe this is
happening right now.
I know.
While we're eating, I'm thinking,
q is like my unhealthy boyfriend.
He's buying me a nice
meal at applebee's,
hoping I just get amnesia
and forget about the fact
that he's left me out of
plans for half of this game.
Like, no, I'm smart, q.
Takes a little more to woo me.
You ready for the main course?
- Yes.
- Ooh. Wow.
- My god, it's mashed potatoes.
- I know.
- You're gonna have to roll me out of here.
On top of that, I don't know
how he could pick me over Liz.
I was like, "damn, q, like, that's cold."
Like, that is cold.
So I'm like, "after all the
nonsense you've pulled"
"the past couple of days, like,
I'm just supposed to forgive you
because we broke bread together?"
Like, that's ridiculous.
Hope you guys are enjoying
that shrimp and chicken..
- It's amazing.
- OMG.
- Here is a burger on the house.
- Thank you so much.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
- Wow. Beautiful.
- My god.
Our stomachs have shrank
so much that my stomach hurt.
And the burger comes out.
This is the bourbon burger that
Liz gets every single Wednesday.
Thank you.
And I can see why.
Like, it's so melty, it's so moist,
and the mushrooms and the onions.
But I'm so full of all the other stuff.
Like, I just couldn't do it.
And I am mortified because
I'm one of the people
who are, like, taking
her burger dream away.
Wow. I'm about to sleep like a baby.
- I could sleep right now.
- Like, immediately right now.
Okay.
It's, like, really hard today.
I'm just in my feelings.
And it's not just about food.
I grew up really poor.
My family had a lot of food insecurity.
Pretty much, we barely ever had enough.
And so, being able to
sit down at applebee's
with my daughter is so important to me.
My favorite part of the week
is... it sounds so silly,
but it's picking her up after yoga.
We go immediately to applebee's.
I turn my phone off.
And that's the one night of the week
where it's just us,
and it's something we bond over.
And to have so much hope that,
"okay, Liz, you're gonna get
this, you're gonna get this,"
and then it's... It's applebee's,
and it's the thing I order.
I really wanted that connection to my kid
and that delicious, juicy burger.
Wow.
This'll definitely tide us over.
- See y'all.
- See you later. -Enjoy, q.
I ain't buying none of this crap.
Play me once, shame on you.
Play me twice, shame on me.
- Yeah.
- I'm not rerouting my game
because you're going on an apology tour.
Q's brought us on this reward,
and we're in this, like, wonderful mood.
And then, like, the minute
q steps out, tiff and Kenzie said,
"q's got to go. Q's got to go."
Right.
Yeah.
Q is still
a number for me. Q is somebody I trust.
But it sounds like
q has really rubbed people
the wrong way long enough, and
it might have to be his time to go.
Not a bad sunrise.
This is stunning.
Yeah.
How you feeling today, Liz?
I feel all right.
A little nervous if we
have a challenge today.
Yeah.
Since they're so well-fed and rested.
- What's up? -Hey.
- Good morning.
We were just wondering
when we'd see you.
We don't need to hear all the details,
but I do want to hear
a little bit about what...
The winners return from their feast, and
I'm ticked.
I don't want to hear
anything they have to say.
I had spinach and artichoke dip.
I'm surprised you didn't bite, like,
- a little bit of the burger.
- Nah, just because
I was so damn full, I
could barely eat any.
I'm listening to them,
and it turns out no one ate the burger.
I mean, honestly, it's just another,
like... Slap in the face.
Oreo milkshake, hands down.
That oreo milkshake was delicious.
I'm lactose intolerant,
- but I couldn't not do it.
- Okay.
"My god.
"I couldn't even eat the bacon.
I'm lactose intolerant, but I
ate the milkshake anyway."
I mean, shut up.
Like, read the freaking room.
I'm just, like, all over the place.
But as much as this not eating is making
my mind kind of crazy,
I do still have my eyes on the prize.
I'm sorry, q. I'm sorry I exploded.
You're allowed to express your emotions.
I was just really hungry.
So I decided to say I'm sorry
for my outburst at the challenge.
It's the biggest lie I've
ever said in this game so far
because, honestly, I want to vote q out.
I was lying. I'm not sorry.
I'm definitely not.
I'm super proud of
myself for yelling at him.
I will be having a hot
girl summer, though,
when I get home.
- Luckily, I...
- The survivor diet.
Be back to, like, my
tenth grade body weight.
Liz apologized for her outburst,
but I'm not concerned
with what Liz thinks.
I'm not ashamed of going
on a reward that I won.
I can choose who I want, and, of course,
there's gonna always be someone mad.
Hey, it's a business decision.
Just like at home, if I fire someone,
I don't care if they're kicking
and crying on the floor.
They have to go.
So, at the end of the day,
an apology out here, you can keep it.
- Okay. What's the quick update?
- All right.
So q proposed Venus, then Liz.
- Okay.
- And then
the ladies proposed q out first.
So, is the tiff blindside off?
For now, but
I think that it's all gonna come down
to if q wins immunity or not.
- Okay.
- But what were you all proposing?
I-I was thinking that it would be...
Tiff. Is that what everyone
here was talking about?
- No.
- Okay.
- Q.
That's all we were talking about.
After q did not take Liz on the reward,
everybody wants him out.
The only thing that scares me is that...
Tiff has an idol.
- Yeah.
- Which is why I'm like
I don't know how long that
can be on the back burner.
Right.
The problem is, tiff has an idol,
and it's something that, like,
we really have to get out of this game,
but everybody is just
like, "we want q gone."
But q is causing chaos.
And he proved himself
capable of winning challenges.
So if we have an
opportunity, he should go.
I think if he doesn't win, he's got to go.
- Yeah.
- I-I agree. Yeah.
I made my feelings pretty clear.
Everybody is saying, "beat q at all costs."
But for me and Maria, Tiffany
could be more of a threat.
So I don't want Tiffany to win either.
So we need to make
sure that Tiffany and q
lose this challenge.
Come on in.
Warriors.
Showing up for battle.
I like it.
All right, shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
First things first, Charlie,
got to take it back.
Man.
- Thank you.
It, like, matches his outfit so perfect.
It's, like, built for you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna hold on to a handle
connected to a bucket containing 25%
of your pregame body weight.
Damn.
As your hands start to fatigue,
that bucket's gonna lower.
When it drops
you're out.
Last person left standing wins immunity,
- guaranteed a spot in the final seven.
- Seven.
Losers, tribal council, where
somebody will be the 11th person
voted out and become the
fourth member of our jury.
One more thing to deal with.
- Lordy.
- My god.
- I knew it.
- -Yeah.
The first time we did this
negotiation, it was four people
have to sit out or two votes
given up at tonight's tribal.
But there were ten of you.
There's only eight of you now.
It's still four people
to sit out or two votes,
which means the price has gone up.
Anybody interested in stepping out?
Four people gets you enough rice
to get you all the way
to the end of the season.
I mean, I'll step out.
Kenzie's one.
Liz thinking about it.
Y'all think you can win this?
All right, let's make this
a little more interesting.
If you can't come up with
four people for the group,
then any individual who wants to step out
your own individual portion of rice.
- It's not a lot...
- Aha.
But there's enough there
to stave off that hunger.
Would you guys hate me?
- No. No.
- Get the rice, Liz. That's yours.
- Girl, go ahead.
- That's all you.
- That's your coconut.
- All right, well, I'll step out.
So Liz is interested in the individual rice.
Well, I mean, if two other people want
to step out, but I know this is,
like, really high stakes.
So let's just find out.
Is there anybody here
that's even contemplating it?
No.
Q? No?
If I step out, I go home.
I'm not dropping that bucket.
So, if we don't make a deal today,
it's safe to assume we're probably
- not going to make a deal this season.
- Yeah.
- All right, Kenzie, you've stepped back.
So you're gonna compete.
If the whole group was in it,
I was gonna go for
it, but I think I'll be able
to make it without the rice
because I can eat coconut.
So I'm not judging Liz at all.
I'm like, "get the rice, girl."
I would judge you more
if you didn't, honestly.
- I would be like, "just do it."
- Liz, your entire tribe
is saying "go for it."
They know you're
hungry. You have allergies.
You've not been eating much.
All right, I'm gonna take the rice.
- All right, Liz. - Good job, Liz.
- Crab fried rice.
Take a spot on the
bench. Here's your rice.
Good job, Liz.
My baby.
All right, everybody else, take your spots.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
All right, Liz opted for the individual rice.
Everybody else is competing.
Here we go. Put your
hands on your handle.
You're gonna pull it back,
and you'll hear a click.
Go for it.
This challenge is on.
No way to convey how
difficult this challenge is
simply by looking at it.
Giddyap, baby. This hurts.
It's 25% of your weight
on day one, so there's a lot of variables.
How much weight have you lost?
How much strength do you still have?
Venus slowly dropping.
Venus is out, joins
Liz. We're down to six.
- I'm sorry, boo.
- Look how sweaty my hands are.
Jeff, give me a Van halen quote, please.
When your bucket drops, it's bottoms up.
Let's hope the cradle does not rock.
Been some crazy tribals lately.
You want that necklace.
Ben, you got this.
I'm doing my best.
Ben dropping a little but
trying to wrench it back up.
Kenzie getting hers back up.
It's going. I can't.
Looks like Ben is gonna
be the next one out.
He is. Ben is out.
Take a spot on the
bench. We're down to five.
New energy now.
You've been up there six minutes.
- Yes, Kenzie.
- My god.
Longest this challenge has
gone was Mike gabler, 38 minutes.
He went into outer space.
Channeling all his friends,
people he was playing for.
The state of Alaska?
Whatever it takes to
keep you in this challenge.
Kenzie gets her bucket back up.
Q fighting it off.
Q dropping a little more.
Q's lost a lot of weight out here.
His pregame body weight
coming into play here.
He's got a lot of weight in that bucket.
Q working hard to keep
that bucket from dropping.
You never know when
it's you going home.
He knows.
Q continues to, inch by
inch, get closer to being
out of this challenge.
Maria's struggling a little now.
No struggle, Jeff.
No struggle. Maria adjusting.
- Thank you.
- Correct.
All right, Maria.
Kenzie's bucket starting to lower now.
- Q drops. He's out.
- Whoo!
Q will not have immunity tonight.
And we are down to four.
Kenzie drops. Kenzie's out.
- We're down to three.
- Good job.
- Good job, Maria.
- Maria drops.
And we got a showdown.
- Charlie and tiff.
- Good job, girlfriend.
You're amazing, Maria.
Tiff's bucket has not moved at all, ever.
21 minutes you've been
up here. That is a long time.
Charlie adjusting his grip.
Trying to wrench that bucket up a little.
Charlie going to one hand. That is risky.
Yeah, I don't know if I
want to do that again.
That bucket drops a little,
but Charlie pulls it back up.
Tiff, rock solid.
- Tiff is locked in.
- This is gonna be a minute.
Tiff has not budged.
Tiff absolutely locked in.
- Charlie adjusting again.
- There you go, buddy.
You're locked, tiff.
Yeah. Whoo, girl.
Tiff quiet like a statue down on the end.
No need to look over.
She's barely moved
or changed her body position at all.
If your concentration lapses
for even a moment,
that's all it takes to drop.
- That gives Charlie some hope.
- There you go, Charlie.
Charlie trying to get that bucket back up.
Get it up there, Charlie.
- There you go.
- Charlie pulling his bucket back up.
Look at that surge of energy.
- Wow.
- Damn.
- That's nuinui.
- Wow.
Suddenly a burst from Charlie.
Let's go, Charlie.
Tiff looks down.
Really?
- Tiff, out of nowhere, drops.
- Whoa.
Charlie wins his second
individual immunity.
Safe tonight at tribal council.
- Guaranteed a spot in the final seven.
- Tiff, are you okay?
Tiff gave everything she had
until her body just gave out.
You all right, tiff?
You want help up?
- Nah, I'm good.
- Okay.
- Proud of you, tiff.
- You did great.
- You did a great job.
- Wow.
You were amazing, tiff.
Good job, Charlie.
- That was epic.
- Good job, Charlie.
- Charlie, you already know.
- Good job, brother. - Good job.
Charlie, come on over.
Once again, back-to-back.
That was a battle.
You outlasted.
Safe tonight.
Guaranteed a spot in the final seven.
As for the rest of you,
after 19 very tough days
of survivor46, somebody
going home tonight.
11th person voted out
will become the fourth
member of our jury.
Grab your stuff. Head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal. Congrats.
Thanks, Jeff.
When I started watching survivor, I saw
that grip strength is
the most important skill
for survivor challenges.
For the past, really, two
years, I've been literally
training my grip with the grip squeezers,
dead hangs on pull-up bars,
anything I can think of to
strengthen my forearms and grip.
It's really validating to
have your hard work pay off
in a way that actually impacts my game.
I was pretty peeved
that Charlie won immunity
because, aside from the
fact that I just want a chance
at wearing the immunity necklace,
I wanted to be the one to beat q
and send him home.
He tried to destroy my
game, and there's no way
under this Fijian sun
that I would let that go.
I want q gone.
Charlie.
Pulling it out.
Tonight is an easy vote.
Myself, Kenzie, Charlie, Ben, Maria,
Venus and Liz are all on
board to send him home.
I haven't heard a single person
utter another name today besides q.
- Liz with the rice.
- Whoo!
But when there's idols in
play, people start to act stupid.
I need somebody to make fire, honestly.
I have been doing a lot
of debating about this idol
because, now that it's out there,
I know that the clock is
ticking on when I have to play it.
- There it is.
- Ooh.
However, q kind of blew up
his own game and has
been causing chaos at camp.
He's now the biggest target.
He's a strong competitor.
He's won the individual reward,
and he's proven that,
like, he can beat us.
Can somebody throw me a coconut?
I think I'm gonna crack one open.
I'm a betting woman,
so I'm putting my chips on the table
and I'm making a bet.
Tonight I'm betting
I can keep my idol in my
pocket because q is going home.
I'd love to get the idol out.
Yeah, I would love to get it out, too,
but if she plays her idol
tonight, and we all vote tiff,
- it's gonna be really, really bad.
- Right. But let's just think.
Yeah. Yeah.
I agree.
It seems to be that
Kenzie is having cold feet.
It seems to be that Kenzie
doesn't necessarily think
that this is the right time
to make the Tiffany move,
but if I keep
sitting back and waiting
for the light to turn green
it may not turn green.
So I'm gonna have to run the red light.
You're basically in final six.
That's so awesome.
As long as y'all not trying
to blindside me tonight.
I have been working on
this, like, tiff blindside thing
on the side, but it's just not singing
the same heart song it was to me.
I have no respect for q.
I have no respect for the
way he's playing the game.
And I don't want to get out tiff,
who wants to be here, for
someone who doesn't care.
It's like spitting in the face
of everyone who has ever applied,
everyone who has
ever tried to be out here,
in the face of the jury,
that he just doesn't care.
It's annoying.
I don't know.
Probably she giving him
some type of encouragement
or something. I don't know.
I'm the easy vote.
But you could change that.
Like, there are options,
but, like, you got to be in the game.
I'm in the game.
If you want to take tiff out,
there are options to take tiff out.
Are you in or are you not in?
Tonight's vote is life or death, for me.
It's gonna be me or tiff.
I go to Vegas a lot, and I'm a high roller.
I hope tonight I can
roll nothing but sevens,
and we can send tiff home.
What are you thinking?
Obviously, q is an easy vote, but
I'd love to get the idol out.
We can take tiff out tonight.
While it may be hard to work with q,
I think we're gonna have to work with q.
I have been thinking about this vote.
Q is a schemer and a bit of a bully,
and I want him the hell out of here, but...
The argument for tiff being the vote
is that everybody knows tiff has an idol,
and the idol's more dangerous
than q at this point.
I think we got to go with the tiff blindside.
- Okay.
- Strategically, it's the most...
- It's the smartest.
- Shh.
Now we have four
votes to get Tiffany out,
but in a game where
there are eight people left,
that's not enough.
This is how we do it.
Q is down to do tiff.
Okay.
Maybe we don't tell Kenzie.
I was thinking the same thing.
We've got q, Ben,
me, Charlie. That's four.
- Thing is, we need one more solid person.
- Personally, I think Liz
is the better bet out of.
- Liz, I don't trust her...
- But out of Liz and Venus,
who do you trust more?
Venus I don't trust.
- She'll cause some random chaos.
- Right.
Venus is not somebody
I could work with,
but the whole fight that Liz and q had
makes it really hard
looping Liz into the plan.
We only have to get one more vote.
I think Liz is better.
I want Tiffany out, and
I want it to be today,
but Charlie's right.
Liz is the key person for this plan, and so
our plan is contingent on the person
that has a personal vendetta against q.
But at some point you've
got to make a move.
And this is terrifying.
It's terrifying because it could blow up
in my face, but it could also
be a game-winning move.
And I agree with that.
Ben hates q.
Like, a lot of us don't want q,
but we have one chance.
For Tiffany?
This is the only night that we can do this.
- Okay.
- And you are the key holder.
Tonight's vote is making
the wheels turn in my head.
I think Maria wants
to make this bold move
for the jury, but I really, really dislike q.
Plus I have a personal vendetta against q
because he didn't pick me
for the applebee's reward.
I know tiff has an idol,
and that is something to consider.
So it's gonna be a really hard battle
between my mind and my heart.
Getting tiff out with an idol,
without her even playing it,
it's a huge, huge move.
On the other hand, voting q out,
seeing Jeff snuff his torch
would be just as sweet as that juicy,
delicious bourbon burger.
Like, peace out, brother.
I am so done with you.
- My god.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- It was on fire.
- Did you burn your hair?
- Yeah. My god.
- Ooh, I smell it.
It stinks.
- It's all good? Okay.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Scared me.
Okay. Let's review where the game is.
Every single person on the jury is there
as a result of a massive blindside.
Q, you have been an
unwitting smoke screen
the last two tribals.
So, once again, let's start with you.
Did the day center
around you a lot? A little?
So, Jeff, over the last three days,
I've been calm.
I lay on the beach. If
they approach me, good.
If not, I don't bother people.
Right now I have no power,
so I can only put the trust
in the people around me.
Tiff, this is a different story,
'cause the last two tribals,
everything was swirling around q.
"Q's going home. Q's going
home. Q's going home."
Nope. Still here.
I mean, like q said,
he kind of just sat back,
minded his business, and
he has a keen understanding
that, at this point, it
really just is what it is.
And today at camp,
for probably the first time
in quite a while, it was actually peaceful.
Kenzie, this is eerily familiar, though.
The last two tribals,
there was this certainty
that it was q going home.
Did it feel different today?
Today definitely felt different.
Q has been, like, such
a good smoke screen
for if a blindside is gonna get pulled off.
But today we were all on a
pretty much an understanding on
what was gonna go down tonight.
So let's go back to the reward challenge.
Biggest reward of the season.
Q, you win. You're in charge.
You choose Maria, tiff and Kenzie.
Liz was left out, was
frustrated, understandably.
It's a long game. She hasn't
eaten, and she let you have it.
Yes.
- That's fair.
- I mean, I said what I said.
I said it very loudly and very publicly,
but I didn't want it to be
awkward for everyone.
So I apologized to q.
That don't mean I'm,
like, really that sorry.
But, like, q, you and I,
we just can't play together.
Q, this is the story.
I know, man.
It's tough, Jeff, but, you
know, I put out a plan,
and if four others get on
board and help me out, we'll see
where things kind of shake up.
But the other folks might just say,
"you know what? Kick this guy out."
So, you know, it's one of those things
where it's not in my control.
Ben, is it possible that
everybody could jump
on board with q's plan,
and it's not q again tonight?
Personally, I'm just a bit over it,
but, if that does happen,
like, it's beyond me.
'Cause everybody has
seemed to have been on, like,
"q tonight? Q tonight?"
I mean, it's almost eerie how
on board everybody is with that.
Charlie, Ben said it.
It's almost eerie.
You can't not consider the
fact that something weird's
gonna happen again,
because look across.
The last two have been
absolute devastating blindsides
using q as the smoke screen.
The eerie silence is scary.
And I think there was a moment today
where I was sort of questioning, like,
"is something going on
that I don't know about?"
And what I realized is that, no,
the calm is because people
are on the same page.
So that's what I'm hanging my hat on.
Maria, let's talk about blindsides
at this stage of the game.
If you're somebody
who pulls off a blindside,
you're happy, you're
proud. You should be.
You hoodwinked somebody.
That's difficult to do,
but they're different
when you have a jury.
I mean, I am sure everybody here
is thinking to themselves,
"how can I get something
on my résumé?"
Right? Like, there are
three unfortunate people
sitting over there who
are thinking to themselves,
"was this a good move, or was it not?
Am I gonna award a
vote to this person or not?"
And so a blindside right now is huge.
That's just not the case
tonight, unfortunately.
Tiff, let's go back to q for a moment.
There's so much energy
around whether he should be here
or not that I'm curious
when the scales tip
and suddenly keeping q
becomes the better move.
- Liz is...
- Everybody's shaking their head.
I don't know if keeping q is
the better move for anybody.
Just based on what I've been hearing,
I don't think that
anybody here thinks that q
is best for their game at
this particular point in time.
Again, for me, Jeff, I
can only put out an idea.
If it doesn't stick with others, it doesn't
make sense for their game, I
can't make 'em vote with me.
And I was prepared to go two tribals ago.
If it's my time, it's my
time. I've accepted it.
If my plan is not their
plan, I'm cool, man.
All right, it is time to vote.
Kenzie, you're up.
Very easy vote.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Q.
Tiff. One vote q, one vote tiff.
Q. Two votes q.
Q. Three votes q, one vote tiff.
Tiff.
That's three votes q, two votes tiff.
Tiff. We're tied.
Three votes q, three votes tiff.
Tiff. That's four votes tiff, three votes q.
One vote left.
11th person voted out and the
fourth member of our jury: Tiff.
Need to bring me your torch.
Tiff, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you.
Time for you to go.
Whoa.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
An idol, at this point in the
game, changes everything.
Next time on survivor... We're screwed.
Everyone's lying.
She went from being a
hero to a villain real quick.
We all know what needs to be done.
He's a jerk.
I don't feel guilty at all.
I broke my own survivor rule.
I should have played my idol.
I should have just gotten rid of it,
but I was trying to stretch my idol out
for one more tribal.
It turns out that it bit me in the butt.
So I'm not gonna sit up here
and pretend that I'm happy
that I just got blindsided,
but if there's any way to go out
on survivor, it's a blindside.