I have... The idol in my hand.
Previously on survivor...
Choose one more person to join you.
For me, it's more like
who is physically falling apart right now?
Liz and q, rock, paper, scissors.
- Paper covers rock. Is that it?
- Yup.
Yeah, I know. I'm, like... I know.
My head is going in
22 different directions.
Yeah.
And I've been playing this
game with Maria since day one.
But at some point,
you have to start thinking
about your own game.
It's one thing to decide who you're gonna
take with on a reward,
but to start off by saying,
"you know, I really
want to choose someone
who is physically weak,"
and then put on this
farce... it kind of felt cruel.
Twelfth person voted out, Venus.
The tribe has spoken.
I was gonna play the idol, but
unfortunately, I'm going home with it.
Tribal went exactly as it should.
They say you can see Venus from earth,
but we don't see Venus
no more in this camp.
Venus thought that
she could rally the troops
and send me packing?
You can cancel Christmas, girl.
That would never happen.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna clear this up right now.
- Was it you?
I'm gonna blow my... up.
I drew a blank.
You actually wrote the wrong name?
- You wrote my name?
- Yeah. I want...
That's why I wanted
to talk to you right now.
Yeah.
Yo, for real,
not lying, I was not supposed
to write Kenzie's name down.
I was supposed to
write Venus' name down.
And I just had a slip of the brain.
You literally told me you
would never write my name,
- and then, like, did?
- Dude, I...
Like, that's, like, a
big blunder, you know?
I'm at this point in the game
where I haven't been
sleeping, and I feel like
I'm losing my mind.
Kenzie has helped me
with my night terrors.
I genuinely blanked.
And you know what?
I just didn't want there
to be any tension at camp.
You've been so good to me,
and I'm like, I can't sit
here and have you be,
like, thinking about that all night.
What do you mean
it was an accident, Ben?
How does that happen?
It's not like it's Kenzie and Kelsey.
It's Venus and Kenzie.
Like, how did that happen?
Either you're telling a really dumb lie,
or you're telling a really dumb truth,
and I'm just gonna...
I'm not gonna harp on it.
- Is that your first vote?
- Yeah, that's my first vote.
Yeah, from my island bestie, you jerk.
It's okay. I have three.
My god. Why?
Because she, like, dragged
my character through the mud.
- My god.
- To say it was an act and a farce.
Like, do you know how hard
that was to make that choice?
- I know. I know.
- Yeah.
She got under my skin so bad tonight,
and I'm pissed at myself for reacting.
- Feel like that just killed me.
- Aw. No.
- I don't think you had much of a reaction.
- No.
At tribal tonight,
Venus came out of the gates slinging.
I felt like she really
attacked my character.
You know, and it just got to me.
- She go home.
- And Venus just got sent to the jury
by an almost unanimous vote.
Except Ben, apparently,
voted for the wrong name,
which I have never heard of in my life.
But now, finally, Venus is gone.
We're at final six, and this is the time
to just, like, go for it.
What up, final six?!
At this point, I've had two wins and
a blindside, and
I've been on the right
side of every single vote.
I know I'm a force to be reckoned with,
so, if they're not trying to get me out,
then that's their mistake.
It's getting way harder for me to sleep.
It's very obvious how weak I
am these last couple of days.
I'm waking up in the middle of the night.
The first time I had a panic attack,
it was very mental.
You know, you're
disoriented, you're in the jungle,
you don't know what's going on.
Now the part that bothers
me and it freaks me out is
my body has a mind of its own.
I had an experience
camping when I was 18
that traumatized me.
I woke up screaming
irrationally, you know,
thinking about college,
thinking I'm gonna die.
And it was very similar anxieties
to what I've been going
through in this game.
Ben's panic attacks have gotten, like,
more frequent, and they've gotten
progressively worse.
I just don't know where
this burst of fear comes from.
So, every night, I just hold his hand,
and we breathe together, and
if he needs to talk it out
and laugh, we do that.
If he needs to just, like,
walk around, like, I go
with him to do that because
Ben can't help that
he has anxiety attacks.
But what I can do is be there for
someone who needs someone.
And I don't care that he
literally wrote my name down.
It's just a game.
I could never let someone
go through something
so scary alone.
That's not who I am.
Do you want a hug?
Time will pass, and the sun will shine,
and blue skies are coming.
But just be with him
through the storm, you know?
- Morning. - Sit right here?
- Scooch together, y'all.
- You guys?
- We can fit six on the bench.
You guys,
not to make it about me, but I had a bm.
I just dropped five pounds.
What? My god.
Day 22!
I went to the bathroom!
I thought I was gonna
be the first survivor
in history to never go to the bathroom
the whole time, but I went.
I feel so good.
I... am ready to play now.
I've been talking about
turning up Liz, and now it's, like,
full-on volume 11.
Liz is in the game.
I have nothing weighing me down now.
My name is not anyone else's name.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
And by the way, don't...
Don't accidentally write "Charlie," either.
Yeah.
I'm never gonna live
that down... No, you're not.
Even though the game is
so, so different with only six people,
my game plan is the same.
Options.
It's like, "Ben, what are you doing?"
It's like, "this is our squad."
- I know.
- And you're, "what?"
And right now, I've given myself
two pathways on this next vote.
I've worked really hard
to plant this idea with
Ben, with Kenzie, with Liz,
that we can take out Maria and q.
I will say, there's
only one bonus to me
being a total idiot last night.
What?
Is that I think Maria and q
might think that's, like, a wedge.
- Between us? Yeah. -Sure.
- Yeah.
At the same time, I could
stick with Maria and q
who trust me completely, but
part of me is, like, what
if I just do what I set out
to do with Maria?
That'd be awesome.
So, I have to really think
about what's best for
my game, and it's just
such a dilemma at this point.
And it's a-a different dilemma
than anything I've faced this game.
You know, I voted out
people who I've really liked,
but no one like Maria,
who I've played the whole game with,
and who I consider to
be my best friend out here.
But I can't be waffling back and forth.
Now is the time where I have
to be laser-focused on getting
to the end, and I have
to make a decision.
Come on in!
- Aw, yeah.
- Hiya.
Look at that.
Down to six.
I know.
- We're a little motley crew over here.
- It's working.
Whatever you're doing, you're still here.
Hi, Jeff.
Good morning, Liz.
All right, shall we get to
today's reward challenge?
For today's challenge,
you're gonna race over an obstacle
to collect a bag containing a ball.
You'll then cross a ladder bridge,
moving that bag along a twisting rope.
Once your bag is free,
you'll crawl under one final obstacle.
When you reach the end,
you'll maneuver that ball
through a maze.
First person to finish wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
- Yes. - Yes, sir.
- Please.
The winner will be
taken to the sanctuary,
where good things
happen, for an afternoon
- of Chinese takeout.
- You called it.
Those little familiar white boxes
will be waiting over
there to fill your tummies.
Worth playing for?
- Yeah! - Absolutely.
- All right, we'll draw
for spots, we'll get it on. Let's do this.
Ooh.
- All right.
- Dumplings!
For reward at the sanctuary.
Survivors ready?
Go! You're gonna high-step this,
- and it's going to burn.
- My god, but...
Q making quick work of it.
Look at Charlie... High-stepping it.
There goes Maria.
- Wow.
- Ben, Kenzie, Liz in the end.
My god.
Untie the first two knots,
start moving that bag...
Through this ladder bridge.
You're moving that bag along the rope,
and you're moving your
body across the ladder bridge.
Wherever that rope goes, your bag goes.
Wherever the bridge
goes, your body goes.
We are still very even.
Big maze at the end,
where anything can happen.
It's Maria in the lead.
She's won immunity twice.
Come on. Go.
Maria's across.
You're good.
Untie that other rope
now and free that bag.
Charlie's good. Liz is good. Q is good.
Ben's across.
- There's Kenzie now.
- I got it.
Charlie's got his rope
all the way through.
Maria has her bag.
She's under that final obstacle.
- Q is through.
- What?
He's under the obstacle.
Maria first to the maze.
Q right behind her.
Get that ball out, start working on it.
Pull down to release your maze.
Here's Charlie.
It is Kenzie, Ben and Liz
still working to free
their bag with that ball.
Here comes Liz.
- Good luck, y'all.
- Here comes Kenzie.
Ben still back there.
I'm so bad, I'm laughing.
This maze requires a nice touch
and a lot of Patience.
Charlie drops, got to start
again. You're gonna drop.
It's gonna take you a
few times to figure this out.
Here comes Kenzie. She's in it now.
Liz is here. She's in it.
Ben has his bag. Let's go, Ben!
Maria making some progress.
Q making a little progress.
Jeff, you know I'm
cranking "pinball wizard"
in my head right now.
Maria doing a nice job.
She has slowed down.
Very patient.
Charlie drops again.
Maria drops. She's got to start again.
Q drops. Everybody's in it once again.
This is anybody's challenge to win.
Ooh, ooh!
Kenzie doing a nice job.
Now Kenzie and Ben.
Nope, it's just Kenzie.
And Ben drops. It's Kenzie.
Charlie trying to make a run at it again,
trying to catch Kenzie.
Ooh! Okay, come on.
Maria drops.
Q gonna start again.
Kenzie doing a nice job,
making tiny movements.
Charlie trying to catch her.
Kenzie still in the lead.
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
Kenzie drops.
It's Charlie in the lead right now.
Let's go, Charlie.
Liz doing a nice job. Liz is in this.
Maria once again back out on the maze.
Kenzie's out there now,
making some progress.
Charlie navigates one passageway.
Liz right on his tail.
Charlie getting very close.
Liz right there.
Liz drops. She's got to start again!
Charlie inching closer and closer.
He's inside the inner circle.
Can he get it to stick?
For reward.
And he's done it!
- Wow.
- Charlie wins reward.
Afternoon at the sanctuary -Charlie!
- For Chinese takeout.
- Good job, Charlie.
- Wow.
- Good game, brother.
Get your stinky butt over here.
All right, Charlie, come on over.
- All right, Charlie.
- Chinese food.
So here's what's gonna
happen. You're gonna leave here,
- go to the sanctuary.
- Yeah.
Chinese takeout.
Beautiful afternoon.
I'm gonna sweeten the deal
a little bit, and in the process,
maybe complicate
- your decision, because...
- Ay-ay-yay.
After you enjoy the Chinese takeout,
you will finish your
afternoon at the sanctuary
with your letters from home.
God.
Wow.
Sorry, Charlie.
Choose one person to join you.
God.
Kenzie, what is it about
the letters from home?
Because when you're watching survivor,
you say "you've only
got a few more days.
It's not that big a deal."
Yeah, it... I know there
are people here with kids,
and peo... Everyone
here loves somebody.
My fiancé moved our wedding.
It was supposed to be
yesterday for this, so it would just
be really nice to hear from him, but I
Charlie, don't, like...
it's... I'm not gonna hold it
against you if you don't choose me. I just
- I'm just thinking about it, you know?
- I know.
Choose one person, Charlie.
I'm gonna choose Liz.
I know Liz can eat Chinese food.
- Really?
- Her daughter Chelsea
is a huge survivor fan.
Those two factors. Liz, come on.
My god.
All right, Liz!
Yeah, Liz.
Thank you.
All right, Charlie, four people left.
You're gonna choose one more person,
which means three of
you will go to the sanctuary,
three others will go back
to camp with nothing.
Honestly, coming into this,
I was thinking the people who
didn't eat pizza would come.
I'm gonna take Kenzie, and I
know she had her wedding day.
And I'm so sorry to everybody else.
'Cause I know what this is, and...
- Wow.
- I'm really, really sorry.
Come on over.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry, Maria.
- Maria, I'm really sorry.
- Maria, I'm sorry.
All right, Charlie, Liz, Kenzie,
you're heading to the sanctuary
for a fun afternoon of food and love.
Grab your stuff, head out, enjoy the day.
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
Thank you.
Maria, all love is good love,
but a parent's love is unique.
It's like no other in that
you created these
people, so your emotion is
obviously understood.
What is the feeling?
What were you looking forward to?
I just wanted to see
I just want to see those
letters so bad, Jeff.
I understand his decision.
I would never wish that
decision on him. It's just,
it's breaking my heart in three.
All right, q, Maria,
Ben, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
No problem.
This reward challenge is one that
I've been waiting for for many days,
and I think my tears
were just the realization
that this is the one I've been waiting for,
and I knew I couldn't go.
It hurts all over. It hurts my head.
It hurts my heart, you know?
Like, I wasn't lying when I
said my heart broke in three.
If you're watching survivor as a family,
and your mom keeps
saying, "I should do that show,"
encourage her. "Mom,
apply to be on survivor."
Yes!
- Thanks for this.
- Thank you so much.
Y'all are the best. This is amazing.
- My god, you guys.
- Wow.
Sorry. I'm, like, ripping
open boxes like a savage.
- No, rip open...
- Savage!
I haven't had a reward
in almost ten days,
and there's been so many feelings.
Feelings I didn't even
know that I had inside me
when I don't get picked.
My gosh. That's soda.
And today, I'm picked.
See, Liz? It all pays off not
getting picked for the pizza.
- This is better.
- You know, I thought about that.
- We are very lucky.
- I thought
it was a series of bad luck, and I'm like,
"that was good I didn't get picked."
More than eating, it feels like,
"yes, Liz, you have done
something right in the game.
"You're working with people
that want to work with you," and
that feels just as delicious
as this beef dish tastes.
We got love.
God. I can't even think about that.
I really... I really feel for them, but...
Obviously, the letters
complicate it, but, like,
literally, before the letters, I
was like, "it's Kenzie and Liz."
Like, obviously, we didn't eat
- the last time, so...
- Right.
Not choosing Maria
was the hardest decision
I've made the entire game.
But I knew that we were gonna be okay.
She is truly a selfless, caring,
just stand-up person.
I told you, like, my favorite
players are Malcolm and Denise.
- Like...
- Yeah, she's kind of, like, that strong...
That strong mom.
We've been saying
we're Malcolm and Denise,
and we've built such a tight bond
over the course of this whole season.
And one reward challenge,
even if it's for love, was
not gonna break that bond.
I think Maria will understand.
I think so, too. She knows, you know...
She knows.
I think the hardest thing... Is I can...
Let it out. Take your time.
I can picture them s-sending their...
Writing their messages.
Yeah.
Working so hard on these letters
to get them to me.
Charlie and I said, if we ever win reward,
we are not taking the other person.
So, I know why Charlie
chose how he chose,
but having my three boys at home and
not having a way to
communicate with them...
Something died in me... today.
I just... I feel like
I just got robbed, it
just got taken from me.
This one would have meant
I would have given up
every reward for this one.
It hurts, it's very painful, but, like,
I've been in positions before
where I've been broken down,
and all I can think of is, like, you keep
some bear cubs from mama bear.
Like, I'm coming.
It's gonna really light a fire under me.
- Letters!
- Letters, y'all.
Liz!
My gosh. That's my name!
- Kenzie!
- It's thick!
Wow, you guys.
- We are loved ones!
- I know. Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- My gosh. Cheers.
I remember coming
into the game thinking,
"Liz, you really don't want your
letters because you're gonna
have to show this
emotional side of yourself."
Aw. Chelsea.
But when the letter is
right there in your face,
that's all you can think about.
And so, to remind yourself
of home and why I came
out here in the first place and
who I left behind.
And it feels like motivation.
I see my daughter's letter,
and I see her little drawing.
She's the whole reason I'm out here.
She dared me to apply. And it just...
It reminds me that there
are people in this game
who are not rooting for
you, but there are people
at home that are.
I have no idea what's
going on with my parents.
going on with my business.
I have no idea what's
going on with my fiancé.
And so, getting to, like,
hear that they're okay...
There's no words to describe
how much it means out here.
Wow. This is the best thing ever.
Thank you, Charlie. Ooh.
I was supposed to get
married literally yesterday, but
my fiancé, when I got
the first call for survivor,
immediately moved our wedding
because he just believed in me.
And it's amazing that I have...
Sorry.
It's just so amazing to
have a support system
that allows me... To
learn, to go... to do this.
You know, like, I'm
used to being in charge,
I'm used to, like, controlling everything.
And I'm used to being,
like, a perfectionist, and...
Relinquishing that
control was a big lesson
for me to even come out here.
I've been self-employed since I was 17.
I started my career at 15 years old.
Like, just because I thought
I was the only person
I could ever count on.
But hearing that my family
can handle everything
like, it's allowing me to
take a break and, like,
I don't have to be perfect all the time.
I don't have to be in charge all the time.
Like, I can lean on other people.
This really... I'll never forget this.
- My god.
- Ever.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you guys
- for being here.
- You're awesome.
Every single letter, every single one
makes me cry and laugh
and just get that one little taste of home
that I need to drive me through.
It's a bunch of Taylor swift quotes.
- From Judy?
- Yeah.
Getting to hear from Judy, my girlfriend,
I get to see what she's thinking
about this whole crazy experience.
I miss her so much, and
think about her every day.
I always thought they were, like,
all being dramatic with letters,
- no.
- But my god.
But if I remember one thing,
it's that my sister, my dad,
my mom, my girlfriend Judy
they all told me to play to win.
That might be what I needed
to push me to make the
right decision for Charlie.
Because if I'm going to play to win,
I'm going to be betraying Maria,
who I've played the whole game with.
And those reminders
to play to win are gonna fuel
me to the end of the game.
That was amazing.
- Lordy.
- This was the reward to win, Charlie.
- I know. Wow.
- That's, like,
- such a bucket-list thing.
- I feel so special.
I feel special, too.
Thanks, Charlie.
Charlie's choices to go on this reward
it couldn't have been set up any better.
This is a chance for the three of us
to actually talk strategy
without looking suspicious.
So, while it would pain me...
To not go q yet again,
I do know Maria is a bigger threat.
Someone just needs
to beat Maria tomorrow.
We have to get her before q, right?
- Yeah.
- I mean, as much as that makes me gag.
Yeah.
- She's so good.
- She's good at everything.
And she made the fire last night.
I was like, "no, you can make fire, too?"
I know.
This was by far the
hardest reward decision
of the season.
All I can say is thank goodness
Maria was not here because
I am cooking something up that
I don't want Maria to
sniff out of the kitchen.
And that is a blindside
of Maria at the next vote.
I know Ben is solid.
So, the key ingredients in this little recipe
are Kenzie and Liz, so,
I wanted to cement
that relationship today.
Wonder what they're
doing back at camp.
They'll probably look for the idol,
but I don't think it exists, personally.
Yeah. Well, let's hope not.
Right now, reward means
absolutely nothing to me.
For me, I need
to find this idol 'cause I need protection.
So the more time that I
have to snoop around,
which... I've looked a lot.
They make it look so easy on television.
People, I've looked for days.
Days... and hours on days.
Nothing.
But today is different.
I've told myself, "q, calm down."
Calm for the last handful of days.
Handful of.
My hand is starting to hurt.
I need the storm.
And I think I found something
that'll help this storm
come a little quicker.
You just sit right there. Hold
on. Let me go in my pocket.
What's in my pocket? What's...
It might be somehow!
What's-what's... What's the matter?
What's going? Look what I found. Lord.
My god. This is a beautiful thing.
I got it.
And behold.
I got the juice. I got the juice now, fam.
Do I tell Maria or do I don't?
I just need to get through
this last vote at six,
and I'm in the final friggin' four!
Hey.
Swear to god. Just found it...
- Stop it.
- I swear to god.
Let me see what it looks like.
I told Maria about the idol because
you have to trust somebody.
- I'm not telling anybody else.
- No, no, no, no, no.
And Maria is my number one.
So, now, her knowing that I have the idol,
she's now more likely to protect me.
Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- So... That's a really nice offer.
Like, if I have someone who's telling me
he's willing to play this for me,
I definitely want to keep him around.
So maybe that's my best move now.
I think it's imperative Liz goes next.
Yep.
We just have to make sure Charlie
don't pull a fast one with those girls.
I don't think he would.
I'm not worried about Charlie
doing anything with them.
But would Charlie
need to go before them?
It would make... It would be safe.
This is the first time
that I've actually voiced
out loud to anybody that I'm
considering voting Charlie out.
It's a very hard decision,
because not only has he been
my number one since day three, but
I have so much trust in him.
Charlie is so lovable.
He'll beat any of us.
Charlie will win, hands down.
Yep.
I honestly do.
- Charlie don't win, get rid of Charlie.
- Yep.
- Which I'm down to do, if you mean it.
- I'm down to do it, too.
- Hello! How's it going?
- Hello.
It's a very hard conversation to have,
but it's also a reality.
He's a threat.
I knew why you picked who you picked.
- Thank you.
- It was just sad.
And, I mean, I know...
It was so sad, 'cause I know how badly
you wanted to read those letters.
I adore Charlie so much,
and Charlie and I have
walked this journey together
with so much compassion
and genuine care for one another.
And we've really
formed, like, a friendship
that will go way beyond this game.
Just so, like, grateful to, like,
have you just in my life, period.
- Thank you for saying that.
- So... so just
I just really want to
thank you for everything.
So it's hard to switch from that security,
that comfort and that camaraderie
to "it's my game now."
Like, it has to be my game.
There aren't many options anymore
for us to be a pair.
Was there any strategy talk?
Were there any pitches to you?
There were.
It was much of the same.
- Which was...
- Like, "get q out of the game."
Okay.
Maria's my number one ally.
I love her to death, but
I've set up this blindside.
I feel so many different emotions.
And honestly, it almost feels like guilt.
It pulls on just every single fiber of me.
I think that was really important,
- strategically, is to keep... yeah.
- Yeah. Keep them from, like,
- talking to too many people, and...
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
I don't think Maria is
considering blindsiding me.
I don't know.
Would he ever do it to me?
I was hoping you-you would find it.
Well, I tried to go look.
I was like, "I hope that's
what Maria gets to do"
- "while I'm gone is, like, find the idol."
- I tried. I tried.
It took me a while.
Or did we really have plans
to go to the end together?
Am I breaking his heart
and messing up our plans?
I think she's dead serious about
taking me to the final three.
If anything, I feel like I got a
good friend out of this thing.
You know, whatever happens, I
feel like, - whatever happens, Maria.
- Always.
- You're such a good person.
The two best buds,
Malcolm and Denise, can't go to the end,
and I want Malcolm to take this one.
Hopefully we get
to keep in touch and
be in each other's lives.
My god, yeah.
My god.
I know it. I literally know it.
At the end of the day,
Charlie and I will be wonderful
friends after this game.
- I want them to meet uncle Charlie.
- And...
Yes! Yes.
But right now, he's standing in my way.
Bring in the boat!
- Doesn't get any more rock star than that.
- Yeah.
Come on in.
Wow.
Down to six.
Shall we get to today's
immunity challenge?
First things first, Maria.
Once again, I have to take it back.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna climb to the top
of a very tall tower and leap off.
You'll then race over a
series of obstacles to the finish.
You'll attempt to solve a dolphin puzzle.
- My goodness.
- Man.
First person to finish wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot in the final five.
Losers, tribal council,
where somebody will
not make the finale.
You'll be the 13th person voted out,
become the sixth member of our jury.
The stakes are very clear: Win
or you are in trouble.
All right, draw for spots.
- We'll get started.
- All righty.
All right, here we go.
For immunity and a
guaranteed spot in the finale.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to swim to that platform
and get up that ladder.
There goes q.
There's Maria. Here
comes Charlie. There's Ben.
Maria first off.
Kenzie's in.
Liz plugs her nose. She's in.
Keep moving.
Charlie in the lead.
Everybody moving very fast
on day 23 of survivor 46.
Looks so easy
when you're watching from
the comfort of your couch.
Q with a nice dive.
Now you've got the beam.
If you drop, you got to go back.
Charlie first.
Only one way to approach
a beam. Look straight ahead.
Go for it.
Charlie falls.
Ben drops. He's got to go back.
Maria.
Look at that. Maria's good.
Maria now in the lead.
Liz falls.
Q falls.
Maria in the lead. Everybody
else still working on the beam.
Kenzie's in.
Charlie falls.
Maria first to the puzzle. Ben is across.
Building a dolphin puzzle.
Liz working on the beam.
Q working on the beam.
He drops again. Charlie's good.
Liz is good.
Kenzie, that works.
Just keep your feet out of the water.
Kenzie falls.
Ben gonna be on this puzzle.
Charlie's in this.
Liz right behind Charlie.
Maria working on the puzzle.
There goes q.
He's looking good. He's halfway through.
Q with a nice leap. You're good, q.
Kenzie in dead last.
Words you do not
want to hear on day 23.
Q up, working on his puzzle.
Right now it's Maria and Ben,
but only with a couple of pieces.
We're still early in this.
Big stakes.
You want to see the final five.
You're good, Kenzie. Get here. Let's go.
Charlie getting the base.
Ben has the base. Maria has the base.
Hey.
Liz has a piece. Mark it down.
Kenzie's here now.
Everybody on the puzzle now,
where anything can happen.
If you get a roll going and you start
to figure this out, you can
catch everybody quickly.
It's now Ben in the lead,
then everybody else.
Everybody now looking next door.
"What can I see on
somebody else's puzzle?
Which piece do I need?"
Ben with another piece.
Ben is on a roll right now.
He's figuring this puzzle
out, but it is far from over.
Everybody chasing Ben.
This would be Ben's first challenge win.
Couldn't come at a better time.
But you never know.
Any given challenge, anyone can win.
Maria with another piece.
Now Ben's gonna feel the pressure.
Look at that.
We got a challenge!
And another piece for Maria.
And another piece for Maria!
Three in a row. Maria now in the lead.
Make it four in a row. Maria's on a tear.
Ben has slowed down
now. He had the early lead.
Right now, it is all Maria.
Amazing.
Maria is on fire.
It would be her third
individual immunity win.
Q now gonna just watch.
Maria down to her last few pieces.
It is time to put this
one in the deep freeze.
Maria down to her
last piece in this puzzle.
Guaranteed a spot at the final five.
And there it is. Maria's done it.
Her third individual immunity win,
guaranteeing her a spot in the final five.
Wow.
That went from competitive to a blowout.
Maria, come on over.
For the third time this
season, individual immunity.
You are guaranteed
a spot in the final five.
We just talked about
the fact that this means
you are in the finale.
Why is that so significant
to a survivor fan and player?
You know, I think
yesterday I hit rock bottom,
to not get that love from home.
And so I thought to myself
I was either gonna be fueled by love
or I was gonna be fueled by
the fierce determination
that got me here.
And so, this win, to me, is just
proving to myself that I
have that determination,
even in the absence of love from home.
Well done. Maria safe tonight.
As for the rest of you,
somebody going home tonight,
13th person voted out, you become
the sixth member of our jury.
Swim out. See you tonight at tribal.
Maria winning immunity today,
my first reaction was,
"dang, Maria, you are a boss."
My next reaction is,
"well, dang. Maria was
probably going home tonight."
So, this is survivor. What do you do?
Adapt.
What's the next best move for me?
And I think, tonight,
it's not a smoke screen.
There's a real fire under q, and I think
his torch could get snuffed tonight.
Congratulations, Maria.
- All right, Maria.
- Challenge beast Maria.
- I know.
- So fun, kids.
Maria is the biggest threat out here.
Maria can't keep winning everything,
but she does, so it's frustrating.
So we can't get her out.
But I don't want to go any further with q.
Yep, yep, yep.
Yeah.
I have wanted q out of my game
for a hot minute now,
and it's just not been happening.
So I am ready to take down king q.
Like, I want him out of here.
I think every time has
been the time to take out q,
but especially this time,
'cause there's only two votes left.
And the only reason q
keeps avoiding getting voted
is 'cause Maria's convincing
us all to use him as a number,
"which is really,"
"they're an alliance. How did
we not put two and two together?"
We're, like, the four court jesters
taking down the king.
- Yeah.
- Finally.
Maria and q think they've
been running the show
for a bit, but now everybody's trying
to come together as one to take down
the king and queen.
This is gonna be my favorite
blindside of the season.
Yeah, this one's really good.
What's the tea?
So, thinking about this... Yeah.
But...
We have to.
He's vulnerable now.
We got to take the shot when we can.
It's survivor.
The safe move is never the best move.
Safe move is never the best move.
I know it's time to get out Charlie.
But now,
I'm removing my number one
and trusting in my number two.
I know you're right, q.
I know he's a threat,
and I knew this day was gonna come.
If everybody wants
to bash me for taking q
further in this game, that's
their prerogative, but...
It's Charlie tonight.
So what are we gonna do?
We got to go Charlie.
Charlie?
We got to stick together, Liz.
I'm with you.
Sounds good to me.
Q comes up with this
plan of getting Charlie out,
but, q, you know dang well
I don't want to work with you.
Ever since Maria and
him have teamed up
and he thinks he's back on top,
he's just been so ridiculously confident.
But you know what?
- I've been ready to get q out.
- I've been ready to get q out, too.
- For a long time.
- Yes.
Tonight is finally the
night q is going home.
See you later, brother.
What are we gonna say to Maria?
I'm just gonna play stupid.
Yeah.
What do you all think about that?
I mean, I'm fine with that.
He is kind of the one to beat.
- Everybody loves Charlie.
- Everybody...
- Yeah, I love Charlie.
- If Charlie gets to the end, he wins.
- Hands down.
- Yeah. Like, look at him.
- Everybody here, he'll beat everybody.
- Yeah.
Maria thinks Liz and I
are gonna vote Charlie,
but we're just bamboozling Maria and q.
I knew this day would come.
We both knew it would come, you know?
And I'm just eating it up, because q
feels comfortable.
So q is not gonna see
this blindside coming
as long as Maria doesn't find out.
If we
take out q tonight and
leave Maria out of the vote,
she's not gonna be with us tomorrow.
Yeah, it kind of weakens her,
but if she wins immunity
tomorrow, which right now,
- looks possible.
- Looks very possible,
what happens to us?
We have to make sure that
we can survive tomorrow.
We need to get q tonight,
but we need to be careful how we do it,
because... If we leave Maria in the dark,
then we go into final five.
All of a sudden, Maria can
team up with Liz and Kenzie
and vote out either Ben or me.
So the way I see it,
we have to bring Maria into the q vote,
which I think she'd be cool with it.
- Yeah.
- I'd have to talk to her,
- but I think that makes us the most safe.
- Yeah.
This is why
I never close any
door on any relationship
to work on. 'Cause guess what?
- I just wanted to talk to you.
- Yeah.
Maria thinks I'm still her number one ally.
That's the key of my game,
is making sure that every side
that I've been working
with, I can still work with.
Yeah.
Charlie approaches me and says,
"tonight's the night
we're gonna get rid of q."
And so I nod and say, "I
think that's a good idea."
What I really feel is,
"please don't look me in the eye.
I feel so embarrassed.
Don't look at me like that."
I mean, what I really feel is,
"I think tonight is Charlie's night to go."
Okay. So...
You think we can get everyone
to write q's name down?
Yeah.
I think the conversation
about getting rid of q
is really just to appease Charlie
and to just distract him
from any other thoughts.
But in reality, Kenzie and Liz and q and I
are gonna be the ones
that make the decision.
So there's nothing
Charlie can do at this point.
You feeling okay?
Yeah. I think you're fine.
You may get a vote,
but I don't think you're going home.
Thank you.
- You'll be here tomorrow.
- Yep.
Right now, I feel confident
that I have Maria, Liz and Kenzie
on board to working with
me to blindside Charlie.
- You got a q-skirt?
- I've got a little pocket in my...
Rock the q-skirt!
Q-skirt! Q-skirt!
Yeah!
After tonight's vote, and
when Charlie goes home,
it is safe to say that I've regained control.
I don't see how it can go wrong,
but here's what I know:
The q-skirt is holding an idol.
Can you believe it?
Nobody knows about
the idol besides Maria,
so this thing is powerful.
And if I feel any spooks or dooks,
I'm playing the idol for myself.
Period.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right, I just want to
make sure because...
- Are we all good?
- Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no.
I think we're all good
on the same page, right?
Okay. Okay.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Awesome.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Day 24. Day 25.
Tonight is a tough vote for me,
because when I started this game, I said,
"I want to find my person."
And I found my person,
and, like, Charlie's been
my person, but I'm stepping forward.
I'm not looking back.
This is the right choice for me
because at the end of this
game, only one of us can win.
So it's going to be a
sad tribal council for me.
I'm going to see my
best friend in this game
walk out the door tonight,
and so it's gonna be
very bittersweet, and I hope I get a hug.
Yo, yo, yo. Let's light it up.
Jeff, we have a show for you tonight.
Wow.
Once again, I forgot popcorn.
All right, let's start with the
reward challenge, Charlie,
where you won the
reward, and much like Maria,
you had a big decision to make.
It was Chinese takeout.
Jeff, it was the classic bait
and switch is what it was.
I thought it was Chinese takeout.
And then you go, "and loved one letters."
So I said, "I'm gonna sweeten the deal
and probably complicate your decision."
Yeah, a little bit, you think?
- I mean...
- So you seemed to base it based on who had
received an earlier reward.
That seemed like a very
simple approach, but Maria
was clearly emotionally
upset at missing out.
Yeah, you know, we talked about it
and had some big, long hugs,
and I was just impressed
with all three of the people
who didn't go on the reward,
who were just very selfless in saying,
"no, you three go.
You know, we'll-we'll talk
to our loved ones soon."
So, it just showed how
close we are out here.
Even though everyone's thinking
of their loved ones, we're
forming bonds here, too.
Kenzie, what was the love like for you?
Because you shared that
you moved your wedding
to come play survivor.
It's indescribable, like,
how much that meant to me.
I told Charlie, like,
"this is a day that I
will never, ever forget."
Like, hearing from home
filled me up so much
with just enough gas, like, left in the tank
to get me through to
the end of this game,
because we are this really
weird, dysfunctional family,
the six of us.
Like, q and Ben are like my brothers
who don't speak and they,
like, pick on me all the time.
Maria's like our aunt
who cooks everything.
You're like our cynical
grandma who's, like, losing it,
but we love her.
Charlie's like our dependable dog.
Like...
Like, we have made,
like, this family here,
but it's not the same as
hearing from the people
you love so much at home.
All right, now let's talk
about the immunity challenge.
Maria wins again, third time,
which puts you just one shy
of an elite group of women
who have won four immunity challenges.
- And that's in seasons that have 39 days.
- Wow.
But when I asked you about today's win,
you said it was the drive
from not getting the love.
Yeah. You know, just
to be super clear, like,
there were no hard feelings
for Charlie's decision.
Like, I knew exactly why
he chose who he chose,
because they needed to eat.
It doesn't mean that, like,
my heart wasn't broken.
And then I went back to
camp and I cried the whole
rest of the afternoon.
But what I said to myself was,
"I either let this knock me down
"and take the wind out of my sails
"or I'm gonna channel this
into this fierce determination
to win the challenge today."
All right, so you look at the jury.
That's five blindsides.
They're essential in the game.
It's the Mark of great survivor game play,
and you have to play that way.
You cannot let the
person who's going home
smell that they're going home,
because there's so many ways
they could disrupt the game.
But Charlie, when it gets
down to fewer numbers,
does it get easier to
blindside or more difficult?
I think, with fewer people,
every vote matters so much more.
People are thinking
about different criteria
for who they're voting out.
Are they good at challenges?
Are they good at making fire?
Are they someone the
whole jury's going to vote for?
You know, do you want them
around camp the last couple days?
And since one vote
holds so much power,
it's much more delicate,
because if you tell
the wrong person the wrong plan
or the wrong name, it is so easy for them
to flip the game on its head.
Maria, it's interesting to me,
in that list of criteria,
"alliances" was not mentioned.
We've seen seasons where alliances go
all the way to the end,
and that's your final three.
We've also seen seasons
where there's a point
where people pivot and
say, "I got to make my move."
I mean, I think alliances are important,
but I think, like he said, it's
also important to think about
who's still here tomorrow
and who's going to be on the jury.
People are really starting to
think more about who could I sit
next to, more so than, like,
are we sticking with alliances?
Are alliances shifting?
You know, it's-it's really hard to know.
Kenzie, that's two people in a row
that have basically said, "I
don't know about alliances."
I mean, I don't know
about alliances because,
not that Ben and I have
been in an "alliance" per se...
But he wrote my name down
and told me, "it was an accident."
- It really was.
- An accident.
- Wait, hold up, listen.
- Have you ever heard that?
- No.
- So I was drunk off the pizza, right?
- I can't wait to hear this.
- We had...
- There wasn't even alcohol there.
- We-we had, like,
- six pizzas.
- To be clear,
- you had soda. Yeah.
- No alcohol. Yeah. -Yeah.
I also know how to spell Venus.
It's a planet, Ben. It doesn't start with k.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm just saying, if we're
gonna talk about alliances,
I think it's kind of a wash after that.
I got to say, Ben,
I watch a lot of police
interrogation videos, -yeah.
And if I'm imagining you in
that room with the camera,
and you say, "I was drunk on pizza,"
I don't think you're
getting out of that room.
Definitely not, Jeff.
I still held his hand after he
wrote my name down, but...
She's like my survivor
sister, so if anything,
this is just some teasing, hopefully.
Hopef... Q, what's
your take on alliances?
Because Charlie didn't
mention them and Maria said,
"look, maybe, but there's only six of us,
and we're trying to get to the end."
Does that mean that
maybe alliances are over
unless they're convenient?
I wouldn't say it's over, Jeff.
I think it's plans in place
with a group of people
that see for this vote, it makes sense.
For next vote, it might not make sense,
but I understand that a vote
will be made tonight based
off a group that agreed.
How about you, Liz? Agree with that?
Yeah. Everyone, since the
hunter vote, has voted together.
And so, maybe I'm naive.
I mean, I think there
are more power couples
that are together than,
like, true alliances.
But we're all thinking
about that final tribal council.
And based on Charlie's criteria,
I'm not gonna win any
immunity challenge,
I'm terrible at fire, and
I'm not in an alliance.
So... Don't vote for me.
Charlie, it's interesting hearing Liz say,
"the last few votes have been a group
of people voting together,
except for the one."
Sooner or later, you're the one.
Yeah. Lightning's gonna strike.
And we're all sitting here,
and tonight we might
get... zapped. And...
This is a group of hardened
survivor players now.
This isn't day one survivor.
So, everyone's getting
freaking good at this game.
So it's hard to tell where
the lightning's gonna hit.
All right, it is time to
vote. Charlie, you're up.
I hope I got you.
Okay.
My gosh.
Boy, I have been trying to
get you out for a long time.
It's been a fun ride.
It's been an honor
and a pleasure working with you.
I love you so much,
but I have to think about myself
as we're moving into an individual game.
I can't wait for the boys
to meet uncle Charlie.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Charlie.
Q. One vote Charlie, one vote q.
Charlie. Two votes Charlie, one vote q.
Q. We're tied. Two
votes Charlie, two votes q.
Q. That's three votes
q, two votes Charlie,
one vote left.
13th person voted out
and the sixth member of our jury: Q.
Need to bring me your torch.
- Sorry, buddy.
- Sorry, q.
- Love you.
Q, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Appreciate it, boss.
Good game, buddy.
See y'all, now.
See you.
- Go get some tater tots, babe.
- Send us a q-skirt.
Congratulations on
making it to the final five.
Over the next three days,
you'll compete in two
immunity challenges.
We'll have two tribal councils,
one fire-making showdown.
For the three who survive,
you will get a chance
to face your jury, plead your case
about why you deserve
the title of sole survivor
and the million dollars that goes with it.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
I'm at final five.
I'm, like, a secret, little, cute assassin.
Next time on the
season finale of survivor...
It's do-or-die. Like, this
is the time to just go for it.
It's such a vibe.
It's, like, electric, almost.
This could be worth a
million dollars, right here!
Holy hot dog on a stick.
This is crazy.
I'm so close. I want to
win this friggin' game.
They blindsided me
with an idol in my pocket.
But I'm happy about
the game that I played.
I played hard but I came up short,
and it happens in life sometimes.
And, Emily, get ready, baby.
We going to applebee's,
and we're getting
that appetizer platter,
and we gonna share it,
and what you don't eat, I will.