I'm ready to get this game rolling.
This feels amazing.
Previously on survivor...
There it is. A full-blown idol that nobody
knows about.
There is a twist.
You're gonna be
randomly divided into two groups of six.
Two people are going home tonight.
Wow.
Hunter's nami, though.
If Tim wants to go against the six,
well, buddy, you are going home,
and you just don't know it.
It could be a blindside tonight...
It's not nami versus siga here.
Tonight, I want to make a big move.
Vote soda.
I want to be the curator of
the first blindside of the season.
Which is why I'm so determined
to at least break one of them off.
Venus is trying really hard, but
she's pretty oblivious.
Seventh person voted
out of survivor46: Tim.
Can I give Tim a hug real quick?
The tribe has spoken.
Eighth person voted
out and the first member
soda.
The tribe has spoken.
Yeah, yeah. I mean,
listen, we'll get into it now.
- Yeah, I want to.
- Yeah.
Before everybody gets back, too. Yeah.
I don't think you guys realize there's, like,
not much to hash out. It's, like
Tim was my first friend, so
it was just, like, a bummer,
- you know?
- Honestly, I know, but still want to chat.
Yeah, dawgs, let's go.
I lost my good friend at tribal council.
There was this unnamed
bromance happening,
the gruesome twosome
twins... me and Tim.
And it kept me feeling
sane during the game.
It's funny to cry over another dude. And,
I definitely think he was...
He was my rock, you know?
- What do I have to go on?
- Yeah.
What do you have to offer me
besides you being like, "we're vibing"?
Right, that's...
They just want to talk about bull ..., bro.
Also, we're all vibing.
- I know.
- Like, everybody here is fully down.
Yap, yap, yap, yap, yap, yap.
- I know! -I know!
- Yeah!
My god.
When we got back to camp from tribal,
I'm the type of guy who
needs to lock in, focus
and move forward with the next plan.
Tim was part of the six,
but Tim was also playing a Tim's game.
So moving forward in this game,
I need to figure out if
I want to bring in someone else.
And with the other tribe at tribal now,
hopefully voting out Venus,
we have little time to figure
out valuable information.
It's not okay just to come to camp
and keke, hee-hee and ya-ya
and not make real moves.
- And I'm, like...
- For real?
I'm a game player and
I'm a game changer and
I'm going to change the
way this game is played.
Here we go.
Who we missing?
What?
So we're all expecting Venus
to be gone, and then guess
who waltzes her beautiful self in?
My god.
Venus' name has been
brought up multiple times.
No one really enjoys working
with her, no one trusts her.
- You want to get into it?
- Yes. Absolutely.
Yeah, let's hear it. Yeah.
Tiff and I make eyes at each other like,
"they didn't do it. They didn't get her."
- You want to hear the tea.
- Yeah.
Well, surprise, surprise.
Two votes against Venus.
- Two votes against Venus.
- Who voted for you?
Tevin and soda.
Ooh. Ooh.
Let's just say a man who
claims his entire identity
in this game is surrounded by honesty
and being an honest person
straight-up lied to my face the entire day
and wrote my name down.
And I saw through that and,
you know, Karma bit them in the ass.
It was four against
soda, and she went home.
- - Damn.
- I feel bad.
No, soda took it real well.
She gave me a big hug.
She was like, "you got
me." I was like, "yeah, I did."
Then we're like.
I'm so sorry.
Venus has taken the accolades,
trying to commandeer the fact
that soda's going home was her doing.
Spicy legs. It was just like...
Yeah, we were just, like
I voted for Venus because I didn't know
if soda had an idol, I didn't
know if Venus had an idol,
and so that I could say,
"soda, I didn't vote for you.
"I told you I'd never write
your name down in the game,
and I didn't. I wrote Venus'."
But I don't need credit.
I'll explain my game
when I get to the final three.
So right now, I'm letting Venus be cocky
because, Venus, you may
not understand right now,
but you will very soon
when your torch is snuffed
and you're going home.
Look, I thought I was a cocky bitch.
She was a poison copperhead.
Well, she thinks it was her idea.
- She thinks the idea was her plan...
- And I told you,
my first opportunity, I was writing soda.
That wasn't, like, an original idea.
But it worked, which is what I wanted.
- It did.
- Went to Maria and Charlie
and they voted with us, so that's good.
My gosh.
Venus thinks she's a genius.
Wow. Tevin made a big move.
Ever since I met all of you,
I've been saying, "hey, soda, soda, soda."
And honestly, they're taking all the credit.
And for someone like
me, who has a giant ego,
it is so hard for me to
give them both the play.
Well, I'll let it lie till we get her out.
Right.
I don't want to get lost
in the shuffle of things.
So, I have to stop hesitating
and I have to start taking action
or the action is gonna be taken on me.
You were a lot more quiet
when you were hungry.
I was hungry as hell,
man, I was saying nothing.
I got some ideas flowing
in this head of mine...
And look.
So the q skirt is essentially
a hoodie flipped backwards like
a pouch of a kangaroo
with two pockets. It's gonna be
the next big thing.
I even said,
for a man, if you don't
want to wear no drawers,
you just want to wear these, you good.
For a woman, you don't
want to carry a purse
when you go to the amusement
parks or a Fanny pack,
you don't want that anymore,
you want a little more
swag... get the q skirt.
- Come on.
- If you just want fashion,
want to rip the runway
in something different,
and want to turn it to the side
get the q skirt.
- Come on, now!
- And it's coming in multiple colors.
This q skirt here will cost
less than a Fanny pack,
an extra bag, a sweater, a blanket.
All together, -all together.
- Dear.
- It's a one-in-one, and it's one for you.
- Buy three, get one free.
- Goodness.
I don't think it's worth a damn, but I think
just because of his
conviction, I want one.
I'm convinced. I want a q skirt.
There we go.
I'm definitely doing a q
skirt when I get home.
- If you a guy...
- Yup.
You just want a little swag,
but you don't want to carry a bag,
- you get the q skirt.
- Yup.
- Why?
- Will you buy a q skirt? Yes or no?
Sign me up.
Q is just a really funny guy
and someone who I am doing my best
to stay on his good side
because I've learned now
that q isn't just driving votes.
He's putting together
alliances and groups of people
he wants at the very end of the game.
So, this morning, I have perhaps
my most important
conversation of the game.
Man, I tell you, if you ever
are playing survivor, get up at sunrise.
Every single major conversation
I've had in this game has
happened at the sunrise,
when everyone's asleep in the shelter.
That's where the moves are made.
Yeah.
- I'm freaking itching.
- Well, Charlie
I'm itching to play the game, man.
- Let's friggin' do it.
- Let's do it then, man.
Let's go. Let's go.
And as we're talking, I realize,
this is an interview for an alliance.
So I'm thinking,
I want to get hired for this position.
You know, I want the job.
Maria is going to approach you
about joining a bigger alliance.
- Yeah.
- This is the first step of me saying,
- "Charlie, I want to work with you."
- Yeah.
- We're trying to get a six.
Okay.
This is the first time
that I'm hearing of the six.
I knew q had some master plans,
but I was never in, you know, the c suite.
I told you, I got your
best interest at heart.
Yeah.
So I've been, trying to
plant the seed for you
to join this alliance for a long time.
- I told you, man. I told you.
- Maria. You got my back.
So this
mystical, powerful six
that q has thrown together
is made up of two
nami... tevin and hunter,
two yanu... q and Tiffany,
two siga... Maria and
myself, the newest recruit.
We got to talk, though,
'cause, like, this game is getting crazy.
I love the six, but the
six isn't impenetrable.
The six is probably the... shakiest six
that's ever existed, because guess what?
Tim was in the six.
Maria seems pretty gung ho on the six.
She sees it as a guaranteed way
to get to the final six,
and I see it as a way
that I might get stuck
with a bunch of people
I can't beat at the end.
Only thing we got to be careful of
and watch is Charlie getting smart
and trying to make a move.
Look, I just don't think
Charlie has it to try to turn.
You know what I mean?
- He don't have that killer instinct.
- No.
We're not the first group of six
in survivor history to say,
"let's get to the final six
together, then Duke it out."
Something always goes awry.
And I have to decide
am I what goes awry?
We can play hide-and-seek.
Hide-and-seek would
be so fun right now.
Q decides that
he wants to play hide-and-seek,
which is no surprise,
because q has been
trying to play hide-and-seek
since we were at yanu camp.
We got enough people
now, and we all full.
My god. Fine.
- Y'all want to play?
- I'm in.
- We better play hide-and-seek.
- Hell, yeah. - Yeah.
And I think it's hilarious, because
here we are, these grown-ass adults
competing with each
other for a million dollars.
And we're like, "let's
play hide-and-seek, y'all."
Eeny, meeny, miny, mo,
catch a tiger by his toe.
My mama told me to
I really am a kid. I really
enjoy playing hide-and-seek.
But I'm gonna use this
as part of my game play.
But everyone else, it's just fun.
Ma. Yeah.
- I'm it?
- You're it.
I'm not playing around.
I'm gonna find you all.
Q, I'm coming for you.
I don't think anyone thinks that
this was a game play move
more than "q wanted to
have fun and be q" move.
I'm at the boat! I'm counting to 40!
- Okay, let's go.
- Okay.
What this game is gonna
represent for me is who
can hide in plain sight the best.
Thirty, 31, 32, thirty-three.
Survivor is a tense game, and
it's nice to just loosen up.
You know, sometimes you just got to
forget the strategy and
play a silly little game.
Thirty-eight, 39.40!
Ready or not, here I come!
- I did not see you at first.
- I know. I... Wow.
People are not half-as sing
this hide-and-seek game.
They are diving in the tall grass,
covering themselves with palm fronds,
going deeper into the jungle
than anyone has ever gone in this game.
Venus!
- No. No.
- Two down. Two down.
How did you see me?
- I saw your hood.
- That was good, though.
This group of ten is competitive as hell.
Whitney Houston.
My gosh.
Honestly, tevin, I did not see you.
- Yeah.
- I almost walked right by you.
That's intense.
Even though it's, like, a silly, stupid game
of hide-and-seek, and it's meant
to be, like, fun and bonding, it still
reveals a lot about
people's personality traits
and their underlying talents.
Tiffany in the grass!
Let's go.
Tiffany... the fact that
she hid with a red buff
on her head-that just tells me that
she's a little sloppy and may not know
to hide those little details.
- Dang, bro.
- Q over there.
- No way. You got q?
- Where?
I'm so proud of myself. I found someone.
Good for you.
It was only Liz
who actually walked
in the woods to see me.
Bad idea, Liz.
'Cause now I know
that you are playing the
game, you are paying attention,
and you do want to
win, as much as you say,
"it's just a million dollars."
Kenzie!
No! You got me.
- My god.
- You guys were like...
Next, we find Kenzie,
someone in this game that I know
to be a camouflage,
blend in, likable person,
which shows she can go undetected.
This was a good idea,
q. My heart was racing.
Maria?
- Maria's definitely in the well.
- Maria?!
Maria.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
We just want to talk to you.
- That's your... Maria.
- Maria!
This one here!
I got some camouflage.
Maria... super creative. Like, she put
a little headdress on for
herself, she blended in.
That says to me that she's
someone who works well
with her surroundings
and is really adaptable.
If you had a sniper, we'd be gone.
We need to step our game up here.
We have 60 seconds.
A mad dash, or else hunter and Ben win,
and that would suck.
Split up. 60 seconds.
- Hunter's somewhere stupid.
- I don't know.
I already know we're not gonna find him.
If I was hunter, I would
definitely get up in the tree.
30 seconds,
and they're both safe
and they win the game.
Five, four, three, two, one. Game over!
Hunter and Ben win.
Where are they?
Let's go!
- Damn! - Where are you?
- Where are you?
Wait. Ben's over here.
- My god.
- I can only hear him.
- I see him.
- Damn, Ben!
- Let's go!
- Good job!
Ben was not found at all
in hide-and-seek, which means
this guy is capable of
playing an undercover game,
but be very powerful at the end.
Ben made a mistake.
Hunter, you win!
- We're done looking!
- That was fun.
- That was really fun.
- Come on, dude.
Good idea. That was fun.
- That was so much fun.
- Nice going.
Hunter's right here!
My god.
I said he's in a tree.
I got q.
- Hunter, you win.
- That's ridiculous.
Hunter made a mistake.
If I can't find you in hide-and-seek,
I can't find you in this game.
If you will risk going
that high in a tree for hide-and-seek,
you would take a risk
and take a shot at me if you could.
Not happening, boss.
Honestly, that was the
perfect ending to this game.
- That was sick.
- That was fun.
And that's what
hide-and-seek showed me.
That was fun. I.
I think it might be
important for us to have, like,
a little debrief chat of
what happened last night.
I feel like feelings ran hot on both sides.
- My feelings weren't hot.
- You were sad.
Yeah.
- And I think...
- Thank you for respecting it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was a little uncertain
how that soda vote would be read,
because in my mind,
it really was my vote.
I put in the groundwork to
get all the necessary votes in
to lock that down and
make it solid, and now,
I'm kind of the first person
to pull off a blindside.
- You want to know how I pulled it off?
- Yeah.
I never even wanted to
write soda's name down.
I had a conversation
first thing that morning
where she'd said that she's
not gonna work for me long-term,
and I knew she was gonna come for me,
so, I... I pulled the
numbers as soon as I could.
- Damn, that's good.
- I know.
- And that's... - My god, today.
- My god, today.
And in terms of damage
control with tevin,
I found it to be very important for me
to air out some of our laundry
and to actually open up a line
of communication with tevin.
Can I ask you, now that
we've gotten it out of the way?
Like, I don't think I've heard you talk,
like, strategy-wise, like, what you see
for the next phase of the game.
- I'm moment to moment.
- You're moment to moment.
Yes, I understand that, but, also,
like, soda was the same way,
and I guess in this game, like,
just, like, for advice, is that you need to
sometimes show a little bit of, like...
Commitment in a direction.
But I think, for at least
this next short while,
we would benefit each
other by being more open.
Tevin's kind of like a fish out of water
in terms of the strategy
portion of this game.
Like, sure, he's a social butterfly, but
I don't think he really
knows what's going on.
Like, he seemed very
impressed that I was able
to pull that move on
him, but to me, it was like,
"how could you not see it
coming in the first place, tevin?
Like, come on."
Whoa. That's a new laugh.
She thinks, honest to god,
she has pulled off the move
that I planned for her.
These two are running around.
- "It's my idea."
- "Actually, it was mine.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha."
Shut up.
I'm about to pee.
I love tevin, but I know now
people are seeing
him as the mastermind?
She said to me, "thank
you for respecting my move."
He navigated the soda vote
without soda even knowing.
So now, I need to give a signal
to the other tribe mates
that I'm here to play, too.
I love this game.
I'm sorry, tevin, but you got to go.
I know everybody's playing
survivor hard-core right now,
but, like, sometimes you got to, like,
pause the game for, like, three minutes.
And hear me out.
What has she actually done
to make you feel threatened by her
besides mentioning your name to people
- that aren't even taking her seriously?
- Right.
- Who cares?
Let her stick around.
That's just another body.
Right.
Venus thinks she's a power player,
but she's really not. I wanted her out bad,
but I think I'd rather deal
with a nuisance than a threat.
So I'm trying to shift
my focus now because...
The point in the game
where you're just getting
out obvious targets is done.
That's the thing. I don't know who's next.
- That's right.
- That's the only thing.
You got to wait and see how
the immunity challenge shakes out
and see what the options are.
Tiffany is in my alliance.
However, Tiffany's getting shaky.
She wants to keep Venus around.
So, Tiffany is
not lining up with what the six wants,
and what the six wants
is six to stay strong.
Tiffany says Venus ain't a threat.
I know what you're saying.
I said, "Tiffany, who you want to go
instead of Venus then, if you
don't want to get Venus out?"
She said, "well, let's
just see what happens"
"in the immunity challenge
and let's just see who's left
and figure it out from there."
Up until this point, tiff has been
my number one ally in this game.
But tiff is trying to keep
members in this game
that are not part of the
six, like Venus, because
she's playing the old survivor
take a goat to the end.
That's not the game that I want to play.
In this game, you have to play a q game.
If you don't play my game
and you want to go off
and do your own thing,
then you're probably not going
to last in this game a lot longer.
And if we feel like tiff's not
gonna play get in the six,
then maybe tiff's gonna
lose, be sent home.
I'm fine with that.
So, I need to confirm that our games
are going in two different
directions, and if so,
then tiff might be the
next vote if she doesn't win.
For me, if I had to... If I
had to throw out names
for who I want to go
next, it would either be
Maria, Ben.
Ben is sneaky, but he's
not as smart as Maria.
And it just comes down to that for me.
Tiff has made multiple mistakes.
She's trying to keep goats.
And now tiff brought up Maria's name.
She's in the six, tiff. Big mistake.
Right now, the six is just
permission for q to fire.
If you bring up a name within the six,
now you've given me
ammunition to take you out
without any recourse.
- From tiff?
- Yeah.
She's making me super nervous.
And-and she-she's really
about keeping Venus.
Yeah.
Tiff said my name, and so, if someone
in our alliance is putting
up someone else's name
in the alliance, they've got to go.
- Which is?
- You can't repeat this.
Tiff has an idol.
Q told me that tiff has an idol.
I am actually really surprised
that q would tell me, that
that makes me trust q even more.
So who's our target?
So, let's go for tiff.
Got it.
Q's game is all about trust.
He does not want to feel
anybody wavering at all.
And so, if you show him
that you're trustworthy,
he's gonna work with you.
The minute you start
looking shady, you're out.
And so, we may have an alliance
of five instead of an alliance of six.
Yes.
Right now, this is the
biggest move yet for me,
to now turn on my number
one ally in the game.
The ideal is to keep my alliance
making decisions that
I want them to make,
under my control, under my rule.
It's almost like I'm a mob boss.
And they dare not to say a
name within my organization.
And if they do, send 'em packing.
I send 'em a q skirt, though.
Come on in!
- Good morning.
Good morning, Jeff.
- Morning.
- Morning, Jeff.
All right, shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
- Let's do it, Jeff.
- First things first.
Ladies, got to take back the necklaces.
No!
- Here, you take it.
- All right.
Thanks, Jeff.
Thank you, Maria.
All right, once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
it is a survivor classic
and one I never get tired of seeing.
You're gonna hold onto a pole...
For as long as you can.
When you drop
you're out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity, guaranteed
- a spot in the final nine.
- Wow.
Losers, tribal council, where somebody
will be the ninth person voted out
and become the second
member of our jury.
Little something else to deal with today.
- I knew it. I knew it.
- How fun.
In this new era of survivor,
you start with very
little, including no food.
And then at a certain point in
the game, you're given a chance
to earn some food.
That day is today.
My god.
- That's a heavy bag.
- Yes.
Enough rice to last you
to the end of the season.
- Wow.
Here's what it will cost you.
Four players...
Have to agree to sit out of this challenge,
give up your shot at immunity
in exchange for the rice.
- And four is the Max?
- Minimum.
The minimum? The
minimum, right? Four is it.
Are you willing to negotiate, Jeff?
- We can't do three?
- No. Four is the set number.
No negotiating, Jeff?
I'll give you an option.
Four of you can agree to sit out,
or two of you can agree...
To give up your vote
at tonight's tribal council
and still compete
and still have a shot at immunity.
I'm gonna say, "hell, no."
Well, it really comes
down to the same thing.
Where does everybody
feel they sit in the game?
How comfortable are
you with your alliance?
Talk about it.
Is anyone thinking immediately,
- "I'm sitting out for this?"
- No one want to sit out?
- Nope.
- No.
Wow. Nobody.
So before we even go further,
Charlie, what does that say
about where survivor46 is?
Everyone out here is a competitor.
- We played hide-and-seek -for nothing.
- Yeah.
Not for immunity,
not for any advantage, and people were
diving into tall grass.
You know, hunter
climbed 20 feet up in a tree.
You know, these people
are here to compete.
And when you give us this,
which is one of the survivor classics,
- nobody wants to sit out.
- Yeah.
I'll be one.
Okay.
- I haven't eaten.
- Okay, so we've got two.
Liz says "I'll sit out." Q
is volunteering to sit out.
We just need two more
and this rice is yours.
If we give you an immediate third,
- would you give us the rice?
- No.
It's four. Four is not even half.
That's fair in this game. Venus,
you're shaking your head
"no," which I understand.
Explain why.
Only one person will win this challenge,
and I have a very good feeling
that that person could be me,
so I don't want to step out.
Is there anyone who'd step
out, like, in a pair, two at once?
- They just don't...
- Are you willing to step out?
If there's someone who's
willing to jump out with me,
- I'd consider it.
- I mean, stepping out now don't commit us
to doing it. If you step out,
and no one else is
doing it, he counts down,
and we just all do it, you
know, so if you want to step out,
- step out.
- Right, and then, we still play.
I don't know. I want to play it, though.
Let's make it interesting.
You keep talking.
I'll just quietly count.
Ten.
- Wow.
- Nine.
Eight. Seven.
Six.
- Five.
- I don't think anyone wants to step out.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One. We don't have a deal.
First time in the new era
we could not come to a deal.
Liz, you can step back.
Y'all, I'm fitting to win this.
- Yeah. You deserve it.
- It tells me
everybody here is playing,
this game is fully cooked.
- Wow.
- That's all you ever want in a season.
We'll draw for your
spots, we'll get started.
Well, it's been one of the
most unpredictable seasons
of survivor, and honestly, it's
why I still love doing this job.
Come on out. Apply to be on survivor.
It is a very tall pole.
I'm so weak.
It can be scary.
Okay.
All right, everybody is in position,
and this challenge is on.
You gave up rice for a
shot at security tonight.
This is what you're
fighting for, right here.
You never know when
it's you going home.
The only way to be certain in survivor
absolutely certain... is
to have that necklace.
Kenzie already adjusting her position.
Liz is going down to a smaller foothold.
- Q is first out. Immediately, Liz is out.
- I can't do it.
Seconds in,
and it's the two people
who volunteered to sit out,
q and Liz, that are first out.
- Kenzie's out.
- Thought she had a shot.
- No.
- We're down to seven.
Ben struggling.
Maria now moving a
little farther down the pole.
Ben sliding down. He's
out of footholds now.
Just the sheer willpower. It's over.
Ben gonna rock his
way -over to the bench.
Yeah.
My feet are too big, dude.
- Maria's out.
- And we are now down to five.
I know.
It is Charlie, hunter, tiff
whistling tevin
- and Venus.
- Like a little bird, Jeff.
You see the little birds out in the ocean
on them little Poles out there?
Sit there all day, just the wind blowing.
That's what I feel like, Jeff.
Tevin, what kind of bird would you be?
Ooh! Well, I'd be a peacock, Jeff.
I mean, I don't see a
peacock in the ocean that often,
but I think if I had to be any kind of bird...
The longest this challenge has gone
in survivor history is two hours.
Ozzy won that.
I'm ready to beat ozzy today, baby.
You all have been up
there seven minutes.
- Several. -Several.
- Several.
I think "several" has entered
the survivorvernacular.
Survivorforty-several.
- Long live jelinsky.
- Long live him.
Jeff, are you dropping
Taylor swift songs for me now?
"Long live." "Speak now."
- Is that your favorite?
- One of 'em.
Come on, tevin, find your foot.
You got this, tevin.
- Tevin slipping a little.
- Trying to get that foot back up.
Literally trying to pull
himself back up that pole,
get his feet back in.
- You're back in it.
- And he does.
We're good.
Tiff adjusting again.
Hunter readjusting.
You got it, tiff.
- You got it.
- Come on, tiff.
That's your last foothold...
Tiff continues to slide
farther down the pole.
- Tiff's gonna opt out of this challenge.
- Aw.
- Good job.
- Good job, tiff.
We are down to four players left.
I'm going down.
- Tevin sliding down a little farther.
- Come on, tevin...
- Tevin looks like he's out.
- And he is. We're down to three.
- Good job, tevin.
- Amazing.
It is Charlie, hunter and Venus
fighting for immunity.
Guaranteed spot at nine.
You're at 15 minutes.
- I know that feels like forever.
- What are you doing?
Hunter adjusting.
Charlie moving down.
Venus confidently
proclaimed she thought
she could win this challenge. Let's see.
Charlie adjusts again.
Bit of a slip.
- You got it, Charlie.
- You got it, Charlie!
And once again, Charlie's back up.
Shake it... You setting me up? Aw.
Hunter adjusting now.
Venus still down on
the end, looking to fulfill
her prediction that she will leave here
with that necklace.
Charlie with another slip.
- Can he regain? And he does.
- You got it.
You got it, Charlie. Stand
up, Charlie. Take a break.
Everybody adjusting
now at the same time.
You got it, Charlie.
Venus adjusting again.
Trying to pull herself up or
find a foothold farther down.
Just anywhere that
will relieve some pain.
Just for a moment.
Venus sliding again.
- Not looking good for Venus.
- You got this, v.
Slipping more.
- That's it. Venus is out.
- Aw... good job.
- She was in there a long time.
- Good job.
A good effort.
Came up short. And
we're down to a showdown.
- Charlie and hunter for immunity.
- Good job, guys.
Been up there 20 minutes.
Keep fighting, Charlie.
The shortest win was 17 minutes.
Q and Liz did not last 20 seconds.
All right. We know.
It's all love.
How long do you think
you would last, Jeff?
Longer than 20 seconds.
My god, today!
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Damn.
That's all right.
Yeah, no q skirt for you, Jeff.
No discount, no nothing.
Not really. You?
Yeah. I found a couple of
rotations that work for me.
Charlie sliding down even more.
And Charlie looks like
he's about to give in,
but he's hanging on by his fingers.
- Don't let go, Charlie.
- Keep on going, baby.
That's how you do it on survivor, charlie.
Just a little tease.
Squeeze those glutes.
- Jeff?
- Yeah.
I've got you right where I want you.
- Great negotiating, Charlie.
- Yeah?
I have all the leverage, so
why don't we go with two bags?
I got to say no.
- Aw.
- Crawl back up, Charlie.
- Yo, don't listen...
Come on. Crawl back up.
- Crawl back up, Charlie.
- Come on, Charlie.
Get up there.
- Got to get to the top. Have that rice.
Charlie drops. He's out.
- Hunter wins individual immunity.
- Damn.
- Safe tonight at tribal council.
- Good job, hunter.
Guaranteed... whoa, hunter!
- What is happening?
- Hunter!
What are you doing?
- He's bragging, Jeff.
- Now, you're just showing off.
I'm so proud of you, dude.
Good job, hunter.
It actually wasn't that
bad to stay like that.
Survivor MacGyver.
- Take a seat.
- Good job.
- What's up, man?
- What up, player?
Good job, hunter.
Hunter, come on over.
All right, hunter!
Well-earned.
- Great job, brother.
- Immunity is yours.
Safe tonight at tribal council.
Cannot be voted out of this game.
Guaranteed a spot in the final nine.
- Yes.
- As for the rest of you,
after 16 days, that's
gonna be it for somebody.
Tonight at tribal, somebody
will be the ninth person voted out,
become the second member of our jury.
You have the afternoon to
figure out who it's gonna be.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at tribal council.
- Congrats.
- Thank you, Jeff.
I'm ecstatic about winning.
I was surprised when
people didn't sit out.
'Cause there were a
few people I was like,
"do you really think you
have a chance to win this?"
But as of right now, my
game plan is to vote for Tiffany.
It seems like everyone's on board.
And now, like, we have an opportunity
to take care of it, so why not?
I don't see why anyone
would want to change it.
- Good job, hunter.
- Nice job, hunter.
- Great job, hunter.
- Good job, hunter.
All that tree time paid off.
- Yeah.
I'm frustrated.
Like, the challenge has
pissed me off so much
because we gave up rice.
All these people that
want to "try the challenge."
Let it out, babe.
Bro, it-it was... It was just idiotic.
This man, in a game of hide-and-seek,
chose to hide in a... tree.
- Hunter?
- You think you gonna
hang on a damn pole
longer than Tarzan?
Get the hell out of dodge.
They can cancel Christmas,
I ain't think they gonna
hang on that damn pole
longer than that boy.
Tell me how you really feel, baby.
- Real mad.
- That was a bad decision, man.
Now we have to go
out and try to find food.
It doesn't affect the vote. It is time
to send tiff to the jury
because she broke my rule.
If you target anybody within the six,
you go home.
We talked about it a little bit earlier.
You still want the same plan or
you want to do something else?
We already knew what was up.
We already said, "hey, if Tiffany doesn't
win immunity today, she's gone."
She's messing with the six alliance.
Therefore, she got to go.
Okay. We got three right now. I know.
- Maria would go for it.
- Charlie would go for it.
You think Liz would go for that?
- Yeah.
- That's all we need.
In addition to the plus-one
alliance, I believe that Liz
would vote with us, as she
has in the past tribal councils.
So, if this plan goes down,
Tiffany will be blindsided tonight.
How's it going over here?
All I know is I'm thinking...
"Liz"
"do you just want to stay in the game..."
- Or do you want to play the game?
- Right. Do you want to
- play the game? Yeah.
- "Or do you want to, like, play
- "and have a... shot?"
- Yeah.
- I mean, I'm just gonna say it.
- Say it.
If this gets out, like, I'm gone tonight.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
I want tevin gone.
I love tevin. We've been number ones,
but he made a really big move with soda.
Do you think that he's the
most logical threat right now?
Yes.
I, personally, I would like tevin out.
I want to blindside tevin.
I've realized who Liz
is, and Liz is a fighter.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Let me just be real with you.
I'm looking back at the last
15 days, laughing at myself
at how many times I let someone else
take the lead, and... I'm done with that.
It's got to be tevin tonight.
- Okay.
- Thank god.
Finally, people have come to their senses
and have realized how
big of a threat tevin is.
From what I'm hearing...
Okay.
And I think if we all,
maybe, work together
- and try to get tevin...
- Okay.
We could probably form a comfortable,
maybe, chill alliance for a vote or two.
- Okay.
- Tevin's got the social
charisma like I've never seen.
He's so likable. In real life, amazing.
In a game where we're
competing for a million dollars,
got to go.
Game time, brother.
Also, the yanu three
has been driving so
many votes in this game,
and right now, I don't want
to be leading all of the votes
to put a bigger target on yanu.
- Liz... Liz wants...
- We got to vote for tevin.
- Liz is on board.
- Ben just told me the same thing.
- Okay, good. We're voting tevin.
- Yes.
But if it gets back to tevin,
- it's gonna be... That's how easy.
- And that's why... and as...
But, also, he has an extra vote,
so he could flip that on any of us.
Yeah.
Tevin is a huge threat.
Also, tevin has an
extra vote in his pocket.
And the deeper we get into the game,
the more power that
extra vote is gonna have.
What's up with you?
But right now,
q and I have a great working relationship.
We share information freely.
I absolutely cannot leave him out
of a vote at this point in time.
Everybody who I spoke
to today is saying tevin.
- Everybody.
- Who?
Liz the one who brought
tevin name up to me.
And she said that she spoke
to Charlie, Ben and Maria,
and they was with it.
She was like, "listen..."
Well, I'm gonna tell you right now,
if you don't vote tevin, people gonna
be looking at you next.
You better get on board.
The idea of a plan being
changed last-minute
doesn't really sit well with me.
Tiff was telling me about the plan.
- Yeah.
- Is that real coming from you,
- or is that just talk?
- Yes.
You talking about t?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- That's real?
I feel like just about
everybody's on board.
I'm not the driver in the tevin vote.
And my game is based
off me being in control.
So I wanted to gain control again.
Everybody you think
is working with us have flipped.
Tevin is the one that's
going home tonight.
- They're voting for tevin?
- All of 'em.
- Every single person in this camp.
- Okay.
We can't stop it.
So there's no need to even bring it up,
because then they gonna
know I said something.
You see what I'm saying?
I ain't trying to... my game
over trying to save one person.
But I know if we write tiff name down,
she's gonna be here
tomorrow. She's not going home.
Okay.
Hunter... Q says it's actually tevin,
and we don't have
the numbers anymore,
but it just seems so off the wall for me.
Tevin's good for all of our games,
and we made an alliance
based off ofandy Griffith.
I want to keep tevin here.
And so it's like, I've got to go
and do this damage control
and get ahead of what's going on,
so it doesn't just
completely destroy my game.
Hunter walks right past me
to go to talk to other people.
And I'm like, "man, this guy,
he's doing exactly what
I did not want him to do,"
especially moments
before going to tribal.
Venus, can we talk to them real fast?
Can we chat with them real quick?
- Without me there?
- Yes.
I made a mistake, and now this plan
is all screwed up.
I should have kept my mouth shut.
The reason we targeted
tiff is because she,
like, went after Maria.
Tevin never did that.
I guess the decision is, are we fine
with tevin leaving right now?
He trusts us so much
that the guy's just sitting
back there thinking it's all fine.
- Y'all... I mean...
- No, no, I-I hear you.
I hear you. I'm thinking.
Anticipating chaos.
For the first time in my life.
I've never seen that man
run to someone and talk trash.
He just... Now he's gesturing
over here. Now he's gesturing
- over here again.
- So, we still
have the numbers, right?
- Yeah.
- Definitely.
The plan is tevin.
There's peace in the
castle. The kingdom is calm.
But now all I see is this
conversation on the beach,
and my radar is going off.
Something's afoot.
All right, bro.
There are no rules. I can go sit there.
Hi. What's up?
Venus, I love you.
I'm really sorry. I have to talk to them.
I know that's gonna piss you off.
I'm sorry, but y'all also realize
the sun is setting, and we all have talks.
So, like, can y'all wrap it
up in the next few minutes?
- Yes. -Sure.
- Thank you.
Yes.
Charlie, I want to know what you think.
- You seem really upset.
- I'm not upset. No.
I'm just feeling, like,
all the whiplash of today.
- It's, like...
- So then you guys want to go back to tiff?
Like, is that what you would prefer, or...
Listen, I'll do whatever
y'all want, at this point.
Yeah.
I know, but we got to
come together as a whole.
I would rather keep
the original and go tiff.
- Y'all do whatever you want.
- I'm voting tevin.
I have no freaking clue
what's gonna happen
because of this chaos
that's been whipped up
at the 11th hour.
- So, so...
- I don't know what the heck's...
Half of the tribe wants to get out tiff.
The other half wants to
get tevin out of the game.
And, at this point, Maria and I
are at another crossroads.
In my eyes, tevin is
the better option than tiff.
Tevin orchestrated the soda blindside,
but this threadbare
alliance of six is thinking
about voting out tiff
because tiff threw out the name Maria.
And, ultimately, Maria's my number one.
This alliance has zero
legs. It's going nowhere.
It's the loosest use of the word "alliance"
that has ever existed, but, once again,
Maria and I have to commit
and we have to make a decision.
Well, all right, I guess we got to start
with the rice negotiation.
It's 16 days with very little food.
Q, you tried.
You were the first to say, "I'll volunteer."
Wisely so, 'cause you were
first out of the challenge.
Has there been any
discussion about that?
I had a bit of a
temper tantrum back at camp, after.
I was still upset and mad.
I mean, I think five people
were out within two minutes,
and there was only gonna be
one winner and one loser tonight.
So everyone suffered
when I think the odds were
in their favor to feed
everybody for another nine days.
Liz, another thing that is very difficult
to try to understand until you're here
is what hunger after 16 days feels like.
Are you surprised that the group
couldn't make a deal?
I was surprised that q sat out.
I thought I was gonna
be the only one to step up
because I can't eat
coconut, I can't eat papaya.
Even some of the rewards I have
barely been able to eat.
I haven't even gone to the restroom yet.
Tiff, is the rice negotiation
just an indicator of where this game is?
Absolutely.
Nobody feels safe enough to step out.
Everybody feels like they
need to compete for immunity,
and that was blatantly obvious.
They said food is not
as important as safety.
But, Jeff, I want to stop before
we get deep into the tribal.
The only person that's
going home tonight is me.
And I'll tell you why.
Wait, wait, w... you mean
you're predicting your vote out?
Yeah. Well, I don't think anyone here
coming into the tribal
council was voting for me,
but I'm gonna ask
everybody to vote for me.
Then all of these nine folks
are going back to camp today.
I feel like...
- Let me just interrupt real quick.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is this news to everyone?
- Yeah. What is going on?
- What the hell? -Totally.
Q, what are you talking about?
So if someone goes
home tonight, and it wasn't
the right way, because, like I say,
there's probably five
people here right now
who are like, "who the
heck am I voting for?"
Because of mistakes
that I made in the game.
And I want everybody to start
just playing the game hard.
You have a new beginning.
Kenzie, it's clear what he's saying, right?
Yeah.
To everyone. He is saying, "vote me out."
Is that clear to everyone?
- It's clear, but, like, what?
- Yeah, it's clear, but it doesn't...
- But it doesn't make sense.
- But I don't understand why.
The math isn't math-ing,
because I've talked to q,
and I know that q is here
and he wants to play the game.
And I guess it's just
kind of out of the blue,
and it's just very unexpected.
It's not something that
was even hinted towards.
- I mean, it is completely off-brand.
- Yeah.
And yet, Ben, we just
talked about how competitive.
It's so competitive,
you wouldn't give up your
shot at immunity for rice.
And here's somebody
saying, "guess what?
Merry Christmas."
You know, q and I did
not get off to a great start,
but everybody knows
he's been playing hard
and in a genuine way.
So it's like this... th...
Even me, who's been, like,
kind of skirting around
him, is like, "what?"
This is actually, like, probably the most
bonkers thing I would
have expected tonight.
Tiff.
I'm very confused, Jeff.
I don't know where this
is coming from because
I've known q since I got
here, and q's a competitor.
So this is completely, like,
coming out of left field for me.
It's-it's not me giving up. Trust me.
I want to play, and I've
been playing since day one.
But again, when something
don't sit right with me
and I feel partially responsible for it,
I got to own up to it and
say, "you know what?
I'm not gonna steal someone
else's joy and dream,"
especially in this game, where
you only get an opportunity
to potentially play once.
- And...
- I think you can own up to it,
person to person,
without leaving the game.
And I don't think anyone wants you to go.
- Yeah.
- And I-I know y'all don't, but
someone is going to get voted out
because of last-minute
things that happened,
and I feel partially responsible for it.
And I'm big enough to say that I want
you guys to go on and play.
I'm serious about this, now.
I want y'all to go on and play,
but start playing the game.
'Cause everybody
have a new opportunity.
So, Kenzie, on one side,
q's volunteering, which means
nobody else here is going home.
On the other side, q is a vote,
and he's probably in an alliance
with one or two or three or
who knows how many people.
So that also will impact the game.
Yeah. Q's saying, "go
ahead. Fresh start."
What if you were a part of
my plans five plans from now?
That's not a fresh start for me.
That's undoing the plans
that I've been building.
Like, it's gonna be
wacky no matter what.
Like, it's not, like, we're gonna
go back to camp and be like,
"well, q's gone. No worries."
Like, "we're all Kumbaya."
Because all we gonna do is
go back with a bunch of questions.
We know exactly who
you were talking to last.
But we can't get answers
Jeff, but at the same
time, q is a grown man,
and this is a game for not one dollar,
not $1,000, but one million.
And if someone wants to
walk out of the game willingly,
then I am not going to
coddle them to say, "stay."
Can we talk? Can we talk
for a minute? Can we talk?
Yeah. It's your tribal.
Boy.
I guess we're at a live tribal, Jeff.
I don't know.
It's like, "dude, what is up?"
I don't understand why...
Okay?
This does not rock.
Kenzie, come here.
My...
Wow.
I don't know who. I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Never seen anything like this.
All right.
In one of the craziest tribals ever,
it is time to vote.
Q, you're up.
That was the dumbest thing ever.
Dumbest tribal ever.
My god.
At this point, I don't know if this
is the real plan, the fake plan.
This is what I was told.
And we want to flush
the extra vote tonight.
Whatever.
I'm as confused as hell.
I don't know what the hell going, q,
but clearly you been out of
Mississippi too damn long,
'cause your brain is gone.
But we can talk about that
when we get back to camp.
I'm gonna put this down.
Give me some good luck.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
Venus.
Tevin.
Two votes Venus, one vote tevin.
Tevin. We're tied.
Two votes Venus, two votes tevin.
Tevin. That's three votes
tevin, two votes Venus.
Tevin. That's four votes
Tevin. That's five votes
Kevin, two votes Venus.
Ninth person voted out
and the second member of our jury:
Tevin. That's six. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
That was so shocking.
Y'all can go eat worms and slugs.
- Tevin, we love you.
- Love you.
- Love you, tevin.
- Tevin, you rock.
- Y'all say that now.
This is so exciting, Jeff.
Okay. I'm sorry.
- Tevin...
- Yeah?
The tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
- Good job, brother.
- Good luck, y'all.
Tevin, you rock.
This doesn't rock.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
You... Are you stupid?
Are you dumb?
Next time on survivor...
Everybody's turning on everyone.
This game's flipped on its head.
These bumbling buffoons.
These two dum-dum meatheads.
I'm-a give 'em hell. They
can cancel Christmas.
I was absolutely blindsided,
which is actually kind of epic.
I was a little bit confused
tonight about q's antics,
but I am so happy
at every single thing that I've done here.
I have shown myself,
and I am so thankful
for the opportunity to do this thing
that I've been watching
since I was a little boy.
This is a dream come
true. And god is so good.