Welcome to the season
finale of survivor46.
Well, it's been a fun
and unpredictable season of survivor.
We've had a lot of
strong players taken out
including six straight
blindsides... forming our jury.
We've had five players voted
out with idols in their pocket,
including the last four in a row.
That's a record.
And to date, it's been 23
days they've gone without rice.
Also a record.
But now we're down to five.
Tonight we'll have two
immunity challenges,
two tribal councils, one
fire-making showdown.
And then our final three will face the jury
and we will crown a
winner of survivor46.
We'll then immediately
go into the after show
while we're still here in beautiful Fiji
and talk about it all.
All right, our final five:
Charlie, Maria, Ben, Liz and Kenzie.
Who will be this season's sole survivor
and take home the
check for a million dollars?
This is it.
Season finale, survivor46.
My god.
And behold.
Previously on survivor...
Hopefully, we get to keep in touch
- and be in each other's lives.
- My god, yeah.
I adore Charlie so much, but right now,
- he's standing in my way.
- I am just
so grateful to, like,
have you just in my life.
I love her to death, but
if I'm going to play to win,
I have to vote her out.
Maria down to her last piece.
And there it is.
Maria's done it. Her third
individual immunity win.
Now everybody's trying to
come together to take down
the king and queen.
- Yeah, I love Charlie.
- Yeah.
Maria thinks Liz and I
are gonna vote Charlie.
- I knew this day would come.
- Yeah.
But we're just bamboozling Maria and q.
All right.
Tonight is Charlie's night to go,
and I hope I get a hug.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Thirteenth person voted out
and the sixth member of our jury: Q.
The tribe has spoken.
Congratulations on
making it to the final five.
One of you will claim
the title of sole survivor
and the million dollars that goes with it.
Charlie, can we go talk?
Yeah, of course. Where you want to go?
My god.
I messed up. I messed up tonight.
I tried to take out Charlie, my closest ally.
But my big move didn't pan out.
And, yeah, I have to do,
like, major damage control.
Yeah.
To tell me that if I sat
next to you at the end,
I was never gonna win.
They pitted me against
you and did a bait and switch
and made me vote for
you so I look like an idiot,
and now q's gone.
I'm, like, nauseated
just trying to explain myself to Charlie,
and I'm really worried my
best friend in the game
is never gonna forgive me,
and my game is done.
That threesome
- that's up there is out to get us.
- Yeah.
They messed up the alliance -like...
- No, no.
- I trusted the most and now it's tainted.
You know what? There's
no reason to call the party off.
I still want to party, okay?
Because we're down to
five people, and guess what?
We just got to think how
we're gonna play this.
Okay.
Final five by the skin of my teeth. Ooh!
Maria, my number one
ally, came for my throat.
You know, it'd be easy for
me to be bitter and upset, but
let's be real. If she didn't win immunity,
I was planning on doing the same thing.
I'm sorry. God, I screwed up.
- God.
- What the heck, Maria?
- Man.
- What the heck?
I'm sorry.
Maria feels terrible,
she feels bamboozled,
but it's completely fake.
I know it.
She came for me and I came out on top.
I totally screwed up.
- Damn.
- But if one thing came out of tonight,
it's that I'm a big threat,
and people are willing
to write my name down.
So, I have to keep every path
open, keep every option open,
to get to the end and
go for the win, go for the million.
- We made final five.
- Honestly,
- that was a great tribal.
- That was a great...
And, Liz, you finally got
your wish to vote q off.
You think that was just Liz's wish?
- No, I doubt that.
- And that's what's up.
Q, my darling, you got played.
I'm so excited!
That was honestly a
really good move, guys.
Y'all are playing way
harder than I thought.
Yeah, we could have
told you that, but we didn't.
Yeah, I know.
Maria says she finally
sees that we are
actually playing the game.
Just a face. I don't even have words.
Just a face for that.
But at this point in the game,
Maria has a giant target on her back.
Q ruined my game tonight and I fell for it.
- Yeah. Damn.
- Y'all want to let me win tomorrow?
I am on the bottom, and
now, you know, there's
a massive target on me.
Winning tomorrow is imperative.
Like, this is the time to just, like, go for it,
to fight as hard as I can, and hopefully
either win or go down fighting.
Come on in!
Mighty fierce-looking final five.
Going back to day one,
nobody would have predicted this five.
No, no.
But here we are.
All right, shall we get to
today's immunity challenge?
- Yes.
- First things first, Maria.
For the third time, I have to take it back.
- One more, Jeff.
- I got one more in me.
Whoa.
That was a big prediction.
All right, for today's challenge,
you're gonna race through
a series of obstacles.
Once you're through,
you'll retrieve a rope
and use it to drop a bridge.
You'll then cross that
bridge and retrieve a key,
then climb to the finish,
where you will use that key
to unlock your puzzle pieces.
Once you've finished your puzzle,
it will reveal the solution
to a combination lock.
First person to solve their combination
and bang their gong... Wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot in the final four,
which means you cannot
be voted out of this game.
At the very least, you're making fire
for a shot to get to three.
In addition, playing for reward.
- I knew it.
- Want to know what you're playing for?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
The winner will be
taken to the sanctuary,
where good things happen, for pasta.
- Caesar salad, - nice. Yes.
- Garlic bread,
- yeah. Yeah.
- Macaroons, chocolate pudding,
wine and soda.
Losers, tribal council,
where somebody will be
the 14th person voted out,
become the seventh member of our jury.
Everybody knows this. I got to say it.
Maria, if you win today's challenge,
- you join an elite group of four women.
- Wow.
The only four women
in the history of survivor
to win four individual
immunity challenges.
A lot at stake. Draw
for spots. We'll get it on!
- Here we go. - Here we go.
- Let's do it, let's do it.
All right, here we go.
For a guaranteed spot
in the final four.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, you're going through a muddy net.
- You're gonna get covered in mud.
- My god.
- It doesn't matter.
- It's day 24.
You want to get to day 25.
Right here!
Everybody struggling through that net.
Charlie's gonna be out first.
Use the water if you need it.
You're gonna need your eyes to see.
- Kenzie's through!
- Ooh!
Maria's through.
Ben is through.
Now you're pulling out
rope to release that plank.
The only way through
is to pull that plank out
and then cross.
Here comes Liz.
Everybody working on their ropes.
Every second could
count in this challenge.
Charlie down to his last bit.
Plank's out. He's good.
Maria's got her plank out. She's good.
It is Maria and Charlie at opposite ends.
Here comes Kenzie.
Charlie through the next obstacle.
Maria's through it.
Charlie's dropped his monkey's fist.
Maria has hers. Here comes Kenzie.
Now you've got to drop your bridge,
using that ball of rope.
Kenzie has hers!
- Ooh. Yay!
- She's in this.
Here comes Ben.
Liz now in the tunnel.
Ben's got his. He's good.
Maria with a nice
toss. That's gonna do it.
Maria first to drop her bridge.
Charlie drops his bridge.
Now retrieve your key.
We are neck and neck right now
with Charlie and Maria.
Here comes Liz.
Ben a little short.
Maria has her key. She's heading up.
Maria now in the lead.
Charlie has his key. He's heading up.
Kenzie drops her bridge,
working on her key.
Now you got to climb up
and unlock those puzzle pieces.
Ben and Liz still working
to drop their bridge.
Liz has her bridge dropped.
Ben's got it. Liz heading up.
Kenzie has her key.
Ben working on his key.
Liz looking for her key.
She forgot it.
She's got to come
back down and go get it.
Maria working on her
puzzle. Kenzie working.
Charlie working. Ben has his key.
He's up top now, working on his puzzle.
Liz had to go all the way back.
She forgot her key.
Day 24, final five challenge, huge stakes.
Reward is secondary.
You want immunity right now.
Here comes Liz heading back up again.
We're gonna have
everybody on the puzzle.
Another complicated survivor puzzle.
It'll give you all the information you need
to solve that combination lock.
Then you bang that
gong and you're good.
Kenzie making a lot of
progress on this puzzle.
Charlie getting a little
more momentum now.
You cannot slow down.
Do not stop digging right here.
We are very close. Kenzie and Maria.
Maria with another piece.
Kenzie down to six pieces.
Maria at nine.
Kenzie with another piece.
And another.
Kenzie down to four pieces left.
Guaranteed spot at four.
Everybody else vulnerable tonight.
She's got the puzzle done.
- My god.
- Now what?
New twist in this challenge.
Could be the end for me.
I've done all I can do,
but if I can pull off this mov,
I'm gonna win this game.
And so, tonight is a massive night.
It's do-or-die for me.
- You are wonderful.
- Thank you, Kenzie.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Liz, Ben and Kenzie
have been very open.
They're voting Maria. So, where are you?
"If you can get me, you should get me."
I think any competitor
knows how to win
and knows how to lose.
And I can honor and respect
any move that takes down a
fierce competitor like myself.
There's also.
Where does that come from?
I guess it comes from my upbringing.
You know, I'm-I'm an immigrant.
I come from Beirut, Lebanon, and
you know, I grew up
with, I guess, an environment of survival.
You know, work hard, be determined
and to be honest and to be respectful
and to be gracious and to be humble.
And I think to myself,
"my husband and I
are raising three boys."
Listen up, future nephews.
Your mom kicks butt.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right. I'll read the votes.
Ben.
Let's go!
Maria.
One vote Ben, one vote Maria.
Maria. Two votes Maria, one vote Ben.
Fourteenth person voted out
and the seventh
member of our jury: Maria.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Good job, Maria.
Bring it in, lieutenant mom.
I want a hug.
Maria, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you.
It's been a pleasure, you guys. Love you.
- We love you, Maria.
- Mvp.
Bye.
Congratulations on
making it to the final four.
At night, I don't know what happens.
Some nights, I have a
reason why I freak out,
but last night, I had all the
reason in the world to chill
you know, I had a
reward, we got Maria out.
But I have this hysteria,
It's weird. It's like I wake up from a drem
and this jolt of electricity
bumps me up like beetlejuice.
I've been suffering since,
like, day 13 or whatever.
I know.
- Ben, is that you?
- Yeah.
- Hold my hand just a little bit.
- I'm right here.
Yeah.
I need water.
I feel very blessed because
people show up for me.
They believe in me.
Anti-anxiety hug.
We got you, bro.
To me, it just comes down to, like,
I went through it.
I didn't quit.
And thank god I had Kenzie and Charlie.
There we go.
There you go, Benny. Nice job.
I'm getting this feeling
that everyone thinks
Liz is the number one threat.
We definitely need to throw her into fire.
I've never had my name written down.
I have four nami members on the jury.
Shall we get to your
final immunity challenge?
Here you go.
Ooh.
For the last time, immunity
is back up for grabs.
While the ball is making
its way back down the ramp,
you can work on your puzzle.
When the ball reaches the bottom,
you got to stop, grab
your ball, roll it again.
But if you fail
to get your ball before
it hits the metal track,
then you have to wait as the ball slowly
makes its way to the bottom.
And during that time, you
can't work on your puzzle.
I barely slept more
than two hours a night
- for, like, 14 days.
- Wow.
And it's, like, been
the most intense time of my entire life.
And, I don't know, I'm
just ready to rock, dude.
That's it.
Shall we finish with the stakes?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's important.
- First person to finish
wins immunity, guarantees
themselves a spot
at the final three.
Let it sink in.
Kenzie heading back. Charlie
heading back. Ben heading back.
Kenzie with another roll.
She's good.
Charlie's good.
Ben has his ball.
Ben's good.
Liz, nice left-handed launch. That'll work.
Everybody back on the puzzle.
You know this logo. You've
been living with it on your buff.
Charlie, stop. Put the piece
down. Go to your board.
Charlie's ball came down very quickly.
He missed it. Now, he's got to wait
a very long time, as that ball slowly
rolls to the bottom.
Giving an advantage to everybody else.
Day 25, survivor46.
Your shot at a million dollars, right here.
She's got it. Kenzie's
quickly getting back in this.
It's now Ben in the lead.
He's yet to win an immunity challenge.
This would be his first.
He's put everything on a
slow and steady approach.
Kenzie, right behind, fresh on
the heels of an immunity win.
Would love it again.
Charlie trying to catch up.
You cannot slow down right now.
Kenzie very close.
Ben down to his last piece.
For the win.
Ben has done it! It's over!
Ben wins individual immunity.
Came down to three pieces
between Kenzie and Ben.
You say everybody wants
some. How 'bout you?
Ben, come on over.
- Let's go, buddy.
- Let's go, katzman.
Dude, I thought I'd
never get to see the day.
- Rock and roll.
- You look great, bud.
Ben, your first individual
win of the season
couldn't come at a better
time. You have done it.
You've guaranteed yourself
a spot at the final three.
You will get a chance to plead your case.
And you get a challenge
that requires split focus.
And of all four, you had the most focus.
It was clear. Where did that come from?
What is that inside you that you,
when you need to,
you can get that gear?
Today, I was just like, "I
have to show up for me,"
'cause I'm always trying to
be somebody's hype man.
And at, like, 1:00 in the morning, I'm like,
"it's okay, dude. I love
you. You came this far."
You know what I'm saying?
And this was, like, the most meditational,
transcendental shred-itation game
of the entire season.
So I just was in the moment,
and I didn't think about anything else.
- All right.
- I know that's a word scramble,
See you tonight at tribal.
- Good job, brother.
- Let's do it.
I was so down on myself,
and I could have quit
when I was at my lowest,
but I didn't.
And for some reason,
the determination just came out.
It's all gonna work out.
And then the weight of winning hit me.
I'm in the final three, and this necklace
allows me to pick who's
gonna sit next to me
and who's gonna go at it in fire.
I have to think, "who can
I beat at this final three?"
So I feel like, no matter
what, it's a difficult thing.
And some people need
the money more than others.
Some people are in different situations.
- Ooh!
- It's okay.
- I'm good with whatever choice you make.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna practice all day.
This season, my
fire-making's been great.
So, tonight,
would I like an opportunity to build fire?
It's gonna be over for them.
Wow, I'm on a roller coaster of emotion.
You can do it, 'cause you are the winner.
I will not be beaten.
Is that Liz yelling?
Perfect in that challenge.
You know, I didn't go into that challenge
expecting to win.
I said that 'cause it was true.
I haven't been able to sleep.
Night terrors, panic attacks.
It's just very, very brutal.
For some reason, today, I just decided
to say, "this is it. I'm just gonna go for it."
I don't know. I had a
blast. It just came together.
Charlie, you were in it for a while,
but a couple of mistakes
cost you this challenge.
What did you reflect on this afternoon?
Today's immunity challenge is potentially.
So, Ben, you had one easy decision.
- You knew Liz, immediately.
- Yeah.
So then the debate
became Kenzie or Charlie.
Yeah. And when it
came down to Kenzie
and Charlie, I mean,
Charlie's the first friend I made out here.
I know that's not great when it comes to
talking about your strategy, but
if somebody can give
you a little bit of kindness,
it goes a long way, whether
they know it or not. And
the hard part is my
friendship with Kenzie
is very similar, except I
only met Kenzie at the merge.
But I'd say her impact
on me feeling sane
it's like, I can't... I can't oversell it.
We're gonna give it our all, baby.
It's down to the ladies tonight.
Like, it is what it is.
All right, it is time
for the final four fire-making challenge.
The winner will take the
third and final spot at our final
tribal council. Kenzie,
Liz... Take your spots.
You need to grab your torch.
Love you, Liz.
I'll love you tomorrow.
- Take your time, mama.
- No, I love you now.
God bless america.
Liz, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
- Last day.
- Wow.
Soak it all in, boys.
I will not forget these.
The sunrises?
All right, let's get into
our final tribal council.
We've been forming
the jury for many days.
We are not looking for Taylor swift lyrics.
We are not looking for pop culture
or rock and roll
references. We are looking
for serious and
thought-provoking responses.
And with that being said,
can you articulate one move
that you made on your own.
That there was a four going into six,
'cause I needed q and Maria as shields,
and if q had gone out there when Maria
won immunity at final six,
I, probably, am sitting on the jury.
Okay, well, since we're on
you, can you tell me what -yeah.
The move is that you made that
changed the course of the game?
My... the move.
That is true.
Yeah. Thank you, Liz.
But just to address
the-the accidental voting.
- Yeah.
- I know you had ate pizza, but were you
a bit lackadaisical in the
tribe, and you weren't...
You listening during tribal, and that's...
No.
I think, on top of me
having pizza in my stomach,
"This is who you shouldn't trust."
Nobody asked me what
my input was on anything.
There was no moment
where it was like, "hey,
this is what I think our
next move has to be."
- Well, that's the point.
- So, can I ask the follow-up question?
- Totally.
- Wouldn't you assert your ideas
yeah.
On the group to try to
make a move of your own?
I took my "chillin' hard"
approach, which was,
"I'm gonna listen, I'm gonna hear what
"they have to say," and using
that information is what I went
to Kenzie with, I went to Charlie with,
what I went to Liz with,
To gain q's trust back to
get back in good graces.
And that's how quick I went
from devastated crying all night,
out for blood to, "okay, I'm
back working with the guy"
"that I want out of here so
I can get him out tomorrow
if I can gain his trust today."
- Great. -Thank you.
- Excellent.
- Charlie? -Charlie?
- Concise.
So, for me, the person that
I used was actually tevin.
For me, coming into the
merge, nami was an enigma.
They're either the
best actors in the world
or there are really cracks everywhere.
Yeah.
But there was so much
information going around
because soda was telling me.
Have a similar game and
that I have a better chance
at beating them than I had beating Liz.
And I would have taken
a chance on myself.
- That's what I would have done.
- Awesome. Appreciate it.
Charlie?
Yes. So, if I had won
the necklace that day,
I think I would have done
things a little bit differently.
- Okay.
- I think I would have taken Liz.
- Soda?
- I have been on the jury the longest.
I have been listening, to a lot.
Ben, my take on you was that
you were playing an emotional game
and that you had no agency.
Also, I'll be the 30-second timer.
When I say "time," please stop.
So, I'm a social player.
I'm not the loudest voice in the room.
I'm not the one who's
gonna be a driving force,
but I am a number, and I
am also thinking strategically.
Like, my social game
is my strategic game.
They are one and the same. I know
they're supposed to be
separate, but I'm a people person.
I've had deep conversations
with each of you.
I've, like, held half of you
while you've cried
about various things. Like,
yeah, I got brought along on votes.
That's how I ended up here.
It's an initiative I've
already been a part of called
young musicians unite.
And having an artistic
expression for kids is a way
for them to feel comfortable
with who they are,
which is something I
had to learn the hard way
'cause nobody gave me that
opportunity when I was a kid.
For me and my family.
You know, part of this
experience has been
getting to meet and know all of you.
And if there's one thing I know, it's that
every single person here had something
bigger than themselves
they were playing for.
I've talked with a lot of
you about the work that I do.
I've worked a lot in immigration law.
There's a lot of
organizations that I would want
to make a donation to,
and I would also want to,
you know, bet on myself and
pay for law school with this money.
Thank you, Charlie.
- Kenzie?
- I've been
in my career since I was 15 years old,
To be 70 years old doing
bang trims on kids, okay?
Like, I'm trying
to set myself up to have a family
and to be able to be
financially secure in myself.
Yeah. I... I just love you all.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Kenzie.
- Thank you. - Ben.
Not that I think it stacks up against them,
but, with everything I've
been through in my life,
I did want to come here
and be the emotional me
and not the bravado front
man performer version of me.
And even though I had a hard time
with the night terrors,
I got from the bottom and had fun
climbing my way through
moves towards the end.
I played the game I wanted
to play, and I'm glad I got
to meet y'all, because y'all rock, and...
- Thank you.
- Who rocks?
- Thanks, Ben.
- You rock. -You rock.
Thanks, Ben.
- I'll accept that.
- Right. The one, right?
Come on. That's for you there.
Charlie, Kenzie, Ben, it's not easy to sit
in those seats and
defend your game, but