[Liz crying]
PROBST:
Liz, do you feel comfortable
talking about
what you're feeling?
I'm pissed!
PROBST:
Previously onSurvivor...
MARIA:
Q is a number that
I can use to vote with me.
I definitely want
to keep him around.
Q kind of blew up his own game
and has been causing chaos
at camp.
Tonight, I'm betting
I can keep my idol
in my pocket because
Q is going home.
-...it's gonna be
really, really bad.
-Right, but...
Kenzie is having cold feet,
but at some point,
you've got to make a move.
We can take Tiff out tonight.
Maybe we don't tell Kenzie.
If I keep waiting
for the light to turn green,
it may not turn green.
We have one chance.
So I'm gonna have
to run the red light.
TIFFANY:
I don't think
that anybody here thinks
that Q is best for their game
-at this point in time.
-And yet the last two Tribals,
everything was swirling
around Q.
"Q's going home.
Q's going home."
Nope. Still here.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Eleventh person voted out and
the fourth member of our jury:
Tiff.
The tribe has spoken.
Thank you.
[sighs]
I broke my ownSurvivor rule.
I should have played my idol.
♪ ♪
KENZIE:
Final seven.
-Final seven.
-Holy crap.
Wow.
This Tribal was
the first time
I've been left out of a vote.
And it's the worst.
It's the worst feeling ever,
because I'm like,
"What did I do
to not, like, be...
in the club?"
Like, who...
Did I...
Like, why am I not trustworthy?
Like, I'm so confused.
And I'm mad because
this was my idea
to blindside Tiff,
and now somebody else
is getting the credit.
Like, I'm mad at myself
for not seizing the opportunity.
Ugh.
I just feel so dumb.
I feel so dumb.
I was having this whimsical,
amazing time.
I just let the game
get away from me.
I got blindsided, too, you know?
I don't know if you want a hug
right now or anything. I...
-No, I...
-I don't even know.
-I just, like...
-Yeah.
Like, why wasn't I included,
you know?
-Yeah.
-Like, I know people
were probably worried
-I would tell her.
-I think that was the worry...
Which I understand completely.
I mean, I'll just say this.
-It wasn't my move.
-Yeah.
-Do you know what I mean?
-Was it Maria?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. I knew it.
CHARLIE: There's always
fallout after Tribal,
but this vote
was different because
everybody who returned
to camp voted for Tiff except
Venus and Kenzie.
And the way
they were left out left them
really feeling bitter.
So, my thinking was,
talk to Kenzie
because this game is
all about working with people,
adapting to what's
in front of you
and keeping your options open.
-It's a great move. It's-it's...
-I know.
-It's my move!
-That's why I'm so mad.
-I know.
Right now, we just have to,
like, bide our time, you know?
There's no time.
There's six days left.
-Well, it's, like...
-And I just, like...
Just, like, find
the right moment, you know?
I have to find that idol,
is what I need to do.
This is the first time
I've been wrong in the game,
but maybe
this is what I needed
to get my head back on straight
and realize
I came out here
to play and to win.
I'm just gonna have
to get a little bit more crafty,
pay a lot more attention.
I can turn this around.
-Final seven together, huh?
[laughs]
-Yes.
-We're gonna rock out, Ben.
-Oh, we're rocking out already.
We're gonna have a good time.
We can have our final five
right here.
MARIA:
Yeah, it'd be a good final five.
This Tribal couldn't have gone
any better.
Oh, my God. [laughs]
This vote was my idea,
and I was able
to get this group together--
Q, Liz, Ben,
me and Charlie--
and just pull off
an epic blindside.
And it was
just, like, the sweetest feast
I've ever had.
[laughs]
This has lit such a fire in me.
I do see the end, and I'm like,
"Is it possible
that maybe
we are the final five?"
I could do this again.
Let's do it again.
[laughs]
The blindside-- even though
we were on the wrong side of it,
was a blessing in disguise.
-Yeah.
-We got rid of big competition
-and Maria put a huge target
on her back.
-Yeah.
Let Maria think
this is her move.
Don't give off the fact
that you're upset,
and realistically, it's gonna
come and bite her in the ass.
Maria's played
a very low-key game
where everyone can tell
she's a potential threat,
but this is the first time
she really
let her freak flag fly,
and she's announcing
to the world,
like, "Hey, this is my move
and I'm here to play."
And it's scary
because Maria has a strong three
with her, Charlie and Ben.
Siga three needs
to be broken up.
Yeah.
But tomorrow's a new day,
and we're still in this game.
-Exactly.
-Yeah.
KENZIE:
Day 20.
Ugh. What a mess.
♪ ♪
-Morning.
-Good morning.
Ooh.
MARIA:
You sleep okay?
KENZIE: [short chuckle]
Oh, no, I did not.
It's all good.
I'm, like, shocked
Tiff didn't play her idol.
MARIA:
I guess that means it's time
to start looking, right?
KENZIE:
Yeah.
[mouthing]
Q: With Tiff idol leaving
in her pocket,
we're thinking it's gonna
come back to play at some point.
We don't know if there's
something out there just yet,
but the only way
to find it is to look for it.
I know.
Okay.
CHARLIE: Idol fever
has struck Nuinui beach.
MARIA: Yeah.
CHARLIE:
It was sort of
a domino effect this morning.
Q started looking,
then I started looking,
then Ben started looking,
then Venus started looking,
then Kenzie started looking,
then Maria started looking.
And everybody's looking
for... [imitates drumroll]
...Tiffany's idol!
♪ ♪
CHARLIE:
An idol at this point
of the game changes everything.
So, as much as I don't
want to look for an idol
because I'm exhausted
and starving
and want to save my energy,
it's a necessity at this point.
VENUS: At last Tribal, for the
first time ever in this game,
I was on the wrong side
of the vote.
So, I need to flip the script.
I need to find this idol
and I need to find it quick.
Q:
I've looked from the front to
the back to the top to the side.
Oh, man. I'm exhausted.
VENUS:
I've gone through
probably some
of the toughest times
that I've ever had
in my life here.
But today, the thing
that calms me down is
A: I know this island
better than anyone,
B: I know
where Randen found his,
and C:
I know where Tiffany found hers.
So I have something
to work off of,
of where to look
and where not to look.
And I'm like, "You know what?
People are going hard.
Let's go through literally
every single corner."
And I take my little stick,
and I'm pushing leaves,
and I'm pushing leaves.
And... I found it.
I found it first!
And I was so ecstatic.
I immediately started
to walk away
so that I could go find
a corner to read it.
But then I realized,
like, "Hey,
that is not the move right now."
So I U-turn it, and
everyone's still up and looking.
So, I bide my time.
And it's so hard.
MARIA: Yeah.
As someone
who's been looking for 20 days,
it's so hard to hide the joy
and excitement that is
building up in my heart.
Where's Liz?
[snoring]
I'm gonna go around the bend
and come back.
Wish me luck.
And finally, I'm alone.
"Congratulations.
"You have found
a hidden immunity idol.
"When played at Tribal Council,
"any votes cast against you
will not count.
"The last time this can be used
is when there are
five players left in the game."
I just got myself a ... idol.
Go, Venus. Go, Venus.
This is sick.
I have the idol in my hands.
And it is just
an amazing feeling.
Like, "Wow, Venus,
"you're not blind,
you're not stupid.
You actually got this."
And if I play my cards
correctly,
I make it to final four.
Like,
"Hey, you underestimated me
"since day one,
and look who's here,
and look who's not."
♪ ♪
Day 20, baby.
I know. We got
to put the sticks in.
Pretty cool.
KENZIE: Being left out
of the vote sucked,
but I have definitely, like,
thought about it, and I was
just... I got too comfy cozy.
I wasn't on my p's and q's.
I wasn't paying attention.
Trying to balance
your own individual game
with a group of individuals
that all have
their own individual games...
Everyone's lying. You never know
who's telling the truth.
You don't know
who's working with who.
Ugh.
Even though it feels like
we're on the bottom,
we're in the perfect position
of being in the middle
of this... this war.
KENZIE:
Right now, like, the only person
that hasn't lied to me
is freakin' Venus,
which is hilarious, but, like,
really, she's the only one
who hasn't lied to me.
I'm so curious
as to what her next move is
because she's not
really hiding it.
KENZIE:
I like Venus now.
I like her as a person.
I never
in a million years thought
we would be
working together, but
here we are, me and my messy,
sweet little friend.
I don't see it.
[Venus laughs]
KENZIE:
Venus is just, like,
looking at trees,
and is like, "It's not here."
And I'm like,
"You have to move some leaves,
honeybun.
Like, what are you doing?"
It's not looking good.
KENZIE:
Venus' technique
for idol-searching, I think,
is to follow around people
that are idol-searching
and wait for them to find it.
[laughs]
Girlfriend is not
really looking hard.
She's, like, kind of does this
with a stick, and she's like,
"No." And meanwhile, I'm, like,
digging holes, and she's like...
Any luck?
[laughing]:
I'm like,
"Venus, what?
What are you doing?"
I doubt it.
KENZIE:
Who knows? Maybe she has it,
and she's bamboozling us all.
But... I think
she's just waiting
for someone
that's close to her to find it
so she can have the tea.
VENUS:
It is so relieving to know
that even though people are
still scattering about,
looking for an idol,
I don't have to worry
about going out
and, like,
solving a riddle, or, like,
going and finding a second part
to this idol. I have it.
But no one will
ever catch a whiff
of me having this because
I don't see any benefit
in-in someone knowing
that I have this power.
Oh, my God. I know.
I cannot believe it.
VENUS:
So it's very much a timing game.
Like, when is the right time
to play this?
No, she shouldn't.
-People were just
really good at lying.
-Yeah.
So, it's stressful,
but it's so comforting.
It's, like,
the sweet, sweet comfort.
Like, I want to... Mwah.
I love you.
It's, like,
I think this is my best friend
on this island right now.
Hello.
What's going on?
Okay.
-We have lots to go through.
-Yeah.
First of all, congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm happy to have had my moment.
-We have not... even talked.
-That was, like, amazing.
-That was amazing.
-Yes.
I'm so glad
to have been a part of it.
-I'm really proud of you.
-Thank you.
-That was... that was...
-It was scary as hell.
-That's big stuff
that you pulled off last night.
-Yeah.
-That was big stuff.
-I know
what the repercussions are,
-but, like...
-Yeah.
Thank you
for doing that with me.
Oh, my God. Of course, you know?
Maria wanted the Tiff vote
to be something that she drove,
she controlled, 100%,
because the more
you can clearly claim
that a move was your own,
the easier it is
to sell and to pitch
to a jury
that's looking for a player
who had real influence
in the game.
And that's where
Maria's head is at.
But it's also
a very double-edged sword,
because Maria getting all the
credit from the Tiff blindside
has made her
a huge, huge target.
I mean, people would be silly
if they didn't see
that, like, you and I
have been working together.
You're a threat.
We voted cor...
voted correctly every time.
-Every single time.
-Taken out three people.
-You're a threat, I'm a threat.
-Yeah.
-I did want to talk
to you about Q.
-Okay.
What are you...
Where's your head at on him?
I think we can use Q
for one more vote,
-because Q trusts me,
and I trust Q.
-Yeah.
-I don't know how that happened.
Like, I do think
he would vote with us
-for one more time.
-Yeah.
I've been playing this game
with Maria since day one,
and we have been lockstep.
We've been talking about going
to the final three together.
But Q is,
as far as I can tell,
in Maria's pocket,
and I want him out of the game.
So this move
and the buildup to this move
is really where...
I have seen my thinking
and my route to the end
maybe start to diverge
from Maria's.
I know.
Yeah.
Luckily, people have realized
Maria is a huge threat.
Nobody likes Q, so he's kind of
on the outs as well.
So the two big threats--
Q and Maria--
have made themselves
very well-known.
They are peacocking, for sure.
Like, everyone can see that
their tail feathers are out,
and that the attention's
on them.
Maria-- she got to go.
I thought she was just...
a sleeper.
-But Charlie, yesterday,
came to me, he was like...
-Yeah.
"That was a game-winning move,
and it wasn't mine."
-And I was like...
-Okay.
"Well, there's hope."
I mean, I want Q out, but...
Maria is obviously
running things.
-Yeah.
-What do you think?
Oh, I think it makes sense.
-If we can pull it off,
then Maria's got to go.
-Okay.
KENZIE:
There's seven of us left,
and we need four.
So the best thing for me is to
figure out who I can work with
to get Maria and Q out of here,
and then at the final five,
we can battle it out from there.
Kenzie, have you
checked the beach?
I'm gonna be honest.
If Q doesn't get up and look
for it again, I'm gonna assume
-he has it.
-Okay.
And Maria's been gone alone
for a long time.
LIZ:
That's what we're talking about.
-Yeah, that's what
we've been talking about.
-VENUS: Okay.
And she will think again
next time
before leaving us out of a vote.
It's not about that.
It's about...
-she's the kingpin.
-She's...
She's the kingpin, she...
She's got the best story,
the best moves.
Yeah. No, she's got to go.
VENUS:
We will have the majority.
A hundred percent.
I am certain one
of the Siga three may be open
to potentially working with us,
especially with Charlie.
I've questioned
how strategic he is,
how cutthroat he can be,
but it seems like he's seeing
that writing on the wall
and realizes
that he can't go to the end
with Maria no matter what.
And eventually, he's gonna
have to cut that cord, and
I hope he sees
that now's the time,
while everyone's still on board.
KENZIE:
Okay, so what are you thinking?
CHARLIE:
I think
Q is in Maria's pocket.
Oh, 1,000%, he is.
-Yeah?
-It's not even a pocket anymore.
It's like she has, like, a...
a full bank vault
that Q is stuck inside.
KENZIE:
Yeah.
CHARLIE:
I was not...
I was not cruise director...
-Yeah.
-last night, you know?
-KENZIE: Ugh.
-So...
-VENUS: That's so funny.
CHARLIE:
In the buildup
to the Tiff vote,
I wanted Maria
to have sole credit
because I need someone
that I can sell as
the biggest target in the game.
If that can overshadow
any attention on me
for the moment,
that's probably what's best
for my game right now.
At this point in the game,
-there's seven people.
-Mm-hmm.
And that has somehow
become the strongest pair.
The whole stuff with Q
and that whole vote
was a big...
-I think, a big wake-up call
for probably everyone.
-Yeah.
Charlie and Maria
are super close.
They're in the Siga alliance.
But Charlie has no real
résumé moves, and he knows it.
He has been
Maria's, like, jester
for this whole game.
And he's-he's a smart kid,
he knows that.
So I think Charlie's ready
to make a move on Maria.
So, who would you rather
go first?
Too early to say or...
I think too early to say, but...
We'll just see whoever wins
and go from there.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, 'cause, like,
I feel like anyone could win.
I've been building trust
and relationships with Kenzie
and Venus so that I could,
if I wanted to,
make a move
against Maria and Q
at any point.
I think we... we all know
what needs to be done,
or else we're all screwed.
VENUS: They will win.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
So they are, like, public enemy
number one and two right now.
CHARLIE:
At some point,
I have to ask myself,
"Is going to the final three
with Maria
handing Maria
a million dollars?"
You have to start
thinking about your own game.
And I'm feeling...
my gut start to go
in two directions.
One way is gonna win,
and it might be
making a move against Maria.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
I like it.
KENZIE:
Hi, hi.
You look hungry
for battle today.
-Good morning.
-We're just hungry.
-PROBST:
Yeah, you just look hungry.
-Just hungry.
PROBST:
Look at this.
-How many are left?
-[whooping]
-The final several.
-Several.
Several!
Long live Jelinsky.
-[laughing]
-PROBST: All right.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-[all voicing assent]
-Charlie,
second time,
got to take it back.
Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna balance
a ball on a pole
while navigating
a series of obstacles.
Once you're past the first
obstacle, you're gonna add
more sections of pole,
making it more difficult.
When you get to the finish,
you're then gonna maneuver
that ball through
a winding snake track.
First player to get one ball
in both of their targets
wins immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal,
guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
-Ooh.
-You're also playing for reward.
-Yes.
-Oh, baby.
-Yay!
PROBST: Want to know
what you're playing for?
-[all voicing assent]
-Pizza delivery!
-Oh, my gosh!
-[whooping]
Delivered to your camp
just like you were home.
-Oh, my God.
-PROBST: Pepperoni.
-Oh. Oh.
-PROBST: Hawaiian.
Vegetarian.
And gluten-free.
-Oh!
-Gluten-free. Liz!
-PROBST: Plus soda.
-Yeah! I'm fighting today.
-PROBST: Worth playing for?
[all voicing assent]
We'll draw for spots,
we'll get started.
-Let's do it.
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Got to keep that ball
balanced on your pole.
If you drop,
like Q did and Charlie did,
just got to start over.
Kenzie's got to go back.
When you get to the center
section, you're going under--
that's how you do it, Ben--
but the pole goes over.
Here goes Maria.
Ben is through first.
Maria doing a nice job.
She's through.
Venus is through.
Here comes Charlie. He's good.
Kenzie got one big last step.
-You're good, Kenzie.
-[laughs]
PROBST:
Here comes Q.
There goes Liz.
Ben has added
his extra sections of pole.
Venus has hers.
Here comes Maria.
Keep your hand under the hilt.
There goes Charlie.
He's going
onto the second section.
-Kenzie has
her additional section.
-Aah!
PROBST:
Ben drops. He's got to go back.
Charlie really whipping
through this.
Here comes Maria.
-Good job, Charlie.
-Charlie's won back-to-back.
No way.
Charlie, you're good.
Start working on that track.
Charlie's at the final stage now
with a big lead.
Ben has to go back.
Here comes Kenzie.
-Ouch.
-PROBST: Maria drops
and hits herself.
Maria's got to go back.
Charlie working
on that snake track now.
You've got two balls
you're gonna have to drop
one at a time.
-[sighs]
-PROBST: Kenzie,
the last,
most difficult section--
getting down off that beam
without dropping the ball.
You're good, Kenzie!
-[whoops]
-Kenzie moving on
to the snake track.
-LIZ: Okay.
-PROBST: We got two
on the track,
five still working to get here.
-Aah! Come on.
-PROBST: Q drops.
Got to go back.
-LIZ: Ugh!
-Liz drops.
She's got to start again.
-Aah!
-Venus drops, almost at the end.
She's got
to go all the way back.
There is a learning curve.
You're gonna drop
a lot on that snake track.
The goal is to get better at it
and start
to figure out that touch.
Once you do, it will get easier.
Liz, Maria,
the final section of the beam.
Maria, you're good. Move on.
Liz, very close.
Liz, you're good. Move on.
Booyah.
Good job, Liz.
Venus, another shot.
Again, very close.
No, Venus! It dropped.
You did not cross. Sorry.
You got to go back.
You got to be in control
of that ball.
Q very close, few steps away.
You're good, Q!
Q now on the snake track.
Maria now has some momentum.
She's about a third of the way
through the snake track,
moving very slowly, confidently.
Q trying to figure it out.
Liz continues
to drop out of the start.
[groans]
Trouble just
getting that ball to sit.
-Venus giving it another go.
-Aah!
No. Falls short.
Ben struggling.
"Struggling"
is an understatement.
Maria very close.
Maria drops her first ball
in the first target.
Maria now in the lead,
working on that second ball.
You got to untie it first.
Maria with a big lead now.
Can anybody catch her
and get their first ball,
make this a challenge?
Here comes Venus again.
Is this the time?
-You're good, Venus.
-Thank God.
PROBST:
Ben has some movement
like he just figured it out.
You're good, Ben.
That's how you do it!
-Let's go!
-PROBST: Ben's now in it.
There's Maria working
on her second and final ball.
She landed her first.
Nobody else has.
Venus doing a nice job,
down in green.
She just made up a lot of time.
Getting closer and closer
to that first target.
Charlie making a move
for that first target.
He'd like to be in this.
Aw, damn.
PROBST:
Maria drops.
Maria has to go back.
The door is open for somebody
to drop that first ball.
Venus has her first ball.
Venus is now in it.
Look at that.
LIZ:
Good job, V.
PROBST:
Charlie drops his first.
Charlie's in it now.
It is now Maria with one,
Charlie with one,
Venus with one.
Q getting closer
to that first target.
Q drops his first ball!
Q's in it now.
Liz drops her first ball.
She's in it.
There's Kenzie. Can she drop?
-[whoops] Here we go.
-Kenzie drops. She's in it.
[laughs]
-I got it in.
-Ben drops his first.
-KENZIE: Yay!
-Ben's in it now.
-KENZIE: You're in it.
PROBST:
Everybody now working
on their second ball.
This is a challenge
that is as wide open as it gets.
Maria very close to the end.
Venus just behind.
Right now,
it's Maria and Venus.
Maria-- can she do it?
-No. Maria drops
-Oh!
six inches from the end.
Got to start again.
Venus getting closer.
-No!
-PROBST: Venus drops.
We are wide open again!
We got a challenge.
-There's another one.
-Any one of the seven can win.
Question is who will it be?
Who's gonna be wearing
that necklace tonight?
'Cause you're earning it
right now.
Aah!
-[groans]
-Aah!
Oh, my God.
[groans]
PROBST:
Venus, again,
with a shot to win it.
-No. No! Aah!
-PROBST: No.
This time, Venus drops again.
So does Maria.
And it's now Q in the lead.
-Come on!
-PROBST: Q drops!
Open again.
Look at that-- day 21,
everybody with a shot at it.
Oh.
PROBST:
Who's gonna grab it?
Who wants that necklace?
Me.
PROBST:
Venus in that same section,
last bit of track.
Maria right on her tail.
But it is Venus
in the lead right now.
Is this the round?
Is this where somebody
closes it out,
claims their victory
for this challenge,
guarantees themself
a spot at six?
Slightest wrong move,
and that ball falls.
Venus inching closer.
Maria catching her.
Venus-- can she do it?
For the win,
individual immunity,
just has to drop it in that net.
-No! No!
-PROBST: And she doesn't!
-LIZ: Wow.
-She couldn't get it
in the target.
-What?!
-PROBST: Wow!
-So close.
-LIZ: V!
-No!
-PROBST: Maria at the same spot
Venus was.
Can she drop it for the win?
-Aah!
-And she does!
Maria pulls it out.
Oh, my God.
PROBST:
Her second individual
immunity win,
guaranteed a spot at six
and pizza delivered to camp
-on day 21. Wow.
-LIZ: Good job, sister.
-Maria!
-PROBST: Nice job, everybody.
-BEN: Congrats, Maria.
-LIZ: Nice job, sister.
[Ben whoops]
Maria, come on over.
[whooping]
Way to go, Mama.
-Well done.
-BEN: Yeah!
For the second time this season,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final six.
-[whooping]
-PROBST: You're going
to have a fun afternoon
with pizza
being delivered for you.
Choose one person to join you.
Walk me through the thought
process of strategy, compassion.
You're also fueling
your competition.
-There's a lot going on.
I mean, Liz has been
eating some rice.
She's been sharing with Venus.
Ben's been falling apart.
He's completely depleted.
Q took me
on the reward last time,
and so I feel
like I need to take him.
And so there's, you know...
Charlie didn't go on the reward.
It's a really hard decision.
How many people do I get?
We'll find out.
Right now, you got one.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna pick Ben.
PROBST:
Come on over, Ben.
CHARLIE:
You go get it, buddy.
[sniffles]
[crying]
This is crazy.
PROBST:
All right,
there are five people left.
You're gonna bring
one more person with you.
Which means three of you
will have pizza,
four will not.
Walk me through
who you're gonna choose.
Um, for me, it's more,
like, my mindset is more like
who is physically falling apart
right now, and it's not
about competition or who I want
to work with or whatever.
It's just whose body is failing.
I'll take myself
out of it, Maria.
I think there are people here
that need the food more than me.
All right, Venus,
Liz and Q, make your case.
Um, I've lost weight.
I would like to eat,
but it's your decision.
I want you to pick
whoever you want, you know?
I mean, I still
haven't pooped in three weeks,
so I'd like
something to get moving.
You know, I ain't too proud
to beg. [laughs]
Love that song.
I think whatever decision
you make
is completely fine, Maria.
You shouldn't-you shouldn't
feel guilty, either way.
♪ ♪
I've never seen
a moment like this, ever.
-46 seasons.
It has never taken this long.
-[laughs]
PROBST:
Nobody's given this much
thought. That's not a criticism.
That's just an observation.
Okay.
Liz and Q, rock paper scissors.
Pick rock. [laughs]
Paper covers rock. Is that it?
-Yep.
-Q, come on over.
-KENZIE: Wow.
[quietly]: Wow.
PROBST:
We don't need
to belabor this anymore.
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody will be the 12th person
voted out of this game,
become the fifth member
of our jury.
You're gonna go back to camp.
Maria, Ben and Q,
you're gonna have
an afternoon with pizza.
The other four, got nothing for
you. Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
KENZIE:
I am shocked.
Maria is like,
"Liz and Q,
play rock paper scissors."
What?
Liz has made it
very abundantly clear
that she's starving.
If you just want to take Q
because he's your number one,
just say that.
Don't be like, "Oh, I want
to take care of the people
who haven't eaten," and
then take the guy who just ate.
Makes no sense.
My jaw, I'm still picking
it up off the floor.
Survivoris still going strong
in its third decade
because of the people
who apply to play.
If this adventure
sounds fun to you,
I'd love to see you
out on the island.
♪ ♪
-MARIA: Oh, yeah.
-Oh, wow.
BEN:
Whoa.
MARIA:
Look at that.
Oh, man.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
-Honestly, I am in shock.
-LIZ: Correct. Correct.
When she said,
"Venus, make your case,"
I'm like,
"I'm sorry. I'm not gonna beg.
You know, physically,
where I'm at."
CHARLIE:
Uh, when she said,
"Rock paper scissors,"
I was like, "Oh,
it's gonna be Liz and Venus."
-Me, too.
-And I was like, "Liz and who?"
I knew it was gonna be Q.
KENZIE:
I cannot believe she said,
"I'm just trying
to judge it
on whose body's breaking down."
-I know. And then...
-Can I just say,
I would have respected her
so much more if she just
picked who she picked, but
the fact that she prefaced it
-by saying that and
then picked the most well-fed,
-KENZIE: I know.
-buffest guy.
He's been to, like,
three rewards now.
-He just finished his Applebee's
feast, like a day ago.
-VENUS: Yeah. Literally.
He hasn't even digested it yet.
It's still in his stomach.
CHARLIE: The pizza picking was
a bit of a...
for lack of a better word,
a ... show.
I thought, for sure,
Maria was gonna choose Venus
or Liz, but Q ends up going.
And let me tell you,
the four pizza losers
were pissed.
-KENZIE: What the ...
-VENUS: She went from being
a hero to a villain real quick.
To emphasize being this,
like, mother to all,
caring about everyone.
I'm so done, like, being quiet
when someone ticks me off.
So, what are we
doing tonight-- Q?
He's evil and self-centered
and selfish.
-My God.
-I know it's a game,
but, like, geez.
The veil has been lifted.
I had a feeling Maria and Q
were working together,
but now it's just blatantly
freaking obvious,
and I cannot respect anybody
who is playing the game
with that jerk.
-I mean, did you know
they were so close?
-CHARLIE: I...
As far as I'm concerned,
Q's Maria's number one.
-That's...
-Q's an idiot.
-[groans]
-It's the classic Survivor
"If you can't
go for your target,
go for their number one."
I was just piling everything on.
"Maria's the worst.
"They're such a tight duo.
I can't believe
she's working with him."
But since Maria has the necklace
tonight, the pizza losers
want to vote out Q.
Which is great,
because Q is someone
that I want out of the game,
and I want him out soon.
Okay, so, we don't think
Q has an idol?
-Definitely not.
-CHARLIE: Uh...
I am 97% sure.
Charlie, thanks
for listening to me vent.
-Oh.
-I know you and Maria are close.
-I'm in my feelings right now.
-We are,
-but, I mean...
-VENUS: That's different.
That's game versus...
Things have been turning
a different corner, you know?
BEN: Damn right.
-I slowed down.
-I just want to say
thank you so much.
You're so welcome, Ben.
If a look could kill...
...I got slaughtered today.
[Ben chuckles]
MARIA:
Liz pierced me with her eyes.
BEN:
Mm-hmm.
MARIA: I was gonna
be damned either way.
Yeah.
Yo, Liz does have rice.
MARIA:
That's what I'm saying.
That's why I was like,
well, what's, you know?
-Yeah.
-Kenzie just ate.
Charlie's like, "Don't take me."
-Yeah.
-So I'm like,
"Well, that's the right move."
-Q: Mm-hmm.
-BEN: A hundred percent.
MARIA:
I'm sure I pissed people off,
but winning this challenge
gives me peace of mind.
It means that I am safe tonight,
and that gives me
a lot of power.
At this point, there
are still three Siga members.
So with seven people left--
although it's
a very unpopular opinion--
I got to keep Q happy right now.
Q is a number for me.
He trusts me, and I trust him.
They know you two are tight.
-It's a little obvious
at this point.
-Yeah.
And they know
you and Charlie are day-ones.
MARIA:
The three of us.
Exactly.
-That's all we need.
Really.
Yeah.
-Q: Is that ham?
-Yeah.
-I think it's ham.
-It's ham.
Q:
I shouldn't have
went on that reward.
I just ate a couple days ago,
a big meal, and now
I just ate
about 23 slices of pizza.
[laughs]
It ain't fair.
But I don't feel guilty
at all, because
I get to now make sure
that I'm not going home tonight.
I say Siga three, plus me,
-take out Venus first, because
-MARIA: Yeah. Yeah.
Liz is less likely
to win immunity than Venus.
-BEN: Yeah.
-MARIA: Right, right.
-Yeah.
-Venus came super close today.
-I know. I thought she had it.
-But...
MARIA:
I say it's time to get her out.
Q:
Venus is the real problem
with all the complaining,
and the pushy and the running
and telling
this story to this person.
And, also, she has the greatest
shot at winning immunity,
as we saw in this challenge.
She is a problem.
So she needs to go.
The negative vibes
have been a bit much.
MARIA:
Yeah.
Any chance Venus found the idol?
No.
MARIA:
It's time to get her out.
I'm ready.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
KENZIE:
Well, well, well.
-Pizza people.
-Look who it is.
LIZ:
Ben, feeling better?
Did you get a slice down?
-Yes.
-I got-I got a slice down.
-What was the best flavor?
-LIZ: That was so fast.
I feel like a Ninja Turtle
right now.
-Dude.
-I'm not gonna undersell it.
CHARLIE:
The pizza winners
come back to camp,
and we do our classic niceties.
"How much did you eat?
Was it delicious?
Oh, tell us all about it.
I'm so glad."
Even though,
seconds before they arrived,
man, I thought that the people
at camp were gonna eat them.
It was tense.
I'm happy with Maria's
choices for me, but
it really put the heat
on her and Q.
I know they probably been
pitching me this whole time.
-Yep.
-Just got to let them know
-that's not happening, so
they don't write my name down.
-Okay. Yep.
-In case V pulls out
an idol, but...
-Okay.
the real plan is Venus.
Okay. Okay.
At this point in the game,
I want the burners turned up
on everyone but me.
So if I can hide this vote
when I don't have the necklace,
and all of a sudden, everyone's
eyes are on Q and Maria,
this is great.
I mean, I did. I just...
I feel really bad,
and I'm not really sure
how to talk about it.
Honestly, Maria,
it was really weird.
-We were all like, "Wow."
-MARIA: I know.
There's no way
to win that situation.
And I told myself,
"I never want to win reward
because I don't want
to have to make that choice."
And I knew I was gonna
piss people off and I just,
I apologize
if I hurt anybody's feelings.
There was just,
there was no way to make
everyone happy in that choice.
Oh, I completely
agree with that.
I just can't stand Q,
and I just
don't know why you would
want to make him happy.
'Cause he's
such an ass to everyone.
He does nothing around camp.
He used all the firewood in,
like, two hours.
I'm done not expressing myself.
MARIA:
Okay. Yeah, go for it.
LIZ:
That is my mindset, Maria.
I guess that's what
I've learned in Survivor,
is, like,
I've spent my whole life
just letting myself be angry
and not
speaking what I'm really feeling
for the sake
of someone else's feelings.
And I think, honestly--
this sounds crazy--
I think that's why
I have so many ... allergies,
because
I've suppressed my own self
for so long
that my body
started attacking things.
So I've said my piece.
I feel better.
Thank you for hearing me.
Normally, I'm not someone
who holds grudges,
but with Q, it just feels
a little more personal.
For some reason,
he just keeps surviving.
And I'm getting more
and more and more and more
and more and more irritated.
MARIA:
I felt
like I hurt you,
and I didn't like how that felt.
I was just shocked about Q,
because I'm like, "He's a jerk."
-So...
-The thing is, Liz,
is that, like,
the only people
that are talking to me are
Siga people and Q.
That's it.
-You know?
-I feel like the only person
talking to me is Venus.
And I don't believe
anything she says.
She's so all over the place.
MARIA:
Well, that's another reason
why I can't work with her.
I can't understand
her game at all.
Ditto.
And so I guess
that's why I come to you,
because it's like...
I liked working with you
for Tevin.
for Tiff.
I like the fact that you said,
"I'm here to play the game.
I want to play the game."
But, like, let's play the game.
Right now,
having not had a chance
to talk to everybody,
it seems like
the ladies want Q out,
and Q, Ben and I have
discussed getting Venus out.
And so,
Venus and Q are
gonna be the targets tonight.
It's my hope
that Venus goes home,
but, you know, you never know.
Like, as the sun starts
to go down,
sometimes things change
and people scramble,
and then a new plan comes out.
In my mind, the people
I'm working with are solid,
but I guess that's
a silly assumption.
♪ ♪
Yeah, I know. I'm, like...
-I know. I know.
-Okay.
Are you and Ben doing Q?
I don't know about Ben.
KENZIE:
Well, Ben can do
whatever Ben wants, but, like,
-if you're gonna write Q,
we're good.
-Yeah. It doesn't matter.
Yeah, exactly.
If an idol comes into play
at six, and Q gets it
and Maria wins immunity,
then we're screwed.
-Yeah.
-Like, we'd be so dumb
to not get rid of him
-right now.
-Yeah, I know.
-We've got to do Q.
-I know.
I don't think Q's a bad person.
I don't think Q's evil, but...
I'm fine with
other people thinking that,
because, ultimately,
down the line, I want
a final four that doesn't
have Q or Maria in it.
What is your ideal final four?
-Final four?
-Yeah.
'Cause, frankly,
we got to think about it.
I've been thinking about that.
'Cause a four at six
controls the vote.
VENUS:
Charlie's in a power position.
He's kingpin right now.
And based off
of discussions from today
and previous to today,
just based off
of my relationship
with Charlie as a whole,
I think that
Charlie really understands
trust goes both ways.
And if he
sticks to the Q vote tonight,
I'm gonna give him
something in return next time.
Can I tell you,
I've got your back.
-And I've got...
-I've got yours, too.
I've got
some things up my sleeve.
-I feel like we'll be fine.
-What does that mean?
You don't have
to worry about it now,
-but I feel like in terms of...
-I am worried about it.
No, you don't
have to worry about it.
I'm saying us,
final four, is locked in.
For tonight's vote,
sure, I have an easy out.
I can just play my idol.
"Oh, there's a risk of me
going home. I can play it."
But that's not what
wins the game for you.
It's about using it correctly
or not using it at all
because your social game
is that good. And so,
even though
I have a guaranteed way
of going into
tonight's Tribal stress-free,
I don't even care.
I don't want to use it because,
for me, if I get this correct
and I get to save the idol
for another vote,
then that just
speaks to more of why
I deserve to win this game
in the end.
We'll make it to final four.
No.
Okay. That's why I was...
That seemed like
things up your sleeve.
Or maybe I do. [gasps]
-Who knows? No, I don't. But...
-Oh, Venus.
We-we will be close
after this vote.
Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
Venus alluded to someone--
maybe her--
having something
up their sleeve,
as an advantage
or some sort of extra spice
that could
shake things up around here.
And I was trying to get Venus
to tell me what the heck it was,
but she kept being
very cagey about it.
In terms of idol,
I really don't think Q has it.
I don't think anyone has it,
unless you do.
-Unless it's up your sleeve.
-No. [chuckles] No, no, no.
-There's something else
up my sleeve.
-You're being all shifty.
-No, I...
-What else is up your sleeve?
There's something else
that's going on
that I'll tell you about later,
but it's not an idol.
And that's why I'm so adamant to
find this idol, too, by the way.
Yeah. I'm curious why
you're not telling me now.
-Because I want Q out for sure.
-Okay.
And as soon as Q is out,
we can have an open discussion
-Yeah.
-about everything that will
guarantee us final four.
-Okay. All right. No, no.
-And that's like, that's like...
-I trust you. I trust you.
-Handshake.
No, handshake promise.
-I trust you.
-Okay.
CHARLIE:
I'm trying to set up
a final four deal
with Venus, and she's
stonewalling me on
something incredibly important.
That, to me, is a red flag.
So I've just got to think
about how to play this in a way
that it doesn't sink my game.
V talked to me,
and she was like,
"I'm totally cool going
to the final four with you
-and Ben and one other."
-Of course.
-'Cause she's a poser.
-Yeah.
The other thing that V said
is that she alluded to some
advantage that somebody has.
So it would either be her,
Liz or Kenzie who has it.
BEN:
She's saying whatever
she can to get out of tonight.
"I want to get Q out."
-Yeah.
-V has got to go.
Q is a heavy target
we got to get out of the game,
but at the same time,
Venus also does have to go.
My reason for Venus
having to go has nothing to do
with her being a threat.
She's just creating more
and more chaos.
She freaks out
before every Tribal,
and she's always running around
trying to pitch some crazy plan,
and I'm sick
of being around that.
So I'd rather get her out first
before we get out anybody else.
CHARLIE:
My head is going
in 22 different directions.
It's being
pulled every which way,
and I just have
to hope that I can figure out
what's best for my game.
But right now,
it's a big old storm cloud.
KENZIE: Okay.
CHARLIE:
...and they're gonna play it.
-Venus is chaos. I don't
want Venus here, either...
-Yeah.
I trust what you want to do.
Okay.
So whatever-whatever...
KENZIE:
I think that
the boys are being babies
and don't want
to make a big move
because they want
to feel secure.
Because if they get rid of Q,
then they're more vulnerable.
But I'm like,
"If I get rid of Venus,
then I'm more vulnerable."
I just think it's foolish
to not take out
the biggest threat in the game
while they're vulnerable.
CHARLIE:
The middle is a safe place
to be and a dangerous
place to be.
It's a double-edged sword
and, frankly,
it's a sword that has
a point also pointing at you.
-I know.
I didn't know where you were.
-I was like...
Even though
I might have power tonight,
I could make a mistake that
sinks my game moving forward.
So it's Venus, right?
Is that what you're hearing?
Yeah.
The way people are
talking about Q and Maria,
working with them
could taint my image.
Right now, I know
I'm a little bit of a threat,
but people are not mad at me.
After tonight's vote,
my main concern is
can I pull people
that I've burned
back into a position
that benefits me?
And I don't know
if I can do that
if I burn people
who are so dead set
on getting Q out tonight.
It might be the last straw,
and I might be
public enemy number one
for stringing them along.
So it's really, really tricky
where I am right now.
♪ ♪
BEN:
What up, Jeff?
What up, Ben?
Somebody had some pizza.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
All right. So I brought popcorn
a couple of Tribals ago because
I was expecting something fun,
so I did bring the cushion.
MARIA:
All right.
And tonight,
I didn't have popcorn,
so I brought some licorice.
-Damn!
-[others exclaiming]
Oh.
So I am really...
LIZ:
Oh, my God.
-...ready to go tonight.
-[laughing]
-VENUS: Jeff...
-BEN: Jeff, that's foul.
PROBST:
But look, I can't
give you the whole thing
because people go,
"What has happened to Probst?
He's giving them food."
But I don't want
to be a bad host.
I really like licorice when I'm
watching my favorite show, so...
I'll give you one.
-You got to figure out
what you do with it.
-[groaning]
-This is Survivor.
-VENUS: Oh, my God. Cool.
BEN: Of course
you put me on the spot.
I'm breaking it even. Let's go.
-Everybody gets a piece.
-VENUS: No.
-Thank you.
-KENZIE: Thank you.
All right.
-CHARLIE: A new taste
that's not coconut.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-CHARLIE: That's pretty good.
I can eat licorice.
KENZIE:
Yeah. Thank you.
All right, so, let's start
with one of
the craziest challenges.
At any given point, any one
of you could have won it.
Maria, you win,
and you get to bring two people.
It's the longest time
we've ever spent
deciding who to bring.
So how did that go?
The first decision
for me was really easy,
but then you have
to start weighing, like,
am I fueling my competition?
Am I fueling my alliance?
Am I feeding people
who are malnourished?
Like, how do I
make this decision?
And I had to give Q a chance
and I wanted
to give Liz a chance.
And I said,
"Let's rock paper scissors,
'cause I can't
make this choice."
Venus, you were clearly upset
that you weren't chosen.
VENUS:
It's one thing to decide
who you're gonna
take with on a reward,
but to start off by saying,
"You know,
I really want to choose someone
"who is physically weak
and really needs
this reward, health-wise,"
and then put on this farce
to ultimately choose the most
well-fed, fittest guy here--
it kind of felt like
a punch in the gut.
-It kind of felt cruel,
you know?
-An act and a farce is...
that's, to me, like daggers.
That was the hardest decision
I had to make today.
So if she
can stand there and say,
"That was an act and that was
a farce," I'd love for her
to take that spot
and make the decision herself.
I wouldn't
have prefaced the decision
with that kind of comment.
I would have just
made my decision and just
been content with it.
But, Jeff, if Venus
would have won the reward,
she wouldn't have taken...
-No way. [laughs] No way.
-Q: ...uh, Maria.
She wouldn't have taken me.
You know what I'm saying?
-We'll never know.
-Q: So...
Uh, we know.
-Trust me. Okay.
-We don't know.
You can't sit there and say,
"Well, Venus
never would have picked me,"
'cause you don't know.
So...
You wouldn't have.
And that's a fact.
Wow.
Charlie, what's your take?
CHARLIE:
So, I think the big theme
of this pizza reward
is really "decisions."
And no decision in Survivor
weighs as much as
who we are voting out
at any given Tribal Council.
So, you're thinking about
who are you putting on the jury?
Who are you leaving in the game
to work with you?
And at this point in the game,
who am I going to sit next to
at the end and have
the jury judge me against?
Everything has consequences,
and it makes this game just
incredibly, incredibly hard.
PROBST:
Kenzie, let's
talk about blindsides.
When you're the architect
of a blindside, it's great.
And yet you can't tell people
because there are idols,
there are advantages.
Tonight's the last night
you can use Shot in the Dark.
Does that get
more and more pressurized
as the days
get closer to the end?
It's extremely pressurized.
I mean, I got bamboozled
by a blindside last time,
and it wasn't even me.
So when it's getting down
to just seven, and everybody's
telling you all these
different things, it's, like,
so layered and weighted,
and you just have to put
your faith in these people who
have literally blindsided you,
even if it's not
your name written down.
It's very jarring.
Liz, it's really interesting
to hear Kenzie say that.
That you get blindsided,
and then you might
actually have to work
with the people who lied to you.
Amen.
I've been incredibly vocal.
[laughs]
I don't know how else to say it.
And I'm just...
About what?
[groans]
-Okay, one more time.
One more time.
-LIZ: Sure.
[groans]
[sputters]
-I'm just feeling...
-Okay. You've been
very vocal about what?
About Q.
I mean,
come on.
I-I feel like I...
[groans] Like...
Everybody's talking about,
"Oh, I want to make a big move.
Let's blindside.
Let's do this."
I feel like I can't
trust anyone right now.
It's like...
Yeah, the-the Q and Liz
rock paper scissors.
And it was like,
okay, in my head,
Maria wants to play
with Q more than I thought.
I don't know.
It's... bleh.
PROBST:
Q, did you hear your name
in the same way you have
for the past few Tribals?
Q:
Oh, yeah. I heard my name today.
But, again, Jeff,
I approach the situation
the same every time.
You tell me something.
I tell you something. We agree.
If I believe it,
I'm going on about my way.
If it's a lie, you will
put my fire out tonight.
That's how I go.
I'm not gonna worry about it.
But, you know, with the people
that I've talked to,
it seem like everybody's
on the same page.
I don't know
if that page is my page
or someone else's page.
I guess we'll find out.
Venus, how would
you describe camp today?
Today was a bit different,
because up until the last vote,
I've been in on what was
gonna happen, and like Kenzie,
I was on the wrong side
of the vote for Tiff.
So, although I felt like
I could trust everyone before,
now it's like I don't know
who's telling me the truth,
who's lying, which way
the vote's gonna go.
'Cause people just
love writing my name down.
Oh, my name is out there,
as well, Jeff.
But to be fair, everybody here
knows to never, ever, ever,
-ever, ever, ever, ever
-VENUS: And yet he did.
-say a name in front of Venus.
-And yet he did.
Why is that, Q?
Why do you think...
Because what Venus will do is
she'll come
up to you aggressively.
-Never.
-"What do you want to do?"
You tell her a name,
this is what she's gonna do.
-Run and tell this person.
-Straight-up...
"Oh, Liz said this."
This person.
-"Q said this." This person...
-With Q, specifically, Jeff,
-I made sure
not to talk strategy.
-No one talks game with her.
-I'm done talking about it.
-VENUS: I would never
in a million years
try and talk strategy
with this man voluntarily.
And that's a fact.
And last vote
proved that exactly,
-with what happened to Tiff.
-Q: That's why
you didn't
know about the last vote.
'Cause they didn't trust you.
Mm-hmm, but I knew
about the previous three,
and you didn't, so...
-Ooh.
-[exclaims]
-PROBST: Ben...
-[chuckles]
...every Tribal,
while entertaining,
has been complicated.
I don't think I've seen
the cynicism and paranoia
be played up to 11
the way it's been
the last few days.
This is a prime example
that some people are just
not gonna be on the same page.
It's about making
it through the next vote,
because one crew that will
do one vote together
is probably
not gonna be a crew
that'll do
a second vote together.
And it's
been this constant shift
since the beginning
of the merge.
PROBST:
So then, Charlie,
what do you do?
Sooner or later
you have to walk up those steps
and write down a name.
What is the final decider?
What do you go to?
CHARLIE:
Even if you can't
trust someone, can you
somehow point yourselves
in the same direction?
You know, set up
your row of dominoes
all in a line and make sure
that they all tip over
and send the right person home
for your individual game.
So, you have to be
able to persuade people
to point in the same direction.
And I think that's
what tonight's about.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Kenzie, you're up.
♪ ♪
Please get off the island.
I'm sick of all your lies.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or
an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Q.
Venus.
Kenzie.
So, that's one vote Kenzie,
one vote Q, one vote Venus.
Venus.
Two votes Venus,
one vote Kenzie, one vote Q.
Venus.
That's three votes Venus,
one vote Kenzie,
one vote Q.
Twelfth person voted out
and the fifth member
of our jury: Venus.
That's four. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
-VENUS: Great job, you guys.
-Love you, boo.
Love you.
Great game, sister.
Venus, the tribe has spoken.
-Great game, you guys.
-Time for you to go.
-VENUS: You killed it.
-Bye, V.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
I've been calm,
but I need the storm.
PROBST:
Next time onSurvivor...
CHARLIE:
I love her to death,
but I have to vote her out.
This is gonna be my favorite
blindside of the season.
MARIA: It's gonna
light a fire under me.
I went home with an idol,
but I'm proud
of the journey I've gone on.
I hope that I have made
made the women of Iran proud.
I have three words
that I want to say,
which is: women, life, freedom.
I hope that I was one voice
that helped uplift
those who are voiceless.
This was a wild ride
and I wouldn't take
it back for a single thing.
[roars]