Or a Fanny pack?
Come on, now!
Get the q skirt.
Dear.
Previously on survivor...
There it is... a full-blown idol
that nobody knows about.
- Tiff has an idol.
- Okay.
I want tevin gone.
I don't want to get lost in the shuffle.
It's tevin tonight.
I need to give
a signal that I'm here to play, too.
Yeah.
Jeff,
the only person that's
going home tonight is me.
Wait, wait. Wha...
What?
- Can we talk to each other for a minute?
- Yeah.
Boy.
Ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury:
Tevin.
The tribe has spoken.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- Wild.
- Stupid.
No.
I don't think anyone... Okay.
He just confused so many
people, and created, like,
massive chaos for no reason.
My jaw will not come off the floor.
- I know.
- I'm so perplexed.
Tribal was bizarre because q tried to quit.
Everyone was so confused.
But we had a plan to get out tevin,
and we weren't gonna let q mess it up.
If you want to "leave,"
there's the door, baby.
Like, walk out.
Don't make us do it for you.
I'm so mad.
- Honestly, I was... I was...
- I'm pissed.
I know. I'm upset, too,
and I was surprised.
Like, that just put a
massive target on him.
Like, I don't understand what
he was trying to have happen.
Going into tribal, I was trying
to switch all the votes at the last second,
and it caused everything
to go crazy at tribal.
I felt guilty for screwing
up everybody's game.
And in my everyday life,
when I make a mistake,
I raise my hand, and I own up to it.
So, I tried to take the heat
and kind of fall on my own sword.
But in the end, they didn't voe
me like I asked them to. Damn.
I guess I'm too hard to kill right now.
I really want to know
what was the... point
of you telling them about my idol?
The point of me telling them
was because of the six.
When we agreed, they said,
"anybody brings anybody
name up within the...
The core group of the
six, we got to send 'em out."
I'm just pissed, man. I
worked so hard for this idol.
But people know I have it now
because q couldn't keep
his big-ass mouth shut.
The only reason I even
knew you said something is
'cause Charlie told me in tribal council
that you told them about it.
And I had no idea you
even told them about my idol.
No, I didn't find out
until Charlie told me, bro.
If you run around
calling yourself my number one ally,
why is you spilling
the beans about an idol
that I possibly could have
used to protect your dumb ass?
'Cause you couldn't have your way?
Are you stupid? Are you dumb?
My god, tiff, do you realize
ever since I've stepped on this beach,
I've done nothing but
try to put plans together
to get us to the final six?
Shut up, bro.
Play your own game. It's so annoying
because now I might have to play my idol
at the next tribal council
because the longer I hold onto it,
the bigger my target is gonna become.
- At that point...
- Why wouldn't you give me a heads up?
- Like, now my game is sunk, bro.
- But...
My... like, I'm literally target number one
because of you opening your mouth.
Tiff is mad tonight.
My goodness. I'm in trouble.
It's like pie just blew up in my face.
So I have to now work harder
than I've ever had to work
in this game to get back in charge,
and if I do, it'll be a miracle.
Tiff is so pissed.
Because he should have told her,
and now
I think there's something
else going on with him
that he was willing to
give up his whole game.
He's literally an idiot.
I worked really hard all freaking day
to get tevin out, but now,
my move is completely
overshadowed by q.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm kind of on the edge here.
I'm just really super pissed.
I was making this move
so that I wouldn't get lost in the game.
Q was, like, the biggest idiot.
- It's like, "okay, cool, q."
- And, like...
"Like, you were a part of my plan!"
- He was begging to leave.
- I mean,
he never should have done
that in the first place, you know?
I feel so mad
because q stole my
thunder from under me.
I wanted people to say, "wow",
"Liz is a fighter and she
doesn't need to be led.
She is a leader."
I will not get lost in this game. That's not
what I want to show my
friends, my family, my daughter.
So, when I get the
chance, I am gunning for q.
Dude, last night was so stupid.
He's just mad he got his game busted
and now, I feel like if we take him out,
there's no weight to the résumé
'cause he blew his own game up.
So it's like, who's the real threat now?
Q doing that at tribal is
like, "hey, I'm a coward"
"and don't want to be at the
bottom and reap the consequences
"of my actions, so please
vote me out so I can look like
I have a moral high ground,
even though I'm a total idiot."
You have no problem
ruining other people's games.
But then when it comes to yours,
there's, like, a moral high ground?
- Like...
- Yeah. I'm like,
"you flip votes on me
because I don't want to..."
Do what you say all the time?
"I don't want to do what you say."
"I don't want to protect you at all costs."
"Bro, I'm out here to
play my own game, too."
Yeah.
What q pulled last night
was a poser move, trying
to act like a noble Saint
when really he just
destroyed his own game.
Well, I tell you this.
Even if he made it to the
end, he's not getting my vote.
- No, he's not getting mine.
- He's not getting my vote.
You can't just force a
blindside last minute.
Siga was never gonna side with them.
Y'all weren't gonna side
with them last minute.
Liz was never gonna side with them.
All they had was tevin and hunter.
I love the mess. I live for the chaos.
Tribal just played out perfectly.
I got tevin's ass out of here, thank god.
And no one's gonna trust q from now on.
No one's gonna work with the man.
And hunter... he was
the king of the jungle
and now is the village idiot
because he was on the
wrong side of the vote.
They really shot themselves
in the foot in this game.
Come on, hunter, Mr. Strategy.
What are you... what's your...
- Yeah, that's me.
- Well, I mean, yesterday,
you tried to pull off a move, so,
what do you think should be the move?
No, yesterday, I didn't
try to pull off a move.
- Yesterday...
- Yesterday, I knew the ship was sinking,
and I knew no one would get
mad if I wrote their name down.
Yeah, except you, but you're always mad.
I mean, it's true.
No. I've been trying to work
with you since the beginning.
- I knew you weren't...
- And all you've done
was stonewall me and
write my name down.
So what do I... What do
you want? I don't know.
These bumbling buffoons,
these two dum-dum meatheads
who think that they are running the show
they've been exposed as these two rats
who are, like, trying for strategy,
trying for power, but
failing miserably at it.
Honestly, they deserve what they got.
And now the rest of
their game is screwed.
The peace of knowing you're
not going home is so sweet.
Guess what, hunter?
You write my name
down, you best believe
I'm gonna return the favor very soon.
Karma is a bitch.
We had decided to keep,
you know, the group together.
And if anybody's going against the group,
we got to try to do something about it,
and to keep strong people in.
And all of those things
did not work last night.
Like, I felt like we just
kind of gave up on that.
- You think I gave up on the plan?
- I...
You didn't think I did my due diligence?
No, I... I am... I believe you did.
Like, I get... I get that,
but, like, I had to play
my game, too, q.
Like, I... like, you got
to respect that, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Last night, my game was totally
scrambled up because of what q did.
The three people that
I trusted the most... q, tevin and Liz
like, they're all done in my book.
I don't want to work with q,
I don't want to work with Liz.
And tevin is gone.
So, I feel like the target's
on my back because,
I wasn't in the majority,
people just see me as a challenge threat.
Tree mail!
But nobody knows I
have an idol in my pocket.
And so, I've got to maneuver how I can
to try to just make it through this vote.
I need to win the challenge today and get
that necklace back so
I can really push things
to make moves that help hunter's game.
I knew it.
- What? - What?
- No.
"Three teams of three."
No. Come on, bro.
"You decide who's who.
"Another joins the jury tonight.
Just make sure it's not you."
No!
All right, me, Kenzie and
Ben are gonna rock out.
We're gonna rock out.
Tiff and I don't even want to look at q.
So when Ben was like,
"y'all want to rock
and roll?," we were like,
"perfect. As long as we're
not with q, yes, let's go."
Like, we don't even want to be on a team
with the man right now.
- Yeah, so, us three.
- Maria, hunter and Charlie.
And then hunter looked
at Maria and Charlie.
They said "yes," of course,
because hunter wins everything.
If hunter would have asked me,
I would have said yes, too.
Doesn't take much strategy there.
- That leaves us. Okay.
- Yeah. Yeah. - Cool.
That was easier than
I thought it would be.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So, the leftover team
was Venus and Liz and q.
I'm sorry for them,
but that's just the way
the cookie crumbled.
Let the games begin.
A trio of trios.
I was a little mad with
how the teams got split u.
I was the one stuck with q,
the man who tried to
quit the game of survivor,
and poor Liz, who has been
really suffering right now.
Like, she's on very low energy,
and the girl hasn't
eaten in, like, 72 hours.
So I'm on the underdog team by a mile,
but I love being the underdog.
Maria and Charlie.
Dang. This might be the
only opportunity right now.
For... a win?
Well, no, no, no, not
for... I'm saying just...
At tribal last night, it was a
mistake to offer myself up.
It was a mistake
on their part now for not
taking me up on that offer,
because now, you've given me new life
to play this game how I want to play it.
I don't have to worry about
tiff or Kenzie or hunter.
Now that I'm here,
I'm gonna give 'em hell.
They can cancel Christmas.
Y'all control it today... you and Maria
because this three-person challenge,
you have to compete
against hunter at the end.
I am aware that a target
might be on my back. That's why I have
to make sure anybody but q goes home.
Hunter is a physical
threat, and they want him out
way worse than they want me out.
Y'all control whether or not
hunter has a shot at immunity.
And depending on what it is,
- I don't know if I can beat him.
- Yeah, so
I mean, what are...
What are your thoughts?
If you don't think you can beat
him at the end in a challenge,
you want to just give
him another necklace?
Q is telling me to throw
the challenge so hunter loses?
That does not jive with me. Not at all.
Throwing a challenge
that's just yuck to me, you know?
Yuck. Not gonna do it.
We'll talk, man. Just-just... Yeah.
We're good. Whatever
you want to do, let's go.
Yeah, yeah. All right, q.
I don't want to just be nestled in behind q
and do whatever he wants.
After what he pulled at tribal council,
q is just a total wild card
and someone who I don't really trust.
Q... when we were talking, he was like,
"you should think about throwing it."
And I don't know. That's
just not really my job.
That's not my job, either.
I was, I think... neither do I.
I like hunter a lot. I think he's solid.
I mean, and I think
that's why he called us in.
Yeah.
He's like, "I want to
work with you and Charlie"
- "in the challenge." Yeah.
- Yeah.
And I don't want to throw
something to make him lose.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Part of me is just, like,
"q, after last night..."
That was just stupid.
- I'm sorry.
- I was... it was stupid.
It made... just left the
worst taste in my mouth.
Yeah. Me too. Me too.
Obviously, hunter's a threat because
he's physical, but I
like hunter as a person.
And then q, with the antics
that he pulled last night,
nobody's gonna want to
award the million dollars.
And so, for me, there are
bigger fish to fry right now.
I think tiff wants to have
another conversation
with me about her idol.
Tiff doesn't tell me anything,
yet she says she wants to work with me,
- yet she's lying to me.
- Yeah. Yeah.
And that's why I cannot work with her.
- Yeah.
- Like, I need her gone with her idol.
To me, tiff is the biggest threat,
and I know she's talking
about me behind my back.
And we know that she has an idol.
That's dangerous, so,
she's got to go. She's got to go.
This is absolutely the
time for a massive blindside.
Come on in!
Wow.
Good morning.
- Hi, Jeff.
- Good morning, Jeff.
- Jeff.
- Good morning. All right.
Guys still looking good, got to say.
- Chilling pretty hard.
- All right.
Shall we get to today's
immunity challenge?
First things first, hunter.
Got to take back the necklace.
Wow, look at that. Now, see?
He meets me halfway.
That's how we're supposed to do it.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
This morning in tree mail,
you were instructed to
divide into groups of three.
Big decision, because you
want a group strong enough
to get you to the end,
but a group not so strong
that you don't have a shot
to win if you get to the end.
Tiff, walk me through this morning.
How did you decide on
who was gonna run with who?
It was super random.
Ben looked at me and said,
"you ready to rock?" I said, "let's go."
And then Kenzie said, "cool. Me too."
Like, it was just super random.
Venus, how did you
end up on your group?
I was, like, the last one to
walk into that conversation.
So I was like, "okay, this is my group."
Charlie, I am stunned.
Security in the game.
Winning one immunity
challenge could keep you safe
at the one tribal council that
you actually need to be safe at.
- Yeah.
- And I keep getting
the same answer from
everybody, which is,
"I just took whatever.
Hey, it was kind of 'rock on.'"
here's what I think it is, Jeff. I think
last tribal... totally unpredictable,
muddier than ever, and people are afraid
of saying, you know, "I'm
gonna pick you, you and you."
And then all of a sudden, "is that a trio?
Did I miss out on something?"
So I think people just wanted
to go completely casual
and not put any target on anything.
I have a different take.
I don't even think it's fear -no.
So much as it is people kind of just
trying to get away from chaotic energy
- and distancing themselves.
- Yeah.
- That's a better way.
- People are kind of just...
That's a better way of putting it.
"I see it's a little chaotic over there.
Let me step to this side."
- Yeah.
- Clearly,
- they're talking about q.
- Yes, we are. - They might be, Jeff.
It's okay. We'll just go
and call a spade a spade.
- Yeah, might be. They are.
- It's okay.
- I mean, I was at tribal, too.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, I don't think a lot of
people were trying to avoid it.
I think the old yanu, maybe.
Maybe tiff was trying to avoid it, so...
No, it wasn't just me, babe.
- You became chaotic for everybody.
- Okay. It wasn't a discussion.
Let's see. Show me
your three. Get together.
- Okay.
- Vibe tribe.
- I'll come to you.
- Team khaki, almost.
There we go.
All right, so, hunter, Charlie and Maria
gonna run as a group.
Q, Liz and Venus gonna run as a group.
Ben, tiff and Kenzie
gonna run as a group.
All right, let's get to it.
Today's challenge runs in stages.
At each stage, the last group is out.
Here's how it works. For the first stage,
one at a time, you're gonna
cross a hinged balance beam
and grab a pair of handles.
You'll then use those handles
to transport a buoy across
a second balance beam.
Once everybody's
across, you'll work together
to dig up three rope rungs.
The first two groups to finish move on.
The last group is out.
For the second stage, you'll use
those rope rungs to build a rope bridge.
Once everybody's built their bridge,
each player in the group
is responsible for landing
one ball on a small ring.
First group to finish moves on.
For the final round,
the winning group is now competing
against each other
for individual immunity.
You're gonna balance with your feet
on a narrow perch, your
hands behind your head,
holding on to a handle.
If at any point, hand
comes off the handle,
foot comes off the perch, you're out.
Last person left standing wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
Losers, tribal council,
where somebody will be
the tenth person voted out,
become the third member of our jury.
I'm gonna put my
survivor fan hat on again
and go out on a limb
right now, q, and say that
you, Liz and Venus are
first out and have no shot.
Geez. Let's see.
Thanks. Thanks for that, Jeff.
Prove me wrong.
Thanks for that vote of confidence, Jeff.
Venus, that's what everybody
watching right now is thinking,
- and that's what this game is.
- Right.
If we can't say what we're seeing,
what's the point of being out here?
- Correct. - Agreed?
- I'm with that.
- Let's do it.
- All right, let's draw
for spots. We'll get it on.
- Here we go.
- Come on, Jeff.
All right, here we go.
First two groups to finish move on.
Last group is out. Survivors ready?
Go! It's gonna be
Maria, Venus and Kenzie.
Yeah, easy.
First, you've got to cross a hinged beam
and grab your handles by untying them.
Kenzie has hers first, -ooh!
- Then Maria.
- There you go, Maria.
Then Venus.
Get it to tip.
There goes Maria. She's good.
Pick up that buoy.
- Ooh!
- Kenzie's struggling.
Venus is across, Kenzie's across.
Now you put the handles in the buoy
- and cross another balance beam.
- There you go, Maria.
- You got it, you got it, you got it.
- Kenzie's on.
You got to be in, though.
You got to be in the holes.
Got to be in the holes.
- Maria doing a nice job.
- You're cruising, Maria.
- You got this.
- Take your time.
- There goes Venus.
- Go, v!
You're good! Go, purple!
It's gonna be Charlie up.
My god.
Kenzie drops, has to go back.
- Sorry, y'all.
- Venus doing a nice job.
- You're good. Go, green!
- You got this, Liz!
- Gonna be Liz.
- You got this, Liz.
There you go, in the middle.
- Charlie has his handles.
- Nice, Charlie.
Kenzie gonna give it another go.
No. Kenzie drops again!
Yes, Liz. You got that!
Liz, you're good.
Charlie doing a nice job.
You're good, Charlie! Go, hunter!
Orange in dead last.
- Kenzie, take your time.
- It's so hard.
Purple in the lead.
Hunter now with the
buoy, moving quickly
across that second
beam, making it look easy.
- Do a triangle.
- Do a triangle. Period.
- I'm trying, v!
- You're good, you're good.
You're good, purple!
Start digging! Kenzie
might have it this time.
Get across.
Kenzie's good! Go!
- You got this.
- Ben is on the beam.
- I grabbed mine.
- I got mine.
Purple has their three rope rungs.
Purple's good.
Purple moving on.
Liz, you got this.
- Take your time.
- You're good, Liz! Go, q!
Purple has moved on. We're
looking for one more group.
Ben, you're good! Get on that buoy.
Here comes q.
Here goes Ben. He has got to get across
for orange to have any shot at this.
And he's looking good, but nope, drops.
All right, take your time.
- Take your time.
- Q taking his time.
Q very close.
You're good!
Start digging!
Come on, dig.
It is Venus, Liz and q digging.
I predicted they would be first out
and I'm gonna be wrong.
It's orange that is the disastrous group.
Nice, Venus.
Venus has the first rope rung.
There goes Ben. Can he get across?
- You got it.
- You're good!
Go, tiff! Tiff has a lot
of ground to make up
as Venus pulls up the second
- of three rope rungs.
- All right.
This is almost over. Mark it down.
- I'll own it. I was wrong.
- Sorry, tiff.
- It's all right, y'all.
- There's the third rope rung.
Come on, give it, give it, give it.
Q, Venus, Liz
moving on. Kenzie, Ben, tiff are out.
- No shot at immunity.
- Good job, y'all.
- Good job.
- Nice job, y'all.
- All right.
Give you a minute to organize,
and we'll move on to round two!
All right.
First three to finish
move on to the final round,
where you will compete
against each other for immunity.
Here we go.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Everybody building a rope bridge
using rope rungs, from left to right,
then right to left.
It is hunter, Maria and Charlie
taking on q, Liz and Venus,
for a shot at individual immunity.
Hunter's now on his rope.
Venus doing a nice job.
She's gonna start crawling.
There goes Maria.
Q now getting on his rope bridge.
- Liz doing a nice job.
- Look at that. Let's go, Liz.
- All right, Liz!
- We see you, girl.
We got a challenge right
now. This is pretty even.
Nice job, Maria.
Liz drops a rope.
- It's okay.
- Your feet touch the ground,
you got to go all the way
back and climb out again.
If you can get it from there, great.
- Power, Venus!
- Look at Liz.
Reaches down and gets it.
Hunter very close to the end.
Venus doing a nice job.
- Maria close to the end.
- Let's go, Maria!
Hunter's across.
- Nope.
- If you want to help,
you got to go all the way back
across yours and then circle back.
Hunter's gonna try to help now.
You can do that.
Who's he gonna help?
He's gonna help Charlie.
Maria's across.
Venus is across. Is she gonna help?
- Nope. She's gonna go to her mat.
- Q, should I come help?
- I'm good, I'm good.
- Good? Go, go, go.
- Liz is good.
- Yeah, Liz!
Yeah, girl!
- Yeah!
- I love that.
Charlie's across.
Hunter's back across. Start
working on balls, one each.
- Go, go. You're so close.
- Q is finished.
You're good, orange! Start throwing.
This challenge is on.
It's now Venus for orange,
hunter for purple.
Requires a lot of touch to get that ball
to land on such a small ring.
- You got it.
- Almost.
- Good job, hunter!
- Hunter lands the first ball.
All right, hunter!
- Charlie's up now.
- Charlie!
Q trying to land for orange.
Got it. So close.
Charlie very close.
Q trying to get one to stick.
He's going for that highest
one. That's the toughest one.
- Come on, q. Almost.
- He's close.
Larry bird in the cut!
Q has it!
Q has one for orange.
Venus is back in. We're tied, one-one.
Good job, v.
Venus with another shot.
- On and off.
- Venus.
Charlie on and... off and on.
Purple has two. Maria,
the last ball for purple.
Venus on and off.
- Maria can win it right here.
- You got it, Maria.
The winning group moves on
to compete against each other.
Out, no shot at immunity.
Just take your time and reset.
There it is.
Maria has it! It's over!
Purple wins.
Hunter, Charlie and
Maria are moving on.
You are now gonna
compete against each other.
I'm gonna give you a minute
to get into that mindset.
Individual immunity on the line.
Take a break. Get it together.
All right, everybody
get up. Get into position.
We're ready to go.
Ooh.
Let's go.
God.
All right, everybody looks
good, and this challenge is on.
- And it already hurts.
- Yes.
Your head can move, but your shoulders
and your butt have to
stay against that board.
And that's important because
if you move, you get relief,
which is why, if you do
it, I'm gonna call you out.
You also can't squat to get relief.
There is no relief in this challenge.
You don't want to show any weakness.
You are too close to each other.
Predator and prey.
You might say "hunter and hunted."
Hey.
Pretty good, too.
Everybody looking good.
Guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
That's getting close.
Where you feeling it, hunter?
Weird, it's in, like, the front of my knees.
How about you, Maria?
Pretty much everywhere, Jeff.
Charlie?
Heels.
Maria is out out of nowhere.
- Good job, Maria.
And we have another
showdown in a rematch.
It is Charlie versus hunter.
Hunter won last time.
Charlie wants to change that this time.
Chill mad hard.
I don't think there's anything
chill about this challenge, man.
It looks painful.
Hunter on one end.
Charlie on the other.
Fighting to guarantee to see day 18.
Been up there ten minutes.
Every minute an eternity.
Well.
Hunter's had a little bit of movement,
but locked back in.
Charlie's been really stable. Who knows
what's going on inside the
minds of hunter and Charlie,
how much pain
management is going on.
Ooh.
Got to hang in as long as you can.
You don't know when the
other person's gonna drop.
They could be seconds
away from calling it,
waiting for you to drop.
Don't give 'em that satisfaction.
You got to earn it out here.
I'm off, I'm off, I'm off, I'm off.
Hunter's out.
Charlie wins individual immunity,
safe tonight at tribal council,
guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
Another showdown
from Charlie and hunter,
- with a different result - this time.
- Charlie!
- Good job, guys.
- Well done.
That is a painful challenge.
Good job. You killed it.
- Good job.
- That was crazy.
Charlie, come on over.
- Yeah!
- Charlie!
Man.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
Charlie, safe tonight at tribal council.
Cannot be voted out.
Guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
We're not at the end,
but we're getting there.
What is the sense of security?
That's what this offers.
You aren't going home tonight.
That feeling is something you can
never get on survivor.
Never, never, never.
And it... what it is is, all of a sudden,
all of the gears in your brain
can stop moving for a second.
So, it lets you get
some clarity and safety.
All right, you are safe tonight.
- Good job, Charlie.
- As for the rest of you,
17 days on survivor is tough.
For one of you, it will be the end.
Tonight, somebody
voted out, tenth person
will become the third member of our jury.
I can't wait to see you at tribal
and hear about this afternoon.
Grab your stuff. Head back to camp.
See you tonight at tribal. Congrats.
- See you, Jeff.
- Well done. - Thanks, Jeff.
- Charlie! - Charlie!
- Charlie, my guy.
I'm so proud of myself for beating hunter,
the top physical threat in the game.
I didn't know if I was gonna
get one of these things. Like,
that was awesome.
We're on day 17
in the final nine on survivor.
No more quitting talk. None of that.
Let's play the game and let's play it hard.
Congratulations, Charlie.
Thank you, hunter.
- Thank you all.
- Good on you, Charlie.
Charlie!
Guys, that means a lot.
- Man.
- Loved your comments.
Y'all were something else.
Today at the challenge,
Charlie beats hunter.
In the back of my mind,
I'm like, "this is perfect."
This is exactly how I wanted it
to play out, because it
gives us many options
as to how tonight can go.
We can vote q, we can vote hunter,
or we could pull a blindside off.
And I love having options, you know?
I love a world of possibilities.
Wild.
So does anyone want to
volunteer to go home tonight, or.
I think the writing's on the wall.
After last tribal, everyone hee
either don't respect what I
did or don't like what I did.
And it's really my own fault.
If I'm here tomorrow, it's a miracle.
Yeah.
Since, you know,
q wants to be captain big mouth pants,
I want q out, and I'm
gonna keep saying it
until he's on the jury bench.
Okay.
So I have to now somehow
come back and rekindle everything,
because I still want
to have this adventure.
This is fun.
I want to cause some more
chaos tomorrow, probably,
if I'm here.
We made a six.
Yeah, I heard about the six.
Tiff has been in a group,
and it didn't include you.
- And-and I want...
- Yeah, you didn't include me, either.
And you want to know why?
And I have, like, no respect
for what you did last night.
- You want to know why you don't?
- Talking about the idol,
the way you were leaving, like, I just...
- But, you know, you want to know why?
- I'm not vibing with it.
No. Q, I'm not working
with you right now.
Like, I'm mad.
I'm not, I'm not asking
you to work for me.
- That was it. That is it.
- I appreciate you coming forward.
I'm not asking you to
work for me. I'm fine.
- I'm cool.
- Yeah. Cool.
- Appreciate it.
- Yeah.
I don't care what q is telling me.
Q doesn't feel in control,
so he's grasping at
straws to get control back.
It was like he was telling me
all this so that I would get mad
- at you. So that...
- Of course that's what he wanted.
So that I could, like, go back to him,
because I'm like, "q, thanks so much"
"for telling me about how
you left me out of everything,
but since you told me..."
"Q, thanks. Like, let's buddy up."
No.
Q, no one wants to
work with you right now.
We're target number one and two.
We don't know which order we're in.
Yeah.
So, tonight could be easy,
but this is a perfect opportunity,
because everyone is so distracted
by q being a mess and
by hunter being vulnerable
that it's, like, the perfect
time for a blindside.
I'm willing to bet someone here's
gonna have the thought -yeah.
That if everyone's distracted on q
and everyone's distracted on hunter,
it'd be the perfect time for a blindside.
- And if they can pull the numbers, then...
- Yeah.
I want to spice it up to hopefully
drive something that's a little risky.
You know, that's how I want to play,
is calculated risk.
And this is a good time
to grab it by the horns and make a move.
- I have a plan.
- Okay.
But it cannot leave right here.
Okay.
How do you feel about tiff's idol?
Tiff's feeling so comfortable
that now we could pull
off a blindside. Easy.
- Yeah.
- Easy.
Tiff has been my number
one this whole game.
I understand that.
And her and I are very
competitive people.
I love her so much for it
and I respect her for it,
but it's always gonna be
like, "you or me first, girl."
And so I would rather go out
swinging than eating
popcorn on the sidelines.
Please do not tell anyone outside of this.
Yeah. No.
- No.
- I'm not going to. I have no option.
One, three, four. We need one more.
- Ben.
- Is Ben down?
I'm down. Yeah.
Tiff is so mad at q and so distracted
that there's no way
she'd play her idol tonight.
Okay.
But I swear I will get
sent home if this gets out.
Yeah, yeah.
Nope. Nope.
Like, please. Because tiff
and I have been like this.
- Yeah, yeah.
- No, i-i...
It's gonna have to... We
may have to pretend it's you.
I'm-I'm super down. I'm down.
Do y'all want me to act like
I'm scrambling super hard?
What'd you say?
- Probably.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Boy.
When we get back from
the challenge, there was
just kind of this miserable feeling of,
"like, it is 100% gonna be me."
Seriously.
Not yet.
War is on, baby. Let's go.
Now, my gut feels like there's
actually gonna be a Tiffany blindside.
That sounds great to
me, because, like, I may
have to play my idol
tonight. I don't want to.
It'd be great to have it
later and keep it a secret.
- My goodness.
- Okay. Can we talk about this?
- Yeah. Okay.
- God. I love this so much.
Listen. Yeah, I'm like, I'm like, I knew.
I was like, "this is music to Maria's ears."
My god.
Yeah.
But, like, it's Kenzie's plan, which is fine.
This is way better.
I know. It's way better.
Yeah. This is wonderful.
You know, I've had this thought of,
like, I need to get Tiffany
ou. She came for me.
And then in comes Kenzie
saying, "I want to get Tiffany out."
- That's why we got to get her.
- Yeah.
- So...
- I'm into it.
- Okay.
- Kenzie's here to play.
I think Kenzie feels that tiff was never
gonna take her very far.
Kenzie wants a big move on her résumé.
And I'm like, "damn,
like, that's my move."
Like, I want to get tiff out.
But I do worry, if Tiffany
gets wind of something,
maybe she tries to play her idol.
If we focus on tiff tonight
yeah. I want to...
Because of the idol, and obviously, like
I want to talk to tiff, if that's okay,
'cause I-I want to try to
make her feel comfortable.
Okay.
All right, so here, here, let
me throw this at you, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
'Cause obviously y'all know I want q.
'Cause q spilled the
beans in front of y'all.
Yeah.
Here's my only thing.
I will gladly write hunter's
name down tonight
because I know he's
a big physical threat.,
but I also,
I got to burn this idol out of my pocket.
I have to play it.
- I just don't want to be blindsided.
- Yeah.
Like, that was my only fear because
- I don't... I'm-I'm fine with flushing it.
- Yeah.
At this point, I don't want
it in my pocket anymore.
Yeah.
Because it's... Because it's a threat.
It's a threat now. I don't want it.
I don't want this idol
anymore. I will play it.
I don't trust nobody on this beach.
Once people know about
an idol, you can't lie about it,
because then that's
gonna make your target
go from this to this.
You don't think Maria will try to flush
the idol prematurely, right?
I don't think so.
My biggest worry tonight
is that everybody lying to me,
and they gonna get me
and this idol out of here.
But the only reason I
wouldn't want to play
this idol is because, as
survivor fans, we know
when the idol is played, it's
coming back to the beach, baby.
And I do not want hunter or q to get it.
So, I'm-I'm gonna... yeah.
- Just, yeah.
- All right.
- Okay. That sounds good. All right.
- All right. Cool.
Unbelievable.
I was trying to make
tiff feel like she's safe
and vote her out tonight.
All of a sudden, Tiffany
says she's gonna play her idol.
The idol has zero value to me
now that people know about it.
- Right.
- I don't even want
this thing anymore. I'm
ready to burn it on the spot.
Right.
I don't even want this thing in
my pocket. Get it away from me.
- Right.
- An idol is scary, it's unpredictable,
and it leaves tiff with a lot of power.
So now this game is flipped on its head,
and we've got to figure out
what the heck we're gonna do.
Plans change
faster than the wind changes in survivor,
and the playing field is wide open.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Well, the tiff idol thing is huge.
- Yeah.
So that plan
is shelved because she may use her idol.
But she's like, "I don't
even want this thing."
Wow. Okay.
The obvious choice
would be to get q out,
but when the time's right.
I'm not, like, blood hungry.
- So we do...
- Shh.
- We do, hunter.
- Yeah.
- And then we try and get tiff tomorrow.
I'm okay with that.
And we can literally drop this plan
- an hour beforehand.
- Or less.
Or less. And be like,
"boom, boom, boom." Okay.
Because hunter doesn't have immunity,
this is the right time to get hunter.
Totally.
Okay.
The plan to take out tiff fell apart.
And now we're in a position
where we could take hunter out,
but I know if hunter goes,
I have more of a chance
at winning something,
because he has crushed
most of the challenges.
We have to make sure
Kenzie's cool with it.
If you guys want me
to talk to Kenzie, I will.
It presents, like, a golden platter.
You only get, like, the
t. Rex in Jurassic park
back in the cage one time,
and we've already done that.
I'm not trying to have a
Jurassic park sequel right now.
I'm trying to get him out
so the playing field is even.
I'm just trying to weigh the options.
- Yeah.
- My worry is if tiff plays her idol,
I just think the consensus
is people kind of want
to get hunter tonight.
We've been talking
about the hunter thing
for so long.
Let's just go with the obvious one now
- and let tiff -feel comfortable.
- Yeah.
So you and Charlie and Maria
- want to do hunter?
- Yeah.
That's the way I view it.
I mean, I think the
hunter vote's boring, but...
It's boring, but it opens up the insanity.
I really wanted to blindside tiff,
but you can't blindside
someone with an idol
when she would just play it.
Now, everyone
wants hunter gone,
because, let's be real,
hunter has dominated everything here.
Yeah. Everyone's in.
We're not telling them.
I would rather vote for q,
'cause I can't stand him,
but I can't speak for the whole group.
If the whole group wants hunter, fine.
We'll do hunter.
Fine.
I do love hunter.
I do, too. He's sweet,
but, like, damn, I can't beat you, buddy.
- Yeah.
- I can't even come close to beating you.
That's part of the thing, too.
I'm beginning to feel pretty nervous.
I've been trying to really get a good read
on what's going on.
You know, is this plan
to blindside tiff actually happening?
These people lied straight
to tevin's face, and he
believed it till the end
and had me fooled.
And so maybe they're
doing the same thing to me.
- Why?
- Just...
Yeah.
Like, I fully trust you, but I'm just, like...
'Cause they could easily just switch.
- I mean, as far as I know, we're good.
- I know. Okay.
I know, but... yeah.
- But, yeah. Okay...
- I know.
- It's uneasy.
- I'm still... Yeah.
I'm not naiïve to the fact
that it can still be me,
which is really, really frustrating.
And so I am constantly
running the numbers,
and I'm thinking about
what has to happen.
I feel like the target's on my
back for a multitude of reason.
So I am 100% playing my idol.
Tonight is about surviving.
If I'm gonna play this
game to win, I think the idol
has to be a tool that I can use not just
to save myself to make another vote,
but to use it to gain potential allies.
Listen, I have an idol and
I'm playing it tonight. Okay?
- You do?
- Yes.
So I think we need to
vote for someone like Ben.
Okay?
All right. Ben.
I think people are lying to me.
And it seems like Maria
and Charlie and even Ben
are kind of in the heart of it.
Me and Ben don't
have a huge relationship.
Like, we haven't talked a
whole lot, and so he can go.
The guy with the glasses
right now is on a mission.
And if I can survive this vote,
I think we're gonna
swing it back into our favor.
I'm ready for a big move.
I'm ready for a change.
I'm ready to get the power back.
I think they're voting for me.
Wait, I'm so confused.
Are we not voting q?
Because I think it's, like,
basically set right now.
No.
It's not. It's not.
Like, you're not gonna have...
But you don't... what number?
Okay. You promise
you're not gonna freak out?
I have an idol.
- I'm playing it.
- I mean... okay.
You look like you're unimpressed.
No, it's not that I'm unimpressed.
So now I'm rethinking the numbers.
I wish you would have
told me this earlier.
Yeah, this is, like, so last minute.
I think the smartest
thing is to just stick with q
and be in the majority.
Just play ball with me this time, right?
And then we'll-we'll
own it together tomorrow?
Last freaking minute,
hunter approaches me,
tells me he has an idol.
He wants to vote for Ben.
No. I'm sticking with voting for q.
I think q is an absolute liability.
- I have an idol.
- Okay.
- I'm playing it tonight.
But if they are playing me,
the votes will still fall on somebody else.
Wait, what?
Hey, mayday, mayday.
Hunter has an idol. Current
plans are in jeopardy.
And it's just pandemonium.
- I think he's bluffing.
- He could be bluffing.
I think he's bluffing, too.
I think he's bluffing, but...
If hunter breaks out his
idol, I'm breaking out my idol,
because, just in case
all hell breaks loose,
I'm gonna be here tomorrow.
You're my number one.
- I trust you 1,000%.
- Yeah.
Hunter drops this bomb.
Whoa. This is bad,
because we are all about to vote hunter,
and it's complete madness.
Listen, if we got to
get up and talk at tribal,
- we got to get up and talk at tribal.
- Then there you go.
Okay.
It's a disaster.
We literally have two idols in play
and everybody's turning on everyone.
Everyone's throwing everyone's name.
This is messy and
dramatic and emotional.
We don't have a clear-cut plan.
Tonight is going to be wild.
All right. So, last tribal
was one of the most unique tribals
in all my days on survivor.
I'm still not entirely
sure what all happened.
For a large part of the tribal,
I didn't think there was gonna be a vote.
Q, I thought you were gonna just leave.
Clearly, I was wrong, because
not only was there a vote,
it was a massive blindside on tevin.
Great game play. Very entertaining.
But after you all left, I did some thinking,
and I realized it could have been better.
I just... This is on me.
I just wasn't fully prepared.
I-I never anticipated it could go like that.
So, on the off chance that
it happens again tonight,
I'm very prepared.
I have a cushion.
I should have done this years ago.
- Nice.
- So I can really sit back and enjoy, and
forgot the best part... I
brought some popcorn.
Come on!
You are such a scorpio.
- That's ridiculous.
- That's messed up. - I...
You've got to pass that around now.
- That does not rock.
- All right.
I invite you to my home
and I eat in front of you.
You're right. Okay.
What?!
- Take it.
- My god.
- Please save me some.
- My god. Okay.
- Please, y'all.
- Everybody will get some.
- Wow, Jeff. Wow.
- Wow. Thanks, Jeff.
Hey, i-I'm ready for a show.
My god.
I'm about to have, like, a heart attack.
- Liz, can you eat popcorn?
- Yes!
I haven't eaten in over 72 hours.
Let's all just take a moment.
Liz can eat something on survivor.
- Thank you, guys.
- All right, Liz!
Thank you, Jeff.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- My gosh.
I think that's the nicest thing
Jeff's ever done on survivor.
I thought spicy Jeff was back in season.
- Spicy Jeff is back.
- Spicy Jeff.
All right, so let's talk about
last tribal. Charlie,
there had to be some
discussion about what
happened when you all got
back to camp or the next morning.
Yeah, there was plenty of talk.
There was a lot of emotions
and feelings and questions.
And everyone wanted to know the why
and how it happened.
Tiff, that's really the big question, right?
- Is the why behind it.
- Yeah.
So, we came into tribal
with one plan, that we executed:
The blindside on tevin.
However, q took it upon himself
to try and go and sink my game
and it backfired on him.
He and I exchanged words.
It got a little heated
when we got back to camp,
and we haven't said a
word to each other all day.
Wow.
Q, you're smiling.
Jeff, I'm happy.
'Cause I'm over the situation.
The way she explained that
story is not how it went down.
- Okay.
- She sunk her own game when she
started throwing out
names, and she got caught.
By the way,
he has been throwing my
name out since two days ago
because he's jealous of
something that I have going on
that he doesn't have
going on for himself.
But, in the interest of
protecting my own game
right now, I'm-a keep quiet.
- So, keep it going.
- She's a liar,
because at tribal yesterday, -okay. Okay.
She was all happy,
and she didn't get upset
until someone whispered in her ear
- the truth.
- That I told everybody she had an idol.
Okay, this story where he told everybody
I had a idol to save my
game was total bullcrap
because he was mad that I
didn't want to vote for Venus
because that wasn't a big enough shield.
The vote was never Venus.
See, these the lies, Jeff, these the lies.
- The vote was never Venus yesterday.
- He been pushing Venus.
Just like you were
pushing Venus this morning.
You were pushing
hunter name this morning.
- What?
- I ain't say hunter name one time.
- Haven't said hunter name one time.
- I didn't know that.
- Yes, you have.
- Yeah. Okay.
- I haven't said hunter name one time.
- Come on now. Please.
You not gonna sit up here
and tell these lies, q. You not.
I've been at the beach by myself
for most of the day, talking to no one.
It has.
So, for the first time in a long time,
q hasn't talked much at all.
Wow, Ben, I'm glad I
brought the cushion.
My instincts were right.
We're right back where
we were last tribal.
Listen, crazy's gonna reveal crazy,
and that's exactly what happened.
It's one thing if you mess your
own game up and you have
to work back from the bottom.
That's survivor. But then
to make a comment saying,
"I'm gonna give y'all a fresh start
so now y'all can play a real game"
was the biggest slap in the face,
as if nobody's been working together,
as if he's the only guy running the show.
This, even right now, is a show.
There's a way to play the game.
There's a way to deceive, outwit, outlast,
out shred, whatever you want to call it.
And now it's like, here we are,
giving him just as much time
as he had yesterday, when
we're all trying to play a game.
Hunter, weigh in.
I was confused last time
and I was on the wrong side
of the vote, and I'm
still trying to figure it out.
You know, last time, it
was a little more okay
to be on the outside of it
'cause I had a necklace on.
And so if crazy happened,
at least you're protected from that.
But now the crazy's
happening all over again
and I'm just like, "what is going on?"
Who does the crazy benefit?
The people that feel
like they're on the bottom.
But it's so hard to know
if you're on the bottom.
That's the thing... is if the crazy happens
and it puts a target on
somebody else, that's awesome.
But other times, the
craziness is just a facade,
and the group still votes the same way.
Maria, do you think this is a facade?
Is q just playing a
sophisticated game of crazy?
I don't think so.
I think that q tells you
what he's thinking, shows
you what he's feeling.
And that might rub people the wrong way
or it might benefit people.
And I think that the group has to decide,
either we live with the tension
and live with the chaos or we don't.
Ben, how is it that Maria's posing
a question like that at tribal,
when you've had all day to decide
if you want tension or no tension?
Because sometimes you have players
that are chaotic, and you
can just let them be chaotic,
'cause you know they're just
gonna keep doing their thing.
So it's like, you either
deal with it or you take it out.
And I think the game's
been chaotic enough
that we're kind of
operating on that chaotic
frequency to begin with.
Q, does this conversation concern you
or are you comfortable
living in this space
of turbulence surrounding you?
Jeff, I am so comfortable
to the point of it don't bother me at all.
So, whatever's going on
around me, it don't matter.
So if everybody right
now is talking and saying,
"let's just vote out q,"
you're fine with that?
If that what it comes
to, I will take my torch,
I will put it down, you will snuff it,
and I'll be happy for the opportunity.
Tiff, it's fascinating.
I don't know what q's real motive is,
but he said that last tribal,
and you didn't vote him out.
- So...
- 'Cause we had other plans.
We ain't letting him hijack our plans.
We had other plans.
So you don't mind the chaos?
The chaos has been the chaos.
The chaos is gonna be the chaos.
People are annoyed. People are fed up.
And is being annoyed and fed up
affecting my game or not?
And if it is, what am I gonna do about it?
Kenzie, tiff said, "this
happened at the last tribal
and we had a plan."
Does that hold tonight as
well? If there's a different plan,
then q can say whatever he wants,
but if he's not the vote, he's not the vote.
Yeah, 100%. But I think it's
very apparent that a lot of us
are annoyed and very apparent
that a lot of us are frustrated.
And that's kind of where
everyone's at tonight.
And it's telling that the yanu three
are no longer together.
Unless it's a real smoke screen.
- Yeah, no.
- Been dead. Six feet under.
- It's dead. Yeah.
- Dead.
We're about to get breakup bangs.
Like, that's what's happening right now.
Like, we're all getting
weird haircuts to deal with it.
Like, that's what's going on.
So, Charlie, where are we?
I'll answer your question with a question.
Can I stomach more
tribal councils like this?
But the game changes incredibly fast,
and there's all sorts of
stuff being whispered.
Everybody knows it. I know you see it.
- That's why I brought the cushion.
- I know.
I feel like I've aged about
50 years in two nights.
Hunter, I think a lot of times when people
watch survivor, they
question if tribals are live.
Any doubt in your mind?
- I don't know.
- Like, like, for real.
Like, 'cause last time, there
were lots of whispers then,
and someone other than q went home.
That's terrifying.
And so I'm, like, trying to, like, really read
into what people are saying
to say, "hey, is this the case?"
Okay, so now to the big question.
Do we need to talk more?
I don't.
I-I don't think so.
All right, it is time to
vote. Maria, you're up.
Wish you all the best.
Have fun eating tater tots.
That was ridiculous.
'Kay, bye.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Q.
Hunter.
Q. Two votes q.
Hunter. We're tied. Two
votes q, two votes hunter.
Q. That's three votes q.
Tied again. Three votes
q, three votes hunter.
Q. That's four votes
Hunter. We're tied again.
Four votes hunter, four
votes q, one vote left.
Ben.
So we have a tie.
We're gonna revote.
You can only vote for hunter or q.
Hunter and q, you will not vote.
Maria, you're up. Will
you come grab the urn?
I'll read the votes.
Q.
Hunter. One vote q, one vote hunter.
Hunter. Two votes hunter, one vote q.
Three votes hunter, one vote q.
Tenth person voted out hunter.
That's four. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Good job, guys.
- You had a great game.
- Love you, hunter.
- Sorry, hunter.
You played such a good game, my guy.
- Love you, hunty.
- Hunter, you rock.
- You rock.
- You're the best.
It's kind of hard to take all that right after
y'all voted my name like that.
You're a fierce competitor, my guy.
There we go.
- Hunter, the tribe has spoken.
- Yes, they have.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches. Head
back to camp. Good night.
Thanks for the popcorn.
You're welcome.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
These people are making my mind crazy.
What the heck, you ho-bags?
Next time on survivor...
Q is causing chaos.
I want him the hell out of her.
Q blew up my whole game!
This could be a game-winning move.
There it is, in all of its splendor.
I had convinced myself
that I was playing my idol
going into this, but I was
lulled into my own
doom, is what happened.
And it's so irritating.
I loved the experience,
but not how I wanted it to end.