Sam said that you're the backup.
I need to flip the switch.
Previously onSurvivor...
We're gonna randomly divide
into two groups of six.
I think Lavo and
Gata... we have some
level of trust.
We are five Tuku strong.
So, we have
an easy vote out tonight.
This gives someone
the opportunity
to have safety without power.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Jeff?
"Announce that you have the
Safety without Power Advantage.
"You will leave
Tribal Council immediately.
You cannot be voted out."
Tuku five, you will
be turning on each other.
Seventh person voted
out of Survivor47: Tiyana.
The tribe has spoken.
All right, well.
Coming back
to camp completely alone,
my head is just spinning,
honestly.
Like, on the one hand,
I am just breathing
the largest sigh of relief
because I'm here
and I'm in the game.
But at the same time,
it's not great
to have, kind of,
the spotlight on me,
and I hope that I didn't
piss anybody off.
I'm feeling
anxiety and relief, but still
nervousness.
But also,
there's a huge question
of who gave me this advantage.
- I know.
- Marco.
Polo.
- Rachel.
- Sorry, guys.
- What a move tonight.
- Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Tribal did not go good tonight.
You know, Rachel is
a very threatening player.
I was very excited
for her to leave tonight.
But she forced
the Tuku five
to cannibalize itself in front
of everybody at Tribal. So,
this was quite a disaster.
- Safety without Power is crazy.
- Yeah.
And it was,
like, a genuine shock.
Yeah.
I would love to know
where it came from, but
I'm just happy I had it.
I was the one who
gave Rachel the advantage,
and nobody knows about it
because I've been playing
this act out here
that I'm kind of goofy.
So, people don't that I'm really
a really strategic guy.
We moved back to Michigan.
My dad didn't want
to be in Thailand that far away
from us, so he moved to Texas.
But he owned
a video store down there.
- Just as immigrants. Yeah.
- My mom owned a liquor store. Yeah.
- Um, like, my...
- Why do all Asians always own a store?
I gave the advantage
to Rachel because
she was, what I felt,
in jeopardy.
Big, big trouble
at Tribal Council.
But also, genuinely,
there is a connection there.
And I'm working on building
the SSAs... Sol's Secret Agents.
When you got up and left,
they were all freaking out,
- like, "Oh, damn."
- Really?
Your ass was gone.
And...
Literally, the second
I found it, I was like,
- "It was Sol." Yeah, I knew it.
- Yeah.
Sol saved my life.
You know, in this game,
no one has
to help anybody else out,
but he was
looking out for me, period.
You have somebody now, okay?
- Clearly, I want to work with you.
- Yeah.
But I definitely don't
want it to come out
because that's a target on me.
- All right.
- Thank you so much.
I'm so excited
for this budding relationship.
I finally have someone
that I can look at
and be like, "I think at least
for now, I could trust you."
One million percent,
you were going.
They were all playing me.
It was very clear
that they were,
- like, planning on staying together.
- That's wild.
I know you had
a really hard day,
so I'd hate to tell you
how good of a day we had,
but we had a really,
really good day, and...
With Lavo.
Oh, my God. Okay.
You...
Well...
Okay, yes. Yes, yes, yes.
At this point,
I don't trust Tuku
as far as I can throw 'em.
So the Gata-Tuku War
is absolutely coming,
and I want to make sure that
I'm on the right side of
the numbers when it gets here.
Holy crap, dude.
- Kemo sabe.
- Hey, Mr. Miyagi.
Dude, some people on my tribe
have never seen The Karate Kid.
And I'm like, "Wax on, wax off."
They're like, "What?"
- I'm like, "No."
- Are you serious?
I'm like, "Please, no."
I like Sol.
You know, Sol might actually
be, like, my favorite person
out here at this point.
He's a jokester.
He's got a beautiful smile.
- Look at that.
- That's primo. That was one swipe.
One swipe.
Oh! Ah.
Hello, hello.
Everyone, I have something
I'm really excited
to show you all.
I was going on a walk
for a little bit,
and I saw something
kind of interesting.
- I think we should all get going.
- Ah, field trip.
Lead the way, Caroline.
Oh, even the suspense
is killing me, honestly.
- Oh, my God.
- Get out.
- Here it is.
- Get out. Oh.
Y'all cool if I read it? Okay.
I see that word
"auction," and, like,
my heart explodes
and I can't believe
I get to be a part of, like,
one of the biggest
bucket-list items.
Oh, my gosh.
Breaking news from
the islands of Survivor47.
A Survivoricon is back.
It's the auction.
The players are fired up,
running around the jungle,
collecting their money, ready
to go to eat some good food.
- Oh.
- Oh, nice!
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh. No. I'm so far.
I hate running, but, like,
I want food, so I need money.
So I'm just repeating to myself
the things I want to eat.
Yes.
Seems like the water wall
would be... Got one.
Oh, nice.
Hey, bro.
There we go.
Bingo. Bingo!
I haven't gotten
a single food reward yet.
Everything I've eaten so far
has come from the sand.
So I'm hungry.
Ooh. I'm gonna get some steak.
I'm gonna get a burger.
I'm gonna get something good.
Like, I want
to make this money count.
Dude, I have one.
Potato salad. Potato salad.
I got you.
It's like an Easter egg hunt.
I've been good
at Easter egg hunts my entire
life. I mean, my family...
we've had Easter parties
every single year.
Oh, yay.
And I truly, to be honest,
I didn't stop Easter egg hunting
until last year.
I was like, "I got to retire."
But I'm, like,
going hard out here.
Oh, my God. Sierra.
I'm live from
the islands of Survivor47.
We're about halfway through
the search for the cash here.
The players are all
going very nuts.
Uh, so far, Andy in last place
and Sierra,
a surprise early favorite,
racking up lots of dough.
Oh.
How's it going, Andy?
- Hold on. Let's see.
- I just need one.
I feel myself in a hole.
A panic sets in, and I just have
to tell myself, like,
"Okay, I'm just looking
for tubes in the jungle."
I can do that. I have my eyes.
They work fine.
At this point,
I just have to laugh.
I recognize what...
I'm on Day 14. Like,
this is how it's going for me.
I just want to make sure
I don't get zero.
No.
All right, we're catching up.
With more time passing,
fewer tubes
are gonna be available.
It's scary
because you can sort of
feel the time running out.
Cool.
And you really don't
want to be left without any money.
You don't want to be broke
at the Survivorauction
before you even get there.
Andy, that's it.
- We found 'em all.
- That's it.
And that's a wrap from
the Survivor47 money hunt.
Sierra comes out on top,
with Andy in dead last,
as usual.
Six, seven. $140.
- $340.
- $280.
Yeah.
For a guy that
only found two tubes,
I got, like, 580 bucks here.
That's more money
than I have back home.
I got 440.
- Six sixty. - SOL: Nice.
- Nice.
One thousand sixty dollars, bro?
I'm rich.
I know. And who wants some?
Anybody?
Well done, Sierra.
Love that, Sierra.
Come on in.
Day 14 smiles.
Survivorauction.
And come on in.
We got room for everybody.
Let's have some fun today.
Welcome to the Survivorauction
for Survivor47.
This is a new-era auction,
so let me remind you
how it works.
This morning,
you had a money scramble
where you raced into the jungle
to try and find various amounts
of cash.
The reason
for the money scramble is
you all start the auction
with varying amounts of money.
So let's take a look
at who got what.
All right, most money:
Sierra. $1,060.
And it goes down from there
all the way to Andy.
Good news is, Andy,
you're not gonna lose your vote.
You got to have
the most amount of money
- at the end of the auction to lose your vote.
- Yes.
You don't have any money.
Bad news is,
- you cannot bid on any items.
- Yup.
So let's get to the items.
We have 15 items
prepared for you today.
But only the first five
are guaranteed.
- Ugh.
- The additional number
of items
will be determined by me
drawing a random number
- out of a bag between six and 15.
- Wow.
The reason this matters is
the auction will end
without warning,
and whoever has the most money
at that point in the auction
loses their vote
at the next Tribal Council.
Let's see how
many items we're gonna have.
Okay. I know the total number
of items that's going
to be in the auction.
You don't.
- So that's been determined.
- Oh, my goodness, buddy.
The question is
how many items will there be?
- Okay.
- Shall we get
this auction going?
All right.
Oh, no.
- Ugh.
- First item.
First $60 buys it.
- $60.
- $60 to Sol. Come on up.
Salted potato chips,
soft drink for 60 bucks.
That might be the best buy
of the day.
- Yeah, I think so.
- $60.
- Ooh, want me to try this, buddy?
- Try these for me, Sol.
Oh, you got it, baby.
Oh, that's a big bowl.
- That's a big bowl.
That's a big bowl.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, buddy.
Ugh.
That potato chip
right there was so money.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you so much.
Attaboy, Sol.
- Let's update the board.
- Thank you, thank you.
Sol goes from $600 to $540.
All right,
shall we get the next item?
All right.
Next item up for bid:
mac and cheese.
- All my money. All my money.
- Oh!
- $640.
- Damn it!
$640. The first bid by Teeny.
Teeny, you're gonna spend
all your money on this?
I like mac and cheese.
- $640. Sold to Teeny.
- Ugh.
- Come on up.
- Yay!
Good job, Teeny.
Here you go, dude.
It's all right.
There's more coming.
- Dip in. Have a bite of that.
- Oh, my God.
That's a big bowl, man.
Oh, my gosh. Good, Teeny.
Worth the money?
- Absolutely.
- All right, take it back.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Mac and cheese for Teeny.
- Oh, my God.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Ugh.
If only she could share.
Shall I get another item?
All right.
I'm sorry, guys.
Okay. Okay. Oh.
- I think there's a drink in there.
- The question is
am I walking gingerly
because I'm worried
about protecting
an amazing reward
or am I walking gingerly
- to sucker you in?
- Oh...
That's the question
you're gonna contemplate
as you bid on this covered item.
- $360.
- $360 to Sam.
- $560.
- $560 to Kyle.
- $800.
- $800 to Sierra.
That's it. Sierra.
Sold for $800. Come on up.
- That's good, Sierra.
- See what you bought.
- Give me the dough first.
- Okay.
All right.
This is what $800 bought you.
Chips, salsa,
guac and a margarita.
Where do you want to start?
Oh, the margarita.
Oh, my God.
Cheers, guys.
Mmm.
- Don't spill it, now.
- Oh, no!
I am having a margarita
with Jeff Probst.
This could be you
if you apply to be on Survivor.
- It's, like, I want to just take a picture.
- Do it.
- Do a selfie.
- I know. I will.
Like, if I could
seriously just be, like...
Yeah, here we go.
All right, take it back. Enjoy.
Oh, my God. Look at that guac.
That leaves you with $260.
I'm using my best acting
skills -GENEVIEVE: Yeah.
- That's what I'm worried about.
- trying to sucker you into
not knowing if that's
a really great item or not.
I think we got
to keep it covered again.
- $80.
- 80 from Gabe.
- $560 for Kyle.
- $560 to Kyle.
- Going once.
- Uh, I didn't like your acting job, Jeff.
I'll let Kyle, uh,
take the cover off.
- Let's find out.
- Hey, Jeff?
Uh, if there's meat under there,
Kyle's not gonna be able
to eat it.
Can I give you my $360
- on the shot that there's meat?
- Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
This is one item. No sharing.
Sold to Kyle.
- Go, Kyle!
- $560.
All right, talk to me
about the meat issue.
Sam said as long
- as it's not meat, you're good.
- Yeah.
So, that's... You know,
I've been a vegan for, like,
six plus years, and then
I switched to vegetarian
not long ago just so that way,
if I had the opportunity
to be here,
I could have more options
available to me.
That was part of why
you changed your diet,
was on the chance you might get on Survivor?
- Wow!
- Oh, my God.
- Ugh.
- It's very interesting,
everything you just said,
because
your reward comes with dairy,
and there is some meat.
Here's what you bought.
A giant tray of buffalo wings...
- Look at all those.
- Oh, my God.
...with ranch
and some celery and carrots.
You know, this is horrible.
Yeah.
So you're gonna take this back.
There's no sharing of items.
- Nobody can buy a buffalo wing from you.
- Okay.
I'll just take it all, you know.
- All right.
- Yeah.
I would have liked that.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, you're thinking about it.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm gonna do it.
If you're gonna do it,
let me see.
All right, so my favorite
was always the wing, right?
Oh, he's going for it.
This is a moment.
My heart's pounding right now.
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm...
Well, why are you doing it?
- I'm hungry.
- Okay.
That feeling like you're about
to do something,
and that something
might be wrong.
Good job, Kyle.
Yay, Kyle.
It's turned me into an animal.
How is it?
I'm a little d-disappointed
in myself for caving,
but if you're gonna cave,
this is a place to do it.
- Yeah.
- Good job, Kyle. - PROBST: Enjoy.
Kyle left with $20.
- Let me get another item.
- Oh, my God.
Look how many there are.
Well, if I had ever been
in Shakespeare in the park,
this is how I would do it.
Sir, I present
to you the most beautiful
of Survivorauction items.
I don't know what's in here.
If you don't like it,
I'm merely the messenger.
$660.
$660 to Gabe.
- Gabe buys it. Sold to Gabe.
- Go, Gabe.
- Good job. Good job.
- Oh, good luck, Gabe.
For all the money he has.
So the good news is
you can't lose your vote.
Well, if you're having
a bad feeling, you can trade it.
Oh, Gabe.
- Yikes.
- For this.
Yeah.
- Sticking with the fish guts.
- Sticking with the fish guts?
Okay.
What you bought was...
a very fresh... coconut
filled with very cold water.
- Oh, no, Gabe.
- All of your money.
Makes me stronger.
Sorry, Gabe.
Just like that, $660 gone.
From this point forward,
any item could be the last item,
which means
if it is the last item,
whoever has the most money after
that item loses their vote.
Sixth item in the auction.
- $380.
- $380 to Sue.
- $540.
- 540 to Sol.
Come on up, Sol.
Sold to Sol for $540.
He got the first item.
This is his second item
in the auction.
Take that from you.
This is what $540
bought you, Sol.
- Oh, you were right!
- Oh, my God.
A giant apple pie,
whipped cream,
which I will let you put on.
I got the wrong item, dude.
- Put the 47 on there?
- 47, baby.
- Doesn't have to be pretty. That looks good.
- Yeah.
- What's this?
- Well, this $60, Sol.
It's called the Survivor
cash-back program.
Some items come
with money that go back to you.
- So you will go back with $60.
- Right.
Before you do that,
take a bite of the pie.
Oh, yeah.
That's how you eat a pie
on Survivorright there.
- How delicious is it?
- Wow. - SOL: Oh, man.
Take it back.
Take your money back.
Enjoy.
So, Solomon is still in it.
If that was the last item,
Rachel, with $500,
you would have the most money
and you would lose your vote.
Okay.
- There is another item.
- Yay.
- Yeah.
- Yay!
Ooh!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, wow.
Next item up for bids
will remain covered.
- $500, Jeff.
- $500 to Rachel.
Come on up. Rachel, out of the
possibility of losing her vote,
which may be
the most important thing.
$500. Thank you.
- What's your feeling right now?
- I have a feeling
it could be bad, but
I also have a feeling that...
- It could be good?
- There might...
I might... For whatever reason,
when you came out,
I was like, "I think
there's a burger in there."
Wow.
How does this happen?
I feel like I should
take a bite, probably.
Yes, take a bite. Take a bite.
That's a
Survivorburger right there.
- Oh, my God.
- Get in there.
Oh, my God.
- Hey, Rachel.
- All right.
Take it back and enjoy.
Wow.
- Well done manifesting.
- Oh, my God.
- I just, like, felt it.
- All right.
Genevieve, at $440...
...you have the most buying
power right now in the auction,
if there's another item.
If there is not another item
and that was it,
you will lose your vote
at tonight's Tribal Council.
There is another item
- in this auction.
- Oh, my God. I thought
he said they're isn't. Sorry.
I'll go get it.
Oh, my God.
All of a sudden, I see
a tiny little piece of paper
in my fries.
And I'm just like, "What is it?
Has anyone else noticed it?
What the hell
could this be about?"
I'm sitting on the bench,
I'm eating my juicy,
delicious burger,
and all of a sudden,
I see a tiny little
piece of paper
in my fries.
Oh, my God,
Jeff put an advantage
in the auction.
But I don't know what to do.
Next item up for bid...
- All my money.
- All right, Genevieve.
Come on up.
Sold to Genevieve.
And I'm
just like, "What is it?"
You know, I can't just, like,
unroll it
and read it right then.
See what you bought.
Give me the dough first.
My heart is pounding,
and I'm waiting, and finally...
Everyone is
staring at Genevieve because
that's such a big moment.
Wow!
Genevieve.
So, I very slyly, like,
reach into my fries,
and I just, like,
go under and adjust my shirt
and stick it in my bra,
and I was like,
"I think I got away with that."
- Oh.
- Smells good.
Oh, there's, like,
a truffle in there.
Chocolate-covered strawberry.
All right,
let's update the board.
Now the person
with the most buying power
and the most risk is Sue.
So now, Sue, you are the person
with the most money.
It's the same dilemma.
At some point,
this auction is going to end,
and if it does, right now,
you will not vote
at the next Tribal Council.
Sue,
you will...
have a shot at another item.
Oh, my God.
- Wow.
- Jeff, I love you.
Oh, my God.
Look how big that is.
- It's a pizza?
- Maybe it's a pizza.
- It's probably a pizza. Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Let me start
by showing you the item.
- Oh.
- We call this
the SurvivorOutwit, Outplay,
Outbreakfast
Sunrise Spectacular.
Everything you could want
from a breakfast.
But this item is not gonna go
to the highest bidder.
Sorry, Sue.
This item comes with a price.
The price is $200.
Anybody who wants a shot
at earning this
can declare their $200
right now.
You will come up here
and compete for it.
- I'm in.
- Sue is in at $200.
Sierra's in.
- I'll go, Jeff.
- Sam is in.
Caroline in. All right,
everybody, who's in,
come up...
Sam, Caroline, Sue and Sierra.
What do you think it is?
What do they have to do?
We're about to see.
I have no clue.
So, Sue, Sam, Caroline, Sierra,
I can't think of a better way
to earn this
- than a Survivorclassic.
- What is it?
Oh, my God.
Two grubs.
This is how it's gonna work.
The first person
to get down two grubs
earns this breakfast,
and I keep your money.
I'm gonna bring you
some freshies.
Oh, they're huge.
Do it.
Ew!
Mine's crawling off the plate.
- Thanks, Sam.
- I, uh...
All right.
Sierra, take your money,
head back.
Sierra's gonna take her seat.
We are down to three.
All right, you ready to begin?
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
First to get two down
and show me an empty mouth.
Sam does one quickly.
Sue spitting hers back out.
You got to keep most of it in,
Sue, for it to count.
Caroline working on hers.
- Sam has it! Both done!
- Yay!
Sam wins.
Sue spits it back out.
Caroline seemed to enjoy it.
Nice effort from everybody.
Caroline, you will take
your $200 back.
- Sue, I'm sorry. You get your $200 back.
- Ugh.
Sam, I will keep your $200.
- Blueberry pancakes.
- This thing looks ridiculous.
Fresh from the Survivorkitchen.
It is ridiculous.
- Attaboy.
- Yay.
Sam spends $200 of his money,
and Sue with the most money.
That was... not the last item.
What?!
Next item...
Come on up.
I did it!
- Yes, yes, yes!
- A giant Survivorburrito
and iced tea.
Mmm, mmm,
mmm. Thank you, Jeff.
Next item.
I'm doing $280.
- All right, come up.
- Go, Caroline! - All right.
The good news is, with no money,
- you can't lose your vote.
- You're right.
Bad news?
Fish eyes.
Oh!
Wow.
That's how you do it
on Survivor, Caroline.
Item number 12.
- $260.
- Sierra, come on up.
See what you bought.
You are going to...
share.
You and two other players
will have
three minutes to eat.
Gabe and
Caroline, come up and join me.
All right, let's do it.
Big handfuls of peanut butter,
chunks of chocolate.
This is one of my favorite
things to watch on this show.
Oh, I'm going back in.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah!
That is it.
This item is over.
Oh, good job.
Well done.
An impressive attack on
the peanut butter and chocolate.
Well done. Well done.
Here's where we stand now.
Sam is in the lead right now
at $160.
So, Sam, if that was
the last item, $160 means
you will not vote
at the next Tribal Council.
That was the last item
of the auction.
The Survivorauction is over.
Grab your stuff and head out.
Survivorcontinues.
Thank you... so much.
- So good.
Okay, the players
are still walking off,
but if the auction looks fun,
apply to be on Survivor.
That was so fun, guys.
Congrats on
the spicy marg, dude.
- Oh, my God.
- That lost vote
just had-had my name
over it all day.
And I'm like, "I'll do anything
not to lose my vote."
- I know, I know.
- And then, it just... it kept following me.
I'm so sorry, too,
'cause I was right above you.
It sucks losing your vote.
Your vote is
your voice in the game.
And now, with 11 people left,
I can't say,
"You got my vote, man."
I just have to say,
"Sure, you have my blessing."
At the auction,
inside the fries was a note
that I desperately want to read,
but I'm very scared
to take out because
there's people everywhere.
But I finally get a moment
where I'm going to check
on my clothes
at the clothesline,
and I have a moment to myself.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Wish I would have known that
last night
when I was alone in the shelter.
Oh, my God.
This is the auction jackpot.
Like, I couldn't
have scored better.
I have been down and out
Tribal after Tribal.
So an idol would give me
the most power
that I could possibly have
in this game right now.
But there's two tarps
at this camp.
Is it at the top? Am I gonna
have to, like, climb a tree
to get to the corner
of this tarp?
My mind is just going nuts.
So, I walk by it
and kind of do, like, a...
a little corner check
and I see a tiny little lump
in the corner of the tarp.
Definitely it.
There's something in there,
but my brain is
reeling on how I'm ever
gonna get this idol.
I can't just, like,
slash the tarp,
because there are people at camp
at all times, like,
mingling around the shelter.
I want you to try
and braid my hair for funsies.
I'm thinking business
on the sides, party in front.
Sam and I... we are, like,
a very strong alliance
and, like, a duo out here.
So him losing his vote...
it's a little scary
at this time in the game.
We know we have four members
of Gata, but obviously,
you think of the numbers.
We need to recruit more.
And it just came naturally
with Lavo.
Like, I feel great with them,
I feel great connections.
So let's work together
and knock out Tuku one by one.
I think we have
all formed, like,
a great bond with all
of you, like, from Lavo.
Like, you, Sol
- and, um, Genevieve.
- Genevieve.
So it's, like, I don't want
to break any of that right now.
What, uh, so, what's our plan?
Are we just Lavo and Gata?
- I would love that.
- I know. I think right now,
we're like,
"Let's just knock out Tuku."
Well, there is a part of me,
also, that would love to,
you know,
if we're getting Tukus,
for it to be the male Tukus.
I think if Kyle loses
in an immunity challenge,
- like, that has to be our first target.
- Yeah.
I think the Gata and the Lavo
people have kind of formed
this alliance together.
And the name
that we're all throwing around
right now is Kyle
because he's won the past two
individual immunities.
So, if Kyle loses
the next challenge,
he'd be the easy decision.
I want to catch you and Caroline
specifically up on yesterday,
and I'd love, if you don't mind,
to catch up on what I missed
with you guys. Um...
You didn't miss much.
We were so focused on...
- Was it gonna be Rachel?
- Yeah.
Yeah. That would have been good.
Right now, I believe
Teeny is trying to work
with the former Gata members.
We all know
they're so charismatic,
they're so big and strong.
But they are the most dangerous
to me on this beach.
So, I'd like to shake things up
and steer the next vote
towards one
of the former Gata members.
I think Sam is charming.
But I do not want to sit
with him at the end.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
But I'd like to keep some
of those obvious targets around.
- You know what I mean?
- Yes.
I don't know how
you guys feel about that,
but I'm almost inclined to...
target, like, Rachel over Sam.
Yes.
Genevieve is a smart cookie.
She is planting the seeds
for a big move against Gata.
And I'm like, "Damn,
that's what I wanted to do."
That's exactly what
I wanted to do. Go, Genevieve.
- It's more under the radar.
- Yes. It's more
under the radar.
Genevieve and I see
Gatas are way too charismatic
and have way much control,
and one of them has to go.
Sam is an obvious choice, but
Rachel is the sneaky,
dangerous one.
I was, like, scratching my hand.
I thought I was so tan, and then
I just scratched it off,
- and I'm pale.
- It's just dirt.
I really want to get the idol.
Unfortunately, this camp has not
been empty since I got the clue.
But there was this point
where almost everybody was
in the shelter.
They were all chitchatting,
and I was like,
"I think this is my chance."
I am looking around,
trying not to look suspicious.
I don't want anybody
to know about it.
I want that power
to stay with me.
I don't want it to be exposed.
I flipped up the edge
of the tarp so I could do it
from underneath so no one
could see that it was ripped.
Oh, oh, oh.
My heart is racing.
I'm freaking out.
I'm trying to get through it.
I don't know how long
it's gonna take.
Oh, my God. I got it.
Look at this guy.
Survivorbucket list.
I genuinely can't believe
I pulled it off
in broad daylight
in front of a lot of people.
Last night, I was seconds
from being voted out, and now,
I'm holding a... an idol
that nobody knows about.
That is the epitome of, like,
aSurvivor turnaround.
Come on in.
Survivor47 down to 11.
Who will survive
to make it to ten?
All right.
Shall we get to today's
immunity challenge?
- Oh, yeah. - Yes.
- First things first.
For the second time, Kyle,
got to take back the necklace.
- Thank you.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna hold on to a handle
connected to a bucket
containing 25%
of your pregame body weight.
As your hands fatigue,
that bucket's gonna lower.
When it finally drops
and breaks your tile,
you're out.
Good news is
men and women
have won this challenge.
Better news is
one of each will win today.
Oh, my God.
The last woman left standing
and the last man left standing
-will win immunity,
-Wow.
guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be
the eighth person voted out
of Survivor47 and become
the first member of our jury.
Big stakes. We'll draw
for spots, we'll get it on.
Here we go.
All right, everybody,
grab your handles.
And pull it back toward you.
You'll hear some clicking.
This challenge is on.
Oh, my gosh.
I already feel slippy.
You are now holding a quarter
of your pregame body weight.
The good news is,
your odds are a lot better
with one man and one woman.
But still, this requires
a lot of willpower.
And already, Sam is struggling.
Come on, Sam.
Sam, you got it.
Genevieve
starting to drop a little bit.
Stop.
Sam trying to hold on.
Not looking good.
Sam, slowly...
Sam is the first person out.
Right behind, Genevieve.
Come over and take a spot
on the bench.
One man, one woman out.
Odds just got a little better.
- Oh.
- Now it's Teeny who's struggling.
Teeny drops.
- Teeny's out.
- Damn.
We're less than
one minute into this challenge.
Three people already out.
Four women left, four men left.
Sue looking good.
Rachel looks like
she's in a trance.
- Damn, I must have been heavy.
- Well, you have been
playing Survivorfor 15 days
on very little food.
No!
- No!
- Little bit of movement now from Sierra.
There it is. Sierra's out.
Gabe adjusting now.
Gabe trying to wrench it
back up. Can he do it?
Gabe. No.
Gabe is out.
Take a spot on the bench.
We are down to three men
and three women.
Two immunity necklaces
on the line, one for each.
Caroline readjusting again.
That bucket dropping.
Can Caroline get it back up?
She's trying to make a move.
Nice work, Caroline.
Push through. You got it.
Caroline
holding it off right now.
You never know
when someone else is gonna drop.
25% of your pregame body weight
is a lot.
Sol dropping a little bit.
Caroline fighting
to hang in there.
Sol fighting to hang in there.
- Caroline's out.
- Come on, Rach.
It is Sue and Rachel
in a showdown for the women.
It is Sol,
Andy and Kyle for the men.
Rachel giving everything
she's got,
trying to wrench that back up.
But it continues
to lower inch by inch.
- There she goes!
- Nice, Rach.
Rachel pulling it
back up now. - Yes!
Nice, Rachel.
Rachel settles back in now.
- Ugh!
- You got it, Sol. Fight!
Sol digging in,
but continues to drop.
Rachel is now moving, Sue is
locked in right next to her.
Sol is out.
We're down to two men
and two women.
It is Sue and Rachel.
Rachel's out. Sue,
you've won individual immunity.
You're good.
Nice going,
Andy! Come on, Andy!
We're now looking for one more.
It is Andy versus Kyle.
Kyle's won it twice.
Andy would like
to break that streak right now
and be safe tonight at Tribal.
You can't drop now.
Dig in. Find that gear
you're looking for.
Bleed, whatever it takes
to stay in this.
Come on, Andy.
Andy digging back in.
Gonna try to wrench it back up.
Can he do it?
- No way. - SOL: Nice job, dude.
- And he is.
Andy getting that bucket
back up there.
Uses a little strength
to do that.
It gives you a little
more margin for a slip later.
Ow.
Kyle's dropped a little bit.
Andy now dropping again.
Andy trying to pull it back up.
Can he do it?
- There's a little bit of yes.
- Yes, you can. - Come on, Andy.
Still dropping.
Andy drops,
Andy's out of the challenge.
Kyle wins his third
individual immunity challenge,
safe tonight
at Tribal Council with Sue.
Nice, Kyle.
Wow. Great showdown.
Great effort by everybody.
That is not an easy challenge.
- So impressive.
- Nice work. - Nice.
- Good work.
- Good job, Kyle.
Sue, come on over.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Well done.
Are those tears I see?
- I'm hugging you.
- Yeah, hug me. I love a hug.
Sue,
individual immunity is yours.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
You will see day 16
in this game.
The emotion is always personal.
- So what is it for you?
- So...
If you're just... Like,
how would this even be possible?
Because I got a bunch
of warriors over here.
So it really feels good,
but I just kept telling myself.
I kept channeling all
the strength of my whole family,
knowing that everyone
at home is rooting for me.
And they'll be so proud
of me doing this.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
That was definitely possible
'cause it happened.
You are safe tonight,
will not be going home.
- Thank you.
- Head back over.
- Good job, Sue.
- Sue!
Kyle, come on over.
- Go, Kyle.
- Hat trick.
This is becoming routine.
Third straight time this season,
individual immunity is yours.
You are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
You will see day 16.
Guaranteed a spot
in the final ten.
Head back over.
- Congrats.
- Good job, Kyle.
Proud of you, brother.
All right, so Sue is safe,
Kyle is safe. Everybody else,
Tribal Council tonight,
where somebody will be
the eighth person
voted out of Survivor47,
and you will become
the first member of our jury.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at Tribal.
I came into this game
wanting to be an inspiration
to my generation.
If I can do this against all
of these younger people,
you can, too.
Age is just a number.
Get out of your beds,
get out of your couches.
Believe in yourself
and come playSurvivor.
Kyle.
- Good work, man.
- Thank you.
Congrats, Kyle and Sue.
- Hat Trick Kyle.
- Yeah, what a battle, guys.
- So amazing.
They're making it seem like
they're happy for me,
but I know everybody here
is gonna want me out,
especially now.
This is my third
immunity win in a row.
So, as you can imagine out here,
I'm really creating a name
for myself.
This is not good.
It's good for me today,
but it could be
the death of me tomorrow.
With Kyle and Sue
off the table and safe, Gabe is,
by far, a bigger threat
than Caroline is
at this point in the game.
Here is my only thought.
- I'm a little bit more scared of Gabe.
- Same.
- Yeah.
- Do you think we need to split
or do you think
we should just keep it clean?
I think we can keep it clean.
Yeah.
Okay.
The Gata-Lavo alliance has been
a very natural and easy thing
for all of us.
And before you know it,
there ain't gonna
be any more Tuku left.
I feel like I was, like...
I just wanted
to catch up with you guys.
- Yeah.
- And it sounds like...
- I feel a little behind, that's all.
- Yeah.
You know, Andy has just been
somebody we're...
we've been keeping around
'cause he's still
in Sam and I's pocket.
He's just, like, an easy number
that we could use.
He's not a threat,
he's not somebody
I'm worried about in the game.
So I'm, like, you know,
might as well drag him along
a little longer until, you know,
we can no longer tolerate him.
But we just want to make sure
- that you're still strong with us.
- I am.
- And, like, that we still have you locked in.
- Yeah.
- You swear?
- Yes, that is... I swear, that is...
- I'm still your island sister?
- Island sister, yeah.
Sam and Sierra still feel like
they own me, and they have me
in their pockets.
They look at me
as an expendable piece,
and as sort of a weak player.
He came over to
me, and he was like, "I'm having
a really bad day,"
and I'm, like...
I just feel like the guy's had
a series of bad days.
- It's really sad.
- I know.
And so, for me,
that's enough to just cut bait.
Like, goodbye.
I feel like this is my, like,
She's All That makeover moment.
I'm starting this game
just like,
"Oh, hi, I'm Andy.
Like, please like me.
"Um, Sierra and Sam,
like, you're the cool kids.
Like, can you... can I sit
at your lunch table?"
And now I'm at the merge.
And I'm getting a lot cooler
and, like, I don't need
to wear these freaking glasses
anymore, and
I could be...
the Andy that
I believe myself to be.
I could be my full version
of myself.
And I can turn into the pivotal
player in this post-merge.
Sam and Sierra.
- And so...
- You don't have to work with them anymore.
Let's do it.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Yeah. It's looking really good.
I can make my
own lunch table. Sam, Sierra
and Rachel... they're gonna be
shocked by the new Andy.
They're not gonna
see me coming, and...
that was stupid.
Like, I've been doing a lot.
I've been doing a lot
behind their backs.
I feel like I'm a Lavo.
I love hearing that.
I want to build
an alliance with myself,
Lavo and Tuku, and I think
splitting up Sam and Sierra
is of the utmost importance.
They're gonna be like,
"Damn, Andy did that. Our Andy?
Wait, no.
He was gonna be our goat."
- I'm looking to change my fate.
- Yeah.
Just have a number of people
who we're actually working with.
- Yeah. That's awesome.
- Yeah.
We can just line 'em up
and take 'em all out
one by one, you know.
- That's promising. I'm down for that.
- I mean...
It is perfect, a chef's kiss.
You know, however many
Gata he wants to turn on,
that works for me.
- I feel pretty good that he's voting with us.
- Yeah. Yeah.
That's the question.
I don't know.
I think Sam's more of a
physical threat, but she is...
- The social game's the dangerous part.
- Yeah.
I see Sierra
as the head of the snake
right now
of Gata, and it's fitting,
because Gata's logo is a snake.
So, I mean, there you go.
You know, I think it'll be
a good time to disarm 'em.
And whether
it's Sam or Sierra or...
Like, how do you feel
about that?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- You're in?
- Yeah.
If there are
eight people strong,
being the four Tukus,
the three Lavos
and Andy,
Sierra will be out of the game.
I think the easy thing
to do, which we could all, like,
see right now is to work with
the Gatas and get a Tuku out.
Right? Like, Gabe,
because whatever. Um...
I kind of want
to work with the Gata...
- Not the Gata, but Tuku.
- Tuku?
- Yeah.
- Me, too.
Would you rather lose Sam,
Sierra or Rachel?
I think it would be Sierra.
Right now
I'm in sort of a pickle where
Sierra is somebody who I feel
like I'm very good friends with.
Working with her in this game
is something I want to do.
But I don't want to
take the reins and be
too pushy about anything.
Are you gonna be choked?
I know you're tight
with Sierra and Sam.
- Like, honestly.
- Um...
- Okay.
- I'm tight with Sierra.
So I would want Sam to be
the Gata who goes home tonight.
My hope is that I can convince
everybody to vote Sam out.
I am very, very scared of him.
He's the bigger threat.
As far as this vote goes, like,
if I had my way,
it would be Sam.
You want Sierra out over Sam?
'Cause that's not my preference.
Sam is the biggest threat
of the three of them.
I think he's the head
of the Gata snake.
I think he is charming.
He gets everybody laughing.
Sam?
Agreed.
- Hey, hey.
- Look at that.
My vote's going on Sam tonight.
That's for sure.
I'd like to break up Sam
and Sierra, but...
If they're nervous
and they have an idol,
they wouldn't play it on Rachel.
- Right.
- She's not in their duo.
Rachel may be the easier one
to go for 'cause
they would never
play it on Rachel.
Voting out Gatas
is in almost everyone's
best interest.
I personally would
love Rachel to leave.
I think she's the best player
in this game right now.
I think she is the most
dangerous. I want her gone.
- I would like Rachel.
- Yeah.
Genevieve would like Rachel.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why? About where everyone is?
I know it's weird
that everyone's, like, gone.
Something just doesn't
feel right to me.
I want to feel good
in this kind of Gata-Lavo,
like, union.
But they're still having a lot
of conversations with people.
You just don't
know what's gonna happen, but
what I do know
is that I have an idol
that nobody knows about.
Now, it's, like,
the pressure's on
that I know when and if
I need to play it.
I want to go Rachel.
I've put too much damn work
in helping out Rachel
to have her go home tonight.
I just want
to split up that duo.
Rachel can be someone
we can use.
Rachel's my
ultimate preference to go home.
But there are many different
cooks in the kitchen,
and we want different things.
If you ask Teeny,
she wants Sam out.
Sol wants Sierra out,
and I would take out Rachel.
She's a strategic thinker,
she's social.
I see her as a huge threat.
And in this group
that will be voting together,
what are the odds
all eight of us
are gonna be like,
"Hey, yeah, that's the target,
we all agree"?
Slim to none.
So this is it.
This is the group
that will define Survivor47.
Because at the very least,
you all will
have a say in who wins,
if not be one of the people
vying for it at the end.
So, Sam,
where is the game right now
and where do you think
it's heading?
The game is...
waiting for war,
and you don't want to be the one
that's still getting ready
while everybody else
is already in battle.
Gabe, agree?
I mean, is there
a war coming? Sure.
Survivoris a war.
It always is, but
there's a lot
of moving parts, and
folks were lied to today,
but that's what
Tribal Council's for.
Your pen goes to parchment,
and it reveals
your true intentions.
Andy, how about for you?
Well, I'm glad everyone's
still getting ready for war.
I got two votes at the last
Tribal Council I attended,
so, I'm under attack already.
Like, the battle cries
are sounding.
Like, I'm at war.
And so, we're trying to see
what factions are linking up
and what factions
are gonna be left
to be vulnerable
to this first attack, which is
tonight, which is a big night.
Gabe?
Just to stick
with our war analogy...
that seems to be the theme
of Tribal Council tonight.
- It's working.
- Yeah.
So, Christmas Day
of World War I, I believe,
there was a ceasefire,
and both sides came together,
and they played a game
of soccer.
And then the very next day,
they just went back to
throwing bullets at each other.
And that's what auction day
kind of felt like.
- Yeah, you're right.
- It felt like
we all had a ceasefire.
And then, the next morning,
you wake up, and
shots start firing again.
Teeny, why were you nodding?
What was it
about what Gabe said?
You know, we've all enjoyed
these milestones
of Survivortogether...
making the merge,
making the jury, at this point.
The next goal
is making it to the end.
So, yeah, we're friends, but
it's not a game of friends.
It's a game of Survivor.
And there's only one winner.
Genevieve, is a group
this large just as scary if not
scarier than a group of five?
Yeah,
because in a group of five,
to have a majority,
you need three,
which means you need
to rely on two people.
In a group this big, you need
to rely on many more people.
And relying on anyone
but yourself is...
treacherous in Survivor.
And Sierra,
to Genevieve's point,
there's also trust.
You can have all the numbers
stored perfectly,
but if the information's bad,
- then the numbers are bad.
- Jeff,
school didn't come
that easy to me.
And keeping all these numbers
and names and, like,
putting all the pieces
together... it's something that
is really taking a toll on me
mentally, 'cause I'm like,
"Oh, my gosh, how do you
keep track of all this?"
But as far as tonight goes,
we will see
where our trust lies,
short-term and
long-term alliances, you know,
starting from back
when it was just Gata,
but also now,
we all have new alliances.
And truthfully, I think tonight
is, like, a huge outcome
of what the rest of the game
will look like.
Sam, you were nodding.
- You agree?
- Yeah, I do.
It's a lot more difficult
to be a shepherd
when you got more animals
to keep track of.
It's scary.
You want to have your finger
on the pulse of the game,
vote or no vote.
Like, you want
to feel like you know
where things are kind of headed.
But you start to wonder like,
"Is there something
I'm missing?"
Kyle, if the
vote goes the way you think
it's gonna go, will it be about
a group, an alliance
getting their way,
or is it taking out
a threat in the game?
We're all
standing here like a bunch
of gladiators
ready to brawl in an arena.
I think that if you
stand out as a threat,
then you're probably
going to get hit.
So it's, like, in a sick way,
almost a compliment,
saying, like,
"Hey, like, you're really good
at this game,
and I need you to not be."
Caroline,
- you agree with that?
- Absolutely.
I honestly think, at this point,
if you're targeted,
it's a huge sign of, like,
respect and admiration.
Andy, how
certain are you that you know
where the vote is going?
Um... I have a plan.
I have a name in mind,
and I do feel pretty confident
that that is what's
gonna happen.
Now, that's not always
been the case.
Actually, you know,
my last Tribal Council,
I felt confident,
and I was surprised.
Point being,
people will be left out
and be upset.
All right, group question.
How many people here
are uncomfortable
that you could be
completely wrong?
So, nobody here
really has any certainty.
Teeny, is this
an obvious question
or does it speak
to where this game is right now?
I mean, there's never
any certainty at Tribal Council,
and if you feel it,
then you should be
in trouble, and you usually are.
But especially
at an 11-person Tribal Council,
where we have not truly
tested our trust
with each other.
And I think it's monumental,
because it's an indicator
of what to come.
What happens tonight
is really going to show
that, you know, there's a level
of play going on here
that we haven't yet seen.
All right, it is
time to vote.
Sol, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Jeff?
I thought I knew
what was going on
coming into this Tribal tonight,
but the longer
the Tribal went on,
the more this feeling of dread
filled my stomach. Um,
and I was supposed
to go home last Tribal,
and I don't want any
shoulda, coulda, wouldas, so,
- Good for you.
- I played my Shot in the Dark.
Ooh. Ooh.
Oh.
Thank you.
So, Rachel played
her Shot in the Dark, which means
there is no vote in here
from Rachel.
If this says you're safe,
then any votes cast
for Rachel will not count.
Rachel, you are...
...not safe.
Any votes cast
for Rachel will still count.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sam.
Gabe.
Sam.
Two votes Sam.
Sierra.
- Wow.
- Two votes Sam,
one vote Gabe, one vote Sierra.
Sam.
That's three votes Sam,
one vote Gabe, one vote Sierra.
Sierra. That's three votes Sam,
two votes Sierra, one vote Gabe.
Sam. That's four votes Sam,
two votes Sierra,
one vote Gabe.
Sierra.
- Wow.
- That's four votes Sam,
three votes Sierra,
one vote left.
Sierra.
We're tied.- ...
Wow.
Sam and Sierra
both have four votes,
so we're gonna revote.
But this is a unique situation
that needs an explanation.
Typically, when you have
two players who are tied,
they don't vote simply because
they can only vote
for each other,
so their votes
nullify each other.
That's the only reason
they don't vote.
That's not the case tonight.
Sam, you don't have a vote.
You didn't cast a vote. Sierra
does, and she did cast a vote.
So, Sierra,
you will vote in the revote.
- Wow.
- So everybody will vote
except Sam and Rachel,
who played her Shot in the Dark.
And you can only vote
for Sierra or Sam.
All right, Sol, you're up.
Will you come grab the urn?
I acknowledge
I'm doing you dirty,
but I'm a dirty player.
I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sam.
Sierra. One vote Sam,
one vote Sierra.
Sierra. Two votes Sierra,
one vote Sam.
That's three votes Sierra,
Sierra. That's four votes
Sierra, one vote Sam.
Eighth person
voted out of Survivor47
and the first member
of our jury: Sierra.
That's five. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Yeah.
If I'm the biggest threat
sitting here, it's pretty...
- I'm pretty honored, so, thank you.
- Good game.
Well done, guys.
Sierra, the tribe has spoken.
- Can I have a hug?
- Course.
Pleasure having you out here.
- Oh. Bye, Sierra.
- Bye, Sierra.
See you, Sierra.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
I have a vendetta.
It's time to cause
chaos.
Next time onSurvivor...
It's an absolute mess.
I think
you blow up everybody's game.
This is nightmare fuel.
You know, I couldn't tell you
what happened.
I'm completely blindsided.
I'm typically somebody
who picks up on cues,
and there was no sign.
So, I'm out here
with some really great liars.
You know, I gave it my all,
and I had a blast out here.
But I do have a big job
ahead of me,
being the first member
of the jury,
and I'm gonna be a pretty
friggin' tough judge now.