Welcome to Survivor 47.
(cheering)
Previously on Survivor...
I was gonna--
I was gonna tell you.
-I went to Towson, bro.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, dude.
CAROLINE: The guys fell
in love with each other.
It's a bromance.
TK:
"I caught you in the act."
So now I know
I can't fully trust him.
That scares me.
GABE:
Now I have power.
I'm a dragon sitting on top
of a pile of gold.
AYSHA:
We saw Rome at the water well.
That is just
suspicious behavior.
You seem emotional.
I crack open a coconut
and they didn't cheer for me.
They cheered for Jon.
(cheering)
That's a good-ass coconut.
Give me some.
They don't like me.
Right now I would vote Jon.
Jon is playing hard.
RACHEL:
Andy is a ticking time bomb,
and you don't know
when it's gonna explode.
First person voted
out of Survivor 47: Jon.
The tribe has spoken.
♪ ♪
It's gorgeous.
There, that reminds me
of Phoenix sunrises.
Tribe morale is
through the roof.
You know, if you realize
you're on a winning tribe,
it feels absolutely incredible.
And in the morning we were
all chilling on the beach,
and the first thing
that goes through my mind is,
I need to go and read
exactly what that box says
because I got the key
for the Beware Advantage.
And so, last night...
...I dug it up,
and once I opened it...
it was pitch black.
I felt the scroll
and I felt the idol.
So I said,
"You know what?
I need to hide this box."
After I re-hid the box,
I started really thinking,
I don't think it's actually
smart to keep it to myself.
Maybe it's actually better if I
let someone else know about it.
That way
they can trust me more.
And Teeny--
she's the vibe
that I'm looking for
in an alliance member,
someone that I can trust
in this game
one million percent.
TEENY: My first thought
when Rome tells me
he has the advantage is,
"Damn it."
Rome was the person
who everybody wanted out,
but it's never that easy.
It was pitch black,
so we couldn't see
what he had to do
to get the idol.
All we could do was
just feel the idol.
(chuckles)
And then go back.
So that changes
the plan that I wanted to do,
and now I sort of have
to work with Rome, but
I'm gonna tell Kishan.
-Let me tell you something.
-Okay, go for it.
-He found it.
-(gasps)
He found it, and he told me.
I don't know why he told me,
but he fully found it.
-What?
-He told me,
and he showed me where it is.
Down-- Oh, oh, come here,
come here, come here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
The text.
KISHAN:
Oh, so that's what...
-Hey.
-TEENY: Hey.
I got caught
with a giant box holding
the biggest secret of the game
wide open.
But one of my superpowers,
I feel, is being able to talk my
way out of any situation.
I just want to say,
like, I told him
because I want to work
with this four.
-Okay.
-Like, and that's,
and that's something
I should have discussed with you
and, like, would have,
but I got excited about the box.
That's the truth.
ROME:
When I saw them at my box,
I'm thinking, like,
"What are you doing?" Like,
100%, I don't know
if I can trust Teeny
as much as I could yesterday.
When I was finally able
to read what was in this box
with them,
I was so disappointed.
This box said,
"You can take it right now,
"and it's good
for one Tribal Council,
"or you can take this other
note, do another thing,
and then your idol is good
for three Tribal Councils."
What about a normal idol?
I took the idol
that's good for only one,
and I played it safe.
TEENY:
Yeah, that's why I was like...
ROME: Now they both know,
guaranteed, Rome is not gonna be
the first one gone from Lavo,
and that is a great feeling.
♪ ♪
GABE:
Look at that. Oh.
Huge crab.
Oh, my God, should we grab it?
(Caroline squeals)
Oh, my gosh.
TIYANA:
Yeah, the pinchers are huge.
GABE:
Oh, I got him,
I got him, I got him.
SUE:
Oh, my goodness.
TIYANA:
Gabe has caught the biggest crab
I think I've ever seen
in my life.
-TK: That's a boy.
-SUE: Let's go.
That's-- need that right there.
That's a good start to the day.
SUE:
I'm gonna head back,
though, I'm sweating.
GABE:
Found a whole beach over here.
TK:
Oh, my God.
-It's like you're in heaven.
-This is crazy.
-Yeah.
-(laughs)
-Wow, this is kind of wild, man.
-If only heaven wasn't
90 degrees and humid.
TK: I came into this game
knowing that
I wanted to at least bring
a strong three to the merge.
-Can't see that.
-The wave that's breaking
-right there?
-Yeah.
Wow.
Kyle is my number one.
Honestly,
he seems super genuine.
I trust this guy
with my life right now.
Gabe, you need to talk
to some people
'cause I-I know...
I don't think
anybody's mentioned, like,
"Oh, I got a really good
relationship with Gabe" yet.
-Yeah.
-TK: Gabe--
"idol-hunting Gabe"--
was initially the strong part of
our three,
but he's been playing
a very erratic game.
You don't have to have,
like, a strategy talk, just...
Yeah, yeah, start forming
that relationship.
TK:
And I don't want to have my game
hanging on the heels
of somebody else who,
right now, I can't, quite
frankly, trust all the way.
Oh, look,
all these hermit crabs.
-Those two.
-Yeah, yeah.
I've been wanting
to talk to Tiyana
for some time
because I think she has
a better ability
to actually connect
with people, something that Gabe
has not been doing
on this tribe.
No, I was just trying to gauge
how you felt
about who you felt about here
that you feel strongly
-like you could
actually do something with.
-Right.
Obviously I-- looking at it
right now, I'm, like, worried
-about a bromance with you guys.
-Yeah.
I never want to be like,
"Oh, okay,"
like, the bromance and then
I'm the fourth, you know,
-'cause that kind of sucks.
-Yeah, yeah.
There's not, like, a bromance
thing happening right now.
TIYANA: I am absolutely
surprised to hear that TK
wants to actually work with me
because, so far,
there's a huge divide
when it comes
to the girls and guys.
-Gabe has already been doing
a lot of...
-stuff.
-Right.
So, I don't feel comfortable
with that.
I really like you,
I really like Kyle, so,
if you, me and Kyle
can figure out
a way for us to just lock down
us as a three,
I'm super comfortable with that.
-Straight up?
-Yeah.
I think that's a great idea.
Okay, I'm glad
we're on the same page.
TIYANA: I am elated
that Gabe actually
kind of shot himself in the foot
because he went off
doing sketchy things,
and a bromance can only
go so far if the bros
don't even trust another bro.
That's not a bromance.
Yeah, Kyle, so, I called Tiya,
and you and I talked,
and I let you know,
like, I really bang
with your vibe,
and you're a cool dude,
and I trust you,
and I would like to have three
people that we can all lock in.
KYLE:
That's how I feel as well.
I think that you're
a real good person,
and I think that
the way that-- that we jive,
that there's--
there's a longevity to it.
-TIYANA: Oh, absolutely, dude.
-It's-- You know?
And I think
that we're very valuable
-to one another.
-TK: Hell yeah.
TIYANA:
I really feel like Kyle is
a genuine soul, and so Kyle
is someone that I think I could
really lean on in this game.
TK:
We can make it work, bro.
ANDY: Day three was one
of the most tumultuous days
of my life,
but now that I'm here
and I actually survived
the Tribal Council,
I just feel like this is
such an amazing opportunity
for a recovery.
I know my role right now,
in a good way.
-It makes me happy.
-Yeah, it's good.
I want to be a lightning rod.
I am feeling a lot better
in a lot of ways,
and I feel
like they're including me,
which is the first step
of improving your position,
is having people include you
in the social vibe of the tribe.
-Let's get it, Andy.
-Ooh, that's a good one.
The layers to Survivor
are mind-boggling.
Like, Andy wants
something from us.
He wants connection,
he wants to feel included.
We want something from him.
We want him to be
in a good mindset,
we want him to perform
in challenges,
but we also want him
to be the easy boot.
(singsongy):
Here we go, Andy, here we go.
Right now everybody on Gata
is trying to make Andy feel
as part of our group
as possible.
-Yes, we see it!
-SIERRA: Yeah!
(whooping)
Let's go...!
RACHEL:
Let's go, Andy!
That's the perfect coconut.
-Thank you.
-It is.
ANIKA:
It's very obvious that Andy--
he needs words of affirmation.
SIERRA: Yeah, you get on that,
you have that.
-ANIKA: That's a good one.
-(Sam whoops)
ANIKA:
I've met a variety
of different kinds of men
on dating apps
and, specifically for Andy,
you can just tell it's giving
toxic, clingy boyfriend.
Yeah.
SAM:
I'm looking forward
to just not doing anything next.
ANDY:
Yeah.
You know, the thing is,
facing death
and being the first boot
and surviving has put me in
a completely different mindset.
I have this just
totally new game plan.
I could never...
SAM:
Right now I'm on Andy duty,
like, just keeping
a watchful eye
on him at all times
because an idol is the
number one thing that is causing
paranoia around Gata right now.
I don't know,
I think they went by the rocks.
I wonder what they have to talk
about for a long time.
-Girl stuff.
-(laughs)
-Talking about their hair.
-Yeah.
ANIKA:
I feel like it's in, like,
a crook of a tree
-or it's at, like,
the base of a tree.
-RACHEL: Yeah.
RACHEL:
Yeah, I mean, it's this
tiny piece of parchment, right?
I can't find anything ever.
I'm like,
"Where's my hairbrush?"
What about Beware?
Sh-Should I look or no?
-Like, I don't think
you should, because
-I agree.
-a lost vote right now, like...
-That's just the...
-Yeah.
-All right.
SAM: Andy is an oddball,
and it would be very easy for me
to kick Andy to the curb.
-I got you. You know I got you.
-Let's go. Yeah.
SAM:
But in sports reporting,
relationships and lines
of communication are key.
You are just as valuable to me.
-Yeah.
-Heck yeah.
I want to be Andy's buoy
in an ocean
where he feels
like he's drowning.
If I can have Andy feeling
like he can come
to me with information,
that allows me options
because you never know when
the athlete who's at the bottom
of the totem pole
is at the top of the totem pole
because they're the hero
in the game.
-My mom's gonna love you.
-Good, I-I--
I'm gonna love your mom.
Okay.
(sighs)
When Sam was gone,
I'm just left alone
and my brain starts spiraling.
What's going through my mind is,
"Okay, there are some options."
I could just chill here,
make sure that they see me
not going off, make sure
my target doesn't grow.
Or
put my pedal to the metal
and find this advantage.
I do not feel
like I have much time.
I feel like Sam and the women
will come back to camp,
really, at any minute.
Really, the clock was ticking.
SAM:
I went to the bathroom,
came back, no Andy.
I looked behind me, no Andy.
I looked in the bushes, no Andy.
Uh-oh.
Andy was gone.
It's like the babysitter
takes their eyes
off the baby,
and then, all of a sudden,
the house is on fire.
(chuckles)
Oh...
The Beware Advantage gives you
a huge decision
with two options.
You can either open it
and take that risk or
leave it and potentially wait
for better timing.
(sighs)
I'm gonna do something new.
I'm gonna try it out.
I'm gonna leave it for now.
I don't think
anyone else is looking.
I'm gonna brainstorm
what I'm gonna do with it.
I have an opportunity
that not many people have taken.
If I know
where the-the advantage is,
and if and when I need an idol,
I can pull the trigger.
Everybody thinks
they'd be a great player,
but there's only
one way to find out.
Apply to be on Survivor.
AYSHA:
Having the camp supplies
has been everything.
We did so much with
nothing for three days,
and now we have an axe,
we have a saw,
we have a hammer,
we just got flint.
AYSHA: So, of course,
Rome needs to be
the person in charge.
AYSHA: He wanted
to be the first one
to make fire.
I tried. I was good
at, like, sparking it,
but I couldn't-- I wasn't
great at building it up.
ROME:
Yeah, I made a fire
every single morning
till I came out here.
So, my record is 16 seconds
to get a fire.
-(Rome laughs)
-KISHAN: I think
Rome's a showman.
That's what he does for
a living. He's a commentator.
This looks incredible.
KISHAN:
He has a bucket list
he came in with.
He wants to make the fire.
He wants to be the one
finding the idol.
He loves the big, flashy moves.
AYSHA:
Try scraping, if you can.
-ROME: Oh, wow. That's
-AYSHA: Yeah.
way different with a machete.
KISHAN:
My strategy-- it's completely
the opposite of that.
I think the more low key
you are, the better,
because, you know, you skate
under the radar.
ROME:
I mean, I think that's enough.
AYSHA:
Nope.
Right there, right there!
-Yes! Kishan! Oh, my goodness.
-KISHAN: Yes.
-There we go, baby.
-Yes.
Besides,
he didn't make the fire.
I made the fire.
KISHAN: Yeah!
SOL: I've never, ever met
anybody like Rome.
-(chortles)
-SOL: Rome is... He's a lot.
Definitely had, like,
aspirations to go,
like, to the NBA.
I did not
have the height,
but I had the speed.
-Like--
-Why didn't you get drafted?
I stopped playing. I stopped
playing in high school.
TEENY: He is just
a little bit cocky.
I always knew, like,
on the low, I could probably
be a rapper
if I really wanted to.
♪ It's been a couple years,
couple stories ♪
♪ A couple smiles. ♪
Uh... uh...
Like, I forgot it
in my head now.
Yeah, I always wish
that I taught myself
all the Michael Jackson moves.
That, like...
Do, like, that.
AYSHA: You want to be
-the one from our season?
-ROME: Yeah.
TEENY: When you're spending
sunrise to sunset with somebody,
it's impossible to ignore it.
(imitates screeching
connection tone)
-(laughs)
-TEENY: It's tempting to just
want to get him out of here,
but Rome has an idol.
If he didn't have it,
he'd be the easy first boot.
So, Rome, right now-- he's
going to be the problem for me.
-I mean...
-(Aysha and Teeny exclaim)
(Rome laughs)
Andy left.
He went looking.
I-I go to the bathroom.
I come back, he's gone.
ANIKA: Sam was babysitting Andy
because we need
to make sure that
he has no chance
of finding
any sort of advantage.
That could mess up
our whole entire plan.
I don't think he found anything.
I need to make sure that
we find it before Andy.
So I suggest to Sam...
What if went--
go looking right now?
Okay.
Anika and I go off
under the guise of filling up
waters for everybody,
which very quickly
turns into a full-on idol hunt.
(groans)
SAM:
You get out here, it is
a massive, massive island.
And you're looking
for something about
yea big.
Like, this tree looks like
a great spot, but...
ANIKA:
I don't think they would
put it in this spot. Yeah.
Yeah, you took it, you took it.
You got it.
SAM:
I'm taking it.
There wasn't really
a second thought.
Like, get the idol.
Get yourself
more power in this game.
ANIKA:
What's going through
my head is, "Thank God
I was there with him."
Head straight to the path.
ANIKA:
Sam is already a threat
without this advantage. This
advantage only makes him
even more of a threat.
(exclaims)
-That's a lock.
-That's it,
-that's it, that's it.
-I think this is a clue.
ANIKA:
We find a map, and
there's a red X
where the key could be,
and it's pointing
to the set of trees
near the water well.
So, we go, sprinting.
We're also carrying
every single person's
water bottle at this point.
(laughs) Like...
-That they're bringing.
-The-- Oh, I know.
Hopefully they come back.
I'm, like, thirsty.
-You got it? Got it?
-This rope.
-SAM: Oh, yeah.
-ANIKA: I find a rope,
and then we pull out this rope
to only discover...
-Oh, my God.
There's a lot of this.
-Okay.
...that there are maybe 300...
knots tied next to each other.
SAM:
Dude, there are so many.
We kind of realize
that this is going to take
a very long time.
We've been gone for a while.
-Yeah.
-SAM: This cannot be done
right now.
I will have to
find time to come back
and complete this later.
But Anika being there with me
is, like, a nightmare.
I don't want to have
a secret with Anika
that I'm not telling Sierra.
Holy crap, bro.
Let's go.
Sierra is my number one,
and I don't want her
ever thinking
I'm withholding
a major piece of information
from her.
Had I found it by myself,
maybe it's a different story.
I don't love that Anika knows.
SIERRA:
I don't love that either.
Because if Anika knows,
I'm worried that Anika's gonna
tell Rachel, and then
that looks bad on me.
-I don't know
if she's gonna tell Rachel.
-Okay,
she's probably
gonna tell Rachel.
Okay.
Pretend that
you don't know anything.
SAM:
Anika knowing
complicates things,
because if Anika has already
told Rachel,
I need to tell Rachel myself.
I need your help.
Where'd you find it?
There's a bunch of knots
around the roots
-of those trees
in the back left.
-Okay.
-A ton of knots.
-Let's go.
SAM:
Because if Rachel
finds out from Anika
and I'm still lying about it
to Rachel's face--
bad, bad look for me.
RACHEL: Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
ANDY:
It's only been a few hours since
I found this Beware Advantage.
So, I'm thinking,
"Okay, maybe I should just
go for it
and go get this thing."
For a player like me,
in this position,
an idol would mean
a hell of a lot.
And so now I feel like
it would be optimal
for me to go ahead
and grab this.
You know, it is
a ticking time clock.
Someone could find it.
And so I go
to my secret hiding spot.
I'm thinking I kind of forgot
which branch it was on.
I see the branch where it was.
(groans)
It is not there.
And I am overcome
with a sense of panic.
Oh, this is not good.
What I thought was
a safety net is not only
gone and out of my hands, but
is in the hands
of somebody else.
RACHEL:
Let's go!
-There we go.
-Oh, my God.
There we go.
We got it.
Finally, Rachel and I
get to the key to unlock
the box.
Um, I'm not
feeling good right now.
I have to think about things.
Oh, boy.
-Okay, let's talk.
-Okay.
ANDY:
Sam-- he is my one foothold
to get back into this game.
And so my gut is saying
I can trust him.
So, like, two hours ago,
I found but did not take
the Beware Advantage.
-You found it?
-Yeah, but I didn't take it.
-Oh, you left it?
-Yeah. Didn't want--
I didn't want to lose my vote.
So, I stashed it.
SAM:
I was in musical theater,
and it's not for my singing.
Like, I can act a little bit,
but I was not ready
for the bomb that Andy
was about to drop.
SAM:
He says one of the girls found
the Beware Advantage.
Music to my ears, Andy.
I think you're right.
They're up to no good.
They've got something.
Damn.
-I think it's okay.
-ANDY: With Sam, I am
telling him this
valuable information
in order to build
the trust I need.
I feel kind of bad
because I'm sitting there
with the key in my sock.
But as silly as Andy might feel
losing a Beware Advantage,
he took a huge leap of faith
coming to me
with this information.
-I trust you.
-Yeah, dude, I got you, 100%.
This is starting
to make me feel
like I can actually trust Andy
moving forward.
TK: Now, obviously, us three
and Gabe are probably set
to not be gone early.
Uh, so,
I just want to see w--
if we're really--
if we could gauge this out.
If we were to say right now,
if we lose next challenge,
who do we think
in this situation we're going?
It's, like,
a toss-up between, like...
TK:
Sue and Caroline.
I just don't think Sue
brings anything to the table.
Gabe.
-I'm moving slow today.
-TK: It's-it's all good.
Take your time, bro.
GABE: TK, Kyle, and Tiyana--
I think they all think
I'm kind of just
a quiet guy and I really
haven't found my place,
socially, with everybody.
We were just trying to figure
out, you know, generally...
GABE:
Uh-huh.
...how we were thinking
about the other two.
-GABE: Yeah.
-But I don't know.
Yeah. I'm down with it.
TK:
The-- This is the four, bro.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm totally cool with that.
They pitched the idea to me
of "this is our four,"
and I think that
they believe that
I'm in with them.
This is our four.
But
that four is not my four.
Caroline and Sue
are way more attractive to me
as alliance partners
than the other three are.
We need to put something
in our stomachs.
GABE:
They're on the bottom right now.
These are wounded birds,
and I want
to bring these birds in,
'cause people who feel like
they're on the bottom--
they're desperate.
Me and Sue are pretty locked in
as number ones.
So, the next
wounded bird
I need to go get is Caroline.
I think TK and Kyle
are way closer with each other
than either of them
are with me,
and the only person
I've talked any s--
real strategy with is Sue.
I feel like
you're a genuine person.
I really want to work with you.
You, me and Sue--
-we can run this thing.
-Okay.
I have zero
working relationship with Gabe.
I just graduated
from business school.
I'm not an idiot. I don't
believe him for a second.
So, I have no trust
in him whatsoever.
I want to work with you.
-Mm-hmm.
-We have a lot of potential.
-Uh-huh. Yeah.
-It's not here yet.
But I don't feel like
I have that thing
where I can, like...
I don't know.
It's just not clicking
-Yeah.
-as much as I want it to.
GABE:
I'm surprised by just
how skeptical Caroline is of me.
And I know I have to squash
that as soon as I possibly can.
So,
at that moment,
I make the call
to pull my idol out
and show her.
(mutters)
Yeah, that's it.
And then he shows me
his idol.
Hey, good job.
-It's huge.
-Thank you.
CARLOLINE:
This is such a weird
show of trust.
So, I actually think
maybe there's a world where
Gabe and I can work together.
-He told me he has it.
-Yeah?
-He has the idol.
-Okay.
-He told me, too. Okay.
-Oh, my God.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-So...
-Interesting.
-Yeah.
I want to be cautious,
but I'm optimistic.
But I-I definitely
think we're good.
I mean, I think
as long as me, you and Gabe
can stay strong,
we're gonna be okay.
Nobody knows that
Caroline, myself, and Gabe
are in an alliance.
And I think that's a big deal.
How are you guys feeling?
SUE:
I'm-I'm really excited.
Yeah.
I agree. I like it.
I have Sue and Caroline.
They're my little birds, right?
And I'm gonna
make 'em warm.
I'm gonna make 'em feel
good and safe.
-CAROLINE: How are you
feeling, Gabe?
-Feel good.
Feel like I'm in a good place.
Yeah, you are.
You are.
GABE:
And if I can sit at
the end with Caroline and Sue,
write me the check.
-Sue.
-Yes?
-How you doing?
-I'm a little--
I'm feeling tired, so
I'm trying to take a little nap.
Hopefully we'll have a down day
on the beach
-and I can fall asleep, right?
-KYLE: Yeah.
SUE:
Sometimes we need a nice break
from the game.
So, Tiyana, myself,
TK and Kyle-- we all felt like
we needed to take, like,
an hour or so nap on the beach.
It's much more comfortable
than our bamboo.
The reason I don't like Florida,
to be honest with you, bro,
is there's too much wildlife out
there that can kill you, bro.
I'm good off of that.
-Aw...
-I just-- Godzilla comes
out the bush, bro.
Like, the biggest alligator
I've ever seen in my life, bro,
comes out the bush.
-Godzilla.
-That was Godzilla, bro.
You can't tell me
it wasn't, bro.
Like, yeah, bro.
Oh, yeah, bro.
Yeah, that's crazy, bro.
So, if you want to go...
SUE:
But TK didn't stop talking
the whole time.
Bro, Super Bowl
was in Vegas last year--
Or this--
this February was in Vegas.
And, bro, it was
so many people there, bro.
Like, Big Bear is fire, bro.
It's, uh...
'Cause that's why
I like Cali, bro.
'Cause you can
literally get anything...
-Influencers, bro.
He's not fighting real fighters.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
-You know what I mean? Like...
SUE:
I'm trying
not to be annoyed at TK,
but two people
are trying to sleep
and he's just talking loud.
And it's just that overpowering
male dominant
-bro energy.
-Yeah, just, like,
come in and get me
out of there, bro.
Like, this has got to be some
backhand strategical move, bro.
SUE:
These bastards,
they don't even realize
that I am somebody
to begin with.
I have the best job ever
out of all of them.
I'm a pilot and I'm a--
You know, own a flight school.
It's just such
a lack of respect.
And it's just
very frustrating. I wanted--
I couldn't wait
for them to leave.
It's so frustrating.
Just annoying.
-Like...
-Yeah, it's so annoying.
I can't fall asleep
with people talking.
-It just. No, it's impossible.
-Exactly.
SUE:
Tiyana knows I can't stand TK
and she agrees with me,
but I can't tell
if she's just
saying that to "yes" me
or if she believes it.
TK is, like,
one of those people that...
I don't have
a solid read on him.
I wish I got to
sleep in all day.
TIYANA:
I don't think I vibe with him
as a person.
But the thing is...
(sighs)
...me, TK, Gabe and Kyle--
that four-- we have the numbers.
And so,
I'm game to roll
with the big dogs.
-Okay, let's get it.
-SAM: So, I tell Sierra
I have the key.
And so, the last step
is going and getting this box,
unlocking the box, and getting
my hidden immunity idol.
SIERRA:
Let's go!
There's not one part of my body
that I'm like, "I can't
trust Sam at this point."
And he wants to include me
in everything.
That, to me,
is, like, friggin' cool.
-There.
-Got the lock?
SIERRA:
It's here. Yep, right here.
SAM:
Gonna get it out.
(Sierra laughs)
I feel like
we definitely have this strong
trust now that's truly building.
I just wanted to share
that moment with Sierra
as number ones and friends.
SAM:
We run off to the water well
and we're like,
"Here we go. The moment
you've been waiting for,
"where you get
an immunity idol on Survivor."
(Sierra giggling)
And we open the box.
And there's another box.
The idol that
I've just found is only
good for one Tribal Council.
I can play it safe
or I can choose
to take on another task
and make this idol good for
three Tribal Councils.
Okay? Let's go! You got it.
I decide, "Let's not
get ahead of our skis,"
and I grab
my very own
Survivor hidden immunity idol.
Yes. It's mine! (laughs) Sorry.
SAM:
And this is a little guy,
but I feel like
this one's gonna
be small but mighty.
We can make something happen
at the next one.
Yeah, we're good, we're good.
SAM:
But right now I'm trying
to figure out how do I use
this idol to position myself
in the best spot possible.
I'm trying to think
a couple of steps ahead.
Hear me out.
Is it crazy
if I play it on Andy?
-I-I hope you can understand
that I'm, like, nervous
-Yeah.
-about going to four with
the three girls and myself.
-Okay. Yeah.
I think that's the right move.
SIERRA:
I do not love the idea
of working with Andy.
I think he's very unpredictable.
But if Sam's
pulling, you know, Andy's way,
I'm sticking with Sam.
I think, surprisingly,
Andy has, like,
a decent head
on his shoulders right now.
Survivor is never
as simple as it seems,
and you got to make big moves
to advance in this game,
and I-I think
I might be on the cusp of having
to make a really big move.
And that's where the fun begins.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
Tuku and Lavo,
getting your first look
at the new Gata tribe.
Jon voted out
the last Tribal Council.
GABE:
What?
ROME:
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Huge reactions.
Wow.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
(all voicing assent)
First things first.
Rome, Sue,
-got to take it back.
-I ain't taking
a step toward you.
-SIERRA: She's hiding.
-Come on, give it up.
Don't make me pull out my knife.
(laughing)
-Spicy.
-Savage.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna jump into the ocean
and race to a tower
where you will retrieve
a large bag of rice.
You're gonna then work together
to get that bag of rice
through a very small hole
and ashore,
where one person
will stand behind a cage door
and maneuver a key
through a maze.
Once you have the key,
unlock the door,
tear open your bag of rice
and retrieve a ball,
where finally,
three tribe members will attempt
to maneuver that ball
through a winding snake track.
First two tribes
to finish win immunity.
In addition,
you're playing for reward.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
(all voicing assent)
(cheering, applause)
-(indistinct chatter)
-Let's go. Let's go.
PROBST:
First tribe to finish--
a massive Survivor fishing kit.
-(whooping)
-ANIKA: Oh, my God.
Second tribe to finish, smaller,
but this will do the job.
SAM:
Yeah!
-(whooping)
-PROBST: Last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers--
I got nothing
for you but a date with me
at Tribal Council
where somebody will be
the second person voted out
of Survivor 47.
As a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Gata, you are working
to get yours back.
All right, we have sit-outs.
Lavo, you have one extra person.
Sitting somebody out.
You cannot sit out
the same person
in back-to-back challenges.
Who's it gonna be?
-It's gonna be Aysha.
-PROBST: Aysha.
-Tuku, who's it gonna be?
-Me.
PROBST:
Sue. All right,
we have our sit-outs.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
-(cheering)
-Go, guys. (whoops)
PROBST:
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
-Everybody in the water at once.
-SUE: Go, Tuku!
PROBST:
Your first job is
to get that very heavy bag
of rice down from the platform.
AYSHA:
Go, Lavo!
PROBST:
Tuku heads up first.
There goes Gata. Andy's got it.
Rome has it for Lavo.
Ready? It's heavy.
Don't drop it.
PROBST:
Tiyana and TK have it for Tuku.
Put the weight on my head.
-I got it, I got it, I got it.
-You got it?
PROBST:
It's Lavo in the early lead now
with their bag of rice.
I got rough footing out here.
PROBST:
You got to get everybody
to that next obstacle
-before you can start over.
-AYSHA: Come on, Lavo!
Lavo, you're good.
-We're good, we're good.
-Gata, you're good.
Tuku, you're good.
The rice is going
through the hole.
The players are going
over the obstacle.
PROBST:
Lavo working quickly
with that bag of rice.
-Here we go.
-Yup, back and forth.
AYSHA:
Good job, let's go!
-You can drop. You can drop.
-PROBST: Rome,
going for style points.
-You good?
-PROBST: Lavo has their
bag of rice
through very fast.
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
PROBST:
Gata has their bag of rice.
They're heading out.
-Nice. Here we go.
-Yup.
PROBST:
Tuku has their bag of rice.
They're heading over
and through.
(grunting)
PROBST:
You got to get everybody
to the mat
before you can move on.
You got it, you got it, Andy.
You're good, Lavo.
It's gonna be Rome on the maze.
Here comes Gata.
Rachel's got to get there.
You're good, Gata.
-You guys are great.
-PROBST: You're good, Tuku.
It's gonna be Tiyana for Tuku,
Rome for Lavo,
Rachel for Gata.
You guys are great.
PROBST:
You're doing this blind.
You're trying to find the hole
and then get the key
through hole.
KYLE:
Make a grid with your mind.
PROBST:
You don't know
if you're making progress
until you get there.
GENEVIEVE:
Good job, Rome.
-We got your back.
You're doing great.
-Go, Rome!
PROBST:
You'll know
when you hit a dead end.
PROBST:
It's much more difficult
when you are blind.
SUE:
Come on, Tiyana! Let's go!
-Oh!
-PROBST: Rachel has it,
drops her key.
SAM:
You got it. You got it,
you got it.
PROBST:
Now you can unlock.
Now Gata-- they have their key.
PROBST:
Now Rome feeling the pressure,
Tiyana feeling the pressure.
Wait, wait.
Keep going, keep going.
PROBST:
Rachel has the door open.
Drop that bag on the table.
Andy has the rice. Gonna use
that knife. Watch your hands!
-Yeah, like the coconut.
-Just like that coconut.
-Yeah, baby. Go!
-(whooping)
-Tear it open.
-SIERRA: Rip it
like that coconut.
PROBST:
Andy now looking for that ball.
-Rome has it for Lavo!
-Yes!
He can unlock that door. It's
now Tiyana who's gonna feel it.
-Yes!
-Andy has the ball.
It is Gata in the lead,
something they are definitely
not used to.
-Oh, yeah, baby. Yeah.
-GENEVIEVE: I don't know what
that means, but it sounds great.
-Ah! Ah!
-(whooping)
-PROBST: Rome has the door open.
-Come on!
Drop that bag on the table.
PROBST:
Tiyana still working for Tuku.
Come on, Tiyana!
-SIERRA: Don't stress.
-SAM: All right.
-We ready?
-PROBST: Sierra, Sam and Anika.
And this will take a lot
of teamwork
and a lot of communication.
It's a very delicate move
you're trying to make
as you guide that ball
along this winding track.
There is a massive
learning curve to this challenge
because it requires all
three players to work together.
There are a lot of bogeys.
Those holes
you've got to get around.
Don't overdo it there.
We want it to stop right here.
PROBST:
Looking for that ball.
He's got it.
It's gonna be Genevieve,
Rome and Kishan.
Yes.
Tiyana finally has the key
for Tuku.
Tuku is through.
-Let's go, guys!
-AYSHA: All right,
let's go! Let's go!
PROBST:
Kyle gonna open that bag.
-I'm going.
-PROBST: Gata working slowly
on their table.
ANIKA:
We're learning.
I want to eat this.
Yeah, me, too.
I was just thinking.
PROBST:
Kyle looking for that ball now.
He's got it.
Gonna be TK,
Gabe and Kyle for Tuku.
AYSHA:
You got this, Lavo!
PROBST:
Lavo drops.
They got to start over.
-Let's go on the other side.
-GENEVIEVE: Yeah.
It is a blistering hot day.
You're already exhausted.
But it comes down to this--
one little ball,
a windy little path,
and victory
awaiting you at the end.
It is Gata in the lead.
Keep it taut.
PROBST:
But Tuku is now catching Gata.
I'm going pressure, you're
giving finesse right now.
Nice guide, bro. Nice guide.
We got it. Easy work.
PROBST:
A little tension,
a little slack.
You need more, I give you some.
I need some, you got to let go.
Guide it at your pace.
-You're good.
-SIERRA: Am I giving slack?
Yeah. Yup. Stop when we get
right before the hole.
ANIKA:
Stopping.
Sierra, you're calling out
which one's thicker.
SIERRA:
Well, my side. Wait. No.
-Left side, left side.
-SAM: Anika's side, okay.
So both of you pull,
get it to the end.
-Let me get this
to the edge.
-ANIKA: Yup.
When you figure out
how to work together on this,
it becomes very easy.
SAM:
Keep going, Si.
PROBST:
Lavo moving very slowly now,
trying to learn
from their mistakes.
-GENEVIEVE: Okay?
-ROME: We're good,
we're good, we're good.
But we are absolutely
neck-and-neck now
with Gata and Tuku
at the same spot, same obstacle.
-Little bit more, Gabe.
Give it a little bit.
-Yup, yup.
-Stop, stop, stop, stop!
-PROBST: Tuku can't navigate it.
That's how fast
this challenge can change.
-Somebody pull. Watch it.
-PROBST: It is Gata in the lead.
-I'm pulling as much as I can.
-Calm down.
Stop! Hey, stop! All right?
-What are we doing? Let's go.
-PROBST: Gata starting to panic.
ANIKA:
Okay, well, I mean,
I can't pull.
Choke up on the rope.
You have more rope.
Sam, Sam, if I pull it
any further, it won't go.
-Please listen to me.
-SAM: All right. All right.
PROBST:
Tuku moving quickly now,
trying to catch Lavo.
They can feel the pressure,
but somebody's gonna be last.
Somebody's going to Tribal.
-Slack, lot of it.
-PROBST: Gata is very close
to finishing this challenge.
There is one spot left.
-No!
-I can't pull anymore.
PROBST:
Gata at the last spot.
One hole. Can they get past it
and drop for the win?
SAM:
Yeah. Watch it. Watch it.
PROBST:
Very close.
-Oh, my God.
-We're good. Stop. Stop.
And they got it!
Gata wins immunity!
Safe from Tribal Council.
We're looking for one more.
And right now, it is Lavo
decidedly ahead of Tuku.
-Keep the ring left.
-PROBST: They have got to move
or hope that Lavo
-makes a mistake.
-Very gentle.
-ROME:
All right, all right, all right.
-Nice move by Lavo.
AYSHA:
Nice recovery. Let's go!
That is not gonna fall
through. We just need to...
Wait, wait, wait, fellas. Wait.
PROBST:
Tuku has dropped
and has to start again.
Now Tuku can feel the panic.
GABE:
I'm telling everybody.
-Slow.
-PROBST: This is it.
It comes down
to this moment right here.
ROME:
Okay, that's good. That's good.
They're on the edge,
and they're past it.
Can they drop it for the win?
GENEVIEVE:
Yup. Got it.
They do! Lavo wins immunity...
(cheering)
...sending Tuku
to Tribal Council where somebody
will be the second person
voted out of Survivor 47.
Yeah!
All right, Gata,
-immunity is yours.
-(whooping, cheering)
And you earn your flint back.
-Yes!
Gata safe tonight,
no Tribal Council.
I will miss you at Tribal.
-I know you won't miss me.
-We won't miss you, Jeff.
-Promise.
I don't take it personally.
Lavo, congratulations.
For the second straight time,
immunity is yours.
Well done.
All right, Gata,
before I send you out,
I have a question for Rachel.
-Yes?
-Did I see you
putting some rice...
in your pocket?
You didn't see anything, Jeff.
PROBST:
Unbelievable.
Empty your pockets.
-Okay. Sorry.
-SAM: You put rice
in your pocket?
SIERRA:
Dude, what a savage!
-(Sierra shrieks)
-(laughter)
ROME:
Oh, my--
-SIERRA: It's in your pockets?
-RACHEL: Yeah.
SIERRA: Well, we were
trying to play smart.
-ROME: Oh, my God.
-Yeah, you got to empty 'em.
Hey, when I was standing
at that bag of rice,
I thought, "Maybe I can
take some home with us."
I respect the try.
-Thank you.
-PROBST: Lavo, Gata,
grab your stuff.
-(whooping)
-Head back to camp.
No Tribal Council tonight.
SOL:
Thank you, Jeff. Thank you.
That was funny.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: That's a first, Rachel.
-(laughing)
-Hey.
All right, Tuku. So, Tiyana,
I see a lot of smiles.
-It's fake.
-(laughing)
I'm trying my best
to keep positive, you know?
I mean, obviously we lost,
so we got to stay positive and
figure something out, you know?
So, it's tough.
TK, now you enter the last part
of the game,
the biggest part of the game,
when you go to Tribal,
and you vote somebody out.
You haven't had
to deal with that yet.
Can you anticipate
what's gonna be different
as you head back to camp?
Uh, I mean, honestly, I'm
genuinely pissed off right now,
so it's hard for me to even
think that far right now.
I'm just... We got way too many
smiles over here for us to lose.
I'm just not used to losing.
I don't hang
with people who are cool
with losing. I don't...
I don't even associate myself
with that.
If I lose,
I'm not gonna be happy about it.
And, uh, I just want
to make sure
that I have a tribe
that has the same mindset,
and if we don't,
then that's a problem.
All right, Tuku,
Tribal Council tonight,
where one of you will be
the second person voted out
of Survivor 47.
And as a penalty for losing--
sorry for you--
I'm gonna take your flint.
Thank you.
You will have a chance
to earn this back
at your next challenge.
All right, grab your stuff.
Head out. See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
SUE: TK threw Tiyana
under the bus because
he was angry
that she was smiling.
Before today's challenge,
I always thought
she was with the boys,
but the rage on her face
and the anger just showed
that she was so upset with TK,
and hopefully,
that put the nail
in the coffin for him.
♪ ♪
SUE:
Oh, dude, please tell me
we have some.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, okay.
-(Sue sighs)
-Yeah.
GABE: At the challenge, I saw
Tiyana rolling her eyes
at everything that TK said,
and that changed things
a lot for me.
Because, initially,
I felt like the lines
were pretty clear in the sand.
And on one side
of the equation, it was
me, Sue and Caroline,
and nobody really knew about it.
And on the other side
of the equation,
it was TK, Kyle and Tiyana.
And I thought Tiyana was in
really tight with the guys.
I hope you guys didn't think
I was like,
-"Yay. Can't wait."
-I can't-I can't-- No.
I cannot stress enough
how nobody thought that.
But I think that what happened
at the challenge today
really put her
in an emotional state
that is gonna guide
her decision-making tonight.
And if that plays in my favor,
then I am all for it.
TK: Playing sports my...
majority of my life--
it really just
builds this mindset in you
that, like,
you don't put all this work in
to go out and lose.
For me, man, I just... I don't
really do well with losing.
We got a tribe that should win
every single challenge,
and we're not doing it.
I feel like
I'm a leader on the tribe,
and if y'all gonna be
on my tribe,
everybody needs to have
the same mindset that I have.
So now, I'm gonna start
telling people what we're doing.
"This is the goal, this
is the plan, let's execute."
TIYANA:
I'm not gonna lie.
When TK popped off--
like, that hurt,
and not just because...
(mockingly): I'm a dramatic
little woman. I...
Like, he basically stood,
like, on his high horse
and called us all losers.
Even if I lose a ballgame,
I walk out on the field
and I slap hands with people,
-and I'm like, "Hey, good game."
-Yeah. Like, the sportsmanship.
-Like, for real.
-KYLE: Yeah.
Y'all talking ... about me?
-No.
TIYANA: The fact that TK
couldn't take any accountability
for the loss as a team--
that pissed me off.
T was a little rubbed off
that you didn't apologize
to her right away. Like,
that kind of, like,
ruffled some feathers.
Bruh, I don't owe her an
apology, but I don't know, bruh.
Like, now I'm starting
to not trust T.
KYLE:
Tiyana was not
feeling the respect from TK,
and, uh, I think that he should
have apologized to her.
But TK, Tiyana, myself--
they're my ride-or-dies.
So, I'm trying
to keep that together.
I just got to make sure
T's not gonna ... this up.
Let me get us together. Maybe
we can straighten that out.
And it's-it's...
The strategy talks-- that's
the hardest part of this for me.
I can hang out in the jungle.
A country boy can survive.
I'm not worried about it.
Hank Williams said it best.
But this is the first time
that my wheels really had
to be spinning like this.
If you have an issue
with anything that I say,
-please come to me
and talk to me about it.
-Mm-hmm.
Like, I don't need you going
around the circle to tell me,
like, that you feel
a certain type of way.
-Yeah. Mm-hmm.
-Talk to me about it.
At the end of the day,
I didn't even
see who smiled on the tribe,
so nothing was pointed
at you, him, anybody.
Jeff said, "Damn, Tuku.
You guys are smiling.
You're going to Tribal tonight."
-And that's what triggered you?
-And I said,
"I'm not comfortable
with anybody smiling right now."
But that being said,
are we straight?
-Uh, yes.
-All right.
TIYANA:
When I came out here,
I knew that I wanted to be
a player that separated emotion
from gameplay.
I could not like you,
but I could work with you.
And I'm...
and then, I'm just like, "No."
TIYANA:
But it's very, very difficult
because right now,
I'm getting a little bit annoyed
at TK with his ego.
However, strategically,
he is a great physical asset
to have in these challenges.
And I know that I have to
sometimes put the emotions aside
if I want
to get farther in the game.
-I just want to make sure
we're all good.
-KYLE: All right.
-Yup. No. Ser...
-Love you. Love you.
-We're straight. We're solid.
-So...
We're gonna
stick to the same plan.
Sue: done.
TIYANA:
I do believe that Sue,
right now,
is one of the weaker members
of the tribe
because she can't
really contribute
to physical challenges,
and it kind of seems like
she's fizzling out on day five.
-I'm good for it.
-TK: I think we stick with Sue.
-So we stick with Sue? I'm game.
-And that'd be the end of it.
TK:
Sue needs to go home.
It's not a hard decision
because Sue doesn't really
bring anything
specifically to the tribe.
So,
think my game plan
is working flawlessly right now.
I think that's
the only way we can play.
Myself, Tiyana and Kyle--
locked in.
And Gabe will do
whatever I need him to do.
So, the way that I'm moving
these chess pieces around,
everybody else
is playing checkers right now.
GABE:
I think T is cool with us.
I think T will go Sue
if we want her to go Sue.
-I think she would.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-You know?
I think Caroline and Sue...
-No, no, no.
-TK: You know?
I feel like T is almost more
like bro than...
With us. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. No, totally, totally.
-All right, so...
-GABE: I...
I think we just go four on Sue.
TK thinks that
it's the three guys plus Tiyana.
That's what I need to happen.
I need him to think,
"Before we go to Tribal Council,
"let me get Gabe in
'cause he's our fourth vote
"and he's just happy to do
whatever we say anyway."
I think we do that
and, uh, call it a day.
GABE:
So, TK feels extremely secure
right now,
which will make this
quite a blindside.
If we can pull it off.
I'm praying to God you do not
need to play your idol tonight.
I could play the idol for Sue,
but the thing with Tiyana
has changed things a lot.
-This is... Yeah. She's four.
-Okay. Yeah.
Yes. 100%.
And I think if we can lock
Tiyana in as a fourth right now,
I don't see any reason
to use my idol tonight.
I will have
a ... conversation with her.
That's what I was gonna say.
You don't know I... Yeah.
I will absolutely be like--
-Whatever you got to say
to make it happen.
-Okay.
All right. Let's go, guys.
We rock.
CAROLINE: Tonight, I really hope
Tiyana's on our side, because
if we go to a tie,
and you can't convince anyone
to change their votes,
you go to rocks.
And the two people the
entire tribe wants gone most--
they're safe.
And the odds of the people
who are drawing rocks--
25% chance you go home.
It's really risky.
-I trust you all wholeheartedly.
-Oh.
Yeah, even if it's a tie.
Well, that-that would have
to put Tiyana,
and she's gonna know if she has
to ... change her vote.
All of us have the balls
to go to rocks.
I'm a risk-taker, and I am not
gonna cow down to anything.
I'm gonna go all out.
I don't want anybody to know
we've been a threesome,
'cause then she'll know
we've been lying to her.
-Good.
-So she's gonna think
it's us girls.
Tiyana doesn't know
that Caroline, myself and Gabe
are in an alliance,
so the only thing
that's gonna have to happen is
Tiyana's gonna
have to jump ship.
I feel like, you know,
I understand
-if you don't want to do TK.
-No.
But I feel he-- Taking out the
biggest threat would be sick.
You... Yeah, it would,
and it would...
-Be epic.
-It would...
No, it would be epic.
-Like, we just need the numbers.
-Yeah.
How else are we supposed
to flip this?
-Yeah.
-Like, then what--
we go to rocks?
-I will go to rocks.
-Yeah.
Sue wants TK
to be the next vote.
Honestly, it'd be
a ep-epic boss girl move.
TIYANA: However, TK and Kyle
are really, really,
really close, so,
that's a big problem if it comes
into blindsiding TK,
'cause I'm also
blindsiding Kyle,
and I don't know how
I could rebuild
that relationship.
It's really taking a toll.
Yeah. As long
as us three stay together.
It's all about if we think
Tiyana will go to rocks or not.
I don't think she will.
TIYANA:
It is really difficult
being in the middle
because it does feel like a lot
of pressure on my shoulders
to deliver to people
that have put their faith in me.
(groans)
This waiting.
That's the worst part, honestly.
Waiting around.
TIYANA:
It would absolutely
make sense for me
to vote Sue tonight because
TK has strength on his side,
but I don't want
to work with someone
who I feel disrespected me.
So, it really is
this toss-up between
emotion and strategy.
I can only hope
that my gut is right,
and that I'm trusting
the right people in this game.
♪ ♪
(chuckling)
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council,
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
When your fire's gone,
so are you.
That's gonna be the case
for one of the six
of you tonight.
So, let's get into
these first few days.
Sue, did you see
any natural pairing?
It often happens when you have
a group of strangers
that you say, "Oh, I'm from
that part of the country"
or "I'm the mom, too."
Did you see any of that?
What I actually saw
was a bromance developing,
and I felt like
from the very beginning,
there were, like, the three guys
and the three girls
on the bottom.
-Really?
-Yeah.
PROBST:
Tiyana, do you agree with that?
I honestly do agree.
It seemed like
they vibed really well.
But also, this is Survivor.
Nothing's ever so cookie-cutter.
"Oh, boys and girls."
-Right.
-So, I really do think
that what once started
as a bromance
maybe possibly could be split.
We never know.
PROBST:
So, let me just check
with the three guys.
Do you agree with that?
Did you all feel like
-you just bonded quickly?
-Oh, yeah.
-I mean...
-I... I bonded pretty quickly
with them.
but I also bonded
with some girls, as well.
I'm not strictly on a bromance
or a romance or nothing.
PROBST:
TK, one thing Sue said
very clearly was,
the men were on top,
and the women were
on the bottom. She didn't say
it was even in her view.
TK:
I think what a lot of that had
to do with is maybe she wasn't
as comfortable initiating
conversation like the guys were.
If you're kind of just
in your own bubble,
that can make you feel that way.
So, Sue, that's
very much your problem.
That's not my problem
whatsoever.
I can socialize and be very good
with men as well as women.
There was a line,
and you could tell,
you know,
they wanted to stay strong.
TK:
I just got a question.
Has anybody really talked to Sue
more than two or three times
as far as, like,
deep conversation?
-Have you?
-I've tried. I mean,
we've tried to have
conversations. I'm just saying.
I'm just asking the question,
like, how much did you actually
initiate conversation
with everyone else?
That's the things that
you have to do on Survivor,
is you have
to have those conversations.
And if you're not,
we all know
by watching the game,
things can change.
Gabe, it can't
surprise you that, already,
there's this division
or misunderstanding
or whatever
it might ultimately be.
That's part of the design
of this game.
You take a group of strangers
and you thrust them into crisis
and say, "Figure it out."
Yeah. I think that
in the game of Survivor,
there's two kinds of
relationships you have, right?
There are your
strategic relationships
and there are
your social relationships.
And I think that people,
especially in early days,
they see social relationships,
and they immediately
associate them
with strategic relationships.
But those two things
aren't always the same thing.
PROBST:
Caroline, is there
a stated philosophy
with this tribe when it comes
to searching
for idols or advantages?
There's really only one person
I can think of who is known
as the person for, like,
you can tell what they're doing.
-So...
-PROBST: You're all smiling.
Do you know
who Caroline's talking about?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
-PROBST: Who is it?
-Gabe.
-Ooh.
So, Gabe, is this a surprise
that they are onto you?
GABE:
I mean, look,
the game says, "Here's
an island, and it's yours."
And this is an opportunity
to be a kid again.
And I like to Tarzan around
a little bit, and,
you know,
I'm not blind to the fact
that that's gonna
raise eyebrows,
but I want to be Indiana Jones
for a little bit.
Let me be Indiana Jones.
Come on.
PROBST:
Gabe, your enthusiasm for that,
to me, is the hallmark
of a new era player.
You all tend to wear your hearts
on your sleeves.
You're more passionate.
We had it with you today, TK.
It was different. You were
frustrated about the challenge.
So, did you have an intention
when you said, "I want people
to know I'm not happy"?
Absolutely. I think the whole
goal of me even speaking out
wasn't to single any one person
out on the tribe,
but more to get
everybody's attention
to reinforce the fact
that we should not
be okay with losing.
And we need to understand that
we want to win,
we need to go as hard
as we can go
and not be happy
with being last place
and not be complacent
with being last place,
especially for the fact that
somebody's going home tonight
because we didn't win.
(thunder rumbles)
PROBST:
So, Tiyana, tonight's vote
is the first test of trust.
Did you find yourself needing
a little more reassurance?
TIYANA:
Oh, absolutely.
And kind of going back
to balancing
social and strategic,
it's like,
"Oh, do I like this person
"and I kind of trust them
for them just being themselves,
"or do I trust them
on a strategy level
of, like, playing
this game with me?"
So, at this point, I'm like, how
will the chips fall? You know?
So, moving forward in this game,
I need to work with people
that I can genuinely trust.
But also, you never
actually know who you can trust
until whoever's
torch is getting snuffed
is getting snuffed.
And on that note,
it is time to vote.
Caroline, you're up.
♪ ♪
Want to see a magic trick?
In one fell swoop,
I will make
your Survivor dream...
disappear.
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
GABE:
Yeah.
PROBST: Okay.
Playing this for yourself?
Yeah.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast
against Gabe will not count.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sue.
TK.
One vote Sue, one vote TK.
Sue.
Two votes Sue, one vote TK.
TK.
We're tied.
Two votes Sue, two votes TK.
TK.
-Hmm.
-That's three votes TK,
two votes Sue,
one vote left.
Second person voted out
of Survivor 47:
-TK.
-Wow.
PROBST:
Need to bring me your torch.
-Good stuff.
-Sorry, TK.
No worries.
(TK groans)
TK:
(exhales) Man.
(TK sighs)
-TK, the tribe has spoken.
-All right.
PROBST:
Time for you to go.
(sighs) Oh, man.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
TIYANA:
Good night, Jeff.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
ANDY:
There's trouble
in paradise here in Gata.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
ANDY:
Ooh.
I'm pissed off.
There they go!
ROME:
I feel like I'm running
this game right now.
We might as well rename it
to Survivor: Rome.
It was a great move.
I mean, I can't be mad at it.
I felt like I had some
really good connections, but,
you know, maybe my personality
was a little too bright.
Me showing a lot of emotion at
the end of that last challenge
put some more fingers
towards me.
But if they don't value winning,
they don't value winning.
And obviously, by this decision,
they don't value winning much.
I'm just excited for
whatever happens in the future,
'cause this proves to me
that there's nothing
I would be afraid of in life.
(roars)