Do like that, like...
Rome is off his rocker.
(imitates screeching
connection tone)
(chortles)
SOL:
He's just... he's a lot.
PROBST:
Previously on Survivor...
AYSHA:
I have to build
an army around me.
Now I feel like
I have the numbers.
ROME:
I took the idol that's good
for only one Tribal Council.
Rome is not gonna be
the first one gone from Lavo.
SAM:
I just wanted to share
that moment with Sierra...
...as number ones and friends.
You got it.
I feel like this one's
gonna be small
but mighty.
TK:
I'm just not used to losing.
I don't hang with people
who are cool with losing.
I don't even associate myself
with that.
TIYANA: I don't want
to work with someone who
I feel disrespected me.
So right now
my emotion is saying, "Vote TK."
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it...
GABE:
Jeff.
-Playing this for yourself?
-(Caroline gasps)
Yeah.
First vote: Sue.
Second person voted out
of Survivor 47:
-TK.
-Wow.
The tribe has spoken.
All righty.
♪ ♪
Here. Try my frond.
CAROLINE:
Yes.
That was so cool,
you played your idol.
GABE:
I know, right?
Honestly, I just,
I heard my dad's voice
-in the back of my head.
-There you go. You know...
And he was just screaming,
"Play it."
Last season on Survivor,
I watched way too many people
go home
with an idol in their pocket.
The dumbest move.
With an idol in my pocket.
There it is.
TIFFANY:
I should have played my idol.
I went home with an idol.
They blindsided me
with an idol in my pocket.
And I'm not gonna
allow that to happen to me.
(Tiyana laughs)
KYLE:
Tribal Council was nuts.
There was some things
that played out
that I didn't really expect.
Mm-hmm.
GABE:
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
KYLE:
I took a risk.
I threw a hit at Sue
instead of TK.
I don't know
if it's a mistake yet,
but I just need to make sure
that I'm in the right ring
with the right bull,
so that way
I'm not the next one going home.
Respectful.
What?
(both cheering quietly)
CAROLINE:
I am so happy to say
the vote went exactly the way
I thought it was going to go.
It was so perfect.
We did it.
Nobody else did it. We did it.
We pulled off
a friggin' blindside.
Like, that's like, "Check."
But Kyle voted for me,
and I take it personally.
That's a man
who's underestimating me.
And I get the same feeling I got
when I went
into the aviation industry,
which is male-dominated.
So I totally know how
to handle guys like that.
If we go
to another Tribal Council,
I am gonna get revenge.
♪ ♪
RACHEL:
Sleeping on bamboo is rough.
I don't have the best back.
(chuckles)
And waking up this morning,
I could barely, like, move.
RACHEL:
Oh, my God.
ANIKA:
I did not get
more than 20 minutes
of closed-eyed time
because our shelter
still looks like
it's a day one shelter,
which made for
horrible sleeping conditions.
And I woke up
so, so, so exhausted.
RACHEL:
So what do we want
to do for priorities?
-I feel like
we need to fix the shelter.
-Floor.
-Floor. Shelter.
-You know, I...
Let me just also say, though,
we did talk about the crabs
and said that
first thing in the morning
would be best.
RACHEL:
True, but if we can't get
-fire today
'cause everything's wet, like...
-ANIKA: Yeah.
I think we should
all be on the shelter
really quickly right now.
And then all of our bodies
need to test it.
It'll be so quick
if we all just do it.
-SAM: Okay.
-Okay.
This tribe
has been focusing on vibes
instead of camp life,
but obviously those tasks
still need to get done.
Sam, can you pull this one out?
-Where am I pulling it?
-Just take it out.
SAM:
We're almost
a week into this game.
We're running on fumes
at this point,
and we have this entire
fishing kit right in our camp.
And instead of being like,
"Hey, let's all go and try
and get some food today,"
we're sitting here saying,
"Hmm. That bamboo
dug into my side
a little bit weird last night."
What if this big boy
we take out and just fill in
with a smaller guy
and put rocks under it?
It's bamboo.
It's not the Ritz-Carlton.
Quit trying
to make it the Ritz-Carlton.
It feels like Anika
really wants to have control
of everything
that happens in camp life.
Where do you want me to put it?
Like, something around here,
because the last thing you want
is for it to cave in.
SAM:
She believes that she's
the figurehead
of the Gata tribe,
but I'm just like,
"Give me a break."
I'm rolling my eyes and
I'm trying not to say anything.
I'm trying not to be
so obviously irritated,
but I'm just, like,
I'm pissed off.
ANDY:
People talk
about a Survivor wall.
And the Survivor wall
is when, you know,
you're trucking along,
and then you wake up one day,
and it all just,
it comes crashing down.
And I think this is
the case for two people
in particular-- Anika and Sam.
ANIKA:
Sam, if you're able to create
a base right here,
I support the two.
If not,
it's gonna be way too heavy.
-Where do you want me to get it?
-Chop it?
ANDY:
Like I said from the beginning,
I want to gather data.
And what people tell you is,
like, second-level data.
It's okay, but there's
better, more substantial,
cleaner data out there,
and that is people's actions.
And when Sam
and Anika are bickering
over the clothesline,
it's like, okay.
That's real.
They're not faking that one.
I don't know.
I think this will hold.
As long as we just don't,
like, throw things.
We, like, put 'em on there
lightly, and it'll be okay.
ANIKA:
I don't think
it's just that, Sam.
It's the pure weight
of the wet clothes.
But it's staying in now.
I-I know now with four pieces
of clothes on there...
-...that are partially dry.
-Okay.
I'm just saying, scientifically
and mathematically,
the weight will pull it in.
Okay.
Then let's machete it here.
ANDY:
Ooh.
We've been sawing it. That's
been more successful, Sam.
Okay.
-Yeah.
ANDY:
I do currently feel
like I am on the bottom,
but there's trouble in paradise
here on Gata.
And so the festering conflict
makes me
really, really valuable.
And it would be
a very sweet turnaround for me.
I think I've got some life here.
I do.
Good work, team.
-ANDY: Great job. Great job.
-Good work.
ANDY:
Yeah.
SIERRA:
All right.
♪ ♪
ROME:
I want to catch a big guy today.
GENEVIEVE:
Yeah.
ROME:
I want to know
the Survivor record
for most fish caught in a day.
Yep.
That's the sole purpose of that.
Yeah. That's the only reason.
Just so I can beat it by one
and be done.
AYSHA: Since day one,
Rome has been talking about,
"I can't wait to get out there.
"As soon as we get fishing gear,
I'm gonna be out there
all hours of the day."
And so I knew as soon
as Jeff said, "Fishing gear,"
I was like, "Oh, we're
gonna have to deal with Rome."
If you have
a six-foot Hawaiian sling,
you have a four-foot
kill radius, essentially.
You want to be that close
to the fish, and then bam.
-Okay. Okay.
-So it doesn't
have time to react.
At random times,
there'll just be water
that comes into the mouthpiece,
and I have
to go up to the top and, like,
readjust it and, like,
just hope
it doesn't fill up again.
AYSHA:
If you ask Rome,
every piece of fishing gear
is labeled "Rome."
ROME:
Oh, you want to try it?
GENEVIEVE:
Yeah.
So, the current's
really strong underwater.
-Like, you'll feel
yourself moving away.
-Is it? Okay. Okay.
-Okay, I'll wait.
-(chuckles)
Catching a fish
with a Hawaiian sling
is so difficult to do.
Like, only a few Survivors
are really, like,
doing it, like, and
doing it all right, you know?
KISHAN:
Rome is the only one,
successfully,
who has caught fish,
but Rome has also been the one
who's been
using the fishing gear
for a majority of the time.
Yeah.
(groans)
-You okay?
-Yeah, just...
AYSHA:
Exactly.
TEENY:
Yeah.
I think I just
have a different mindset.
Like, if somebody was
catching fish for me, like,
bro, I'd be
getting the pot ready.
I'd be trying to make a fire.
-Yeah.
-This is just ridiculous, man.
AYSHA:
I bet you
-he thinks we're so lazy.
-TEENY: He does.
We're spending
24 hours a day together,
and that's obviously
going to expose us
in our raw forms--
what our annoyances are,
what our patience levels are.
ROME:
Yo!
There was a shark about
ten feet away from me just now.
I know. (laughs)
TEENY:
Which, for me, works out
perfectly because Rome
is a large personality person.
Why didn't
you bring the flippers?
I hate flippers, but, uh,
no flippers, no problem.
(excited chatter)
ROME:
And I realized,
hey, I'm kind of good
with the Hawaiian sling.
That's a great feeling
because now I realize,
"Man, I don't have
to starve out here."
-Pass it off. Ah!
-(laughter)
But then I started to realize,
okay,
I had to make the fire.
-AYSHA: Oh, there we go.
-TEENY: There we go.
ROME:
I had to clean the fish.
I had to get the fish.
So, like, at this point,
how appreciative are you?
And why should
I even give you some?
GENEVIEVE:
Rome has caught a few fish.
They're, like, this big,
like the kind
you would have as a pet, and...
Rome decided to eat
two of the four fish himself.
-Can I put this whole thing
in my mouth?
-Yeah.
AYSHA:
We only got the smallest bite.
I'm literally, like...
You're trying to savor it
as much as possible. Like,
"This is all I'm gonna get
from Rome.
I know this is all
that he's willing to hand over."
Excuse you? You did absolutely
nothing to deserve this.
Absolutely nothing. You aren't
even in my alliance, Aysha.
Why should I give you
a big chunk of meat?
So guess what I did.
The last two fish,
I ate them right next to Aysha.
Right next to her.
And I made sure
I was smacking a little bit,
so she could hear it,
so she could know,
"Listen,
if you want some of this fish,
you better
put in some work, too."
(spits)
-Huh?
-I said,
"You just spit that on my back."
Mmm.
♪ ♪
ANIKA: You'll like it.
You should try it.
-Pineapple?
-ANIKA: Yeah.
Hmm.
I've also ne--
Here's a weird one.
I've never had watermelon.
-Oh, my God.
-ANDY: Oh, my God.
-How is that possible?
-Not at any barbecue? Nothing?
-RACHEL: Sam...
-No.
-ANDY: Why not?
Wait, why?
ANIKA:
So, you haven't been around
a lot of watermelon
is what you're telling me?
No, there's...
No, I'm around watermelon a lot.
I just, like, don't eat it.
RACHEL:
And you have no desire
to just see what it tastes like?
Like, barbecues and stuff,
I just don't eat it.
-Yeah, I don't,
I don't really care.
-That's so crazy.
Sierra, this kid
has never had watermelon.
-What about different berries?
-What?!
Or pineapple.
-That's your favorite, right?
-Yes.
-What about, like,
blueberries, raspberries?
-I've had blueberries.
Uh, um,
I've probably had a raspberry.
-I don't remember it well,
but I've had blueberries.
-(gasping)
Oh, my God.
Your 24 years of life.
RACHEL:
Sam's very funny.
There's just things
that he's never tried
that boggle my mind.
Okay, let's
go through vegetables.
-Eggplant?
-Never had it.
-Zucchini?
-Squash?
-Never had it.
RACHEL:
Bean sprouts?
I don't know. Probably not.
Broccolini?
-I don't know what that is.
-Okay.
He hasn't tried
the most basic-ass foods.
This man is an, is an enigma.
I do not understand him.
Um, tomatoes,
you said you don't care for.
SIERRA:
What about,
like, an heirloom tomato?
I don't know what that is.
♪ ♪
SIERRA:
It looks...
-What do I look like?
-I mean, you look normal.
-Like, you just have long,
like, beachy hair.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Thick. Like,
it's not, like, knotted.
ANDY:
My game so far
has not been what I expected,
but right now
I'm-I'm working it.
I'm finagling.
You know, Anika and Rachel,
they're a duo.
So it's pretty simple.
I want to gain a majority
with Sam and Sierra.
And I'm really trying
to line this up
so that Sam and Sierra
feel like they can trust me.
Now, I feel like I already have
a pretty good bond
established with Sam.
We've been talking game
since day one,
but without Sierra,
I'm dead in the water.
SIERRA:
I know it might not be tonight,
but Sam and I, we are
just nervous
because we need your number.
ANDY: My game is just
to hitch my wagon to you.
-Yeah.
-Like, so we're, like...
-We need you to know, like...
-I know. Yeah.
-Look, do you...
-Do you know?
Like...
-Do I? Yeah.
-Do you want
my Shot in the Dark?
-No.
I can give you
my Shot in the Dark.
-What?
-Just to borrow it.
-Just to give me before Tribal?
-Just to give you
another action.
I mean, I would love that.
-All right.
-SIERRA: I'm not sure
I'm ever going to be able
to trust Andy, like, fully,
but he's willing to give me
his Shot in the Dark
before the next Tribal.
And that, to me,
is like, "Holy crap. Okay."
I-- That would make me
feel so much better.
I'm giving,
I'm giving you my game.
SIERRA:
I don't need
his Shot in the Dark,
but that absolutely built
more trust with me.
And that's exactly
what I needed from Andy,
'cause I still was getting
a little nervous about him.
But now it's like, "Shoot,
you know, he trusts me."
So, yeah, maybe
we could possibly work together.
♪ ♪
(hammering)
-This is a nut.
-GABE: Oh, really?
(grunts)
-And you can eat it?
-Yeah.
GABE:
Mmm.
That's pretty good.
In a game like Survivor,
things are ever-changing.
And now that TK is gone,
I don't want Kyle
to leave this game.
Kyle is somebody that
I believe can be controlled,
that will be Tuku strong,
even if the ship is sinking.
And that's
very attractive to me.
I really,
really want to work with you.
-I really do.
-Likewise.
And I just think
you're such a decent guy.
-Thanks, Gabe.
-And I...
I love the way
you're approaching this game.
He's on the bottom right now,
but if I could bring him
into a position of stability,
I don't think
he would ever turn against us.
I mean, shoot.
I could probably
call on that guy
to be my limousine driver
for the night
after this game is over,
and he'd fly out from Michigan
to Baltimore and do that for me.
This is something that I would
like to stay between us.
Yeah.
You got one, you got two.
Exactly. Yeah.
KYLE:
According to Gabe,
Sue and Caroline
will not vote for one another.
And as long as you have them,
you got two extra votes with
your vote everywhere you go.
But that's cooked in my head.
I don't like it
because if he's trying to make
relationships with me,
he's gonna want me
to flip on Tiyana.
And there's no way in hell that
I'm gonna try to go after her
unless I absolutely have to.
So if I can get
Sue and Caroline roped in,
then there's a way that I can
keep Tiyana around,
and we'll be able
to have the numbers
to go after Gabe successfully.
KYLE:
Gabe's been kind of shady.
He thinks that you and Caroline
are his goats.
Hmm.
-And he told you that?
-Yeah.
-Hmm.
-Kyle is at the bottom,
and he's desperate
to save his life,
but I will never forget
that Kyle wanted me out.
So there's no way I could live
with myself giving him a pass.
How do you feel about him
staying in the game?
Well, I hate
that we're talking today,
'cause I wanted
to wake up thinking,
"Let's just be pumped,
be juiced, be all positive,
not talking so much game."
I'm the type
that I need to focus on...
-And I respect that. That's why
I'm willing to squish it now.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, okay.
-Because I see that...
I see that you require that,
-and I'm willing
to give you that.
-I do require that. I require
positive thoughts,
positive tribe vibes,
positive everything.
-And having
any negative vibes...
-All right. I'll bring it
-to you later.
-...shooting out the-- Yeah.
KYLE:
Sue, man. Sue.
I just told you
that somebody thinks of you
as a goat in this game,
and it doesn't even faze her.
She is irritated at the fact
that I'm trying to bring
any kind of information
in this game to her attention.
Sue, what do I do with you?
♪ ♪
-CAROLINE: Guys, there's a...
-Guys, there's a boat.
What is happening?
There's a boat.
-There's a boat!
-TEENY: Oh, my God.
SIERRA:
Whoo!
-Okay, let's bring it in.
-This is it!
All right, you ready?
Gather round.
One, two, three.
-Oh!
KYLE:
This is beautiful.
A journey means that you're
gonna have opportunities.
And after
that conversation with Sue
and how it went,
I could be in trouble here.
So this is, like, exactly
what I need to help my game.
Y'all want to volunteer?
-I don't mind...
-RACHEL: Oh, yeah?
...if we all are okay with that.
I'm fine with that.
I'm great with that.
Anika wants
to go on this journey,
and everybody
seems cool with it,
but I don't want her to go
because that's my next target
in this game
going on a journey
to potentially get
an extra vote
or Safety or something
that could
really throw off my plans.
No, don't tell everything!
Yeah, don't tell everything!
SAM:
Tell us everything.
-Oh, okay.
-Oh, okay. Yeah.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
A'ight.
-TEENY: All right.
-ROME: All right, guys.
Absolutely the worst-case
scenario for all of us
would be to send Rome because
I believe that Rome has
something in his pocket already.
So I don't want Rome
to go on a journey
and potentially
get an extra vote, a Steal
a Vote, an amulet, anything...
anything that's gonna
help him in this game.
♪ ♪
-ANIKA: Hi!
-ROME: How's it going, guys?
Rome. Kyle.
-Awesome. I am so happy.
-Monica, right?
-Anika. Yeah.
-Anika.
-I'm sorry.
-I always say,
"Monica without the M,"
-and then people
remember it immediately.
-I got you, got you.
-It's nice to meet you guys.
-Oh, my God. Nice to meet you.
-Yeah, right? Oh, my gosh.
-Oh.
I'm so happy
it wasn't you last night.
-Oh, my gosh.
-No, wait. Literally, me, too.
-Kyle,
it's so good to see you again.
-Thanks, guys.
So who was it last night?
-You guys really want to know?
-Of course we want to know.
-I hope it's TK.
-ANIKA: Rome's like,
"Gossip now."
-(Rome laughs)
TK's gone.
-Yes!
-You're kidding.
-Hallelujah.
Oh, my gosh. I just
couldn't stand his ego.
I was not a fan of TK at all.
He was just being way too cocky,
way too arrogant.
So that was
exactly what I wanted.
I wanted him out the game first,
but, look,
I'll take the second boot.
-Sam, right? Is his name Sam?
-Yeah, Sam.
-Okay, and then what's, uh...
-ROME: Sierra?
-KYLE: S-Sierra?
-The blonde one?
-Is she kind
of the prettyish girl?
-Yeah.
-My whole tribe
thinks they're a couple.
-Okay.
Is there
anything tying on there?
-Well, they both
have couples back home.
-Oh.
Sam is actually engaged.
-Oh, okay.
-Oh, yeah. Okay.
They kind of made a really
tight, like, bond or whatever.
ROME:
My tribe has been making jokes
that they're a couple
this whole time.
KYLE:
We all kind of figured that Sam
was gonna be running
the show at Gata,
but you can't
run the show by yourself.
And so now that Anika
exposed this information to me,
I feel like I can use that
to my benefit
in the future.
ROME:
So, listen, my tribe,
it's Sol and Aysha.
They are
running the show over there.
-And, like,
you know what I'm saying?
-Damn.
-And, yeah, like, they've...
-Is it rubbing people
-the wrong way, kind of?
-It's rubbing me
the wrong way, but I think that
-they already have, like...
-They're already jiving.
Yeah, they're already jiving.
No. I've not...
Not one person
has talked strategy
-with me this whole game.
-KYLE: Dang.
ROME:
I want them to feel like
I'm on the bottom,
and I don't have anyone
that I'm working with over here.
Is that true?
May or may not be the case,
but guess what.
As long as they
go back to their tribes
and say that Sol and Aysha
are the ones running the show
over here,
that's all I need
because I need targets
on Sol and Aysha's backs.
-Oh, God. Okay.
-All right, guys.
-Good luck, guys.
ALL:
Hope to see you again.
-Best of luck to you.
-Best of luck, guys.
-Do your damage.
-Lovely meeting you.
-Good luck.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Whew.
(exhales sharply)
Dang.
Okay. So I have to pick once.
Wow. This is super risky.
So I've got a one-in-three
that I'm
gonna gain an advantage.
If a doctor told me
that the surgery was gonna have
a one-in-three chance of
me dying, I would never do it,
but I have no choice.
I'm playing with fire
either way.
My heart's beating.
I am nervous at this point
because
right now, with the losing
streak we have as a tribe,
I cannot lose my vote.
All right, money.
(sighs)
Dang.
Oh, my gosh. This sucks.
I'm not in a position
where I can, I can lose my vote.
I've already lost one vote.
I can't risk two.
I'm not gonna
go back in this bag.
Damn.
This is scary.
Now, it's a 50-50 chance
if I reach in again,
but the risk is so, so big.
(sighs)
I-I think I'm gonna,
I'm gonna stick
with my one Lose a Vote.
Let's do this.
(exhales sharply)
Please, please, please.
This is exactly
what I needed, baby.
Now I have an idol
and I've got a Steal a Vote.
Oh, my gosh.
I don't know if I was
really expecting to have
this much power in the game
this early,
but, hey, look, I told myself
this is what I wanted to do,
and I'm doing it, baby.
That's how you do it
on Survivor.
If I can show this
to my alliance,
this solidifies it
because there's no way that
the alliance would flip on me
since I've got a Steal a Vote.
Oh, my goodness.
I feel like
I'm running this game right now.
I feel like Survivor 47 is mine.
We might as well
rename it to Survivor Rome.
Ooh.
If I can make the last 20 days
anything like these first six,
you're looking at a Survivor
winner right here, baby.
Oh, this is everything.
♪ ♪
-Yeah.
-SIERRA: Oh, shoot.
That's crazy. (chuckles)
GENEVIEVE:
There's a boat.
It's Rome.
Whoo!
CAROLINE:
Hello.
-We're happy
to have you back.
-GABE: Give us the lowdown.
KYLE:
All right, let's go sit down.
I'll give you the lowdown, then.
-Okay. Are we ready
for story time?
-Yeah.
So, for starters,
they sent Kyle and Rome.
SAM:
I have a feeling
Anika is somebody
who is looking out for herself,
first and foremost.
So I have a lot of doubt
about whatever Anika says
probably
is not the entire truth.
And if not, why am I
not getting
the full side of the story?
They asked me,
were you two dating?
-(Andy laughs)
-Who?
-ANIKA: You two.
-You two.
-Us two?
-RACHEL: Oh, my God.
-(Andy laughs)
Yeah, they were like, "You got
to tell us. You got to tell us.
Is Sam and Sierra,
like, a thing?"
SAM:
This is ridiculous.
I am engaged.
Hannah, babe,
if you're watching this,
I am not in a relationship
with Sierra on Survivor.
It is a strict,
strategic relationship.
I promise you.
I'm thinking about you
the whole time,
and I'm talking about you
every day.
So they're not a thing.
-GABE AND SUE: Really?
-TIYANA: What?
They actually both have fiancés,
but Anika said
-that they're jiving
on a whole different note.
-GABE: Yeah.
-They're basically like
head dogs at the moment.
-Uh-huh.
-Wow.
-TIYANA: What the hell?
-Yeah.
That's crazy.
SIERRA:
What? I'm 27 years old.
He's 24 years old. He's engaged.
I'd better be engaged
when I get home.
So it's like, "Come on."
Like, it concerns me that now
there's this speculation
that Sam and I
are working together because
that could really
blow up both of our games.
So I'm not really sure where
they're getting that from,
but that's something we
definitely need to keep in mind
moving forward in this game.
KYLE:
There are three scrolls.
And so two of these scrolls
are Lose Your Vote.
Oh, no.
One of them is an advantage.
-TIYANA: Holy...
-KYLE: And you have to pick.
And so I put my hand in the bag,
and I nailed a Lost Your Vote.
No.
-I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
-...if you lost it two times.
So I lost my vote there.
So my ass is burnt
for the next Tribal Council.
-You had a choice
to play the game.
-RACHEL: Yeah.
And I chose to save my vote.
♪ ♪
ANIKA:
I don't want
Andy knowing
that I lost my vote,
but I need to make sure
that my alliance members
are aware of that
if we go to Tribal.
The thing is, there wasn't
a choice to play the game.
-I had to play the game.
-Okay.
And I had to reach in
and get a scroll.
And I unfortunately got one out
and it said, "Lose Your Vote."
-Okay. No worries.
-Okay.
-And...
-Okay, good.
-Fair.
Yeah.
SIERRA:
Don't let it stress you, though.
Don't let it get in your head.
You're good.
I think I'm actually okay.
-You're okay.
-Yeah.
Even though I lost my vote,
Sierra, Rachel and I--
we're solid.
They've given me the confidence
that I'll be okay.
I pick one,
and it was Lose Your Vote.
But in my head I'm like,
"There's no way
I'm going for the second one."
Like, I'm not losing my vote
for two Tribal Councils.
So I was like, "You know what?
I'll take the loss,
and that's it."
No, I don't. It was up there.
I just left it in the bag.
I left it at the table.
Yeah.
There is no way in living heck
that I'm telling Aysha and Sol
I got an advantage.
I was lying my butt off
to them, man.
They have no idea.
And right now I feel
like I'm playing it perfectly.
-All right. So, anything new
to actually say, or...?
-(chuckles)
-You think I would go out there
and lose my vote? Come on.
-Oh, my God.
So what'd you get this time?
-Steal a Vote.
-Get out.
Yep. So, guaranteed first Tribal
goes the way I want.
TEENY: Every advantage Rome
brings back, it kind of
pushes me more and more into
the alliance with him, Rome,
Genevieve and Kishan, because
there's not much I can do
when Rome has an idol
and Rome has a Steal a Vote.
You know? Like, those are things
that I can't really
fight against.
So I'd rather swim with.
"You now have power in the game.
This advantage
allows you to steal a vote."
TEENY:
If I'm reading it right,
Rome sees me, Genevieve, him
and Kishan as the Lavo four--
the group that's gonna go
into the merge together
and play this game.
I'm so happy for you and us.
TEENY:
I believe Rome's loyal.
He's shown us
with telling us
about his advantages,
and he's shown us
by being very clear
that he does not have
any interest in working
with Sol and Aysha.
♪ ♪
Bring in the boats.
That is the Survivor
rock star arrival right there.
What's going on, Gata?
Good morning, Jefe.
What up, Jeff?
PROBST:
Lavo and Gata
getting your first look
at the new Tuku tribe.
TK voted out
at the last Tribal Council.
ROME:
Wow.
Shocking.
Way to go, guys. (laughs)
PROBST:
All right.
-Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
-(all assent)
-First things first.
Got to take 'em back.
-Come on.
Come on.
Don't make me fight you for it.
Yeah, okay.
-Nice.
-Let's go.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
-(Rome exhales)
-For today's challenge,
one tribe member is gonna climb
to the top of a tall tower,
leap out into the ocean.
You're then gonna climb over
a crate and back into the ocean
where you will
retrieve a key underwater.
You're then going
to cross a balance beam
and swim to the finish.
The rest of the tribe is going
to run the same course,
only in pairs,
retrieving two more keys
along the way.
Once you have all your keys,
you will use them to unlock
and solve
a Survivor seahorse puzzle.
First two tribes
to finish win immunity,
safe from the vote, nobody
going home from your tribe.
In addition,
you're playing for a reward.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-(all assent)
PROBST:
It's not food,
but it'll help.
SUE:
Yes!
-PROBST: A large tarp.
-Hammock. Wow.
Two hammocks, the tarp.
(all exclaiming)
-I'll take that.
-Duly noted.
-Yes.
-Second tribe to finish--
no hammocks.
One small tarp will still
make a big difference.
-Yeah.
-PROBST:
The last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers,
got nothing for you but a date
with me at Tribal Council...
-Hell no.
-...where someone will be
the third person
voted out of Survivor 47,
and as a penalty
for losing,
I will keep your flint.
Tuku, you are playing
to earn yours back.
Before I send you out
into this challenge,
let's just take a moment,
because when you're at home
and you see this, you think,
"Oh, that'd be so fun."
Now that you're here
in the middle of the ocean
with a very tall tower
and a very deep ocean,
anybody here willing to say,
"It's a little more intimidating
than I thought
it might have been"?
-Absolutely.
-Definitely.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-PROBST: Kishan, what is it
now that you're out here?
I never knew how to swim
until four months
before I came out here.
-Wow.
-And I took swimming lessons,
so, of course, there's that
voice in the back of my head
that's like, "Dude,
you just learned how to do this.
"Now you're doing this
in an ocean.
"You're doing this exhausted
in a deep, deep ocean."
It-It's-it's scary. It becomes
very real, real quick.
-The ocean is definitely not
a swimming pool.
-Exactly.
All right, Lavo,
you have one extra person.
Sitting somebody out.
Cannot be Aysha.
Who's it gonna be?
-Me.
-PROBST:
Genevieve gonna sit out.
Now, I'm curious. I got to ask.
Kishan, you admitted
swimming is not your strength,
but you're gonna participate
in this one. Why?
You got to believe in yourself.
It's a mentality thing.
And if you don't
believe in yourself
and you start doubting yourself
in these moments,
it's gonna carry forward.
That's why you apply
to be on Survivor right there.
All right, Genevieve, take
a spot on the sit-out bench.
Everybody else,
give you a minute to strategize.
-We'll get it on. Let's do it.
-Yes! Let's go!
-SUE: Yes, I agree.
-CAROLINE: I agree. Sounds good.
Like, I'm-I'm gonna...
All right, fine.
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
-Go!
-GENEVIEVE: Go, Lavo!
Gonna be Kyle, Rome
and Andy in the water.
(overlapping shouting)
PROBST:
You got to climb to the top
of that tower and leap.
TIYANA:
Yeah, watch yourself. Let's go!
Go!
-Nice!
-PROBST:
Kyle in the water for Tuku.
-Look at Rome getting some air.
-SOL: Let's go, Rome!
AYSHA:
Nice, Rome!
PROBST:
Here comes Andy.
-(whooping)
-SAM: Come on, Andy!
PROBST:
Your next stop is that crate.
You got to climb up
and over the crate.
-SUE: Keep going, Kyle!
-PROBST: There goes Kyle
in the lead
for Tuku,
Rome right on his tail.
Kyle with a nice dive.
Rome in the water.
SUE:
Go, Kyle!
-Kyle up quickly with the buoy.
-(whooping)
Rome made it look easy.
-SOL: Let's go Rome!
-KISHAN: Let's go, Rome!
PROBST:
Andy underwater for Gata.
He's struggling,
didn't get it on the first go.
-SIERRA: Go, Andy!
-Now you've got
the balance beam.
-SUE: Go, Kyle!
-If you drop,
you got to go back.
-CAROLINE: Yes, Kyle!
-SUE: Go, Kyle!
Kyle has the buoy for Tuku.
-SOL: Go, Rome!
-Rome's across the balance beam.
-SAM: Go, Andy!
-PROBST: Andy has the buoy
for Gata.
Kyle, no issues
with this challenge at all.
-You're good, Tuku! Go!
-Go, Tuku.
You're now running in pairs.
Andy on the balance beam.
SIERRA:
Take your time.
PROBST:
He falls, got to go back.
-It's okay, Andy! You got this!
-PROBST: You're good, Lavo!
Go. Go, go, go, go, go!
PROBST: Gabe and Sue.
There they go.
TIYANA:
Yes!
Andy's still working
on that beam for Gata.
Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run, run, run!
SIERRA:
Yeah!
PROBST:
Oh, and a big fall. Nope.
Nope, you're no good.
-Foot hit the water.
-(overlapping shouting)
Come on, kid!
For Lavo,
it is Kishan and Aysha.
-GENEVIEVE: Come on, Kishan!
-ROME: You got this!
-Ready? Okay.
-Ready. Ready. Go.
(Genevieve whooping)
Yeah, Kishan!
-TIYANA: You got this, Sue!
-PROBST: Sue taking on
-that balance beam.
-CAROLINE: Let's go!
PROBST:
Sue is across.
-Let's go, Sue!
-GENEVIEVE: Go, Kishan!
You got it! You got it!
PROBST:
Kishan jumps.
He's back in the ocean.
PROBST: Taking on a challenge
that terrifies him.
Said he was afraid of heights,
said he was afraid of water,
but he's out here doing it!
Crawl, crawl, crawl.
PROBST:
Andy drops again.
-Andy!
-Crawl!
PROBST:
Gata in dead last.
-ANIKA: Crawl!
-PROBST: Gabe's good.
He's got the buoy.
Tuku in the lead now.
-Come on, Andy.
-PROBST: Andy just needs
to keep his feet out
of the water.
SIERRA:
You got it, Andy! Nice work!
PROBST:
You're good, Andy.
All right, guys, you got this.
-You're good, Gata!
-Yeah! Dig deep!
You're good, Tuku! Go!
-Kishan taking his time.
-GENEVIEVE: Good job, Kishan!
Undoing the knots,
trying to release that buoy.
TEENY:
You got it, you got it.
-Oh, no.
-PROBST: Kishan falls.
Got to go back.
It's gonna be Sam and Anika
for Gata.
Ready? Let's go. Let's go!
SUE:
You got it. Looking good.
Yeah, baby. Let's go.
Gata trying to catch Lavo now.
Kishan and Aysha
have taken a long time
on this part of the challenge.
So much so that Gata,
after a disastrous run
by Andy, is now back in it.
We got a challenge.
SOL:
There we go! There we go!
PROBST:
Aysha has the buoy.
Can she keep her feet out
of the water?
-Good job.
-SOL: That-a girl, Aysha!
PROBST:
Aysha's across. You're good.
Anika's across. Here comes Sam.
Nice work!
PROBST:
Gata has now passed Lavo.
SIERRA:
Yeah!
It's now Lavo in last place.
SUE:
Good job, TT!
-Let's go!
-PROBST: Tiyana with the buoy.
SUE:
You're rocking it, girl!
-Here comes Lavo.
-ROME: Good job, Aysha.
Go, Gata! It's gonna be
Rachel and Sierra now for Gata.
You're good, Lavo! Go!
(whooping)
PROBST: Sol and Teeny
now for Lavo, the last pair.
You're good, Tuku.
Start working on the puzzle.
One, two, three.
-SAM: Attagirl, Si.
-PROBST: Rachel and Sierra leap
from the platform.
(indistinct shouting)
There goes Sol and Teeny
for Lavo.
Whoo! You got this,
-you got this.
-Let's go, guys.
PROBST:
The faster you get back here,
the sooner
you are working on that puzzle.
It's a Survivor seahorse puzzle.
-PROBST:
It's Tuku in the lead still.
-Let's go.
PROBST:
Pieces got to stay on the table.
Now you've got the beam
and one final buoy.
Rachel untying the buoy.
She's got it free.
Sol, nice job on the beam.
-Making that look easy.
-Good job, Sol!
PROBST:
Gata's across!
You're good, Gata!
SAM:
Come on, girls!
-You got this, Teeny.
-(groans)
PROBST:
No, Teeny's got to go back.
Come on, you guys.
Got to get everybody
up here first.
-You got it.
-PROBST: You're good, Gata.
Start working on the puzzle.
-Let's go, girls.
-It's gonna be Anika
and Rachel on the puzzle.
It is Gabe and Caroline
on the puzzle for Tuku.
GENEVIEVE:
Good job, Teeny.
PROBST:
Teeny has the buoy for Lavo.
It's all good. It's all good.
Teeny back in. Got to go again.
Come on, come on, come on!
TIYANA:
It's all right, guys.
You got it.
Got a lot of time. Here we go.
Nice and methodical.
PROBST:
Day seven, Survivor 47.
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
Caroline, yes.
-Let's go, Teeny. You got this.
-Teeny at that same spot.
Teeny, you're good. Let's go.
ROME:
There you go.
Let's go, guys!
-GENEVIEVE: Good job!
-AYSHA: Right here, right here.
ROME:
Let's go. Right here,
right here. I'll take the buoy.
-I'll take the buoy.
-Looking for two tribes.
Rachel with a piece for Gata.
Gabe and Caroline
doing a nice job together.
Rachel with another piece
-for Gata.
-Beautiful.
Gata's got some momentum
right now.
Lavo would like to get
a little momentum, get in this.
Does this go here? No.
Caroline trying
to get another piece for Tuku.
Will it fit?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
And it does.
That's another piece for Tuku.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
PROBST:
Rachel with another piece.
Lavo now in trouble
and decidedly in last place.
The only tribe that hasn't gone
to Tribal Council.
It is Gata and Tuku
doing a great job on the puzzle.
That's it. That's it.
PROBST:
Lavo in dead last.
The inevitable appears
to be coming.
Yeah, that one right there.
That one that-- That was it,
that was it, that was it.
That was literally the piece.
-I saw it.
-Yeah, this could be right.
PROBST:
It is Gata, then Tuku.
Yes. Yeah.
-SAM: Yes. Yes.
-PROBST:
Gata with another piece.
Gata down to three pieces now.
This is in the deep freeze.
Lavo's going to Tribal Council.
I'm gonna call it.
Genevieve can only watch.
Rachel trying to get
that piece in. She's got it.
Gata down to their last piece.
For immunity and reward.
-Gata has it.
-(screaming)
Gata wins immunity and reward--
large tarp
and two hammocks.
It now just comes
to a nice finish for Tuku.
SUE:
You got it, Gabe.
There it is.
Tuku down to two now,
as Tribal Council's inevitable
for Lavo.
Tuku down to their last piece.
(cheering)
PROBST:
There it is.
-Tuku wins immunity and reward.
-(cheering)
Safe from Tribal Council,
sending Lavo to Tribal Council
for the first time
this season, where somebody
will be the third person
voted out of Survivor 47.
Ah! Come on!
Gata, congratulations.
Nobody going home from Gata.
No Tribal Council tonight.
In addition, nice reward
waiting for you back at camp.
Hot day like this,
that tarp will help a lot.
Two hammocks will make things
a little more comfortable.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
Tuku, nice job.
(overlapping chatter)
Yeah.
PROBST: Nobody going home from
Tuku, no Tribal Council tonight.
Smaller tarp waiting for you
back at camp.
-Well done.
-Appreciate it.
-In addition...
-(whooping)
...you also earned
your flint back.
-Thank you.
-We'll take it.
All right, swim out,
enjoy the night off.
-Big jump?
-PROBST: Celebrate.
-Go, guys.
-(laughing): Yay!
(Kyle howls)
All right, Lavo.
New part of the game, Rome.
You have not had
to vote somebody out.
Some fans would say you haven't
actually played Survivor
until you've gone
to Tribal Council.
What are you feeling right now?
I mean, me personally,
I'm feeling
a lot of nervousness. I mean,
I came back from the journey and
told my tribe
exactly what happened.
So they all know
that I don't have a vote.
So, really, I have no say
in what happens tonight.
So I'm just gonna be sitting
there like a bump on a log.
So, who knows
how tonight's gonna go?
All right, Lavo,
Tribal Council tonight,
where somebody will be the third
person voted out of Survivor 47.
And as a penalty for losing,
I'm gonna take your flint.
Sorry for you, Genevieve.
-(Genevieve sighs)
-You will have a chance
to earn it back
at the next challenge.
Swim out. See you tonight
at Tribal Council.
SOL:
Apparently,
Rome does not have a vote.
Just from reading
his body language,
I think that guy's lying.
I don't believe
what he's saying right now.
But we just need
to be prepared for everything
because who knows
what could happen tonight?
Outwit, outplay, outlast.
Think you have what it takes?
Apply to be on Survivor.
♪ ♪
AYSHA:
Yeah. We win as a team,
we lose as a team.
Yeah, that was a tough one.
Those are the breaks.
-How about we move on?
-TEENY: Yeah.
-GENEVIEVE: Mm-hmm.
Let's not dwell.
So... what now?
...does anyone want to go home?
-Yeah. Who wants
to volunteer to leave?
-(Kishan laughs)
All right. Okay.
We got that out of the way.
TEENY:
This loss means that it's time
for lines to be drawn,
lines that I've been really,
really procrastinating
having to show.
My number one is Kishan.
And I know that we're leaning
more towards working
with Rome and Genevieve.
That means the decision is now
who to vote out-- Sol or Aysha.
I have to decide
and try to hurt as little amount
of people as possible
so that I can still keep
this position I'm in,
which is pretty good.
How are you feeling?
-I mean, I feel so good
with you guys.
-Mm-hmm.
I feel scared,
the same as I did about Rome.
(sputters)
AYSHA:
Then how would you feel
if it was Genevieve?
TEENY:
I think it's the safer option.
AYSHA:
I would love more than anything
to target Rome, but I cannot,
because we have
this large suspicion
that he has something
that he found on this beach,
because
that man was looking like
his life depended on it.
And then there was a hard stop,
and he just stopped looking.
If we focus today
on getting out Genevieve,
'cause I just don't think
we can get Rome out.
-I don't see us there.
-No, I don't. Neither do I.
-We can't take that risk.
-Exactly.
But I just want to let you know
that, like,
if they start talking
-and it seems like
it's gonna be one of you...
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Okay.
-I do.
-I really do.
-I appreciate that.
I would not be comfortable
with you going home.
With Aysha,
I want her to feel like
I'm good with her and that I'm
going with our original plan,
that I'm working with her
and Sol and Kishan.
Though, in small ways,
I'm trying to give her
little warnings that, "Hey,
"just maybe this might not go
the way you want.
"And if it doesn't,
are you going to be down
"to work with me
and vote out Sol
to preserve your own life
in this game?"
So, the plan is actually going
to be Aysha,
-but we want Sol to play
his Shot in the Dark, so...
-Okay.
-I hear you. I hear you.
-That's.... and... Yeah.
You know, if I had to choose
one, I would choose Sol.
ROME:
Okay. What's your reasoning?
Teeny started
to break it down a little bit,
and she made perfect sense,
because right now, for my game,
the biggest threat is someone
else finding that next idol,
because I have
to play mine tonight.
You made such a good point.
-'Cause I have
to play my idol tonight.
-You have to.
Which means that there's gonna
be an idol back out here.
Yes, absolutely. And you know
it's gonna be a mad dash.
The second I get back to camp,
I'm hitting the jungle
in the middle of the night.
-Exactly.
-Like, I'm that type of person.
And you know who else would?
-Sol.
I have wanted to vote out Sol
since the start of this game.
I cannot stand the dude
at this point.
So the fact that it ended up
turning from Aysha over to Sol,
that just made me smile
ear to ear.
I'd be willing to write
Sol's name down lickety-split.
I cannot wait
to do that tonight.
So as long as we can get him
to not play
his Shot in the Dark,
then the plan is foolproof.
-But...
-Oh, do you?
-Yeah.
-'Cause I have no ... clue.
-Yeah, well...
-So...
I'm, at this point,
99% sure it's gonna be Aysha.
-99? Bro.
-Mm.
-Yeah.
-99% is a done deal,
and we've been here
for 30 minutes.
I mean, it wasn't really a lot
of conversations...
-Really?
-...to have. Yeah. Like...
-Ah...
-They-they feel like
they want to keep you around
-because you're strong.
-Thank God.
And you do carry us through
a lot of these challenges
-and different parts of it.
-All right, man.
And I don't have a vote,
so I literally don't have a say.
So all I'm doing
is getting information
-from other people, you know?
-Yeah.
ROME:
Being in character
and playing it
like I don't have a vote,
it comes natural, man.
I can lie in Survivor
all day long.
I'm sorry, Mom. I know
you're gonna be disappointed
watching this right now, but
I'm lying
for my life in the game.
I'm playing hard, man.
If Boston Rob was the godfather,
there's got to be
a godson somewhere, right?
SOL:
Is there any chance
that you're coming up to me,
saying, "Hey, Aysha's the name"?
I mean, why... why would I...?
To make me feel good,
and then it's like,
"Hey, y'all, it's-it's Sol."
It's a... it's a...
it's a question that...
-I mean, I don't know...
-It's a potential, right?
It's a potential?
I guess, but, like, I just don't
see the point in me doing that.
-Yeah.
-'Cause I don't have a vote.
So, like, I'm trying
to stay good with everybody.
-Right, right, right.
All right, cool.
-Just in case, like...
-You know what I'm saying?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, that would only hurt me
if I was like...
That's right. That's right.
I-I get what you're saying,
but, yeah, that just doesn't...
Yeah. No. Like, I...
Tonight I can't.
I just got to be honest
with everybody and stay mellow.
That's-that's my best game plan,
like I said.
That's all I could do, so...
SOL:
Rome is talking to me
like I'm an idiot.
"Sol, I don't have a vote,
"so I'm not gonna get voted out.
"Just so you know, everyone
is gonna vote Aysha out."
I don't know if Rome
is just completely clueless...
If I was you,
I'd just draw the continent.
Asia. Like...
(laughing)
Yeah. That would be
very cool of me.
...or if Rome
is one of the best
Survivor players ever.
ROME:
Me and Sol just talked, and
-I told Sol that
the plan is gonna be Aysha.
-KISHAN: Mm-hmm.
"And if you want to be
on the right side of the vote,
you should just vote Aysha."
And he was like,
"It sucks, but I want
to stay in the game, so..."
There was no inkling
he was scared
-about maybe using
the Shot in the Dark?
-I made him feel
really good about it, so...
Is there any world where
we bring in Aysha on this four?
-Yes.
-TEENY: Yeah.
KISHAN:
Aysha's genuinely someone
I would love to work with
in the future
because
she is such a strategist.
This is also a bit
of a selfish move
of looping Aysha into the plan
because I want it to be
that Teeny and I tell her, so
that, going forward, she knows,
"We saved your butt
'cause your name was gonna be
the vote today."
Okay. So he does for sure?
-TEENY: He's not telling us.
-Right.
TEENY:
There's only one guaranteed,
I feel, safe situation to do,
and it is vote Sol.
AYSHA:
The fact that they trusted me
with that information about
Rome's idol means the world.
But I don't want Sol to go home.
I think the worst thing
in the world that we could do
is keep Genevieve
and Rome together.
KISHAN:
Yeah, but, hey...
Aysha is not budging
from wanting
to vote out Genevieve.
And, you know,
that's definitely
very concerning, 'cause if Aysha
keeps discounting
any potential other options,
that's really hard
to work with going forward.
She was not...
-KISHAN: She was not budging.
-...hearing us.
TEENY:
I feel a very close
personal connection with Aysha,
and I know we're both rooting
for each other
in this game
and want to work together,
but she's kind of digging
her own grave at this point.
TEENY:
So tonight the question is,
if Aysha won't work with me
and vote out Sol, is it worth
keeping her in this game?
But, yeah,
somebody's gonna be upset.
Somebody's going to be betrayed.
But I have to make the decision
that's going
to guarantee me
to go further in this game.
♪ ♪
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead and grab a torch,
dip it in, and get fire.
♪ ♪
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council,
because in this game
fire represents your life,
and when the fire is gone,
so are you.
So let's get into it.
The first Tribal Council
for this group.
-Rome, every first...
-(Rome laughs)
-Why are you laughing?
-I just
was, like, hoping
that you didn't pick me first,
but it's okay.
Let's do this, man. We here.
PROBST:
Is there a curse about getting
-the first question?
-TEENY: No.
-That's just Rome.
-ROME: I got a superstition
about sitting
in the front middle,
and I'm sitting
in the front middle.
So, I mean, I already got
a lot of nerves already.
-Yeah. We're already 0 for 2.
-ROME: Yeah, exactly, exactly.
-Not looking good.
-Yeah. No, sir.
Let's do something different.
Let's go to Genevieve.
-(Rome sputters)
-Genevieve.
-Thanks, Rome.
What I was gonna ask was,
coming into tonight,
what do you think this tribe
hopes to be with tonight's vote?
GENEVIEVE:
I think everyone
today was a little emotional
because tonight's
killing someone's dream,
and so the hope is
that the five
who go back are still cohesive.
So, Sol, do you get the feeling
that tonight's vote is based
on trying
to make the tribe stronger,
or this is about alliances and
I got to make sure I'm in one?
I thought
it was about alliances.
I felt really good
with who I was paired with, but
I got a very uneasy feeling
in my stomach, and so...
So, as we sit here right now,
you're feeling that uncertainty?
Yeah, it's, uh,
it's not a good feeling
that I'm feeling right now.
Can you overthink it, Rome?
You can definitely overthink it.
Once you get paranoid
and, you know, you start
talking with people, and
you might say the wrong thing,
and that might make them think,
"Oh, man,
this person's
not really trusting me."
Even though
they weren't gonna be the vote,
now they will be the vote
just because
they're getting
a little bit too paranoid.
PROBST:
Aysha, do you feel the same way?
That it can literally
change like that?
Everything was fine,
then somebody says the wrong
thing and everything shifts?
Yeah, it can change
at the drop of a hat.
Like, you could have
a conversation with a person,
and an hour later
they're not being as reassuring.
It's like, "Oh, okay,
maybe that may not be the plan.
"Maybe that was just something
in the moment just to tell me.
Maybe I should be worried."
PROBST:
Kishan, the dangerous part
of somebody feeling
on the outside
is something as simple
as the Shot in the Dark
or some other advantage
or idol in the game.
Did you sense
that there's someone
feeling on the outs today?
I did not sense that, and
that's probably a misperception
on my end, because, for me,
I'm strong to the core four.
And you know, I want to go ahead
and move forward
with whatever we believe in.
-So...
-PROBST: Who's the core four?
-I'm not gonna say.
-But there is four?
-Maybe.
-PROBST: Teeny?
TEENY:
I mean,
when he says "core four,"
you have no choice
but to believe him.
It's interesting because people
who aren't involved in the plan
have to know something.
So you have to be talking
to everybody.
And if that means that you feel
like you trust somebody enough
to where you're locked in
with them,
and you don't need to reassure
them as much, then there you go.
Sol, that sounds like a message.
If you're part of the core four,
the core four is saying,
"Dude, come on,
we're good. Relax."
SOL:
Yeah,
that's what it sounds like, um,
but this is Survivor,
and I'm trying to find out,
is this, like, part of the game
where I'm going crazy,
or is it, they're just
having, like,
real conversations with people?
You know what I'm saying?
And I hope I'm not going crazy.
PROBST:
Kishan,
it's a fine line because,
as Aysha was saying,
you want to make sure
you're solid,
but if you dip into the well
one more time,
you might say the wrong thing.
Do you worry about that as well?
KISHAN:
Yes. It's so easy
to get tripped up.
And that did complicate things,
which is, I think,
what's causing
this uneasiness,
because now we're just like,
"Holy cow. How many
other different conversations
"were happening that
"I wasn't a part of or
someone else wasn't a part of?
"Maybe if we just took
a step back
"and kind of kept it
a bit more calm,
maybe those feelings
wouldn't arise."
Today felt like you're in
this trio of best friends.
Like, you have a group chat.
You talk every day, right?
Three people.
But then you're just walking.
You know,
you're walking your dogs,
and you look in a restaurant,
and the other two
are having lunch.
And you're like,
"Wait. They didn't put that
"in the group chat.
Like, what's going on?
"Like, I'm so confused.
Do I go up?"
Because I'm a part of this.
Like, I should feel welcome
to come up.
Genevieve, Aysha's example
is straight out of real life.
Sometimes
it's a misunderstanding.
Sometimes there's more to it.
Is that a relatable experience
for you out here?
Yeah. You don't know
what is real and what is not
and what's a bluff and
what is not and who's looking.
Like, you know, Sol's making
eyes at Aysha across the back.
And you don't know,
like, how much
do I dial in on this or not?
PROBST:
Even you just saying that
now lights up Teeny,
who looks at Sol and says, "Why
are you making eyes at Aysha?"
You're fighting
for a million dollars.
This is Survivor right here.
You're in the belly
of the beast right now.
We're about to vote.
If you're not playing,
it probably is you, and
it should be you going home.
So, Kishan,
what's your take on this?
All that cohesion
that we talked about?
Yes, it's nice,
but it's honestly just a facade.
And we pushed it off as long
as we could until we needed to.
And at the end of the day,
we knew
that one person's name
will be written down,
and they will be voted off.
And that's a harsh reality
that we all knew
when we came in today.
All right, we feel good to vote,
or do we need to talk more?
I just want
to say one more thing.
I don't want
to call anybody out,
but I hope the person
that agreed
to vote with me sticks to that.
Otherwise, I know that I could
be at risk of going home,
or an ally could be
at risk of going home.
♪ ♪
PROBST:
And on that note,
it is time to vote.
Aysha, you're up.
♪ ♪
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
One second, Jeff.
I got full faith in the people
that I have faith in,
but I went on a journey
at an absolute perfect time,
and, you know,
I was able to get an idol
that's good
for one Tribal Council, so
I'm gonna use it now, but
I don't think it's me tonight
'cause I got faith in the people
that I got faith in,
and I'm just gonna ride
with that.
This is a hidden immunity idol.
Any votes cast
for Rome will not count.
I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Rome,
does not count.
Genevieve.
Sol. One vote-- Sol.
♪ ♪
Aysha. One vote-- Aysha,
one vote-- Genevieve,
one vote-- Sol.
Aysha. Two votes-- Aysha,
one vote-- Genevieve,
one vote-- Sol.
♪ ♪
Third person voted out
of Survivor 47--
Aysha.
Need to bring me your torch.
(sighs)
Yeah.
That really hurts.
I'm not gonna lie.
Wow.
Was it you, too, Sol?
No.
Aysha, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
-Good luck.
-SOL: Thank you.
-Bye, Aysha.
-Thank you.
-Love you, Aysha.
Grab your torches,
head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
SAM: Andy's like
Survivor George Costanza.
Andy!
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
No. It's Survivor.
I don't have to.
What the hell?!
TIYANA:
We found Sue,
and there's blood everywhere.
People on TV make Survivor
look so much easier than it is.
Day one, I was saying,
"This is the hardest thing
I've ever done
in my entire life."
And so, to be able
to last seven days,
I really can pat myself
on my back.
Just having the experience
to go from the podcast mic
to actually putting my feet
in the Fijian sand--
it means everything.
(roars)