My god.
Yes!
Bye.
That's insane.
Previously on survivor...
Yeah.
The five of us are uniting.
One of us... And we're gonna
flip this game on its head.
Genevieve telling Rachel that
she's dragging me is laughable.
I've been playing a game
that no one is seeing.
I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of being
underestimated in this game.
- Kyle? - Yes.
- But we have to get him first.
I knew his day would come,
and I've been drooling... ...for this day.
Eleventh person voted out
and the fourth member of our jury: Kyle.
The tribe has spoken.
I'm hoping that this thing
will last through the night,
so, we'll push these
down a little bit more.
You know, Kyle was definitely a big part
of the fabric of season 47.
Tonight, I am on top
of the world, because
Kyle is now gone.
It was always just about his story.
- Right.
- It was, like, the Kyle show.
It was too annoying
and I couldn't let it go.
The longer he was here, the
more annoying he became.
He walked around calling Caroline and I
"tweedleydee and tweedleydum."
And tonight, we got sweet,
sweet, sweet revenge.
I was, like, dead set on having him gone.
He was taking away our opportunity
and slowly just picking
off, one by one, all of us,
right? Because he was winning.
Having Kyle was a really,
really useful shield, but
there's really nothing I could have done.
I was kind of powerless tonight,
because there is a posse
of five players: Andy,
teeny, Rachel, sue and Caroline,
picking off the big threats one at a time.
- Final seven.
- Yay.
Unbelievable.
Genevieve and I are in a really tight spot,
but this game is not over for us yet.
And as long as I'm on this island,
I'm gonna fight.
It's supposed to be two
thirds, so, that's right.
Okay, let's light it.
Maybe we'll let it keep
cooking like that a little bit more.
Here, I'll do
I practiced making rice
before this, like, once.
I'm actually so not a cook.
Really, at this point,
no one is as close as sue and I.
I wonder if sometimes she sees
her daughter in me in terms of
if her daughter was playing,
maybe she imagines this is
what her daughter would be playing like.
I'm proud of you, you know?
As a duo, we have
all of the tools and all of the roles that
we need to make it to the end.
I'm a planner, I'm a strategist,
but I feel like sue is my provider,
and she's most willing to,
like, put her neck out there
and do the dirty work.
- We're animals, aren't we?
- Yeah.
She is the one who's crawling
through the mud, searching for idols.
Come on.
She's, like, literally crawling
on, like, you know, hands and knees,
getting dirtier, dirtier every single day.
We all know getting to the end
on survivor is complex
and messy and crazy,
but I could not think
of a better alliance to go to the end with.
Yesterday, I was, like,
discounting your game.
That was so, like,
stupid and unfair of me,
and, like, I hope we can
still be friends after this,
that'll you'll forgive me, - I...
'Cause I'm really sorry, honestly.
- That was so disrespectful.
- Of course.
I had no business
doing that, and I feel like,
now you feel, like, awkward around me.
- And I'm so sorry, Andy.
- I know what we signed up for.
Like, we're playing a game.
And within that game comes perception
of other people's games, and it's all fair.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry to
make it uncomfortable
- with you guys.
- It's okay.
I've sort of been branded as someone
who is just calculated and strategic
and doesn't really care about people.
And in this game, if everyone is afraid
that I'm too big, too much,
I think the best thing
for my game is to shrink.
Game-wise, we've had...
We've had an interesting
relationship, and I
just think it's kind of fun.
I think what's also fun is
that we're both still in it.
Well, I think you'll be in it for a long time.
I think I'm... I'm, in it for now.
I would love to be, like,
the big, bad wolf, still,
but that is going to end my time
quicker than playing possum.
And at this point, I will play possum.
I will play sad puppy dog
with tail between its legs.
I'll play giraffe, elephant, whatever I need
to play to stay in this game a little longer.
I'm really not that dangerous,
you know. You've-you've
taken off my claws and teeth,
and now I'm just a house cat.
There are folks on this beach
that are the bigger
threat than I am right now.
Look where we've ended up, Genevieve.
From the insane asylum of lavo,
all the way to beka beach,
where bad things happen.
I do think if Rachel goes out,
everyone's chances
of winning get better.
- I hear you.
- Like, I think
everybody actually likes her the most.
She's playing the
game that I wish I played.
It is, like, very calculated,
organized and controlled.
You think that's what the jury's thinking,
is Rachel is the biggest threat right now?
Rachel has been, like,
tactical about everything,
like, flawlessly.
Like.
I'm not a slam dunk
for you if Rachel is there.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Sounds like a threat.
I say it's not a slam dunk for you
and then you come back
and tell me that's a threat?
Okay, that was a... thing to say.
Genevieve doesn't respect my game.
She doesn't think I can beat Rachel.
And I'm insulted by her words.
You definitely use
emotions as a weapon.
Genevieve is desperate,
trying to cause some chaos,
and I'm not falling into that trap
because Sam and Genevieve
are both on the bottom.
They're people who have hurt me
in the past, they're people
who bothered me in this game.
I'm just giving you my
opinion, 'cause you asked.
All right.
At this point in our
coalition of underdogs,
we're sick of Genevieve and Sam.
We're scared of Genevieve and Sam.
One of them is going home,
and there's nothing they can do about it.
So awkward.
My god.
I hate that they're almost, like, just c...
Wallowing together. I don't know.
Like, commiserating, but, like...
They just think...
No. I mean, they're-they're
very outwardly joking
- about how they know it's them two.
- Yeah.
It's almost, like, uncomfortable.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Yeah.
I found out this morning
that Sam and Genevieve are
actively trying to target me
and giving all these
reasons why I'm going to win.
It is scary, but I also feel pretty secure
in the people that I have my trust in.
I think that, no matter how
scary they make me out to be,
they're always going to
be more scary than me.
But also, I do
have this idol that nobody
knows about, and I do have
a block a vote advantage,
and the alliance of five knows about it.
All of them.
So, I feel good.
And I'm loaded. Locked and loaded.
Come on in.
Boy.
All right, shall we get to today's
reward challenge?
For today's challenge, you're gonna race
through a series of obstacles
and retrieve a ball from a net tunnel.
Then you'll retrieve a second ball
and crawl under a net to the finish,
where you will attempt to land both balls
on a two-level perch.
First player to finish wins a reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
The winner will enjoy a nice
afternoon at the sanctuary,
where good things happen.
An afternoon filled with.
Italian food.
Pizza.
Cheese.
- Cheese. My god.
- Pepperoni.
- Margarita.
How about some pasta?
- Bolognese?
- Yeah.
Mushroom? Yeah.
Crisp, fresh, Caesar salad.
Fixings?
Fixings. Why not?
- Yeah.
- You like red wine?
Some red wine or soda,
if you prefer, and for dessert, tiramisu.
Worth playing for? All right.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get it on. Here we go.
- Wow.
- Sanctuary awaits.
Sure.
All right, here we go.
For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go! First you got to get rid
of all those sandbags.
Three of them are easy. Push 'em over.
Three of them are tied up.
You're gonna have to
quickly untie those knots.
Then you go over the
same way the bags go over.
Just keep ripping through that rope.
Launch those sandbags
and toss yourself over,
and you're on to the next stage.
Rachel, you're good.
Rachel's over first.
Rachel in the lead.
There's Sam right behind.
Got to move that ball
through the net tunnel.
Here comes Andy.
- Ooh!
- There's Genevieve.
Here comes Caroline.
Ooh.
There goes teeny. Here comes sue.
Everybody now in the net tunnel.
You can go from the side,
you can go from the top,
you can go from the bottom.
You just want to move that ball.
Rachel still in the lead, moving quickly
through this second stage.
And it's Sam and Genevieve on the end.
Everybody else trying to catch up.
Rachel close.
She's got it. Rachel still in the lead.
Rachel now gonna
untie that second ball.
Genevieve has it!
Here comes Andy now.
Sam's at the very end.
Got to knock it through, Sam.
Rachel has her second ball.
She's working through
the net crawl with both balls.
Sam's in it now.
Got four people in the
third stage of this challenge.
- Let's go.
- Rachel still in the lead.
Good job, Sam. You got this.
Let's go, man. Let's go, man.
Genevieve has her second ball.
Teeny through the net tunnel.
She's at the third stage now.
Genevieve working to catch Rachel.
Here goes Sam. Quickly
got his second ball.
Sam now ripping through this net.
Sam is making up a ton of time.
Sam is gonna catch Rachel.
And Sam comes out
ahead of Rachel now.
It's Sam and Rachel
at the final stage of this challenge.
Here comes Andy.
On the end is Genevieve.
Caroline, sue, still back
at the second stage.
Now you got to land both balls,
one on each level of this perch.
Andy's through now.
He's in on it.
Sam lands his first ball.
Sam can win it with this toss.
On and off.
Here comes teeny. She's
in. Genevieve's in on it now.
Rachel with a toss.
Andy trying to land his first.
It is Sam in the lead.
Would be a nice victory for Sam today.
An afternoon at the sanctuary.
Rachel lands her first ball. We are tied.
It is Rachel and Sam both
now working on that second
and final ball. Sam on and off.
Rachel could win it.
No, just short.
Sam is on and off again.
Rachel could win it.
On and off.
- Yes!
- Sam does it!
- It's over.
- My god.
Sam wins reward,
good job, Sam. An
afternoon at the sanctuary
for pizza and pasta.
- Amazing.
- Wow.
Fun finish.
No problem, man.
Sam, come on over.
- Good job, Sam.
- Good job.
Well done.
So, here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna go to the sanctuary.
Nice afternoon.
Pizza, pasta.
When the afternoon ends,
you'll have a pillow, you'll have a blanket,
'cause you're gonna spend the night.
My god.
Get what might be your only
good night's sleep out here.
This is the fuel you need
for these last six days.
And to make it a little more enjoyable
and a lot more complicated,
you will also have
your letters from home.
What?
You're gonna have a
little reminder of why
you are out here.
So now, big decision.
- Yeah.
- Choose one person to join you.
Yeah.
The problem with being in this position,
as happy as I am for myself,
there's people that I have to
take that opportunity away from,
and that's difficult to stomach.
Nobody wants to miss
out on the letters, Jeff.
So, the letters are arguably
more valuable than the food.
It's more important... it's
more important than the food
for most of the people here, I think.
- I...
- Genevieve, agree with that?
- Yeah.
- You can't even talk.
Sue, what's going on with you?
I understand he has a
really tough decision to make,
and I know every single one of
us has the exact same reason
of why we want our letters from home.
So, it's gonna be hard,
you know, for anybody
who doesn't get those letters.
There's one person here that I promised
I would take on a reward no matter what.
I think they're the most
deserving person over there.
So I'm gonna go with Andy.
- Good job, Andy.
- Andy.
Andy, you look surprised.
Come on over.
Thanks, man.
Andy, why so shocked,
given that Sam's already
told you he would take you?
I'm the last person I expected
to be picked for this
reward, to be honest.
I'm... Game-wise, we're up and down,
and I don't think we're on the
best terms currently, game-wise.
I-I do what I say I'm gonna do.
Yeah.
And I told Andy I would
take him, so... I take him.
All right, Sam, you have
one more choice. That's it.
So three of you are
gonna be at the sanctuary.
Four players will be back at camp
with nothing but some rice.
Tell me who your final choice is and why.
I don't think it would be right
for me to eat Italian
food without Genevieve,
- so I'm gonna pick Genevieve.
- Genevieve,
come on over.
Thanks, man.
All right, here's what's gonna happen.
Sam, Genevieve, Andy,
you're gonna leave here,
enjoy the nice afternoon.
You'll spend the night. You'll
return to camp in the morning.
Grab your stuff, head out.
- I'm sorry, guys. Sorry.
- You're gonna slam some pasta.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Well done. You earned it.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Jeff.
All right, they're gone.
So, what impact does this
have, game-wise, if any?
'Cause this is always a
big turning point. Teeny.
I mean, Genevieve
and Sam have already
made themselves a very clear duo
in that they're both the targets
and the threats in this game.
And as far as I see it,
relying on me to try and pull me in
- to get one of the remaining people out.
- Right.
So, leaving me here
and not choosing me
it-it definitely pushes me one way.
And so, I think it was
a bit of a foolish decision
for Sam to pick her.
I think it's actually going
to have a horrible
outcome for their game.
- Yeah.
- All right, Caroline,
Rachel, teeny, sue, got nothing for you.
- Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
- Thank you.
Hope they enjoy the last supper.
Yeah. We're eating all the rice.
Loved ones letters is always contentious.
People get pissed. It's
like choosing bridesmaids.
Like, you just don't want to do it.
And so, as hard as it
was to lose that challenge,
Sam doing this and just, like,
pissing off so many people is
a pretty good thing for
my game and my alliance.
It's going to make us tighter.
- Lady and gentlemen...
- Welcome to the sanctuary.
My god.
Can't win immunity to save my life,
but boy, can I win reward. Third time
at the sanctuary. I
feel like a seasoned vet
showing a couple of
rookies the lay of the land.
Food! Gorgeous!
- Shall we? - It smells so good.
- Yeah, let's figure it out.
Probably not a big shocker
that I've never had tiramisu,
but this is not just Italian food.
This is an overnight reward
with blankets, and the cherry on top:
Loved ones' letters, something that every
survivor player dreams of getting.
- Cheers. - Cheers. Cheers.
- Final seven.
- Loved ones.
- Italian feasts. - My god.
- Thank you, Sam.
- Thank you so much.
Yeah, man. I knew
coming into the challenge
that I wanted to pick you two,
but I hope the people at
camp aren't mad at me.
No.
Dude, Andy, you've been through
21 days of this game
with a lot of really low lows.
You've kept a smile through all of it.
I have so much respect for that.
And early in the game, I was not
the friend or ally to you that
I needed to be, and so, I
want to make up for that.
- I'm speechless right now.
- Yeah.
- So...
- Dude, it means everything.
Yeah, man.
There are probably four people at camp
that are not thrilled with me right now,
but I knew I was gonna choose Andy
before the challenge
even started because
I feel like I do owe Andy a little bit.
My god, this is basil.
And Genevieve and I have felt like
we are on the bottom.
So, giving her the emotional support
of letters from home... easy no-brainer.
This is, like, insane,
like, timing for this day.
Like, Sam, you don't
know this yet, but I talked
to Andy this morning,
it got a little intense,
and now I'm, like, the happiest I've been.
Can I ask you something?
- Genevieve okay.
- I'm-I'm just curious
to your non-emotional approach.
Like, where do you
think that comes from?
I wasn't planning to be
closed off and detached,
but kishan was, like,
one of my first friends here.
- Yeah.
- And when we voted him out,
his, like, last words were, "I trusted you."
Like, very, very sincerely and very sadly.
And I just kind of, at that point, was like,
"I don't want to get
emotionally close to people
"or, like, let them get close to me,
knowing I'm going to vote them out."
And I kind of regret that.
Like, you know, it's-it's
hard to hurt people, but then
you miss out on all
of the connection and,
like, I wish I learned that day one
instead of day 21, but...
You learn by going through it,
- by having these experiences.
- Yeah.
- Better late than never, though.
This girl has learned
keeping everybody at
arm's length makes it easier
to vote them out, but it makes it easier
for them to vote you out, too.
And so, what I need to focus on now is
to let everyone in a little bit... The letters.
- I'm ready.
- Yours are heavy.
Even though
it's awkward and uncomfortable
and vulnerable and I hate it.
My dad was telling me, "you can do this."
"We love you, and I'm sure you have
so many friends."
And I have no friends out here.
And it's my fault. Like, I chose
I chose to have no friends.
Who does that?
But my husband says,
"if you have a bad day,
"try to slow down.
"Remember that mistakes
can be fixed, especially in survivor."
"No matter what happens out there,
you are coming home to the
same amazing life you left."
My brother wrote, "I know some days"
"you probably want to get
on a plane and fly home,
"but I want you to know
" that I'm proud of you.
"I've always admired
your sense of adventure
"and your willingness
to do something scary
because it might be fun."
It gives me a lot of confidence
in who I am as a person,
and it's what I needed to remind myself.
My loyalty is to the
people writing these letters.
My mom is an absolute
super fan of this game.
When she first learned that
I might be going out here,
it became, like, the light of her life.
This is the proudest she's ever been.
It's so meaningful to
hear from her right now.
This game is intense.
I've had tough times.
Nothing's been perfect.
It hasn't been easy, but I persevered.
It's been completely life-changing,
and these letters are
exactly what I needed.
There's less than a week left to go, right?
And my decisions will
dictate what my fate is and,
dare I say, my survivor legacy.
All I have to do is just go
all frigging out until the
very, very, very bitter end.
I'm more than fueled
for the rest of this game.
I honestly feel like I
should give myself a second
- before I say things I'm gonna regret.
- Yeah. Okay.
But I also couldn't think
of the three better people
to sit here and dissect - yeah.
Every inch of why
that was the dumbest
thing Sam could have done.
- He's really not playing.
- Sam just quit the game.
- He's not smart at all.
- In my opinion,
Sam just quit the
game. Sam just decided
that he was going to have his last meal
with his best friend
and enjoy a last supper.
- I agree.
- And there we go.
It's so idiotic to me.
You'd think just maybe, just maybe,
he would try a hail Mary,
to pick me, somebody he could pull over.
But you know what,
guys? He's a stand-up guy.
- Yeah. Go, Sam!
- He's a hero!
Most generous man I've ever met.
Sam wants to be the hero.
He is just this honorable,
strong, just smart guy.
So he picks the only other
guy out here... Andy, his boy.
Sam thinks him and Genevieve
are gonna talk to Andy,
get him a little red-wine drunk,
and that they're gonna convince.
- Andy to flip on this...
- And me.
And that they're going... Yeah, on you.
- I'm not worried.
- He's not gonna flip.
- You don't think so?
- If he does again,
- they still need another person.
- Doesn't matter.
We just have to worry about
any advantage that they get.
- Sam just has to go, period.
- Yeah.
- And... -Yeah.
- Bam.
It just feels like Sam
is checking every box
on teeny's list
of why he needs to
be the one to go home
in both personal and strategic ways.
Am I just, like, a man-hater
at my core? Like...
No.
I think he's just always
been, like, popular,
the class clown, like...
- And that...
- Yeah, he was probably prom king.
Having somebody who's, like,
your typical, all-American,
quarterback-looking guy
around all the time... it's just not...
It's just not my thing.
Sam's gonna come back
and be like, "it was good."
"Like, we had pasta,
"and you know, like, I'm sorry, guys.
"It was a really rough spot to be in.
"I hope you get it. Like, me
and Genevieve are just, like,
on the bottom together and, like..."
- He'll be crying, too. He'll be crying.
- "I just, you know,
the Italian, she'd be talking
about that chicken parm, and"
I'm also jealous. I want to be there.
I'm not gonna lie about
that. I want the food,
I want the loved-one letter.
But Sam left the four of us girls here
to basically plan his demise,
which will be coming imminently,
and will be something I take great joy in.
- Me too.
- Me too. Me too.
I mean, I am obsessed
with the idea of all women.
- Me too.
- I would be proud
to sit by all four of you, and I also think
same.
All four of us, I think,
have a genuinely, like,
pretty good shot against each other,
- in the best way possible.
- Yeah. Me too.
- In a positive way.
- It would be, in a positive way.
I would be proud to
end my survivor journey
- side by side by any of you.
- Yeah. -Me too.
I would have zero regrets.
Me too. And I would be
happy if any of you won.
I'm liking this four a lot, so I'm hoping
to use some, like, morale, Kumbaya,
"we're four final women,
we got this, let's go."
We're gonna vote out Sam
first, and it's gonna be glorious.
That smug face.
I just can't. I can't, I can't, I can't.
We are gonna be the final four women.
So, we're really solidifying
how is it we're gonna
get rid of Sam, then
how are we gonna get rid of Genevieve,
and then how are we
gonna get rid of Andy.
- One, two, three.
- Got it.
- Nice.
- My. Balance a sec.
We got it.
This is the four who are
going to run this show
to the very friggin' end.
Girl power!
Girl power.
I'll be honest.
I can see the million dollars.
I can see the final
tribal. I can see my pitch.
I can see myself winning this game,
and it's intoxicating, and it's so exciting.
Good job, guys.
I think this might be a
good time to talk game.
I'm not sure if you brought
me here for a specific reason,
to, like, wine and dine me. Regardless,
I woke up this morning with a plan.
I like day 21 plans, Andy.
Me too. Me too.
This is an opportunity
that we cannot pass up.
What I want this to be is
the defining conversation
and night for the rest of this game.
I don't conduct much
business in beanbag chairs,
but Andy calls a meeting and, like,
the last couple days, I
have been on this slow march
to death in this game.
I'm all ears. Talk to me,
Andy. What is your plan?
I'm coming over to you.
But here's what's working against us.
There is a five-person alliance
called the underdog alliance,
and I've been voting with them.
It's highly unrealistic we pull any of them.
Really? You think so?
There is no... There is no chance.
So what we have in our favor is
that we have the time and space tonight
to come up with a pretty elaborate plan.
The goal is build suspicion
that one of you has an idol.
If we do that, they will be
compelled to split the vote.
Then all I have to do is
swing my vote over to you guys
and we take out Rachel.
Obviously, she's a big threat, right?
She also has an advantage.
She has a block a vote.
Does everybody know that except us?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Wow.
Andy is my hero.
This is what Genevieve
and I have been waiting for.
It's time to get the band
back together to take out Rachel.
I'm going all out, and I have no fear.
This is really our only chance of winning,
is getting together right now.
It really is high time
for me to go for broke.
The way I started this game
built an initial perception
that I was a goat.
This is my opportunity to make my Mark
and finish this game off in a
way where I can get first place.
Do you think they're gonna be
suspicious when you come back
to camp?
Yeah. We have to come
up with a whole fake story.
We have to milk the time
that we have on the sanctuary
to put together a very difficult mission.
This is not simple.
It's going to require thorough planning,
a lot of stealth and just pure execution.
Yeah.
This is the biggest heist
of season 47 of survivor,
and we're calling it "operation Italy."
- Hello.
- Hello, hello.
- Hi.
Long time no see, people.
Step one of operation Italy
is to channel all of
my theater experience.
I'm obviously sorry about that yesterday.
It was a hard spot.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Don't worry about it.
I'm laying it on thick. I'm apologizing.
I'm kind of going right back to the
playing-dead Sam that
I was before this plan.
And I'll do anything to live
another day in this game.
I would rather do Rachel,
but if I have to do Genevieve,
I will do Genevieve to stay in the game.
- And I am... and I am... I...
- Like, I'm not...
Looking pretty dire for me.
Still kind of a free agent, out here.
I don't know how you see things now,
but, you know, I'm trying to just survive.
If this works, there's gonna
have to be a couple oscars
handed out to Genevieve,
Andy and myself.
It's gonna take that level of performance
to, like, really nail this thing down.
But I'm feeling pretty confident.
Operation Italy depends on a split vote,
and the only reason
people would split a vote is
if they're worried you have something.
At the sanctuary, Sam
gave me his original idol
from gata, which is expired.
He also gave me two bracelets
from tree mail that I'm going
to craft together to try and make an idol.
I love this plan, but for operation Italy
to have any hope,
everybody's story has to
paint a picture for the broader group,
and it has to all seem
like it's making sense...
This could work. This could work.
Until the moment
people realize it doesn't.
And that moment has to
be when the votes are read.
I have made a beka merge idol.
I'm sorry. We were...
We all felt bad for you, honestly.
Everything but the let... Yeah.
My role for operation Italy is
to reingratiate myself with
my underdog alliance of five
because I had been
away for a really long time.
It was bad energy because
they pitched me hard.
Yeah. We knew they were gonna.
I need them to feel
that I am still trustworthy
and that I am still a number for them.
I don't like how they approached me
because it just felt like
they brought me to wine
and dine me and try to, like,
be a vote for them.
It just felt, like, really premeditated.
Like, they brought me
to wine and dine me.
I could just tell that they just picked me
- to wine and dine me, that, like...
- Of course.
They're saying, like, "you
just have to come with us."
- Yeah.
- It's very strong-armed.
And it was just not the
right approach for me,
because it was, like, strong-arming me.
Well, I'm all set. I'm
right where you left me.
Step number two:
Foster suspicion
that Genevieve has a
hidden immunity idol.
I'm most afraid of the idol.
Do you know if they got
any kind of advantage?
- They did, didn't they?
- It's hard to say.
- Shoot. Okay.
- I don't know.
This fake information
that Genevieve has
a hidden immunity idol
is going to cause paranoia, insecurity,
and that will help me
convince my alliance
to split the vote.
Teeny and Rachel were kind of preferring
for Sam to go out first.
- How do you feel about that?
- I'm down for it, but
- I'm most afraid of the idol, so, I...
- Yeah.
If you... if we were to decide
that we put more on Genevieve,
then we can guarantee we're flushing it.
But anyway... sorry. Go ahead.
We were thinking...
So, instead, prioritize Genevieve?
Yeah, because then, we
can get that idol out tonight
- no matter what.
- I'll be honest.
The idol scares me the most, too.
So then, we would need to then
- split the vote to make sure.
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's the best play... splitting
a vote to account for an idol.
Operation Italy has been
executed to perfection.
My underdog
underdog alliance of five
has no idea what I'm cooking.
It's really smart.
Thank you, Andy.
It's time to strike. It's time
to pull the trigger
on the juiciest target left in the game.
And the target is Rachel.
It's season 47, and players
are still evolving the game.
You want to be a part of the fun?
Apply to be on survivor.
Come on in!
This one looks very fun.
It is gonna be fun... For somebody.
Wow.
All right.
Day 22. Should we get into it?
All right, first things first.
Rachel, got to take back the necklace.
- Thanks, Jeff.
- Thank you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
Today's immunity challenge
will require a combination
of balance, dexterity
and touch. Here's how it works.
First, you must navigate a balance beam
while transporting a ball on a pole.
Once you're done
with that, you must then
quickly maneuver two
skulls through a metal maze.
Once you've completed
that, you'll move to the finish,
where you will need touch
as you roll balls along a paddle,
attempting to land three of them
in any of the five targets.
First person to accomplish
all of that earns this.
The immunity necklace.
Safe tonight at tribal council,
guaranteed a spot in the final six.
Losers, tribal council
where somebody will be
twelfth person voted out
and become the fifth member
of our jury.
Shall we get to it? All right.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get it on. Here we go.
All right, here we go. For immunity
and a spot in the final six.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First stage is about balance.
You've got a balance beam
and you have a ball on a pole.
It's gonna want to drop
off like it just did for Rachel.
- Oop!
- Genevieve drops.
She's got to go back.
Teeny out to a fast start.
Sam on the course, Rachel back out.
Everybody now doing it.
Teeny's first across. You're good.
Drop it and move on.
Here comes Sam. Sam's
across. You're good.
Rachel's across. You're good.
Caroline drops. She's got to go back.
Teeny, Sam, Rachel
all have their double-ended warrior staff.
They're maneuvering
skulls through a metal maze.
This is tougher than it looks.
Teeny now struggling
in this second stage.
Sam moving quickly through.
Andy's across the beam.
He's trying to get back in this.
Every single second's gonna count
when you get to that final stage.
You got to get through
those beams. Let's go!
Andy's now in it.
Rachel doing a nice job.
Sam and Rachel pulling ahead.
Andy's starting to gain some ground now.
Sam's gonna be out first.
Sam, you're good!
Sam is moving on to the final stage.
This is where it is won
or lost with your ability
to navigate that little ball
down your paddle into a tiny dimple.
Sam trying to stick his first.
He can't do it.
There goes Rachel.
It is Rachel and Sam.
Teeny has hers. Let's
go, teeny! She's through.
You just need three balls
in any of the five spots.
This is all about touch.
The question is who's gonna
figure out the touch first?
There's definitely a learning curve,
but once you learn it, this can go quickly.
You've got to get it to stick
in one of those little dimples.
It doesn't matter which one.
Rachel has her first.
Sam's still trying to get it to stick.
He's all around it.
Teeny having no luck.
Andy now gonna be in on the paddle.
Can he make up some time?
Sue trying to get in on it.
Here comes Genevieve.
Immunity on the line.
Sue's good!
Sue, you're in this.
Here comes Genevieve.
These paddles are heavy.
The weight is not distributed evenly.
This is gonna be hard. Okay.
Rachel, another ball out.
This is her second.
Very close. Can she get
that second ball to stick?
And she does.
It is Rachel in the lead
with two. One ball left.
Nobody else has anything.
Andy drops, got to start again.
- Teeny struggling.
- My god.
Sam still trying to get his first.
Nobody else having any luck right now.
Hey.
Rachel now one ball away
from winning her second
individual immunity and
guaranteeing herself a spot
in the final six.
She's in, she's out.
And she's in! It's over!
Rachel wins individual
immunity, guaranteed a spot
- in the final six.
- Damn.
- Wow, that was fast.
- Good job, Rachel.
- Wow.
Rachel, come on over.
Going right back on.
Thanks again, Jeff.
Once again, safe tonight at tribal council,
cannot be voted out of this game.
You will have a spot in the final six.
As you inch closer to that final four,
where you know nobody
can take you out, -yeah.
What is the feeling?
You're that much closer.
It's crazy, you know? I mean,
I had a really rough entry into the merge,
and so, to be standing here
with the immunity idol again
I feel amazing. Like, this is wild, and
- I'm excited.
- Here's what we know.
You are safe. For everybody else,
somebody's dream of
survivor 47 will come to an end,
twelfth person voted out,
fifth member of our jury.
Grab your stuff. Head back to
camp. See you tonight of tribal.
- Congrats.
- Thanks, Jeff.
Rachel... she wins a challenge,
she dominates, and
now she has immunity.
And... that's a setback.
It's a setback
for operation Italy
'cause she was the target.
She was the hit. Now
that Rachel's off the table,
the real big question is
who is the new target?
First thing I want to say,
if this is our last tribal
council together, it was
an absolute pleasure playing with you.
If it's... if it's me going, fight like hell,
get there, and you got my vote.
- Likewise. Likewise.
- If you go, I'll fight like hell.
The hit was out on Rachel,
and she wins the challenge.
Of course.
Not great for me.
Not great for operation Italy.
But operation Italy was
designed to be flexible.
- I would love to do Caroline instead.
- Yeah.
We have to pick between
Caroline and teeny,
- and somehow let Andy know.
- Okay.
'Cause I still want to do the plan,
- basically, as usual.
- Yeah.
- Did you do it? Okay.
- Yeah. Yeah.
But the string you got was a black string
- to make with the beads.
- This is beautiful.
This is b... this is good.
Pretty good, I think.
And so, my plan with this
is to ensure there is a vote split tonight
because we need the vote split.
We need Andy in the
majority side of the vote so that
he can flip, and that is the recipe
to success for operation Italy.
Obviously, this move is, like
Andy is the straw that
stirs the drink in the move,
and he plays the most pivotal part.
To final six.
I don't think she has an idol.
- Really? I think she does.
- I don't think she has it.
Yes, I... I don't think she has it, but, like,
- I just want him out.
- Okay.
I think she... I think she has the idol.
She
I still want operation Italy
to really succeed tonight.
And so, I'm like,
"here's what we should
do. We should split the vote.
"We should split the vote.
Then we should flush
out Genevieve's idol."
The only hiccup here
is that teeny, teeny,
teeny has her own agenda.
The thing is
I think it makes more sense to just, like...
It's, like, we get the idol out
100%, and we do it that way.
I guess... I guess your plan's better,
but I just don't think
she does, and I think...
It's the path of least
resistance in terms of risk.
My preference to go home
tonight is definitely Sam.
But we also want to
flush this hypothetical,
mysterious idol that we think.
Genevieve has. I'm scared,
if Genevieve doesn't have an idol,
and we stack the votes on her,
she's gonna walk out the door
and Sam's still gonna be here.
As teeny walks up to Sam
and I, now I'm nervous,
because my fake idol is not perfect.
It's fake, it's counterfeit. I know that.
If she looks too closely,
she may know that.
Why?
Keep it on me.
If it changes, let me know.
Am I... am I gathering
what I think I'm gathering?
You're gathering what you think.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah.
I need to show it to her
to have her believe it,
but I can't show it to her too long
because then she'll know it's a fake.
Okay. No.
I flash this idol and then, thank god,
Andy's coming around the
corner. I jam it back in my pocket.
And so I'm thinking I'm
in the clear. I've given her,
like, just a glimmer,
and that should be good.
But I don't think they
think I have anything.
Are you sure that's real? Do
you have a note or anything?
I buried the note.
But, yes, I know it's real
because I had to do
the steps this morning.
Why do you think I was
down by the freaking water?
Yeah.
When Genevieve shows
me that she has the idol,
I'm relieved in a way, like
it was written in the stars.
I already wanted Sam to go.
Now I know for a fact that
Genevieve has an idol, I think
I'm gonna sit on the information.
I'm gonna know
Genevieve's safe tonight.
I'm going to. I'm going to.
And now knowing that
tonight's vote will go
exactly how we think it will,
it's just... chef's kiss,
and I'll see Sam later.
- We are 95% there.
- Okay.
- Has it?
- And it's... yeah.
- That's perfect.
- Let 'em split...
- Which is exactly what we wanted to, so...
- Okay.
- I agree.
- That's what my gut tells me.
I'm the mafia boss. I'm the
architect of operation Italy.
The target has to be Caroline.
- So, you want Caroline?
- Yeah.
Everything's a go. It's perfect.
Operation Italy is in a
good place right now.
She's got her number one: Sue.
That little loyal, loyal, loyal bond,
which makes her powerful in this game.
And Caroline is the
brains of that pair, and so,
she's got to sleep with the fishes.
All right, beaut... Beautiful, beautiful.
Let's go.
Operation Italy, baby.
I have this optimistic feeling in my gut
that we're gonna be able to pull this off.
But the underdog alliance needs
to believe that nothing has changed,
and I'm still little old Sam
just trying to survive another day.
I think Genevieve's voting for you.
I'm down to write whatever
keeps me in the game.
I'm writing down Genevieve.
Look at me. Writing down Genevieve.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I know that Genevieve is voting for me.
It's actually gonna be the first time
I've seen my name on parchment.
And part of me is like, "okay."
"This is actually giving
a little bit of validation
that I am a threat."
It's reminding the jury
before I do, which is nice.
But it's nerve-racking.
Yes. Where is it?
The biggest concern is
does Genevieve have an idol.
- I got my eye on 'em.
- I get to go through
her bag, but what sucks
is I don't think I'm gonna
get any definitive
answers, even from that.
I didn't see anything in hers.
I can't say I went through it completely,
- but, like, didn't see anything there.
- Okay.
Granted, I trust my alliance,
but it's just an unsettling feeling
to know that there is a bit
of a door open for you to go home.
So, she's writing my name down.
We-we need what's-her-name
to play her block a vote then.
I just... I mean, if everything
- goes according to plan...
- But we need to make it through tonight.
- I'm-I'm afraid so, like...
- Yeah?
I'm putting, put... Playing my idol for you.
- I mean, I know it's my neck on the line.
- I'm gonna go with your gut,
- but, like, I want you protected.
- I think it's...
Thank you. I mean, I
want to be protected, too.
Caroline being voted out is
- my worst-case scenario.
- I still have my idol.
If I get a gut feeling,
I'm whipping that thing
out and saving Caroline.
It's just weird that they're
so relaxed and comfortable.
- Yes.
- Like, something's going on.
But as long as my group all stay strong,
we can't go wrong. We can't go wrong.
I think I have different plans
about, like, how we want
to approach it tonight.
Basically, we want
Genevieve to think it's her
so that she plays an idol if she has it,
even though we're voting Sam out.
And we can flip.
Basically, I mean, load up on Sam,
and then, one hinky
on Genevieve, probably.
I'm a little nervous
about doing the split vote.
The biggest concern
with this alliance of five
is just the idea that someone
or... someone could flip.
'Cause I could always
block, too, if I have to.
Don't we... We need your block for six.
And then also, I could use
this block a vote so that if there is
any kind of shenanigans with an idol,
we still get to decide
who goes home between
Sam and Genevieve.
My god, if this actually works...
If this actually works, I will die.
I will die.
In my heart, I hope it works.
In my brain, I mean, how could it?
There's so many ways it could go wrong.
Let's run through all the
ways operation Italy is a bust.
The split vote doesn't actually
fall the way that we think it's gonna fall.
Well, I also think, we don't need to split it
because if we tell Genevieve
- it's her, she'll play it.
- Yeah.
We need the stars to align,
and Rachel not to play her block a vote.
What if Andy gets cold feet?
I mean, Rachel was the hit.
Is Caroline enough,
or will he be tempted
just to take out Sam and I
and preserve his
placement in the underdogs?
Beyond that, we need Caroline
who knows her name is out there
to not have anything, as well,
because if she's nervous,
maybe she'll protect herself.
In my head, I'm doing the math,
and, it's grim, to say the least.
There are more ways this can go wrong
than ways it can go right.
Now bring in the members of our jury.
Okay, let's start with
the reward challenge.
Sam, you win it. It
comes with a big reward.
- Yeah.
- Go to the sanctuary,
Italian food, you're
gonna spend the night
and you get letters from home.
So, winning that reward
comes with strategic power
and strategic risk.
You chose Andy and
Genevieve to go with you.
So, walk me through how
that went at the sanctuary.
Yeah, I mean, it was all
of your wishes of what you
want on a survivor reward.
But as good as it feels for yourself,
as good as it feels to give
somebody that opportunity
to, like, have that day,
you're also the person taking that away
from four other people.
What was the sanctuary
like for you, Genevieve?
Can I give you a bit of a
longer answer to this question?
- Sure.
- So, when I came into this game,
I was Genevieve the person
and Genevieve the player.
And before I knew it, I put up,
like, a little wall to make it
easier to think strategically,
and I thought I was blocking
out all the bad feelings.
But what I was doing
was keeping them in.
The letters from home
gave me just the perspective I needed.
It made me feel like myself again.
It reminded me
you are better off if
you connect with people.
It was the first time today that I felt
the value of community here.
So, it was a very
meaningful experience for me.
Andy, Genevieve shared
a very personal
experience at the sanctuary.
How was it for you?
Well, first of all, I mean, I resonate
with what Genevieve is saying.
I mean, we have our games,
and we have our journeys,
and they're intertwined.
So, choosing who you're gonna
bring on something like that
it's a game decision, but
we see beyond the game
when we're letting each
other into our home lives
and the people who love us.
It's just undeniable how much it meant.
Teeny, you have the
reward on one part of this.
That's the strategic
decision that Sam makes.
But then you hear the impact
on these humans that
you've been living with
in this jungle with this community
while playing against them,
but the result is the same.
You weren't chosen.
Here's the thing, Jeff.
I don't think it's a secret
that I came into this game,
and I really didn't have
an emotional wall up.
The way that I approach this is
by connecting with other
people, being open, being myself.
It's the only way that I've ever been able
to survive in any situation.
And so, not being chosen
was, oddly, an opportunity
for me to strategically think
about my placement in this game,
why I wasn't chosen, who was chosen,
and a path forward. So,
it sort of reversed me
out of this emotional
rut I have been in in the game.
Caroline, that is fascinating
that you can have such
different experiences
as a result of one challenge.
Absolutely. I love teeny's mindset.
I feel like there were a lot of opportunities
in us not being chosen.
The people who are left
behind are in the majority.
We have so much time to think,
so much time to talk all to ourselves.
Sue, the words from teeny
and Caroline certainly sound foreboding.
Like, "go ahead."
"Have your little" reward
and your nice journey.
The four of us will be back at camp
"plotting your demise."
I mean, am I wrong?
No, you're not wrong.
I think the part that
got me was, I pictured...
Getting those letters.
So, it's painful, but it didn't kill me.
It made me stronger.
And that's what I love
about this game, is that
we're all hitting low notes,
but we're coming back
feeling more empowered
to say, "you know what?
I got to take the reins by the horn..."
You know, the horn, whatever
it is, whatever it's called,
and just, like, go with this
and just keep pulling forward.
And that's what it did for me.
Teeny, would it be reasonable
to assume that maybe
the four of you... sue,
Rachel, Caroline and yourself
taking out one of the three of them?
I think you'd be stupid
not to have that thought cross your mind
if you're one of the three of them.
Just like I think we'd
be stupid to not think
that the three of them
are coming up with a plan
that's against one of us.
But the thing is, seven people,
I think, have three
questions in their mind.
One of them is,
"who can I beat sitting
next to at final tribal council?"
The second one is, "how
do I get to final tribal council?"
"Who is in my way?
"Whether I'm not a part
of their endgame plans,
they're not a part of mine."
And the third one, I
think, "is our perception"
"of who the biggest threat to win is
"the same as their perception
of who the biggest threat to win is?"
And I think the phrase
"perception is reality"
in survivor is as common
as hearing "bless you"
in response to a sneeze.
Like, it is something
that is almost just desensitized
at this point, regardless
of who was on the reward
and who was at camp.
It's something that's wheeling
through all of our minds
the second we're all back together.
Rachel, you were nodding.
Yeah. I mean, I agree. This is day 22.
The only thing you have to
do is think about your endgame
and who you want to be with.
Can you trust those people
that you think want to be with you,
that you want to be with?
It's a cyclical thing that my brain just
continues to mull over all day, every day.
So, sue, after today's
immunity challenge,
Rachel wins her second necklace,
is safe again, you all get back to camp.
What was the vibe today?
Today was almost like
a more relaxed vibe.
People weren't scurrying off
and going, having conversations.
It was very different than
what you would normally expect.
Andy, does that line
up with what you saw,
that it was kind of an
easygoing afternoon?
It's the classic survivor thing. Like,
everyone's sitting pretty,
and everything's so easy.
What's really going on?
Like, where's the catch, right?
But it's not that we're happy-go-lucky
and relaxed.
I think what you're seeing is
a plan being acted out
that doesn't need much talking to act out.
Jeff, the thing is, a lot of us
have proved to each other trust already,
and a pecking order has been decided,
and that's that.
Wow. Andy, if that's true,
that's terrifying if you're
not in on the vote because
it's essentially saying,
"you won't change us.
We've already talked through
it, and we have a decision."
I mean, typically, I would say,
conventional wisdom says
if you're on the outside of it,
you got to be tearing walls down,
you got to be, like, going nuts.
And so, obviously,
I don't think anyone
wants to go home tonight,
but at the same time, I don't
think everyone feels secure,
and it's either going to be resulting in
something kind of cut-and-dry
that people have accepted
or it's masking something
that I can't see right now.
Sam, are you expecting
that it might be you tonight?
Yeah, I mean, I think
it's kind of been, like,
I'm at the end of my rope in a lot of ways,
and I've been hanging on
as I get closer down, like, the knots.
And the reward didn't help.
And so, it's a really powerless feeling
tonight, for me.
How you feeling right now,
Genevieve, getting ready to vote?
I'm totally fine and
confident, in a weird way.
Not on how the vote's gonna go,
but just of where I'm at.
And tonight's vote
isn't about just scraping by for me.
I'm swinging for the fences because
I don't want to just get
to sixth and go home.
I want to try, like everyone else is,
and I know what I want to happen,
so that's what I'm gonna
try and make happen.
All right, it is time to vote. Sue, you're up.
Let's see if operation
Italy really is a thing.
Either way, one of us gonna
be sleeping with the fishes.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it, now
would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote: Sam.
Genevieve. One vote
Sam, one vote Genevieve.
Caroline. We're tied.
One vote Sam, one vote Genevieve,
one vote Caroline.
Sam. That's two votes
Sam, one vote Genevieve,
one vote Caroline.
Genevieve. We're tied again.
Two votes Sam, two votes Genevieve,
one vote Caroline.
Caroline. We're tied.
Two votes Sam, two votes Genevieve,
two votes Caroline, one vote left.
Twelfth person voted out of survivor 47
and the fifth member
of our jury: Caroline.
Need to bring me your torch.
Okay.
- That was really well done, you guys.
- Good game.
- Good game, Caroline.
It's been an honor playing with all of you.
Wow.
Caroline, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org
yeah.
With six people left, I don't trust anybody.
Next time, on a two-part
season finale of survivor
I am in a grand conspiracy
to take over the game.
- Isn't this friggin' crazy?
- I'm so mad.
I see betrayal, I see fear.
This island isn't big
enough for the both of us.
We are going to clash,
and we're gonna see
who comes out alive.
I've been thinking about the situation.
I've been analyzing it.
And Andy flipped. He took me out.
And I'll be honest. I think it was smart.
I think I would have won at the end.
But most importantly,
I'm grateful beyond belief
that I've made it this far, and
I've made it to the final seven.
I feel like I didn't win the ultimate prize
but I was able to live my dream.