I was the murderer, and now I'm trying
to cover my tracks.
I'm gonna kill Jeff.
Previously on survivor
I don't think Andy's gonna be loyal to me.
Why?
Sam wants to work with Andy, but
I want to stick with the three girls.
We're just bickering like a friggin' old
married couple.
Yeah.
Gabe's gonna want me to flip on tiyana,
and there's no way in
hell that I'm gonna try
to go after her.
We can agree to play
these amulets together,
and they would have the effect
of a hidden immunity idol.
Yeah.
I don't want to just be
going along with plans.
So maybe it's time to stop
going along with kishan's plan
and make kishan the plan.
Kishan, the tribe has spoken.
I feel like I don't even
know what happened tonight.
I've been bamboozled.
I've been betrayed, I've been humbled.
Walking into tribal, I was
expecting the vote to be Rome.
But in one fell swoop,
I've been blindsided and I've lost kishan,
who I consider to be my number one,
end-all, be-all in this
game above anybody else.
A little bit.
I'll be all right.
Why? What's going on?
Teeny, did you know about the plan?
I did know about the plan.
Is there a reason you
didn't tell me, though?
Because I didn't have a
vote or any way to control it.
I thought you had my back, though.
I do, but, like...
How can you say that if you
know it's gonna be me tonight
and then you don't tell me?
It's hard to say
what this means for me moving forward.
You know, my first thought is, like,
"how close was it to being me?
"How far on the bottom am I?
Can I crawl back up?"
I really don't know.
Like, can you be straight-up with me?
Was there a debate? Like...
No. No. No. No.
- I feel that no matter...
- You are right in the middle.
You're not at the bottom.
Rome and sol are on the bottom.
You and me are in the middle,
because they both want to work with us,
and they don't want
to work with each other.
Rome doesn't want to work with me.
The idea to vote out kishan was mine,
and I knew I had to vote him out.
It was better for my game.
He is the player that is the threat
that you don't see until it's too late.
And I just couldn't take that chance.
Like...
He's pissed off at you
tonight. He's gonna be...
Well, what do I say to him, dude?
Because I didn't come up with that plan.
- No.
- I was told the plan.
I was also told the plan.
At this point, I feel good
that I've done the damage
control I need to do with teeny.
And now I have Rome,
who really trusts me,
because I tipped him off
and saved him from going home tonight.
So, I think I'm in a good position.
Like, from the bottom of my heart, okay?
But I want you to know I
feel freed from the shackles
of, like, kishan being
a person in this game
that I have to, like, make decisions with
or be associated with.
I do feel liberated.
And, I mean, I do, too, because, like,
you know, when I came into this game,
I said that I wanted to get an alliance,
and I want to do everything possible
to get that alliance as far as possible.
And so that's why tonight,
I was more hurt by kishan than anything.
I thought that I had a
solid alliance with me,
Genevieve, kishan and teeny.
So, the second that I heard
kishan put my name out there,
I knew that that trust with me
and kishan was out the window,
was sayonara, goodbye.
And that's why I had
absolutely zero problems
stealing his vote tonight,
writing his name down twice
and seeing him get his torch snuffed.
I feel like teeny most definitely feels like
she's on the bottom right now,
and that's exactly how I want her to feel.
So, yes, teeny, you can be remorseful.
You can be, you know,
sad that you were left out of the vote,
but at the end of the day,
that trust is 100% broken.
Come on in!
Wow.
Tuku, gata, getting your first look
at the new lavo tribe.
Kishan voted out at the last tribal council.
Wow, man.
All right, day nine, survivor 47.
Let's get to today's reward challenge.
There are only two
lanes for today's challenge
because we're doing something different.
- Man.
- I know.
Brand-new survivor twist.
My gosh.
There are only two
lanes for today's challenge
because we're doing something different.
My god.
Holy cow.
Here's how it works. We're
gonna do a random draw
across all three tribes - wow.
And form two teams of seven.
These are teams just for this challenge.
- Wow.
- You will
compete together, and if you win, you will
celebrate together with the reward.
- Wow.
- All right, before
we get to the draw, let me
walk you through the challenge.
For today's challenge, you're gonna
race under an obstacle,
collecting keys along the way.
You'll use those keys to unlock a ladder.
You'll then work together
to maneuver the ladder
until it's free.
You'll use the ladder to collect five balls
from an overhead structure.
Race to the finish, where you will attempt
to land those balls into
five different targets.
First team of seven
to finish wins reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
The winning seven will be
- taken to the sanctuary...
- Are you kidding me?
Where good things happen
for a brand-new survivor reward.
It's called the survivor social hour.
Here's how it works. You're
gonna barbecue hot dogs.
- What?! You're kidding.
- My gosh.-!
Play a little survivor cornhole.
And you will also have
the advantage of opportunity.
The opportunity to hang out
with players you don't know
and maybe forge bonds that
will help you later in the game.
Losers, I got nothing for you.
You will head back to
your camp and then hope
that somebody will share
with you what really went down.
Worth playing for?
All right, then. Let's draw for teams.
This reward is something
totally unprecedented,
and the biggest advantage of it is
you're getting this opportunity to really
cross-pollinate and mingle
with the other two tribes.
If you are blue, go to the blue mat.
If you're yellow, go to the yellow mat.
So, it's huge strategically,
because we know how
close we are to the merge.
And any time you can get with people
who you're not very
familiar with right now
is gonna be invaluable.
All right, so let's look at
these temporary teams.
For today only, we
have Anika, sol, Rome,
Gabe, Andy, Sierra and Genevieve.
Over here in yellow,
we have sue, Kyle, teeny, Sam, Rachel,
tiyana and Caroline.
So, both groups have
members from all three tribes,
which means, if you win,
this will truly be an advantage
because, for the first time,
you will have a sense of
what's going on everywhere.
- Wow.
All right, give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do this!
All right, here we go. For
reward at the sanctuary.
Survivors ready?
Go! First you got to
get under that obstacle,
and you are untying bags.
Every player is responsible for one bag.
You cannot grab more than one.
Once you have a bag, get to your mat.
Once everybody's at
your mat, you can move on.
- Y'all got this!
- Good job, team.
Everybody funneling out
quickly. Got to get all seven there.
Go, blue! You're good!
- Go, yellow! You're good.
- Come on, come on, come on. Go.
Now you're looking for three keys.
Once you have
all three keys, you can
try to unlock the ladder.
You're good, blue!
All right. Go, girl.
Yellow, you're good.
You're good.
You have to untie. You have to untie.
It is blue in the early lead.
Their ladder is unlocked.
Now you got to maneuver that ladder
through a tricky maze.
It looks a lot easier than it is.
Do you have the rest?
We got it.
Yellow has their ladder unlocked.
Yellow has some momentum now.
It is yellow in the lead.
Blue is stuck.
- That's it.
- There we go. There we go.
- Keep pushing a little bit more. Yeah.
- Yeah. Good job.
Yellow can feel it.
They have figured this out.
Good teamwork, guys.
Yellow has the ladder
free. You can move on.
- Right here.
- It is yellow now in the lead.
- Down. All right.
- Okay.
One person going up.
It's gonna be Kyle going up the ladder.
- Unclip.
- It's so steady.
There's one.
There's two. Kyle can reach three.
- Down he goes.
- Now you got to make
just one move to get the other two.
Blue still working on
freeing up their ladder.
Lift up, Rome. There you go.
Yellow now increasing their lead.
Kyle quickly unclips those balls.
- Can we drop it?
- Drop it.
Do that, do that, do that.
That's how you do it on survivor.
Drop one in every slot.
You got two rebounders
up here. Let's go!
It's gonna be teeny taking
the first spot for yellow.
- Just shoot. You're okay.
- Rachel and sue gonna rebound.
Wow.
- Just misses.
- Nice, guys. Good work.
Blue has their ladder free.
- You're good, blue!
- They're still on their first.
Get it up and get one
person up the ladder.
- Okay, everyone, stabilize.
- All day, Rome, all day.
- Stabilize!
- It's gonna be Rome going up.
You're unclipping, Rome.
- Soft touch.
- Yay!
There you go.
Teeny scores the first basket for yellow.
Caroline now taking her spot.
- Hold up. Hold it tight.
- Rome taking a lot
of time on that second bag.
Nice, Rome!
Kyle whipped through it.
There's Rome with the third.
- And a big leap.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Now it's Gabe going up.
- Go, move.
- Go. Okay.
- Still got me?
- Yes, yes, it's stabilized.
They're gonna swap out.
Yellow has one.
Caroline going for two. Just misses.
Gabe working for that final bag.
Unclip it. He's got it.
Drop the ladder, and you're good.
Get all your bags in.
- Go! Go! Go!
- In the hole, in the hole, in the hole.
Okay, there it is. That's it.
Caroline scores the second for yellow!
Here comes tiyana.
Gabe gonna take the first shot for blue.
- Yeah!
Gabe scores the first for blue!
We've got yellow with two, blue with one.
- You got this, tiyana.
- There goes tiyana
- with a huge toss.
- Yeah. Yup. Yup.
Just out.
One more.
There goes Sierra.
- Ooh, get in there!
- Yes!
Sierra scores a second for blue.
We are tied, two-two.
You got it, tiyana. Come on.
Tiyana, deep breath.
- Nice launch. That looks good.
- Yes. Yes!
There it is! Yellow has their third.
Here comes Kyle with the fourth.
Andy going short.
- In and out.
- God.
Here goes Kyle.
Yeah!
Kyle with a huge toss.
Scores it. That is the fourth for yellow.
It is now Sam with the
fifth and final ball for yellow.
- Andy scores the third.
- Good work, Andy!
Here comes sol now working
on that fourth ball for blue.
Sam's way back. It's a long ways away.
Takes a lot of touch and a lot of strength.
Can Sam close it out
for yellow? In and out.
Sol trying to tie it up for
blue to give them a shot.
- In and out.
- So close, sol.
There goes Sam for the win.
Is that it? It is!
Yellow wins reward!
Rachel, sue, Caroline, tiyana,
teeny, Sam, and Kyle
earn an afternoon at the sanctuary.
- My god.
- Wow.
Huge effort by everybody.
All right, Caroline, Kyle, Rachel,
Sam, teeny, tiyana and
sue, enjoy your afternoon.
Grab your stuff, head out down
this way. Boat'll pick you up.
- Thank you, Jeff.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
All right, Andy, sol, Rome,
Gabe, Sierra, Genevieve, Anika,
all of you are going back
to your individual camps.
Grab your stuff, head out.
I was so psyched my team won.
And the survivor social
hour is the kind of thing
where I'm just like, "my
god, this changes my game."
The merge is coming up,
and I'm the only lavo
going on this reward.
So, I get a chance to
talk with these people
and tell them exactly what happened,
coming from a place
where I'm on the bottom.
My goodness.
- First sanctuary, guys.
- Beautiful.
- Bucket list.
- Finally. My god.
We've made it to the sanctuary.
Yeah.
We arrive at the sanctuary,
and I'm looking over,
and I see this big banner
that says "survivor social hour."
- It's a fun sign.
- Yes, it's a great sign.
And it's looking like a real good time.
I see that there's a
cornhole, there's sodas.
- Cheers!
And there's a grill with some dogs.
The vegan dog!
- What?! No way!
- Kyle!
And there is a veggie dog, even, for me,
because I'm a vegetarian.
So when I seen
something that I could eat,
I lit up inside. I...
That's the happiest I've
ever been for food in my life.
Come and get it while
the getting's good, guys.
Yay!
But my main thing about this is, like,
coming this close to the
merge, this is a prime opportunity
for people to start creating
new bonds and figuring out
the different cracks
that exist in other tribes.
I feel like we've got a
lot of eating and a lot
- of talking to get to.
- Yeah.
So we need you to give us the down low.
- Yeah. I'll fill you guys in.
- Yeah.
- Do you want to start?
So, basically, we get to tribal,
and I just start getting this,
like, weird feeling, and
they all voted together.
Damn. I'm sorry, teeny.
So now you feel like
you're on the bottom?
I'm just nervous all around.
I feel like this might be my last supper.
Like, that's where I'm at right now.
That sucks, teeny.
I'm so excited for this
survivor social hour.
I'm here with Sam from gata,
and we're getting to bond with
other people on other
tribes for the very first time.
If we hit merge, having
as much information
as possible is gonna be
really good for my game.
So, tell us about you guys.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. It's been weird.
We're the weirdest Kumbaya tribe ever.
- We go everywhere together.
- Do you really?
You don't split off at all?
- Not really.
- We go everywhere together.
I felt like the only
thing that we heard was
that you and Sierra were,
like, sort of running the show.
No. It's crazy.
Sierra and I have a very
secret bond with one another.
And so it's really frustrating to know
that two tribes might already suspect that
going into the merge.
And that perception is very
dangerous for my game.
I'm not gonna lie. This is probably
the best-case scenario for me right now
of the tuku being here.
This is not gonna blow
up anyone else's game.
Gabe has been the one
looking for idols this entire time.
Like, if anyone's gonna
find it, it's gonna be Gabe,
and he's alone right now. I'm pretty sure
he's looking for it at this
current moment as we speak.
Shoot.
It kind of worked out perfectly
because the one person
that I'm a little sketched
out about is not with us.
I know that Gabe has
thrown my name out there,
so now I can make sure that
Gabe is the first name that
kind of goes to people's heads
when they think of
people who are suspicious
and that they can't trust post-merge.
It's a perfect play for my game.
Gabe threw his idol
at our first tribal council.
He found... wait. He
already found an idol?
- And he played it.
- What?!
None of us knew that he had the idol.
Tiyana just opens
up, talking about Gabe,
literally throwing him under the bus.
It was shocking.
- I go off of vibes.
- Yeah.
No matter how many
times, like, me and Gabe talk,
it feels a little iffy.
Gabe is basically my number one ally.
And tiyana put a target on
Gabe's back 100% for the merge.
Yeah, sue.
Yeah!
- Almost.
- Ooh. That was close.
This is, like, my second sport... cornhole.
- Be, like... - Yeah!
- Kyle!
It's nice. It takes us away
from the game a little bit.
- Right?
- Yeah.
How do you feel about the people
- here on your tribe?
- I think the people here are good.
I think there's still some personalities
that kind of rub each
other the wrong way.
Some people go out,
play a game of cornhole.
I decide to keep playing survivor.
I haven't talked to sue at all.
She is my number one.
I love to work with her,
and whoever I'm working with...
Okay. Amazing.
The survivor social
hour... it was so good.
I'm definitely feeling
good vibes from both teeny and Rachel.
Rachel is someone who I
just feel comfortable around.
So, do you feel good with the women?
I feel really good with the women.
So, I could see us working
well in a bunch of different ways.
- Yeah.
- Teeny,
on the other hand, I've
already met and established
a great relationship with at the journey.
I'm over the moon. I'm absolutely thrilled.
Yeah.
When we lose the reward challenge, it is
the worst feeling in the world.
I would have loved to be on that reward,
but I had to come back
hungry, knowing that I'm gonna
be eating coconut some more
and have nothing but water.
It was definitely, definitely rough.
But the good thing is,
with teeny not at camp,
it definitely opened up the door
for me to start talking with sol
about potentially getting out teeny.
It's just gonna be about
convincing him that he can fully trust me.
So, I've got no problem
telling sol everything,
because at the end of the day,
you share knowledge with people.
That's how you build trust in this game.
Teeny now has the opportunity
to go talk with everybody,
she's got food in her belly.
She's gonna be a
serious threat post-merge.
And this is the other thing.
Teeny did get a three-way amulet, so,
if her and the other two people
with the amulets use it
together, it counts as an idol.
Fart.
I am in complete shock.
Teeny has an amulet
which I was not aware of.
And here's the other thing is,
Genevieve has told me before
that she doesn't want to
work with you long-term,
and she'd rather work with teeny.
But I want to work with you more
than I want to work with teeny.
After last night's vote, I thought
that Genevieve and I could
build something strong.
So that was pretty hard.
Rome is vomiting information to me,
none of it that I knew.
And that's where I came back to reality.
It's like, "sol,
you don't know anything
that's going on right now."
That sucks to hear.
Coming in here, I have
over 20 years sales experience.
I have been very, very successful
in my selling career, reading people,
convincing people to do things.
So,
I'm getting a big dose
of humble pie right now.
I know that you want sol out
- more than you want teeny out.
- Yeah.
So, hear me out.
Sol, at the end of the day,
when it comes to actions,
even though I might
not be fond of the guy,
actions speak louder
than the words in this game.
Yeah.
So, he has shown more
loyalty to us than teeny.
Right now, Rome is very chaotic.
Even though we only
lost a reward challenge,
it's very reminiscent of the scramble
that would happen after
losing an immunity challenge,
which...
Yes, he's tried to come
for me, things like that.
But at the end of the day,
he voted with me last night.
Yeah.
He was the one that
brought up teeny, and
I think that that's our
better long-term play.
Rome is saying
that sol is pitching teeny hard to him.
But out of all the lavo
members left standing,
teeny is the one that is just easiest
for me to work with, so...
You got me, girl.
- You got me.
- What does that mean?
- Rome said that?
- Yeah.
That's very different
than what he said to me.
He just said you were pitching teeny.
- No.
- That's really interesting.
My conversation with sol
I was a little caught off guard.
I learned that
Rome has been very
naughty and told sol
that I don't want to
work with sol long-term.
I mean, I know I've said it,
we all know I've said it,
but I don't want sol to
know that I have said it.
So, you really weren't
pitching teeny to him?
Absolutely not.
And not only that,
but Rome was the one targeting teeny.
It's not sol. So,
if he's not telling me everything,
his value to me goes down
and his danger level goes up.
And at some point,
that will tip the scales,
and it won't make sense
for me to keep Rome in
this game anymore, and
the scales be tippin'.
We're just letting 'em go
- right now?
- We're letting 'em go
'cause I don't think
they can lay eggs in that.
You don't think they're gonna, like
go away as soon... Like,
as soon as they come out?
Sam and Rachel are the ones who go
on this survivor social hour.
And so, back at camp,
myself, Sierra, and Anika
the three of us are hungry.
You know, we did not win any hot dogs.
We have no food to speak of.
- Are you ready?
- Yup.
And these chickens are,
like, unwanted members
on the gata beach at this point.
Hey!
We won this, like,
beautiful fishing kit a few days ago.
Let's put it to use. Maybe
we can catch some fish,
and that would be, like,
a huge morale boost.
We're almost at the end!
There's a lot of different
ways to go about,
you know, fishing with this thing.
This is just such a joke.
And nothing's working.
So it was just kind of
like salt in the wound.
It was sort of,
kind of a bad afternoon after a defeat.
Damn, that net is huge.
Yeah.
We get back to camp, and Sierra, Anika
and Andy are in the middle of trying to do
something with the
net to get fish, I guess.
But people are
chomping at the bit to find
out what the heck happened.
Okay, well, here's the deal.
Tuku goes to the second tribal council.
So, Rachel and I sit everybody down,
and I, of course, left out the fact that
sue actually came forward and told me,
"we heard that you and
Sierra are running things
back at your camp."
So I asked sue
if they had heard anything
about our tribe dynamic,
basically just trying to play dumb.
And then sue was
like, "well, we heard that
you and Sierra are kind of
running things over there."
And that's what... I shot that down.
- Yeah. Good.
- It's just like, that's
- I'm happy you shot that down.
- And I was like,
"I don't feel like Sierra
and even talk all that much."
Yup.
I was a little bothered to
learn that it was brought up
that Sam and I were on,
you know, the top and
dominating the gata tribe.
This is not good for my
game, but I have a few options.
I know I have Rachel,
Anika, and myself... the breadwinners
we're this tight, core alliance.
So, first off, Caroline said,
"the women are together
"and we're basically just, like,
waiting to see what to do with the men."
But Sam and I have a very tight alliance
with Andy.
I'm sure Sam filled you in.
- Right.
- The three of us... that's secret.
- That is confidential.
I feel like I could go either way.
Can either kick it with
the boys or with the girls.
So, I'm like, "what is best for my game?"
I know I have a lot of power
right now, but it's kind of
stressing me out.
I'm not complaining whatsoever,
but everyone got one hot
dog, there were no condiments.
- It was like...
- Really?
Yeah. There wasn't,
like, potato salad and that.
Yeah.
During the survivor social hour,
I told the other tribes
the entire, whole truth.
I told them that I was on the bottom
and I'm a little bit scared.
So, I decide to tell my tribe
a minorly-tweaked version
of what I told everyone at the social hour.
About our tribal, I told
them what happened,
except for I didn't say
he stole kishan's vote.
Basically, I wanted to make them feel like
I didn't give up any information.
I did not get a chance
to one-on-one talk to sue,
but she seems like a sweetheart.
Who else was there? Tiyana.
I feel like teeny almost got no information
when she could have
got way more information.
That's just appalling to me, so,
there's a lot of red flags at this moment
with teeny in the game.
He told that to your face?
Hundred percent.
So, the second Rome walks away,
Genevieve and sol start telling me
that Rome went absolutely nuts
when they got back from the challenge,
and that is music to my ears.
And then he goes,
"teeny has the amulet idol."
Okay.
- Figured.
- Yeah.
After last night,
I was so nervous about
my life in this game,
and now the tables
have turned a little bit.
Because of the madness
that occurred today,
I feel like sol and
Genevieve finally see the light
on what I've known, basically,
since the beginning of this game,
which is that Rome's unpredictability
and manner of playing this game is just
too chaotic to have, long-term.
I want him gone.
I'm not even gonna say "if."
When we get to the merge, all of us...
Those guys are scattering,
like, friggin', like...
- Like, I swear to god.
- Yeah. They're running.
We come home, and I
felt horrible knowing that
tiyana put a target on
Gabe's back in front of
the whole social hour.
I'm just gonna hop in
the water really fast, then
- I'll go crabbing.
- Yeah.
And then, also, cutting
up coconuts for Gabe.
And I want him to do,
like, literally nothing.
I think tiyana did it intentionally so that
others will look at him as a threat.
So, if she can't take him out
with us, she wants him gone.
And that makes me
pretty upset because he's
basically my number one ally.
My strategy right now is
trying to keep options open,
but tuku is falling apart.
It's looking more and more likely
all five of us might be
making it to the merge.
And I'm just thinking, "how
can we work together?"
My fear is that Gabe has
all trust gone with tiyana because
she threw him under the bus.
I'm trying to be the mother hen
and help us all form a
cohesive, wonderful family.
And they're all running away.
And I'm like, "let me try to
get one back in the Coop."
I want her to tell Gabe the full truth.
'Cause I'm worried about
Gabe finding out about it.
- About?
- About what you said.
I just don't see a world in
which if he's at the merge,
he doesn't find out
about what happened.
'Cause I'll be honest. I don't know
if Gabe will trust you after this.
Caroline suggested to me
that I come clean with Gabe.
I didn't feel, in that moment,
that I needed to apologize, but
if I ignore their advice,
no one will trust me because they know
I'm not listening to them.
So, if Caroline wants
me to apologize to Gabe
and it would make Gabe feel happy,
it just seems like the right thing to do.
Tiyana said that she
had a private conversation
with two other people,
that I played the idol,
but I don't believe it in the slightest.
Yeah.
But I also wanted to
be completely honest.
That was it. Like...
The whole time, I'm just like,
"yeah."
- Yeah.
- "Okay."
- Okay.
- Tiyana,
I've never once trusted anything
that comes out of your mouth.
It was just that I played the idol, it wasn't
anything about, like,
my game or anything?
No. I literally only told - okay.
- Rachel and teeny about that.
- Okay.
- Don't worry about it, we're totally cool.
- Dude. Gabe.
We're totally cool. Don't worry about it.
- I really am, like, so sorry.
- No worries.
I get my bs apology from tiyana.
That doesn't make me feel good.
I-I think if tiyana was not
compelled to apologize to me,
then she would not have.
She said that she only
talked to Rachel and teeny,
and it was in a private
conversation with them
that she said that I played my idol.
I'm angry at how open and brazen
tiyana was about throwing
my name out there.
But I've been ready to cut tiyana out
for a long time. I want to
crush her survivor dreams.
I want to watch her torch get snuffed out
and I want to smile while it happens.
Look, there are a lot of
things required to win survivor
but ultimately, it's gonna
come down to your relationships.
Do you think you have
what it takes to pull it off?
Apply to be on survivor.
Come on in!
Good morning, tuku.
- Good morning, Jeff.
Morning, sunshine.
Come on in, lavo.
Down to four.
Here comes a very
slow-moving gata tribe.
With their chickens.
Got all three?
- All three, Jeff.
- All three.
This gonna be interesting.
Well, let's just start with the obvious.
Are they family members
that travel with you now
or is this about something else?
You know, Jeff, we,
as a tribe, would like to
- propose a negotiation with you.
- I love a negotiation.
- I know you do.
- Tell me what you're thinking.
Well, the thing is, we
you know, we saw that
second place got the six eggs,
initially. They -okay.
Popped out, in two and
a half days, three eggs.
Two of them shattered before
we could even get to 'em.
'Cause they just pop out.
So, first of all, Sam, is the reason
you've not chosen to eat the chickens
a moral decision?
Not everybody was comfortable
with the idea of eating the chickens.
- Okay.
- So, you want to make sure
everybody's comfortable on our tribe.
Eating the chickens...
not really an option for us.
And they kind of suck at making eggs.
So you're saying you want to trade
- the chickens for eggs?
- Correct.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- What's the offer?
- I think
two dozen sounds pretty good, Jeff.
So, 24 eggs. Okay.
On survivor, we see
the chicken as a dilemma
in this sense:
You can eat the chicken
or you can use the
eggs from the chicken.
Those eggs are gonna
be hatched over 16 days,
so that's a little bit
like winning the lottery,
and you get paid a little every year.
You want to put all
your eggs in one basket.
You want to get paid right now.
That comes at a reduced price.
So, you're asking for 24 eggs,
which is eight per chicken.
I'll counter at five per chicken.
That's 15 total eggs.
- Twenty.
Shall we meet in the middle?
Which is never great negotiating,
but I'm willing to do it. 18.
- Let's do it.
- Eighteen eggs.
- Done, you have a deal.
- Deal. - Deal, Jeff.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Eighteen eggs will be
waiting for you back at camp.
- The chickens will stay with me.
- All right.
- Thanks. -Thanks, Jeff.
- Good for you guys.
All right. Shall we get
to - good for you guys.
Today's immunity challenge?
All right,
first things first. Got
to take back the idols.
Thank you. Thank you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're gonna drag
a very heavy net... hey! Sorry.
- What happened?
- He's just
biting my foot, and I - pecked her toes.
- Take care of him.
- That's what
family members who are
left on the side of the road do.
They got to go.
If you... I'll just step away.
- Sorry.
- All right.
For today's challenge, you're gonna drag
a very heavy net
full of coconuts and
sandbags along the course.
Along the way, you're gonna
collect more sandbags
and more coconuts,
making it even heavier.
When you get to the finish,
you're gonna throw the sandbags
at a puzzle wall until
you knock off every block,
then race to reassemble
the exact same puzzle.
First two tribes to finish win immunity,
safe from the vote,
will not be sent home.
Tribal council, where somebody will be
the fifth person voted out
of survivor 47. All right,
we have sit-outs. Gata,
one extra person who you
can sit out. It can be anybody,
because everybody
participated in the last challenge.
- Jeff, I'm gonna sit out.
- Anika gonna sit out for gata.
- Tuku, one extra person.
- I'm gonna sit out.
Sue, you're gonna sit this
one out. All right, sit outs,
take a spot on the
bench. Everybody else,
give you a minute to
strategize. We'll get it on.
Here we go.
All right, here we go.
For immunity.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, you got to drag
that bag to your first mat.
Yep, yep, we're on it.
- Go. Hey, go, go, go!
- You're good, you're good,
- you're good.
- Good job, guys!
Now you're gonna saw a rope.
We've got Kyle for tuku,
sol for lavo, - nice, sol.
Andy for gata.
Come on, gata!
Let's go, Andy.
Turn it around, turn it around.
- Flip it. You need the blade.
- Yeah, that one.
There you go.
Kyle working it for tuku.
- Come on, baby.
- Yes, Kyle.
Kyle has his for tuku.
Good job, Kyle.
Now you got to get all your coconuts
and your sandbags into your bag.
- Don't throw them so hard, guys.
- Okay.
- Yeah. There it is, sol. Go!
- Go! Go!
Sol has his.
Andy, still working for gata.
Keep cutting, Andy.
Come on, Andy!
- Good job!
- Andy struggling.
Come on, Andy. We need you, bud.
- Let's go.
- One, two.
Tuku thinks they have all their sandbags.
- You're good!
- We're good.
Hurdle. Hit it hard, hit it hard.
Tuku in the lead, still.
Tuku at the second stage.
Come on, guys!
Got to get all the coconuts in that bag.
Try to get as far back as you can.
- All right, we're good.
- Lavo, you're good! - Go!
Those bags are heavy.
- Andy still working.
- Keep pushing, Andy!
You got this.
This is a huge early setback
- for gata.
- You got it.
Gata has theirs!
Finally. They got a lot
of time to catch up now.
- Help put them in the bag.
- I need help!
Once you have all the
coconuts, you can move on.
Go.
Tuku, you're good.
Hit it hard, hit it hard, hit it hard!
That bag is very heavy now.
One, two, three, pull!
Tuku doing a nice job working together.
It is tuku in the lead, then lavo.
Rome, help him lift it.
- Gata has a lot of time to make up.
- Let's go.
- One, two, three, pull!
Tuku now can empty the bag.
- Sandbags in the...
- I'll organize it. Yup.
I got coconuts.
Everyone watch your step.
Let's go, lavo! That bag is heavy.
Gata, you're good. Let's go!
Gata, you got this!
I believe in you!
Let's go, gata. You're in this.
Keep pushing.
Tuku with a huge early lead.
Lavo trying to close the gap.
Almost there. Five more steps.
Once you have every sandbag,
then you can start knocking
down your puzzle wall.
- That's it. - Good.
- You're good! Go, tuku!
- Toss it, Caroline. Go.
- I got it. I got it.
Anybody can throw.
Tiyana up first.
Kyle with a toss.
It is gata working at the second stage.
Shoving 'em.
Kyle with a big arm.
There's a couple of blocks for tuku.
Good job, guys.
You're good, lavo.
It is now lavo that can start
breaking down their wall.
- Got it!
- Kyle with another nice toss.
- Nice, sol!
- Sol, wow!
Sol knocks five blocks completely off.
And gata is still inexplicably working
at the second stage.
There goes tiyana. Nice toss.
Yeah, tiyana!
- Yeah, sol!
- Sol with another big hit.
- Yes, Rome!
- Rome with a nice toss.
We are neck-and-neck.
- Yup.
- Yeah, sol!
Sol with another one.
And now it gets harder to
get those bottom blocks off.
- Yes!
- Yes, Gabe! -And Gabe for tuku
with a nice hit. There goes Rome.
They're moving them slowly.
You have blocks blocking
the blocks. That's a problem.
Tuku, you're good. Start rebuilding.
- Come on, tuku!
- Now you got to get
all your pieces back on your mat.
- Go, gata!
- Push!
Gata finally out of the second stage.
Push, dig deep!
You're good.
Now unload.
You got this, gata!
Tuku working on putting
their puzzle back together.
But lavo has hit a roadblock.
It's gonna take a big
gun to move those blocks,
'cause they are jammed up.
- Got to get 'em off that table.
- We're so close.
- Let's go.
- You're good, gata. Let's go!
Big gun from Sam
knocks off four blocks.
Sierra with a nice rocket.
Gata's made up a lot of time.
It is lavo slowing down now.
That's okay. We can do this.
Come on.
Everybody's in this now,
'cause we're looking for two.
You got this, guys, you're in it!
Another gun from Sam.
So frustrating.
- Yup. Good. That's it.
- Yup.
Tuku with a huge lead right now.
- Ready? - Yup. Yeah.
- Yes.
Here comes Sam
again with another toss.
Lavo, keep working. They cannot
- be touching the frame.
- Yeah, sol!
Here comes Andy.
Yeah!
- Andy did it! You're good!
- There you go, Andy!
A huge comeback from gata.
- One more, one more.
- There goes Rome.
You're good!
Let's go, lavo!
- And then this one.
- Yeah.
Tuku with another piece, getting closer.
You guys ready?
- Double-check.
- Jeff! Jeff!
- Tuku thinks they have it.
And they do!
Tuku wins immunity,
safe from tribal council.
- My god.
- Hey, hey.
Lavo and gata... they are literally
starting on this puzzle
at the exact same time.
- This is top left.
- Yeah, that's right. - Nice.
- Immunity on the line.
- Yeah, perfect.
Somebody going home tonight.
Player number five of
survivor 47, say bye-bye.
- Face 'em all the right way, si. Don't...
- I... they're the right way.
No. Like, this needs to face us.
- Yeah, but she needs to be able to see.
- Hey, no fighting.
Gata was dead last but
once again, a huge comeback.
Fighting to stay alive in this game.
Wait, wait, wait, gimme that one back.
I can't see the puzzle
if we're facing the pieces
upside down and sideways.
- That's it? - Yeah.
- Yup.
Lavo with another piece.
We are still neck-and-neck.
You're so close, you're
so close, you're so close!
I think something else is wrong.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- There it is. There it is.
- Wing needs to go on this side.
- This is gonna
- come down to the wire.
- You got it, guys!
- That's right. That's right.
- You got this!
Quick, quick, quick!
- One more. - Jeff!
- Jeff!
Lavo thinks they have
it. Get back to your mat.
Put it back. Put it back.
- Go, go, go!
- Move! - Sol falls.
There you go. You got it.
That's it. That's it.
You're good!
Lavo pulls it out in the
last seconds over gata...
Thank you!
My god!
Sending gata back
to tribal council, where somebody
will be the fifth person
voted out of survivor 47.
My gosh.
That was tight.
- Wow.
Lavo, big, emotional win.
- Rome, tell me - about the emotion.
- I mean,
we knew coming into today
that we're the only tribe
where the majority of us hasn't had
anything but coconut the last six days.
We came in knowing that
we're gonna be super low energy,
and we just told everyone,
"just give it our all.
"Just put your whole heart
into it and don't give up,
"no matter how hard it might get.
Just power through
and try to not go to tribal."
And the fact that we
were able to do it today,
it just shows us why you
never give up on survivor, Jeff.
All right, tuku, congratulations.
Immunity is yours.
Nobody going home from your tribe.
Lavo, big win indeed.
Immunity is yours.
And you get your flint back.
Let's go. We got fire,
man. Thank you, Jeff.
Most importantly, nobody
going home from your tribe.
Tuku, grab your stuff, head out,
enjoy the night off. Nobody going home.
Great job.
Great job, guys.
Lavo, grab your stuff, head out.
- Enjoy the night off from me.
- Thank you.
So, Rachel, the afternoon started off
pretty well. We had a nice negotiation.
Eggs waiting for you back
at camp, but the result is
- tribal council.
- And no way to cook the eggs.
The great irony of having
- 18 eggs back at camp.
- Shoot.
Because I'm gonna take your flint.
- You're gonna take our flint.
- All right, gata,
tribal council tonight,
where somebody will be
the fifth person voted out of survivor 47.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take that flint
and your ability to cook.
All right, grab your stuff,
head out. See you
tonight at tribal council.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Jeff.
This immunity challenge,
was a tough one, and
after ten days out here, I can conclude
I'm not good at challenges.
So, tonight, it could be me.
I've been on the bottom
for a very long time in this game, but
I've laid a lot of groundwork
on what could happen
if we were to go to a tribal council.
And I feel like this is
the real start of my game.
I'm looking forward to tonight.
- Great job, everyone.
- Great job. - Great job.
The challenge was a total flop.
We rode the high of
our chicken negotiation
all the way down to rock bottom.
No, it's okay. Just for my part.
Andy, once again, can't seem
to get out of his own way in a challenge.
At one point, Andy is sawing the rope
with the non-saw part of the saw.
You come that close to immunity
and then your mind goes,
"would have been nice
if we would have sawed
that rope just a little bit faster."
I can't stop thinking
about how much I
want to cook those eggs.
- Yup.
- This is the only morning
since we got here that
we didn't make a fire.
- That sucks.
- Yeah.
The fact we were able to negotiate
for 18 eggs is so major.
The only downside is that
we lost the immunity challenge
and had to give away our flint,
and therefore, have no fire.
- Wash off?
- Yeah. I'm down for that.
There are multiple times
throughout the challenge.
Andy made it harder for
my tribe and not easier.
I like Andy as a person,
but I think our tribe will
be genuinely better off
without Andy here.
This shirt is so nasty,
no matter how much I scrub.
I'm gonna pee.
- I'm gonna go this way.
- You pee.
I lost my vote on a journey, but
even though I don't have my vote,
I am not worried
because I know where my alliances lie.
So, I'm sure Andy is going home tonight.
Yeah, me, too.
Andy is definitely a little bit
of a liability, challenge-wise,
and it is super, super frustrating. But,
long-term, I don't trust Anika, so,
I want Anika out of here.
I-I'm ready for her to go.
I feel in danger tonight, so,
whoever extends a lifeline is the person
- I'm ready to be loyal to in the game.
- Yeah.
- Does that make sense?
- No, it does.
- Yeah.
- Like, numbers.
After all my efforts, I truly believe
that Anika is buying what
I'm selling, that she believes
that I truly feel on the bottom.
It would just be... It would feel so good
to, like, you know, be a part of the group.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah. Yeah.
My alliance with Sam
and Sierra is top secret,
and I think that Anika
is very, very confident
and very sure about
what's happening tonight.
Suffice to say, I think she
underestimates people,
and she underestimates me.
- I don't feel secure tonight.
- Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm-i'm a
free number right now.
I'm a completely free number, so,
if at any point today you're like,
"I need a number for this," - yeah.
- You just let me know.
- I mean, I appreciate that.
- Yeah.
- And, like,
- I don't know what's happening yet.
- Okay.
I know my role. I have a
very specific role to play here
if we're gonna blindside Anika.
If there is some plan out
there, let me be a part of it.
Here's how my plan works.
I want Anika and Rachel
to see me as someone
feeling very much on the outs,
which they believe I am.
So I say to Anika and Rachel,
"pull me into your master
plan. I will be so loyal to you."
I want them to respond to that
and be like, "okay, the
best thing that we can do"
"to prevent Andy from
playing his shot in the dark is
to feed him a fake plan."
So, since Andy is so eager
to be part of a plan,
then we sell him one.
I feel like it'd be believable
that we were trying to get Sam out,
- yeah, I agree.
- 'Cause we're trying to keep the girls.
I go back to camp, and
then pretty soon after.
Anika and Rachel pull
me aside. They're like,
"hey, Andy, come here,
come here, come here."
Yeah.
Well, just lay it on me, please.
Please, yes.
They do exactly what
I expected them to do.
They're giving me a fake plan.
It is the name that I expected: Sam.
Yeah.
I'm in. I'm in.
I was very well prepared for that,
because I set it up.
I set up that conversation.
They don't know that,
but that's exactly what happened.
I'll act completely natural.
You can trust me with that.
- Yeah.
- They're believing
exactly what I'm feeding them,
hook, line and sinker.
I feel like I have all my eggs
in the right basket right now.
I just got to boil 'em.
Dude,
why am I sitting here, like,
over and over in my head,
making sure that we're
making the right decision?
We are doing the right thing,
I'm a million percent sure.
Anika getting out is the thing.
I'm looking at her in
her eyes, and I'm like
I know.
I feel like a piece of crap.
- You... I know you do.
- I mean, what the hell am I gonna
I think right now, Sierra
and I are just trying
to figure out how to
navigate as a pair when both
of our individual interests
might be slightly different.
Sierra really wants to keep Anika around.
I know how you're feeling
about looking into her eyes,
but, like, this whole, like,
"ani is your best
friend" thing is her game.
That's what she's trying to play.
I really want to keep Andy around,
but Sierra is my number one.
So we have to find a way
to keep each other calm
while we figure out what
the heck we're gonna do.
Are you, like, 100% sure ani can't vote?
- Ani 100% can't vote.
- Okay.
Going into tribal tonight,
Sam and I... we have
to get on the same page.
He wants to keep Andy,
but is keeping Andy the best
for my game? I know it's probably best
for Sam's game, but is it best for mine?
I have to figure out
what to do with the idol.
Your...
- 'Cause everything...
- That's the thing.
Keeping Andy.
He's now gonna lose a little trust.
He's gonna be like, "why
did you keep that from me?"
- Yeah.
- That's a target on your back.
'Cause he's gonna tell other people.
I know he would tell other people that.
You know that, like, for
me, that's a huge risk.
My hidden immunity idol is only
good for my next tribal council,
which means it's only good tonight.
I have to play it tonight, but
that creates some fireworks.
If I play an idol
and I've kept it from
Andy this entire time,
how does that impact my relationship
and my trust with him moving forward?
So, maybe the safe move
is voting out Andy tonight.
But I've wanted Anika out of the game
for a long, long time.
Basically, it comes down to
what Sierra and I want to do,
who we want to take with us further.
So, tonight, that's all the power.
All right.
Let's go back in time and talk about
the social hour reward.
Rachel, you were a part of that.
What was the most interesting
thing that you learned?
Yeah, I mean, we learned
about a few of the dynamics
that happened at tribal.
We learned that Gabe played an idol
at the first tribal council.
That was shocking to us.
- Yeah.
- We also learned teeny was
blindsided by the kishan vote.
So, yes, they could be lying, but
those would be kind of
weird things to lie about.
Sam, what do you
think was the impression
- they had of your tribe?
- I mean,
I think they bought, like,
everything that we said.
We kind of tried to not
give too many details
and just be "gata the
listeners," in the background.
Andy, what do you think
about how Sam and Rachel did
as spies going out to get information?
I mean, I think they did an excellent job.
I trusted them completely
because we've talked a lot about
managing our perception
to the other tribes,
and there's a very clear picture
to paint that I'm on the bottom
as a result of my emotional
moment on day three
at the challenge. I said things that were,
explosive, you could say,
but I've made so much
headway, especially socially.
I don't think, at the end of
the day, people really care
how good I am at a balance beam
or sawing a piece of rope.
- Well, your tribe mates care.
- True.
True, true. That is... It's important,
but I think what's more
important to my tribe is
getting to learn, you know,
what I am made of on the inside,
and I-I like what I see.
So, Rachel, this is setting us up nicely
for the conversation about tonight's vote.
Who do we vote out and why?
That's the tricky, tricky
part of survivor, where
you have to weigh out the
pros and cons of each person.
Like, this person may
be really emotional,
and they wear their heart on the sleeve.
That could really help you
or it can really hurt you, you know?
And so, I wish I knew the answer, Jeff.
Very tricky.
Sierra, where do you sit with this?
I mean, I think it's
great to keep individuals
who you trust, you form bonds with,
because going into a merge,
which can be a shaky situation,
you want to feel strong and
comfortable with your alliances.
But I also think there's 100% a benefit
of keeping somebody who is not exactly
as "liked" and fitting in and
gelling with the whole crew
because to me, that's a person
you want to keep around
because, you know,
that's somebody that's
an easy number out
come later on in the game.
Anika, how about for you?
Every tribal decision
each one of us makes
creates a completely different pathway
for our own personal game.
There could be eight billion diff...
Well, actually, in this case,
five different pathways.
Okay, there's five different pathways
that you could possibly take in this game,
and tonight we are going to find out
which is the next
pathway we decide to take.
Rachel, one big word
in what Anika just said.
"We." what is your sense of confidence
in knowing who the "we" is, and that
- you are a part of the "we"?
- I mean,
I believe that the "we"
that I established today, like,
is the "we." You know?
And I-I look around, and I...
Meet the eyes of the
people that I believe.
I... I'm working with, and
I feel confident about that.
But having cohesion
coming out of this vote is
the most important thing.
And so tonight is about
solidifying the alliance
that I want to be in come the merge.
And Sam, what Rachel
says seems simple.
Four people get together
and you vote out one person,
and you four are in Harmony.
But it's not always easy.
So is there some fear that maybe
we don't come out of this with
- everybody in Harmony?
- Yeah.
Cohesion is not always a guarantee,
but I feel confident tonight
that my "we" is going to
be cohesive after the vote.
Anika, how confident are you
that are part of the "we"?
It is so silly, but I also think
that I'm also hopefully in the "we,"
and we'll just have to see.
Andy, how confident are
you that you're with the "we"?
Yeah, for right now,
tonight, I'm trying to turn
the "me" into a "we." I'm trying
to build this vote to be the one vote
where I really feel like
I've entered into a group
of people that I can trust.
And if I can survive,
then, yeah, now I'm part of a "we."
I'm nervous for sure,
but I feel like I have a...
A shred of hope.
And I just want to
sort of get to it and, you
know, sort of see my fate.
All right.
It is time to vote.
Rachel, you're up.
I've been burying you
for the last ten days.
Here's your headstone.
I don't have a vote tonight,
but if I did, I'd be voting for you, Andy.
I simply can't trust you.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right.
I'll read the votes.
Anika.
Andy.
One vote Anika, one vote Andy.
Anika.
Two votes Anika, one
vote Andy. One vote left.
Fifth person voted out of survivor 47:
Anika.
Need to bring me your torch.
You're kidding me, you guys.
- Sorry.
Okay.
Did you know?
I didn't know.
Who-who owned this?
There's three of us.
Three votes.
Anika, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Nah.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org
my god!
Next time on survivor... It's animalistic
- at this point.
- What a dick.
I'm fixing to squish him like a bug.
I'm gonna be feasting on sol's bones.
I'm on survivor, baby.
I'm not gonna lie. I'm pretty devastated.
The worst part Is how confident I felt.
I got played before I could play them.
Yeah, it came to an
end too quickly for me.
I don't know, I'm just.
I'm-I'm devastated.