My heart is racing.
My god. I got it.
Survivor bucket list.
Previously on survivor...
It just came naturally with lavo.
Let's gata and lavo work together and
knock out tuku one by one.
- Tuku?
- Yeah.
The former gata members
want to work with us, but
I'd like to shake things up.
- You're in?
- Yeah.
I'm going to try and steer the next vote
towards one of the
former gata members.
Sam and Sierra look at
me as an expendable piece.
They feel like they own me.
You don't have to work
with them anymore.
Yeah. Yeah.
But Sam, Sierra and Rachel
they're not gonna see me coming.
Eighth person voted out of survivor 47
and the first member of our jury: Sierra.
The tribe has spoken.
Thank you for... For keeping me.
I appreciate another day.
Tribal council tonight was horrible.
Rachel and I get blindsided,
Sierra gets sent home,
and we happen to lose
Andy in the process.
So, gata is no more. Gata got got.
And now... It's every man for himself.
All right.
That sucks really, really, really bad.
I want to look out for you, too, and see...
Yeah.
Tonight, both Andy
and lavo flipped on gata.
It was a brilliant acting job,
like, across the board.
These people had me fooled, and
right now, their only mistake
was keeping me in the game.
That lava group is a bunch
- of very, very good liars.
- Yeah.
And then, I don't even
want to look at Andy.
Yeah.
But I just... I don't know
where to go from here.
Like, I don't know who to trust.
I kind of had this gut
feeling throughout tribal that
there's something going on, but
I didn't know what.
And so, I played my shot in the dark.
Not safe.
Any votes cast for Rachel will still count.
I played it to Gauge the reactions
of everyone at tribal to
see if they were looking
worried or surprised.
And based on the
reaction that everyone had
when I played my shot in the dark,
I did not feel like I was the vote,
and I didn't play my idol.
We just got to play our
own individual game and
try to do what we can for each other.
Moving forward, I'm willing to work
with just about anyone that will have me.
I don't have a lot of options.
My door is open, I'm taking calls.
We'll see who comes knocking.
It was nice that we all stuck
to the exact plan, though.
I want to say that.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Andy, thank you for voting with us.
It was a team effort.
Yeah.
After this vote, I'm a certified flipper.
I flipped on gata,
and I feel like this is the first step
of me taking my fate into my own hands.
And so, the only thing I have to do
at this point is damage control
with the gata members
who are left in the game.
From my perspective,
we come to the merge,
and I feel like I was left
to my own devices a bit.
- Okay.
- So
I wanted to better my
position in the game.
Since the start of this game, I felt like
I was the outcast.
I feel like I was on the bottom, and I was
sort of an expendable piece.
And so, now, for me to be the one
to get one over on all of
my original tribe members,
like, it's complete survivor satisfaction.
Not everyone gets to feel that...
That chef's kiss that I
have flipped the script.
Today, the target was
square on your back,
and I spent some
social capital I just gained
to make sure it was Sierra and not you.
Going all the way back to day three
after the immunity challenge
and the moment I had on the mat,
I fell on the bottom of my tribe,
I succumbed to paranoia,
and I thought that was
just gonna be it for me,
and that was gonna be my legacy.
- I appreciate it.
- All right. Yeah, dude.
And so, I feel like I've been given
the biggest second chance
you could ever have in this game.
I am learning every day out here, and
have just a huge amount
of just overall gratitude that...
That this is my story, and it's continuing,
and I'm still getting to write it.
Dude.
It was Sierra, predominantly,
that was like, "we could do Andy."
- Hah.
- And then, I was like,
"I am not putting Andy's
name down again."
Rachel and I have
both been on the bottom,
and so, I feel like if I
were to have a future
with any of the gata members,
it would definitely be Rachel.
But the stars have not aligned
for various reasons.
I'm not gonna lie.
That little chain of events...
- Did make me lose trust - in gata.
- Yeah.
I feel like Andy and I have kind of
orbited each other this entire game.
And we've, like, wanted to connect,
and then not wanted to connect
and we just kind of, like,
ping-ponged off each other
for a long time.
It was like a rock and
a hard place for me.
- So I'm sorry, and...
- That's completely fine.
- I want you in this game.
- Yeah.
I wanted you in this
game the entire time.
I feel like
we should be working
together in this game.
That was my plan on day one.
Yeah. We're-we're in alignment.
- We're synchronized.
- I agree.
I'm like, "you're strong. I'm strong."
- Yeah.
- I feel like it's good.
There were points in the
game where I was like,
"I kind of want to work
with Andy, but, like,
he's frustrating to work with."
You have to be careful, though.
I totally... I'm so sorry.
It's just that... I just.
Rachel didn't feel the
same way about me,
so I was leaning in to
my role, which was the bottom player.
Yeah.
I'm in. All right.
Fifth person voted out of survivor 47.
I blindsided Rachel on the Anika vote.
Anika, the tribe has spoken.
Andy blindsided me at the Anika vote
and then he blindsided me
again last night. And so,
I feel like I'm climbing a sand dune
and every step I take
up, I slide two steps down.
Despite all this, it's like,
I've always felt the same way about you.
Like, we should probably
take this opportunity to, like, actually...
Okay, can we, like...
- Work together?
- Maybe we can work together.
- Actually work together? Yeah.
- For real.
Throughout this game,
I've definitely broken
trust with Rachel, but
I do like her.
I feel like we have chemistry,
and we could definitely
have game chemistry out here.
I feel like, given the game board,
I feel like you are
an absolutely key
relationship for me right now.
- Andy.
- I know.
Is there anyone you're really wary of?
- There's Kyle with the challenges.
- Yeah.
Sue and Caroline, like, don't like him.
- They wanted him out forever.
- That's true.
- He just won't lose.
We've had a rocky road, but we're finally
in a place now where we
can maybe start to kind of, like,
come together and be like,
"hi." like, "hello. I'm..."
Like, "I'm Andy." "I'm Rachel."
And it's like, almost like
we can start over and,
like, reform something
and work together on some votes.
I still have some sort of life in this game.
I just want to say sorry.
Like, I know it sucks - Sam: Yeah.
To, like, be blindsided like that.
I feel like it was...
We're... from our standpoint, kind of like,
tuku wanted to split you and Sierra up.
Like, thought of you
guys as a power couple,
and that was really hard, and I'm sorry.
And I know how it must feel.
I hope that there's still a way
we could, at some point,
you know, come together.
I'm ready to play.
I have a vendetta against lavo.
We thought we were working
with lavo and, turns out,
we never had lavo.
So, I'm ready for them to feel
what I had to feel last night.
I want to pick myself
back up and, you know...
For real.
'Cause, like, I really
want to play with you guys.
Right.
But I need to play along, at least for now,
and then come for my revenge later.
I wasn't turning my back on Sierra.
I think everybody knew that.
So, something had
to be done about that,
from everybody else's
perspective, I get that.
I was a part of that
blindside against Sam,
but I like Sam's mentality.
He's not getting emotional,
he's not getting pissed.
Did you and Andy mend
fences, or, like, what was...
- What did he say?
- Look, I get it from Andy.
You know, I don't have
any hard feelings there.
Right.
And so the fact that Sam's telling me,
"hey, I get it. It's all good."
It's like, "okay, maybe I
can work with this guy."
Even though I worked
with Gabe last night
to take out Sierra, I
think that dude's a player.
I'm starting to get, like, just
I'm so unsure of their dynamics that, like,
we should try and make it be Gabe.
Yeah. Okay.
At some point, we need to get out Gabe,
and, that's what I'm trying to do.
Wow.
Okay.
Tree mail says, "only one of us is safe."
So, what's tricky about
this type of pairing is
you're really trying to think about,
"okay, who will get me to that last stage
"of the challenge where
I can actually compete
for individual immunity?"
But I also want to be
careful not to pick someone
who's so competitive and so strong that
they're gonna be a
shoe-in to win immunity.
Andy?
Let's do it.
- I'll go with Andy.
- All right.
Sam grabs me and
is like, "Andy, let's go."
"Let's do this." I thought
that was interesting
because I really betrayed him last night.
But I kind of looked at it
as a pretty good opportunity for us to
at least, like, in a challenge setting,
just be kind of bros again.
I'm really down to go
head-to-head against Andy.
If it comes down to me and Andy,
I'm gonna beat him out.
Me and Kyle are partners
going into the challenge today, and that's
a very exciting thing for me
because he's won the
last three challenges.
So,
if there's anybody you
want going to battle with you,
it's the guy who's on a
winning streak, and I got him.
Based on just general
knowledge of the game,
you can expect to work
together in a pair to a point.
And then that other person
in your pair is going to become
your mortal enemy at
the end of this challenge,
which is exactly why I picked Gabe.
I think that I can beat Gabe
when we go head-to-head.
Come on in!
Welcome.
All right, let's get to
today's immunity challenge.
First things first. Got to
take back the necklaces.
Look at sue coming to me.
- Look at this.
- How kind. Thank you.
- Thank you, Kyle.
- Absolutely.
Once again,
individual immunity is back up for grabs.
This morning in tree mail,
you were given instructions
to divide into pairs.
So let's get into those pairs.
Let me see what happened.
Get next to your partner.
Let's see what's what.
So, Kyle, you made these pairs.
How did that go?
- What happened?
- I think
everybody just kind of jived pretty good.
You know, Gabe and I locked eyes, and
I asked him to be mine and he said yes.
All right, let's review our pairs.
We have sue and Genevieve.
We have Caroline and
Rachel, teeny and sol,
Gabe and Kyle, Andy and Sam.
All right, today's challenge
is gonna run in stages.
For the first stage,
you're gonna crawl
through a narrow tunnel
filled with sand and
retrieve one puzzle step.
You'll then race to dig up a second step.
The first three pairs to
get back with their steps
move on to the next stage.
The last two pairs are
out. No shot at immunity.
For the next stage,
you will use those
steps to build a staircase.
Once you get to the top, you will attempt
to cross a three-level balance beam.
The first two pairs to finish
move on to the final stage.
You are pairs no more.
You will compete as four individuals.
You'll use your hands
and arms to brace against two walls
while your feet balance
on very narrow footholds.
It will be painful. You will feel it.
When you drop, you are out.
Last person left standing
wins immunity, guaranteed a spot
in the final nine... single digits.
Losers, tribal council,
where somebody will be
the ninth person voted out
and become the second
member of our jury.
In addition, you're playing for a reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
Final four... those last two pairs
that move on to the final round
you will enjoy an afternoon
picnic back at camp.
Blt sandwiches, potato chips, soft drinks.
Worth playing for?
All right. One more thing.
- Ooh.
- No.
The first two pairs who
are out lose their vote
at tonight's tribal council.
- Wow.
- What?!
Yeah, one more thing.
You will take a journey with a chance
- to earn it back.
- Wow.
Now we got some
stakes worth playing for.
- All right.
- We're gonna draw for spots. Here we go.
Let's go.
All right, let's do this.
First three pairs to finish move on
to the next stage.
Last two pairs are out,
no shot at immunity.
Here we go. Survivors ready?
Go! One at a time,
you got to get through this tunnel
and retrieve one puzzle step.
You're working through a very narrow,
very low tunnel with a lot of sand in it.
- Kyle working on those knots.
- Hell, yeah, teeny.
- There goes teeny.
Your knot's at your right. Yeah.
You got to then untie that puzzle step,
and get it and you through
the rest of this tunnel.
It is Kyle in the early lead,
yet to lose an immunity challenge.
You're good. Go, Gabe.
Here comes Sam with his puzzle step.
You're good! Here goes Andy.
Three pairs are moving
on, so keep digging.
You're doing good, Genevieve.
Genevieve down on the end.
- And teeny.
- My ass is too big!
Come on, man, -
Probst: There goes Gabe.
We got this. Come on, buddy.
Andy's through. Start digging.
Gabe's through. It is Sam and Andy,
Kyle and Gabe in the lead.
- Genevieve is through.
- Good job, good job, good job!
You're good! Go, sue!
- Let's go, teeny!
- Hell, yeah.
Gabe and Kyle working
on that second step.
Andy and Sam working
You're good. Go, Caroline!
Sorry, Caroline.
Abe and Kyle moving on.
Yeah, sue, yes.
Sue is through. You're good.
- Start digging!
- Okay. Dig.
You're good. Go, sol!
Jeff?
- Our piece is out of the bag.
- Yup.
- That's on you all.
- I'm through.
Caroline's through. Find a step.
You got it, sol.
- Let's go.
- Sol is through.
Everybody now digging
for their second puzzle step.
Sam and Andy... they
are on their puzzle step,
but they cannot get it out.
We're so close.
Kyle and Gabe are moving on.
We're looking for two more pairs.
- Yeah.
- Who is it gonna be?
Look at that. Teeny and sol have it!
They're moving on!
We're looking for one more.
- My god.
- It is going to be Rachel, Caroline,
Sam and Andy, or Genevieve and sue.
Sam and Andy have been
working on that piece for a long time,
- cannot get it out.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Andy's pulling on it.
Can we wedge it out?
One, two and three.
- Go, go, go! Go!
- Good job, guys.
There it is!
Genevieve and sue kept working,
- and they have moved on.
- We did it. We did it.
- Sam and Andy are out.
Rachel and Caroline are out.
No shot at immunity.
That was hard.
You have lost your votes.
Will have a chance to
earn them back later today.
Sue and Genevieve, you're moving on.
Sol and teeny, you're moving on.
Kyle and Gabe, you're moving on.
Move up to the next
stage and we'll keep going.
All right. Moving on to the next stage,
sue and Genevieve,
sol and teeny, Kyle
and Gabe, you're gonna
use your puzzle steps
to build a staircase,
cross the balance beam
and get to your mat.
First two pairs move
on to the final round.
Last pair is out, no shot at immunity.
Here we go. Survivors ready?
Go! It is one puzzle step
at a time. That's the trick.
And you got to build it in order.
You got to figure out
what piece you need.
These are all puzzle pieces.
The question is which
spots do they go in?
Pull out the next one.
It's a lot of communication.
- What do you got?
- One jumbo.
So, one jumbo in the middle
Kyle, no. Got to go back.
If they don't fit, it's not right.
They may look right,
but they may be a little off.
This is part of it.
- This is a puzzle staircase.
- Got it.
It is not easy. You're
gonna learn as you go.
A lot of experimentation
and a lot of memory.
- Here comes Kyle.
- No.
That's not right. Teeny
now gonna get into it.
She's got one.
That's three for red
and that's four for blue.
One jumbo in the second spot.
Genevieve and sue in the early lead.
- We're good. Good. - Yup.
- Gabe has the second piece.
There goes Genevieve
with another piece.
Blue has got some momentum.
Sol sprints with another piece for red.
- Good.
- Gabe's got one for yellow.
There goes sue with one for blue.
One jumbo at both ends.
Two jumbos on the end?
Teeny with another for red.
- Good.
- This is very tight right now.
- All three pairs are in it.
- Good!
Genevieve and sue
have been in the lead
for most of it, just barely.
Then teeny and sol, then Gabe and Kyle.
- There's another piece for red.
- Yell it out.
Big, small, medium!
- What?
- Teeny big, small, medium, teeny.
- There's another piece for blue.
- One jumbo on the end!
Gabe and Kyle trying to stay in it.
- Go, Gabe.
- Go, buddy, go.
- Sol with another piece.
- Red down to three.
Okay. Bring it up.
Blue down to one.
Here it is... the last piece
for sue and Genevieve.
You're good. One person
across the beam now.
- Let's go.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here comes sol with
another piece for red.
- Big one on this side.
- Gabe with another for yellow.
Sue gonna take on that beam.
It is sue and Genevieve in the lead.
Here comes teeny with another piece.
- Here comes Gabe with another piece.
- No good. No good.
- Good, good, good, good, good!
- Here, try this.
- We have time.
- Sue taking her time on the beam.
Red down to one piece left.
- Got to get it in there.
- Nice.
That's good. You're
good, red. Now it's teeny
- and sol on the balance beam.
- Good.
Gabe with another for yellow.
- You're still in it.
- Big one on this end.
Slow and steady. Slow and steady.
- It's a regular balance beam.
- Teeny whips across it!
- You're good!
- Come on, sol. Just go.
Sue's across!
Go, Genevieve! Kyle
and Gabe now down
to one piece left. Here goes sol.
Come on, sol.
Sol falls. He's got to go back.
Slow and steady. We got tons of time.
Here it is, the last
piece for Kyle and Gabe.
- Got it. Come on, Gabe.
- Yeah.
- Let's go!
- You're still in this.
Kyle and Gabe now are crossing quickly.
- Kyle jumps on that beam.
- Just keep stepping.
This is gonna be a close
finish. Sol now struggling.
You're good, on the
mat. Here comes Gabe.
Sol's across. You're good!
Gabe's across. You're good. Head down!
What a finish on the beam.
Wow!
What a comeback
- by Kyle and Gabe.
- Nice job. Hell yeah.
After having the lead
the entire challenge,
sue and Genevieve fall short
- on the beam. - Sorry.
- No, don't apologize.
What a finish.
That was instant classic.
And now lots of congratulations.
- Good game.
- My god, yeah.
Even with your adversaries.
You're seeing it on display again.
Huge effort.
All right, we're moving
on to the final round.
Wow.
All right.
We're gonna start on
the highest foothold.
At regular intervals, we're gonna move
farther down, making it more difficult.
You are gonna feel it.
When you drop, you're out.
Last person left standing wins immunity.
Everybody looks good.
This challenge is on.
Day 16, survivor 47.
Teeny smiling big as ever.
Sol concentrating.
Done a lot to get here.
You dug through a
tunnel, built a staircase.
You navigated a very tricky
three-level balance beam.
Willpower.
This is about pain.
Good job, guys.
This is as good as it will get.
That next foothold is a lot more narrow.
All right, we're gonna move
down to the next foothold.
Start making your move.
This is a live transition.
If you fall during this process, you're out.
Much more narrow.
Gabe, you got to go.
Good job. Everybody has transitioned...
Hang in there. To the next stage.
Everybody's good.
You're gonna be up
here for five minutes.
Now this challenge is really gonna dig in.
Kyle has won all three
individual immunity
challenges this season,
has not lost.
A chance to extend that to four.
Kyle, how you doing?
Doing all right.
It's not as bad as you thought?
I wouldn't go that far.
Everybody looking really good up there.
Whatever you are doing
right now, it's working.
Watched people do this
challenge for many years.
There's nothing about this
challenge that is comfortable.
Gabe, you all right?
Politely, Jeff, don't talk to me.
You got it.
Politely accepted.
All right, it is time for
another live transition.
Start making your way down.
You can't grip along the way.
That's good, Gabe. Got to start moving.
Gabe's good. Teeny's good.
Kyle's good. Sol is good.
Gonna be here for ten minutes.
We're now into this third foothold,
and this one is really small.
You cannot give in.
You came out here to play survivor.
You came out here to win.
Outwit, outplay, outlast right now.
This is why you came out here,
for this kind of test.
Teeny, hang in there. Let's go.
Dig in. Find some more pain tolerance.
One minute left in this round.
Then we go to the most narrow foothold.
If we get there.
Sol with a bit of a slip. Can he recover?
Sol trying to get it back.
He's got it.
Come on, guys. Hang tough.
Good news about this challenge.
Nobody knows if you're struggling or not.
Nobody can see anyone else.
But anybody could drop at any moment,
which is why you want to hang in there
as long as you can.
Teeny drops and sol drops.
- Hang in there!
- We have a showdown
- from an original pair.
- Hang in there.
It is Kyle versus Gabe
for individual immunity.
Great job.
All right. We're gonna
make our move to that final stage.
Before you move, let me remind you,
it is a live transition. You both have to
start moving at the same time.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Start moving.
Get down to that last foothold.
Both guys have done it.
Now it's on.
Kyle versus Gabe.
The last and most narrow foothold.
This is it. We go here
until somebody drops.
Game on, brother.
Keep digging. Let's go.
Use your arms to brace
against those walls.
This would be Kyle's
fourth individual immunity win,
a perfect record this season.
Kyle drops. He's out.
Gabe wins individual immunity.
Safe tonight at tribal council,
cannot be voted out of this game.
Good job, Gabe.
Wow, what a huge effort.
- Gabe, wow.
- Good job!
- Nice job. - Good job.
- Well done.
Gabe, come on over.
Yay, Gabe.
Gabe, individual immunity is yours.
You are safe tonight,
guaranteed a spot in the final nine.
- You're in single digits.
- Yeah.
- Cannot be voted out.
- Head back over.
Can I hit a dance for
the people back at home?
Please do.
My god.
Good job, Gabe.
You rocked it.
All right, little business
to take care of right now.
Andy, Rachel, Caroline, Sam
first two pairs to lose.
You have lost your vote.
So as of now, you do not have a vote.
Good news is you're gonna
leave here, go on a journey
where you will have a
chance to earn it back.
It is not guaranteed.
Grab your stuff, head out.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
You will return back
to camp this afternoon
before tribal council.
Everybody else going
back to camp, but sol,
Kyle, Gabe and teeny
you're gonna enjoy an afternoon picnic.
A little bit of a break from the game,
a chance to bond, fuel for your body,
help your mind for
the big decision tonight.
Who's gonna be the
ninth person voted out
and become the second
member of the jury?
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at tribal.
I am a little disappointed in myself
because I thought that I can beat Gabe.
I really gave it my all, but now
I'm a sitting duck.
I can be picked off just
as easy as the next guy.
So, I'm nervous about tonight.
I mean, what can I say?
Th-these are the moments.
If you want this, you got
to apply to be on survivor.
It's a very interesting
dynamic after the challenge.
We're all split up into
three separate groups.
There are the no-vote journey people,
and they're off on a different
island somewhere doing
god knows what to try
and earn their vote back.
Then there's Genevieve and sue,
who didn't lose their vote, but
they didn't get a reward, either.
My god. My god.
And then there's the reward group:
Me, Kyle, teeny and sol.
Congrats, guys.
Gabe's not with us right now.
This is one of the best days of my life.
This is bucket list. This is, "my god.
I'm wearing the necklace."
And then, on top of that, it's the first
proper meal I've had in 16 days.
I got dizzy from just how good it felt.
I'm hallucinating right now.
All we're hearing
from Gabe right now is
just pleasureful moaning
and groaning as he bites into this bit.
And on the other side of me,
I have sol, who is just a burp machine.
I grew up burping in front of my family.
Whenever I'm just so
comfortable around people,
I'll let it go.
I was trying to keep up with sol.
It was impossible.
I'd much rather have a cool
cartoon burp than, like, a weak-ass burp.
I would chug some soda
to try to force more out,
and I would just get a little, like...
And then, sol just would
be, like, have his head down
and lift up and just go...
And then put his head
back down, and I was like,
"I feel small right now."
Yeah.
I mean, you wanted Sam last night.
You know I did.
How do you feel about tonight?
I'm so down for it.
Sam, I necessarily don't want to get out.
I believe he trusts me.
But honestly, the reason why
I would vote out Sam is 'cause
that's what everyone wants
to do, and I'm riding the boat.
It's not my name, number one.
That's the most important thing.
My name's not on there.
Genevieve will be on board
with whatever we bring to her.
Sue will give us the majority we need
if we get Genevieve.
This is the first time
I'm actually vulnerable in this game.
I'm nervous because
you never know what Genevieve
and sue would be talking about.
But, you know, I don't
really see Genevieve
as, like, a super social,
like, a thinker in this game.
This is what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Sol wants Gabe out.
The first time tuku went to tribal,
Kyle wrote my name down.
So tonight, my plan was
to do a blindside on Kyle.
I quite like Gabe,
and I don't want him to go home yet.
I know. He's such a good guy.
- That's a huge...
- And so, like, my preference would be
get out sol.
But I learned that sol is after Gabe.
If I lose Gabe
like, my whole game is shot.
- Sue is... yeah.
- You know...
- She's great to have on our side.
- Yeah.
- I think it's, like, very nice.
- Sue is not gonna be
the person to be, like, "hey, everybody,
it's sol tonight."
We could do a big blindside on sol.
It would have to be
a total blindside because he's so clever.
I've had a bee in my
bonnet since my lavo beach,
where sol targeted my ally Rome.
And we've mended fences-ish.
But, like, in this game,
I am so petty, and so,
I've really just been waiting.
"When can I get sol?"
I'm going into this mystery journey
without a vote.
I feel vulnerable and in danger
and completely powerless.
I have to find a way to get my vote back.
The last two times, it was
- the same puzzle for every person.
- Yeah.
Three people were separated
and did the same puzzle,
and if they won, they got their vote back.
I went into the challenge with such heart
and such motivation
that this was gonna
be the one that I won.
I... I really wanted that one.
I want it because I don't want
to be the guy that's scratching to,
you know, hang on.
I don't know what's in store, but
I still have a fighting
shot at getting myself
back into this game.
All right.
These journeys are like
nightmare fuel for me.
We have to compete in a game,
and the loser of this game
is going to be the one player
that loses their vote tonight.
I'm like, "okay, survivor
put me on this journey. Like,
let's see how things shake out."
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hey, there.
It was nice.
No.
I'm not depressed. I'm full.
So coming back into camp,
the four of us have this plan to tell sue
and Genevieve about Sam.
And it doesn't really take
any time for sol to just shout out,
"so, we decided Sam."
- Yeah.
And everybody agreed
upon Sam to go home.
But, yeah, I think
if everyone's cool with Sam tonight,
we got numbers right now.
We all worked together last night.
Let's work together again tonight.
Everyone is happy with Sam going, but
unfortunately for everyone else.
I had a lot of downtime with sue.
And when I pitch the
idea of blindsiding sol,
sue is open to it on the condition
that I talk to Gabe.
He is the missing piece to this plan
going forward or not.
Yeah.
The reason Gabe is pivotal
to this plan is because.
Gabe has the numbers behind him.
All of the tukus will listen to him.
He's the one who will make this happen.
Okay.
And so, I think
I can use the conversation
from this morning
to my advantage because it allows me
to approach it in a way that he will be
extra receptive to.
Basically, the name
that was said... Was you.
So me and Genevieve
go on a walk together
and she tells me.
She goes, "hey, this morning,
sol and teeny were
throwing your name out."
My preference would
be... I would like - yeah.
To take out the, like, subtle threats.
Literally, no one is talking about sol.
And she said, "I think that
we should make a move
for sol tonight."
He's good with
everybody, and I think - no.
Him and teeny want to
play between gata and tuku.
No,
I-I think you're right.
There are dangerous
players I'm working with that
I need to be prepared to strike against
before they strike me. And
if sol is coming after me,
he's gonna regret that.
It'll burn my bridge with teeny,
which makes me more
vulnerable to you guys.
- And, yeah, yeah.
- But, like,
if he skates by a couple
more, like, it will be you,
it will be Kyle, and then it'll turn to me.
Yeah.
I think we could do this
but there are people
that I need to be on board.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Sol's been, like,
kind of working
everybody. Like, everybody
feels like sol is their bff.
Would you be okay writing sol's name?
I'm hearing from Genevieve
that sol's gonna go.
Sam's not even the target anymore.
Yeah.
Hey, I'll do whatever you guys say
as long as I stay around.
I'm just really hoping that
the rest of the tribe mates
that have votes are going
to side with me and decide
to keep me in this game
a day longer than sol.
Yeah. Yeah.
I am a planner, and this sol plan has.
"Genevieve mushaluk" written all over it.
But it's very complicated to pitch a plan
when you really have
no idea what ingredients
are going into your plan.
And how do you count the numbers
when four people are on a journey?
And will they all come back with a vote?
Will they come back with no votes?
And we need one more vote to do it.
So, it all depends
on what's coming back from the journey.
It is a game for the four of us to play
against one another in which three of us
will earn our vote back, and one of us
will be without a vote at tribal council.
So, the stakes are high.
This game is kind of
like building a house of cards.
We have to stack up these cards
and not knock over the tower.
We have to form triangles
on top of triangles on top of triangles.
And each card that you
put down feels high-stakes.
Got it?
Wow.
Seriously.
I knocked over the tower.
It all tumbled down,
and I lost my vote tonight.
- Back to camp we go.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Not a fan of losing my vote.
I like having some control in the game,
and I'm kind of opinionated
on who I want to have go home today.
I think a lot of people are on board
- with that right now.
- I agree.
I am, definitely.
If Kyle gets to the end,
he's just gonna be
absolutely hard to beat.
Kyle is a big challenge threat.
And I could see him winning
- all the way to the end, and, like...
- Yeah.
I really want it to be Kyle, but
without a vote, it's more
challenging for me to do so.
- All right. - Let's do it.
- All right. Let's go.
I don't have agency
regarding who goes home tonight,
and so, I'm worried.
Hey!
Welcome back!
No way.
Sam, Rachel, Caroline and Andy
all return from the journey.
And of course, Caroline's the person
who loses her vote.
And I needed Caroline's vote
'cause she was gonna
vote with us no matter what.
We basically had to
do, like, reverse jenga.
We had to build a tower,
and first one to knock
over the tower lost their vote.
The way the votes are
shaking out right now are me,
Kyle, Genevieve and
sue are gonna go sol.
And because Caroline
doesn't have her vote,
five is a majority tonight.
So, if we can get
one more vote, there's our five for sol.
The difficult part of this is
who else gets to know this is happening.
Hi. So, what are we discussing?
One of the stronger men going home.
Right. Yeah.
I am fully aware that lying to teeny
and voting out sol is going
to burn my bridge with teeny.
She is someone I have a complex
relationship with in this game.
I care deeply about her. I
believe she cares about me.
But I still think that this
is the right move for me.
Sol.
I was thinking that he can't...
We can't keep him for a long time.
I think that Genevieve is
feeling pretty froggy tonight.
I think she's ready to jump
and hop and make a big move.
But my current viewpoint
on how to use sol
is to really just kind of use
him for a couple more votes
and get rid of him.
And on the other hand,
whenever there's a really
exciting blindside in the works,
the last thing you want to be is,
you know, missing the boat on that.
Check back in with me and
I'm, like, if it's lined up, then...
- Then you'd do it?
- Yeah, that'll be fine.
Let me see if I can line this up.
As luck would have it, Andy told me
sol was also on his mind. Not for tonight.
But with a little encouragement,
Andy's also in on this plan for sol tonight.
And then the question Mark became
what about Sam and Rachel?
And I thought,
let's bring in Rachel and let's let
Rachel decide does
she want Sam in or out?
Okay.
I am now an underdog in this game.
And so, as much as I
owe sol for sending me the advantage,
I am genuinely torn.
But even more importantly,
I don't know if I should
let Sam in on the vote.
This tribal
is my opportunity to
show these new allies
that I am with them and
that they can count on me.
I want to, like, know what's happening.
I know. Hey, I can talk to you more later.
Just know that we are
still looking out for you.
I can't tell you who it
is. It's not you. It's not.
I feel very uneasy.
I've been a social pariah around here.
Like, nobody wants to talk to me.
Rachel is the only person in the game
that I believe I can genuinely trust,
and I... I need her right now.
So, I'm just gonna guess,
and you don't have to
confirm anything, obviously.
Yeah.
You're working with tuku.
You're blindsiding one of the lavo.
Yeah? Okay.
I want...
Please. Please don't
blow up my spot, okay?
I won't. I won't.
Okay. I won't.
I get the information from Rachel
that there is a plan in the works
to blindside sol.
And maybe I shouldn't blow
up her spot right after I tell her,
"hey, I'm not gonna blow up your spot,"
but I have to be able
to look out for myself.
And so, it's time to cause chaos.
It's time to blow this thing up.
Okay.
You're going home tonight.
- S... shut up.
- Let's go.
Are you serious?
I just found out two seconds ago.
Rachel.
She was like, "Sam, please
don't blow up my spot."
And that's exactly what I'm doing.
They're telling you it's
me, telling me it's Kyle,
and they're voting you out.
Me?! I'm going home tonight?!
My first reaction is panic.
But I work the best
when I'm at the bottom.
- And I promise you...
- Okay.
That if we don't do something,
- you're going home tonight.
- Okay.
You, me, Andy, Genevieve and teeny.
I want sue out of this game because
sue is probably the most insulated player
in this game.
I love you so much.
Not only does she have.
Caroline as a tight number one.
She's got Gabe and she's starting
to get inroads with
Andy, Rachel, Genevieve.
If I can get sue out,
it'll free up a lot more
players to work with,
and that's important to me at this point.
I think you blow up everybody's
game if you take out sue.
- All right. Sue.
- What's Caroline got to do?
- Sue.
- All right.
And Gabe can't... Nobody
on tuku can find out.
Okay.
My head is on the chopping block.
The sun's coming down.
I know tribal council is coming, and
I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
The vote was me tonight.
- What?
- Yup.
So, you, Genevieve, Andy,
Sam and I are voting sue.
Teeny, vote sue.
Okay.
My red flags just instantly go up.
I have heard nothing about this.
And sol's my number one ally
and best friend in this game.
So, my first instinct is,
we have to do something about it,
we have to save sol.
Lay it on me. What are you thinking?
I'm trying to take out sue tonight.
And if you vote with us, she's gone.
Who do you... Sue?
- Who do you got?
- It's me and lavo.
And I think if we take out sue... Yeah.
Tuku is no more.
Things have totally exploded.
I need people to make ballsy
moves with me in this game.
Sam is ready to make his big move.
He wants to gun for tuku.
Dude, this is an exciting day.
This is the best day yet.
But can I work with Sam again
and get rid of sol later on?
This is, like, very big
decisions that need to be made
in a really short amount of time,
because tribal is looming.
It's happening, like, very soon.
We're good.
What?
Unfortunately for me, my beautiful plan,
which was carefully laid out,
all the pieces were in place...
- It's...
- I don't really understand
how they could have
the numbers to do you.
I feel it
slipping through my fingers,
and have the panic of,
"no. Like, what if it is not sol?"
Yeah, yeah, so, it was rach...
They pulled Rachel in.
Sol is coming to me and teeny,
and teeny's getting
pulled in, and it is a mess.
Sue is the best target.
'Cause we were already
gonna do that. So it's not like...
- You guys want to do Kyle then?
- Yeah.
We're getting Kyle out.
It's Kyle. Will you please vote Kyle?
I saved you.
I'm pretty conflicted about what to do.
There's so much going on
and there's so much chaos.
It's starting to dawn on me
that I should have never
said anything to Sam.
Sol is just freaking out.
Once word spread that sol was getting
more paranoid, more paranoid,
we all changed all of our plans.
And we kept going
back and forth, jumping
from person to person
to person to person.
It's just a lot of running around,
it's a lot of craziness, and
I'm starting to sweat
a little bit on this one.
It's an absolute mess,
and the sun is setting,
and we do not have time for a mess.
- Yeah.
- This is nuts.
This is nuts, man.
Conversations are still live
about "what are we gonna do?"
Okay, is it go ahead with sol
or are we pivoting to
something else? If we're pivoting,
who are we pivoting to... sue or Kyle?
And the sun sets and it stops.
And those are the questions left.
And there are no
answers to those questions.
Now bring in the first member of our jury.
All right, so let's review today.
Three-stage challenge that ran in pairs,
but it ended up in a showdown
between Kyle and Gabe.
Gabe pulled it out.
Before we get into the details,
one of the things that I noticed was
this group camaraderie.
Lots of people hugging,
"congratulations, man. I gave it my best."
But at a certain point,
the reminder that it's
personal is going to take over.
So, Kyle, can you have both? Can you
have a group of people
congratulate each
other, and you mean it,
and then you immediately start thinking,
"but I'm taking you out,
and you have no idea"?
Yeah, Gabe and I were a
perfect example of that today
because, like, when Gabe was able
to pull off that w today, I
was genuinely proud of him.
I was happy for that.
But then, obviously, that
comes with repercussions
because that means that necklace
is no longer around my neck,
which means my
safety is not guaranteed.
But then there's the war at hand, where
we do have to face off, we do have
to start talking about what
we're going to do and-and
who needs to go home and why.
Genevieve, does it make it harder
to vote somebody out when you
have established a society
that says, "we're gonna
treat each other kindly,
even in defeat"?
I don't think so because
everyone sitting here
is... A fan of the game.
And so they can compartmentalize
the different aspects of the game.
And it doesn't feel good, but it's not
because we've decided to give
it our all and be a community.
It just doesn't feel
good for other reasons.
But for me, personally, I
saw my name on parchment
at the first tribal council I was at.
And that gave me, you know,
007 license to kill in this game
because that could have
been my last tribal council.
So, Sam, one of the elements of today
was four people lost votes.
You had a chance
to get 'em back. How did that go?
I was able to finally
earn my voting power back in the game
after feeling pretty helpless
for the last two tribal councils.
But, you know, Caroline
ended up losing her vote tonight.
So, Caroline, - you will not vote tonight?
No.
How impactful is that
with all the uncertainty
that's going on?
It's a really weird feeling
in that there's so
much chaos happening,
even just behind me
in this very moment and
leading up to tribal council.
And I want to know what's
happening, and I want
to be in the know, but it feels so bizarre
because I actually
can't do much about it.
I can share the knowledge
that I have and my opinions,
but at the end of the day, I
can't put pen to parchment.
Sue, something else I'm noticing
about tonight's tribal is from
the second you sat down,
there are tiny little
conversations happening.
Yeah. In my peripheral vision right now,
I can see conversations going on.
So, it-it's sort of freaking me out a little
that people are having
these conversations already
and we're still trying to
have conversations with you.
Sol, the chaos that
is happening right now
is this what it was like back at camp?
Yes. You know, you would like
to have a solid plan going in.
And there was just confusion
and then more confusion.
Bottom line, this game
means a lot to everybody,
so you want to make sure
that you're all on the same page.
And, it looked pretty chaotic, yeah.
- Andy, do you agree?
- Absolutely.
The chaos is happening right now
because we did not finish at camp.
I don't feel like there's a need to hide it.
It was explosive, this scramble today.
Pure disarray. No one's
feeling secure right now.
I think there are conversations
that still need to be had,
but we're sitting here
answering your questions,
and we're just trying to
deal with that right now.
And it's your tribal,
- so, I got some questions.
- Sure.
- You got some talking to do.
- Definitely.
- We got all night.
- You just want everyone
to shush? Except for
me, and I... let me whisper.
I want to get my whispers
in, and then no one else can.
That would make me
feel the most secure,
but that's not possible out here.
Teeny, survivor requires you to be
on point at any given
time, but this is very specific.
This is, "not sure what the plan is",
"not sure who I can trust. We only have
"a few minutes before we
vote, so I must..." What?
- Can you repeat the question?
- Yeah.
If there was one skill
that you could rely on
right now, what would it be?
Adaptability.
I mean, I've had different experiences
going to tribal council.
I've gone in confident and sure
and been blindsided
and absolutely wrong.
I've gone in confident and sure
and been right and
found people I could trust.
But tonight, it's completely unfamiliar
because I am going in absolutely unclear
of what I'm doing,
what the people who
I've talked to are doing.
And I think a lot of us
are feeling that way.
Genevieve, that's the fear.
You can never trust,
ultimately, if the last
conversation was the last one
you needed to have.
What I would say is,
good players are good at
deciphering new information,
I.e., my plan needs to change
from information that's just noise.
And so, I am going to stay the course.
And I think there are
other players out here
who want to make moves
and can also tell the difference
between news and noise.
Kyle, is this distracting,
this animated conversation?
Heck, yeah, it's distracting.
There's something about it that just,
is, like, tugging on my ear.
Every time I see somebody
lean over or do something,
all I want to do is, like,
climb in the middle of it
- and hear what's being said.
- Yeah.
Sol gonna join in.
So, Caroline, do you have
an idea of why there's chaos?
All I know is that chaos is beneficial
for people who are in bad spots.
If you're in a good spot,
and you have good "plaos"...
And you have a good plan,
chaos can just destroy you.
So I'm not a fan of chaos. I... yeah.
But again, I'm not voting,
so, I'll let the chaos happen.
But they can vote for you.
You know, that is true.
I do not like that.
But the thing is, we also have to think
about what are the other dynamics here.
And I love what Genevieve said.
The best survivor players
can tell signal from noise.
And I'm seeing a lot of noise right now.
Kyle, it's happening, it's real, it's alive.
This is a million-dollar vote.
Somebody's dream
will be squashed tonight.
This is it, man. The game is afoot.
It's happening right before your eyes
and right next to my ears.
I mean, this is what I signed up for.
I didn't know it was
gonna be this chaotic.
There's a lot of things to balance
when you have so many people.
It's not, "okay, I know"
"my two or three
people. Like, they're good.
"I know they're good
because I know them
"and I've been with them.
"I need six or seven people
to do what I need them to do
to move forward in my game."
And, I mean, this
makes it very unreliable.
It makes it shaky.
All right. I'm sorry.
All right, well, I said
that you will have as much
time to talk as you want.
I'm ready to vote. Are you all?
- Good.
- Good. Yeah.
All right. It is time to vote.
Sol, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it, now
would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Sol.
Sue. One vote sol, one vote sue.
Sol. Two votes sol, one vote sue.
Sol. That's three votes sol, one vote sue.
Sol. Four votes sol.
Ninth person voted out and
the second member of our jury:
Sol.
That's five. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
- Good game, guys.
- Good game, sol.
- Good luck, everybody.
- Good game, man.
Sol, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org
people see the charming Andy.
But I'm a smiling assassin.
Next time on survivor
I don't care who I have to burn.
I'm gonna get my
revenge and twist the knife
while I'm at it.
Hate him. I want to kill him.
I want to kill you, Kyle.
They got my ass. I'm gone.
I thought I had my troops rallied,
but, they were also in on it.
But this was a dream come true.
I'm completely humbled
by this experience, and now,
I get to be on the jury, and
so, it's not a loss for me, man.
- I'm-I'm good.
- This was just...
This was awesome, man.