Previously on Survivor...
This Rome guy's
playing really aggressive.
No. It's Survivor. I don't have to.
Really hard.
That's not a threat. That's an ultimatum.
And you best believe Rome's causing
a whole lot of ruckus.
We can agree
to play these amulets together,
and they would have the effect
of a hidden immunity idol.
Sierra really wants to keep Anika around.
I feel like a piece of crap.
I really want to keep Andy around.
So, we have to figure out what the heck
we're gonna do.
Fifth person voted out of Survivor 47:
Anika.
Who-who owned this?
- It was the three of us.
- Three votes.
The tribe has spoken.
Look,
Tribal Council sucks.
Not.
That was fun as hell.
That was blindside city.
Anika wanted me out since day two.
I wanted her out at the same time.
It was really exciting
because it just felt like
this big plan that really came together
exactly how I wanted it to go,
which is a new feeling for me out here.
I have flipped the script.
Rachel was feeling
so confident,
and now, ostensibly,
Rachel is on the bottom.
I first want to apologize that
you were left out of the vote
because I genuinely
feel connected to Ani,
and I know you do, too.
So, it's like, I don't want you to be
- upset with us.
- Yeah, I mean, obviously
I'm not mad, guys.
We're playing Survivor.
- Like, I get it.
- Well, I mean...
But I'm confused - Well, I
- why I was left out.
- Wait, wait, wait. I know. One-one
- I mean...
- I'm sorry for leaving you
- out of the vote, as well.
- I'm so sorry.
- That's not what we wanted to do.
- Because I
really, really, really want
to play the game with you.
- Yeah, so...
- Just for my part, like, I feel like
Anika was sort of a wedge between us.
I knew she wanted me out.
Yeah. I mean, she did
want you out from the start.
Yeah.
And I'm sorry for
putting your name down, Andy.
I thought that that was
the consensus vote, and I'm
I'm just trying to be
with the numbers and be safe,
and that's not a good excuse.
- And we can talk about it, but...
- We can talk, yeah.
I was absolutely taken aback
by tonight's vote.
It felt like a big betrayal,
and it's not a good reality
to be at the bottom of the tribe,
especially when you consider, like...
Wow, I really thought.
Andy was at the bottom
of the tribe for the last week,
and somehow I am the person
at the bottom of the tribe.
- This went about as good as it could have gone.
- Yeah.
It was clean, we didn't
break out the idol, so
I chose
not to play my hidden immunity idol.
Tonight was the last
Tribal Council it was good for,
and I didn't play it tonight
because Andy doesn't know
I have said idol,
and I didn't want to lose trust.
So, I chose to see
if I can use it further down the road
as a decoy or a fake
or something to just have some fun with.
Man, this game.
As soon as you think you have
a grasp of what's going on,
- it just flips you on your head.
- It just changes.
But tomorrow, maybe.
I know.
- Yeah.
- But it's, like, we can just start from zero.
Things change on a dime.
I've hit my rock-bottom game
at this point.
I need other pathways.
And so, I want more than anything
for merge to come, like, immediately.
I'm hoping for, like, a lifeline.
A boat?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- He's coming?
- Yeah, he's coming.
- My God. - God.
Thank you.
- It's not a journey.
Not a journey. Not a journey.
Please.
Yes!
The angels were singing
to me this morning
after the disaster that was last night.
Now I get
an entire beach
of new people waiting to help me
further myself in this game. Like, it is
the lifeline that I desperately need.
- Drop 'em.
- Drop 'em.!
And now I hope
that I can take the lessons
of being blindsided
and use that as rocket fuel
to get myself into this merge.
No.
"Drop your Buffs!"
My God!
Yeah!
- My God.
- Baby.
- My God! Wow.
Every Survivor player
wants to live to see the day
that it says, "Drop your Buffs."
And for me in particular,
this just feels like
a new lease on life
because I was so nervous
about my life in this game.
But at the same time,
I'm Buffless right now.
I don't have a home. I don't know
if I'm going to have a home.
But I'm certainly very excited
to go and find one.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Let's go, man. Let's get it.
My God!
- What the heck?!
- Come on.
I was somebody
who wanted to etch my legacy in stone.
I want to put my head on
the new-era Mount Rushmore
of Survivor.
And to do that,
you got to make the merge.
We're not quite
at the merge yet, but pre-merge,
in Survivor,
it's Survivor elementary school.
And the actual merge
is Survivor high school.
That's where the big dogs come out, and
I'm ready to graduate.
They're coming here?
- They're coming here.
- They're coming here. - What?!
When I heard that they were all
coming over, I'm like, "Shoot.
They're gonna look through our bags."
So that got me very paranoid
because I knew I needed to clean my idol
because it's covered in freakin' red paint.
The idol, when it came crashing down,
it was in a jar
of red paint.
It took me so long to clean up
the mess to begin with.
I just took
the idol and put it back
in the paint-filled tube.
But while I was scurrying at the water
while trying to rinse off any evidence of
my... crime,
I hear a boat.
Shoot.
Yeah!
We made it!
There is not enough words
to explain how excited I am.
We're finally getting a chance to be
in the same vicinity as one another.
It's amazing.
It's wonderful to finally meet.
And as I'm walking up the beach.
I see a sign.
Excuse me.
We have to read this!
My God.
"Read with all tribe mates together."
My God. What is it, Jeff?
Wow. Right now?
What?
This is nuts.
We all kind of take off, but there's just
endless forest. This place is massive.
It's impossible to search every tree,
every crack in the ocean.
Like, this is a needle in a haystack.
Look behind me.
There's 50 trees behind me
in just what you can see.
No, I-I was hoping you guys did.
I'm like, "Somebody needs
to have found it by now."
I ended up losing my vote
on the journey, and.
No-Vote Kyle feels a little
uncomfortable in the world, so,
of course an advantage
would be nice for me.
I want this advantage
very badly, but unfortunately,
the clue says "somewhere,"
and I have no internal compass,
so...
This is nice.
This should be a swimming spot.
- This water...
- What is the...
- What is the buoy?
I have no idea.
I think I've seen a couple
of those floating around.
You are.
- Yeah. Yes.
- Right.
Of course it's so important
to have an advantage
in that pivotal, pivotal challenge.
But you know what
we want to do right now?
We want to meet each other.
We want to get to know each other.
We don't want to go run around and, like,
sow paranoia right now.
So I've done Willy Wonka.
Which... Who were you? I did that, too.
- Mike Teavee.
- Me too!
Hey!
What, are you crazy?
- I'm 45, so...
- Right. I'm 42.
- We have to...
- You're 45, I'm 42.
- We look good for 45 and 42.
- Yeah, we do.
- We do.
- Right?
I don't want to put a target on my back
looking for this advantage, but
I want to look for that damn thing so bad.
Who isn't?
Like, what are we doing? We're chilling
at the camp right now?
There's an advantage out there.
What the hell, guys?
I get it. Time to build bonds,
but it's, like,
we got work to do.
We have to find it.
- We have to find it.
- Right?
I mean, that would be...
There's, like, red paint up here, too.
Has anybody looked over here yet?
What the hell is up with this paint?
Yeah, there's a lot of red.
Right here, too. Look.
We're at the water well.
Red, splattered paint everywhere.
It looks like a murder scene out here.
It's all over this area, though.
Whoa.
And then there's some, like,
pottery pieces
that are saturated red paint.
Here's another one.
What the heck?
That's interesting.
It starts feeling like a murder mystery.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah, gotcha. Thank you.
And then, Rome digs a little bit
and sees a huge
pot with a bunch of red paint.
That's shattered pottery.
With a bunch of red in there.
What the heck?
When I see that red paint,
my mind flashes to Sue
at their water well.
Did you fall?
I was playing with the machete.
I'm good. I just...
It's okay.
And I think.
Sue found the idol!
Sue is playing this game.
I am proud of Sue,
and I'm gonna keep her secret
no matter what.
Hi. You missed out on a fiasco.
There's a weird,
- like, red paint thing going on.
- What?
When I heard that
everyone found
this mysterious red paint,
my heart sunk.
No way.
Now I know I am busted.
I feel like a criminal
that they found a little piece of evidence,
and now the cops are coming
and I can hear the sirens
coming closer to me.
It looks like a crime scene.
- Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
- It really does.
And I had this panic inside.
But the smartest thing to do
is just keep my mouth shut
right now and see how it plays out.
Everyone's chilling, but I just can't let go
of this advantage concept, and I've got
one place in my mind
that I want to check.
I can't stop thinking
about this stupid buoy.
It's like this little bee in my bonnet
of, like, why is that out there?
It's probably nothing.
All of the Tukus would have checked this
if it was something.
But it stands out to me as something.
I'm going in the water.
I hate it. This is not gonna be it
and I'm gonna get eaten
by a shark just 'cause
it's bothering me in my head.
I get out there, and even
as I'm one foot away, I'm like,
"This is just a random buoy."
But as I'm, like, one inch away.
I see something is attached to it.
I'm like, "This can't be real."
My God. I never find
anything.
And now, I finally found something.
- Guys?
- Yay!
You found it?
- It was the buoy?!
- Yes.
Genevieve, it was the buoy?!
It was the buoy, Sam.
No way.
Sam was kicking himself,
'cause he's like,
"Yeah, we saw that buoy.
We said it was nothing."
Should have gone for a swim, Sam.
Boo.
So, what was the deal with the red paint?
- I have no idea.
- We don't know.
So now we know the paint
is something different.
- Someone's got something else.
- Boy.
- Let the games begin.
- Yeah.
A few days ago,
Caroline and I found Sue
covered in red stuff.
And immediately, my red flag
was raised, because I was
kind of confused as to what
she could have possibly done. But now
it's kind of starting to make sense to me.
Caroline figured it out.
I trust Caroline the most.
I feel that she'll keep my secret.
But the problem is I feel.
Tiyana knows, and
I see how she can flip-flop.
So she's always gonna be
that middle person
that I'm not gonna always trust.
And if I have to chop the head
of the snake off
I will, to protect myself.
- I wouldn't get rid of him.
- Okay.
Wow. You see that rainbow? Yeah.
Where?
- It's so random.
- Rainbow.
Good.
What I'm trying
to do right now in this game
is try and get as much
information as possible
because information is key.
And so, if you're able to trust someone
with some information,
that's massive in this game.
So last night, Kyle... me and him
while we're sitting there talking,
he'd let way too many names
fly out of his mouth.
He's sitting here saying
that Sam is the person
that he feels like
could win this game easily.
Then I asked him,
"Okay, if that's how you feel
about one of the guys"
"which lady
are you most threatened by?"
And he said, "Tiyana."
He also told me with Caroline and Sue,
they're not really good at challenges,
and they're not really doing
that well socially, either, so,
he's essentially writing them off already.
So what do I do with that information?
That's not true.
The more information
that I have like that,
the more I can warn the people that are
the targets of someone that,
"Hey, people are coming for you."
I'm not surprised that he's bashing me.
I mean, he wrote my name down.
And if people feel like
I'm the one
bringing them that information,
then I'm the one that they're
gonna want to keep around.
- Thank you for letting me know.
- Yeah.
After hearing that Kyle's still chirping
about me and Caroline,
my daggers are out again.
I want Kyle to be the first target.
I was talking with Kyle,
and pretty much he was telling me
the scarier thing
in the game right now is Sam.
- Really?
- Like, to him specifically. Yeah.
I asked him, "Okay, well, for the ladies",
who's the most threatening?"
And he said you.
What the ..., dude?
I'm just letting you know.
My mind immediately
goes racing because
Kyle is one of my closest allies.
Like, it wouldn't make any sense
for him to start throwing out my name.
That makes no sense to me.
I said it a million times.
I'm gonna play with my gut.
And once he told me that, my gut feeling
it wasn't a, "my gosh,
I'm nervous, and I am paranoid."
It was a, "That doesn't feel right."
Rome told me that
Kyle threw my name out there
- last night at the beach.
- Last night? That's wild.
Just so you guys both know,
this is what Rome does.
He, like...
Really?
- You think he would make that up to us?
- Yes.
- This is how he plays his game.
- It's good to know.
The thing about Rome is,
Rome just talks, talks, talks,
and it's crap, crap, crap.
So I needed
to make sure, like, "Hey,
whenever you're talking to Rome,
you got to fact-check this stuff."
True.
So, Rome told Tiyana that you said
she's the biggest threat in this game.
- My God. Really?
- Yeah.
Did you say anything? I mean, I'm not...
No. He told me that he thinks
Tiyana's the most dangerous girl
because she's able
to mingle with everybody.
Rome doesn't know how
to keep his mouth shut.
And he twisted up a bunch
of words that I told him early
this morning because I was trying
to have general conversation with him.
Damn, man. What a dick.
I am fired up, buddy.
I am feeling froggy as it gets at this point.
- You don't?
- No.
I'm still No-vote Kyle.
I'm a sitting duck.
- I'm gonna crush him.
- Yeah.
So, at this point in time,
all I have is my social skills.
I'm fixing
to squish him like a bug.
I'm just gonna throw it
out there for everybody.
Seriously.
I thought-I thought
I had a connection, and now.
- Wow.
- I find out that he's, like,
making it sound like I threw at you.
And I'm just like,
- "... that."
- Yeah, like,
- I'm chopping it immediately.
- Can I say something, Kyle?
He also, this morning
at the beach, told me
that you were bashing Caroline and I.
No. And see,
I didn't bash either one of you.
What I said was, you have, like,
a mother-daughter relationship.
Everybody knows I'm one of
the most honest dumb asses here.
- I believe you.
- Rome is now my number one hit.
I ain't never working with Rome.
He buried himself.
Like, the first opportunity
I get, Rome's outie.
Come on in!
Look at this. First time getting to see
everybody together.
We are in the individual portion
of this game.
All right, shall we get to it?
Yes. Let's go.
All right, well, typically,
this is the part of the game
where you compete
in a physically demanding,
emotionally challenging course
to determine
who will earn the merge meal,
who will earn the merge,
who will get their Buff,
who will be safe tonight at Tribal Council,
who will be vulnerable tonight
at Tribal Council.
Good news is we're still gonna do that.
But with a twist.
Here's how it works.
We're still gonna divide
into two teams of six.
The winning team will earn a meal,
but it is not a merge meal
because winning the first team challenge
does not earn you a spot in the merge.
For that, you will have
to work even harder.
The winning six will then
move on to a second challenge,
where you will compete
against each other.
- My gosh.
- For individual immunity,
and the winner of that challenge
will earn the individual
immunity necklace.
Wow.
- I love it.
- That person
will be safe tonight at Tribal Council.
That person will make the merge.
That person will get their Buff.
That will be the only person...
- Holy.
- Wow. Wow, wow, wow.
Who is safe tonight at Tribal Council.
One will be safe.
- 12 will not.
- Wow.
All right, there is one more twist.
Yesterday, an advantage
was planted at your camp.
- How did that go?
- It went well for me.
Great. Bring it over to me.
Good job, Genevieve.
- Thank you.
All right. So,
this advantage is a good one.
Tell you how it works.
Genevieve, you do not have to participate
- in this arduous team challenge.
- Yes.
Instead, you move directly to
the second individual challenge,
where you will have a one in seven shot
at winning this necklace.
You have also earned the food reward.
Thank you.
All right, let me walk you
through today's challenge.
For today's challenge, you're gonna race
through mud and wood shavings
until you reach a cage.
You'll then use a grappling hook
to retrieve a large bag
containing a ball.
You'll then work together to get
to the top of a very steep ramp
to the platform,
where two players will use that ball
and attempt to maneuver it
through a table maze.
The first team of six
to win earns the food
and the right to move on
to the next challenge.
The losing six... got nothing for you.
- Make sense?
- Yes, sir.
All right, we're gonna divide into teams.
Think we need to do something
different here, as well.
We've never done a schoolyard pick
in the new era,
so we're gonna do
a random draw for captains.
- Wow. - Boy.
- Here we go.
Biggest challenge of the season.
Come on, now.
All right, we have our two teams.
For Yellow, it is Sierra,
Rachel, Sam, Sue,
Kyle and Teeny.
For Blue, we have
Rome, Caroline,
Andy, Gabe,
Tiyana and Sol.
Genevieve with a nice, comfortable
spot to watch.
This is the first stage
of a two-stage challenge.
The winners of this group earn the food
and the right to move on
to the second stage,
where you will compete
for individual immunity.
Losers of this walk away empty-handed.
Here we go. Survivors ready?
Go! Start in pairs.
It's gonna be Sam and Kyle,
Andy and Tiyana.
You got to get through that mud
to your mat.
That is a low crawl.
You got to work on your belly
to get through and under.
It is tight.
Here goes Kyle. He's good.
Here comes Sam.
Go, Yellow!
Gonna be Sierra and Rachel
now in the mud.
Blue still working to get to the mat.
Andy taking a long time.
Go, Blue!
There's Sol and Rome in the mud
for Blue.
- Come on.
- You got to get to that mat.
You're good, Yellow!
Rome now taking a long time to get out.
You're good, Blue!
Let's go.
It is Sue and Teeny for Yellow,
Caroline and Gabe for Blue.
Come on, Gabe.
Once you get to that mat,
you go individually.
Here comes Sue. Here comes Caroline.
You're good, Blue, good, Yellow!
You go over
and then through the wood chips.
You got this, Sol.
Thataway, Kyle.
Kyle getting through that quickly.
There goes Sol for Blue.
- Get to the mat.
- Go, Kyle.
Go, Yellow!
Here comes Sam for Yellow.
Sol's got to get to that mat.
You're good. Go, Blue!
Here goes Andy.
Sam whipping through this.
Go, Yellow!
Andy working for Blue.
- Go, Blue!
- Yeah, Sierra!
Sierra moving through
that first obstacle quickly.
You're good, Yellow!
Here comes Tiyana for Blue.
Teeny working quickly.
You're good, Yellow.
It's gonna be Sue,
the last person for Yellow,
- Rome for Blue.
- There you go.
Sue's got to get to the mat.
You're good, Yellow! Move on!
Come on. Come on, Rome.
You're good, Blue. Move on.
At this stage of the challenge,
now you're removing jungle debris
to reveal a big bag
containing a ball.
And the two people up top
are using a grappling hook
to retrieve it.
Good job, you guys!
Yellow has their grappling hook
on the bag.
Now they got to get it up.
You're ready. You're ready. Go, go, go.
Help, help.
Blue has their grappling hook on the bag.
Now they got to get it up.
Grab the bag! Don't drop it!
You got to get it up and over.
Y'all got it.
- Sol holding it.
- One, two, three.
- Rome trying to pull it.
- One more!
- Heave!
- Sam bear-hugging it now,
trying to do it himself.
And he's done it!
You're good, Yellow! Go!
Good job!
Blue has it! You're good! Go!
Got to get everybody down
into your mats.
Slide. You need that bag.
Now you got to get all six players
and your bag to the next mat.
Yellow working together.
- Blue working together.
- Let's go.
You're good. Start untying.
Now you got to release that ball
- from the bag.
- It's open, it's open, it's open.
Wait, I see it, I see it, I see it.
Yellow has the ball.
Blue has their ball.
You're good. Go!
Yellow gonna take on the ramp.
Blue now gonna take on the ramp.
If you weren't tired already, this will do it.
Gabe not messing around.
Immediately gets up,
grabs the rope,
and he can now help people up.
Here goes Rome.
He's got the rope. There goes Kyle.
- There goes Tiyana for Blue.
- Help her!
Kyle gets up now for Yellow.
Teeny gives it a go.
It's not gonna happen.
That is a very steep ramp.
Tiyana falls back down.
Another attempt by Sierra.
You've got sandbags if you need 'em.
Sol is up for Blue.
Most difficult part
of this challenge is getting up
to the table maze.! So close, Sue!
Sue with another huge effort.
- Not a bad idea.
- Yellow now gonna go get their sandbags.
You can build a ladder
to help you get up higher,
but it takes a lot of energy
to drag those bags over.
There goes Tiyana.
She's got the rope!
Can she hang on?
Andy grabbing Tiyana's arm.
Sierra's up for Yellow.
Can you pull her all the way up?
Tiyana is up for Blue, and we're down
to one person left.
Here goes Caroline.
Close.
Yellow stacking sandbags
strategically.
You get that high enough,
you just reach up and grab that rope.
Gabe coming down.
Gonna give Caroline a hand.
Andy being held by Sol and Rome.
You got this! All you got!
There goes Caroline again.
And she's got it. Andy has her.
Andy is being held by everybody else.
This is a test
of trust right now.
Caroline is there.
Now it's up to Gabe.
He's already been up there once.
Gonna have to pull himself up again.
Blue now looking very good.
They can move on to the
table maze. Two tribe members.
Yellow's still working to get up.
- They are building a wall of sandbags.
- Pick it up?
- You-you... you let go.
- It's got to go this way.
Gabe and Rome
for Blue on the table maze.
Sue is up for Yellow!
Yellow's got some momentum now.
Here comes Teeny.
That strategy of sandbags is working.
Tiny bit from you.
Yeah. You, you, you, you.
Rachel's up and over now for Yellow.
Here comes Kyle.
This should be easy for Kyle.
He did it once.
Everybody's up for Yellow. You're in this.
It's gonna be Sam and Kyle
on the maze for Yellow.
It's Gabe and Rome for Blue.
Okay, not too hard, not too hard.
Slowly and touch.
Now it's gonna be all about touch
and working together.
Two people is
much more difficult than one.
One, you just worry about yourself.
Two, you got to worry about that
other idiot you're playing with.
- Guys!
- That was me. We're good, we're good, we're good.
You got to be subtle.
Tiny movements around those obstacles.
Okay. Chill, chill, chill.
- Blue is all over the place.
- Come on, guys, take your time.
Moving with crazy, jerky moves.
Rome, you're being... touch
is way too much right now.
Sol, Sol, we're good, brother.
I appreciate it, man.
- All right.
- We're good. We got this. Don't worry.
Sam and Kyle very steady.
They have not changed their
approach the entire challenge.
Blue making huge moves, - Guys.
Playing much more carefree.
Blue drops, and they're back to the start.
It is now Yellow in the lead.
You need to pick up on your side a little.
Gabe and Rome drop.
They've got to start again.
- Is there a swap-outs?
- No.
- Bro, relax, relax.
- All right. My bad.
Yellow, slow and steady,
getting closer to the center.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- There goes Blue again.
Aggressive out of the gate.
They've got a pattern.
They are quickly catching Yellow.
Sam and Kyle making more progress.
Blue trying to catch them.
Blue very close to catching Yellow.
Too close to call right now.
So once it goes this way,
- I'm-I'm pulling down.
- While Yellow is
taking their time talking,
Blue is now catching.
Now Blue in the lead.
This is very close. Both balls
in nearly the same spot.
Go!
Yellow's in the inner circle.
Blue is close to the inner circle.
Blue drops.
Yellow wins! That's it!
- Yeah!
- Wow, what a finish.
Within inches
of each other.
Defeat for Caroline, Tiyana,
Gabe, Rome,
Andy and Sol.
No food, no shot at immunity.
What a huge effort in stage one.
Wow.
All right, you six,
you're now gonna move on
to the second challenge.
Head down with me. You six,
take a spot on the bench,
we'll get this going.
This challenge was grueling,
and even though we won,
we have to continue, totally exhausted,
and compete for the first
individual immunity.
Survivor is tough.
All right.
You all are eating this afternoon.
Food is gonna be waiting
for you back at camp.
But all you care about right now
is winning this.
This is the second part
of earn-the-merge.
You win this,
you win individual immunity,
you are safe tonight at Tribal Council,
you will get a Buff,
which means you will be the first person
- of Survivor 47 to earn the merge.
- Wow.
The stakes are never higher.
Who knows what's gonna
happen this afternoon
with 13 people in the game?
All right, here's how it works.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna stand
on a very narrow beam
while balancing a ball on a wooden bow.
At regular intervals, you will
move farther down the beam,
making it more difficult.
If at any point you drop or your ball drops
you're out.
Last person left standing wins
individual immunity and
everything that comes with it.
Losers, you will join the other six,
going to Tribal Council
tonight vulnerable.
All right, everybody take
your spots, and we'll get it on.
Here we go.
All right.
Everybody's in your first position.
Place your ball on your bow.
Ooh.
- My gosh.
- Come on, baby.
Wait till everybody's good and centered,
and then I'm gonna call it.
All right, everybody is looking good,
and this challenge is on.
We'll be in this first section
for five minutes.
Genevieve, as fresh as you can be,
given it's day 12 of Survivor.
She is not covered in mud,
is not exhausted.
- That is the big advantage Genevieve has.
- Come on.
Sierra drops.
We are down to six.
Sam with a nice save.
Can he get it back?
One end to another.
No, Sam is out.
You can leave the ball, Sam.
Take a spot on the bench.
We are down to five.
Now it's Rachel with a little movement,
and a nice recovery by Rachel.
You cannot lose your concentration.
Whatever it takes
to keep your mind occupied,
- that's what you got to be doing.
- Back to the center.
If you get comfortable,
and you start to drift, so will that ball,
and before you know it,
you're out, you're on the bench.
15 seconds left.
Survive this, you move to the next stage
of this challenge.
Get a little more difficult.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
You can grab your ball. Everybody's safe.
Well done.
You will now move down.
Don't get off the beam.
You're gonna move now
down into the next section.
- So hot.
- This is more narrow.
- Scalding.
- It's gonna be a little more difficult.
Ooh. All right.
Everybody, place your ball.
Everybody looking good,
and this challenge is back on.
You're gonna be here for ten minutes,
twice as long as that first section.
Teeny with movement,
but a nice recovery.
It's tiny little moves to save that.
She's doing it.
Genevieve with a nice save.
Was nearly off the end,
and she pulled it back.
Rachel's ball on the move.
She cannot recover.
Rachel's out. We're down to four.
Genevieve's ball on the move
again. Can she recover again?
Genevieve cannot stop it this time.
Genevieve is out.
She earned the advantage
to get the shot.
Couldn't capitalize on it.
And we are down to three.
Kyle locked in.
Sue locked in.
Teeny locked in.
We got a challenge.
Little bit of movement by Sue.
Teeny, out of nowhere, drops.
She's out. We are down to two
Kyle versus Sue.
They're side by side,
and Sue's ball is on the move.
Just 30 seconds left in this round.
If you can survive this round,
you get to grab that ball,
and you get a fresh start.
Kyle's ball hasn't moved in a long time,
but neither had Teeny's until suddenly,
it dropped, and she was out.
That's how fast
this challenge will get you.
Sue with a lot of movement.
Can she hang on
for another ten seconds?
Five, four,
three, two, one.
You're both safe, you move on
to the final round. Nice job.
Amazing.
All right, Kyle and Sue,
move down to that final section.
One toe has to be touching the paint.
Balance your ball again.
Both of you look really good.
This challenge is back on.
This is it.
Final round, final section.
Sue, out of the gate, ball is on the move,
but a nice recovery.
Slow, steady moves is what it takes.
Nice.
Another nice save by Sue.
Wow.
Sue trying to get that ball
back under control.
She's doing a nice job
of little movements
to move it back toward the center.
Kyle with a lot of movement.
- Ooh.
- Sue with another nice save.
And another nice save.
Sue can't do it. Sue drops.
Kyle wins first individual community.
My moose, my baby boy.
Thank you.
Kyle safe tonight at Tribal Council,
first person to earn the merge Buff,
and will enjoy food this afternoon.
What a day.
- Slayer.
- Good job, Kyle!
Kyle, come on over.
Kyle!
Congratulations.
Thanks, bro.
First person to wear
the individual immunity necklace
from Survivor 47.
- It looks good on you.
- Thank you.
With this, you are safe tonight
at Tribal Council.
With this, your merge Buff...
go ahead and open it.
- Go, Kyle.
- This means
you are the first person
of Survivor 47 to earn the merge.
- Sick.
- Yay!
Look at that, man.
How does that feel?
You just went through a lot
to earn that Buff.
You know, Jeff, it feels really good.
And, anybody that
knows me out here understands that
I'm here for my family and my kids,
and when I give it, I give it a buck 20,
and I do it for my family.
Well done. All right, Kyle,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
the only person
who will be safe tonight at Tribal Council.
To complicate things
a little more, though,
Kyle, you, along with Genevieve,
Sam, Sierra,
Rachel, Sue and Teeny
you're all going to enjoy a meal
at a separate part of camp.
So you will be fueling your body
and you will be bonding,
while Gabe, Sol, Caroline,
Tiyana, Andy and Rome are
at another part of camp
wondering what is going on.
And later in the afternoon, you'll all
come together and start to talk.
All right, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
See you tonight at Tribal.
I am the first merged member.
Huge check mark on Survivor
bucket list. Thank you.
I'm really excited now that
I have my name off the table.
So everybody's gonna have
to do some scurrying around.
They're gonna have
to paint their own pictures.
And I have a pretty good idea
of who the picture's getting painted of.
When the pressure
of Tribal Council is looming
is when the great players shine.
Think that's you? Apply to be on Survivor.
My God!
Walking into the feast
is like.
Thanksgiving afternoon when Mom says,
"Food's ready,"
and the football game's about to kick off.
- Charcuterie! - Charcuterie.
- Look at. Charcuterie.
I've been craving charcuterie.
Since, like, day three
out here, I've been asking,
"Jeff, get me some meats and cheeses
to put into my belly, please."
And so, I see this big old platter
of salami and pepperoni and prosciutto
and every cheese that
I don't even know the name of,
but I know I want to eat it.
I know right away,
"You're gonna make yourself sick,
and you're okay with that."
Wait. Should I do my first pineapple?
- My first pineapple, Si?
-. Yes!
- Yes! - Let's go. Cheers.
- First pineapple ever.
- Cheers. Pineapple!
- Cheers to Pineapple.
Take a chug.
Breaking news. Sam's a pineapple guy.
After a few sips of wine,
I was almost impatient in
waiting for somebody to bring up
the fact that we have a vote tonight,
and we are all still vulnerable.
And even though we pulled out
this big win, it doesn't mean
that one of us might not
be going home tonight.
I know the big question,
million-dollar question.
- Are you guys saying Rome?
- I'm gonna go with the majority.
- I'll vote with everybody else.
- I'm voting majority. - Yeah.
- I want Rome to go tonight.
- I'll do Rome.
Sitting down at this merge
feast, there's only one hombre
with an immunity necklace,
and that he is me.
I don't have a vote tonight,
but Rome has got to go.
Dude's a rat, man. I...
You can't trust that... for nothing.
Okay, so are we all
in agreeance tonight?
- Yes.
I think everybody here
would be very happy
voting Rome tonight.
My concern is I would love it
if there was a second name.
- Yeah.
- Are you guys okay with Andy?
Even though Rome is, like,
everybody's, like, number one name
that they want to write down
at Tribal Council,
we do need to have a backup,
whether Rome has an idol,
whether he plays a Shot in the Dark.
Andy's somebody I've been working with,
but he's been sloppy
throughout this whole game.
So it's like,
"You know, sure."
Teeny, I can't have you
getting too drunk here.
You got to hold it together
- through Tribal for me.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna need, like, a buddy.
It's like every single crevice is
- covered in mud.
- A wild day.
Biggest Tribal Council ev...
Like, damn, that is, like,
an insane twist that he threw.
As opposed to years past
in the new era where,
you know, at this stage,
you only have six
or seven people vulnerable,
everybody except for Kyle,
who won individual immunity
we're all on the chopping block tonight.
I'm one of those people, so,
that's something that is both
exciting and scary.
- 'Cause...
- No, stay.
Every single person
on this island knows about it,
and every single person will know
- what we're doing tonight.
- Yeah.
This three-way,
shared amulet... it's something that
myself, Caroline and Teeny agreed
to take just because we didn't
all want to lose our votes
on that journey that we went on together.
And so, the best option is
to get these off of our hands,
play 'em in a public way,
and we do it tonight, and we go
into the merge with no targets
on our back.
I'm so happy with Rome.
I mean, I think everybody wants Rome...
- Right.
Earlier, at Lavo,
I was struggling with Rome.
I don't think
anyone has meditated out here
more than I have, and I've had
to do it because of Rome.
I have the biggest hermit crab
I've ever seen in my life.
- My God.
- I'm ready to eat.
He's a pain in my ass, so,
to finally, like, have a chance
to take out the Rome show
feels like Christmas morning.
What are you thinking for tonight?
My God.
I'm trying to think if it won't be Kyle...
The second that Kyle won
individual immunity,
I knew, "Okay, all the seeds
I've been planting about Kyle?"
"Ooh! They got to go out
the window, and I got
to come up with a new plan."
So guess who I want out the game?
I mean, there's only one person
that's been, like,
genuinely mean to me at different times
in this game, and that's Sol.
Sol. So guess what I used?
I used one little thing
that Sol said during the challenge today.
Did you hear him when, like,
- we dropped the ball twice?
- We were, like...
Did you hear him yell at me?
He tries to be encouraging
and all this stuff, but
he literally just makes me feel
like such a little person,
like, and it sucks.
Yeah. It's, like, such a... Yeah.
'Cause, like, I already, like, have
I already have, like,
self-esteem and, like,
pride issues with, like, myself
and, like, not being able
to do things and, like,
you know, things like that.
So when someone's, like, they're
not believing in me, clearly,
- it just... it sucks.
- It doesn't help. Yeah.
- I don't want to deal with it anymore.
- I know.
I might have shed a little crocodile tear
here, too, talking about my pride
and how...
how Sol's been demeaning me.
So, it was, like... it was rough.
I didn't want to deal with it.
- I don't want to play with people like this.
- Yeah.
You could tell Caroline and Tiyana
they were like, "man,
that's just not right."
And as long as I can keep
on playing on people's emotions,
I feel like I'll at least
be good to go for tonight.
Well, I mean, we were just trying
to hear where his head was at.
He said, "Well, the only person out here
who's been mean to me is Sol,
so, I'd like to vote for Sol."
That was it.
I do not like that Rome
is putting a target on my back.
But honestly, I expected it.
I mean, he's been trying to get me out
since our first Tribal Council.
Hello?
- Where are they?
- Yo.
The one thing, though,
that I have going for me
is that Rome's ego is gigantic.
And right now, everyone
is pumping that thing up,
and it's getting bigger
and bigger and bigger.
Can I give you, like, a big hug?
- Of course you can give me a hug.
- Good.
Tonight, you need seven votes
to get Sol out of the game. Kyle
does not have a vote tonight.
Dude, that immunity necklace is so cool.
I have a damn bat tattooed on my back.
There's also three amulets.
We don't know what those three
amulets are gonna be doing.
The only crazy thing that I can see
happening tonight is those
three amulets playing it on Sol.
But Caroline does not like Sol
at all right now.
I'm feeling, like, at peace with this vote.
So I do not see that happening
whatsoever.
It's a good feeling.
So, the big thing is is to get the people
that have the influence
down to vote out Sol.
Really?
Okay, sure. That's one plan.
Unbeknownst to Rome,
Rome is the other plan.
So right now, the plan is gonna be Sol.
Okay.
Hey, that's great, Rome.
You keep throwing Sol's name around.
Gonna be Sol tonight, so...
Yeah.
It's looking like it's gonna be Sol.
Okay. Is everyone on board?
I think I might be a little bit
of a mastermind right now, you know?
I got a plan in motion.
I've been setting the seeds.
Did you hear about it?
- What? Sol?
- Yeah.
The fact there's 13 people
in the game and I can
corral this many people to vote my way?
That must say a lot
about how I'm playing the game.
You guys all heard
the real plan?
- Yes. Okay.
- Perfect.
Yeah.
And I actually feel like
Rome is comfortable.
Yeah, I feel like he's comfortable, too.
They did a lot of work today.
We did. We friggin' babied him.
Thank you.
- I love you. Stop it.
- Thank you.
- Right.
- Thing is, does he have anything?
And if he does?
And if he does, we need something else.
- I appreciate this.
- Yeah.
Rome's coming.
Tonight is about
sending a message to Sol,
letting him know
that I won the war.
Everyone's voting Rome,
and then Sol is voting Andy.
It's all good. I'm gonna be
feasting on Sol's bones tonight.
I got a big old smile
on my face because it's feeling
like everything's gonna be rolling my way.
Okay. Cool.
Man, like, I am running this game.
This ain't even Magic versus Larry.
This is Michael Jordan versus.
Kirk Hinrich, all right? This is
this is not even a competition
right now, all right?
I'm playing this game
on a whole 'nother level.
I'm on Survivor, baby, and
I'm leading a mastermind vote
at a potential historic
Tribal Council. It might be
a Rome game or a home game,
and, Sol,
I'm sorry, it might be
a home game for you, buddy.
Wow.
There are so many torches here.
It's reflecting parts of Tribal Council
I haven't even seen until tonight.
All right, so let's talk about the twists.
Only one person is safe
at the merge vote.
Andy, what did you see this afternoon?
'Cause I'm guessing everybody thought
it's a lot more dangerous.
Yeah. I mean, there's just this insecurity,
a little bit. There's just, like...
You just want to be safe. You want
that pretty, pretty purple Buff.
Everyone wants that.
And so, we're all trying
to portray that we are trustworthy,
we're a good number.
And so, everyone's
playing this little tango,
and it's fun to be a part of,
- but it's scary.
- And Rome,
you got this big group of people, so,
you're trying to get to know each other,
but you're also watching other people
watching you, trying
to get to know each other.
Well, it's only been,
you know, a little over
24 hours that everyone's
been on the same beach
and been able to get used to each other.
So, right here, you got to
really build trust very quickly.
And I think the big thing today is just
don't ruffle feathers. If you hear a plan,
"All right, I guess that's the plan."
Kyle, what did you notice in terms of
the scrambling, given that
you're the only one
with the purple Buff,
so you had no stress today?
I wouldn't say "no stress."
Just sitting back, I can see
that many individuals
walk off off together,
and it happened so frequently, I think
a lot of people are trying to fact-check
to make sure that there wasn't a bunch
of phony baloney getting tossed around
of this twisted-up conundrum that
we've created on a beach.
Sol, what kind of conversations
did you have today?
Well, even going back to yesterday,
like, there was an advantage out there,
and we all looked for, like,
one minute, and then
- we all came back, and it was, like...
- For one minute?!
I mean, it was... it was surprising, like...
- Pretty much.
- There's a few people
that were concerned we were
gonna let you down, Jeff.
Taking notes, but not let down.
So, Rome, is it possible
advantages are starting
to be seen as disadvantages?
Well, the amulet is for sure
seemed like a disadvantage.
That's why the people with the amulets
tonight are gonna be
getting rid of it
and getting it out of the game,
- because...
- My heart is breaking.
So, you don't think
that's a good advantage?
- No, they... I'm...
- School me.
Maybe you should be sitting here.
If you want to trade for tonight, I
Rome, come over and sit here.
Tell the group... and I will listen
why the Amulet Advantage is not good.
All right, so,
we've got an Amulet Advantage
out there right now.
We know that three people
have the amulet. They all went
on a journey together.
Usually when you go on journeys,
when you come back, you tell
your whole tribe
what happened. So everyone knows who
has the amulets right now.
And everyone knows that the
amulet by itself has no power.
You have to use it together
- with the other two people.
- I mean...
So, the only options is,
target the other two people
so that you have all the power
with the amulet,
or say, "I don't want
to be one of the two targets."
"Let me just go ahead and
get rid of this thing right now.
"We'll use it together.
- "That way we don't have a target on our back."
- Wow.
And I think that, as a group,
sums up the Amulet Advantage
right now in the game.
Well done. Well done.
Get back over there.
- Wow.
- That was great.
- That was better said than...
- Duly noted.
Thank you. That was awesome,
being able to sit there.
You know, like, I love hosting,
I love commentating, and
you literally have my dream job,
so the fact
I even got to do that for 30
seconds right there, that just
made the...
That meant the world to me, man.
Seriously, I'm about to cry.
Like, that was...
- Really?
- Yeah, seriously.
Like, that was... that was a lot.
I appreciate it. Thank you, man.
Well, I don't want to make light of it
because I know this is a great job.
I have the best job
I'll ever have in my life.
Rome, I know. And I hope
you're not coming for it, even though
I'd love to be your protg
one day, man. I'd love it.
- All right, for now, we'll stick to playing.
- Yeah.
And I'm-I'm glad we had that.
We'll talk later. Yeah.
All right. Gabe, let's talk about
the deliciousness of a blindside,
because everybody here
has been involved
in a blindside this season,
either as one of the architects
or as somebody who was
on the wrong side of it
- and survived it.
- Well,
an interesting word that you used
in that question was "architect," right?
When it comes to blindsides,
it's not important
for me to be the architect
of a blindside, necessarily.
What's important to me is
that I know where the votes are going.
Rome, where do you stand
on blindsides?
I think blindsides are really only fun
when you're in on the vote.
When you witness it and you weren't
part of the blindside, you can
feel blindsided yourself.
Andy, how about for you?
Blindsiding Anika was fun as hell, dude.
It was super fun.
It was the most fun I've had
out here because, you know,
my name's been in her mouth
since day one, since day two.
And so, to see her shock, it just shows
it was a job well done.
All right. So, Caroline,
tonight's vote is big
because you want to make the merge.
Why is that significant?
When I am watching the show,
and you hear
the confessionals of people
talking about the merge,
everyone says,
"This is where the game starts.
"This is where you separate okay players
from great players."
And the stakes are so high
'cause we're all
itching and craving
and wanting that experience.
Andy, you were nodding.
Every single day out here is a lesson,
is a gift, is its own adventure.
I don't want to minimize that experience
if I lose out tonight.
But when you think about
the legacy of Survivor,
you're like, "I'm a pre-merger."
Like, that's your identity.
And so, you want
to be known as someone who
made an impact in this game,
and it starts tonight.
And if you just miss out,
you're going to feel the FOMO.
All right, well,
one thing seems very clear to me.
Tonight's vote is gonna be
great news for 12 people
devastating for one person.
Hot take.
It is time to vote. Andy, you're up.
Come on, now. Don't ever
put my name out like that.
They say Rome wasn't built in a day,
but your game
sure was destroyed in one.
I think everybody has finally caughten up
to the way that I feel about you.
Man.
I just don't want Sol on the jury,
'cause I know he'd never vote for me.
Dude can't stand me, so,
Sol, I know it's already
gonna be you tonight,
so I'm gonna shake things up a bit.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time
to do so.
Jeff?
I have one I'd like to play.
Other people as well?
- Yes.
- Wonderful.
Would you like to be
our spokesperson?
Sure. All right.
Assuming everyone
who has an amulet agrees,
I would love to play my amulet for Teeny.
- Agreed.
- Yes.
All right.
Yeah, I can't say "no" to that.
Plot twist.
Thank you.
These are the three amulets
that, when played together
for the same person, do form an idol.
Any votes cast for Teeny will not count.
I'll read the votes.
Sam.
Andy. One vote Sam, one vote Andy.
Andy. That's two votes Andy,
one vote Sam.
Rome.
That's two votes Andy,
one vote Sam, one vote Rome.
Rome. We're tied. Two votes Andy,
two votes Rome, one vote Sam.
Rome. That's three votes Rome,
two votes Andy,
one vote Sam.
Rome. That's four votes Rome,
two votes Andy, one vote Sam.
Rome. That's five votes Rome,
Sixth person voted out
of Survivor 47: Rome.
That's six, that's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
- Good game, you guys.
- Sorry, Rome.
- Good game, man. - Good game, Rome.
- Sorry. Good game.
Just want to say thank you guys
all for the experience.
It was awesome getting
to play with you all.
Got to live out a dream.
I got to sit in your seat.
It's all love for all you guys.
You guys don't got
to worry about nothing.
I appreciate you all, man.
Thank you.
Rome, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
- Can I get a hug?
- Course.
Aw.
You got it.
All right, you guys, all love,
man. I appreciate you all.
I have something for you.
Congratulations.
You have made the merge.
Pass it around,
pass it around. Take a Buff
and put it on.
Guys, let's go.
It's gorgeous.
It smells really good.
- We made the merge, guys.
- We made it.
- Yes!
- Wow.
- Congratulations.
Now grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
The game continues.
- Come on.
- Good night.
- Good night, Jeff.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org.
I need to take control. If they're gonna
come for me, I need to get them first.
Next time on Survivor...
We're going to eat all the men.
Of course.
These people are just
tools for me to use.
No one knows
what I'm about to pull.
Well, I got blindsided and, you know,
I-I should have seen it coming,
but at the end of the day,
that's my only regret.
Didn't make the merge, but, I mean,
I got to sit in Jeff's seat
at a legendary Tribal Council.
I played super hard, and...
You know, I might have
I might have ruffled
a few feathers here and there,
but hopefully, I brought
a little bit of entertainment.