Can I hit a dance for
the people back at home?
Hey!
Previously on survivor... Sol.
In this game, I am a planner.
And this sol plan has.
"Genevieve mushaluk" written all over it.
Okay, I won't.
S... shut up.
I should have never
said anything to Sam.
- What?
- Yeah.
Voting out sol
is going to burn my bridge with teeny.
Ninth person voted out
and second member of our jury: Sol.
The tribe has spoken.
No, I'm sorry, 'cause you were so close,
so close to accomplishing the goal
of making me look stupid for no reason.
I... Am devastated that sol went home.
And Genevieve is actually the one
who orchestrated sol's
blindside to begin with.
And I only found this out from Andy
during tribal council.
Of course I do. Of course I obviously do.
But, like, give me a second.
I'm just pissed off.
I don't want to be treated like an idiot.
Once again, I'm back
in this position like I am
when kishan went home,
where Genevieve has just
completely blindsided me.
I've never been more left out or confused
or completely in the dark
on what was going on.
And that is the worst feeling
you can have in this game,
is not knowing what's going on
and being blindsided by
your closest alliance member
and having to then blindside
your other closest alliance member.
I cannot honestly believe
that you would not
include me on the plan.
Like, I can't. Like, it actually just
speaks volumes to how
you see me, and, like,
I'm... hurt.
I have wanted sol out for so long.
- And that's...
- And the only reason
I didn't do it earlier was because
of my emotional connection with you.
He was not good for
my game, teeny, at all.
That's why I don't want
emotional connections
with everybody because I
already feel so beholden to you.
And when I see you
crying, like, I genuinely regret
what was a good, right move for me.
I knew there would be
fallout from the sol vote.
The fallout's name is teeny.
But I did not anticipate the fallout being
teeny feeling like it
was intentionally done
to humiliate her.
And I try very hard not
to have any emotional connections
to people in this game because
it makes it harder to play.
And when you... Hurt someone
and see them so distressed
and know that is entirely your fault
doesn't feel like a fun game anymore.
Sorry.
Our relationship
- is, like...
- I know. I just...
So... complicated.
- We're so different.
- I know.
'Cause I'm, like,
"everyone's telling me
the truth all the time."
And I'm like, "my closest
person is lying to me."
Like, that's... that's...
I'm never lying to you.
I know, but at some point, you will,
and you will have to for your own game.
Teeny and I had very honest discussion,
and we both kind of acknowledged
there's an end coming for us,
and it's not sharing a million dollars.
Okay.
I don't know if I believe Genevieve.
I'm playing this game
with so much emotion,
which was my biggest
fear coming in here,
and I don't know how to switch it off.
Honestly, my head is in a swirl, and
after this tribal council,
I truly don't know how
to pivot in this game.
- Dude, it's okay, teeny.
- It wasn't a good night.
It was not a good night.
And you didn't freak out. You cried.
You didn't, like, scream at people and...
And I did snap at Genevieve, but...
Well, I think she knew
you were gonna be mad.
Yeah.
How did things go last
night, from your perspective?
Unfortunately,
everyone knows I'm behind the sol vote,
including teeny, who is
holding it against me, personally.
So, that is why I need
to be careful today, because
tallest blade of grass gets cut,
and I grew a lot yesterday.
What do you want to do now?
What do you think?
And so now, there's
four relatively strong tuku.
And so, I think today,
everyone's gonna be eyes on the four,
'cause we'd like to get it down to three.
How are things this morning?
Genevieve was just here.
She says she's down for
splitting up Kyle and Gabe.
Okay, but Genevieve scares me.
You know, it's kind of funny because
I was someone with zero options
on day three, but now,
strategically, I feel like
I'm in a very interesting
place in this game.
She's-she's scary.
- She's good.
- What I'm observing
is a bit of a power shift.
In early gata, when I
was truly on the bottom,
Sam had all the power over me.
But this time,
there's just a different dynamic right now.
I'm like a slithering snake, I feel like.
I am in the middle, and I'm
whispering different things
in people's ears.
I would be very excited
to work with you, Kyle.
Same with you.
There's an expression I like.
It's called "loyal to the soil."
Once I'm loyal,
it just goes all the way down to the soil.
Yeah, I like that. That's good.
- Whatever I do...
- It's... tonight...
Yeah.
Right now, I'm like a
pendulum, swinging this way
and swinging that way, and what
I really try to do is play
people off each other because
I'm in so many conversations right now.
How do you feel about Genevieve?
She's a silent assassin.
And then she was also floating,
"we have to look out for Rachel."
Yeah.
Okay. Yeah, I don't.
I've been looking for an ally
in this game for a long time,
and it's pretty ironic that
it all comes back to going with Andy.
I think we're all, like,
pretty safe right now.
- We're all pretty safe. Yeah.
- In the grand scheme
- of, like, threats.
- Yeah.
We've had a rocky road, but I think.
Andy's kind of my guy right now.
- Andy, we're doing it.
- We're doing it. This is fun.
- We're playing survivor.
- I know. I'm down.
What's happening?
I'm a smiling assassin.
Like, I feel like I have ice in my veins,
but, you know, people don't see that.
People see the charming Andy,
and that really is my greatest strength.
I've built a web of different alliances
that no one really sees
the full picture except for me.
And it's very sticky, and
everyone's caught up in it.
And, you know, all I got
to do is crawl over here
and decide, you know,
who my next victim is,
bite their head off and crawl over here
and decide who my
next victim is after that.
I'm a lethal player in this game.
Come on in.
Final nine.
Forty-seven seasons.
Let me do some quick math.
Carry the one. That's a lot.
That's a lot of seasons of survivor.
All right, let's get to
today's reward challenge.
For today's challenge, you're gonna be
randomly divided into
three teams of three.
Each player will have
their feet tied together,
their arms tied to their side.
You're gonna slither through the sand
as you move a ball with your head.
- What?
- My god.
Once all three players are at the finish,
each player is responsible
for rolling one ball
onto their target.
The first three to finish win reward.
Want to know what you're playing for?
The winning three will
be taken to the sanctuary,
- where good things happen.
- Where good things happen.
For an afternoon of delicious food.
You'll have wraps... veggie and chicken.
You'll have salad.
- My god.
- You'll have fruit.
You'll have juices, you'll have iced tea.
And for dessert, cake.
Want to know what kind of cake?
Yeah.
Cookies and cream.
Come on, now. Worth playing for?
All right, we're gonna draw
for teams, and we'll get started.
All right, we have our three teams.
In yellow, Genevieve, sue and teeny.
In red, we have Andy,
Caroline and Gabe.
And in blue, we have
Kyle, Rachel and Sam.
Here we go. For reward.
Survivors ready?
Go! Got to drop to your knees.
- It's one person at a time.
- Yeah. Attaboy.
You're using your hands
and your belly to move.
Yeah, Andy!
You're using your head...
- You're doing good, Andy.
- To move the ball.
Kyle off to a quick start.
Yeah.
Kyle squirming through that sand.
- Yeah, Kyle, nudge it, nudge it.
- Yeah.
Kyle out to an early lead.
- Kyle is over the second mound now
with the ball.
His mound is gonna be lower.
Andy trying to get over that first mound.
- Genevieve is almost there.
- You're doing great.
- You got it, Genevieve.
You're at the top.
Okay, breathe for a minute, Genevieve.
- You got it.
- Genevieve has that ball
over the first mound.
Andy now using his
entire face to move the ball.
- There goes Andy.
- He's over that first mound.
Now you're getting it.
- Blue is good.
- Kyle, you're good! Go!
- Go, rach.
- Rachel out for blue now.
Kyle, you can take off those shackles.
Yeah, rach. You're killing it.
Genevieve at the top of the second.
So is Andy. Andy's now figuring it out.
Rachel is gaining on
both Andy and Genevieve.
Yeah, Rachel. Your feet.
Andy now over the second mound.
Here goes Genevieve. She's got
that ball over the second mound.
Now she's got to get her body.
- Yes, good job, Genevieve.
- Use your head.
Here comes Rachel
now, really using her body.
Hang in.
Attagirl. Keep that ball.
Andy's got it now.
He's got a nice rhythm going.
Nice, Andy.
You're good, red. Go!
Here comes Caroline.
Here comes Genevieve
for yellow, but right now,
Rachel has lapped her.
Caroline working on that first section.
- There you go, Caroline.
- Nice and easy.
You're good, Rachel! Go, blue!
Here goes Sam for blue,
third and final person.
Genevieve, slowly but
surely inching closer.
You're good, yellow. Go!
Sue onto the course for yellow.
Good job, sue. Good job, sue. Good job.
Caroline with a nice headbutt.
- She's got the ball over.
- There you go.
Sam has his ball over.
There it is, Sam.
Sam is working through that sand.
It is blue with a big lead right now.
Sam. It is brute force
moving through that sand.
- Sanctuary on the line.
- Here comes Caroline.
- There you go.
- Get those legs involved.
There you go.
Sue working it now with her head.
That's how you do it, sue!
- Blue is good.
- You're good, blue.
Take off, Sam. Start working on it.
Thanks.
Two on the mat, one on the ball.
It's gonna be Rachel first
for blue with a big lead.
Stage two of this reward challenge.
You got to find the touch
to roll that ball and stick it.
Rachel, close.
Good job, rach.
Caroline, you got your ball there.
Yeah. One more push. One more push.
You're good! Go, red!
Here goes Gabe for red.
Sue, you're almost there.
You're good, yellow! Go, teeny!
Yes, teeny. Yes!
It's teeny and Gabe
now out on the court.
Rachel close. Here
comes teeny and Gabe.
Gabe is working very
fast, trying to make up
- a lot of time for red.
- Go!
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Rachel sticks
the first one for blue.
Here comes Kyle.
They've got a big lead.
There are three balls to
land. They have landed one.
- My gosh.
- Kyle short.
Now you got to wait
for that ball to roll back.
Gabe is working very fast,
trying to make up a lot of time for red.
That's it. My god.
Kyle in and out with that second.
Gabe is whipping through this course.
He could give red a shot at this.
Icy, Kyle.
Kyle in and out with the second.
- That's the right touch, buddy.
- Blue has only landed one ball.
Gabe is moving very fast.
Nobody got through this
course faster than Gabe.
You are a good, red! Untie him.
Wow, what a comeback by Gabe.
Yeah. Yeah!
- Yes!
- Kyle lands the second.
It would be a massive comeback for red.
Here it is for Sam for the win.
One ball left for blue.
Red trying to get in it.
And it won't matter.
With one toss, Sam sticks the third ball.
That was insane.
A Valiant comeback effort by red.
They will not get a shot.
This challenge is over.
Wow.
My god.
Sam, Kyle, Rachel, you
pulled it out. Nice job.
Here's what's in store.
You're gonna leave here
and head to the sanctuary.
Nice afternoon of food,
different environment.
Food is fuel for your body and your soul.
Food is also a chance to bond.
Grab your stuff, head
out. Enjoy the sanctuary.
Good job, guys.
- Well earned.
- One of the more difficult
survivor challenges.
Everybody else, got nothing for you.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
I feel like I've been on
a losing streak, and so,
to get a win is
a nice confidence booster
for me to just say like,
"hey, you can still do this."
And now I'm gonna have a full belly
and gonna have some time
to maybe talk some strategy as well.
Buddy.
All right, guys.
My god. Cheers.
- Cheers to the sand. The sand babes.
- Good job.
Yes. We were eating sand.
Now we're eating food.
For winning the challenge,
we were rewarded with the sanctuary.
So, right away,
we just start going ham on the food.
I mean, you can put social
hour on hold because we're just
gonna start stuffing face holes.
You guys, this is so good.
Everybody get some rice?
- There's plenty.
- My god.
I'm in heaven.
I'm just so excited. I
see the giant bowl of rice.
Like, I mean, come on.
In survivor, you're supposed to eat rice.
I haven't had any rice
yet. You know, I tried.
I put it in my pocket,
but I didn't get any, so...
Like, it's amazing to just feel nourished.
- Any fruits here - you've never had?
- Basically,
- all of these.
- My god, Sam.
- We're gonna do a taste test.
- I don't know.
- What is this?
- That's kiwi.
Okay, I haven't had kiwi.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Cheers. My first kiwi.
Okay.
Good work, Sam.
Pineapple over kiwi for me.
I'm bringing that cake up.
- Do it.
- Yeah, I'm ready for cake.
My god. That looks so good.
- That looks amazing.
- I needed this really bad.
Feels like forever since
something's, like, gone my way.
And been, like... Like, gotten, like, a win.
So this... this is a big
pick-me-up, for sure.
Yeah, it's tough.
Yeah, I think that the script
is gonna get flipped here real soon.
- You think?
- Well,
I think it's pretty obvious
to many people that
if there's somebody to be weary of...
Talking about Gabe?
I'm thinking so.
I know that it's just a
matter of time before,
like, he strikes me or I strike him.
I love Gabe to death,
but out here in the world
where we have to
play for a million dollars,
it's every man for himself right now.
And with my reputation rapidly growing
in this game as a physical competitor,
it's kind of hard to trust in
the alliances you have because
you never know when they're
gonna try to cut you short.
I really, really am flexible at this point.
I'm just... I'm looking for people.
I'm looking for people. Like, I don't want
to just be strung along
for votes and stuff.
This is a prime
opportunity for me right now.
I need to be able
to make a move on Gabe
before he makes a move on me.
And Sam and Rachel
are the perfect candidates
to start stirring that pot.
If-if we can orchestrate a move.
I think people are sketched
out by tuku a little bit right now.
Well, then maybe it's time
for me to really jump ship.
I would love, love, love to
get Gabe out of this game.
He's somebody who is
a massive strategic force.
And it doesn't hurt that he
was part of the reason why
Sierra and I got split up.
Get my revenge a little bit
and twist the knife while I'm at it.
If Gabe wins, he's out of
the question completely.
If Gabe wins, what do we do?
Because if Gabe wins, Kyle,
a lot of people are gonna
want to write your name down.
Yeah.
So then, do we take Genevieve out next?
If we can't get Gabe,
that might be the move.
Genevieve... she
definitely has a mindset of,
"this is a game and I don't care who
"I have to burn." But
Gabe is not somebody
who I think we can get later.
Because if we don't get
Gabe, he's gonna get us.
Clearly, these two boys.
Kyle and Sam... want Gabe out.
And I think a lot of people
in this game feel that way.
But if I could vote anybody out next,
I would like to vote out Genevieve.
I think that she, out of everyone,
is the most, like, onto me.
And so, I think it's just
me trying to figure out,
is that my next best step?
- Talk to me without Kyle here.
- Yeah.
Is any of what you're
saying... for his sake?
- No.
- Okay.
Rachel, I want to play
the game with you. Like...
Can you explain to me a little, like...
Okay, I do, too, and I...
- I-I will air all my cards out for you.
- I just feel like
last night, I told you not to blow my spot.
You immediately went to sol. Like,
those things aren't helping me trust you.
I get that. Here's the thing.
To me, you're the only person
that I owe loyalty to in the game.
And so, what I'm hoping
is that we can get a tuku out.
Right.
And then, we can go
after, like, Genevieve,
and we can start knocking people out.
Now I think there's more room
for you and I to actually play together.
I agree. I agree.
Sam and I were able to really
have it out during this reward,
but I feel like every opportunity
that I give Sam to not lie to me
or screw me over in
some way, he still does.
So, I'm open to hearing
the plans. I want to know
what they want to do,
you know, at the next tribal.
But I'm also not sure if I'll actually
go with them or not.
So, the way that I'm playing this game,
I'm looking for opportunities
to build bonds on all
different sides of the fence.
And my next move, I
want to go, across the aisle
and build a really good relationship
with someone on tuku.
- Sue, sue, sue, sue.
- I'd love to hear what your thoughts are,
'cause I think you're
probably a genius at this.
Sue, I've been thinking
very hard about it.
Okay.
- I think we could sit at the end together.
- We could.
I don't want to just
vote with you anymore.
Like, I feel like I look at
you, I see, like, a partner.
- Right.
- Like, in crime.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Like, a partner in this game.
Like, I really want to work
really, really closely with you.
Okay. So let's do it.
- Let's absolutely do it.
- Okay.
Sue is
the exact player that I
want to have with me,
because she plays this
game with her emotions
and how she feels about someone.
And I know that when it comes to Kyle,
there's sort of beef
- with sue.
- I want to kill him.
That's why I don't even
listen when he talks.
I'm like, "I want to kill you, Kyle."
- He is a liar.
- Yeah.
He does the "poor me," the "woe is me."
How many times do we
have to hear that he's poor?
"I'm a good guy. I'm a dad. I'm a this."
He's so hypocritical.
Done.
The sooner Kyle is cut,
the-the happier I'll be.
I will give him back his
name on a parchment.
He wrote my name down.
- Exactly.
- He didn't feel bad.
Like, I can't even look at Kyle.
I hate him.
Because he wrote my name down.
He wrote my name down.
'Cause he wrote my name down.
So, Kyle... he...
He calls you and Caroline
tweedledee and tweedledum.
- Really?
- He does, yeah.
- Okay.
- I didn't think that was very nice.
No, not nice at all.
"Tweedleydee"
and "tweedleydum." Do you want to
I want to be like, "you, you."
I cannot wait to write that name down.
- We need to get rid of Kyle when we can.
- Yeah.
Feel like it's a good three
to have gone together.
I'm curious what
they're gonna talk about.
- Me too.
- And I'm hoping Rachel will tell us.
- I know.
- Yeah.
I think she will.
Obviously, they're pitching
one of us. It's not like
they're pitching one of each other.
Yeah.
I worry about Kyle sometimes
when it comes to me.
When it comes to you?
- Yeah.
- Really?
I mean, we've just gotten,
like, personally, pretty close
over the past few days,
and if there was
somebody who was gonna
be in position to pull one over my eyes,
I think it'd be Kyle.
Nobody's beating Kyle.
It's just not happening.
No. I'm sorry to tell you all.
If he is there, I will vote for him.
I'm starting to have to reconcile
with the fact that Kyle
might have to leave this
game earlier than I'd like him to.
I-It's tough because, on a strategic level,
I know how Kyle's gonna
vote every single vote.
A-At least I think I do.
And so, I'd like to keep that
for as long as I can. But I have to
weigh the benefits of
having Kyle in this game
and the negatives of having
four tukus that intimidate
a lot of people. And of all four of 'em,
Kyle's gonna be the easiest sell.
Yeah. I think you're right.
- Hello, hello.
- Hello.
We have returned.
My game plan coming
back to camp is I need to find
whoever else is feeling like
they're at the bottom and start to,
one at a time, assemble an army.
- There's some stuff in the works. Like...
- Okay, cool.
- Let me hear it.
- I would like to get Gabe.
And if the five of us
outcasts form a little alliance,
we have a little bit of power.
I think I've established a little bit of trust,
maybe, with Andy and teeny
to potentially work together.
I might burn 'em tomorrow.
In fact, I probably will. So,
they can't trust me, but I want 'em to.
There's a lot of people
that are really trying
to find footing in the game.
Why don't we find footing together?
- Yeah.
- Like... Absolutely.
I never thought I'd say it,
but I'm interested in working with Sam.
I think
Sam kind of finds himself
in a similar position as me.
He's lost somebody he's super
close to. He's been blindsided.
And right now, I'm trying to latch
on to anything that's available
because it is beyond overdue
for a vote to go my way.
- Let's do it.
- I like that.
I like it a lot.
But I don't want to be too trusting,
because my attachments
to people in this game have been
a kryptonite for me.
This character started in
- a book. - The grinch.
- That's the only good one.
It's the grinch!
- I really like that game.
- Yeah.
I am having a survivor low.
I feel like I am sort of in mourning of
my relationship with Genevieve.
Like, I feel like what we went through
was almost just, like, a breakup for us.
Because I really wanted
to play in lockstep with her. And realizing
she doesn't view me like that
in this game is... devastating.
And it messes with my self-esteem,
and it's really just throwing me for a loop.
And I feel like a lot of it,
what's coming out is, like,
stuff with my identity that
I haven't fully sorted out.
In my real world,
I do distract myself by
being with my friends
and being super social
and feeling like I'm well-liked.
And it takes away from the insecurities
I feel in my own skin
a lot of the time, and...
Throughout my life,
I've worked through
a lot of identity issues.
I've discovered my sexuality,
I've come out of the closet.
But I feel I've landed at a
place right now in my life
where I don't know exactly how I fit in
in a sort of man-and-woman,
binary world.
I feel like I'm dealing with a lot
of very personal inner-world issues
and trying to mask them
for the sake of my game.
And it's getting harder
because I'm losing
people who I care about.
And people who I thought
I could trust, I can't trust
anymore. So I just feel really alone
in processing myself in this game
and my place in this world and who I am.
But then, all of a sudden,
I see the entire side of my bag
is just embers and flames.
What the heck?
The bag that carries my life
in this game and all of my items
now looks like this.
I feel like this is just another
cherry on top of the mess that
my game feels like right now.
I've been kicked while
I'm down, but it does light
another fire under my ass
to get this game moving
in the direction I want it,
and... I think it's a sign
of a new life in this game for me.
Come on in.
Day 18.
Nine players left.
Yup.
All right.
Shall we get into it?
First things first, Gabe.
Got to take back the necklace.
Thank you.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
Now, yesterday, you
squirmed like a worm
for a shot at reward.
Today you're gonna
have to be more sloth-like.
Because today, you're
gonna be balancing a ball
on a wooden disc.
At regular intervals, we'll add more balls,
making it more difficult.
While you're balancing
those balls on the disc,
you're gonna be
balancing your entire body
on a tiny little piece of wood.
You know the drill. You fall off,
ball drops, you're out.
But if you outlast everybody else,
you win immunity,
guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
Losers, tribal council,
where somebody will be
the tenth person voted out
and become the third
member of our jury.
There's one more element
to today's challenge.
It's been 18 days without any rice.
That can all change.
- That's a bag of rice.
- My gosh.
Enough to get you to the end.
This is the rice negotiation.
I need four people
to sit out in exchange for rice.
This is always a reflection
of where the game is,
because on the surface,
the easy deal is four
people agree to sit out.
You agree, "tonight,
we won't vote you out.
We'll all have rice."
That's not how survivor works.
No, it's never that easy, and,
you know, it'd be great if
four people felt safe enough
that they could sit out, but I don't think
that's where the game is right now.
I think everybody's still very on edge and
very much wanting that necklace
a little bit more than the rice.
Is that true? Anybody instantly say,
"I'd consider sitting out for rice"?
Push it to three?
No. The set price is four.
What if two of us gave
up our shots in the dark?
No.
What if you got all the shots in the dark?
All the shots in the dark?
- Every shot in the dark - down the line.
- Wow.
Everybody here willing to
give up your shot in the dark
on only day 18?
- I would do that.
I don't have one.
I would do it if everyone else does it.
I-I... I just want to make sure
you're thinking clearly,
because this is a massive sacrifice
from where I sit over here.
The shot in the dark is your last gasp,
your hail Mary, your one last chance.
I'll do it if everyone does.
- I'll do it if everyone does it.
- Okay, I'm not gonna say no.
- I'm thinking.
- What's that?
- Sam,
walk me through the
reason you're reluctant.
Yeah, I mean, I'm on the bottom.
I-I've been on the bottom, and
it's easy for the people on the top to say,
"I don't need my shot in the dark."
But when you feel like that
might be your only other chance
at surviving in this game, that rice
I can go eat rice after I get voted out.
Your vote is more powerful
than that shot in the dark.
Your vote is how you
get out of the bottom
by giving people your vote.
I've been offering my vote.
- Nobody's wanted to take it.
- And you're still here.
They've been trying to
leave me out of the vote.
You're still here
because you have a vote.
And if you want to lean
on your challenge aptitude,
that rice is gonna help it.
If you feel like you're on the bottom,
that rice is more valuable
to win an immunity necklace
then get a one-in-shot
chance at immunity.
You reconsidering or
you locking in, Sam?
I'm not... I'm not gonna
keep rice from the group.
So, Gabe persuaded you?
- Sure. - Okay.
- Thank you, Sam.
- All right, let me just
make sure I have this right.
Everybody who has a
shot in the dark is prepared
to give it to me right now?
- Yes.
I'll make that deal.
- Okay.
- Get your shot in the darks.
Be very interesting to
see if this comes back
and have a little second guess
- at some point.
- I don't have one, Jeff.
- Nice.
- Yeah, this worked out really well
for Rachel.
- Sorry, guys.
- Yeah, right?
If you're all willing to give it up,
I'll take 'em.
Can't believe I proposed
something that you were in on.
I know. Survivor history here.
Survivor history for sure.
Thank you.
All the shot in the darks
in exchange for one bag of
rice waiting for you back at camp.
Well done.
All right.
Let's get into this. Made a little history.
I got Sam to give up his shot in the dark
so that I can eat rice today.
So now I know for a
fact there's gonna be no
"hail Mary toss-up, this person's safe."
It was a very good thing for me.
All right, let's do it.
I never saw this negotiation coming.
Every player gave up
their shot in the dark
in exchange for a bag of rice.
If you have clever ideas like
that, apply to be on survivor.
All right, everybody grab one ball.
Step up on your perch.
You're gonna place one ball on that disc
and when everybody's
good, this challenge starts.
Everybody looking good.
And this challenge... Is on.
The game has just changed
because you all agreed
to give up your shot in the dark
in exchange for rice.
So, now immunity is really important
because you got nothing else
other than some kind
of advantage or idol.
Could have a big impact
in these final days of season 47.
Here comes the wind.
That will change everything.
Instantly, Caroline feels the impact.
A little bit of a breeze.
Another big gust of wind.
Andy with a little
movement. Nice recovery.
That ball wants to roll.
Once it starts rolling, it's hard to stop it.
And the wind is gone.
Once again, it is calm.
You've got 15 seconds
left in this first stage,
and then we will add another ball.
Ten seconds.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Grab your ball. Everybody's safe.
You are good for a moment.
Take a second. Then we're gonna
grab a second ball.
All right, everybody grab a second ball.
It's gonna get a little more difficult.
I'll give everybody a clean start
and then we're back on.
Everybody remove your hands.
And this challenge is back on.
We've got ten minutes in this round.
It just got a whole lot
harder with two balls.
And if they start going
in opposite directions,
it's even more difficult.
- Man.
- Caroline drops.
She's first out. Take a spot on the bench.
No shot at immunity.
Here comes the wind.
Andy can't navigate the wind.
Andy is out. We're down to seven.
Just like that,
less than a minute into this round,
we lose two players.
That wind will come up out of nowhere.
Another big gust of
wind moving Sam's balls.
Rachel teetering on disaster.
Both balls at opposite ends of the disc.
Rachel can't navigate that.
Rachel's out.
We're down to six.
Genevieve drops. She's out.
We're down to five.
Gabe drops. We're down to four.
This is it.
A potentially million-dollar game
with a ball on a piece of wood.
Ten seconds left in this round.
Five, four, three, two, one.
You are all good. Grab your balls.
Take a moment. We'll move on
- and add another ball.
- That was really well done.
Well done.
Everybody grab your third ball.
This is gonna be a lot more difficult.
We're gonna place your
hand over the three balls.
I'm gonna call you in
and we're gonna go.
Here we go. In three, two, one.
Move your hand.
This challenge is back on.
- Teeny drops out of nowhere.
- Teeny.
Teeny's out. We're down to three.
On one end, Kyle.
He's won it three times.
On the other end,
sue. She's won it once.
In the middle, Sam. He has not won it.
And here comes the wind.
Sue, for the first time
in a long time, with a
little bit of movement.
Kyle now has a little bit of movement.
Sam drops. We have a showdown.
Kyle versus sue.
Here comes the wind.
Welcome to survivor.
Sue's balls are on the move.
This is a battle.
Now Kyle's balls are starting to move.
Sue again with movement,
and another nice recovery.
Here comes more wind.
Now Kyle's balls are starting to move.
Sue drops. It's over.
Kyle wins his fourth individual immunity.
- Safe tonight at tribal council.
- Baby girl, baby boy.
What a showdown
between Kyle and sue.
- Wow!
- Good job, Kyle.
That was so impressive.
Thanks.
Nice work, Kyle.
- Thanks, teeny.
- Good job, dude.
- Damn, Kyle.
- Yeah.
It just starts to hurt after a little while.
- Yeah. - Thank you.
- Yeah.
Kyle, come on over.
Good job, Kyle.
- Once again... - Yes, sir.
- Immunity is yours.
This is your fourth
individual immunity win.
There are
an elite group of players
who have won it five times.
- Geez.
- What is that feeling?
Nobody could really
expect to do this well,
even though you dream
that it might happen.
Growing up, I never really
took first place seats in anything.
All I can say is that I'm
really proud of myself
and I'm really proud of
the people back home
that give me the drive
to want to hit a buck 20
every time I come out here.
All right, well done, Kyle.
You are safe tonight,
cannot be voted out,
guaranteed a spot in the final eight.
As for the rest of you,
tribal council tonight,
where somebody will be
the tenth person voted out
and become the third
member of our jury.
Grab your stuff, head back to camp.
I'll see you tonight at tribal council.
- Way to go. Congrats.
- Thank you, sir.
Boy.
Getting that immunity necklace
around my neck was
so important to me today
because I've been trying to get Kyle out.
So, Kyle big-time saved himself, but
I can't cry over it.
And now, unfortunately,
we need to figure out the next target.
That was fun.
Kyle, good job again, man.
All right, let's get some
food in them bellies.
Let's feed the family.
I did not want to give up
my shot in the dark for rice.
I kind of know where I stand in the tribe.
I know that my name is one
that is frequently tossed around
as somebody who could go,
but I feel cautiously optimistic
about my place in the
game because I've started
to sort of get the ball rolling
on this alliance that I'm hoping
can really take control of the game.
If we can get Gabe tonight, that's great.
Getting Gabe out tonight
puts the control in our hands.
- I think so, too.
- And then we can decide.
I feel like the margins
are really tight right now.
- We need a tuku out.
- No, I agree with you.
Gabe is such a threat in this game
because he is the leader of tuku,
and once you get Gabe,
you kind of blow up this tuku alliance.
I also think that Gabe
would throw Genevieve's
name out there.
I'm, like, it's so tempting for
me, because, like, I'm like
- I know. I want...
- Dude, I want her out, too.
It is such a delicious option to think
of Genevieve walking out
the door right now and knowing
that she will not have the chance
to pull something over on me again.
And we just can't let her...
- Like, do her poison again.
- I know!
But I know there's people
on board to get Gabe out,
so I know the timing
is not right right now.
I know we need to get Gabe out first,
and that's what I'm sticking to.
She's playing really hard.
- She scares me, dude.
- She got that sol vote.
I think she's got an adrenaline
kick from that sol vote.
- She's ready to keep it going.
- Exactly.
Tonight, I want
Genevieve out of the game.
Genevieve put a huge target on her back
when she made that sol move.
- She is smart. She is...
- That's what I'm saying, dude.
And she's been really
down-low this entire game.
- Yeah.
- And then she emerged for that sol vote.
- She's scary.
- She emerged too early.
Right now, I feel the best
I've ever felt in this game.
Yeah.
With nine people left in the game,
we have four tukus left:
Me, Kyle, Caroline and sue.
And we need five votes for a majority.
We got the numbers, and as long
as there's no funny business
with idols or advantages,
I'm making it to eight with three
other tukus. And the fact that the fellow
players around me have allowed this
to happen is mind-blowing.
This is it. This is...
On day three, we... dreamed of this.
And it's going to be you,
me and sue as the final three.
Gabe is a close
alliance member of mine.
And while I love
the honesty I have with Gabe
and I love our relationship
with the track record right
now of the merge votes,
he's played a better game than me.
So, while Genevieve is a big threat,
I'm starting to feel like if I vote out Gabe
it means that I can really start my game.
This will get me in trouble.
Please, please, please
- don't say anything about it.
- I won't. I won't.
I'm getting quite worried about Gabe.
Our opportunities to get
him out are narrowing.
Yeah.
And while Genevieve
is a threat right now...
Yeah.
So, I think the numbers are there.
I want to collaborate with you.
And now that Kyle has won,
Gabe is an even bigger target.
I know.
But you will?
Things are opening up now, but
I'm still not entirely sure
when is the best time to get out Gabe.
Because targeting
Gabe means targeting sue
and betraying her trust
and potentially destroying our alliance.
I actually think we're in
an incredibly good position.
- Okay.
- Incredibly good position.
And my alliance with
sue is so important to me.
So, I'm still figuring out exactly
what the right move to do is here,
'cause it could ruin me in this game.
My only fear about doing Gabe right now.
Like, once Gabe's gone,
who is everyone else looking at now?
Everybody is so hell-bent
on cutting Gabe because
he's just such a big threat.
But I do think that Genevieve
going before Gabe would be better
for my game because
everyone will still have their eyes
locked on Gabe after that,
and no one will be
looking at little old Rachel.
And I think Kyle would be on board
to keep Gabe for, like,
another vote if we wanted.
Interesting.
And so,
I would love to, like,
convince a player like Kyle
to go after someone like Genevieve
because if Gabe goes,
he's next, full stop.
So...
Do you want to vote Gabe or
do you want to vote Genevieve?
The only reason why, and in my gut,
I feel like I shouldn't
vote Gabe, is because
he's the only, like, bigger threat than me.
- That's what I feel like.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So, I'm really nervous
that if Gabe does go home,
I'm going to become
public enemy number one.
Right.
I really struggled for, like, a while
to get any footing, but I think that
the position that I'm finally
in right now is the position
that I always wanted to be in.
- What would you rather do?
- I'd rather do Genevieve.
I just want the votes to go
the way I want them to go.
You know, I came into
the game saying that,
like, I don't want to be the captain,
I want to be the ocean.
Like, I want to just, like, turn
the ship in a direction I want.
I don't need to be
holding the steering wheel.
But I'd prefer Genevieve
goes home next.
- They'd be in here?
- Ooh!
- Rice.
- We're gonna eat, baby.
- Rice. Rice.
- We're gonna eat.
- A sack.
- Amazing.
It's the best rice I've ever had in my life.
Soon as I ate the rice, I was like,
"I want my shot in the dark back."
Because now I'm worried.
I am the most worried for myself.
Coming off the sol blindside
and, like, the fallout with teeny,
like, I'm truly eating this
rice around camp being like,
"last meal on the beach."
Like... and it gets to you.
Tonight, I have
the least amount of
confidence I've had in the game.
It's gonna be me or Gabe tonight.
Right. Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's gonna be Gabe.
Yeah.
People are telling me
they agree on Gabe.
Don't fully believe it, but
I'm just really hoping people see Gabe
as a bigger threat than me.
What do you think's
gonna happen tonight?
It's gonna be you or Genevieve.
Sue and Caroline aren't going me.
They-they will not go me.
Like, and all we can do is put
Genevieve's name down tonight.
I've been the decoy for
a lot of votes this season,
but today, I have a lot of paranoia.
I feel like my threat level is sky-high.
- Okay.
- And somebody... I'm not saying you,
but somebody has my name out there.
Okay, okay. Okay, okay.
I know that Genevieve
wants it to be me tonight.
Everyone... it seems like
everyone is avoiding me
and talking to you.
No one is dying to talk to me today,
and maybe that's because
- I'm not gonna be here tomorrow.
- The two biggest targets
right now are you and me.
I have no idea where the alliances are.
Like, our merged tribe is
such a hodgepodge mess.
There is the tuku four,
and then everybody else
is just a random group
of people who have lied to each other,
been on the wrong side of votes,
been on the right side
of votes, and it's, like
anybody's guess.
If tonight's vote goes
the way that we want it to
and Genevieve is gone, this game
is going to be in the palm of my hand.
For me, this tribal
council is about survival.
If I can make it through this one...
And if I can get through the night
the game will be wide open tomorrow.
I think I got it.
And now bring in the
members of our jury.
All right.
So, I want to understand something.
We've talked a lot this season
about this idea of community.
Teeny, one thing that
was never clear to me
is what is the criteria
for being one of the people
that gets asked to be in the community?
I think, in the beginning, when
it was someone like Rome,
who was very outwardly predictable,
the criteria was more, "just don't do that."
Just don't be that extra about everything
that you're doing in this game.
And with Sierra and sol
gone, I feel like a lot of
plans were made for each person.
After Sierra, we'll do this person.
After sol, we'll do this person.
But what I'm noticing is
there's not a lot of consistency in that.
So, I'm about just as
confused as you are
in terms of what the criteria is.
Sam, is the idea of
community ebbing and flowing
or are you trying to conform?
I don't think it's ebbing and flowing.
I just think we're getting to
the point in the game where
people's criteria of their community
is different from everybody else's.
Like, the criteria is shifting
depending on who you ask.
And I think that's kind of why
we each have our own plan for
how we want the game to unfold.
Gabe, what I'm hearing tonight is,
"well, we decide, but none of us
really agree. It shifts every day."
Well, survivor is a game that
you build a community that
is destined to be torn apart.
You put work into building a community,
and then you have to put in
maybe more work into tearing it apart.
It's a hard thing to do.
Let's talk about today's rice negotiation.
Because, on one hand, I was
impressed that you came up
with an offer that I thought was
so good I couldn't pass it up.
But what I'm struck by,
Andy, is that in agreeing
to give up all of your shots in the dark,
you all agreed to make it easier
to vote every single
person out of this game.
Yeah, the shot in the dark is
most useful to disrupt what would
otherwise be an easy vote.
- Exactly.
- And that was
very symbolic in terms of we all agreed
on how we're going to
- sort of play the rest of this game.
- Sam,
I'm curious about what
Andy said. "We all agreed."
That's not what I saw.
- Yeah. - And I'm hearing laughs.
- Eventually.
Eventually, - Probst: I felt like
Gabe certainly was persuading
or cajoling, even you,
into doing this, but maybe
that was just my observation.
Yeah. I mean, it's no secret that I wasn't
fully on board with giving
up my shot in the dark.
I think it all depends on, like,
your position within the game.
And ultimately, what it came down
to me was, like, this is still a community,
and it's still a social game.
It's not worth taking rice away
from eight other people
that I'm living with.
There are just hills that
aren't worth dying on.
Teeny, it was a little bit, though,
on theme in that it was about
conformity to the community.
There was one person
who said, "I don't know."
And everybody else said, "what
do you mean you don't know?"
"We're gonna do this." So Sam said,
- "okay."
- yeah.
Absolutely. It all goes back to adaptability.
Like, you know, Sam
advocating for the fact
that he wanted his shot in the dark
could have the exact
opposite effect than he wanted
in trying to keep himself safe,
and actually puts a
target on his back because
he's fighting for the one
thing the rest of us agree on.
But it kind of just opens
up the battlefield a bit more.
Gabe, what's the criteria
right now for tonight's vote?
I think people are
starting to think about who
they want to sit at the end with.
I think beforehand, it was,
"let's build the community
we want," and then it was,
"let's get rid of some chaotic characters."
And now it's, "let's figure out
who I want to sit with at the end."
What do you think it is, Sam?
What's the criteria for
this group in terms of
who you want to get
rid of and who you want
- to go deeper?
- Yeah. I mean,
right now, I don't know
if there's really a clear line of, like,
"these are the people that I
can take to the end and beat."
And I think that's going
to be what decides
what happens tonight and probably
what happens moving forward.
Rachel, agree with
that, that we are looking
for the biggest target,
and like any good player,
we got to take 'em out when we can?
I mean, I don't think
that Sierra and sol
would be sitting over there
if we were voting out the
weakest people on this tribe.
So, yeah, obviously, people
are looking to vote out people
that they're scared of.
Andy, if you're voting out the people
who are the biggest threats,
then you got to decide on
what's the criteria for what is
- the biggest threat tonight.
- That's the big question.
I feel like, yeah, the mentality
on this tribe right now is
we're going threat-hunting.
You know, everyone is looking
for who they want to sit
with at the end, but I think
that people want to defeat
the big threats here on the
battlefield of tribal council
before the final tribal council.
Caroline, do you agree with that?
Absolutely.
There's a lot of different
ways to view threats.
Sometimes a threat is just someone
who doesn't want to work with you.
Sometimes a threat is the
person who will prevent you
from getting to be where you want to be
and could throw out my
position in the community.
For me, I find that to be a huge threat,
and that's personally what I
am thinking about a lot right now.
Genevieve, do you get that sense,
as the day is unfolding, that you can tell
when something's just a little off?
Yeah. I'm not sure
if it was information or
misinformation, but, like,
people who were talking to me yesterday
were talking to me less today
and then reassuring me.
And that's where you just
check in with your people
and hope that they would
give you an honest heads up
if your name was out there. But
yeah, I missed my shot
in the dark this afternoon.
So you're really second-guessing that.
Yeah, but I'm always paranoid.
And now I think I just feel,
like, a little less confident
without it. I didn't realize
what I had until it was gone.
- Sam, what'd you sense today?
- Today was
the first day that I
think I started to feel like
part of the community again.
And so, it made me feel good.
But the last time I felt
good, I felt really, really bad
- immediately after.
- Yeah.
Gabe, why are you laughing?
What is it about that that is
so enjoyable to hear or relate to?
It just sums up the game so well,
in so few words,
of, you can feel really,
really good, and then
feel really, really bad immediately after.
But then there's the flip side
of it, too, where you can feel
really, really bad, and then
something just happened,
and you feel really, really good again.
I mean, we're getting to the point
where those emotional swings
are just so intense sometimes,
and it's tough to deal with. It really is.
All right, it is time to vote.
Sue, you're up.
If you play an idol, I'm toast.
Even if you don't play
an idol, I might be toast.
So it's been a crappy day.
You're the biggest threat out here,
and we would be fools to
not do this while we can.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
Gabe.
Genevieve.
- One vote Genevieve.
- Crap.
Genevieve. That's two votes Genevieve.
Gabe. We're tied.
Two votes Gabe, two votes Genevieve.
Gabe.
That's three votes Gabe,
two votes Genevieve.
Gabe.
That's four votes Gabe,
two votes Genevieve.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member Gabe.
That's five. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
- Good game, everybody.
- Good game, bud.
- Good game, Gabe.
Gabe, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Grab your torches. Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored
by CBS and Toyota.
Captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
I don't trust anybody.
A family man is a dangerous
person to have in the endgame.
Next time on survivor... Anything can
and often does happen.
No way.
I think Rachel's got
something up her sleeve.
Now I have the power.
I'm in a crushing position in this game.
I felt really good about my
chances to make it to the end.
It was just a matter of, was
I gonna get through nine?
I didn't get through nine.
But I forged the exact relationships
that I wanted to forge.
I never woke up saying,
"what am I doing?"
I never went to sleep saying,
"god, I really messed up today."
So I did everything and played
as hard as I wanted to play,
and I got a good feeling, like, I'll be back.