My god! Yeah!
Hey, hey, hey, let's go!
Previously on survivor
I'm just letting you know.
- Thank you for letting me know.
- Yeah.
I think I might be a little bit
of a mastermind right now, you know?
Rome just talks, talks, talks,
and it's crap, crap, crap.
Rome is now, in case
anybody wants to know,
my number one hit.
First opportunity, Rome's outie.
Everybody here would be very happy
voting Rome tonight.
I would love it if there
was a second name.
- Yeah.
- Are you guys okay with Andy?
If it's Andy, it's Andy.
Yeah.
Andy.
Sixth person voted out
of survivor 47: Rome.
The tribe has spoken.
Yes, congrats.
Yay.
Right now, I am feeling
so, so, so, so good about
what happened at tribal council.
Rome, my biggest source
of paranoia and stress in this game,
was collectively voted out.
And not only is the amulet advantage
out of my hands.
It was also played on me
so that I didn't even have
a chance of going home.
- Congrats. All right?
- Congrats.
But beyond that, sol
is the only known person
who wrote Andy's name down,
and he needs to do some
damage control, because
obviously, Andy's
gonna be upset with that.
I did not want to do that.
I promise you with all my heart,
- I did not want to do that, okay?
- Yeah.
I genuinely believed Rome had an idol.
- Right.
- I really did.
- Okay?
- Yes.
And if he puts my name down...
- And everyone is on Rome...
- Yeah. - I'm gone.
Okay, so you're very confident - yeah.
That he has an idol
and he's gonna play it.
Right.
That means you're very confident
that you're sending me home.
Well... Of everyone on god's green earth,
- right.
- You chose me.
Right.
- Why?
- Okay.
Me voting for Andy
gives me some work to do.
I knew there was a chance
that Andy would still be here,
but I had to protect myself, so now
I know I have to give up some things
to earn his trust back, and,
I have no problem with that.
I didn't want to do it, Andy,
but they were all coming back to me,
and were like, "hey, Rome wants you."
I was like, "okay, fine, but
we have to have a backup."
Okay. Okay.
- So that's when I was like...
- Who-who, exactly?
It was Sam.
Sam is the one who said
that you're the backup, okay?
I did a lot of work to get
out of gato alive and have
a decently strong alliance
with Sam and Sierra,
but I feel like,
as time has gone on,
little things have started
to not add up in terms of how
they're moving in this game.
And when sol tells me
that they are using me
as a sacrificial lamb, I wasn't shocked.
I wasn't that surprised,
but I was, you know, sort of
woken up, and things
became very clear to me.
Based off what you're telling me, - yeah.
I need significant help from real allies.
So, I want some protection
from this in the future.
And what I want is an alliance - yeah.
Where people are not
gonna be throwing my name
as a backup option.
- Do you want to be a part of that?
- Absolutely.
- You...
- The next, like, three, four moves,
you need to make are just...
Need to be exactly how I expect.
- Okay, man.
- And we get rid of gata.
You got it, man. My man.
After this vote, I realize
if I'm gonna survive the
second half of this game, like,
I need to flip the switch.
I need to take control
and have authorship
over how the rest of this
game is gonna go for me.
And right now, that
means I should just gun
for my gata tribe mates, because
if they're gonna come for me,
I need to get them first.
Whatever you need, Sierra.
Do you want my shot in the dark?
I can give you my shot in the dark.
I mean, I would love that.
I'm so thankful for you.
- Yeah, man. I got you.
- Let's go.
- You know I got you.
- Yeah, I do.
It was Sam.
Sam is the one who said
that you're the backup.
Last night really got my head spinning
because I really feel like I invested
in those relationships
with Sam and Sierra
on the early days of gata.
But I'm realizing that I am a third wheel
and ultimately, very expendable.
Not even just at the
endgame, but even now.
And so, I'm reevaluating my game
coming into this merged tribe.
I feel like I have an opportunity
to find, really, sort of my people
that I can really roll with for
the long term in this game.
And, long story short.
I want to swing away from gata.
Did you have an okay sleep?
I slept okay.
Tribal council was interesting, obviously.
I know.
My god. How are you feeling?
I really just need to know
how to go forward, like...
Last night, my number one
went home, and I'm, like
I'm not taking a second to mourn it.
"All I'm thinking is," okay,
I'm in the market for a new ally,"
and top of my list is Andy.
We need to find a way to, like,
not just be the singles, you know,
- because the singles, no one's afraid of.
- Yes.
- Yeah, let's do something about it.
- Yeah.
Like, let's take the
game into our own hands.
I love that.
After the first immunity challenge,
Andy had what I can only describe
as a moment of, like,
true, raw, vulnerable panic.
But I really felt for him in that moment,
and he's still here.
I think, probably, because
people were using him
to further their agendas,
but now he has an agenda
and I have an agenda, and if we can
work together, we
can take back a little bit
more power at this stage in the game.
Okay, so if there's 12
of us, we need seven.
So, if you and I always have,
like, open conversations,
we can kind of figure out
what's going on and
who's telling what to who.
You know what I mean?
Like... I have a vision.
I have a vision for how
this game could go for us.
- Okay.
- And I like it.
Is it good? Is it a good vision?
- Yeah, it's a good vision.
- Yeah.
It could be, like, a big sneak attack
- in this game.
- Yeah.
That'll serve us both so well.
- That would be so good.
In order to change my fate,
here's what I'm missing right now:
A real number one in this game.
I've worked closely with a few people.
I've worked closely
with Sam, but that's drifting away.
And until now,
Genevieve is someone I
didn't know left from right.
I didn't really know where she stood.
I didn't know what her game plan was.
But I'm kind of seeing her, really,
as a pretty good opportunity for me
to pick up that one person who
also doesn't have a number one.
- I'm excited for what we could do.
- Yeah.
The possibilities.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Wait, sue. They told me
I can't believe you don't play pickleball.
I'm, like... Being a tennis player.
I have played it, but it's not...
- It's not?
- I play racquetball every day.
- Yeah, so that's...
- So, and then...
She needs her adrenaline high.
This morning, we're
just getting our buffs,
we're just officially
making it into the merge.
And it's, like, there's been
so much going on at once.
Like, we're trying to,
like, all chill at camp.
And then, of course,
Genevieve comes about, and she's like
I have tree mail.
In survivor,
you can't let your
guard down, and it's, like,
actually the most exciting
part, but also terrifying.
"A nerve-racking situation,
"the vote looming overhead.
"Lose your focus and lose this test,
tonight, your game just might be dead."
Nice.
So at this point, I'm, like, really
trying to look ahead, and I'm really trying
to see who I'm clicking with.
Got to get out of this
blazer before we friggin'
- I love that you have a blazer.
- My god.
Right now, I feel really
good about the tuku women.
I feel really good
about, I mean, most of the
women in this game, honestly.
I think that, ideally,
I'm going to find six
to eight of these people
that I really feel like can work together,
and we can start kind of
picking off "the other
side," quote, unquote,
you know, whoever that may be.
Like, we all...
Exactly.
- Dude, that'd be... sick.
- Yes.
I would love...
And we have the power
to do it, so let's do it.
In the survivor lexicon, I feel like
the all-girls alliance is almost, like,
mythologized at this point.
It's been done before.
We've seen the black widow brigade
pull off some of the
best moves in this show.
Since then, it gets
snubbed before it even
gets a chance to kick off and start.
But the way that I would
dream to play this game
is to form an all-women's
alliance and eat all the men.
That's, I mean, just an
ideal-case scenario for me.
And I really like the ladies here,
and I think that we could
all get on the same page.
So, who are... who are
some prospects? Like...
My god, I... Like, me,
personally... I'm sorry.
Gabe is a threat.
There are more
women than there are men
in this post-merge sequence.
But for me, I have to really start
to weigh the options of if I want
to continue to stay in this tuku five
or if I want to completely flip ship
and try to form genuine connections
and a genuine alliance
on the other side, because
I think that this is a perfect
opportunity to get Gabe out.
I've been wanting Gabe
out since the beginning.
I feel like I cannot trust this man.
But no matter what, I
want people to see me
as an individualized player, and that
I can make my own moves
on my own time, in my own way.
Come on in!
Day 13, the merged tribe of survivor 47.
So, Andy,
the last tribal council,
you voted out Rome.
It wasn't unanimous, but
it was the vast majority.
You've got the 12 people
that you want to move forward with
- and battle against.
- Yeah.
So now how does the game change
as we head into the next challenge?
It's just gonna get a lot tougher.
I feel like we got into the same beach,
and one person sort of
sunk their own game, immediately.
And that's a really
good consensus-builder.
That built this community.
But, now, it-it just starts.
It gets that much more dangerous.
We don't know who the next target is.
We have to play survivor
and see what shakes out tonight.
All right. Well, let's get
back into the game, then.
First things first. Kyle, got to take it back.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Thank you.
- You're holding onto that.
- Yeah.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna need balance,
concentration and endurance.
Here's how it works.
You're gonna stand on a narrow beam
while balancing a ball at
the end of a very long pole
while holding the pole above your head.
At regular intervals, you're gonna
move farther down the beam,
making it more difficult to
balance and concentrate.
And the longer you're in the challenge,
more difficult to keep
that pole above your head.
If at any point you fall
off or your ball drops,
you're out.
So, now that you have
the community you want,
let's divide that community
and pit you against each other.
Here's how it's gonna work today.
We're gonna randomly
divide into two groups of six.
The one person who lasts the longest
for the entire challenge wins,
for their group, immunity.
- My god.
- Everybody on that team
will be safe tonight at tribal council.
You will watch tribal council
but you won't cast a vote,
and you can't have a
vote cast against you.
You are safe. You will see
- day 14 of survivor 47.
- Wow.
The person who lasts the
longest for the losing group
earns individual immunity,
and you will need it,
because that group is
going to tribal council,
where somebody will be
the seventh person
voted out of survivor 47.
And as a penalty for being voted out,
you won't even make the jury.
In addition,
- you're playing for reward.
- All right.
Want to know what you're playing for?
The winning six will go
back to camp and enjoy
an afternoon of baby back ribs.
- My god.
- No!
- No.
- Potato salad.
- Potato salad. Potato salad.
- Yes.
- Potato salad.
- Corn on the cob.
No. Shut up.
Beer and soft drinks.
- My god.
Losers, nothing but a date
with me tonight at tribal council.
Big enough stakes?
All right, gonna do a rock draw.
- My gosh.
- Always twisting, Jeff.
- Always twisting us up.
- All right, take a rock. Don't look at it.
You know I love this part.
Which color are you gonna get?
Which color do you want?
Who else is gonna have the same color?
Who are you gonna be competing with?
Who you gonna be competing against?
Let's see what we have.
Everybody, put out your palms,
and let's reveal.
If you are blue, come
right over here on my left.
- Yellow, the far end.
- Okay.
Feel like we got some
endurance in here today.
All right, so let's see
how this worked out.
We have Genevieve, Sierra, teeny, sol,
Andy and Sam.
Sam, what do you
make about this draw?
Yeah, I mean, it's three gata, three lavo,
and I think this is now
a team of six because
if one of us can clutch up for
the other five, we're all safe.
So, I'm trying not to think
too much about the dynamics
and trying to focus on
how can I make sure
that all six of us, feel good tonight.
All right, the other six.
We have Rachel,
Caroline, sue, tiyana, Gabe
- and Kyle.
- Wow.
Tell me, sue. You've got your hands out.
We have our whole tuku tribe.
- Plus me.
- Plus Rachel.
Rachel. On one hand,
if you lose, things, on
paper, might not look good.
- Yeah. Sure.
- Five versus one.
But we're in the merge.
Everybody's wearing purple.
Yeah. I mean, there are
other dynamics in play here.
And if worse comes to worse,
and we're the group going, like,
I'll-I'll do everything I can to stay safe.
I am terrified.
I look down the line and see
the entirety of the tuku tribe and me.
So, I need to win today
or I'm leaving the fate of my game
in the hands of five tuku members.
I cannot believe that this is happening.
All right.
Here we go.
Everybody has their
Poles above their head.
Balls are balanced.
This challenge is on.
Everything that you
are focused on right now
is about one thing:
Balancing that ball.
Do not let it drop.
The stakes are big.
The person who lasts the longest overall
wins, for their group, immunity and food.
The person who lasts the longest
for the losing group earns for themselves
individual immunity, which
you will need, because
the losing group is going to tribal council.
Andy drops. Set your pole down.
Take a spot on the bench.
My god.
Rachel's ball on the move.
Rachel cannot survive the first round.
Set your pole down,
take a spot on the bench.
Just like that, we are down to five
in each group.
Now we're gonna
move to the next section,
and it's a live transition.
You have 15 seconds to do it.
Starting now.
You got to have both feet
in that next section of beam,
the wood section that isn't painted.
Now, with everything else
you're doing, you've got to move.
Sierra can't do it. Sierra's out.
Tiyana drops. She's out.
Genevieve, you're good.
Gabe, you're good.
Everybody's good.
Back to concentrating.
We're down now to four on yellow
and four on blue, just like that.
You are earning it every
single day on survivor.
Tribal council tonight.
You don't know who you
can trust, who you can't.
Person voted out tonight will have no say
in how this game plays
out, won't make the jury.
All that work, you make the merge,
but you're one day short.
One tribal council, and it's over.
Sol drops. Sol takes a spot on the bench.
We're down to three for yellow.
Remember, all it takes is
one person in your group
to outlast everybody
else, and you are safe.
Day 13, survivor 47.
This is it, right here.
This is the only thing you care
about right now, nothing else.
All right, start making your
move to the next section.
Tiny steps.
You got time.
Sam, you're good.
Teeny, you're good.
Genevieve, you're good.
Gabe, you're good.
Caroline, good.
- Kyle, good.
- Thank you.
Shoot.
Sue drops. She's out.
And we're down to three on three.
It is a showdown right now.
Sam, teeny, Genevieve taking on
Gabe, Caroline and Kyle.
Comes down to one person.
Who can last the longest?
Keep concentrating.
Check in on your ball.
Little movement with
Sam, but a nice recovery.
Nice.
You are vying for immunity
for your yourself and,
potentially, immunity
for everybody else on your team.
You want to be a
hero, here is a moment.
- Nice job, teeny.
- Big food reward,
security tonight. It will be worth it.
Yeah.
This is where you got
to get into that tank.
You've got a little gas in
there. You know you do.
Caroline really shaking, but still in it.
Nice recovery.
All right, here we go.
Let's move to that next section.
I will tell you when you're good.
Everybody start making your move
down the beam. This is a live transition
to the last section.
Gabe can't do it. He's out.
Caroline, you're good.
Caroline drops. She's out.
Genevieve, you're good.
- Sam, you're good.
- Keep going, Kyle.
- Good job, Kyle.
- Kyle's ball is on the move.
Sam drops. He's out.
Kyle trying to hang on.
Teeny fighting to hang in there.
Genevieve fighting to hang in there.
No.
Kyle's out. That's it. It is over.
Just like that.
Teeny, Genevieve, you don't have
to compete anymore.
Kyle's earned individual immunity.
It doesn't matter on yellow.
The entire group has immunity.
Wow.
My god, I didn't think I'd last.
Good news for Genevieve, teeny, Sierra,
Andy, sol and Sam.
Group immunity, no need
for individual immunity.
Nobody from your group going home.
You will go to tribal council tonight.
You will watch tribal council.
You will not cast a vote,
and nobody can cast a vote for you.
But for now, the six of
you are going back to camp.
Baby back ribs, potato
salad, corn on the cob,
beer and soft drinks.
- Yes.
- On the other side, Kyle, come on over.
For the second straight time,
individual immunity is yours.
Well, you're still struggling.
- Man, that's no joke right there.
- Yeah?
That-that messes with a guy.
- Good job, Kyle.
- Kyle,
for the second straight time this season,
individual immunity is yours.
That means you are safe tonight,
cannot be voted out of this game.
- Thank you, sir.
- You're welcome.
Have a spot back with your group.
All right, for the six of you... Gabe, sue,
Caroline, tiyana, Rachel and Kyle
you are not going
back to your tribe camp.
You're gonna go to the old lavo camp,
where you will spend the afternoon
with no food, nothing
but time to figure out
what's gonna happen
tonight at tribal council.
You'll go to tribal council
directly from that camp.
Tonight, the seventh person
voted out will not make the jury.
Biggest stakes so far in this season.
Grab your stuff, head out.
See you tonight at tribal.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Jeff.
We're going to tribal.
And even though I was, like,
trying to herd cats with this
alliance at tuku sometimes,
we have a great contingency plan
because Rachel's the only
person who wasn't on the tuku tribe.
We have an easy vote out
with Rachel, in my opinion.
However, the easy vote
might not be a smart vote,
and I want to make a smart move.
- Let's go.
- My god.
Holy cow.
Potato salad looks like the best
thing I've ever seen in my life.
- Who wants a beer?
- Yes, please! -I would love a beer.
Today was another
fantastic day in Fiji because
I surprised myself and
maybe everybody else
and helped win the
challenge for the yellow group
which included safety for all six of us.
It included food for
all six of us, and we all
have the certainty knowing
that we made the jury.
So, today was, like,
chef's kiss, perfect day.
This looks like the best
potato salad I've ever seen.
- More ribs? -Please.
- Yeah.
I feel like I'm not even taking the...
The proper amount of time to, like
- I know.
- Appreciate the fact
- that we are all safe tonight.
- My god.
- We make it to...
- We made the journey.
No matter what happens, we are here
to vote for the winner.
I want to know what's happening.
I want to know what's going on.
- We're gonna watch it.
- Are we watching
or, like, participating?
We're watching.
- Really?
- Only watching, not talking, yeah.
Yeah.
- Poor Rachel.
- I know. Can we talk about
Rachel being the only one?
- I think she's in trouble.
- I think... - Really?
My former gata members
and I get to bond with the former
lavo members, a-and
really kind of solidify
some trust and common happiness
and joy with sol, teeny and Genevieve.
But then, I realized,
my gata girl Rachel's over
there with the losing group.
She's sitting there with five tukus,
the entire tribe.
She's the odd woman out. Like,
if things hold to form,
she's just getting picked off tonight
and there's nothing
that I can do to save her.
The fact that that tuku group is...
Five strong is scary.
So, if it is Rachel
tonight and Rachel goes,
I would like to see this six
- vote together in the next...
- Yeah.
- Truly.
- Thing.
I know.
I think we need to knock
off some of those tukus,
- especially if there's five of 'em.
- Yeah, we would.
- If they stay strong tonight.
- I agree.
Because there was a triple amulet played
at the last tribal council,
which acted as a full idol,
I think it's possible that there
could be some sort of idol
or advantage hidden, which
would be massively important.
And if anyone were to find it,
then it could change everything.
I think someone's gonna find an idol.
I think it's gonna be a crazy tribal.
My gut is just on the ground.
This is worst-case scenario.
There's just nothing you
can do in certain situations
if you draw the wrong-colored rock,
and you just get put between
a literal rock and a hard place.
You can always hope that
there's divisions and cracks
within original tribes, but you can't look
at five tuku members
and one gata member
and not think, "well, that's easy."
Look, guys, I know it's a pretty
precarious situation for me.
So, if you guys want your
time, I will give it to you,
but I'd also appreciate
everybody else's time.
Of course. Yup.
Rachel was somebody
who has been perceived
as a very big threat in this game early on.
She's very personable,
she's very charismatic.
She's also very smart.
So to have her in this
vulnerable of a position
is very advantageous
for everybody in season 47 right now.
Yeah.
Okay.
The way that rock draw
at the challenge played out
was also perfect for tuku
because it's one more tribal
that all five of us get to survive.
All these people are in this game
are tools for me to use,
and having this tuku majority survive
as long as it can is a very valuable tool.
Yeah.
The thing is, though,
that means when Rachel
leaves, they have six now,
with three lavos, three gatos.
They're gonna come after one of us.
From the outside looking in,
Rachel is the obvious
vote. It's super easy.
However, I know with
my whole frigging heart
that if we go back to our camp
with five strong of tuku,
we are going to be picked off
because we don't have the majority
and we totally blew our cover.
We technically lied to everyone else
about how close we were.
So, not only are we really,
really strong, but we're liars.
What are we supposed to do with that?
This kind of seems like
the perfect opportunity
to get Gabe out.
- Yeah, it is a perfect opportunity for it.
- Yeah.
"Right away, I kind of was
like, "Rachel, you're doomed.
No doubt about it."
But then I realized it
doesn't have to be Rachel.
This could be the prime
opportunity to get rid of Gabe.
There's a very good
chance that it could stick.
You have a better connection
with Rachel than I do.
- Do you think you could pitch it to her?
- Okay. Caroline?
So, we need Rachel to be all in on this.
We need her to not play
that shot in the dark because
we're about to make
something awesome happen.
I'm gonna be, like, totally
straight-up and honest with you.
I want to work with
you, and I know that, like,
you are also close with,
like, Sierra, and, like,
you make good connections
because I feel like
you're a genuine person.
I feel really good about you ladies.
Like, so good.
So... my game plan
that I just brought up to Kyle
I'm gonna pretend like it's five strong.
But I've been itching for an
opportunity to get Gabe out.
Okay.
I mean, I love to hear
it. I wasn't sure because,
you know, like, it's hard
to read the dynamics.
E-Exactly.
And, like, you do a good
job of, like, you know,
- seeming very tight, so...
- No.
Tiyana comes up to me and says,
"I actually want to get Gabe out."
I mean, that's music
to my ears, obviously.
I'm gonna vote for whoever that's not me
to get me out of this very sticky situation.
The thing is, it all comes
down to, I think, Caroline.
But I know she's a smart girl.
She knows, moving forward,
if we go back with five, we are
- completely screwed. Like, there's no...
- Yeah, I get it.
Everyone is gonna gang up on you.
- Everyone is gonna gang up on us.
- Yeah.
And honestly, what better way
to prove that we have cracks
- than to vote out Gabe?
- Yeah.
What tiyana's saying is completely true.
Tuku is already a very
threatening presence as it is.
And to go back and
show that they are united
in voting out someone who, you know,
is pretty much on "the bottom,"
as far as anybody can tell
I was left out on the Anika vote and now
I'm the freaking underdog here... like,
that's not a good look for them.
And so, tiyana has, like,
a very good point that
taking out someone like
Gabe would be really smart.
So, if tiyana can swing Caroline
and Kyle wants to also go
along with this Gabe plan,
like, I'm in.
Wow.
I don't normally like ribs,
but those are amazing.
So psyched we won that.
I'm full. I don't even want to say it.
This has been a very
interesting and weird season
in terms of advantages.
They've all shown themselves early.
A lot of advantages have come out
and kind of just been
flushed sort of preemptively,
or in weird situations, like
at last night's tribal council.
And when those leave the game,
new ones come to replace
them, typically, and so,
finding an advantage could be
a very, very, very beneficial thing for me.
Andy has just been somebody
we've been keeping around
because we needed his vote
on gata, so I am not surprised
that Andy is searching for an advantage.
And he's a sloppy
player, plain and simple.
He's just all over. You
can't, like, track him.
And I'm like, that's just not
somebody I can work with.
Now that I'm working with Andy,
I cannot stress enough
how important it is
for him to be careful.
I honestly feel like if you
go looking for an advantage
this early into merge,
you have to be sure that you can find it.
I'm at this amazing reward.
I'm loving everything
about life in this moment.
We're all just kind of chilling, you know,
getting our, food comas on, taking naps,
and, I'm just not tired, and
I'm like, "hey, sometimes
there's something on these,
rewards, some type of advantage."
And so, I start creeping
around, you know, taking a look,
and I'm making sure
everyone's got their eyes closed.
So, I feel like I have free rein
to go searching for an idol.
I'm, like, looking, you know,
around the plates and everything.
And so, I'm like, "ain't nothing here."
Then, all of a sudden, on
the corner of my eye, I see
and the way it was positioned,
it was hidden very, very well
because it almost camouflaged.
Like, it was right next to me for an hour,
and I never saw it.
Feels so good to just lay in the sun.
I'm just, like, taking it in.
This is amazing.
I've been looking for so long.
I do my very best to be chill, be calm,
"but inside, and I'm like," damn,
this could shift the game."
- Look at it.
- My god.
- I don't like that.
- It was so good.
Look at it. Bones!
- Well, hey, we did that.
- Bones.
- You guys did it!
- Well done. Look at that.
Okay. We talk out loud.
This is not... I'm not saying that I'm
- going to do it.
- Let's purely brainstorm. Yes.
Purely brainstorm.
You would never think of actually
getting Gabe out, would you?
Are you debating?
Let's... I want to hear your...
'Cause, like, the whole
thing is that this is an alliance
- where we talk things through.
- Right. Exactly.
- Yes.
- Like, I just know,
keeping the five strong
would be awesome.
But we can't.
If we come back with five...
- We are screwed.
- Yeah.
Tiyana mentioned, you know,
going after Gabe is an option,
and it's something we should debate.
And there is a fear that
if we successfully vote out Rachel,
five tuku strong,
we get picked off one after one after one.
I think you're right
in that they're gonna come after us
- yeah.
- When we're five.
Here's the thing. I think
they will go after us,
but they're not going after us.
They're gonna go after Kyle if he doesn't
get the necklace. And if he does
- get the necklace, it's Gabe.
- Yeah.
Here's another thought. I
personally think Rachel is
the most dangerous player in this game,
and I actually think
it's much easier for us
to get numbers with
girls with Rachel out,
because Rachel's the one
who's connecting everyone.
Rachel is the best
I've seen in a long time.
I personally think Rachel
is the glue of the gata tribe,
and if we get rid of her,
a lot of options open up for tiyana and I.
Once Rachel's gone, it's easier
for us to be in the mix.
If it was anyone but Rachel, I'd be down.
I agree with you.
That's so... For Rachel, man.
I like her, too. That's
the issue. Guess what?
Out of all of them, I liked her the best.
I do like her the best.
- She's that good.
- Right.
Caroline does bite just a little bit,
but she does have some reservations.
And since Caroline is not on board,
it really is disappointing, because
I wish, wish, wish
that there was a way to
get Gabe out of the game.
I think tonight can be
- one of two things, right?
- Yeah.
We can go tuku strong, five deep.
But, like, what problems does that create
- when we get back home?
- Yeah, definitely.
And I think it creates
a lot of big problems
- when we get back home.
- A lot of big problems.
Or we can get somebody
we've been wanting to get out
for a bit now out of the game.
Everybody on tuku seems
to be on the same page:
It's Rachel tonight.
The dilemma is how can we get her
to not play her shot in the dark?
Because if she plays her shot in the dark
and it hits, then we got
to cannibalize each other,
and we don't want to do that.
We can go back,
and we don't have this tuku majority
- target on our back anymore.
- Right.
And that's the thing
that I'm most scared of.
Y-You know, I'm no dummy.
If we were to take all five of us back,
I'm not the last person on the list
- that people want to get out.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I'm gonna be high on that list.
- Yeah.
Gabe's plan... because he is also
so adamant that if they
go back as a strong five,
that he'll be next or
he'll be the one after next
he wants Caroline out.
I want to believe it, but all the bs
that I've bought along
the way in this game
it's felt so good, it's felt so right.
In that moment, it made
sense, and yet it was all fake.
If nothing else, you, me, Kyle
could throw a three on Caroline,
and in our worst-case
scenario, we're going to a tie.
But then what happens?
I mean, I would go to rocks
- over that, because...
- Genuinely?
Well, I mean, what the... am I
supposed to do at that point?
Yeah.
Because then it's like,
"hey, Caroline, like,"
- I put your name down."
- Yeah.
And then, "okay. Hey, I'm sorry."
- Yeah, valid, valid.
- Like, i-I'll backtrack,
and, you know like,
"okay, let's just do Rachel."
Yeah.
- So, it's, like... you know?
- My god, Gabe.
I mean, you're giving
me so much hope here.
It's, like, the best thing I
could have ever hoped for
and it sounds so
implausible at the same time.
Either tuku is completely playing me
or maybe I have some
kind of hope in this game,
and I'm still figuring
out which-which one it is.
- Well, thank you.
- So... yeah, of course.
- Can I hug you?
- Of course.
- Yeah, of course. Of course.
- My god.
This is by far the most precarious place
I've been in this game,
because at least in the other situations,
I wasn't actually the person
on the chopping block.
If I screw up tonight, I will not be
on the jury, I will not
be in this game anymore.
And I... That's... terrifying.
No foul balls over here.
Change up. Change up.
I found my first advantage in this game.
I was cool, calm, and I found it.
And so, I'm pretty
sure no one else saw it.
In fact, I know nobody else saw it.
Otherwise, they would
have said something.
Home run!
So now, I'm gonna have
to put on my Oscar-winning performance
and go off all by myself,
because in this game,
secrets are very, very rare.
But for me, I'm keeping it to myself.
So right now, no one else knows
in this game what I'm about to pull.
Come on, come on. What is it?
What is it? What is it?
I got a lot of power right now.
I finally get to use an
advantage in this game
and change the outcome of some things.
My god. That's gonna be so great.
What this advantage does is it gives
someone the opportunity to block a vote.
Which is simply, if someone
writes a vote, you can say,
"nope, that's not gonna count."
Or they can have safety without power.
So, in the middle of tribal council,
they can literally just leave tribal council,
go back to camp, and they're safe.
I got to think about this.
It's a good day, baby.
I just want go to tribal.
My god. It's close to sundown.
I think we're leaving soon.
I want to go to tribal right now.
- Like, right now. I can't.
- I can't think of that now.
Like, I'm... Like, my entire body is just
- I just want to get it over with.
- Yeah.
This is a big decision, and
I'm not sure what I'm gonna do yet.
I could give it to Rachel, but I'm not sure
if that's actually good for my game.
And if I don't give it to Rachel,
then I could build incredible bonds
with someone on the tuku tribe
and have another
option to get to the end.
Ultimately,
what it's gonna come down to
is what's gonna help my game.
I want to help somebody else,
but this decision is based
on what's best for me.
My heart is beating very, very fast,
and I just can't wait to get it going.
Now bring in the other six.
All right. So, last tribal council,
we had everybody... 13 people.
Now we're back down to small numbers.
Six people chosen
randomly, and we had the most
lopsided draw we
could have with five tuku
the most people left in
the game from one tribe,
and Rachel. On top of it, you have to
make this decision in front of six people
who can just watch
because they're not in trouble.
They don't vote. But,
man, they can observe.
All right, so let's look at the obvious.
If there was no emotion or game play
and it was just
numbers, take out Rachel.
But any time you hear
the word "easy" on survivor,
you should be terrified,
because survivor is never easy.
Caroline, five tuku.
Maybe this is a time to make a move.
Maybe you don't want
to be part of all five tuku.
Here's an opportunity, because
you have Rachel as a vote.
I can guarantee you that was
running through people's minds.
We have to realize
numbers are numbers,
and it's gonna look threatening.
But it sucks, 'cause I see
pros and cons both ways,
and it's hard to figure out
which one is gonna hurt my game less.
Gabe, one of the premises of survivor
is numbers. You got
to have the numbers.
But if you have too many numbers,
then you got to get rid
of some of the numbers
because too many looks threatening.
I look around and I see the five people
that I've been with for 13 days so far.
And I know, on the
surface, it looks simple,
but any of those five people might say,
"tonight's a hell of a night to
make one of those moves."
So, Rachel, the minute
the challenge ended
and you had lost and you
knew you were coming here,
you could not have predicted to hear,
"Rachel's not a for-sure.
There are opportunities
all over the place."
I mean, yeah.
This rock draw, nobody
can deny that this is, like,
the worst-case scenario.
But I don't know
if Gabe is blowing smoke
up my ass right now.
If you're actually a tight five,
and you're trying to stay together,
the plan would be to convince
me that you have cracks,
and to get me not to
play my shot in the dark.
So, it's scary.
It's not been an easy day for me.
Kyle, once again,
you have individual
immunity, and it does give you
just a little bit of breath
that you can stand back and
say, "I'm noticing some things."
What'd you see?
Yeah, so, Rachel did a good job today.
I mean, she took time
to pull everybody aside.
She talked in groups,
she went on solo
adventures with people.
She did her job, trying to find cracks,
and may have found some,
and... And she did her little wiggle.
Tiyana, I find it fascinating that you have
five tuku members, all
maybe independently thinking,
"how could I use Rachel?"
You really just put
our pickle on blast, Jeff.
That's exactly what I've been
thinking all day long because
this is a very important vote. Like,
being able to make the
jury, for me, personally,
it just means the absolute world,
and I know it means the
world to everybody here.
So, I got to go with my gut,
and honestly, with the vote tonight,
I'm just hoping that I send a message
to the people that I really trust
that I can be worked
with and I'm someone that
can be trusted in an alliance.
Caroline, tell me more about
the importance of making the jury.
I think the universal feeling that
I want to say almost every
single survivor player has
who actually cares about the game
you want to have an impact on the game.
It's not that we're sitting here
dreaming of being on the jury,
but we're dreaming of
having an absolute, tangible,
irrefutable piece of evidence
that we made an impact on this game.
All right. So, Rachel,
for you, this afternoon,
the subject line is easy.
"Vote, vote, vote. I'm a vote."
But you're not just a vote.
You want this vote to have
some impact tomorrow.
Well, I think
sometimes in survivor, you
can plan three steps ahead
and sometimes you just
have to get through the night.
And today was one of those days
where I just had to get through the night.
And so, today was
anybody else that I
can possibly, like, hope
that these people want
to vote out that isn't me.
When you went from person to person,
was your hope meter undulating?
It undulated. There was some chaos.
There was some
paranoia. There were stories
that were not cross-checking, and
this has been the hardest
day of survivor for me.
So, sue, given where
we are in the game,
and all the uncertainty,
maybe the five tuku,
for tonight, take out Rachel.
That's the easy move.
"And we all make the
jury and we'll figure it out."
Yeah, that is the easiest move,
and it's almost like
the most obvious move.
But, you know, I learned real quick,
this game basically
changes almost on the hour.
You can't predict anything.
You can say, "okay,
I'm set in stone this way."
Next thing you know,
you're totally flip-flopped.
So it's just, like, my head is spinning.
It's really, really... this is
very difficult for me tonight.
Tiyana, part of playing
survivor is making a move,
but also, maybe to not make a move.
Is that part of the discussion
that tuku was having?
"We could just vote out Rachel"?
Absolutely, that was always an option.
I mean, just look at five versus one.
It kind of seems like the obvious option,
but you want to make big moves
because if I just go for it
and I swing for the fences
and it doesn't work out,
at least I know I went for it.
What happens if tomorrow,
I didn't take that chance
and I go home with regrets?
That is, like, my biggest nightmare
from this entire experience is
going home with any regrets.
This is your shot.
This is your opportunity.
You got to go for it or
you're gonna miss it.
Caroline, the risk is
the tuku five blow it tonight.
You had five. This was easy.
And you make a move
and it was a little too soon.
I think you're hitting the nail on the head.
In the new era, there's such
an emphasis on big moves,
and granted, big
moves win you the game,
but it's big, smart moves.
There's a very big
distinction between a big move
that changes things
in a way that's not good for you,
in a way that blows up your game.
And that's what I'm
playing my game on, is
what are the smart
moves that I can make?
Sometimes they're not always flashy,
but I'm making the moves
that are best for my game
and for my alliance.
So, Rachel, it all centers around you.
The tuku five are in charge.
The question is can you find a way
to get at least one or two
of them to come with you
and try to make a
move? What's the feeling?
Is it optimistic, pessimistic or hopeful?
You know, still anxious,
but anxiously hopeful.
I think that I know
what the plan is tonight,
and I think that I'm a part of that plan,
and I have given my word
that I'm gonna do something
and I intend to do it
and I just really hope that
no one's giving me a shakedown.
Gabe, concerning at
all that Rachel's saying,
"hey, man, I was told there's
a plan and I'm a part of it
and if it works, I'm
gonna be here tonight"?
Well, I mean, it's concerning
if you don't know what that plan is.
And depending on what
perspective you look at it on,
Rachel could be totally helpless,
drowning in the water, hoping
somebody grabs her hand.
But if she can sow enough
discord between all of us,
all of a sudden, Rachel might be sitting
on top of the mountain saying,
"I'm choosing who's going home tonight."
And that's a pretty
crazy thing to think about
when you really dig deep into it.
So, as we get ready for the vote,
it seems like it is a very simple question.
"Will the tuku five stick together
or are the tuku five going
to turn on each other?"
All right, it is time to vote.
- Sue.
- Jeff?
About 20 minutes...
and I mean 20 minutes
before we left for tribal,
I found a scroll in my
bag. And when I ran
into the woods to
read it, I discovered that
somebody sent me... An advantage...
Only good for tonight.
Rachel, read your advantage for me.
Sorry. My hands are shaking.
"When Jeff says it's time to vote,
announce that you have the
safety without power advantage."
"You will leave tribal council immediately.
"You will not cast a vote
but more importantly,
you cannot be voted out."
So, I hope that you all understand.
My husband gave me a
couple words of wisdom
before I came out here
and one of them was,
"do not go home with
something in your pocket."
So, assuming I was
getting strays tonight,
this is a lifeline, and thank
you to whoever sent it.
All right. So, Rachel's playing
the safety without power. Rachel,
you can grab your
torch, head back to camp.
Well, that answers that question
about the tuku five.
My god.
So... Now what?
- Clearly, - this was a shock.
- Yes.
Yeah, little bit.
We're going to vote tonight.
It is going to be a tuku member,
and it's going to happen
soon. So, Gabe, where are we?
I mean, you know,
the game has changed.
- Just like that.
- That goes without saying.
The game has certainly changed.
There were many times
where we had to be
prepared to go to tribal
as a tuku five before the merge.
People kind of got to wind the clock back
in their head a little bit
and think about, "well",
"if we lost immunity with five people,
"what were we gonna
do again?" You know?
And so, I think that's kind
of where a lot of people's
- heads are at.
- Kyle, this is fascinating.
I mean, what Gabe just said
"it's as if we did a time warp.
We're back to the tuku tribe."
So, where's your heart right now?
It's pounding through
the back of my... my body.
I-I don't really know.
I mean, yes, of course
I'm safe, so, great.
But this vote, whatever
happens right now,
is going to propel into the future.
It's gonna have repercussions, right?
And that could break my
game apart, like, quick.
Tiyana, you are looking up to the sky,
you're looking for
answers from somewhere.
What is the game now?
Damn. This is... I'm not gonna lie to you.
Spending 13 days with
people is not something
that I take for granted, and it just is, like
I don't know. My anxiety is,
like, really through the roof
and it's hard to think
and process words and
I even just told you that
the jury means everything.
Like, getting there means everything.
So... I don't know.
It's gonna suck.
Is the emotion more that you're worried
you will be voted out tonight
or is the emotion that
you're not sure what to do
because this wasn't the plan?
Both.
Like, it's very, very
possible that it could be me,
and that would just, like, devastate me,
and that would be horrible, and...
Damn. But at the same time,
I have a pit in my stomach
that I got to send somebody home that
I know really, really wants to be here.
So it's almost like I'm
crying for both myself
and others, and it... I've never
done this before. I've never
cried for myself and others.
It doesn't even make
sense because it's literally
the exact same situation.
I got to say, from here,
it makes total sense.
You're terrified it could be you
and if it's not you, you're
horrified by the thought
that you have to do it to somebody else.
My family's gonna kill me that I'm crying.
Damn.
Awesome. While I'm crying,
everyone's talking. Okay, cool.
I'm just gonna get up now.
I was, like, "time
for frigging debates
to happen over here."
- So, we're back on?
- I...
Okay.
So, Caroline, what's
in your head right now?
I'll be honest. I don't even know how
to answer your question.
My brain is not equipped
to handle this at this moment. It's not.
So it's-it's just overwhelmed right now?
Yeah.
How about you, Gabe?
We all have relationships.
Survivor is a game of relationships,
and you got to trust 'em.
So tonight, I'm trusting my relationships,
and we'll see
if that trust pays off in
a few minutes, I'm sure.
All right, it is time to vote.
Sue, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage or an idol
and you want to play it, now
would be the time to do so.
Okay, I'll read the votes.
Gabe.
Tiyana. One vote Gabe, one vote tiyana.
Tiyana. That's two votes
tiyana, one vote Gabe.
Seventh person voted out of survivor 47:
Tiyana. That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
Tiyana, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
No. No. No, no.
Grab your torches, head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
captioned by media access
group at wgbh access.Wgbh.Org.
I see that word "auction,"
and my heart explodes.
Next time on survivor...
War is absolutely coming.
We're gladiators ready
to brawl in an arena.
- Yeah.
They're not gonna see me coming.
I thought I could trust
the people that were
in my alliance, and I got bamboozled.
To come this far and to literally
be one vote away
from making the jury... I'm
beyond devastated right now.
I think I played a genuinely honest game,
and it was true to myself,
and I don't regret the
way I played the game.
I just regret who I trusted.