♪ ♪
GABE:
I want to be the very first head
on the Mount Rushmore
of the new era.
AYSHA:
I am ready to forge my own path.
ROME:
I'm 100% gonna be writing
my own Survivor story out here.
CAROLINE:
Listen, I am either gonna
blaze my own path out here or
I'm gonna burn down this island.
SAM:
I think I am dangerous
in Survivor.
I have what it takes,
physically,
but I'm versatile enough to fit
into different groups of people.
You don't find a guy
who looks like me be
super unsuspecting, right?
It's often the people that say,
"Oh, I'm a...
I'm a wolf in sheep's clothing."
I'm a wolf in wolf's clothing.
♪ ♪
AYSHA:
I march to the beat
of my own drum.
And no matter how nerdy it is,
these are the things
I love in life.
But I don't do anything
unless I'm gonna succeed at it.
(whooping)
'Cause I just don't like losing.
I look like somebody
who wouldn't hurt a fly,
but they don't know,
like, I have a flyswatter
in my back pocket. (laughs)
KYLE:
Growing up,
life was a struggle, man.
I spent
five years in foster care,
over 26 different homes
I lived in before
I would graduate high school.
I could have just flipped over
and laid on my back,
but I didn't.
Life dealt me the recipe
for disaster,
and I baked
a ... brownie with it.
PROBST:
These 18 strangers
will be abandoned
in the islands of Fiji.
TIYANA:
I am the first native
Hawaiian to play Survivor.
I want to show
that Hawaii can roll
with the big dogs.
(howling)
PROBST:
They must learn to adapt
or they'll be voted out.
JON:
I am sure that I have friends
and family
watching this right now.
And I'm pretty confident
that I know what they want
for me out of this experience.
They want me to suffer.
PROBST:
In the end, only one will remain
to claim
the million-dollar prize.
ANIKA:
I'm gonna play hard.
I might get a little evil.
Who knows?
(cackling)
SUE: When I win Survivor,
my final words will be,
"I'm 59, and
I beat all your asses."
Who will have what it takes
to outwit,
outplay and outlast
all the rest?
This is Survivor 47.
♪ ♪
-(laughing, whooping)
-(clapping)
You're here.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my gosh.
TK: I would say, looking
at my fellow contestants, uh,
I see a million dollars, man.
Like,
I really don't think
I see anybody on here
who can do anything with me,
to be honest.
So, I'm ready to go.
All right.
Welcome to Survivor 47.
(whooping)
-It's crazy.
-PROBST: So,
every season of Survivor
starts the same way,
with the forming
of a new community.
That's what's happening
right now. Take a look around.
This is gonna be your community
for the next 26 days.
And the reason community has
always been the foundation
of this social experiment
we've been doing
for 24 years is because humans
have always
craved community.
And I get it. If you're at home
watching Survivor,
you could say
"Ah, it doesn't fully jibe.
"I mean, they're not
really abandoned.
You're not really on your own."
That's true.
There are cameras
shooting you right now.
But what you all
are going to experience
because you're here is that
when you're tired
and you're hungry
or you feel left out,
it's gonna feel very real
because you're gonna
have those same cravings
for community.
And what truly
sets Survivor apart
from any other social experiment
like this
is the game
that sits on top of it,
a game that's
played with humans.
The same humans you are
forming your community with
are your adversaries.
So you have to build a community
with people you can rely on
while you vote them out
and then
after you vote them out,
you go back to them
and try to persuade them
to give you the vote
for the million dollars.
How do you pull off
that magic trick?
So let's see if we can solidify
your community a little bit
by giving you an identity
with a tribe name.
We'll start with Blue.
Blue, you are Tuku.
-Tuku!
(cheering, whooping)
In the middle, Red, Lavo.
-Lavo!
-(cheering)
-Yes.
And on the end, Gata.
-Gata!
-Gata.
-(cheering)
PROBST:
All right,
so let's see if we can get
a little personality
from our tribes.
Guy in the front, in the middle,
what's your name?
My name is Gabe,
from Baltimore City.
What do you bring
to your community back home?
I mean, when it comes to
working, I'm a grinder, man.
I try to lead by example,
and I try to be
the guy that says, "I'm just
as tired as you are, but
"if I got energy to keep going,
I know for sure
that you got energy
to keep going."
In the front, in the middle,
introduce yourself.
Uh, my name is Teeny.
I know it looks like
I'm from the Wild Wild West
right now,
but I'm actually
a proud New Jerseyan.
I feel like this is, like,
aggressively scarecrow,
and, uh, that's not really
New Jersey's vibe, but,
you know, I like to change it up
with, like, my style.
Just to be clear, it's not like
I gave you these pants.
-These are your...
-No, I... I... It's my style.
It's my style.
I own it.
I'm just saying:
New Jersey proud.
(laughing)
PROBST:
Guy in the corner.
-What's your name?
-Hi. I'm Andy.
Andy, talk to us
about your role back home.
What's your life about?
Growing up,
I had, like, four friends.
So unpopular because
I did not have an identity,
and I kept trying
different things.
I would wear
Grateful Dead T-shirts
to be... pretend I was a stoner.
I'm afraid of weed.
-I can't smoke weed.
I can't do that.
-(laughing)
I was a poser, right?
But I learned
that I just have to be myself,
and it's become a super magnet
for everyone in my life
that I have today.
-PROBST: Guy on the end.
-Yeah.
-Introduce yourself.
-I'm Jon.
I'm a podcast host,
and I really care
what people think of me.
(laughing)
So much.
Four friends
in high school?
Must be nice.
(laughing)
PROBST:
Well, Jon, it's always
so exciting to start
a new season of Survivor.
So, what's the energy right now?
You know,
I'm here in part because
every episode you say,
"Apply to be on Survivor."
And you have this idea
of what you would play like
or what you could play like.
And I think
we're all nervous because
what we would play like
or could play like
is about to be fact-checked
against what we will play like.
-PROBST: Wow.
-And if you're cocky,
that's exciting.
(laughing)
And if you're not, it's not.
Well, shall we get
to the next phase?
-(all voicing assent)
-PROBST: All right.
Your first test as new tribes
is waiting for you
in the jungle.
-AYSHA: Oh, my God.
-Follow me.
AYSHA:
Oh, my God.
Oh.
ANDY: Jeff
walks us down the beach,
turns a corner
and takes us to...
It could only be described
as, like, a gladiator's arena.
Look, I've seen a lot
of Survivor.
There are opening challenges,
but this one
really takes the cake
in terms of the grandness.
And the pressure is on.
Like, you have to perform
or you're gonna
be in trouble immediately.
All right. Let's get to your
first challenge as new tribes.
Here's how it works.
Two players from each tribe
are gonna crawl
under a muddy net.
You're gonna race
into the jungle...
...and retrieve
two puzzle pieces
from one of three
different obstacles.
Then you race back,
the next pair goes.
Once you have all six pieces,
two tribe members
will use those pieces
to solve a rectangular puzzle.
The first tribe to finish
earns their camp supplies.
You know the drill.
It's not much--
a pot, a machete and a flint--
but out here, it's everything,
and will provide
a massive head start.
The two losing tribes will have
to try to earn it another way.
-Make sense? All right,
-Yup.
give everybody a minute
to strategize,
we'll get started.
-All right.
-SUE: Let's go.
Here we go.
First challenge of Survivor 47.
Survivors ready?
(cheering)
-Go! You're going out in pairs.
-(cheering)
Get through that mud.
Come on, guys!
SIERRA:
Come on, Gata!
That mud is birthing you
into Survivor right there.
SUE:
Let's go! Yeah!
(whoops)
Go, Caroline, go!
PROBST:
There goes Kyle
in the lead for Tuku.
Camp supplies on the line.
Biggest head start
you can get in this game
is the pot, the machete
and the flint.
(cheering)
-Let's go!
-(whooping)
All right, here we go.
Let's go.
-I'm on left.
-Okay, go.
PROBST:
Working together
to free up these puzzle pieces.
Got to get
all that rope through.
-They're all spooled up.
-All right. Watch that one.
-O-Over.
-Watch out.
PROBST:
Once your pieces
are free, you can head back.
These pieces are heavy.
Sam heading back
with the first piece for Gata.
SIERRA:
Come on, Gata!
-(whooping)
-Let's go, Sam!
-(overlapping shouting)
-I see you! Come on!
Aysha has her piece.
Kishan has his.
SAM:
Come on.
PROBST: Sam's back to help.
-Okay. Ready?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-PROBST: Kyle and Caroline still
-working for Tuku.
-KYLE: Okay.
How do you feel about it?
KYLE: Keep going.
SOL:
There we go. There we go.
That's how you do it
on Survivor, right there!
-(cheering)
-Let's go!
Got to get back with both
pieces. Keep going, Aysha.
You're good, Lavo. Head out.
It's Teeny and Genevieve.
SUE:
Guys, get ready.
-Go!
-You're good, Gata! Head out!
Rachel and Jon.
Go, Jon! Go, Rachel!
PROBST:
You're good, Tuku. Head out.
It's Gabe and Sue.
CAROLINE:
Yes!
Make it up.
PROBST: Jon whipping that rope.
Wow!
-This way, this way.
-Okay.
-PROBST: Teeny and Genevieve
doing a nice job
working together.
Threading that rope through.
Sue has hers, Gabe has his.
-Tuku, you can head back.
-TEENY: Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
PROBST: Sue! Lok at that.
PROBST:
Gabe heading back with a piece.
Sue heading back with a piece.
-Go, go, go.
-PROBST: You're good, Gata. Go!
TK:
There we go, let's go!
Let's go, Tuku!
Get 'em back to the tower.
You're good, Tuku. Head out.
-Tiyana and TK. Whoa.
-Whoa!
TK whipping through the mud.
(overlapping shouting)
You're good, Gata. Go!
Sierra and Andy.
PROBST:
Lavo, you got to keep moving.
You're good. Head out.
Sol and Rome.
The last two.
TK heads back to his team.
(overlapping shouting)
PROBST:
Sol heading back with
a puzzle piece for Lavo.
Lavo's closing the gap
right now.
Rome is free.
It's now Gata in dead last.
Andy and Sierra-- they have
blown the little lead they had.
Tuku with their final
puzzle piece.
You're good, Tuku.
Start solving the puzzle.
It's probably the, um...
Let's try it.
PROBST:
It is Caroline and Kyle
for Tuku.
That's gonna be an end piece?
Solving a rectangular puzzle.
Have to just put in...
-All right, let's go.
-Lavo, you're good.
-Start working on the puzzle.
-Oh.
-Go, Gata!
-Come on, Gata!
PROBST:
Here comes Andy.
He's got one piece.
Gata still has one piece left.
-Can you catch it?
-PROBST: Gata's dead
last right now.
(grunting)
Now you're good, Gata.
Start working.
Rachel and Anika
trying to make up
a lot of time for Gata,
who are working together
to solve a complicated
Survivor puzzle,
with tribe supplies on the line.
We scoot it once.
That could go... here.
PROBST:
There is no second place today,
just two losers.
-Yeah.
-Yes, and then that one there.
-PROBST: Gata now has
new momentum.
Anika and Rachel
feeling excited now
that maybe
they have something sorted.
-Yes, guys!
-Yep.
-Yes!
-This one right here.
-Gata with a lot
of enthusiasm right now.
Guys, guys, don't worry,
don't worry, don't worry.
-Let's go!
-PROBST: Is this it?
Have they solved it?
-Yes, go!
-They got here last.
Can they finish first?
-Push it in there! Yeah!
-Put that in there!
PROBST:
Put the top on.
-Oh, my God.
-You got to get up.
Why you never give up
in this game, ever.
-Let's go! Let's go!
-Let's go!
PROBST:
They got to get the top on.
And they've got it!
Get to the top!
-(whooping)
-PROBST: It's over!
Gata wins tribe supplies.
-That's it.
-(whooping)
PROBST:
A lot of effort from Gata
to stay in this.
-That was hard. That's no joke.
-No, that was tough.
-GENEVIEVE: Good try.
-PROBST: Wow.
None of us could get it.
One, two, three.
GATA:
Gata!
All right.
Gata, congratulations.
-(whooping)
-Tribe supplies are yours.
It's not much.
A pot, a machete and a flint.
But out here, it is everything.
Come grab it.
Along with a map to your home.
Gata, grab your stuff, head out.
You get the big advantage
of starting work on your camp.
SAM:
Thank you, Jeff.
-Good job, guys. Good job.
-Thank you.
-Killer. You were a killer.
-Oh, thank you.
PROBST:
All right, Tuku, Lavo,
no tribe supplies for you.
You're gonna have
to try to earn them another way.
Here's how it's gonna work.
Each tribe's gonna choose
one person to take on this task.
You're not gonna get
any information
about what is required,
so you're making a blind choice.
How about rock, scissors,
odd man out goes?
-Do you want to go?
-No.
All right, who's it gonna be?
All right,
Aysha's going for Lava.
Tuku, how about you?
Make a decision?
There's three people
that want to go,
so that's why
we're gonna either throw
a rock or scissors,
and then the odd man out goes.
I love this!
-Yeah.
-Ready?
Rock, paper, scissors.
-Geez.
-Not you throwing paper,
and we said rock first.
Is that what you said?
(laughing)
TIYANA:
But, yeah, you're odd man out.
Decision has been made.
We have Aysha for Lavo,
TK for Tuku.
You two are heading
out together.
Head down.
Boat'll pick you up.
Good luck.
All right, Tuku,
map to your new home.
-Thank you.
-Lavo, map to your home.
-Hey, yeah, baby.
-Yeah!
-Grab your stuff, head out.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, Jeff.
-Thank you, Jeff.
ROME: Aysha chose
to go on this journey,
which-- props to you,
but big mistake.
The social game
is the biggest aspect
of the game of Survivor,
and I am not gonna miss out
on those first few hours
of strategizing.
It's so important.
That's exactly how
I'm gonna win the million
dollars at the end of the day.
♪ ♪
ANIKA: Yeah! Gata.
(whooping)
-Victory.
-Okay, you guys,
we got to give it a second.
Group hug.
We did that.
We really did that.
RACHEL:
This is the best moment
of my life.
I love competition
and I love to win.
SAM:
Yeah, let's go in the water.
RACHEL:
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's do that.
Okay, let's go, let's go!
RACHEL:
We solved that puzzle, 100%,
because of good communication.
Like, it was a community effort,
like, full stop.
SIERRA:
Guys, I'm just so proud
to be a part of a winning team.
(laughing)
JON: It felt like baptism
by mud. Like, we're gonna
win this challenge and
every challenge that follows.
JON:
We don't really know each other,
but this is a tribe
that can win challenges
because we did.
I live in Los Angeles.
No, I started in WeHo,
where all the gays go.
I was a speechwriter
for a while.
-Okay.
-Whoa!
And then I started a podcast
-called Pod Save America.
-Wow.
JON:
I was a speech writer
for Hillary Clinton
back when she was a senator
and then I became
a speechwriter in the
White House for President Obama.
And now, when people
ask me what I do,
I have to say that
I'm a ... podcast host.
-Am I good?
-You're good. You're good.
JON:
When I was a closeted teen,
I watched Richard Hatch
win the first season.
I ran around the house
screaming about
what I had just witnessed.
-JON: What should we do?
-ANIKA: Most important thing:
-shelter?
-Yeah.
JON:
And now, all these
years later, I'm here.
I feel a little bit like
the dog that caught the car.
-So, something with a...
-A piece of bamboo
across, like, that?
-And then one over there.
-Yeah, something
with, like, a crotch.
I am a numbers guy
and that's how I want
to play this game.
Because I look at Survivor as
ultimately, a numbers game.
-Good? All right.
-Yup.
ANDY:
There are only six
people on the tribe, but
that constitutes
15 one-on-one relationships.
You could do the math.
It's a pretty simple equation.
It's a combination.
Six, choose two,
factorial equals 15.
So if I connect with two people,
it would actually be very hard
to get voted out.
ANDY: Because if I could
count on two people
to not write my name down,
it would be very difficult
for four people
to write my name down.
Who has to come out
to their own girlfriend?
And I'm like, "Okay."
And they're great vibes.
But I'm just saying,
I just think,
you know, we just have that...
-We don't need to try.
-I love it.
-You know what I mean?
-Unspoken.
-Guys, like, unspoken.
-All right.
(laughing)
SUE: I like your idea
of getting a shelter started.
Let's do it.
-The more we have,
the more comfortable we'll be.
-Yeah.
TIYANA:
Not winning that challenge today
actually sunk me to my core.
Fingers crossed
that TK comes through and
brings back something good
for this tribe,
because we're gonna
need it tonight.
What type of vibe
are we going for here?
Looking around at my tribe,
I feel like we stack up
incredibly well
in terms of physical strength.
SUE:
You guys rock. This is crazy.
(laughs)
TIYANA:
But puzzle-wise, we have
some work to do.
Tie? Uh, I mean,
at least for right now.
If we find more,
we can always reinforce it.
Coming into this game, I want
to work with an older person.
I want to work with somebody
who's a little more mature
because
I got a bit of an old soul
in me, right?
SUE: Uh-huh.
What?!
In my opinion, an older person--
they know how to operate
without getting caught up
in the social games of it all.
That's somebody
who I want my day one,
number one
alliance member to be.
People are gonna be running
around with their heads cut off.
People are gonna
be whispering at Tribal.
When that happens...
Thank you. Ditto.
GABE:
Let these kids gossip
and clique up among themselves.
We'll run things in the shadows.
Yeah.
-Grandson. Aiden.
-Grandson.
-Yeah.
-Aiden. How old is he?
He's four.
I love Caroline.
She is literally
the sweetest person
in the world.
Survivor is really
my mom's and I thing.
Now, see, it's me and Chelsea's.
Same thing, so you get it.
She's so excited,
and that's like my daughter,
so, it's cool.
Like, there's something there.
Yeah.
Uh, what do you mean?
You're the main person
that I feel, like,
-I've got, like...
-Oh, good.
-Oh, no, no, no. Exact opposite.
-Okay.
At my age, I thought for sure
I would be the very bottom.
But now I feel
like Caroline and Gabe--
they're-they're my number ones,
and so I'm feeling good with it.
Now we're gonna
be a force
to be reckoned with.
KISHAN:
All right. We're just
organizing them from, like,
-Biggest to smallest.
-biggest to smallest so that
it's, like, a nice incline.
-I think this one over here...
-This one's got some girth.
Yeah.
So, let's move this one.
-Yep.
-KISHAN: Losing that
first challenge--
it sucks.
We're not the tallest tribe.
We didn't look to be
the strongest, but Lava--
we're-we're resourceful.
We just have to trust
our instincts and kind of
fall back onto our training
and our, like, gut.
So, that's what we're doing.
Yeah! Like...
KISHAN:
I'm an emergency room doctor.
I love the chaos.
TEENY:
I think it's a dead hermit crab.
We could eat it.
Oh... Doctor.
KISHAN:
You're just
constantly surrounded
by the unknown,
and I'm so ready for that,
'cause that's what I do
every single day for a living,
and I'm really good at it,
and I'm gonna be good at it
on Survivor, too.
TEENY:
Can you guys tell me,
on a scale of one to ten,
how dweeby
my first buff look was?
It was some variation of this
for all of the opening events
of the day.
Where are you gonna place it?
Give it to me straight.
-SOL: You want it straight?
-TEENY: Yeah.
SOL:
It's at, like,
a four and a half.
-(all laughing)
-(indistinct chatter)
TEENY:
Playing Survivor is about
the social relationships
you make.
In school, the one thing
that I really excelled at
was being able to make friends
and talk to people.
And so I'm gonna
play this game by being
every single person's
number one.
(laughing): Exac...
Keyshawn and I bonded
almost immediately.
So, I mean, he's an ER doctor.
He has an ability
to work under pressure.
And I feel like he's a bit more
introverted to my extrovert,
so I felt like he was
a cool yin to my yang.
I think she's
got the perfect vibe.
-Yes.
-I think it's gonna be great.
Us three stick together,
we're good to go.
GENEVIEVE:
The new era of Survivor
is a very fast-paced game,
and right now,
I just really like Rome.
-ROME: Oh, oh, I got it.
-GENEVIEVE: Oh, my God, water!
-(whooping)
-(clapping)
-SOL: Wow.
GENEVIEVE:
I like him. I get along with him
so well. He's so enthusiastic.
I just feel happy
when I talk to him.
Oh, that's so good.
Oh, my gosh.
GENEVIEVE:
I'm also trying to solidify
something with Teeny.
I would love
to have her as my ally.
(gasps)
Me too. Me too.
I really like Genevieve.
I want to play this game
with her. But
let's remember we have
an entire tribe member
coming back here.
(whoops)
My goodness.
-So, TK.
-How you feeling?
-Aysha.
-Nice to introduce me,
-nice to meet... For sure.
-Yes.
-This is wild.
-We have... Oh, my gosh.
-Okay.
-You want to break it down?
When I read that
one person was going to
get their camp supplies
and the other was gonna
go back to camp empty-handed,
my stomach dropped.
This man looks like he currently
is in the NFL.
-So, on three?
-All right. Yes.
-One, two, three.
-One, two, three. Whoa.
Here we go.
Okay.
What am I looking for?
So, when I uncovered the clue
and saw that it was a picture,
I realized
this is my guide.
I have to match the two
to find the key.
It's gonna look
identical.
Okay. Agua.
I look at this map.
I see the first X,
and it's this huge rock face
that is near.
So I'm thinking,
"Just look for a big rock face.
I'll find the X."
I look around-- there's, like,
eight rock faces.
So, everything looks
exactly the same.
This is this rock.
It's saying "between two rocks."
Ah, there it is.
That's what I'm looking for.
That's it.
(quietly): Yes!
So, when I got my first key,
that gives me the clue
to be able
to find that second key.
A mountain of rocks.
Okay.
This a mountain of rocks?
Oh.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes. Let's...
I get that first key
and I'm hyped.
Now I got my confidence.
Now I know I can do it.
Come on, T, come on, T.
(grunts) Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
Yes! This is it.
Perfect. I found my second key
and I feel like
I'm cooking, we're going,
I have it.
Okay.
(sighs): Okay.
Come on, bro.
It has to be over here.
Let's see if it's right here.
Here it is.
I never would have thought that
the final key was in the ocean.
This is it.
Whoever finds
the fourth key wins.
See, thi-this is the tree.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, that's two keys.
I'm hyping
myself up like, "They don't
know who they messing with."
All right.
Three trees by theirselves.
Come on, T.
I don't even know
how to get back down.
I don't even remember
where the path was.
How am I--
I'm lost. I'm lost.
Let's go. Let's go.
Now I'm getting my rhythm.
Give me my money.
Uh-oh.
Hold up.
In the ... ocean is insane.
Well, got to go back down, then.
(grunts)
Oh, my God, dude,
where is the exit?
The forest is so dense.
And I'm like, "You know what,
"forget that path.
Make your own path,
like you've done
your entire life."
I am about
to muscle through this.
Oh! (whoops)
I don't care what I hit.
I'm making my own path
through this brush
and I'm figuring it out.
Where is this thing?
This is the path?
No, this is just where I was.
I can't believe being lost
is what's setting me back.
It's to where
I can't get out of here
because I'm lost?
Where?
Come on, come on.
Oh, I can't see
all the damn mud, dude.
There we go.
You got it?
Oh...
(sighs)
Hey, no, no, no, no.
-Let's go.
-Oh, you got it?
Let's go, bro!
AYSHA:
The fact that I was
so close-- oh, it
hurt.
It hurt so much.
TK:
At the end of the day,
there is honestly
no better feeling in the world
than seeing this
pot and machete and flint.
(whoops)
And it's because of me.
So, I'm gonna
take the credit on that.
Nice little pat on the back.
(laughs)
Ooh!
AYSHA:
I was heartbroken.
And I know from being
a Survivor podcaster
that going back with
no camp supplies-- that's...
surefire way to paint myself
as a target.
-♪ ♪
-(birdsong)
-(chopping)
-ANIKA: You guys ever have
-a sprouted coconut?
-RACHEL: No.
Sprouted coconut. So, basically,
it's, like, when a coconut
falls to the ground
and starts growing a new plant.
If you catch it at specifically
the right time
and you crack it open,
it has, like, this fluffy,
-foamy, like,
good-textured coconut.
-RACHEL: Oh!
-So, that might be a good thing.
-And there's one--
No, it's a great thing.
And it's over there
and it's growing, and we
can all, like, have dessert.
JON: Anika
is just prepared.
She's a prepared person.
She watched
a YouTube on coconuts
and she spotted
a sprouted coconut, which
is a trendy food in Los Angeles
and also available in Fiji.
The first base-- we'll want it
off the floor, right?
So, we have to dig four holes.
Even though I told myself before
coming out here,
"Do not take the lead,"
I'm a project manager
true at heart.
My head cannot help but say,
"Hey, guys, these are the steps
"that need to happen
in order to get
"from A to Z.
Let's do that."
We're gonna need
way more bamboo.
-RACHEL: Okay.
-SIERRA: All right.
Take a loop.
SAM: I love Anika
taking the leadership role,
mainly because I don't want it.
I want to be
the glue guy. Every sports team
knows what a glue guy is.
They're not
the best on the team.
the worst on the team.
They find their way
somewhere in the middle,
but somehow the team
just doesn't
function the same without them.
RACHEL:
Wait, we can dig
before we make it, right?
Yeah, we can dig, we can dig.
-(laughs): Oh!
-Oh, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Boom!
-Was it right
in between your legs?
-No babies for you!
SAM:
It's the guy in
a friend group that it's like,
once he's there, you feel like,
"Hey, the whole group's here."
Crisis averted.
But I think if you keep
the glue guy around for too long
in this game, you end
up getting burned by him.
You know what
I would love a lot? Fire.
ALL:
That's what we're doing.
SAM:
L... I love that you guys
are proactive enough
to think of it on your own.
-SIERRA: Can I give the fire
a go for a second?
-Yeah.
SIERRA: I'm always
looked at as like, "Oh,
"just the pretty blonde
with, like,
a cute little smile."
I was a pageant queen.
I competed at Miss USA.
But my dad
always wanted a boy,
and I just ended up
being my dad's little boy.
This is for you, Dad.
Let's see if I can do it.
I'm gonna try to make fire.
And this is why
winning the first challenge
was so important.
Hot flint and a machete--
that's everything.
We wouldn't be able
to build our community
without that stuff.
ANIKA:
Yep, keep going.
-(whooping)
-Fire!
SAM:
Pageant queen does fire.
-Pageant queen did it!
-SIERRA: We're off
to a hot start.
We are killing it out here.
There's no better feeling.
TK: I can't wait to just see
my tribemates' faces when I walk
onto that camp and I have
the tribe supplies.
(grunts)
Yo, yo, where the squad at?
My tribe is gonna be happy,
and I just can't wait to see
how much equity
that builds me in my tribe.
-Whoa!
-Whoa.
-Oh!
GABE:
No way!
(all shrieking, cheering)
(indistinct chatter)
TK:
Everybody's running up to me.
They're doing, like,
jumping and--
like we're in we're in the NBA
or we just scored a bucket
and we all
jumping up and doing
our shoulder bumps.
-Really?
-Only of us could get it.
-And you-- Oh, bro! Oh, my God.
-(whooping)
SUE:
Wow! TK!
Come on.
Wow.
TK:
There's no way, now, that
you could look at me and say,
"this guy needs to go first"
or "this guy needs to go"
at all.
Aysha comes over and then
she starts trying to, like,
wrestle me for the key.
And I'm like,
"Whoa, wait a minute."
Hey, all good, man, all good.
Look,
as long as we are comfortable.
(laughs)
CAROLINE:
Oh, my gosh, when TK
arrived at camp, the guys
flocked to him.
Where you from?
PG county.
-Really?
-TK: Yeah, man.
I already know. I was
gonna-I was gonna tell you.
-I went to Towson, bro.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-GABE: Hell yeah, dude.
-Hell yeah.
-TK: That was good times
over there.
CAROLINE: The guys fell in love
with each other the moment
that they saw each other.
KYLE:
I live in, like, a small town.
Like, "four stoplights for
the whole place" kind of thing.
-GABE: Get the hell
out of here. Really?
-Yeah.
We got a lot
of, like, inland lakes
and waterways
that connect to and from.
CAROLINE:
I'm not an idiot. I can tell.
It's a bromance.
GABE: Yeah.
TK:
Hold on. I'm-I'm gonna
pull it with you, though.
Hold on one second.
Oh, hold on, here we go.
I'm just pulling it this way.
There we go.
GABE:
Oh, my God.
At the base
of this really big log,
I see a Beware Advantage staring
back at me, and then I kind of
lean on top of it and I just put
my hand over it.
You know, instantly,
I start calculating
in my brain,
"How can I get TK
away from this?
I'm not totally sure
I want to bring him
that deep in quite yet.
Luckily, TK leaves
and I just get a chance alone.
Once I
make the decision to take it,
that is set in stone.
This is something
that I want to move on fast.
And a note says...
"You will dig up a box
that contains
"everything you need
to claim an immunity idol.
"Until you take possession
of the idol,
"you cannot participate
in the vote at Tribal Council.
That's why it says 'Beware.'"
I realized that
the branch where I found
the Beware Advantage was
right on the path.
And then, lo and behold,
found this box
with a lock on it and a tube,
which has more instructions
on what to do.
It says...
"Unbraid the vines to release
the key that unlocks the box."
And of course I know
what the rock face is.
It's a massive,
massive rock base
right next to our tribe's camp.
So, I know I have to bring
what's up there
down to me with these vines.
I can see the key wrapped around
the ring on the top
of this rock base.
My precious!
There it is.
GABE:
Do you want to find out?
I'm such an idiot.
-You want to help me?
-Yeah.
GABE:
Right away, I was like,
let me not play coy.
Let me just bring him into this
right away and say, "Let's
find out what this is together."
That's a key, dude.
Dude.
That's probably for the...
We found a key
before we found anything else.
That doesn't sound right.
Like, that's
not adding up.
So, in my mind, I'm like,
"I caught you in the act
but you weren't gonna
"tell me about this,
so maybe we aren't
as close as we thought we were."
GABE: I kind of
feed TK this story
of "I just found it"
and I think I he bought it.
Yeah.
I finally have this key
in my possession,
and I-I really
need to find time
to return to the box,
but not be
too hasty about it, because
it just leads to mistakes.
AYSHA: Riding back to camp
with no camp supplies,
I was so fearful.
I'm just thinking,
"I haven't just disappointed
myself in this moment, but I've
disappointed my tribe."
Hello.
Oh, Aysha!
-Aysha!
-KISHAN: Yeah!
-Okay, story time, story time.
-Oh, my God.
AYSHA:
I knew
that the only way to approach
talking to my tribe
was being honest.
I literally had nothing to hide.
Um, we arrived to the beach,
and there's this stand
and the instructions say
there are two paths
and only one tribe
was gonna get the camp supplies.
TEENY:
Being a Survivor fan,
I've listened
to Aysha's podcast before.
It seems like she's very bright.
She picks up on a lot of things
that even I miss from the show,
and that could
be helpful for my game.
-Well, thank you for going.
-GENEVIEVE: Thank you
for trying and going.
I was like,
"Oh, it was for nothing."
TEENY:
So, the first thing I did
was pull her aside
and say, "Listen,
I think I know who you are.
-Okay.
-And I...
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Right, right, right.
So, I don't plan on...
-I would never tell anybody.
-Okay.
-I just wanted to tell you.
-Thanks.
So, when Teeny approached me
about recognizing me
and knowing me
from Rob Has a Podcast,
that made me so nervous.
But I really do feel, like,
a genuine connection with Teeny.
I'm just trying to make sure
that I'm not
blindsided by...
good vibes.
SOL:
Yeah, Lavo.
-TEENY: Yes.
-(Genevieve laughs)
AYSHA: Everyone playing
the game of Survivor
is here to win
a million dollars, and so
I'm trusting everyone until
they give me a reason
to lose trust.
Who knows
what's about to happen?
AYSHA: Yeah.
-Oh, for real?
-Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Seems like
my whole tribe likes me,
which is good.
I said that
when I start this game,
the main thing that I want to do
is immediately start looking
for advantages
and try to do it
in the smartest way.
It is hard,
in this new era of Survivor,
to look for these advantages
and not
get caught.
I need to go this way.
I don't know. I just-- I...
I feel like we just--
Yeah.
ROME:
On day one,
looking for an idol--
that could put a huge target
on your back.
But at the end of the day,
I want to play this game
as hard as possible.
So I have to make sure
that if I'm looking,
I am looking everywhere,
and if I look everywhere,
I feel like I'm-a find it.
(gasps)
I didn't even
see the word "beware."
I just see the word "advantage."
That's all it is.
Because guess what?
That advantage is gonna be in my
hands instead of someone else.
It said right there at the path,
you'll be able to find a box
with everything you need
to get your idol.
Oh, my gosh.
Once I started
to dig on the path
in the broad daylight,
that was when I realized,
"This is not a good idea."
Thing is, it's right there
where everyone's walking.
It's directly
on the way to the well.
And so I almost
have to do this at night.
I just feel
absolutely incredible
at how I'm playing the game
to start things off.
This is a Survivor moment
right here.
-I know.
It's a huge Survivor moment.
-Right here.
-Is it dead, though?
-No, it's-it was moving.
GABE: This is a group that
I imagine most
Survivor tribes are like
in the early days,
where everyone's just
really, really excited,
understandably so.
-Let's run into it.
-(Caroline whooping)
-TK: Yes! Let's go!
-CAROLINE: Let's go, Tiyana!
(whoops)
GABE:
But I've had a lot of time
to be excited.
Now's not the time
to be excited, now's the time
to take care of business.
It's why we're here.
It's what I plan to do.
I found a key earlier today
to unlock this box
buried in the ground,
but TK walked up and caught me.
And now I'm realizing
I need somebody
to keep an eye out for me.
And Sue was somebody
that I could
work with to actually accomplish
the tasks that were at hand.
When he told me he found
the Beware Advantage,
that was huge.
Like, I never expected
anybody to ever tell me
that they found an-an advantage.
-All right.
-Okay.
He'll be coming
from what direction?
Okay.
So, I'm definitely
gonna be the lookout
for when Gabe goes off hunting
for this advantage.
♪ ♪
The fire's doing good.
GABE:
I hear from Sue,
and I have no more time.
I grab that lock that's
hooked on the box and I just
rip it out of the ground
as hard as I possibly can
and I just take off sprinting.
Let me just
get off this path
as soon as I can.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
When I open it,
I find a second box
within the first box.
And I'm not happy about it.
I broke my neck
to get this thing, and now
it comes with this big caveat.
It's only good
for one Tribal Council.
If you want to keep going,
there's another task,
and that will give you
an idol that's good
for three Tribal Councils.
I fancy myself a gambler
in real life.
I like betting on sports,
I like going to the casino.
Scared money don't make money.
So I put the one-time-use idol
inside the smaller box
and I took the clue,
and it says,
"Follow the map
to the driftwood.
"Break open the driftwood
to find the key
that unlocks the box."
So, I realize I have
to hide this box somewhere and
figure out what the next step
of the equation is.
That did not sound that great.
(sighs)
I don't even know
what's happening up there.
I couldn't even possibly guess
what he was doing
up in the rock mountains?
GABE:
I am just panicking
and-and panicking.
My heart rate is pounding.
I had a rough start
to this game.
I sit here with no vote,
no idol, a whole task to do.
It's gonna be
a very mentally stressful
next couple days.
♪ ♪
Where am I needed?
-Vining?
-RACHEL: There's a ton
on the floor there.
And there's, like,
that one back there.
SAM: I love Vine.
RACHEL: Mm.
Oh, my God!
I was just wondering
'cause you...
Vine was awesome.
That's right.
I was still a young person.
JON: Looking at my tribe,
I'm realizing I'm not
getting to know
a group of people.
I'm getting to know
a group of young people.
I am 41 years old.
Okay, so I'm old now?
No, I really like Vine.
I like...
There's so much
"back in my day" stuff
coming out of my mouth.
But, being a speechwriter,
I learned
that you need to be able
to put yourself
in other people's shoes.
I'm addicted to TikTok.
-It's so good.
-I am, too.
SAM:
All the boomers are like,
"We got to ban TikTok."
And I'm just like,
"I need my videos
of, like, dogs getting adopted."
JON:
I'm realizing that
I'm the oldest person here,
but I'm not gonna
let that stop me
from trying to build things
with these people.
We're doing great.
-We're doing amazing.
-Yeah. Also, I learned
this thing I read. My stepdad
was like, "You're gonna
die out there." He gave me,
like, this survivor book
for Christmas,
and if you hold your fingers up
to the bottom of the sun,
-every finger's 15 minutes.
-SAM: I read that.
-I read that.
-Oh.
-JON: You read that?
-SAM: Yeah.
A book or a website?
A book.
Mine was a book.
-SAM: It was on the Internet.
-It was hard copy.
ANDY:
I first saw Rachel, and
I just knew she was someone that
I wanted to hitch my wagon to.
I feel like
we've got, like, two hours.
Okay. All right.
ANDY:
Right now, I feel like
I trust Jon
and I'm working with Jon,
but that's it.
And that makes me uncomfortable,
as a numbers guy.
Yeah. Let's go.
So I really put it upon myself
to find an opportunity
to get a moment with Rachel.
That's awesome.
I feel good about you, too.
We're... in alignment.
We're synchronized.
I agree. I'm like,
"You're strong. I'm strong."
-Yeah. Yeah.
-I feel like it's good.
Part of the appeal
of Survivor to me is
that I love games, and
Andy is just the sweetest,
but I don't think
he's strategic.
-...in a minute.
-RACHEL: He just, like,
is a little too eager, maybe,
to, like, just to bond
and to get to know each other.
You have to be careful, though.
-Maybe not tomorrow.
-Yeah, yeah.
-I'll follow your lead.
-Okay.
RACHEL:
It's super suspicious to
get up early
and meet on the beach to talk.
Like, absolutely not.
I am not doing that, Andy.
ANDY:
I couldn't sleep.
I wasn't sleeping at all.
I was just in these sort of
negative thoughts,
feeling like, in this
new community, I'm somewhere
where I don't belong.
And I just needed
to talk with someone,
someone I felt good about
because
I feel like...
I am spiraling, in a way.
-It's just that I...
-No, like, you don't
even need to say.
Like, someone definitely knows
we're here,
-and so, like, that, actually...
-Yeah, you're so right.
RACHEL:
One of the things
a Survivor player shouldn't do
is go off to talk.
This is really obvious.
People just heard us
in the shelter.
All right,
do you want to sit or what?
RACHEL:
And I just literally told him,
"That's a bad idea.
We shouldn't do that."
And then he does it anyway.
It doesn't make me
more confident that he's going
to be a good alliance member.
ANDY:
I just can't sleep.
-I just need to talk.
-No, no, you're fine.
-No, tell me.
-I thought I would come in here
and be a little different
than I am.
RACHEL:
What did you think
you were gonna be?
I thought I was gonna
be the version of myself
that, like,
I feel like I am today, but
-feel like I'm going
a little bit backwards.
-Yeah.
He's feeling insecure,
and I totally empathized
with him, but
you can't take those moments
of downness
and then just kind of rip
somebody else's ga... game
and pull them down with you.
-We need to get the fire going?
-ANDY: Yeah.
RACHEL:
Make coconuts first, then fire,
-'cause we need to eat.
-Right.
ANDY:
Rachel's someone
I felt so good about on day one.
-Thank you for doing this.
-Of course.
ANDY:
But I tried opening up
to Rachel.
I thought that would give me
a sense of relief,
but I don't feel like
I got that closure at all.
And that put me
in a very difficult
and negative headspace.
ANDY:
Right now. I feel like I've felt
very often in my past.
RACHEL:
Yeah!
ANDY:
Sort of a high school feeling,
like I'm different,
I stick out in a bad way
with a group of people
all enjoying
each other's company...
RACHEL:
You're so accurate.
That's really hard to do.
-ALL: Oh!
-That's a good-ass coconut.
ANDY:
...without me.
-SIERRA: Yes! Give me some.
-That was beautiful.
ANDY:
When I'm cracking my coconut,
people aren't even watching me.
Jon-- he cracks a coconut
and there are cheers
from everyone else at camp.
And I had this gut feeling
I am on the bottom.
This could be my last day
playing Survivor.
-JON: It could be any of us.
-I'm going crazy.
I'm the least popular
on this tribe, and it's okay.
It's okay.
JON:
I feel like I'm in a really
good place with Andy, but
there's some anxiety
under there,
beneath the surface,
and that makes me nervous.
I don't know if I want
to work with somebody like that.
♪ ♪
GABE: The next clue told me
I have to go find a piece
of driftwood out on the beach
that has a key inside of it that
will open up the second box
that will then give me
the three Tribal idol.
And the clock is ticking.
So the X on the map
says it's into the brush,
and lo and behold, there's
a piece of driftwood there.
I know that there's
a key inside of it,
so, I just smash it
like I'm Donkey Kong.
(groans softly)
Every slam of this driftwood--
it's deeper than
just getting this key.
This is giving my vote back.
Who knows how much time I have
before people get up,
and I don't know if I'm gonna
have another opportunity
to keep looking for this thing.
Come on. Oh. Come on!
(sighs)
Bingo.
So, now that I finally have
this key in my possession,
I'm exhausted, but I can't wait
to get back to the box.
(sighs)
There's a catch.
There's a third box
within the second box.
It never seems to end.
Leave it to Survivor
to just not let me
take a breath.
This was a tough call
I was making,
but this has been so damn hard.
I'm really excited
because I have power again.
I have my vote back.
I'm a dragon sitting on top
of a pile of gold.
-Personally love him.
-Yeah, personally love him.
-Yeah, I hear you.
-Yeah, truly.
SOL:
I-I really think
he has something.
Last night, I dug up a box.
There was a gigantic lock
on the box,
and then I found the scroll,
and I knew there was no way
I was gonna be able
to read the scroll
in the pitch black.
And so, today,
I walked away by myself
so I can read this advantage
and do the next step.
"Soak... soak the drift..."
That's so random.
Okay.
All right.
I can do this, though.
Once I got that second clue,
I realized, "Okay,
this is absolutely insane."
But, man, if I can find this
and get this done fast,
that'll be awesome.
All of a sudden,
I heard a twig snap.
I look up,
and Aysha's right there.
Hey.
Huh?
ROME:
Granted, I don't think
she saw me
pouring water on the driftwood,
but she saw me
looking really, really hard.
-And...
-Like, fully, like...
-Fully looking.
-Okay.
Where was he looking?
AYSHA:
By the rocks.
We need to see
if he's still over there.
Rome is playing amateur hour.
He's searching for idols,
and he's a complete liability.
Rome is off his rocker.
(whispering):
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
The key to the box
"is at the bottom of the well."
When I read that,
my heart dropped.
(grunts)
It feels so, so difficult.
You can almost feel like
Jeff wants someone else
to be able to know,
he wants someone to catch me.
I got the key. I know
that the key unlocks the box.
I'm hoping that
I can go open this box up
and that there's gonna be an
immunity idol right inside it.
(quietly):
Here we go.
What?
AYSHA:
Me, Teeny, Kishan
and Sol saw Rome
at the water well.
And he
goes the other way.
No, "Hi." No,
"Hey, what are y'all doing?"
Like, that is just
suspicious behavior.
-Yeah.
-Should we just keep going?
TEENY: Mm. Yeah.
AYSHA:
I have this huge fear
of Rome having an idol.
I think that's great.
AYSHA:
But now I feel like
I have the numbers.
If we do end up
at the first Tribal Council,
Rome is the first person
I want to go.
♪ ♪
Come on in!
Here's Tuku.
-Ooh.
-PROBST: A lot of smiles.
-Yeah.
PROBST:
Here comes Lavo.
Come on, Gata.
(whoops)
All right.
Shall we get to your first
immunity challenge?
-(all voicing assent)
-Let's go!
-(whooping)
-PROBST: All right.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna start out
in the water on a platform.
On my go, you're gonna dive in
and swim to a boat.
You're gonna paddle that boat
back to shore,
collecting three
very heavy chests along the way.
Once you get to shore,
you're gonna drag your boat
along the track and under a net
to the finish
where three tribe members
will use the keys
in the chest to unlock
and solve
a massive Survivor logo puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity,
safe from the vote.
Here are the immunity idols
for Survivor 47.
-(cheering, whooping)
-SIERRA: I love it!
They're so cute.
(indistinct chatter)
You have one
of these at your camp,
it means your fire stays lit,
nobody going home.
It's a great feeling.
Without it, you are vulnerable.
In addition,
you're playing for reward.
-Want to know
what you're playing for?
-(all voice assent)
TIYANA:
Oh, my God!
First tribe to finish--
a very nice
Survivor building kit.
-(whooping, cheering)
-Oh, my God.
PROBST:
If you don't have
camp established,
this'll do it.
If you do, this will improve it.
Second tribe to finish--
smaller, but will help.
Smaller tool kit.
-Oh!
-Nice one.
-Okay. Yeah.
-PROBST: All right.
Last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as
-the losers,
-ALL: The losers.
date with me at Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the first person
voted out of Survivor 47,
and as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
All right, I'm gonna give you
a minute to strategize,
we'll get it on.
Here we go.
(whooping)
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Our jam.
Go!
Everybody's in the water.
You got to swim out
to your boat,
get everybody on the boat.
The boat can't move
without everybody on it.
Pull.
PROBST:
Once everybody's on,
you unclip in the front.
Then you start paddling.
Clip, clip, I want that clip!
(indistinct,
overlapping chatter)
Go.
(indistinct,
overlapping chatter)
PROBST:
All three tribes now paddling.
(overlapping chatter)
You're going
to that first chest.
-We're going
the wrong way, guys.
-PROBST: Gata immediately
is way off course,
going completely
in the wrong direction.
Tuku to their first chest,
Lavo to their first chest.
Sol gonna do it by himself.
Kyle and TK doing it for Tuku.
Once everybody's
back in the boat,
you can start working
toward that next chest.
(indistinct,
overlapping shouting)
PROBST:
Gata now has their first chest.
You got to keep that boat close.
You can't let it drift.
Go, go, go. Okay, do it.
PROBST:
Here comes Tuku.
They're at their second chest.
We've got Sol once again
for Lavo.
Sam falls off.
-Wait, wait, wait!
-PROBST: He's in the water.
-Andy's in the water.
-Up, up, up. Up.
(overlapping shouting)
Tuku flips their boat.
Absolute disaster for Tuku.
(muffled chatter)
PROBST:
That boat is upside down.
-Both chests are off.
-Here, here, here.
PROBST:
That opens the door for Gata.
(yells)
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh!
Now it's Gata
that's upside down.
It is an absolute
-disaster
-No!
in the first immunity challenge
of Survivor 47.
Paddles everywhere.
Chests everywhere.
Players everywhere.
You wanted Survivor,
you got Survivor right here.
PROBST:
This is one of the worst starts
to any challenge
in 47 seasons of Survivor.
-Absolute struggle
-(indistinct chatter)
for both tribes in the water.
Lavo with a big lead.
-Yeah! Yeah.
-You're good.
Lavo, you're good.
Get off, start unloading.
Gata trying
to get that chest on.
They're taking on more water.
-Got to get that lift.
-(shouting)
There you go.
They've got it.
Will it sink them,
is the question.
No, no, no, no!
PROBST:
Tuku's at the third chest.
TK back in the water.
-(grunting)
-PROBST: Lavo making
a lot of progress.
-Yes!
-PROBST: Gata got
their third chest.
Lava with a giant lead.
-One, two, three!
-(grunting)
PROBST:
That's how you do it!
-Tuku's at their third station.
-Bring it in to me.
RACHEL:
Just a little breather
for a second.
Yeah, let's go!
PROBST:
Gata, you're good!
Tuku, let's go!
(indistinct chatter)
You're good here, Lavo.
Now you got to get the three
chests to your three spots.
-Okay.
-Then the three puzzle makers
take over.
Hey.
That's good.
Push, push, push.
PROBST:
Both tribes now
back at the beach,
they're not giving up.
You are both still in this!
We're looking for two tribes.
All you got to do
is not be last.
All right,
the bottom on the side...
Aysha, Kishan
and Rome solving
the puzzle for Lavo.
Gata, you got to keep digging.
Tuku, you got to keep digging.
-Yes! Yes!
-KISHAN: Yeah.
-Yeah!
Lavo wins immunity and reward.
Safe tonight at Tribal Council.
We're looking for one more.
(grunting)
PROBST:
This is it.
It is a showdown.
(yelling)
You're good, Tuku.
Get your chest out.
-Three.
-RACHEL: Come on, guys!
PROBST:
Gata getting closer.
-One. One more!
-One more.
-Three!
-You're good, Gata. Unload!
TIYANA:
Come on, come on, come on.
-SUE: Yes!
-TIYANA: Come on.
-Yes. That's it.
-PROBST: Tuku's got
the pieces free.
Now you can start
solving the puzzle.
Everybody on fumes, but you will
sleep well tonight at camp
-Straight ahead, Gabe.
-a lot better
-than you will at Tribal.
-Okay.
PROBST:
We have Sam, Rachel
and Anika for Gata,
Tiyana, Caroline and Gabe
for Tuku.
Your future rests in your hands
when you take the puzzle spot
in the first immunity challenge
on Survivor.
Yeah, but on the other side
is right.
-Wait.
-We got the "Survivor."
PROBST:
Gata was dead last
in the first challenge,
and they pulled it out.
-Right here.
-PROBST: Can they
pull it out again?
Yes. Other way, other way,
other way, Sam.
-Other way, Sam.
-How? This is right.
Here we go.
Another two pieces for Tuku.
Feel like they're
getting closer.
-Here, here, here.
-Gata starting
to fall out of this now.
They're gonna have to move.
It's coming down
to a few pieces for Tuku...
Hey, hey, right there.
...and a lot of pieces for Gata.
RACHEL:
Here. Can you move the top one?
Can you move the top one?
This does not look good
right now for Gata.
I want to say that Gata probably
count on going to Tribal.
They got to probably start
figuring out who's going home.
No, out, like...
Listen to me.
-Grab this one.
-SAM: Where am I bringing it?
You all right?
Andy.
(indistinct chatter)
Are you just chilling? Are
you okay? Do you want medical?
Okay. Gotcha.
-Medical!
-Are we going?
-Yes, keep going.
-Sam.
Sam, I want to take it off.
How you doing?
PROBST: We have Andy being
-looked after by medical.
-MEDIC: Nice deep breath.
PROBST: Don't worry.
He is in good hands.
We will stop if we need to.
(coughs)
Right here. Here we go.
Watch out, watch out.
Move out. Here we go.
-Let's go.
-PROBST: Tuku down
to their last piece.
TK:
Last piece.
-Let's go! Come on!
-Check, check, check, check!
PROBST:
There it is. You've got it.
Tuku wins immunity,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
sending Gata to Tribal,
where somebody
will be the first person
voted out of Survivor 47.
SIERRA:
Don't be sorry.
(indistinct chatter)
-Oh, you're in good hands.
-I was...
PROBST: No.
Dude, you're in the game, still.
-Okay. Okay.
-Stop. Okay, I'm with you, okay?
-SIERRA: You're good, Andy.
-I didn't...
-Your tribe lost.
-Yeah.
-So you are going to Tribal.
But you're still in the game.
There's still a lot of game.
You're overheated.
-And we're in no rush. Okay?
-ANDY: Yeah.
You don't have
to worry about anything.
-This is part of Survivor.
-ANDY: Yeah.
-PROBST: We got you.
-ANDY: Okay, okay.
-ANDY: Thank you.
-PROBST: Yeah. Just sit here
until you're good.
Okay, but they
haven't voted you out.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yup.
-Right?
Yup. I get it.
-Okay. I'm gonna
let you cool down.
-Okay.
-Not talk.
-Yeah.
We'll go when
you're ready, okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay. All right.
-All right, love you, Jeff.
-Hey, I love you, Andy.
He's good.
We're just giving him space.
-It's just... He's good.
-(applause)
-RACHEL: All right, Andy.
-SIERRA: Come on, Andy.
MAN:
All right, good. Good timing.
No. He's up, he's up, he's up,
he's up, he's up, he's up.
All right.
Andy is okay.
(whooping, cheering)
Head back to Gata.
GABE:
Attaboy.
-(whooping)
-KISHAN: Yes, Andy.
So, Andy, give
everybody else the update.
I was overheated.
I'm okay now.
-PROBST: Okay.
-I'm okay now.
-I'm cooled down.
-PROBST: All right. All right.
-You feel all right?
-Yeah.
Okay.
You seem emotional.
-Yeah.
-What's the emotion?
I was fighting for my life.
I'm on the bottom.
I see it in their eyes
when
they don't...
I crack open a coconut
and they didn't cheer for me.
They cheered for Jon,
and they... And then I-I...
They don't like me.
I don't think.
-That's not true.
-Okay. Okay.
-ANIKA: Andy, Andy.
-ANDY: Okay.
-I know it's the game.
I'm not...
-It's in your head.
PROBST:
So, Andy, you haven't even
-gone back to camp
to strategize,
-ANDY: No.
much less get to Tribal,
-where all kinds
of things happen.
-No.
PROBST:
And it sounds like
you're conceding defeat.
No, no, no, no.
I'm a strategist.
I was gonna try everything.
My best friend out here is Jon.
And as they were
finishing the puzzle,
I was...
...thinking I was gonna
throw him under the bus
to try to stay.
Just, I just want
to play the game.
-(quiet murmuring)
-Um...
-(quietly): Wow.
-ANDY: And then, I, like, uh,
stopped seeing straight.
(chuckles)
And I just want to,
you know, be in the game.
PROBST:
So, Andy, what's great
about Survivor--
you might be right.
It might be
a five-O vote tonight.
-Yeah.
-PROBST: You might be wrong.
-PROBST: You don't know.
You fight until
I snuff your torch.
That goes for everybody.
You're all gonna feel down.
He's just the first.
This is why you're out here.
You want something soft,
pick another show,
'cause you are on Survivor.
That's a badge of honor,
-Andy.
-(Sue whoops) Yeah.
Go, Andy.
PROBST:
All right,
let's get to the results,
'cause there is some
positivity out here,
starting with Lavo
in the middle. Congratulations.
-Yes.
-(whooping)
CAROLINE:
Good job, guys.
PROBST:
You are safe tonight.
Waiting for you back at camp--
that nice Survivor tool kit,
which will improve
your living conditions.
-Yes, sir.
-CAROLINE: Good job, guys.
Tuku, it took some work,
but you got it.
That's all that matters.
-You're safe.
-That's all of us.
This is all of us.
Waiting for you back at camp--
a smaller tool kit.
Tuka, Lavo, grab your stuff.
Head out.
Enjoy the night off.
Congratulations.
-There he is.
-PROBST: Lavo,
before you leave,
-you get your flint.
-(cheering)
We got fire tonight, baby!
Let's go.
Come on.
PROBST:
All right, so, Gata.
What is happening right now?
Jon, can you give
any perspective?
How does Andy's confession
impact anything?
JON:
Uh, what I take from Andy--
uh, previewing a trip for me
under a bus--
is... is that he is wrestling
with the fact
that he wants to stay
and he values
the relationships he's building.
But he knows that
in a situation like this,
you may have to turn
on people you care about.
PROBST:
All right, Gata,
Tribal Council tonight.
Somebody from Gata
will be the first person
voted out of Survivor 47.
And as a penalty for losing--
sorry for you--
I'm gonna take your flint.
Thank you, Rachel.
You'll have a chance to win
it back in the next challenge.
Grab your stuff, head out. See
you tonight at Tribal Council.
Thanks, Jeff.
ANDY:
I was being very honest
in a vulnerable moment
at the exact wrong time.
I feel like
I am a dead man walking.
But...
I'm here because I...
will give it my everything.
And I have to play
until my torch is snuffed.
The last thing I'm ever gonna do
is concede.
♪ ♪
RACHEL: At the immunity
challenge, Andy had a meltdown
in front of everybody, and
in my head, I was like,
"What is he doing?
"Like, what is going on
right now?
Is this actually happening?"
In all of my Survivor watching,
I don't think
that's ever happened before.
I mean, people have
had meltdowns, but I don't think
it's ever happened
in front of everybody else.
RACHEL:
The other tribes-- their jaws
were like...
"What?"
And, I mean, so was mine.
ANDY:
On the mat, I was at 80%.
But I've fully
gathered my thoughts now.
Survivor is a game of paranoia.
It's extremely possible that
I was just susceptible to it.
I realize now,
in many ways, how unfair
some of the things
that I said...
Some of the things that
have always plagued me
have just started
bubbling up insecurities that
date back decades, right?
ANIKA:
He said he was 80%.
He wasn't 100% better yet.
Which makes me nervous.
All of us aren't
gonna be 100% out here.
That's the whole entire point
of the game.
If you're gonna have outbursts
like this on day three--
like, that is a huge concern.
I like all of you a lot.
And so...
-I appreciate that.
-RACHEL (laughs): Yes.
SIERRA:
And, Andy, know how much
you contributed to this tribe.
You've done beyond
the coconut cutting.
-The bamboo, our shelter
where we're sleeping,
-And challenges.
challenges, your strength.
You provided...
-ANIKA: Such an asset.
-such an asset.
JON:
Andy is messy. That was messy.
I don't know that I've seen
something like that before.
And because of how
it all went down, like,
you would think that
they're going for Andy, but
I'm a little bit paranoid
because
I feel like I have been
struggling to fit in,
and that makes me nervous.
So I'm gonna go feel it out.
ANIKA:
Do you want to talk about Andy?
JON:
Yeah. I'm a little frustrated
because, like...
-He called you out.
-I know.
-He called me out.
And it's like, "Hey, man,
"like, we've-we've been
talking for two days.
I genuinely, really like you."
This is somebody that I was,
like, beginning to think, like,
"Oh, this is a person
that could play with.
-I could play with them." Right?
-SIERRA: Mm-hmm.
-Right.
You know, like...
And then instead, it's like,
-how do I go to bat
for you right now?
-Mm-hmm.
-SIERRA: I know. I understand.
-How do you
play a game with him?
It stinks.
-RACHEL: This stinks.
-It just stinks.
It... So, like,
I think we need to,
like, tell him it's you.
Is that okay?
Cause I just don't know
that he's gonna believe
anything else
because he already is the one
that's pitted himself
against you.
Okay.
-I mean, right?
-I know, that's true.
JON:
Anika, Rachel and Sierra
are all saying it's Andy,
but they all immediately
are like, "And we're gonna
tell Andy it's me," which sucks.
Uh...
SIERRA:
Bring it in.
We got to get to the end here.
What I'm hearing
doesn't totally make sense,
so I'd much rather
try to figure out my best
strategic option with the votes.
JON: I...
-know that, like,
you had, like, a moment.
-ANDY: Yeah.
-I want you to stay.
-I want to stay.
I want to stay, too.
-I want you to stay.
-And I never was gonna
throw you under the bus.
-Okay.
-And that's my...
But what do you want to do?
Anika.
Anika is the person I want gone.
-Okay.
-How do you feel about that?
I...
I would like to do it.
ANDY:
I'm patching things up with Jon,
and he gives me sort of, like,
a lifeline for me in this game
to get out a person
I actually want out,
which is Anika.
At this point, my main,
core priority
over everything is just
fighting to stay in the game.
JON: If we can turn this into
a move, I think we can turn...
-Yeah. Yeah.
-like, you having that moment
on the mat
-Yeah.
-into something.
I think that Sam has
a working line of communication
with Sierra.
All right, let's go talk to Sam.
Right now, it's either
me or Andy.
Or I can try to vote Anika.
If I'm gonna be on this show
for one episode--
one glorious
and perfect episode--
I'd rather go out swinging
and ha--
and-and making
some kind of a move
rather than just
hoping for the best.
I don't want
to hope for the best.
I want to try
to figure something out.
-Here's where we're at.
It's you, it's me or it's
-ANDY: Yeah.
-Okay.
-Anika. For tribe strength,
what is Anika offering, right?
I think you, me and Andy
vote Anika
-and pull someone
into the group.
-SAM: Yeah. Yes.
Well, I mean, that
would be our option there.
JON:
I think Sierra
will listen to you,
and I think we have to just sort
of not talk to Rachel about it.
-Right?
-N-- Yes.
JON:
I just also, like...
Hi. Don't worry,
just going to the water well.
You guys can keep going.
SAM:
Jon and Andy expect me to throw
a vote on Anika tonight.
Love you, Jon,
but I'm not doing that.
I'm starting to think
Jon is playing hard.
-JON: We can make this work.
-SAM: Yes.
-I got it, right?
-Okay. Okay, I'm-I'm gonna go.
He's a strategist.
He's very, very smart,
which is dangerous for me.
And Andy is strong.
He might be able to help us win
a challenge or two.
ANIKA:
I know we're at a point in the
game where we need strength, but
will we actually
win more with Andy?
Because he is messy and not only
in his words, but, like,
-all he is is brute force,
and it's not even
-SIERRA: That's so true.
-that strong a force.
-SIERRA: Having somebody
like Andy can be a liability,
and it's somebody we definitely
need to worry about.
However, I think
right now we need strength.
I don't think these challenges
are going to get any easier.
We need some strength
and, honestly,
we're not getting that from Jon.
I think we need to touch base
and get on the same page.
-Yep.
-Yeah.
-SIERRA: We have to be quick.
We need strength right now.
I think that makes sense.
Right now,
I would vote Jon.
RACHEL:
I still really worry about Andy
imploding again.
Like, yesterday was a bad day,
today's a bad day. He's given up
halfway through the challenge
-before we even lost.
-ANIKA: Mm-hmm.
I just think there's legitimate
pros and cons to both.
If we keep Andy,
I think he's more loyal
to me than he is
to anybody else on our tribe.
But I don't know that
that's actually a good thing
because Andy is a ticking
time bomb and you don't know
when it's gonna explode.
On the other hand,
if we keep Jon, who is
more even keel and levelheaded,
we might lose the next
few immunity challenges
without Andy's strengths.
I am genuinely torn.
Our ability as a tribe
to make the right choice
is gonna
decide the fate of Gata,
and that
is so scary.
♪ ♪
Behind each of you is a torch.
Go ahead
and grab a torch,
dip it in and get fire.
This is part of the ritual
at Tribal Council
because in this game,
fire represents your life.
Fire's gone, so are you.
And that will be the case
for one of you tonight.
But before we get to the vote,
we got a lot to talk about.
It has been a roller coaster
for the Gata tribe.
Sierra, give me an idea
-of camp life.
-Oh, my God, Jeff.
I mean, my back
feels broken, my legs
feel broken, I have bruises,
and it's been
three days.
I mean, Jeff,
I have the Survivor 101 book
at home.
I have
25 coconuts in my backyard,
machetes.
My neighbors definitely
have a lot of questions about
who's living next door to them.
But I do have to give props
to Anika. I mean,
she definitely led the tribe
for a good bit.
She had the basics
and got us, like,
a good base start.
PROBST:
Anika, walk me through that.
How did you step up
to be the leader?
So, I'm flattered
that you think that. Um,
I had general consensus
and a general idea of
what we should be doing,
realistically.
-How would you
describe camp, Jon?
-JON: I think we spent
the first three days
finding commonality.
You're doing that
because you genuinely want to.
There are genuine connections,
those are real,
you can't fake it.
And even if you wanted to,
I don't think you ultimately
could succeed unless you were,
like, a sociopath.
And so, yes, we're a community,
but we're also competitors.
And I think a little bit
out of fear and trepidation,
people really were reluctant
to break out
into groups and start
having strategic conversations.
So, a bit of a delayed start
to the strategy part?
Uh... yes.
PROBST:
All right, let's get
into the emotional part
of the first three days, Andy,
-all circling around you.
-Yeah.
Today at the immunity challenge,
what stood out to me
were the comments you made
about your tribe.
-Yeah.
-"Nobody noticed me
open a coconut.
Nobody likes me.
Everybody wants me gone."
Walk me through that
a little more.
Well, I feel like
I grew up on the outside, 100%.
I never felt like I belonged,
but coming into this experience,
I felt like I changed
just by getting rid of all this,
like, need to please people.
PROBST:
So, you're saying,
in your recent life,
-Yeah.
-just back home,
you felt like you've broken out
of that feeling left out.
-Yeah.
-And do you feel like
you have a community?
An unbelievable community
has formed around me,
and it did not happen overnight.
It was because
I challenged myself.
I kept saying yes to things.
I kept putting myself
out of my comfort zone,
and succeed or fail
based off of that.
PROBST:
So, it's fascinating
-that you would work so hard
-ANDY: Yeah.
and then sign up
to take on the biggest test
-Yeah.
-of social resiliency
anybody could
ever volunteer for.
ANDY:
But I've made myself
ready to conquer that.
And now I can go show,
you know, the world, any--
everyone in my life,
you know, how far I've come
and how, you know,
easy it will be for me now,
which is not the case,
as we can see.
PROBST:
So, Jon, regardless
how it played out today,
do you respect the fact
that Andy's intention
of coming out here was to try
to take on this social test?
Um, did Andy have a moment?
People have moments.
Sometimes they happen
on a beach in Fiji.
People shouldn't be judged
by their worst moments,
even if you are frustrated
that they're saying it
-in front of everyone,
including Jeff.
-(laughs): Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
-JON: So I don't think
any of us came away
from that not being frustrated.
PROBST:
So, let's talk about that.
Andy, you shared
a lot of information.
-Yeah.
-It'd be very easy to say,
-"He's a loose cannon.
You got to get rid of him."
-Yeah.
PROBST:
So, when you get back to camp,
-what did you do?
-I want to be very, very clear,
and I was clear to everyone.
I think it was pretty obvious
that there was absolutely
zero premeditation.
That old part of me just set in
and that paranoia,
and now look
at these five people
who Andy threw under the bus.
-You only threw one person
under of the bus.
-Well, yeah.
With my words.
Yeah.
But despite all this,
the one thing
I absolutely cannot do
is say that it's okay
to vote me out.
Let's just play Survivor.
I will accept the result.
So, Sam, what was the fallout
from a strategic point of view?
Because you don't want to come
back to Tribal Council again,
and a lot of that is gonna
be harmony and tribe strength.
I never had a perception of Andy
that he was out here to do
anything other than give 100%.
He fought so hard
in the challenge
that he's passed out
on the side.
But then he's willing
to turn on his best friend.
Well, that's hard for somebody
to jump into bed with.
Rachel, can Andy
recover from today?
I-I...
I empathize with
Andy completely,
but what if he goes
on a journey and says
whatever he's thinking,
which-- who knows--
you know, what plans
he has that I don't know about.
But Survivor does that to you.
Like, everyone has
those moments of like,
"Is everybody just
lying to me right now?"
PROBST:
Jon, it's interesting that
playing out right now
is everything
we talked about
at the marooning.
The idea of building
a new community
where you can feel safe in it,
but then you put on top of it
the game.
So, how confident are you
about the vote?
I don't know
what kind of conversations
would have taken place
if Andy hadn't
drawn the... the evil eye.
I-I really don't know.
But when you know
that there's all these different
conversations going on
and that there is
a natural target,
it really starts
to make you wonder,
who's the unnatural target?
Could I be trying
to find that person?
Could it be me?
♪ ♪
PROBST:
All right.
It is time to vote.
Sierra,
you're up.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
(laughs softly)
I'll go tally the votes.
♪ ♪
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Jon.
Anika.
One vote Jon, one vote Anika.
Jon. That's two votes Jon,
one vote Anika.
Jon.
Three votes Jon.
First person voted out
of Survivor 47: Jon.
That's four. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
JON:
All right.
Jon, the tribe has spoken.
(chuckles)
Time for you to go.
All right.
-See you.
-JON: Bye, team.
-Bye, Jon.
Good job.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
ANIKA:
With Andy, it's giving
toxic, clingy boyfriend.
PROBST:
Next time on Survivor...
-That looks...
-SOL: Rome is...
Ah.
SOL:
He's a lot.
SUE: The rage on her face--
that put the nail in the coffin.
SAM: I was not ready
for the bomb that Andy
was about to drop.
Nobody imagines that
they'll be the first to go.
But when you take a risk,
sometimes it doesn't
go the way you want.
But that's why
they call it a risk.
This will bring so much joy
to my friends and family
making fun of me for years
that maybe in the end,
it'll be worth it.
First out.
Let me have it, people.
Let me have it.
(roars)