It's called "loyal to the soil."
I'm whispering different things
in people's ears.
All I got to do is decide
who my next victim is.
I'm a smiling assassin.
Previously on Survivor...
My heart is racing.
Oh, my God. I got it.
Survivor bucket list.
Nobody knows
that Caroline, myself and Gabe
are in an alliance.
We're gonna be a force to be reckoned with.
It's just a matter of time before
he strikes me or I strike him.
I love Gabe to death,
but it's every man
for himself right now.
It's going to be you, me and Sue
as the final three.
Gabe is a close alliance member of mine,
but things are opening up now.
He's played a better game
than me.
Targeting Gabe means targeting Sue...
...and betraying her trust
and potentially destroying
our alliance.
Tenth person voted out
and the third member
of our jury: Gabe.
The tribe has spoken.
We're doing this, bro.
I know that was hard, voting with us.
- I know.
- Yeah, it's tough.
I'm sorry, man.
I know he was your buddy.
It's tough
to watch someone you love go.
It's got me kind of
in an emotional funk right now,
the fact that Gabe went home,
and that I played a part in that
because I really enjoyed Gabe
as a person.
- It'll be okay.
- Yeah.
But Gabe's threat level
has been climbing,
along with mine, so I have to
draw a line in the sand
and say, "Hey, I'm gonna hit you
"before you hit me
and make sure it sticks."
So now, back at camp,
I don't trust anybody.
I feel like I need
to win every single immunity
after this in order
to ensure the fact
that I'm still going to be here.
Thank you.
Tribal really sucked tonight.
They really blindsided Gabe,
big-time.
It sucks.
And the whole tribe knew
except for me.
Thanks for getting the fire going, guys.
- Wow.
- Gorgeous.
You guys are miracle workers.
I feel crushed.
I can't even trust
Caroline anymore.
Something like that
really lights the fire
under my rear end to, like,
really start taking down
everyone, but especially Kyle.
I can't believe he's still here.
That just--
ew-- turns my stomach
more than him
writing my name down.
Like, I just...
I want write his name down
for Gabe.
And I can't wait for that day.
All right, what are the odds the sun comes out today?
Is the rain stopping?
Last night, it was tough.
It was pouring rain.
Winds are blowing,
we're shivering, freezing.
And you're just...
you're miserable.
You're frozen.
You don't want to talk.
You just want to, like,
cower up, and I kept praying
for a little of the heat
from that fire to come my way.
Yeah.
But the worst thing
is that Gabe's gone.
My security blanket, my...
You know, my number one
from day one, gone, and now,
I'm miserable, I'm all alone.
It-It's a tough, tough, tough
environment to be in.
I'm okay.
It's just...
Last night, blindsiding Sue
was maybe a huge mistake.
I knew that there was a chance
she was just
gonna be like,
"You're on my hit list,
you're out.
"You betrayed me.
I thought I could trust you.
I can't trust anyone.
Our relationship is over."
I hated taking that chance,
but I knew that,
from the bottom of my heart,
this is the game I need to play.
So, I need to talk
to her.
I need to make sure
she understands
why I did that vote.
I felt my only true friends
were you and Gabe.
I just don't like
non-loyal people.
That's just who I am.
It's not that I don't like you,
but, you know, it's just...
- You can see, I'm loyal.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- I want to explain
one thing to you. - Mm-hmm, yeah.
This is not in any way making me
feel like I am not loyal to you.
But I kept feeling like I was
making decisions good for Gabe.
And I started feeling like
I didn't have any control
- over my own game.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
I felt like I waited
my whole life for this
- just to do what someone else
was telling me to do. - Exactly.
And I was like, "That, to me...
"I will go home earlier
and play my game
"than make it to the end feeling
like someone's carried me,
- and I just sat around."
- Right. Right.
Gabe had a vision of me,
that he was gonna
bring me to the end,
and I will have done no strategy
of my own, just
followed along with him,
and he gets to take the credit
for a lot of the moves.
That is never the game
I was going to play.
I wanted to be on Survivor
ever since I was five years old.
Like, this is my biggest
life dream.
That's what
I care about the most.
I feel like my goal out here is
to play a game
that I'll be proud of.
Like, I'll be able to rewatch it
- and be, like,
as, like, a little girl. - Yeah.
Like, I proved
to that little girl,
- like, I did,
and I was so proud of myself. - Mm-hmm.
I have ADHD,
and the way it, like,
impacted me as a kid is,
I just felt like
I was constantly failing.
So the way I internalized that
growing up is
I was like, "I'm just dumb,"
because I grew up
saying I would do something
and then I would get distracted,
or I couldn't will myself
to do something.
And I felt like a failure.
And so I feel like
I've just lived my life
just trying to prove to myself
that I'm not that failure.
Resilience was all I had,
and Survivor was experience
where I could see
how great it is
if you persevere.
And what's crazy is, I feel like
that is what has been
pushing me in this game.
- I want to go
to final two with you. - Right.
And we complete each other.
It's weird, but we do.
And you're my number one.
- You're my number one girl.
- You're my 100% number one.
Even though Caroline voted Gabe,
I feel like she came to me and
sort of gave me an olive branch,
and that's all I needed.
I feel good with her.
I still feel we're number one
and number two together.
And now, this is our time
to take control of this game.
We're at eight,
and we're the tightest three.
We are, like,
a three-person alliance.
- All we have to do...
- We are locked in. - Yes. Yes.
Like, for final three,
all we have to do
is play our cards right.
Yeah.
Sound, yeah.
- Hello. Hello.
- Hi. - SUE: Hello.
Good morning.
How's everyone feeling
this morning?
- How are we feeling?
- Okay.
I think that
having Gabe not here anymore
opens the door
to kind of these, like,
endgame strategies
that we're all looking
to start creating right now.
- It was a hard vote last night.
- It was hard. - I know.
But I don't want you to feel
- worried about, like...
- Thank you. Thank you.
I was grateful
that it wasn't me.
Yeah. It wasn't you. Yeah.
I feel, like,
good about this group
standing here
- Yeah.
- Me, too. - um, moving forward.
I really do, as well.
This is really good, I think,
because that leaves
Genevieve, Sam, Kyle.
Underdog alliance, guys. - Yeah.
I love an un...
good underdog story.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
This is what I've wanted since
the start. I really mean it.
I am trying to build a group to go to the end with.
I think that my best options
in this game are
a playing field that
does not include Genevieve,
Sam or Kyle.
I think the remaining
five players-- we all have
a fighting chance
against each other, um,
if it comes down
to the five of us at the end.
I'm sure you would probably want
Genevieve out sooner than later
- since you've already
written her name down. - Um...
I... You know, I...
I-I'm, like...
The only person I want...
I am targeting
right now is Kyle. - Yeah.
We can decide whichever one of
them we want for the next three.
Let's just do it.
Depending on who wins,
that'll affect the order.
But, like, we can get
to five with our...
- Oh. This is getting me excited.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- I pray for one of us. - Yes.
- Absolutely.
- I'm in a real good position.
With Gabe gone, we pull in
Caroline and Sue. That's a five.
That's a majority at eight.
And we collaborated
at the water well.
We're just like, "Yeah. We stick
together, we run this game."
One more week, man.
But we're down to eight.
There are people who scare me
in terms of jury votes...
- Yeah.
- more than you guys.
Are we worried that those five are gonna just,
like, try and pick off
the three of us?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- I think so.
I think we're the three
big, sitting threats.
Yeah.
As soon as one of us goes,
we're then at the mercy
of who wants to save us.
Yeah.
I mean, I want to protect the biggest threats of the game,
and you two are the
biggest threats in this game.
- Yeah.
- Like, you're the people
- I want to go the distance with.
- Yeah.
I had an interesting
conversation with Kyle and Sam.
But I don't like
using the word "alliance"
or even saying, like,
"I trust people" or "I'm close
to people" because I don't--
I genuinely don't feel
any of those connections
to anyone out here by design.
Like, if there are people
who everyone wants to sit with,
maybe we just
take out those people.
In real life,
I love connecting with people,
and I'm, like, an open book.
And in the game, I made quick
connection with Kishan.
And as he
left, his parting words
to me were,
- "Genevieve, I trusted."
- Genevieve, I trusted you.
And
from that moment on,
I realized, like,
that's the power that
connections have in this game,
and I don't want that power.
You know,
I'd rather be a villain
that people didn't connect with
than the best friend
who killed their dream.
You know?
I think it's all just the game,
- like, nothing personal.
- It's very easy for
any of us three, I think,
to pick off the other two
with that five,
but then you're sitting at six,
and I don't know where any of us
are getting numbers from.
Yeah, I agree with you.
I don't have anyone
that I feel like
- would be solid at that point.
- Like, I feel like if you...
If-if you go and you go,
I'm at six,
but I'm the easy next target.
The beginning of this game,
I was deceptive,
I was a liar, I was in control,
and that's kind of how
I kept my power.
After Sierra got voted out,
I had all of my power
in this game stripped from me.
And since then,
I've had to pivot my approach
and really come to people
with full, open honesty,
and that's when
they first start to trust you.
Who would have thought
that just telling the truth
worked pretty well
on Survivor sometimes?
I-I'm not gonna lie.
I wanted... It's, like,
there was an emotional part
of me that did not want
- to write Gabe's name down.
- Totally. Totally.
But last time that I voted with
my emotions
instead of a strategy,
it hurt my inner game
for somebody that was no longer
part of the game.
- Yeah.
- And so I had to separate that last night.
In the beginning,
I had a hard time separating
my emotions from the game.
But I'm realizing now
that you have to be able
to separate your emotions
and who you were,
and you need to be able to adapt
and be somebody
that you need to be out here
if you want to go the distance.
They've been pitching my name
for a while now.
- Yeah.
- So I'm not really bonded.
Yeah.
In my younger years when I was
being put through the ringers
left and right, you know,
different foster cares,
different school systems,
sometimes I had to be somebody
that I didn't want to be.
And over the years, I've let
that part of me go dormant.
But I do
have the ability to lie,
I do have the ability
to manipulate,
and I do have the ability
to deceit.
It's very different.
Yeah. And it's, like,
I try to make my family proud
when I'm here.
But there's major potential
of my kids and my family
seeing me be somebody that I...
I don't want to be.
I do think
you're making them proud. - Thank you.
I don't think you're doing
anything that's out of bounds.
'Cause everyone knows,
when you watch this show,
- you know what it's about.
- Yeah.
Doesn't make it easy, though.
I've learned a lot
about myself coming out here.
I am a numbers guy,
but I can't just sit here and
algorithmically determine
the correct path
because there is
so much variance.
And all this variance comes
from the people themselves.
People are tricky
because they have all these
different priorities,
and not everyone out here
is a AI agent playing
to optimize
their win condition.
It's wild to think about.
And it's just all coming
to a head in a week.
- Yeah.
- It's unbelievable.
An unbelievable thought.
But now I'm at the final eight,
and I do have all
these amazing relationships.
Now I look at Sam, I look
at Kyle, I look at Genevieve.
I'm the one with the best
relationships with each of them.
Now I have the power, and I can
look at this as my game board,
and I can arrange the pieces
how I want them to go.
And so,
I'm in a crushing position
in this game.
- Oh, my.
- There's a boat.
Wow.
Boat!
All of a sudden, we hear a boat
down on the beach.
And a boat means that, usually,
somebody is getting on it,
going on a journey,
and has the chance to either
earn an advantage in this game
or lose their vote.
Gather round, gather round.
And with eight votes left,
all you need is five people
for a majority.
So, whoever goes on
this journey--
a lot is at stake.
I've never been on a journey,
so I would want to.
I've been on two, so I won't.
I've been on a journey,
I'm good not going.
I know Genevieve wants
to go on this journey, but
I'm perceived as a pretty
big threat within this group.
So it's high-risk, high-reward.
But for where my game is right
now, I want to get on the boat.
Can we do that?
Anybody else want
to draw a rock?
You're staying? You're staying?
- I'm staying.
- All right, I'll go.
- You're gonna draw?
Yeah, I'll draw.
I don't really feel like
I need to go on this journey.
I don't really want a target
on my back.
But the thing that I really
don't want is Sam or Genevieve
getting some kind of power
because they're two
of the three people
that I am not working with
that are left in this game.
All right, reveal.
- All right, palms up.
- Two, three.
Lo and behold, I have the purple rock.
I'm a little nervous
about what people will perceive
is gonna happen
and what I might get.
And so, there's this element
of risk that you have
to be willing to take on.
But I think what I've learned
throughout this game is
that I can just trust myself.
And, so, hopefully,
it will not come back
to bite me in the butt.
I'm on a boat that takes me
to the middle of the damn ocean,
and I'm coming up to this barge,
and I'm just like,
"That can't be it."
You know, like,
it's in the middle of the ocean.
Like, that's not a thing.
That's not what a journey is.
When I realized that
that was my destination,
I became very nervous about
what the hell
this could be about.
"Today you have a chance
to earn an advantage
"and it all revolves
around a simple puzzle.
"Slide the balls
into the columns
"so that all the colors match,
"and your advantage will be free
for the taking.
"But there is one more layer
"that will complicate things.
"The puzzle is tied to a rope
"and the rope is connected
to a series of weights.
"The weights are going
to pull the rope into the ocean.
"You must finish the puzzle
before the last weight
"pulls the puzzle
and your advantage off the deck
"and into the water.
"If you do not complete
the puzzle in time,
"you will not participate
in the vote
at the next Tribal council."
Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
Well, it is simple, I guess,
but I have no idea
how much time I have.
The point of the game is to get
all the balls in every column
to be the same color.
So I understand
the concept of this game,
and I think that anybody
could do it with enough time.
But the question is, like,
can I move fast enough
that I will not run out of time
before I complete it?
That's very scary,
and I hope
I can get this done, um,
'cause I want to know
what's in that box
before it just sinks
to the bottom
of the ocean.
This is the perfect example
of games that I like
to do at home with myself
where I'm like,
"Okay, we're gonna set a timer
and we're gonna
see what we can do."
The stakes are much higher.
And so, I'm going to have
to see if I can turn off that
part of my brain that's like,
"This is big stakes
in Survivor,"
and just play
the fun little game
that's set in front of me.
This is a very
intense timer.
I can hear,
the whole time,
that rope just unspooling.
I am trying not
to look at the rope because
I don't want to, like, lock up
in panic and fear.
But the whole time, I'm just
like, "Am I moving fast enough?
Can I move any faster?"
All right, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Yes!
Bye!
Oh, how close.
Oh, man, that was a thrill.
It was so satisfying.
It was just, like...
Like, advantage aside, I was
just like, "I'm accomplished.
I've done something today."
I'm shaking.
Interesting.
This does add to my options.
Plus, I get to walk out
of this situation
with my vote, and that's huge.
But I think that it also means
that I do need to be
more vigilant about ensuring
that people are still on
the same page with me, because
this can still paint a target
on my back
in way where they're like,
"Well, we were all
at a level playing field,
"but now Rachel has this power
and she could use it to,
you know, make a big splash."
And so,
with the things in my arsenal
and the people on my side,
I am genuinely having
that teetering moment of, like,
"Could this actually result
in me winning this game
or could it be my demise?"
On any given day, anything can
happen on Survivor,
but only if you apply.
I hear a boat.
Should we go welcome her?
I think so.
Rachel!
Welcome back, Rachel!
Oh, my God. Hi, guys!
I've never seen
anything like it.
- What?
Coming back from a journey
and thinking about
what you want to tell everybody,
it's sort of a lose-lose,
because not everyone's gonna
believe you,
no matter what you say.
But I think that what I'm trying
to do is err on the side
of 99% honest,
because there are three people
that I don't want
to know that I have
an advantage, and I think
keeping them in the dark
about this is
the best choice, in my opinion.
I'm assuming
I'm going to, like, an island,
and then, all of a sudden,
I see this, like,
barge in the middle
of the ocean.
- Yeah.
- And I walk up to this puzzle,
but literally, to start it,
I have to throw a weight
overboard,
and it starts unspooling
all the things,
and I was like, "Come on!"
And it runs out,
and the table flies off
the barge into the ocean.
- What?!
- So what happened?
Did you lose a vote then
or what?
Yeah, so I can't participate
at the next Tribal Council.
Damn.
Rachel comes back
and she tells us this story
about being on a barge
in the middle of the ocean.
And it's all very extravagant.
But
I'm thinking
in the back of my mind,
"This is exactly
what I would say
if I had something
and I got a big advantage."
So, I'm not buying it.
I think Rachel's
got something up her sleeve.
Hi.
I got...
I got a Block a Vote.
It's only good till six.
No, I won't, I swear.
But I was thinking I could tell
Andy and Teeny, because,
as long as the five of us
are actually solid,
we could use it if we need to.
When Rachel told
Caroline and myself
that she actually won
the Block a Vote,
I felt very bonded,
because I feel like
you don't share that
with people unless
you truly trust them.
- Can I tell you something?
- Yeah.
Day one, Gabe walked up to me,
and was like, "Sue, I want you
to know I got you."
And he pulled out
the Beware Advantage.
And that's why I wanted
to always protect him, because
- I trusted him because
- Yeah.
- he was upfront
and honest with me. - Yeah.
And that's where,
you know, like,
you doing this
makes my heart happy
and makes me 100%
trust everything
- you say to-to...
- Yeah, yeah. I know.
I knew I wanted to tell you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Sue actually tells me
about how Gabe,
at the very beginning
of the game,
approached her and told her
about his Beware Advantage
and how that bonded him
to her and how this was, like,
a similar thing
for her to me.
And I genuinely believe that.
I think Sue
plays very emotionally,
and I think that
that's great for my game
right now.
Do you think that
the five is, like, legit?
I know us three are.
- I know us three are.
- Right. Yeah.
I actually feel like all of our
interests are genuinely aligned.
That's why I agree.
So, Rachel has an advantage,
and funny enough,
I actually would prefer
for her to have an advantage
because I want Rachel
to increase her threat level.
Rachel doing well in this game
just makes her
an even better ally for me,
because someone
who becomes a threat now,
they just become a shield later.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Yeah.
Usually, the people
who I put my trust in this game
have gone ahead
and twisted the knife in my back
and blindsided me
or not included me in plans,
and I'm sick of that.
I'm over it, and
finding Andy and Rachel
has been a solace,
a sanctuary away
from this distrustful betrayal
that I had going with Genevieve.
And so, I am
feeling very good
about my group of three
with Rachel, Andy and myself.
Oh, it's a giant puka.
- Ooh. Pretty.
- Crazy.
They're everywhere.
Yes.
- If Kyle wins,
- Mm-hmm.
would you be open
to considering
one of the people
who are, like, basically
being just, like, shepherded
to final three,
like, Sue and Andy?
Yeah.
So, the general consensus
around camp is
Sue and Andy are great
to bring to the end with you.
But from
a strategic perspective,
I would love to take out
some of the people
that are being brought
to the end,
because that frees up
more seats for us.
I am open to that.
I'd have to think about,
like, who and... what.
That would mean to,
like, get out...
At this point in the game,
Kyle is just
this insane challenge beast
that everyone's just
itching to get out
the second
he doesn't win immunity.
But Genevieve is so much
more dangerous to me because
Genevieve is actively
seeking people out,
planting seeds in people's ears,
planting distrust.
And to me,
that is a very important person
to get out as soon as possible.
Earlier, when I was
picking up shells...
- I want Genevieve.
- She's stirring the pot,
- and I don't want...
- Like, that stresses me out.
- That's not the first time
she's said my name.
It's not the third time
she's said my friggin' name.
If I'm looking
at the game board,
the one piece that has just
become a big nuisance
and a direct threat
to my game is Genevieve.
People throw my name out,
- I want them out. Genevieve
- I know.
has been doing that for days.
So, she's gonna do it
with Caroline and Sue, too.
She's gonna throw
all our names to that person.
Yeah. You're right.
So...
Genevieve telling Rachel
that she's dragging me along
is laughable.
I've been playing a game
that no one is seeing,
and I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of being
underestimated in this game.
Genevieve is
a snake in the grass.
We need to get her out soon,
and I'm confident
I can make that happen.
Come on in!
You're looking like
Survivor players.
Little worse for the wear.
The smiles are still there.
Excuse me.
So, let me just check in.
Twenty days into this adventure,
Kyle, have you noticed
or learned
or reflected on any part of
your life while you're out here?
Absolutely. You know,
growing up a little bit rough,
and in the conditions I did,
there wasn't, like,
a lot of stability.
And, uh, after being out here
for so many weeks, it's...
my reflection on that is,
just as long
as I have my family,
any calm and casual Tuesday,
a plate of food in front of us
and just being together
is what I want,
and just to share that love
with one another.
Sue, I got to check in.
You seem emotional.
I'm very proud of myself
for being here.
And it's...
I knew I was gonna
have tough times
and I actually
was looking forward to it
because I feel like
when I am knocked down,
I do come back stronger.
So, my desire is-is,
like, so powerful inside me,
and I believe in myself
that I can do it.
I just want to say, like,
I relate to Sue a lot
in this moment.
I was standing
in this exact same spot.
I recognize it.
- You're talking about day three.
- Day three, exhaustion.
I was feeling like
I gave it my everything
and it wasn't enough.
And that was gonna be my story.
None of us have sailed through
the first 20 days of this game.
It's been rocky
for every single one of us.
But this is what
I feel, altogether,
that we have learned
and grown this sense of
backbone and composure
and resiliency
that we could take
into the rest of our lives.
Well, it's one of
the great things about Survivor.
It is a roller coaster of highs
and lows, but there is one thing
that is always there:
opportunity.
Including right now.
Shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
All right, Kyle. First things first.
For the fourth time,
I am taking it back from you.
Thank you, sir.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you're gonna use a rope
to balance a wobbly table
while you stack letter tiles.
If at any point
your stack drops,
you got to start over.
The first person
to spell "immunity"...
...wins immunity,
guaranteed a spot
in the final seven.
Losers, Tribal Council,
where somebody will be
the eleventh person voted out,
become the fourth member
of our jury.
You are 20 days
into your adventure
on Survivor 47.
You want to guarantee
you see day 21?
Win this.
Big enough stakes?
All right.
We'll draw for your spots.
We'll get it on.
Here we go.
All right, here we go.
For immunity
and a guaranteed spot
in the final seven.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Ooh, everybody gonna
take time out of the gate
to stack their blocks.
Some people gonna race out,
some people are stacking
their letters in order.
You're racing out
with that first letter.
You're spelling "immunity"
from the bottom to the top,
so you're spelling it backwards.
You're balancing that table
to make sure
it doesn't fall.
This is all about touch.
How fast can I move while still
keeping that rope really still?
It's not so difficult
with the letter Y,
but as that stack gets higher,
it gets more precarious.
Genevieve drops, got to
come back. That's gonna happen.
That's how you start to find
where that tipping point is.
You want to go
just as fast as you can,
but not so fast
that you're out of control.
Unless, of course,
you find yourself behind,
in which case
you have to catch up.
So, it's gonna be a lot
of changing strategies out here.
Sam moving quickly
on his way back.
Rachel moving quickly.
Kyle and Teeny
moving very slowly,
taking a different approach.
Teeny's gonna go slow and steady
and hope for
a late-game fail that will
open the door for her.
You got to focus on your game
in Survivor
and in this challenge,
because you never know
when somebody's gonna drop.
You just keep
building your stack.
Sam places his seventh letter.
- Okay.
- Genevieve places her seventh.
Rachel places her seventh.
Here comes Kyle with his sixth,
trying to get in on this.
...- Caroline drops.
She's got to go back.
It is now Sam in the lead,
then Rachel, then Genevieve,
all heading back for their
eighth and final block.
This is it right here.
Three people in it.
Everybody else chasing.
Teeny places her sixth.
Teeny hoping
for a disaster from all three,
and that will open the door
for her.
And she gets one of 'em. Genevieve drops.
Sam drops and loses everything!
It is now Rachel
solely in the lead.
Rachel drops
and loses everything!
This is what Teeny and Kyle
were hoping for,
and they got it.
Kyle now in the lead,
along with Teeny.
That is why you always
keep fighting on Survivor.
That is why you never give up.
'Cause anything can
and often does happen.
Now it's Kyle who has to worry
- about it getting too perilous.
- No way.
- Come on, Teeny.
- And Kyle drops everything.
- Go, Teeny, go.
- And just as though
she had written it out,
Teeny got what she wanted.
It is Teeny
with her seventh block.
Kyle had done such a good job
of catching up, but lost it.
It is now Teeny and then Sue
at five blocks,
and then Andy at four blocks.
And now it's Teeny that has
to worry about the same thing.
Just a little too much slack
in that rope,
and it will dump.
It wants to tip.
It's top-heavy.
And there it is--
the opportunity you want.
Teeny drops everything.
The lead is gone.
And once again,
we have a fresh start.
And now it is Sue in the lead.
She has been slow and steady.
Sue loses everything!
We have another new leader.
It is Andy.
Andy loses everything!
Oh, my God.
We're back where we started.
Damn.
Right now, where we're at is
Rachel's in the lead with seven.
Kyle places his sixth block.
Genevieve places her seventh.
Genevieve and Rachel both
at seven letters,
both with one letter left.
Rachel has her eighth letter.
She's heading back out.
Genevieve still has
to get her eighth letter.
Kyle one full letter behind.
Everybody else not in it
right now.
Damn.
Rachel slowly but surely
inching closer.
Genevieve slowly but surely
inching closer to Rachel.
We could have a race
to the finish here.
Rachel very close to placing
that eighth and final block.
Genevieve right on her tail.
Genevieve loses everything.
And that is a huge opportunity
for Rachel.
She can slow down now.
Kyle the only person
chasing her.
Kyle now placing
his seventh letter.
This'll put him
one behind Rachel.
Rachel has spelled "immunity."
All she has to do now
is get back to the end
and get two feet
on the platform,
that necklace is hers,
day 21 is guaranteed.
Can she do it?
Kyle has a big decision.
Does he go for it?
Do you push it,
put your foot on the gas,
or do you hope Rachel drops?
One wrong move,
and this game
is back up in the air.
Rachel slowing down now.
It is a game of cat and mouse.
Kyle on the platform now,
reaching for his eighth
and final block.
This is where
things get really tricky.
One wrong move,
and you will dump everything.
Rachel now down
to about six steps left.
Kyle has made up some time,
and he's coming back
with his eighth letter.
It would be a huge comeback
for Kyle to place this letter
and catch Rachel.
This is coming down
to Rachel's last few steps.
Can she hold it steady,
get two feet on that platform
and win immunity?
Kyle moving quickly
on his way back.
He's gonna go for broke
and try to pull it out.
Can he catch Rachel
or is this over
unless Rachel drops?
Rachel two steps away
from immunity.
All eyes on Rachel.
She's got one foot
on the platform.
Kyle's hoping for a mistake.
- It's over. Rachel wins
- SUE: Yay, Rachel!
individual immunity!
Rachel!
Guaranteed a spot
- in the final seven.
- Rachel!
Tribal Council tonight.
- Oh, my God.
- Somebody will be the eleventh person
voted out and become
the fourth member of our jury.
It will not be Rachel.
Wow! What a challenge.
Oh, don't believe that.
- Rachel, come on over.
- Go, Rachel! - Yeah!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Immunity is yours,
safe tonight at Tribal Council,
cannot be voted out
of this game.
You will live to see day 21.
What did it take
to win this challenge?
You know what's so funny? My husband Derek is
the opposite of me.
He is so patient.
I'm the most impatient person.
And so, like, I was just...
In that moment, I was like,
"Just harness him.
"Like, he would be screaming
at you to slow down,
to just focus and just,
like, take my time,"
which is something
I'm not very good at.
It worked today.
You are safe, not going home.
As for the rest of you,
after 20 days,
somebody's Survivor dream
will come to an end,
eleventh person voted out,
fourth member of our jury.
See you tonight
at Tribal Council. Congrats.
- Thanks.
- Good job. Rachel.
Grab your stuff, head out.
It is beyond overdue for us
to take Kyle out.
Getting Kyle out will be a way
to help all of our odds
in this game.
'Cause I don't think there's any
beating Kyle in this game.
He's too good of a competitor,
he's got too good a story,
and people just like Kyle.
So, the best thing
for this entire group
to do is to vote Kyle out.
Coming back
to camp with immunity
is this incredible feeling.
That's something
that I wasn't sure
that I would ever get
to do in this game.
- Good job, Rachel.
- Good job, Rachel. - Rachel!
Everyone's clapping and saying, "Good job," and, like,
whether they mean it or not,
it feels good.
Where do you hang it?
I don't even know. Here?
Yeah, just hang it up there.
Kyle has had this necklace
around his neck for so long
that we have not been able
to take any shots at him.
And so,
it's an "easy vote"
to vote Kyle out tonight.
On the other hand,
when it's a really obvious vote,
that's a perfect time
to take out somebody
that's unsuspecting,
like Genevieve or Sam.
And frankly, I want all three
of them out of this game.
I don't really care
what order they go in.
And so, it does feel like
by winning the necklace,
I have way more options
for who's gonna
go home tonight.
I've been waiting patiently,
and there will be nothing
that will bring me more pleasure
than writing Kyle's name down
tonight at Tribal Council.
I knew his day would come, and
I've been drooling.
Drooling... for this day.
I think it would be a little bit
dumb to do anything else.
Everybody will have
a better chance at immunity,
everyone will have
a better chance at winning.
Do you guys agree?
- Yes.
- I agree.
If I had my way,
Kyle would stay.
Unfortunately,
I have zero power right now.
The group is gonna do
what they want,
which I'm told is Kyle.
But my name was out there
for the Gabe vote
and, thankfully,
I was able to, like,
by the skin of my teeth,
hide behind Gabe.
And so, tonight, I hope
that everyone is more afraid
of Kyle than me.
It is not good for my game
to get Kyle out of here.
As soon as Kyle is gone,
everybody that's looking
at Kyle is looking at Sam,
and it's way too early to have
everybody looking at Sam.
We can do Sue,
we can do anybody.
- Or Andy.
- I'm not doing it.
Okay.
The problem tonight
is getting one
of the other five players
in the tribe on board
to save Kyle, and
I don't know
if the numbers are there.
I'm not doing that, and I would really appreciate
if you guys didn't do that.
We can't do it without you, so...
So, I might have
to just go with the group
once again, and that sucks,
but that's the game.
I'll keep it short.
You don't have an idol, do you?
- No.
- Okay.
I don't think
you have the numbers.
Especially if Rachel has a vote.
I don't know about that or not.
Not bringing home
that necklace really means
that I've got a lot
of work to do.
I've been so vulnerable
with my story
and the reason why I'm here.
They know it's an excellent
story, and that a family man
is a dangerous person
to have in the endgame, so,
now it's time to step away
from my physical abilities
and just
try to get
into the social game of this
and try to get somebody
on a different direction,
other than headed at me,
at this point.
If the votes are
that unanimous against me,
would you take a risk and shoot
one direction to try to help me?
I promised you, right, that...
I would want Gabe first
and then Genevieve next,
and I meant it.
Everyone's eyes are set on Kyle,
but I'm thinking that if I want
to leave my imprint on this game
and start making my mark
and start flipping
the win switch,
I have kind of maybe
other ideas.
If I had it my way,
I would 100% prefer
for Genevieve to be the one
to leave tonight.
And so, I have to
pitch a case in which
I can make that happen.
- Yeah.
- So...
The likelihood
he's gonna win all
of the next four immunities
is 6.25% chance.
It's not that risky.
It's a calculated risk.
I like thinking about things
in terms of probability.
That gives him a coin flip
to win a given challenge.
Roughly,
for a coin flip to land on heads
four times in a row
is, um, one out of...
two, four, and...
Wait. Two, four...
It's one out of 16,
and that is a 6.25% chance
of happening.
That's not that risky.
The risk of winning out
is too high.
Even if he doesn't win...
People will see it as too high,
I would see it as too high.
"The chances of him winning
another immunity challenge
are 6.2%."
No, that's not 6.2%.
I don't know where
you got that number from,
but it is... baloney.
Yeah.
The only thing Kyle's gonna do
from here on out,
he's gonna sit in the shelter,
make the fire,
talk about Shania.
That's-that's who he is
as a game player.
She's threw my name out,
your name out, your name out.
I look at that
as more threatening
to our five-person alliance
than Kyle.
Andy and Rachel
are definitely heavily weighing
taking out Genevieve tonight.
I think they are starting
to feel the fear of Genevieve.
"She's just going to find a way
"to win a challenge and stay
in this game long enough
to take the rest of us out."
It's a valid concern.
I'm not not hearing it.
I know that
we have to get him first.
His run is overrated.
That's all I'm saying.
Getting rid of Genevieve honestly makes sense,
but targeting Genevieve
means targeting Sue
and betraying her trust
and potentially
destroying our alliance.
So,
I'm really hoping,
with every fiber of my being,
he agrees with me and we can
stick to the smart plan.
I think that Genevieve is way
scarier of a player
than Kyle is.
So, if everyone
is staring at Kyle
and assuming he's going home,
this would be a perfect time to
get a player out like Genevieve.
Kyle has won four immunities, so to
not take him out when he doesn't
have a necklace on
would just be
the dumbest look ever
for us as players in this game.
A lot of people go by their gut or their heart.
Those things are really not
in my decision-making right now.
Like,
I'm playing the numbers,
but the hard part is
getting everyone else on board
and trying to convince them
that my plan should be the plan
to happen tonight.
Now bring in the members
of our jury.
All right, so with tonight's vote,
eleventh person voted out
becomes the fourth member
of the jury.
So, Sam,
as this power starts
to shift more to the jury,
what changes about the vote?
I think everybody goes into a vote
figuring out who is a threat
to them later on.
But, you know, I actually think
this group might have
a bit of a warped perception
of that because
I think there's people
in this game
that go through the motions of,
"Here's the people
that can beat me,
so I got
to take all of them out,"
but not consider the fact that
if they just go down the line,
they're not gonna get there.
And all of a sudden,
those votes mean nothing to them
'cause they'll be one of them.
Rachel, do you agree with that philosophy?
Yeah, I mean, I think it's clear
that power players are being
taken out of this game,
but I think that Sam's
perspective is Sam's perspective
because he may be somebody
that is more powerful
than other people sitting here.
And so, whoever
Sam thinks is a threat
and whoever Sam thinks
he can beat is different than
who I think is a threat
and who I think I can beat.
It's different
for every single person here,
and that's what
makes it complicated.
Kyle, what do you think
about that?
The way that I'm seeing things
is a little bit different,
maybe, than the way
that other people are
seeing things right now, because
I'm sitting in a hot seat.
They want to vote me out,
mostly because of like,
"Wow. this guy
is physically challenging."
Yes, I've prevailed
in challenges,
but ultimately, the social game,
the strategy game,
all the other parts of this game
that come into play, I might not
have executed so good.
We've had people on Survivor
that have just
annihilated challenges,
got to the end
and not received votes.
I might not be as big of
a threat as what people think.
Andy, Kyle makes a valid point.
Half of the people that have won
five individual immunity
challenges did not win Survivor.
They might not have even
got to the end.
Yeah. I do kind of
understand what
Kyle's saying, to an extent.
Like,
I didn't do much sugarcoating.
I lied to all three
of those jurors
- on their way out,
to their faces, so, - He did.
it just goes to show how there
are so many different sides
to Survivor and what
makes a good player.
Whether that's pitching that
you are beatable at the end,
that you can't win at the end,
that you're
a one-dimensional player--
that all goes into it.
And you just have to weigh,
like, how to survive.
And you just have to
give yourself the best chance
to win the game at the end.
Teeny, was there a big debate about
"threats" in terms of
what kind of threat
is most dangerous right now?
Absolutely.
If you are more
of an outward-facing threat,
somebody like-- sorry-- Kyle,
who's won
four different competitions,
like, that's a big
physical challenge threat.
Or if you're somebody
who's leading and orchestrating
a lot of votes,
you're getting your voice heard.
That's a big outward threat.
We all sort of know
who falls into the big,
outward-threat section,
and who falls
into this sort of underdog,
maybe sneaky,
come-from-behind threat.
And that's where
decisions like this
are super important.
Genevieve, are you displeased
or just thinking?
Both. Both.
So, Teeny mentioned
outward threats--
"are you great
at immunity challenges?"
She's not talking about me.
But then she said,
"Or you get your voice heard
or you lead votes," and
I've heard my name a lot.
The pitch I try and make is
if there are people
who everyone
is comfortable keeping in,
they're probably taking up seats
you want in the end.
So, it's difficult
to make a pitch.
I mean, once you get that stamp
of threat, it doesn't wash off.
So, Andy, you go back to camp,
you start talking.
There's one thing
very different.
There were no Shot in the Darks.
So, unless someone has an idol
or some other kind
of new advantage,
there's nothing they can do.
Did you sense that today?
The safety net is off
for sure, but
we're still kind of playing
the way we're playing,
and we're not just gonna walk up
to a target and say,
"You're the target."
We're trying
to be more sophisticated
with that, and layered.
We're not playing a simple vote.
We're not just doing
load up on one person
and not worry
about the consequences.
Kyle, you're smiling big. -
- You don't buy that answer.
- Well, it's not that I don't
buy that answer, but, like,
there's a couple of points
that I'd like to highlight on.
When we got back to camp,
it was pretty obvious
that I didn't have a necklace
around my neck
at this point in time.
There was no safety
for me, right?
So I pulled a couple
of individuals.
And one of those individuals
told me
that "There are so many people
gunning for you right now,"
which tells me that
people are still
hiding behind one another
and making an obvious play.
But this is opportunities
for moves to be made.
This is, like,
time to flip the switch.
This is when you start
to think about
maybe there's different threats.
So, did anything change
to give you some optimism,
or as you sit here right now,
do you believe you're the vote?
You know,
I'm gonna be optimistic
in this position.
I'm not going to roll over
and just give up.
That's not who I am,
and that's not
who I want to be perceived as.
So, we have the opportunity
to have a crowd-pleasing moment,
something that we can shift
to the point where, like,
you know, somebody
didn't see that coming.
Sue, that's an interesting comment.
"We could have
a crowd-pleasing moment
if we don't take me out."
Right, well,
personally, I feel
every single person here
is making up their own mind.
They're not really
being swayed by anybody.
I certainly am not
having anybody
try to sway my vote.
I know
what I'm planning on doing
and I'm sticking to it.
Sam, what did you experience
this afternoon?
Uh, I think my experience
was pretty similar to everybody
else's in the sense that
Kyle is the obvious target.
But he also makes
some very good points.
The fact that he is a vote,
the fact that he is a shield
to a lot of people who feel like
they're also targets,
and they're also threats
in this game.
- How about you, Rachel?
- Yeah,
I mean, I think it's being
underplayed a little bit.
I definitely
had discussions today
about targets that were not Kyle
that were seriously considered.
So, I don't
think that it was just,
Kyle doesn't win immunity,
and we're voting out Kyle.
There...
It is more nuanced than that,
whether people want
to believe that or not.
Genevieve,
when you hear Kyle say,
"Well, I was told it was me,"
does that give you comfort?
Uh, I don't think it'll be...
a dogpile on Kyle tonight.
Genevieve, you're very quiet tonight.
Your energy is quieter,
your voice is quieter.
Is that 20 days of exhaustion
or is that the pressure
of being at Tribal
feeling that your name might
actually be the name tonight?
I'm a little bit...
all over the place, mentally.
Um, half of my mind is,
"I wonder if
I'll get through tonight."
And the other half is...
"Then how do I
get through tomorrow?"
Funny enough, this is actually
a moment where
I would remind Genevieve
of one of my absolute
favorite Tribal quotes
I've heard so far, which is,
"The great Survivor players
can see through the noise
to see the news."
- Who said that?
- Genevieve.
And I have honestly thought about that quote
- almost every day.
- Genevieve,
so you have a player
telling you,
"You actually said something
that I'm using right now.
You should use it
yourself tonight."
That's community, Jeff.
And it's so twisted out here,
and it can feel awful
and it can feel, like,
rejuvenating and like,
"Oh, yeah.
Maybe I'm not on an island
all on my own."
So, thank you, Caroline.
Absolutely.
I mean it.
Genevieve,
there's one more layer
that starts
to creep into this
at 20 days and only
eight people left
is that you know each other.
It starts to become personal.
Yeah, since
the Kishan vote,
I have made
a very specific effort
to separate Genevieve the person
from Genevieve the player,
which is how I am able
to think strategically
without clouded vision.
But people I've known
for a long time trickled through
and pulled in some emotion
from Genevieve the person.
People
I've known only for a short time
were able to access that,
and it does make it
more complex for me.
I wish I could
truly just
be Genevieve the player.
It would be a lot easier.
Andy, more difficult for you the
longer you stay in this game?
I do think it gets more intense,
but at the same time,
the finish line is right there.
Right?
We see eight slots
and five people have to go.
I feel like
there's a happy medium
where you have to determine
the big calculus of
thinking about
everyone's threat levels,
because it is dynamic,
and it's gonna change
after this vote.
It's gonna change after
the next vote.
And the real goal is to be
not at the top, not at
the bottom. You have to just
figure out a way to get through
and have a shot
to win at the end.
Kyle, do you agree with that?
I think there's a lot of truth to that, but
it's getting to the point
where you may not want
to just go
majority rules anymore.
I think this is time
where you can really start
flipping the script,
making moves happen
that people really
weren't expecting,
and prove to the people
that are sitting over there
that you have in the tank
what it takes
to make things happen.
Okay, it is time to vote.
Genevieve, you're up.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right.
I'll read the votes.
First vote:
Genevieve.
Kyle.
One vote Kyle,
one vote Genevieve.
Teeny.
That's one vote Kyle,
one vote Genevieve,
one vote Teeny.
Kyle.
Two votes Kyle,
one vote Genevieve,
one vote Teeny.
Kyle. That's three votes Kyle,
one vote Genevieve,
one vote Teeny.
Eleventh person voted out
and the fourth member
of our jury: Kyle.
That's four. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
All right, guys, line 'em up.
Let's knock 'em down.
Thank you for each
and every one of you,
for the kind words
that you had to say for me,
for my family.
Every one of you are beautiful
and have a wonderful story.
You are playing your hearts out.
Thank you so much
for this experience.
for your friendship.
Love you, man.
- Good game, you guys.
- Good game, Kyle.
Bye, Kyle.
If you have a family,
when you're out there,
give it a buck 20.
We do 100% for ourselves,
but when it comes to our family,
we put 120%
into everything we do.
I'm gonna need a hug
from you, too.
You got it.
Kyle, the tribe has spoken.
Thank you so much
for this opportunity.
Thanks for coming out.
Bye, everybody.
- Bye, Kyle.
See you, bub.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
We are gonna
be the final four women.
And it's so exciting.
Next time on Survivor...
This is what
I've been waiting for.
This is the biggest heist
of Survivor.
It stings a little bit
having your torch snuffed,
knowing that the title
of Sole Survivor won't be yours,
the million dollars
won't be yours.
But I'm pretty proud of myself
and all the things
that I've accomplished,
and I think
I've made my family proud.
There's only gonna
be one winner in the end,
and I gave it my all.
I gave it a buck 20
the whole way through, and...
and I'm proud of that.